Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Get back here!
Give that chart back,
you damn woman thief!
What great weather!
If we keep going this way,
we should see the
navy base island soon!
Another big haul today!
Wow, Coby! You're amazing!
Buggy-sama won't be mad at us,
now that we got all this!
We're actually gonna
reach our destination?
Huh?
But of course!
Fire!
These are the bare
minimum skills all sailors need!
Hey, check it out...
W-What?!
A person fell from the sky!
This is no time
to be laughing, Luffy-san.
What's with that boat?
Now I'm safe!
He's being held prisoner there.
Whoa...
The famous pirate hunter...
That was a pretty neat experience I had!
What are you--?!
Luffy-san!
Roronoa Zoro!
Straw Hat?!
"A Terrifying, Mysterious Power!
Captain Buggy, the Clown Pirate!"
The man who's chopped up
bounties like a bloodthirsty beast...
"I'm Luffy! The Man Who's
Gonna be King of the Pirates!"
That doesn't work!
I-It's a girl!
Hey! What's wrong with you?
People say he's a
demon in human form!
I'm starving...
B-Boss! You came to save me!
Oh! Am I dreaming?
I told you I was strong!
Wha--?
Running into someone
on this wide open sea...
W-Who the hell are you?!
Who're you?
No worries!
"Enter the Great Swordsman!
Pirate Hunter Roronoa Zoro"
I-I don't know who you are, but... water...
A whirlpool of that size
poses no problem to this ship!
Sorry, but they're all yours now!
I'm Luffy!
The man who's gonna
be King of the Pirates!
Might I ask for a cup of water?
I can give you all the money you'd like.
Miss.
Hey! The girl got away!
That's okay!
Her boss is still here!
May I have this dance?
Please, help me!
"Morgan vs. Luffy!
Who's the Mysterious Pretty Girl?"
Ah! Tryin' to cover
for your crony, huh?!
We made it! The navy base city!
No problem! We'll help you!
But not until we see what treasure ya got!
Alright!
Say, is there any place to eat around here?
W-What?!
The King of the Pirates?!
Don't mind us!
Quit screwin' around, kid!
Not again...
Seriously, Luffy-san!
Batter out!
You're crazy to want him to join you!
Do you even know
what that means?!
What're you doing? You suck!
I can't get it open...
Does it go like this?
I still haven't decided yet.
I just wanna see if he's a good guy...
King of the Pirates
is King of the Pirates!
He's been caught
because he's a bad guy!
Are there any other meanings?
Don't touch my treasure!
You can keep my entire boat, if you'd like!
--Bastard!
I was shocked, too!
Mm! Yum!
But Luffy-san is serious!
That's how he is!
Wonder if they killed that guy...
Do you know if Zoro's at the base?
Our boat!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
He intends to become the King of the Pirates
You tricked us!
and obtain this world's
ultimate treasure... the One Piece!
This thing's heavy!
Must be filled with booze, then!
A cold front accompanied by low
clouds spotted in the southern sky!
It would seem the name "Zoro" is taboo here...
Wow!
It's all ours now!
Intense winds and
squalls expected very soon!
Well, let's check out the base anyway.
You're really strong!
Here's your treasure!
You're gonna be a marine, right?
All small boats take
caution not to capsize!
Which is yours?
I couldn't tell, so I brought three of 'em.
Y-Yes... But I'm not really ready yet...
You beat people with sabers barehanded!
All three are mine.
Rumor has it...
...a guy named
Captain Morgan is at this base, and...
Hey! You're that... who?
I use the Three-Sword Style.
Ship off the starboard stern!
I'm a thief who steals from pirates!
You'll take 'em, right?
There's a pirate flag on its mast!
If we fight together now, you'll
be a government-defying villain!
The name's Nami!
Hey, wanna team up with me?!
It's a pirate ship!
Enemy raid! Enemy raid!
Bingo!
What a funny town!
No. I don't feel like
teaming up with you.
Would you prefer that, or
being killed by the navy like this?
See ya! I'll just take
your treasure now!
It's strange...
I understand Zoro, but why are
they afraid of a navy captain's name?
H-Hold on!
What are you, the devil's son?!
Wait! You bitch--!
Well, whatever.
Wait, I said!
We'll get you for this--!
I suddenly feel uneasy about this...
I'll be your pirate,
if I'm just gonna die here instead!
Oh. I just remembered!
You sure they didn't jump just for fun?
I'm starving...
Hurray! So you'll join my crew?!
Nobody would do that!
"Luffy's Past!
Enter Red-Haired Shanks"
Shall I treat you to some food?
Captain! Pirates!
Alright! This's the place!
Alright! Woo-hoo!
This is great! Alright!
Really?!
What?!
Y-Yeah...
I'm finally here!
Okay! Now untie these
stupid ropes already!
I'm starving...
Everyone, stay calm!
I guess this is where
we part ways, Luffy-san.
Stay calm!
What... is he?
They still haven't caught the thief?!
When the hell're
we gonna reach land?
He flung the bullets back!
Follow instructions
in a calm manner!
It was only for a short time, but...
T-They should be pursuing her
as we speak, Captain Buggy! Yes!
Who knows. We're just going
with the wind and waves, after all...
He's no ordinary human,
that Straw Hat...
Upsy-daisy!
Luffy-san! What in the world are you doing?!
Must've eaten one of
those rumored Devil Fruits!
I wonder if we'll reach land...
Now where's this demon?!
Nah, I'm sure we will, sometime.
Fire!
--A Devil Fruit?!
--The hidden treasures of the sea?!
How did the map get stolen
so easily in the first place?! Huh?!
He wouldn't be out here.
I'm sure he's in
a prison cell or something...
Isn't it kind of weird that someone
tryin' to be King of the Pirates...
There he is!
The Devil Fruits...
Alright!
doesn't even have
any navigational skills?!
Just when we're about to enter
the Grand Line and go on a rampage!
Whoever eats one is said to
gain seemingly unworldly abilities.
It's not weird.
I just drifted around.
See! There he is!
Yeah, right!
He wouldn't be out--
But aren't you a bounty hunter
who wandered the high seas?
A-Actually, the shack was unlocked,
so it was easy to take for foes...
Coby!
The power to breathe fire...
Y-Yes, ma'am?!
I have no memory of ever even
calling myself a bounty hunter.
The power to cause tsunamis...
Who's the most beautiful
of all on these seas?
What did you say?!
There are all sorts of rumors,
As I said, it was easy to take for foes...
A black hood and a haramaki...
T-This ship's captain,
Alvida-sama, of course!
but there are many types, and
almost nothing is known about them.
Who has a fake nose?!
I set onto the sea in
search of a certain man...
It's said the secrets to
them lie in the Grand Line...
That's Roronoa Zoro!
but then couldn't
get back to my village.
Do you find this nose funny?!
Just like a fake nose?!
I had no choice, so I just went
after pirate ships to earn a living.
He can get away easy
if we untie those ropes!
but there's no question
Straw Hat just displayed a devil power!
D-Don't be stupid!
You have it all wrong!
Well done!
Oh. So you're just lost.
T-Thank you!
It's huge and all red?!
There's no telling what'll
happen if we let him loose!
Don't put it like that!
Alvida-sama.
This is our first prey in a while.
Hurry! Hurry!
I bet he'd try to kill you too, Luffy-san!
Damn! These knots are tight!
That's right!
Help!
Don't worry! I'm strong!
Hey! Quit wastin' time!
Alright! Start pounding the ship!
I can't believe this guy!
No matter who they are,
everyone who opposes me gets executed!
Hey, you guys.
Shanks!
If guns won't work,
then chop them to death!
--H-Here it comes...
--T-The Devil Fruit power...
You're an eyesore.
Get lost!
This straw hat is dear to me--
Huh, that's weird! It got tighter instead!
Luffy-san! There's no way you
could survive with him on your crew!
it's been with me through many a fight.
Give me a damn sword!
Who am I?
Luffy. I can't give this even to you.
C-Captain Buggy...
Luffy-san!
What happens if someone defies me?
Oh no! Stop her, Luffy-san!
A flashy death awaits them...
Roronoa Zoro!
She'll be killed!
Please forgive me!
So cool!
What?
You must be hungry!
I made you some rice balls!
I'll never say it again!
Move and you're dead.
Please forgive me!
Do you wanna get killed, pipsqueak? Scram!
Too scary!
You haven't eaten anything this whole time.
I'll overlook your verbal slip-up
and forgive you just this once.
Men! Show them the terror of
Iron Club Alvida, the woman pirate!
Here! This is my first time,
I'll be a pirate. I promise you that.
but I worked really hard to make them!
Now get that map back! Screw up...
and you know what happens.
I'm officially a criminal,
now that I've fought the navy.
I ain't hungry!
But I'll tell you this right now.
Yes, Captain Buggy!
You're an eyesore!
Get the hell outta here!
Then take me on your
next voyage, Shanks!
I'm only going to fulfill my ambition!
But...
I don't want 'em!
Don't make me kick your ass!
I wanna be a pirate too!
Ambition?
To be the world's greatest swordsman!
Coby! What're you doing?!
It's not nice to be a bully!
Yum!
As if you could ever be a pirate!
I-I'm not good
at this sort of thing...
Do you live alone in this house?
If I wind up having to give that up,
Why not?!
Hmm?! Are you tryin'
to give me backtalk?!
I don't live in this town.
You seem surprisingly well, Roronoa Zoro...
you'd better accept
responsibility and apologize to me!
Luffy.
Just bein' a good swimmer doesn't
mean you'd make a good pirate.
Everyone here ran away because of Buggy.
P-Please, anything but the club!
Now there's another weird guy!
The world's greatest swordsman?
That sounds great!
Thank goodness!
--Then you're a sneak thief.
--How rude!
I'm good at fighting too!
My punches are like pistols!
He must be with the navy!
Now that girl will be safe!
Then get yer ass in gear!
The King of the Pirates would
need no less than that on his crew!
I'm a thief who only
steals from pirates!
Oh, really?
Oh? Those are some
tasty-looking rice balls.
What's that mean?!
Don't compare me
to scumbag sneak thieves!
You sure talk big.
He means you're too
much of a kid, Luffy!
Stop!
At this point, whether it's as
a criminal or whatever else,
But a thief's a thief.
Seriously, you're as old as my own kid!
I will spread my name throughout the world!
Too damn sweet!
I'm not a kid! I'm a grownup!
My goal is to earn 100 million Berries,
no matter what it takes.
Those're full of sugar!
What're you standing around for?!
Slaughter them this instant!
You're supposed to use salt for rice balls!
Now, now. Don't get so mad.
Here! Have some juice!
But I thought they
might taste better sweet...
Wow! Thanks!
What do you need that much for?
Duck, Zoro!
--Take this! And this!
--Stop! Stop!
It's a secret!
--See, you are a kid! Ha!
--That wasn't fair, Shanks!
Gum-Gum Whip!
But with a map of the Grand Line,
100 million is a real possibility!
H-How horrible!
We won't take yer lives, but
we will take all yer valuables!
Don't laugh!
A map? Are you a navigator?!
Y-You did it! Incredible!
Stupid cheapskate Shanks!
Anyone who tries to fight back'll
wind up at the bottom of the ocean!
And I worked so hard to make those...
What the hell are you?
Much more skilled than
your average navigator!
I ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Oh, that's perfect!
Do you wanna be our navigator?!
Gum-Gum Fruit?
Did you not read this notice?
A rubber person!
"Those who help
criminals will be executed!
So he does have Devil Fruit powers!
Really?
Pardon us.
Yeah! Our new pirate crew member!
Captain! We don't stand
a chance against them!
Hello...
Navy Captain Morgan"
These guys are crazy!
No!
We can't even handle Zoro by himself!
There's no one in here, right?
Looks like even little brats
know how scary my dad is!
So you're a pirate?
Oh... So these are "pirates."
Yeah. I swore to the person
who gave me this straw hat...
What a relief...
This is a direct order!
Dad?
Look pretty damn dumb.
Then that's Captain Morgan's son?!
Everyone who spouted weakness just now...
that I'd gather a crew
and become a pirate!
That's a rather large barrel...
must now shoot themselves in the head!
You. Throw this kid out.
I have no need for weakling soldiers!
Sir?!
There's nothing I hate more
in this world than pirates!
Welcome...
I said throw her over the wall!
I only like money and tangerines!
Or can you not follow my orders?!
Don't make me tell my dad!
These troops are mental!
We're mountain bandits.
Hey. Be our navigator.
But we ain't here
to tear up the place.
I said no.
Y-Yes, sir! Right away!
Luffy-san!
No?
Sell us some booze.
Ten barrels oughta do.
No!
Crush this navy!
Who're you?!
Never seen you before!
I-I'm sorry, little girl.
Curl yourself into a ball.
--Hey! You find her?!
--Can't find her anywhere!
I'm sorry.
I just ran out of alcohol.
Where'd that girl thief go?!
That's odd.
We're in trouble if
we don't get that chart back!
These pirates seem to be drinking
something... What is it, water?
I gotta do something about them...
Rankless, low-status bums have
no right whatsoever to defy me!
No, what they're
drinking is the last of it.
T-Thanks...
Well, I might consider it
if you agree to certain conditions!
Are you all right, Luffy-san?!
My apologies. Looks like we
drank the whole place dry.
I am Navy Captain
"Axe-Hand" Morgan!
Are you all right?!
Really?! I'll do anything!
I can't believe how
horrible that guy is!
Hey, coward!
I'm Luffy! Nice to meetcha!
Sorry!
Are you hidin' out in a
place like this again?!
I want you to come with
me to see Buggy the pirate.
Do you hurt anywhere?
You can have this, if you'd like.
It hasn't been opened yet.
Die!
Damn you...
N-No! I thought I'd haul this
big barrel of alcohol over...
But!
You sure are stubborn about staying alive...
We'll lighten it for ya!
Why am I tied up?
I was just feelin' thirsty!
It's just rope.
Is there a problem?
Yeah! I will live the full month!
You can't! Alvida-sama
will kill us if she finds out!
There's an eight million Berry
bounty on my head, you know.
Oh well! I was hoping to
meet other pirates! Let's go!
T-The captain!
Well, good luck with that.
Then you just need
to keep yer mouth shut!
R-Runt...
One bottle ain't even enough for
a bedtime drink! Don't insult me!
Hold on, now!
Right, Coby?
Ten days left, you know!
Die!
Y-Yes! You're right!
What?!
Assuming you can live that long!
No thanks!
The thief got away?!
Thing's pretty heavy!
Now the floor's all wet.
Can't wait!
C-Captain Morgan is...
Hold yer horses!
I'll bust it right open!
Sorry about that, Makino-san.
Do you have a rag?
How can he be so cruel, Luffy-san?!
Please forgive us, Captain!
All three of you are pathetic!
Die flashily!
Oh, I'll do that!
being trounced completely...
He's gone?!
And you call yourself a navy?!
I hear you're a bad guy.
Captain Buggy!
You've destroyed Coby's dream!
What is it?!
Are you still here?
That thief from earlier
came back on her own!
Being stuck out here for all to see...
Seems you like to clean.
Hold it, Straw Hat!
Check this out!
Then maybe you'll find this more fulfilling.
What?!
Are you really strong at all?!
Mind your own business!
I said hold it! Are you stupid?!
Not worth our time if
they're out of booze. Let's go!
That's them!
Pay attention!
I have a hostage here!
If it were me, I'd probably
starve to death in three days!
I slept great!
She's the one who stole the chart!
I got more spirit than you.
Helmeppo-sama!
Later, wimps!
Ow!
Hey.
I will live through this...
If you value this guy's life, don't move!
I've captured the thief,
Captain Buggy the Clown!
I swear it!
One move and I'll shoot!
Huh?
Here's your chart back!
What a strange person!
I appreciate it.
Wait!
But why the change of heart?
Could you pick that up for me?
Who're you guys?
Are you all right, Captain?
Are you hurt?!
No, who are you?!
Oh, I'm fine. No problem at all.
That guy's gonna catch cold
if he sleeps there, y'know.
You're gonna eat this?
My boss and I had a fight!
I'm fed up with him!
You did that!
Luffy-san! I don't
want to get in your way!
It's mostly a mud ball now.
Just shut up and give it here!
Are you toyin' with us even
when you know we're pirates?!
Please let me join your crew!
Even if it means dying!
--He got you good, boss!
--Talk about lame!
Yeah, I know!
C-Captain Buggy is angry!
Give it up, stupid son!
Man, I'm hungry!
You got any food?
Coby really is ready to die!
Listen when people are talking!
He's gonna use his Devil Fruit power!
Told you so.
Why are you laughing?!
It was good.
Devil?
You damn kid!
Don't move!
That was so uncool!
I told you not to move!
I-I'll shoot!
Thanks for the food.
Why didn't you fight them?!
Die!
No matter how many there
are or how strong they seem,
Behind you!
Really?!
Gum-Gum...
Fed up, huh?
you're not men-- or pirates--
Yeah! He ate every last bite!
I am Navy Captain
"Axe-Hand" Morgan!
You're a flashily amusing girl!
if you laugh after something like that!
I like you!
You can join my crew!
I'm so happy!
Is Zoro really as evil
as the rumors say?
I can understand how you feel,
--Dad! Kill him, quick!
--...Pistol!
but he only spilled some booze on me.
No!
Infiltration successful!
After all, he let himself
get crucified in our place...
It's nothing worth getting mad over.
Pirates are so dumb
and easy to manipulate!
Whatever!
Nice!
Huh? What do you mean?
Why am I in a cage?
It's all that Helmeppo's fault.
What's the big idea?
W-Who are you?!
He's Captain Morgan's son...
I feel great today!
--Eating out of frustration, Luffy?
--Shut up!
Me?
I'm Monkey D. Luffy.
Nice to meetcha!
Girl! What name do you go by?
Zoro.
Outta the way!
Nami!
My pleasure, Captain.
Wait, what're you eating?!
Alright! Let's hold a
welcome party for Nami here!
Make way for my adorable pet-sama!
That box! Did you eat
what was in that box?!
Celebrate flashily!
Get in the way, and you get executed!
Y-Yeah...
What the... What just happened?
Spit it out! Right now!
Every last bite!
Captain Morgan's been beaten!
What's with them?
--Unbelievable!
--These guys are insane!
W-What're you doing, Shanks?!
R-Run, hurry! If they come back
with their friends, you'll be killed!
No! Stop that!
If anyone else still wants
to catch us, come forward!
Hey, you!
You gonna complain about
what my pet-sama's doin'?!
But man, I sure am hungry!
How can you be so carefree?!
Rika! Stop that!
We'll get in trouble
if we go against him!
--Hurray!
--We're free!
There are still lots
more of them up on deck!
What's wrong?!
This party's in your honor!
What... was that?
--Yahoo!
--Morgan's reign is over!
C'mon! This way!
What you ate was
the Gum-Gum Fruit!
Eat up!
Hurray for the navy!
H-H-Hey! Not this way!
The Gum-Gum Fruit
is known as a Devil Fruit!
Yes! Thank you!
--Oh, crap!
--He's in trouble now!
Huh? Everyone's happy
their captain's been beaten...
Eating it turns your body to rubber,
I'll just keep my eyes peeled for
a chance to take the chart back.
and makes you lose the ability
to swim for the rest of your life!
Who the hell are you?!
Everyone was just afraid of Morgan!
And maybe I'll swipe all of
Buggy's treasure too, while I'm at it!
Eh?! No way!
Don't tell me you're...
Food! Food! Food! Yes! Food!
...pirate hunter Zoro?
You dumbass!
And if I am?
Actually, they might
not find us in here!
What's wrong, Zoro-san?!
Are you hurt?!
Why is a pirate hunter defying the navy?!
I'm... hungry...
Just shut up and let me eat in peace!
Which should I choose?
This box? Ooh, jackpot!
I... wanna eat, too!
Why, you...
These look great!
M-My name is Coby.
You're Luffy-san, right?
Sorry!
Dammit!
Just endure it for a while!
That was incredible just now!
How did you do that?!
People were drinkin'
and havin' a nice time.
These things are great!
You're annoying me.
Both you and your pet-sama!
What's the idea, boy?
Is this a pirate ship?
This is flashily great!
No, it's a passenger ship that's
being raided by Alvida-sama.
Dammit! Apologize!
How dare you make fun
of Shanks and his crew!
Men! Prepare
a Special Buggy Ball!
Did I say something to offend you?
Well, it doesn't matter.
You do realize that if my
dad finds out about this,
Doesn't seem to be in here, either...
Do you know if there
are any boats onboard?
You did! Now apologize!
I-I think so...
they're gonna get
executed for sure!
Mayor!
My ship got swallowed
by this giant whirlpool...
You mean that whirlpool?!
No one could survive that!
Whadya say? Let's make a deal!
You see the looks
on those pirates' faces?!
Boy, was that a real surprise!
You get strung up in place
of this mother and daughter!
He got covered in booze
but didn't say a word!
Talk about pathetic!
For, yeah, one month...
Are you one of those pirates, too?
Pirates are just a bunch of wimps.
If you can survive for one month,
Yes! A chart of the Grand Line!
They're nothing but talk.
I'll let you live, too.
All set, sir!
Stop it!
I knew they had one!
Whadya say?
W-What's about to happen?
It was on that fateful day...
Stop making fun of
Shanks and the others!
"I've flashily taken the map! Buggy"
Observe the might of the Buggy Ball!
They are not wimps!
One month.
"I've flashily taken the map! Buggy"
T-This isn't a chart!
What is this mark?!
That day, I got in a boat on
the outskirts of town to go fishing...
Stop, Luffy!
Light it.
T-This isn't a chart!
What is this mark?!
Stop making fun of Shanks and
the others! You stupid bandits!
It's been three weeks since then.
Captain Buggy...
Helmeppo punches and
kicks him while he's tied up!
The man known as Buggy the Immortal...
...but it turned out the boat was
actually headed for a pirate ship.
You oughta watch your mouth, boy.
I... I...
No one who's ever made me
mad has lived to tell the tale.
I see...
It's been two years since...
Wait!
In exchange for my life,
I've been forced to be a chore boy.
I'm hungry!
Let us all eat for free!
Let the boy go! Please!
Man, you're dumb and stupid!
I don't know what Luffy has done,
Hey! Bring me some booze!
You're brutally honest...
If you don't like it, then run away!
nor do I intend to fight with you!
Quit dawdling! Hurry it up!
I-I can't! No way! No way!
If you're not offended,
I'll even pay you!
What's that explosion?
Just the thought
of Alvida-sama finding me...
Just, please!
Spare the boy's life!
One of Buggy-sama's
beloved Buggy Balls!
Oh, yes.
...frightens me and makes
me weak in the knees--
I've been bored lately,
Mayor!
Oh, you're a wimp, too?
so I've decided
to execute Zoro tomorrow.
Buggy Balls?!
Leave it to senior citizens
to know how the world works.
Man, I hate you!
Look forward to it!
I'm stuffed!
But no, it's too late for him now.
I was definitely at my rope's end,
Hey, now! Quit dawdling!
After all, he's made me angry...
having not eaten for three weeks!
Haul it all off before
the navy gets here!
You're the bad guys!
You mountain apes!
Anyone caught dawdling
gets a taste of my iron club!
W-What the hell're you doing?!
Huh? You're finished already?
You're a lost cause, kid.
Luffy-san! Please stop!
--What a haul!
--Seems like a pretty rich ship!
You can regret all this in the next life!
How the heck can you have
a bigger appetite than me?!
This guy is scum!
Hey! You'll get the club
if she catches you slackin' off!
Y-You hit me!
--Luffy!
--Please! Let him go!
It tastes good! Right, Coby?
I'm Captain Morgan's son, you know!
Oh, whoops!
Truly flashy!
I was wondering why
the bar was empty...
Yeah, one hit from
that and you're a goner!
Thank you for treating me to food, too...
So what?!
With Buggy Balls and Devil Fruit powers,
I'm gonna tell my dad
and he's gonna execute you!
I can conquer the Grand Line!
It's no problem!
The town has been saved, after all!
...looks like it's those
mountain bandits from before.
Fight me yourself!
Right, Nami?!
Alvida-sama!
Captain!
You really are amazing!
Luffy-san! Calm down!
Y-Yes! Of course!
It's bad!
Are you trying to get
on the navy's bad side?!
Eh?!
Yep, I am!
And I'm gonna be even more amazing!
What is it?! You're annoying me!
I've made up my mind, Coby!
A b-b-barrel!
I'm the one who's
gonna rule the Grand Line!
Shanks!
'Cause I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
M-M-Monster!
I'm... going to have Zoro join my crew!
Huh?!
What?
And I even have a crew!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
So, how many others have
you gathered besides me?
Who're you calling a monster?!
You idiot!
I am...
You said you were in the
middle of gathering a crew.
I see why you're sick of him, Nami!
great!
Yes! You're exactly right,
Captain Morgan, sir!
Yeah! He takes the world too lightly...
To be King of the Pirates,
N-No... Some weird guy
popped out of a barrel...
But hasn't tribute to me
been a bit lacking lately?
you must have
a good number gathered.
and misunderstands everything!
I couldn't put up with it anymore...
Just you.
He might be...
a bounty hunter...
Huh?! Then...
W-Well, the citizens'
wallets do have their limits...
Naturally!
In that case, I'll give you a
Buggy Ball to blow away your old boss!
Yep! Just us two!
What?!
So you pirates are still here, huh?
We're gonna call just
us two a pirate crew?!
The issue is the level of respect for me.
Have you been scrubbing the
village clean this whole time?
What's wrong with that?
We are strong!
It'll also serve to prove
your loyalty to me. Do it!
Luffy!
What about a ship?
Where's your pirate ship?
Wouldn't you agree?
I thought your punches
were as strong as pistols?
There.
Dad!
S-Shut up!
I dunno why you're here, but
you'd best leave before you get hurt.
There's someone I want you to slaughter!
Any closer and he'll
shoot your head off, wimp.
Yeah... That's right...
That?
We'll have a ship this big before long!
No, that's okay!
C'mon, this is a welcoming party!
Let's have fun!
If only I had the courage to
drift the ocean in a barrel...
He said no closer!
And how's that?!
Don't make me blow your head off!
...there's actually
something I want to do, too...
And I'd like a pirate flag, too!
Do it.
This is my style of welcoming party.
Umm... What compelled you
to set out onto the sea, Luffy-san?
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
Put your life on the line.
I'm gonna be
the King of the Pirates!
Huh?!
Yeah! Yeah, yeah! So cool!
Now that you've drawn your pistol,
put your life on the line.
I think Luffy-san was born
without any sense of planning.
--K-K-King of the Pirates?!
--Yep.
What the hell're you talkin' about?
--Are you serious?!
--Yeah.
I'm saying those aren't
for threatening people.
Wait, you're a pirate, Luffy-san?!
Did I really make this guy my captain?!
If I don't shoot, I'll be killed!
Yep.
Well, we'll get more
crew members before long!
What about your crew?!
Don't got one.
I'm just about to look for one.
But if I do shoot, I'll wind
up no better than pirates!
You're still as weak as ever, Zoro!
Hey, hey! Where are you guys gonna go to now?
I promised her...
Isn't it obvious?! The Grand Line!
K-K-King of the Pirates is
the title given to the person...
I can't afford to die
in a place like this!
...who obtains everything in this world!
You still only have two members!
--N-Now you've done it!
--These bastards fight dirty!
That means seeking the great
treasure of wealth, fame, and power...
There's no way you can go there!
--Dirty?
--Cut the crap.
No way! No way! No way!
Is the Grand Line that terrible of a place?
...the One Piece!
What, do you think you're
dealing with saints or something?
Yup!
Naturally!
Yup?! Pirates all over the
world are after that treasure!
You're looking at pirates!
Alright! Light it flashily!
You know this world
has two oceans, right?
Shut up! You got nothin' to
do with this in the first place!
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
You again?
You sure have lots of free time.
Me too!
No way! No way, no way, no way!
Absolutely no way!
And the giant continent that cuts
them right in two is the Red Line.
Listen, bandits.
I'll untie you, so join my crew!
Whether I'm splattered with
alcohol or food or even spit on,
There's no way you can stand at
the apex of this Great Pirate Era!
Say what?!
I'm looking for people
to join my pirate crew.
Supposedly, there's a town right
in the middle of the Red Line,
most of the time I'd just
laugh and forget about it.
No way! No way!
Forget it!
Me, stooping to a criminal's level?!
and the Grand Line goes
through it at a right angle...
But!
Nami! Don't wimp out on me now!
No matter what the reason,
Why did you hit me?
Screw that!
anyone who hurts
my friends has to pay!
Just because.
and stretches around the world.
What's wrong with being a pirate?!
But it's all right.
I'm used to it now...
What's the matter?
Pirates are despicable!
As if I'd wanna be one!
Shanks...
It was said that Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates,
Your hands are shaking!
Oh, come on!
Has to pay, huh?!
once obtained everything
this world has to offer,
You're already known
as an evil bounty hunter!
That's what happens when you take
on pirates with half-assed resolve.
Lousy pirates! Kill 'em, men!
It's not about whether I can or not.
and before he died, he said he left
the great One Piece treasure there,
People can say whatever they want,
I'm gonna do it because I want to.
Resolve to do what?!
but I ain't done anything I regret.
I'll handle this.
Should be easy enough.
To kill people like it's nothing?!
I've decided to be the King of the Pirates,
Is that a pirate's resolve?!
so pirates everywhere have
since set sail for the Grand Line!
I will live through this
and accomplish what I want!
No!
so if I die fighting for that,
that's fine with me!
It's now an intense battlefield,
and even called a pirate graveyard!
The resolve to put your own life on the line!
Yeah?
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
But I've decided you're gonna join me!
Now, then! My belly's full--
guess I'll go get me a boat!
Don't get cocky, bandit.
Quit deciding on your own!
If you wanna fight us, then go
drag a warship here or somethin'.
I hear you use swords.
I wonder if they'll give me one if I ask.
I've heard from patrons before...
Yeah. But that stupid son took my stuff...
Hey, new chick!
Quit bein' a tease!
Hopefully they're generous.
that whoever enters the
Grand Line never comes out alive...
So strong!
This is how you light it!
I never once thought about it...
--I'll go get it back for you!
--What?!
H-Hold on! The kid attacked us!
So if you want your sword, join my crew!
But the One Piece is somewhere there,
Do you suppose I can do it, too?
You are a wanted man.
You're really getting on my nerves!
so we're going there!
If I'm prepared to die for it?
Damn it!
Guess it can't be helped!
Do what?
Is he planning to bust
into the base by himself?!
Not you too, Zoro-san?!
A smokescreen!
Do you think...
even I could join the navy?
What's it matter?
You're not going, are you?
You idiot! The base is
in the other direction!
N-No, but I'm worried about you!
Luffy!
Navy?
Yes! Catching bad guys is my dream!
Crap! I let my guard down!
Luffy's gone!
Is that so wrong?!
Gum-Gum Rocket!
Luffy-san and I haven't
known each other long,
What do we do, guys?!
What the--?! What the--?!
It's been my dream ever since I
was little! Do you think I can do it?!
W-Who the hell is that guy?!
Quit freakin' the hell out, boss!
but we are friends!
Crap! I didn't mean to--
Right?
It won't take us long to find him!
How should I know?
Yeah! We're gonna part ways,
but we'll always be friends!
No! I'll do it! If I'm gonna be a
chore boy for the rest of my life,
Nami! What is the meaning of this?!
I can't believe this guy...
then I'll break out of here and
catch even Alvida-sama-- no, Alvida!
I'm sorry!
What?! Apologizing won't fix things!
I made a clean getaway!
Since I was a little kid,
I've never had friends...
They'll never expect a mountain
bandit to escape onto the sea!
Huh? Now you're saving me?
Alright! Stop there!
Much less anyone who
would fight for my sake...
Dammit! Let me go, you stupid ape!
Don't be stupid!
Stand it up in one shot!
I only did it because of the situation!
I hope you die!
You're gonna team up
with him to catch who?!
But more than anything,
I never tried to fight for anything...
Dad! Why aren't you
going to get revenge?!
I just didn't want to wind up
like these inhuman pirates!
You wish!
You're the one who's gonna die!
The guy hit me!
After all, you've made me mad!
Oh, the situation!
Not even you've ever hit me in the face!
Huh, Coby?!
But you two taught me
how to live for my beliefs!
Pirates took the life
of a person dear to me!
So long!
Do you know why I've never hit you before?
As if I'd ever be one!
Dammit! Dammit!
Oh, so that's why... Huh?
I've decided to make
my childhood dream come true!
Those guys are scum,
but I couldn't even
hit them once! Dammit!
Eh? Because you think I'm--
I want to join the navy!
It's lit!
Shouldn't you be more
worried about yourself, then?
Keep your ridicule to a minimum, girl!
Yes. Because you're...
Sorry! I got no use for you anymore!
Kill her flashily!
Even if you were just a chore boy,
Yahoo!
you did spend two years
on Alvida's pirate ship.
You don't seem to be Zoro, the pirate hunter.
...a stupid son who
isn't even worth hitting!
Don't underestimate the
navy's info-gathering skills.
Zoro?
Coby!
If they find out about that,
you'll never get to join.
Who's the most beautiful
of all on these seas?!
W-What the hell?!
Don't get the wrong idea!
Water! Water! Water! Water!
N-Now that you mention it...
O-Of course that would be--
Pardon me!
Your dad is the one who's great! Me!
Who's this big chunky lady?
Not good!
Help!
Is it true that you are pirates?!
Which reminds me, I hear a rat
snuck into the crucifixion yard.
Yeah. We gained a member
and became a pirate group just now!
You're...
--Chunky?
--Not good...
I-I-If you mean that pipsqueak,
I made sure she was dealt with--
You runt!
We appreciate that you saved our
base and this town from that tyrant!
You killed her, I hope?!
N-No! I mean, she was just a little kid...
However, now that we know you are pirates,
Let's go!
You, there!
Shanks!
Behind you!
in the name of the navy,
we cannot stand by quietly!
Go into town and exterminate her!
Die flashily!
Y-You can't be serious!
She's just a little girl!
You will leave this town at once!
I can't in good conscience...
Why, you...
Anyone who disobeys my
orders is a traitor, even little brats.
Out of obligation, we will refrain
from contacting headquarters.
Get lost!
B-But... I can't do it!
Hey, navy guy!
How can you talk like that?!
Hey, now...
Even you guys were
subdued and terrified of Morgan!
Whoops!
How many of you are
taking on one girl at once?
We owe these people our lives!
Lieutenant!
Y-You didn't have to go that far!
Zoro!
Yeah! Yeah!
It was with my strength that
I rose to my rank of captain!
Well, guess we should go!
Listen! In this world,
titles mean everything!
You hurt?
It's not fair to attack from behind!
Thanks for the food, lady!
I'm in your debt, Luffy...
You guys are leaving already?
Are you hurt?
Makino-san told me everything.
That means that I, the captain and
highest ranking officer at this base,
N-No, I'm fine...
Yeah.
You fought for us.
Whew, what a relief!
am the most superior person here!
How'd you find us?
Hurry and get me outta here!
It's not fair to attack all at once!
Hey, don't cry! You're a man!
So everything I do is right!
What do you keep playing around for?
Aren't you part of their crew?
But... Shanks!
Eh? I...
First some bird runs off with you,
and now you're inside a cage?
Isn't that right, you guys?!
I'm...
Your arm!
It's pretty interesting, actually.
Yes, sir!
You're absolutely correct!
"Zoro"?
It's only an arm. It's no big deal.
The kid's death can wait for now.
T-That's what he just called him, right?
Hold it!
Observe! This is the symbol of my authority,
Well? Is he?!
Gotcha!
I'm just glad you're alright...
The crew member he mentioned...
was Pirate Hunter Zoro?
I know what he's done until now.
Gum-Gum...
which took many years to finally complete!
Now, stand it up!
Luffy-san! You wouldn't!
What's going on?!
There was this really fat pirate lady,
Display my greatness
at the top of this base!
...Rocket!
So you're Zoro?
I think her name was Ahiruda.
What do you want? Are you here
to take my head or something?
Luffy-san!
What?!
If they find out I was on a pirate ship,
Nope. Not interested.
I gave up pirate-hunting.
That's weird.
There's no one here...
I'll never get to join the navy!
I gotta find that stupid son
and get Zoro's sword back.
L-Luffy-san... What are you?
And she had this iron club.
Man, she was an ugly hag!
I'm interested, though!
Killing you will increase my name.
You're leaving, then?
Me?
Pull! Pull!
Yeah. It was a long stay,
but now we part ways.
I'm a rubber person!
And for two whole years, this guy was her--
I wouldn't try it. You'll die.
A rubber person?
You can't be serious!
Bet you'll miss me, huh?
Oh? That so?
Well, yeah, but I won't
ask you to take me anymore.
Please don't!
Please don't, Luffy-san!
You, there!
You've eaten a Devil's Fruit, haven't you?
Guess words aren't enough for you...
I've decided to become
a pirate on my own now!
You bumped it, didn't you?!
--Get 'im, Captain!
--Captain Buggy!
Yeah! The Gum-Gum Fruit!
I heard something up there...
I wasn't gonna take you anyway!
I see! I'd heard the rumors,
but I guess they really do exist!
You'll never be a pirate!
I-I'm sorry, sir! I was careless!
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Now you've done it, you bastard!
I told you to think
of this statue as me!
I will too!
Damn you! Damn you! Damn you!
Someday, I'm gonna gather
a crew every good as yours,
You also seem pretty skilled.
You a bounty hunter?
The slightest scratch or speck
of dirt is treachery against me!
and I'm gonna find the
greatest treasure in the world,
Stop that!
I'm a pirate!
We won't allow you to cause
any more trouble in this town!
A pirate?! Hah!
All by yourself?!
and I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates! I'll show you!
I'll just check it out!
Gum-Gum...
It's just me right now, but I'll
find some more sooner or later!
Hey! You've gone too far.
That's enough.
...Rocket!
You're gonna surpass us, huh?
Now you pay!
Yeah... Ten crewmen sounds good to me!
I jumped too far!
In that case...
Ah, so you're a pirate too, huh?!
--What is that?!
--It flew up from below!
Die flashily!
It's very clear that you
guys aren't crewmates!
...I'll leave this hat with you.
Then that means you
and me are enemies, huh?
I stopped!
Now leave this town at once!
It's dear to me.
--L-Luffy-san! Let's get out of here!
--Why?
Take good care of it!
You saw how powerful her club is!
In these waters, she's the most--
On purpose...
Sorry...
He did that on purpose...
I've decided to be
the King of the Pirates,
Seize him!
I'm going to kill him!
so if I die fighting for that,
that's fine with me!
For me...
Yes, sir! Right away!
He had no resistance to him at all...
Dad! That's him!
He's the guy who hit me!
He purposely got me
riled up to make me hit him...
Whoa! He's weak!
Oh! It's you!
I'm the most what?!
No way...
Come bring it back to me someday!
I've been looking for you!
Even in the very end,
I wound up relying on him!
Come with me!
There's something I want you to give back!
T-T-The...
--Let me go!
--Helmeppo-sama!
Once you've become a great pirate!
The most ugly,
cragged old hag ever!
After him! Don't let him escape!
That's our promise, Luffy!
Captain! There's someone
in the crucifixion yard!
Nothing's changed at all!
What?!
What's with them?
H-Huh? Their captain's been killed...
Am I an idiot?!
But they're laughing!
It's one traitor after the other...
Please!
Hey! What's so damn funny?!
Please... let me join the navy!
Hey.
You're gonna drop it
again if you space out.
I'll gladly do chores or anything else!
What did you say?!
After him! After him!
Isn't it important?
Yeah.
I... I'm going to join the navy!
Hurry!
If it means I can be a marine!
Thank you, Zoro!
And then I'm gonna beat up pirates!
Zoro!
Man, I'm hungry...
Someone just had to interrupt...
Do you even know
what you're saying?!
Lieutenant Colonel! I'm against the idea!
What's that arm?!
What... the hell?!
I do! I'm gonna do
what I want to do!
I still don't fully trust this kid!
Where is Zoro's sword?!
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna join the navy...
I'll tell you! I'll tell you!
Just stop dragging me!
There have been cases of
marines being pirate spies!
A bird...
...and catch your lousy ass!
The Chop-Chop Fruit...
We'll first need to
conduct a background check...
Alright! Talk!
You damn pipsqueak!
That's the name of
the Devil Fruit I ate!
In my room...
We just passed it...
Let's eat it!
I'm a man who will become a navy officer!
No regrets! No regrets!
I said it! I fought! For my dream!
Huh? How?
What? Why didn't you say so?
Now we gotta go back.
Leave it to me!
I'm a chop-chop person who can't be cut!
Gum-Gum...
--Freeze!
--Let Helmeppo-sama go!
Well said!
...Rocket!
No.
I see...
His body reattached itself!
Go ahead and shoot, if you dare!
I thought the
Devil Fruits were only a rumor!
Countless comrades of ours
have been killed by pirates.
No! Don't!
A chop-chop guy?!
You mean he's a monster?!
Don't take the navy lightly.
Please escape, Zoro-san!
That doesn't work!
"Rubber Person"
Help!
Then...
You'll be killed for doing that, you know!
What?!
Permission to join granted!
Moron!
What the hell're you doing?!
'Cause I'm rubber!
I can't stand to watch
the navy like this anymore.
I didn't hit any vital spots,
Yes, sir!
but that's a pretty
serious wound! I win!
Gum-Gum...
I want to be
an honorable marine!
You're too much, Captain!
Hey! Stop! You there! Stop!
Stop! I can't escape!
I only got ten days until--
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
...Pistol!
"I've flashily taken the map! Buggy"
You're going to be
executed tomorrow!
Shipwrecked people,
at a time like this?!
Crap! The tables have turned!
What?!
I can't stop!
Jump in on your own!
Helmeppo never once
intended to honor your agreement!
If we don't do something quick,
me and these two guys are dead!
That was a pretty lame act.
What?!
Wouldn't be shocked if they saw through it.
So Luffy-san got angry and punched him!
That one hurt a bit...
Coby'll handle the rest on
his own now. I just know it.
I'm impressed you got on!
Are you trying to run us over?!
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
He did?
It's a nice way to leave, though.
Hey! Stop the boat!
The navy is after Luffy-san now.
Being unable to turn back
'cause everyone hates you--
We're members of Buggy
the Clown-sama's crew!
it's pirate-like!
I won't ask you to be a pirate.
This boat is ours now!
That's true!
The sky is so blue...
But please, help Luffy-san!
Luffy-san!
Stabbing him from behind is unfair,
Huh?!
Big Nose!
Thank you! I'll never
forget all you've done for me!
We had no idea you were the
famous Pirate Hunter Zoro-san!
Luffy-san is the only
one who can save you.
Y-You idiot!
Don't call him that!
--Forgive our rudeness!
I've never heard of a pirate
being thanked by a marine...
Thanks to you guys,
I lost sight of my friend.
And I think you're also the only
one who can save Luffy-san now.
Just keep padding straight ahead!
Hey!
--Yes?!
Who's... got a big nose?!
Let's meet again sometime, Coby!
--Yessir!
Give Coby a small boat!
Knowing Luffy, he'll manage
something once he spots land.
--Luffy-san...
--Bye!
He's gonna join the navy!
Keep your mouths shut and let him go!
End of the line!
Luffy!
All hands, salute!
--R-Right!
But what now, Bro?
Buggy!
For the crime of treachery against me,
Luffy-san!
I will kick your ass!
I'll now execute you two where you stand!
See ya!
Good question...
If Captain Buggy finds out a
girl stole our boat and treasure...
That's a great friend you have there.
This the room?!
Y-Yeah...
Kick my ass? You're a real riot!
It's the navy!
Who's this Buggy guy?
Oh, perfect timing!
You should go see 'em!
You've never heard
of Buggy the Clown?!
All three of you are
gonna die here, you know!
Bingo!
Yes, sir!
Nope.
But there are three here!
Our salute just now is
in violation of naval law!
How should I have my ass
kicked in this situation?!
But I'm a pirate! I'm outta here!
He's the head of our pirate ship!
Hey! Which sword is Zoro's?
Get serious!
I can't just join the navy like this!
He's eaten one of the Devil Fruits,
Oh, he passed out.
Therefore, we will all go without
food for three days! Understood?!
I'll be captured instead!
and is just an
all-around terrifying person...
Coby!
Yes, sir!
It's no use... It's all over...
I'm sure...
I'm sure we'll meet again
sometime, somewhere, Luffy-san!
I refuse to die!
This is some interesting
stuff you guys've pulled!
Run! Zoro!
Even if we're divided
as pirates and marines...
Were you two and that straw hat
kid plannin' a coup or something?!
What?!
Wait! He came here to save you!
let's meet again someday!
What're you gonna do?!
I've always fought alone.
Looks like we managed to get away...
Unlike arrogant bastards like
you who use soldiers as cronies!
Yes! I finally got it!
Whew, that was fun!
Alright!
Our pirate crew finally sets sail!
Understood.
Nothing makes sense anymore!
This is why I hate pirates!
--Get back here, you!
--You wench! Give the map back!
Roronoa Zoro...
Umm, Luffy-san.
Looks like some pretty good
adventures'll be waiting for us.
Don't you dare underestimate me!
If you're heading for the One Piece,
We just stole that
chart of the Grand Line!
Impudent fool!
As if I'd let you escape!
--that means you're going
to the Grand Line, right?
--Yeah.
You may be strong,
but before my authority,
you're as good as scum!
Dammit! If we don't get it back,
we're dead meat, too!
I will be King of the Pirates!
That place is also referred to
as a pirate graveyard, you know.
I don't wanna be killed by one
of the captain's cannonballs!
Aim!
Yeah. That's why I need a strong crew.
I...
You really seem obsessed
about this King of the Pirates thing.
What about that pirate hunter guy?
What's he like?
Fool!
Your Three-Sword Style has no effect on--
...can't afford to die here!
Is there some sorta reason for it?
Captain Buggy!
I see something in the sky above the port!
You mean Zoro? I heard he's
being held prisoner at a navy base.
No reason. It's just...
Hey! Listen when
people are talking!
It's just?
Shoot it down!
I swore to a certain man that...
Aw, he's a weakling?
You're still as weak as ever, Zoro!
Nothing of the sort!
He's as terrifying as a demon!
...someday I would gather a great crew,
Gum-Gum...
find the world's greatest treasure,
W-What the--?
...Rocket!
and become King of the Pirates!
Fire!
Why are you asking about him?
Thought I might have him join
my crew if he's a good guy!
--What are you--?!
--Luffy-san!
Straw Hat?!
This straw hat knows!
You're being reckless again!
Oh, crap!
The cannon's pointed this way!
C'mon, he might be a good guy!
W-What?!
I see...
What the--?!
He's been caught
because he's a bad guy!
--Hey! Light it!
--Eh?!
That doesn't work!
A person fell from the sky!
No! No way, no way, no way!
Absolutely no--
--Hurry!
--R-right!
Dammit! What are
cannonballs flying at me for?!
Wait, wait, wait! There's still
a Special Buggy Ball in there!
Why did you hit me?
I told you I was strong!
Just because!
Alright! Let's go!
W-Who the hell are you?!
Set sail for the Grand Line!
But now I'm safe!
You lit it!
That was a pretty
neat experience I had!
I'm Monkey D. Luffy!
Wait! No! Stop! Stop!
The man who's gonna
be King of the Pirates!
"To be continued"
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
before someone else
could beat me to it
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Hey, Zoro! Are you okay?!
I'm gonna be the world's greatest swordsman!
Hey! I'll untie your ropes,
so join my crew!
Geez, you don't even
know how to navigate right?!
Yeah, don't worry. I'm better now.
Whoa! Being alive while all
chopped up is no human technique!
Great! Why not be a great swordsman pirate?!
I refuse to team up with a pirate!
Great!
--Do you know how?
--No!
What're you talking about?!
You can't possibly be better!
Oh, come on. You're already
known as an evil bounty hunter.
Don't talk like it's so easy!
Ahh! Hey, stop rocking the boat!
My hat'll fall off!
What? As a rubber guy, you're
plenty of a monster yourself!
The soldiers have started to go berserk!
Really?
Oh no! What's that?!
Probably 'cause we're
enemies of the navy now!
Screw that! I ain't done a single
thing I regret! And I never will!
--What an unfriendly dog!
--I'm not referring to that!
Nothing makes sense anymore!
Is your straw hat that important?
Here! I'll untie your ropes!
A rubber guy, a chopped-up guy...
Who are these people?!
Yeah! It's my treasure!
Oh!
There's a polar bear on top of a lion!
I gotta hurry! There has to be a
map to the Grand Line in this base!
So I ain't gonna be a pirate!
I have to return it to him
after I'm King of the Pirates!
They followed you guys here!
--Pirates.
--No! That's not what I mean!
I've decided you're gonna join me!
Huh? The ropes are tighter now.
On the next episode of One Piece!
Who's "him"?
Quit deciding on your own!
On the next episode of One Piece!
Hey!
"Desperate Situation!
Beast Tamer Mohji vs. Luffy!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Terrifying, Mysterious Power!
Captain Buggy, the Clown Pirate!"
"Luffy's Past!
Enter Red-Haired Shanks"
"Enter the Great Swordsman!
Pirate Hunter Roronoa Zoro"
"Morgan vs. Luffy!
Who's the Mysterious Pretty Girl?"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!