Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Alright! Light it flashily!
Die!
Huh?
Yahoo!
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
Oni Giri!
Beaten by mere sneak thieves...
Crunch his head for sure this time!
A-Are you all right?!
We ain't sneak thieves...
We're pirates!
Yeah! It's okay, it's okay!
Yes! The chart of the Grand Line!
Gum-Gum...
They're new recruits who heard
all about me and came from afar...
...Hammer!
I'll never forgive him!
...to join the Usopp Pirates!
No, not me!
I'm here to ask a favor!
Join our crew, Nami! Okay?!
A favor? Of me?
"Who is the Victor?
Devil Fruit Power Showdown!"
--Yeah! We want a big ship...
--You, there!
How about we team up
for our common goal?
Zoro!
What are you doing?!
Terrible news, everyone!
Alright! Fire!
Stabbing him from behind is unfair,
In all my life, I've never been
as mad at someone as him!
Pirates are attacking!
Klahadore...
Big Nose!
Pirates! Pirates!
That bastard Shanks stole
enormous riches from me!
I don't appreciate you breaking
in here without permission!
Pirates are attacking!
Run for your lives!
I don't know how
you two are connected,
"Epic Showdown!
Swordsman Zoro vs. Acrobat Cabaji!"
Pirates! Run for your lives!
but I can say whatever
I want about him!
--Get him! Get him! Fight!
--Don't neither of you lose!
I'm here to kick your ass,
just like I promised!
Hey, Zoro. You're hurt, you know...
"Liar of Justice? Captain Usopp"
--The North Pole!
--No, the South Pole!
Just shut up and stay in there!
You still say that, huh?!
That's right! I'll always say it!
'Cause I'm right!
Who's there?!
I'm gonna do things my way!
Oh, you got guts! I'm gonna
settle this once and for all today!
Go ahead and try it!
Straw Hat?!
Alright, you bastard!
I'm gonna bust you up flashily!
Who is this guy?!
It'd be reckless to go straight
into the Grand Line now!
"The Weirdest Guy Ever!
Jango the Hypnotist"
Counterattack!
Knock that off!
Who cares which is colder,
the North Pole or the South Pole?!
Luffy... Who's she?
How dare you just come waltzing
back here, to Captain Buggy!
Yeah, some meat would
be nice to have first.
If you wanna know that badly,
go to both and find out!
Oh, she's our navigator!
A-Actually, Klahadore,
these people are--
Eating nothing but fruit
everyday is no good...
Now cool it!
Get serious! Who are you guys?!
A ship!
That can wait for now.
Listen! All I want is the
map and the treasure!
Need some booze, too!
Enemy ship to the north-northeast!
Move...
I can hear all about your reasons later.
What're you talking about?!
Alright! Get ready! It's fightin' time!
Yeah, I know.
You're in the way!
Now leave, all of you!
That's not what I mean!
Young'uns... Why are you here?!
The Grand Line is the most
dangerous place in the world!
Alright! I'm gonna plunder like crazy!
Or do you have something to say?
Stay out of this. You're outsiders!
You sure seem happy, Buggy!
Well, actually, we want a ship!
Obviously! Enemy ships
are like treasure chests.
On top of that, it's crawling with
strong pirates after the One Piece!
No!
This is my fight! I will protect my town!
It's natural for pirates
to raid 'em! Am I wrong?!
And they're all on
powerful ships, of course!
--Usopp-kun!
--Crap!
We need more people, too.
I've heard all about you.
"Desperate Situation!
Beast Tamer Mohji vs. Luffy!"
Well, there is some truth to that.
The number of crew members,
the lack of equipment on this ship...
You're too weak!
You're well-known in the village.
I don't need your meddling!
You and everyone else here
never talk seriously about treasure!
There's no way we
could survive like this!
Yeah?
I hear you've been
on many an adventure.
You don't know what it
means to be a pirate!
Yeah, we need a cook. And a musician.
Quite impressive for
someone so young.
You can call me Captain Usopp, too!
A musician?!
What the hell?!
You're so stupid...
Since you admire me so much!
Why did you attack the mayor?!
Captain, huh?
Why would you go that far?
A little to the south of here is
an island with people living on it.
W-What's this?!
He was in the way!
You're a pirate!
I've heard all about
your father, as well.
A-A-A treasure map!
Good thinking.
It'd be best if we can get
ahold of a real ship there...
No doubt this old man
plans to die otherwise.
What?!
I-I've never seen
one before! Awesome!
Klahadore! Stop!
Those three think they
can mock me! Screw that!
This is for the best.
You're nothing but the
son of a filthy pirate!
Alright! Time to eat some meat!
Is it sitting on the
bottom of the ocean?
Don't be crazy!
Don't forget the booze!
Looks like I can consider this
a declaration of war against me!
There were plenty of other
ways you could've done it!
You guys!
Nothing you do will surprise me,
Yes! Now my life
is flashily decided!
but I ask that you stay away
from the lady of this house!
Mohji! There you are!
Pirates are here! Pirates!
Alright, here goes...
F-Filthy?!
Would you mind if I take
Roronoa Zoro's head?
Big Nose!
She and you are from
completely different worlds!
Everyone run away! Pirates are here!
Be my guest!
Is it money you're after?
How much do you want?
That's the one thing you shouldn't say!
--Today was another easy win!
--Hey! Drink up!
That's enough, Klahadore!
Apologize to Usopp-san!
Damn you, you flashy idiot!
Pirates!
Hey, Buggy!
How dare you...
Hey, now! Be careful, Kaya!
Terrible news!
You're not gonna party with us?
We found some neat loot!
What reason is there to apologize
to this savage man, my lady?
Flashily fire the Buggy Ball!
I-I don't got anything special!
I don't know anything!
Pi... rates...
Why'd you say that?! You idiot!
I am merely stating the truth.
What're you talking about?
Hey, Luffy! Run!
Oh, uhh...
That...
I feel for you.
Time to blow up!
The pirates...
You must truly hate your
great idiot of a father
...won't work on me!
...are just a lie!
You said you were gonna
leave this ship sometime.
Gum-Gum...
for abandoning his family and village
because of his lust for treasure!
What do you plan to do?
...Balloon!
Klahadore!
Oww...
I'm gonna have my own ship.
Don't you dare insult
my father any more!
I'm gonna gather a reliable
crew and then see the world.
What is he?!
You exaggeration-spewing kid!
I'm gonna get you today for sure!
Don't tell me the Buggy Ball...
I'm gonna take my time.
All as a pirate, of course.
What's with this dog?
Usopp-san!
Stay right where you are!
He bounced it back!
I'll show you a thing or two!
Dog!
--You always spew that weakling crap!
--Say what?!
Say something beforehand, geez!
It's coming this way!
Here they come!
Here they come! Here they come!
I only admire your fighting skill.
What are you getting
unnecessarily riled up for?
Were you just not soft-hearted,
I might've made you my henchman.
Get back here, you damn kid!
Why not simply tell another of
your special lies at a time like this?
Your henchman? Get real!
Just try and catch me!
Alright! Now there's fewer enemies!
About how your father is
really a traveling salesman,
What the heck are you?!
Huh?
Come and get me!
Hey, Zoro! It's not moving at all!
We think differently, so we should
just go in our own directions.
You really know how
to freak people out...
or how you're not
really related by blood...
Hell if I care!
It can do whatever it wants!
Shut up!
That's what pirates do.
I wonder if it's dead?!
Dammit! He got away again!
Talking like you're an expert, huh?
But if we ever meet on the ocean,
it'll be a fight to the death.
--He's one hell of a troublemaker!
--He's in trouble if I find him!
I knew something was weird from
the time you fought that lion!
Yeah. That's another thing pirates do.
No human can do that! Explain yourself!
--Captain!
Oww! Oww! Oww!
Where the hell'd he go?!
You never make sense.
S-See! You immediately
resort to violence!
What was that balloon-inflatey
thing you just did?!
Oww! What're you doing, stupid dog?!
Anyways, you said
something about loot...
Like father, like son!
The Gum-Gum Balloon!
Do you know the situation
we're in right now?!
Yeah, we found a Devil Fruit.
Shut up!
I'm asking what that is!
Devil Fruit?
I'm proud that my father is a pirate!
What are you, a monster?!
I heard they're incarnations
of the sea devil.
Another job well done today!
Damn dog!
I'm proud that he's a
brave warrior of the sea!
How dare you flashily try to do me in...
I sent the wind of excitement
into this boring village!
Supposedly, if you eat one,
you gain devil powers...
Not enough blood...
...but the sea will hate you
and take your ability to swim!
You're right, I am an exaggerator!
There he is!
You'd have to be stupid
to eat something like that!
But I'll never lie about my pride
to be related by blood to a pirate!
Heya, Navigator!
Oh, it's you guys!
He used his henchmen as shields!
I'd never get that treasure on
the ocean floor if I couldn't swim!
Good morning, Captain Usopp!
I guess you can have this,
since you did save me!
I'm the son of a pirate!
The Usopp Pirates have arrived!
Still, I bet it'd sell for
100 million Berries...
Oh! The key to the cage!
Pepper! Carrot!
Captain...
You went and got it for me?!
Is it just you two? Where's Onion?
What happened here?!
Don't get the wrong idea!
What?!
A pirate, a brave warrior of the sea?
I just didn't want to wind up owing you!
I, pirate apprentice Buggy,
will now eat this Devil Fruit!
You!
That's quite a twisted
way of putting things...
Terrible news! Terrible news!
Heya!
I'm saved!
The Straw Hat guy!
Gotta love kids!
Oww!
But you're the undeniable
proof of his savage blood!
C-C-Captain Buggy! Be careful!
Never thinking about consequences...
Terrible news!
He has Devil Fruit powers too!
You run around spouting lies,
--Onion...
--What's he freaking out about?
He's a rubber person!
He ate it!
and act violent whenever you're angry!
What?!
Terrible news! Terrible news!
Rubber person?!
And to top it off, you cozy
up to the lady of this house
Well, Buggy? Anything
different about your body?
Terrible news! Pirates are here!
Yeah! See!
so you can get her fortune!
Stupid dog! Stupid dog!
No... Not really...
What?! I only--!
A Devil Fruit...
There's a boat with a skull
mark at the north shore!
That's not food! Gimme that key back!
Aww, it was a fake?
The fact that your father is a pirate...
That explains how he
bounced a Buggy Ball back.
Not surprising, I've only heard
about Devil Fruits from rumors...
Yeah, right!
...is more than enough proof
that you'd hatch such a scheme!
Give it back! Give it back!
It's the truth!
Damn it, you still won't let up?!
Stop, Usopp-san!
This is the greatest insult we've
had since we hoisted our flag...
T-The truth?
Yes! That worked flashily well!
Stop that!
It's true! This is bad!
Please, no more violence!
Quit bullying Chouchou, you young'uns!
What I ate this afternoon
was a fake I made!
...Captain.
Oops! It's time for my snack!
Oh, Cabaji! I'm so
angry I can't even fart...
Can't believe everything
went so smoothly!
Klahadore isn't a bad person!
Chouchou?
Don't run away!
Now to jump ship before
they find out the truth!
Who're you, old man?
He's just...
Cabaji! What the hell
did you do to Richie?!
Actually, I have "I'll Die if
I Don't Eat My Snacks-iosis"!
I'm this town's mayor! Who are you?!
He's just trying too hard
to do what's best for me!
With the money from the Devil Fruit
and the treasure on the map,
This cat? I used it as a shield,
I could form my own
pirate group right away!
to keep my clothes from getting dirty.
Huh?
Liar!
My, what a terrible injury!
Hey, Buggy!
Don't you want to be
a real pirate, Captain?!
Richie!
Whatcha grinnin' about?
I take it Buggy went after you folks, too?
Leave this place!
O-Oh, it's you!
Don't scare me like that!
Hey, Richie! Say something!
Are you all right?!
What good is a pirate
who's afraid of pirates?!
Never come near this mansion again!
What kind of look is that?
We need to get you to a doctor!
Don't steal too much
food from the kitchen;
If I recall correctly,
it was Buggy the Clown's mark!
Yeah, I get it.
the cook'll get mad!
I don't need you to tell me!
B-B-Buggy the Clown?!
Richie!
Whew, that was close...
Damn you, you bastard!
Oh, that reminds me!
The captain just--
I'll never come back here again!
How's Zoro?!
He needs to see a doctor,
I think I'll just...
Out of the way!
Usopp-san...
but he said he'd sleep
it off and went to bed.
But it was two small boats!
No, you move!
--Shanks! Damn you!
--What?!
You stupid butt-ler jerk!
And three people or so...
Our captain's not that kind of guy!
My... My... I'm...
Alright! Let's go, Usopp Pirates!
--Yeah! You stupid-head!
--Stupid-head!
Captain Buggy.
What's that scrap of paper?
To protect this village's peace!
Stupid-head!
Yes, Cabaji?
Ahh! My map!
Why're you saying it, too?!
Please leave this to me.
Alright, let's go! Follow me!
H-Hey, Buggy!
So this dog's name is Chouchou?
Alright! Show them your acrobat show!
R-Right!
W-What the--? I can't move...
--What's your problem?!
--Hey, now! Stop!
What's it just sitting here for?
--Let go! You stupid butler!
--What?!
Was it true you lose
the ability to swim?! Crap!
It's guarding the shop.
Come fight me, if you can!
--Guarding?
--Yes...
I, Acrobat Cabaji, Chief of Staff,
Oh! This is a pet food shop!
Hey! Buggy! What're you doing?
You will leave at once, too!
take on Captain Buggy's anger!
Finally on dry land again...
You're great at swimming!
Yes. This shop's owner
is a good friend of mine...
There's a village past here?!
Buggy!
Yeah. It looks like it's
a small one, though...
I'll clash swords with you.
H-Help me...
Oh! In that case, meat, meat!
Meat, meat, meat!
It's an honor, Roronoa Zoro...
I'll save you, Buggy!
There's a place to eat
in this village, right?!
There you go.
To think I would get to slay you,
as a swordsman myself.
Forget about meat
for a minute, will you?!
So I'm here to feed his dog in his place.
Hey, Zoro! You should
really rest! I'll handle this!
Your meal, my lady.
Huh?!
No thanks. I don't want it.
--In his place?
--Yes.
Stay out of this!
So Shanks saved you?
He died three months ago, from an illness.
That's the stab wound the
captain gave him. The fool...
That's not what I'm trying to say!
Careful!
I sense people!
Because of him, my plan in life
was suddenly delayed 10 years!
Acrobat Technique: Old Man Arsonist!
The cook would be sad
to hear you say that.
Where?! Where?! Where?!
Don't tell me he's been waiting for
his master to return all this time?
Look out!
And then I had a revelation!
He works his hardest to come up
with meals that suit your needs.
If underwater's no good, I'll
obtain all the treasure on land!
That's what everyone says...
...Using this Chop-Chop power.
What's wrong? I'm sure I
didn't kick you that hard...
That's why I won't let anyone
who touches my treasure live!
Why did you talk like that?
...but I don't think that's it.
He fights dirty, going
after his injury like that!
I know I was wrong to talk with
Usopp-san without telling you.
Chouchou is a smart dog.
So cool!
Acrobat Technique:
Murder at the Steam Bath!
He's probably long known
that his master is dead.
Is this the time to be impressed?!
Let go...
But you didn't need to
kick him out like that.
...of my treasure!
I am Usopp, leader of the great
pirates who reign over this village!
Acrobat technique, my ass!
Crap! He spotted me!
That's just an ordinary cloud of dust!
Then why is he guarding the shop?
People praise me--
and then praise me more--
Don't think you can escape me, Nami!
I think it's because this shop is
a treasure in Chouchou's eyes.
as "Captain Usopp"!
May I sit?
I'm going to flashily chop you up!
Go ahead.
I think he continues to protect it
He did it again!
Huh?
If you're thinking of attacking
this village, then forget it!
because it's a memento
of his dog-loving master.
What's wrong? A grown man
moaning is disgraceful!
It's been nearly three years...
My 80 million subordinates
won't sit by quietly!
I've tried to make him
evacuate on many occasions,
Well? Now do you see
how foolish it was...
but he won't take as much
as a step away from here.
...since the day I came to this mansion.
Awesome!
...to make an enemy
of the Buggy Pirates?
I'll never forget what
happened that day...
You're lying, aren't you?
M-My balls... balls...
Yikes! She saw through it!
He's crazy to fight while
so seriously injured!
See, you admitted it.
You're still dealing with me!
He's hurt so bad it's almost
mystifying that he's still alive!
I admitted it to her!
Why're you just
standing there watching?!
Something's wrong.
He's gonna get killed!
The mayor's never been
gone this long before...
What?! He was lying?!
Curse you, you crafty tactician!
Something must be
happening in town after all!
80 million may have
been an exaggeration,
There's been more
cannon fire than usual, too!
but I do have great men
under my command!
What's that war cry?!
Roronoa Zoro...
It's him! Beast Tamer Mohji!
Alright! I'll go into town and
check it out! You all stay here!
...is defeated!
I was kicked off the ship I worked on
Annoying bastard!
I'm coming too!
What do you mean by "Beast Tamer"?!
Fool! There are pirates in town!
because of a blunder I made,
W-Wait! Hold on!
Like maybe three people?
Is poking my wound...
The despicable Buggy Pirates!
and with no work or money,
Exactly! I'm coming too!
...that much fun?!
I was on the verge
of dying like a beggar.
She saw through it!
What kind of citizens are we...
C'mon, something's here!
R-Run!
Hey, you! Get out of here!
Give me the key back!
...if we can't even
keep our mayor safe?!
Get up! This is no place
for the likes of you!
Oww!
H-Hey, you guys! Don't run away!
It's no use trying to stop us!
This is all of our own accord!
I've never heard of pirates
using slingshots before!
Oh, I see your friends have deserted you.
W-Why didn't you dodge that?!
Fine, whatever!
Just after you managed to escape, too...
Is that enough of a handicap for you?
Let's go, everyone!
Who're you?
Huh?! Sir?! But...
You're neat!
I am Beast Tamer Mohji,
a member of the Buggy Pirates.
Now I'll show you the difference
in level between you and me!
Hey, you! Don't insult me!
That sure is a weird
animal suit you got on!
I'm a very proud man!
Understood! Take him
inside and tend to him!
So cool!
Because of my great
pride, people call me...
So this is Roronoa Zoro, huh?
How rude! This is my hair!
In my eyes, I owe my life
to your late parents...
You think you can mock me...
"Proud Usopp"!
That's even weirder!
My swords aim to be
the world's greatest!
Do you think you can rest easy
because you're inside that cage?
And to you, their daughter.
You saw it yourself just now!
I can't lose even once to anyone
who calls himself a swordsman!
Hey!
You must not know my terrifying skill!
Leave that treasure
and get out of here!
My slingshot skills are far
greater than your average pistol!
There is no animal in this world...
He'll come after you again!
I realize that it isn't my place
to interfere with your friendships.
I see...
...that Beast Tamer Mohji can't tame!
No!
Leave the treasure and go?!
Absolutely not!
A strong resolve keeps you going.
Now that you've drawn your pistol,
put your life on the line.
Shake!
Why should I have to leave
my own treasure behind?!
But never fear.
Wounds as bad as yours will be
more than enough of an excuse...
But that Usopp lad isn't exactly
known for his upstanding character!
Your treasure?!
Huh?!
Duh!
You're nothing but a
nameless sneak thief.
...for losing to me!
I'm saying those aren't
for threatening people.
I'm a thief who only
steals from pirates,
If... if anything should happen to you,
I have no interest in taking your life.
The hell with that...
and I just stole from one!
Tell me where Roronoa Zoro is!
If I lose to someone like
you with such light injuries,
Which means this
treasure is mine now!
No!
I would never be able to ask for
forgiveness from your kind parents!
Sic him, Richie!
Ah, I see!
I won't have much of
a bright future ahead of me!
What you're looking at
now are real pirates!
Do you think ill of me
for what I did earlier?
Yes! The cage is open!
Nonsense! That's my treasure!
Why, you--!
Do you think stealing
it makes it yours?!
No, not at all!
Do it, Zoro!
I'm glad to have you, too, Klahadore!
Honestly! What kind of
upbringing did you have?!
I can't go along with this!
But please don't misunderstand.
An instant death.
You pirates can injure
yourselves for all I care!
A criminal, trying to lecture
another criminal? Ridiculous!
Good Richie.
Usopp-san is a very nice person.
Now let's find Zoro,
However, whether he's
nice or not is irrelevant!
so I can defeat him
and increase my name!
It doesn't matter to me
whether you guys win or lose!
What?!
What is it?
I haven't fallen so low that I
need to be corrected by pirates!
Klahadore! Urgh! You blockhead!
Ah, a pet food store.
I'm gonna use this chance to swipe
their treasure and get outta here!
Yes, "blockhead" will do just fine!
Alright, make your meal quick!
Huh? Don't tell me this is this
pathetic little shop's guard dog?
I hope you're ready to face
the consequences, Nami...
Let's team up again if
we ever get the chance!
See ya! Good luck with the fight!
Chop-Chop...
Yeah! Thanks!
Taste my ultimate acrobatic move!
...Festival!
Whew, what a shock!
Just try and help your friend,
if you can, Gum-Gum!
But now I'm out of that cage!
Hey, where'd Luffy go?
Acrobat Technique:
The Dance of 100 Kamikaze Tops!
Who knows? Probably
ran after that "captain."
Damn, he broke into even more parts!
Alright! Now it's time
to beat all of them up...
Our captain would be at his spot!
Those aren't normal guys,
that Luffy and Zoro!
...and have Nami the thief
be our navigator!
Yeah, the shore!
What the--?
He always goes there
when something happens!
Nami!
Nothing good'll come from
being involved with them!
How are you alive?!
--Give me my back my treasure!
--You wish!
You're alive!
Wanna check it out?
Is it wrong to be alive?
Huh? Nah, that's okay.
Being just fine after flying
through houses isn't normal!
Coochie, coochie, coo!
But never mind that,
isn't one of you missing?
It's not?
--Yeah, Onion!
What is your purpose
for coming to this town?
He always just ups and disappears!
Here we are!
Geez, you're stubborn!
Why are you involved
with those pirates?
Yeah! And then he
shows up all freaked out!
I just decided our purpose!
Now to steal their treasure
and chart and get out of here!
Now that you've drawn your pistol,
put your life on the line.
Knock it off!
To get a Grand Line map and a navigator!
No, you knock it off!
Bad news!
Huh?!
--See?
--A b-backwards guy!
I'm saying those aren't
for threatening people.
I think that guy in the animal suit
said he was looking for Zoro!
Acrobat Technique:
A Hike in the Mountains!
A weird guy is
backwards-walking this way!
I'll go check on him!
--Liar!
Thanks for the treasure back!
Acrobat Technique:
Fireworks in the Cool Summer Breeze!
It's the truth!
Just look!
Whoa, he's high up!
--Let go! Let go! That's mine!
--Let go?! This is my treasure!
Sting of the Unicycle!
Ground-hugging Chop-Chop Cannon!
You let go!
Chouchou. This shop
belongs to the two of us!
Hey! Who's calling me a weird guy?!
Die!
Cabaji! I'll hold Zoro
down! Finish him off!
I told you... you're dealing with me!
As you wish!
I am not weird!
This bag is too big for you, Chouchou!
Damn you guys!
Seem pretty weird to me.
R-Real pirates definitely have way
more punch behind their words...
Don't be stupid!
I'm just an ordinary,
passing-by hypnotist!
H-Hypnotist?! Awesome!
Luffy!
Awesome...
D-Damn you!
Show us something!
Yeah! Do something!
Stay out of Zoro's fight!
What?!
Don't be dumb!
Why should I have to
reveal my techniques
You don't want to get hurt, Chouchou!
--We stole those lines!
--Eh?
to a bunch of strangers?!
Just leave it to me!
From Shanks, a pirate I respect!
--Alright. Watch this ring closely.
--You're gonna do it?!
Bad Chouchou! I told you
not to eat the merchandise!
S-Shanks?!
Consider that finishing move
a kick from the old mayor guy!
You'll feel sleepy at the
count of "one, two, Jango."
You know Red-Haired Shanks,
the great pirate?!
Now let's chow down!
Alright, here we go!
T-Thanks, I owe you one...
Yeah. Your dad's Yasopp, right?
One, two,
Yeah, no problem!
Jango!
Eh?
--Oh yeah! The map!
--My treasure--!
Geez, what's with this guy?!
This isn't over yet, Gum-Gum!
Oh? You still come at us...
Wow! Look at all this!
He's still alive!
Shut up!
Chouchou. I'm getting up in age now.
And it's all mine!
How dare you flashily
do this to me!
Yeah, Yasopp is my old man...
I gotta check into the hospital.
You'll pay for this!
But I will get better!
Yo!
Assemble! Chop-Chop Parts!
What're you doin' with
our treasure, now?!
Here you are!
Guard the shop well until I come back!
But how do you know that?
Oh, it's just you!
At least say something, will ya?!
"Food"
Crap! He woke up!
Hold down the fort!
So, what, do you want something?!
Not really.
By Captain Buggy's orders,
anyone who gets near here is to be--
Huh?
Good, huh?!
Huh? I'm all out?!
Oww...
I met him when I was a kid!
Looking for these?!
So my old man's on Shanks' ship?
My parts!
It hurts!
W-What?! What's wrong?
Yep! You guys look the same,
Way to go, thief!
My chest suddenly started to hurt...
so when I first saw you, I wondered...
That damn butler,
S-Stop!
What?! Your chest?!
insulting my old man like that!
Go flying, Buggy! Gum-Gum...
Really?!
Yeah, I hate that guy too!
My old man's on such
an awesome ship?!
No matter what anyone says,
Yasopp was a great pirate!
...Bazooka!
I dunno about now,
but I bet he's still with him.
Yeah, huh?!
In this day and age where
pirates are everywhere,
After all, your dad was
a good sharpshooter!
Hah!
I'm proud of my old man for living
with his life on the line at sea!
Yet, that bastard
stomped all over my pride!
I win!
He'll pay for this!
Yes!
But you're not gonna
go see the girl anymore?
Hey! Captain Buggy went flying off!
That tickles, Chouchou!
The chart of the Grand Line!
W-What do we do now?!
Y-Yeah, I dunno...
--Act unconscious for now!
--Good idea!
If that butler comes and apologizes
to me, I might consider it.
Awesome!
I think it's because this shop
is a treasure in Chouchou's eyes.
That's nothing. I could even shoot
an ant right between the eyes!
That butler?
I can defeat you easily enough,
Yeah, that butler...
even without my captain's help!
I think he continues to protect it...
What's that butler doing out here?!
Enough... I'm tired...
It's all torn up now...
...because it's a memento
of his dog-loving master.
Oww! That hurts!
Well, that's okay! I can still put it on,
Y'know, Luffy,
Hey, Jango.
I got a kid named Usopp,
just about your age!
plus I sent Buggy flying,
so I'm satisfied.
Finally given up, have you?
I told you to avoid doing
anything to make you stand out.
Though I must say, I'm impressed
you could fight with such injuries.
You've already told me
lots of times! I'm sick of it!
Yet you go and sleep in
the middle of the village...
What?!
Don't be stupid.
I don't stand out one bit.
I'm not weird, either.
It's all right.
I'll fix it for you later.
I meant I'm tired...
of your crappy-ass acrobatics!
Well, I'm gonna keep on
tellin' you more about him!
Eh? What?
There's someone else
with him. A weird guy...
Nothing!
It was sad to say goodbye,
but there was no other choice!
Never seen him before. Who is he?
Hey, anyways, I split it into
two bags, so carry half of it!
Then I'll finish you off...
So, preparations for the
plan are ready, I hope?
There was but one reason:
the pirate flag was calling me!
It's too heavy for me!
There sure is a lot!
Of course.
...with my real sword skills!
If anything, Buggy does know
quality treasure when he sees it!
Damn it! That dog even bit me!
Die!
All this should go for no less
than 10 million Berries!
We can start anytime...
Stuck! Stuck!
The Rich Girl Assassination Plan!
Oni...
...Giri!
Usopp. I heard enough about
you to make my ears sore.
Wait! I just killed you!
--Here you go.
--Eh?
A-Assassination?!
Cabaji!
It's the chart of the Grand Line.
Didn't you want it?
Yasopp was a great pirate!
We, the Buggy Pirates,
I won't die that easily!
--You're giving it to me?!
--You did save me.
Yeah, huh?!
beaten by mere sneak thieves...
Crunch his head for sure this time!
I'm proud of my old man, who leapt
onto these possibly endless seas...
Thanks, Nami!
I finally got a map of the Grand Line!
Hurray!
...to live with his life on the line!
We ain't sneak thieves...
I won't lose to some lion!
Oh! Does that mean you'll
join our crew now?!
Then that makes this easier!
Gum-Gum...
I told you I'm never going
to join a pirate crew!
Do you have any friends in this
village who know how to sail...
We're pirates!
...and anyone who
can supply a big ship?!
Luffy! I'm goin' to sleep now!
...Hammer!
But okay! Staying with you
guys seems profitable enough.
Right! I'll handle the rest!
As you can see, it's just a tiny village...
Don't call it assassination, Jango.
That has a bad ring to it.
But I'm only teaming up
with you, just so you know!
Sorry, but we can't
live up to your hopes.
Richie!
Oh, right. Accident. It's an accident.
Always remember that!
Yeah!
On the top of the hill...
There was a huge mansion.
What are you?!
Hey! Zoro! Wake up! Zoro!
I'd expect no less from the
notorious Buggy Pirates' treasure...
Hey, what're those
guys talking about?
Say! Do you know them, Usopp?!
I ate the Gum-Gum Fruit!
D-Don't look at me!
That's what I'd like to know!
Think you could ask them
to help pay for one?
We're going!
Hauling it is exhausting!
But with this much treasure--!
Did we take care of everything?
You can't go there!
You mean you have Devil Fruit powers,
We can't simply kill her.
Yeah! We also got
the map and a navigator!
I-I just remembered
something I hafta do!
just like Captain Buggy?!
Miss Kaya must perish
in an unfortunate accident.
I have lots of influence here!
Don't mess that up!
Anyways, I gotta get
off this island ASAP!
A-all right! I peacefully
apologize to you!
Eat and drink as much as you want!
No good... Out of blood...
I don't think I can walk...
So basically, on your signal,
the men and I storm
the village and kill the girl.
Alright! Later!
Of course you can't! You wouldn't
be human if you two could walk!
You don't need to apologize now.
And then you'll get her inheritance...
Why was he in such a rush?
'Cause that dog's treasure
is never coming back.
Why am I included?
You're the most suspicious of all!
You fool! You don't
understand a thing!
Anyways, we gotta help the mayor...
That's why I'm gonna kick your ass!
How would I, an outsider,
inherit Kaya's estate?!
You guys are pirates?!
Oh yeah!
We gotta wake up
the old mayor guy now...
You'll work hard to?
Yeah! We're going to the Grand Line!
You, there!
Working hard won't amount to squat.
Are you outsiders?!
That's no simple voyage nameless
bums like you can handle, dimwit!
Listen, this is the
most important thing!
Yeah... Who are you?
We're this town's citizens!
Before you kill her, you'll use
hypnosis to make Kaya write her will...
Did the pirates have
a falling out or something?!
What're you gonna do in
the Grand Line, anyway?!
...to say, "I leave my entire
fortune to my butler, Klahadore!"
If you know anything, tell us!
Go on a sightseeing trip or something?
Oh, it's just the citizens!
I thought they were
more of the pirates...
Only then will I inherit
her enormous fortune...
Oh, Mayor!
--Oh, no! Say something!
--Hey! Mayor!
You wish to see Usopp?
Become King of the Pirates!
Pirates are all the same, every last one!
--He's out cold!
--The pirates definitely did this!
Get real, you flashy idiot!
Not this again...
In a completely ordinary manner...
How horrible!
You, King of the Pirates?!
Would that make me God, then?!
May I? I want to talk to him.
They take what people hold dear
without a second thought!
Sorry! I kicked that old man's ass!
I've spent three long years gaining
the trust of everyone around me
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates
and obtain this world's treasures!
That will not do.
What?!
Oh, you're alive, pirate!
That man is the village's
biggest exaggerator!
Hold on! You don't
need to tell them that!
so that it would be unsurprising for
her to leave her inheritance to me.
I figured the lion ate you for sure!
Quit your dreaming!
--You saw it.
--Yeah, but you had an actual reason...
For someone in your weakened state,
You're annoying.
Usopp's exaggerations
would be too much to handle!
Three years as a butler for that, huh?
As a pirate, you'll do the same thing!
Just bring it on already!
Why did you guys do
this to our mayor?!
But...
Your late parents firmly
instructed me to protect you...
But you sure scared us back then...
Maybe I should kill you right here
before you can gather a crew...
Seeing that straw hat of yours
brings back memories of him...
Captain Kuro.
Don't give us your excuses!
...and attack people too!
...to the fullest of
my abilities, Miss Kaya.
Who are you?!
Are you with those pirates?!
Three years ago, you suddenly said
you were giving up life as a pirate.
Come! Stop that, girl!
...and irritates me!
As if you could ever kill me.
They're really bloodthirsty...
Now then, I'll leave
your medicine here.
Memories of that damn
cheeky red-haired man!
In no time flat, you set up
a subordinate to be your double,
If we accidentally say
we're thieves or pirates...
--Maybe I'll try and see, then!
--I said stop! What's with you people?!
Please be sure to take it.
then let the world see
Captain Kuro get executed.
We're pirates!
Red-haired?!
Red-haired... Does that
mean you know Shanks?!
Cheapskate.
--Just as we thought!
"Cheapskate" will do just fine.
Huh? Yeah, but why?
--You idiot!
--It's the truth!
What's bad is bad.
Pirates! How dare
you ravage our town?!
Where is he now?!
Dunno! Maybe I know where
he is, or maybe I don't!
We won't show mercy
just 'cause you're kids!
So that was the very
beginning of this plan.
This is all I could take back.
What now? Doesn't look
like they'll hear us out...
Bastard ate all the rest.
You truly are Kuro,
Man of a Thousand Plans.
What're you talking about?
Are you stupid or something?
He... fought with that lion.
For that dog's sake...
Don't call me that.
Not as much as you!
Run!
I abandoned that
name three years ago.
I ain't nice enough of a guy to
just tell you what you wanna know!
I now want to obtain
great sums of money
There's no escape!
How dare you hurt
our beloved mayor?!
without the government on my back.
Pardon the intrusion--
Then I'll make you tell me!
In other words, I'm a pacifist.
You fought good!
I didn't see your fight, but I can tell!
I'll kill you before that ever happens!
Some pacifist you are,
Ugh! Why did you
make things worse?!
Usopp-san!
I doubt rubber can
bounce back blades...
killing off an entire rich family
for this "peace" of yours.
Heya! You seem as down as ever!
--This is a good town!
--Eh?!
Everyone's so mad,
just for the old mayor guy!
Nope, it can't!
I'm sorry!
Hold on, now.
The father's death was real.
I'd really like to invite
you in as a real guest...
Chop-Chop Rice Cracker!
I hadn't planned on that.
...but Klahadore refuses to allow it...
Well, whatever. It doesn't matter.
I think they'd get mad
at any excuse we give!
He's not a bad person, though.
Anyways, hurry and give the signal.
Can't move in midair, can you?!
Don't sweat it!
We're turning here!
We've been sitting in the waters
near here for a whole week now.
After all, I am a brave
warrior of the sea!
H-Hold on!
Don't say that so suddenly!
Yeah! Good luck to you, too!
Can too!
They ran into the alley!
I'd only feel cramped inside a house!
The men are starting
to grow impatient.
So what adventure are you
going to tell me today?
Oh, quite interesting!
Chouchou?!
Hmm, let's see...
Dog!
You, too!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Alright!
This is bad! We heard
something really bad!
The story of when I fought the
giant goldfish at the South Pole...
H-Hey! Move, Chouchou! Hey!
Those are interesting abilities,
...when I was five!
but they leave you wide open!
You were beaten?!
Goldfish?
Those guys are bad pirates!
Hey, what's going on?
This sounds kind of bad.
Yeah! What first shocked me...
You're barking at the wrong people!
I'm gonna carve you up!
I- I'm very sorry, Captain Buggy!
Weren't you listening
this whole time?!
Gum-Gum...
...was the immense size of its poop!
Chop-Chop Quick Escape!
--Why are you getting in the way?!
--Chouchou! Let us through!
It was so big that I landed on it,
Mohji! I can't believe
you'd lose to Zoro!
This is seriously bad!
They're the real deal!
...Sickle!
thinking it was solid ground!
Captain Kuro is said
to be the smartest
No, it wasn't Zoro!
It was that Straw Hat!
Chouchou!
What?! That straw hat kid beat you?!
and most brutal pirate of all!
Not good enough, Gum-Gum!
He's eaten the--
Word had it the navy caught and
executed him three years ago...
Now I'm pissed!
...but Captain Kuro is alive!
Prepare all the Special
Buggy Balls we have!
Later, dog!
Damn, you keep breaking into pieces!
As Klahadore, the butler!
I'm gonna blow this entire
town to smithereens!
Is this really the place?!
He's been after Kaya's fortune
for these past three years straight!
Yeah, the pirates dragged him inside!
W-What a fight...
It's almost like I'm dreaming...
--Sorry about earlier!
--Huh?
We gotta save him!
But they're real pirates!
I didn't mean to yell at you...
They might've grilled and eaten him!
H-Hey, you see that?!
It's okay! You've been through a lot!
You idiot!
It's old hags who eat people!
That was scary!
They're gonna attack the village!
You dumbass!
Keep pretending to be knocked out!
We managed to escape
thanks to Chouchou!
Kaya's in danger, too!
Why do we have to put up with this?!
Get caught up in that, and you'd
never have enough lives to survive!
I don't feel like hearing
about it though.
Does it matter now?
We're done here anyway...
Alright! Get ready, you guys!
I'm so pathetic!
Chouchou and this
young'un will fight so hard,
Chop-Chop Cannon!
--Maybe so, but...
--Hey, is this your boat?!
Bad! This is seriously bad!
This will be the most epic battle
since the Usopp Pirates' formation!
yet why must I, the mayor, sit by
and watch our town be obliterated?!
It's great!
Separate!
I don't think it's so great.
Yeah!
I stole it from some idiot pirates.
Calm down, Mayor!
The Usopp Pirates have arrived!
That's a big mouth ya got!
40 years ago, this place
was nothing but barren land.
Well?! Now do you see, runt?!
Hey! Don't stand up! They'll see you!
Been waitin' for ya, thief girl!
Hey, you guys! Don't attack that girl!
We all worked together to
clear the land, make fields,
What're they?
Never thought you'd
run into us here, didja?!
open stores, and build our town.
--The captain is gone!
--You don't think he...
Who're you?!
You idiot! They spotted you!
--You know them?
--Yeah... sort of!
This town is a treasure
to me and all the citizens!
You bastard!
H-Hey, pirates!
Hurry and hide before they kill you!
Not sort of! We're bound by fate!
Oh? Was I not supposed to
scratch your face or something?
What'd you do with
our Captain Usopp?!
Oh... If it isn't Usopp-kun.
I cannot let them
domineer over it any more!
--What'd you do with him?!
So you had friends, huh?
Guess we'll hafta punish you, too!
How dare you...
That meat was yummy!
How dare you damage this hat!
Fire a Special Buggy Ball!
Blow the town away!
They spotted me, too!
You're gonna learn how bad it is
to steal other people's stuff!
--Meat?!
--Don't tell me the captain...
Did you... hear anything?
Huh?
Hey, you! Quit ignorin' me!
This is my treasure!
W-What?! What did you do?!
N-No! Whatever do you mean?!
Whoever damages this
hat absolutely must pay!
If you're lookin' for your captain...
We just got here now, so of
course we didn't hear anything!
Huh?!
--We heard everything!
--Hey, you!
Yeah. I swore to the person
who gave me this straw hat...
...we ate him.
Even my own house...
...that I'd gather a crew
and become a pirate!
--Old hag!
--What're you looking at me for?!
Zoro's sleeping in there!
I thought there was nothing
that could faze him...
Oh, all right.
Mayor! Are you conscious?!
The young'un is dead now...
You just had to say something stupid!
To think he could get this upset...
Hey, you guys!
Watch this ring closely!
Hey! Zoro! Are you alive?!
--Thank goodness! You're all right!
--What on earth happened?!
That's one hell of a way
to wake a guy up...
Whew, it was just a joke?
What?
T-This is bad!
It's a throwing weapon! Dodge it!
What in the--?!
It would seem that
hat has a history to it.
It was already like this
when we got here!
Not enough sleep...
At the count of "one, two,
Jango" you will get sleepy.
There were some pirates left,
but they all ran off!
That's right!
Is it that important of a hat?
Ready?
How are you still alive?!
Huge!
--One, two...
--Hide! He's gonna kill us!
Did you not see anything
that happened?!
Thank goodness! You're alive!
If our captain ran off at
this hour, he'd be here.
I refuse to let them get away with this!
...Jango!
Where are the young'uns?!
Oh? What's he come here for?
Do you mean those three kids?
If so...
I can stand this no more!
To lie!
...then protect it better!
Some random scum has no right
to suddenly destroy our 40 years!
So they're alive?!
That's a bad thing!
Hey! Wake up, Jango!
He's not bad! He's great! Right?!
Have you still not
fixed that habit yet?!
Those fools! How dare they
harm a senior citizen like me!
Yeah! He's great!
How does that work?
H-Hey! What're you doing?!
You're gonna fall!
I am this town's mayor!
--Kaya, the girl who lives here,
is weak, and she's had depression...
--There was a ship
stopped near the goldfish,
--Kaya, the girl who lives here, is weak, and she's had depression...
We just finished driving
those idiots away!
I will protect this town!
--There was a ship
stopped near the goldfish,
--...ever since her parents died from an illness a year ago.
--and on it was a pirate
bigger than even a mountain!
--...ever since her parents died from an illness a year ago.
But it's still not enough!
Head-first...
They almost seemed
to be mocking us!
I didn't mean to kill him,
--His face was hilarious!
--...ever since her parents died
from an illness a year ago.
Stop! Stop, Mayor!
They'd never understand how we
felt when they attacked our town!
--His face was hilarious!
--Even though she has lots
of money, she's so sad.
but he couldn't have
survived from that height...
There are fights a man cannot run from!
Shanks!
Damn it! He killed him!
Isn't that right, young'un?!
Yeah! Yeah!
So our captain tells his special
made-up stories to make her laugh!
That's right, old man!
Your arm!
There's still time to go
after them and catch--
Don't urge him on!
That bastard! Damn it!
Shut up!
What can he possibly do by
going to see them?! It's reckless!
'Cause our captain's
the best at telling lies!
I'm the only one who's allowed
to complain about them!
What about the other one?
Shall I take care of him?
I'm fully aware it's reckless!
Never heard of a pirate with
a face like that, have you?
I'll leave this hat with you.
I won't let anyone else
talk badly about them!
No need.
No matter what he does,
it won't matter.
It's dear to me.
Oh, so he's great!
W-What?! Why are you
protecting pirates?!
I'm coming for you, Buggy the Clown!
Take good care of it!
Yeah!
I like the captain's meddling side!
Damn them... So they
plan to just disappear?!
Tomorrow morning, Jango.
Attack the village at daybreak.
The mayor was crying...
Where did they go?!
I like his bossy side!
He was? I didn't see it.
They, uhh, ran toward the port.
Tear up the villagers'
homes a good amount,
I like his exaggerating side!
Looks like the party's
gettin' more exciting!
Come bring it back to me someday!
and make certain Miss Kaya's
murder looks like an accident!
So that's helped her
feel a little better?
--Damn it!
--Mayor! Mayor!
Sure does!
They think they can do whatever
they please in my town!
Yeah, a lot better!
Once you've become a great pirate!
This is no time to be laughing!
Tomorrow!
Great! Let's ask her for a ship after all!
I have lots to say to you all!
You heard me, Usopp-kun.
It's okay! I like that old guy!
That's our promise, Luffy!
There's nothing you
can do to stop my plan.
It's thanks to Usopp
that she's gotten better.
I absolutely won't let him die!
In that case...
Just getting in is impossible!
Alright! Let's get going!
Damn it!
You're gonna go, too?!
With that wound?!
There are way strong
guards at the gate!
Isn't that Buggy's mark
on your sail there?
The injury to my name is much
worse than the injury to my gut!
--Huh?
--Where'd Luffy go?
I'll go ask!
You sure about him?
How is this old,
tattered hat a treasure?
Well, this is his boat.
I'll get rid of it sometime!
Of course. My plans are flawless.
Wait, you're not gonna--?!
Our destination is the Grand Line.
Gum-Gum...
Hey! Wait! Young'uns!
Treasure refers to sparkly gold,
silver, and jewels...
So we're gonna steal
that map back now!
This is bad, this is bad, this is bad!
--H-His arms stretched!
--He's a monster!
The old mayor guy!
Everyone in this village I grew
up in is going to be killed!
...that display their owner's grandeur!
...Pardon...
Join our crew, Nami!
--Hey!
--Wait, Luffy!
Kaya's going to be killed!
You call this filthy
straw hat a treasure?
...the Intrusion!
I'll never be a pirate.
Even though I love them all!
Cut the crap!
...And so we escaped into the sky
atop a gigantic slingshot ball!
I was ready to die!
How about we team up
for our common goal?
That's the hat Shanks
and I swore over!
I was ready to die
filled with despair!
What?!
Meaning this is Shanks' hat?!
The second shot is ready, sir!
Huh?
Thanks! We're in your debt!
Alright! Fire!
Yahoo!
No wonder it seemed familiar!
Come out, Buggy the Clown!
Who are you?!
He always wore this by my side!
Don't worry about it! Take it easy!
I'm Usopp!
A brave warrior of the sea!
You and Shanks sailed
on the same ship?!
Damn you young'uns...
I am Mayor Boodle!
I hear you've been unhappy lately!
Yeah, back when we
were pirates-in-training.
This town is our treasure!
I've come to protect it! Fight me!
--That worked great!
--Did not!
I'll cheer you up with a story!
Damn you young'uns...
A-Are you all right?!
We were comrades.
Mind your own business!
What are you, stupid?!
Treasure is gold, silver, and jewels!
That damn detestable,
red-haired bastard!
Yeah! It's okay, it's okay!
Please leave! I'll call for someone!
I have no words...
They're new recruits who heard
all about me and came from afar...
This town, a treasure?! Cut the crap!
Shanks is a great man!
...to join the Usopp Pirates!
And then? What happened after that?!
You'd never understand how I feel--
You, his comrade?!
What?!
No, not me!
I fought, of course! Bravely, at that!
Don't compare yourself to him!
You left one of the treasure bags?!
I'm soon going to conquer
the Grand Line and flashily obtain...
I'm here to ask a favor!
First, for the giant cat,
I used a cattail plant...
Yeah.
Chop-Chop Quick Escape!
Just one is worth
5 million Berries, you know!
A favor? Of me?
...all of the world's riches!
--Yeah! We want a big ship...
--You, there!
But they need money to fix
their destroyed town, right?
The world's riches are mine!
Hi, I'm Buggy!
No one else in this world
needs treasure but me!
That was my treasure!
What are you doing?!
Never say you and Shanks
are comrades ever again!
Damn it!
Do you know how much I
suffered trying to steal it?!
If this town's that important to you,
shall I destroy you with it?!
Klahadore...
Why did you do that?!
--Stop! I can't swim!
--That's the whole idea!
Quit prattling and fight me!
I don't appreciate you breaking
in here without permission!
I can say whatever
I want about Shanks!
Don't get cocky now!
If you want it,
go back and get it then!
I won't let you destroy this town!
Even if it costs me my life!
I can't do that! You go get it!
Tell me! What happened
between you and Shanks?
No! Wahh, that's dangerous!
I could die, you know!
Who's he?
Die once!
Fire!
Damn it! How dare you
tear up my treasure!
Do that again and I really will
throw you into the ocean!
The straw hat guy!
Well, for better or worse,
Do you wanna know that badly?
looks like a navigator's
joined our journey.
He's the one person
I absolutely can't forgive!
I'll curse him for the rest of my life!
I'm here to kick your ass,
just like I promised!
I'll never forgive him!
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Usopp ran by with a really
intense look. Did something happen?
Wow! We actually reached land!
Get ready, Buggy!
I'm gonna kick your ass!
Huh? Now there's some
swordsman or whatever guy!
Who does that butler think he is,
treating people like thieves?!
Yeah! Beat him!
--I'll clash swords with him!
--You sure? You're injured...
Of course we did!
We followed the map!
Yeah! We only came
inside to get a ship!
That butler is a pirate!
He told his crew to attack the village!
You'll pay for damaging the hat
me and Shanks swore over!
There's a village up ahead!
That has "thief" written all over it.
Now they'll know, and can run
away beforehand! That's a relief!
I'll show you our difference in level!
--They got a place to eat, I hope?!
--I wanna eat some meat!
That weird guy's way more suspicious!
Ooh! Cool!
Okay, get going, Luffy!
Beat him up to protect my treasure!
My ambition is to be the
world's greatest swordsman!
Forget about food, you guys!
--Oh, no!
--What is it?!
What's that ring?
We need to stock up on food
before the meat shop guy runs away!
I can't afford to lose to anyone
who calls himself a swordfighter!
Hey, look! That butler is
with him! What's going on?!
--Hey! Who's he?!
--Where?!
Huh? That doesn't sound right...
He says he's a pirate captain!
That's not the issue at hand here!
It's basically the same thing!
Don't sweat it!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Epic Showdown!
Swordsman Zoro vs. Acrobat Cabaji!"
"The Weirdest Guy Ever!
Jango the Hypnotist"
"Expose the Plot!
Pirate Butler Captain Kuro"
"Liar of Justice? Captain Usopp"
"Who is the Victor?
Devil Fruit Power Showdown!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!