Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"Yuba" "Erumalu" "Nanohana" "Katorea"
"Rainbase"                 "Alubarna"
"Spiders Caf"
"Yuba" "Erumalu" "Nanohana" "Katorea"
Three years have passed
since a single drop of rain fell
Three years have passed since
a single drop of rain fell
Three years have passed
since a single drop of rain fell
in the kingdom of oases.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people took up weapons.
in the kingdom of oases.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people took up weapons.
in the kingdom of oases.
The burning land is now
enveloped by a mighty swell.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people took up weapons.
The burning land is now
enveloped by a sad bellowing
After parting with Ace, Luffy
and company continue to trek
and a mighty swell.
The burning land is now
enveloped by a sad bellowing
and a mighty swell.
through the vast desert
as they hurry to Yuba.
Vivi tells that Koza, the
leader of the rebel army,
Princess Vivi, in her attempt
to prevent any fighting,
To stop the maelstrom of war
spreading throughout Alabasta,
and a mighty swell.
As for whether they can stop
the beleaguered rebel army...
arrived at the Yuba oasis, but the
rebel army was nowhere to be seen.
possesses a passionate heart and will
fight to the death for his friends.
Princess Vivi was in a rush
to talk with the rebel army.
Princess Vivi, in an attempt to
stop an orchestrated rebellion,
...the setting sun watches
over them silently.
Luffy's party continues its trek
through the desert toward Yuba,
However...
And, at long last, Baroque Works'
Officer Agents sprung into action.
decides to talk with the
leader of the rebel army.
I wanna kick Crocodile's ass!
where the rebel army is gathering.
The ruined Erumalu behind her,
she now heads straight for Yuba.
The clash between the royal and
rebel armies is close at hand!
"Ruins and Lost Ways!
Vivi, Her Friends, and the Country's Form"
If we stop the people rebelling,
will that stop Crocodile?
"Showdown in a Heat Haze!
Ace vs. the Gallant Scorpion"
"Luffy vs. Vivi! The Tearful Vow
to Put Friends on the Line"
At least try putting all of our
lives on the line together!
"Spiders Caf at 8 O'Clock--
The Enemy Leaders Gather"
Aren't we friends?!
Excellent work today, my fellows!
Now tell me...
So let's hit the hay for now and
regain our strength for tomorrow!
...where Crocodile is!
It was at this moment
that Vivi made up her mind.
Hey, Luffy...
Nighty-night!
Looks like he's back with us.
What did your brother give you?
You've been sleeping this whole time!
"The Battlefront of Alabasta!
Rainbase, the City of Dreams"
I dunno.
Huh?
Why, you...
Are you finally sane again?
--It's just a scrap of paper.
--Just a scrap of paper?
Don't compare me with you monsters!
You're such a nuisance.
Lemme see that.
Huh? Wha? Huh?
Now you've done it!
What is it, Popo?
--Where are the others?
--Dunno.
It really is just a scrap of paper.
It's not even a note or anything.
Huh? You don't know?
Besides, you win today's
laziness award, Blue-Nose!
--I'm not sure, to be more precise.
--Don't be funny.
Smoke!
Everyone...
A-Are you serious?
It's not my fault I can't stand the heat!
--This is no time to be laughing!
--Yeah.
Sanji-san. That's my--
Yes. I thought you might have a
hard time sleeping alone tonight...
I'm not really sure either, but...
So we're lost again?
Luffy-san is exactly right.
I've made up my mind now.
Is that--?!
Whose fault do you think that is?!
The tattoo on his back...
No question about it!
And what do you think you're doing there?
Wha? M-My fault?
Let's go to where Crocodile is!
Hey! Don't eat that!
Fire Fist Ace! He finally showed up!
Oh, that took some nerve.
Which one of you is spoiling for a fight?!
Sheesh!
--Give me your hat, Luffy!
--Huh? This?
Yeah!
That does seem to be
the quickest shortcut.
Do you guys not understand
the point of a nap?!
If it's that important, I'll sew it to
the underside of your hat ribbon.
Portgas D. Ace! How I've
been longing for this day!
Meaning no more of this
annoying, roundabout traveling.
Alright! You're in trouble now!
Oh! Great! Sew it good!
Yes, yes!
So, where is this damn Crocodile?
--Get back here, Crocodile!
--Huh?
--This is all the breakfast we get?!
--Seconds! Seconds!
--What's he freaking out about?
--I'm gonna kick your butt!
Okay! All done!
Let's see here...
Plus he's flying...
This is the capital city of Alubarna,
where my father rules from.
Did he eat another weird cactus?
Don't act wasteful!
You've had enough calories!
--Here you go!
--Thanks! Now I don't have to worry!
And the rebel army is currently here,
preparing to invade Alubarna.
Ugh! Can't he ever not cause trouble?!
Hey, old guy. There's still no
water. My throat's bone-dry...
There's nothing written on it.
What point is there to keeping it?
Hey! Luffy! Why, you--!
Chopper!
--Keep your hands off others' food!
--C'mon! Gimme food!
So we need to take care of
Crocodile before that can happen.
Ace told me to keep it, so I'm keeping it!
I don't think he can help.
--Don't sweat it!
--There isn't any more!
How can you live in a place
like this? This is bad...
Why does this happen at every meal?
Crocodile is here. Rainbase.
Your confidence isn't based on anything.
There'll be water.
The Yuba oasis is still alive.
Oh, geez. Alright, Zoro. It's up to you.
Don't make eye contact.
So what? It's right a lot!
--Why me?!
--Want me to talk more about your debt?
Rainbase...
Look! Ace-san is cleaning his
fork and plate after his meal!
Yuba, you see, can't be
beaten by some lousy sand!
--I don't know about that...
--Someone carry me...
It's about a day's journey north of here.
I'll dig it back up
as many times as it takes!
If you don't end up in hell,
I'm gonna kick you down there myself!
Yeah! He's completely different...
Everyone! Yuba is just over those big rocks!
This is very important land
that the king left in my hands.
--Damn you! Give it back!
--No!
I look forward to it!
Okay! Let's get going!
Let's make one more push to get there!
...from his incompetent little brother.
Eh? Shouldn't we wait for them?
Okay!
But you'd never guess from
Ace's well-mannered personality
Oh! Okay! Then let's dig!
They can just follow our footprints.
--Yuba, huh?!
--Yep! Yuba!
C'mon, I told you to
quit moaning, you two!
Oh! Wait! Stop!
Don't re-fill the hole I just dug!
Yuba!
With their strength,
they'll catch up in no time.
that he has an immense
bounty on his head.
--Carry me, Zoro...
--Don't be a wimp!
Who're you to say anything
when you're riding the camel?!
We can wait somewhere relaxing.
Ace-san has a bounty?!
--Ooh! Carry me too, Zoro!
--Rock-paper-scissors, then!
Are you trying to fill holes?!
Agreed...
Yeah! Let us ride, too!
I hear it's such a large amount
that bounty hunters around the world
You camel-woman!
No, I'm digging.
Will they really be all right?
--Nami-mel!
--Good one!
drool at the thought of it.
No, the sand you're digging out
is going into the hole I dug,
Chopper! You haven't collapsed today!
You idiot! Wake up!
The operation will commence
at high noon two days from now.
Fire Fist Ace of the
Whitebeard Pirates...
Yeah. I'm gonna try extra hard.
so I'm trying to say that all my
hard work will be for nothing!
Pirates the world over fear
the mere mention of that name.
Have you finished the arrangements?
Vivi. Does Rainbase have water?
Urgh!
Stick him with a needle
or something, quick!
Yes. Everything has gone smoothly.
Oh.
Which means this Blackbeard pirate
Ace-san is seriously chasing
Yes, there's no problem there.
Oh! So it's a mystery hole!
150 Billions are on standby in Nanohana.
It's a gambling town, almost
completely detached from the rebellion.
O...kay...
must really be something, too...
Come on, now...
Ooh! Gambling?!
No, it's not!
Blackbeard... The traitor who
killed his own crewmate...
I've also called Mr. 2 back.
It appears he failed to capture Mr. 3.
Hey, now! What're you thinking?!
Can't count on anyone!
Crocodile!
I guess even here in Alabasta
there are carefree cities.
It looks like Ace is going to keep
chasing him as long as it takes.
Gum-Gum No Way!
The officer agents' gathering is at
8:00 tonight, at the Spiders Caf...
I found you!
What're you talking about?!
No! No! No!
Fire Fist Ace!
Come to think of it, the sand
has stopped flying this way.
I'm gonna...
--Gimme some!
--Gum-Gum No Way!
--You dumbass! Don't make me...
--...kick your butt!
I'll start off with a little gift from me!
Gum-Gum...
Yes. Very good.
C'mon! Just one sip!
That is why we have it!
All this, in such a short time?!
...wake you up!
No, I ain't gonna kill ya.
...Submarine!
It is past 5:00 already.
Even though he must be
exhausted from his long trek...
I'm just gonna blow up that
rock you're sitting on first!
That dry old guy spent all
night digging this water up!
I assume they'll start
gathering around now...
Even though this happens
every single time...
...stopping him when
he's gone crazy is a pain!
We can't just drink it like
it's nothing! You dumbhead!
Urgh!
May you have a nice rest tonight.
Wow! Sometimes you
can restrain yourself!
I have my pride! So my aim
is to capture you alive!
Of course I can! How rude!
Meat...
You're rude!
Pleasant dreams.
Can't take another step... W-Water...
Gimme a break!
So?! How long until Rainbase?!
Okay! Let's get going! Today--
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Merry Christmas! Merry Christmas!
What a long, exhausting trip!
My back's killing me!
--Dammit! Give it back!
--What's the big deal?
Just how long are you
going to make us wait?!
Luffy-san.
How did I wind up
following a captain like this?
Knock it...
Thanks. I never would've been able
to make this decision on my own.
"Miss Merry Christmas"
Honestly! It's all your fault, Mr. 4!
At least offer me an Octopar!
...off!
Don't make me dance! I'm a swan!
Don't make me spin around!
Your slowness is backache-inducing!
Then gimme food.
--Here we go!
--Yeah!
I'm... sorry...
Eh?
After I kick Crocodile's ass,
gimme so much food I might die!
Now hurry and clean up!
We're leaving for Yuba!
Mr. 2. Just wait quietly.
Yes! Yes! Yes! How's business, Paula?
The place is empty today!
Okay! I promise!
Seriously! You imbecile! Imb!
--You too, Miss Merry Christmas.
--You make my back hurt!
Place empty! Plempty! Ple! It's ple!
"Rebel Army Camp in Katorea"
W-Wow! Awesome!
I guess there's no chance
of you all getting along.
It's good to see you again.
Welcome, Miss Merry Christmas, Mr. 4.
--Oh no! They saw us!
--Hurry, big brother!
Though that won't be necessary anyway.
This meat can talk!
"Paula"
You have the shop all to yourselves today.
What? What're you talking about, Luffy?
Miss All-Sunday...
Oh! The meat!
I can make you some orange pekoe
and... apple tea, was it, Mr. 4?
Thank you for coming all
the way to this gathering
Please, Koza! Let me join the rebel army!
Oww! Hot!
The meat's running away!
--Wait, meat!
--Luffy!
in the town of Rainbase, where the
people dream of winning it big.
What am I--?!
No.
Why not?! I have the right to
join the rebellion too, don't I?!
Never mind the hot drinks! I want
something I can drink right away!
Make some right away! Right away!
Right now! Right away!
What are you doing?!
I despise the king! Let me fight with you!
Welcome to Raindinners,
the largest casino of all!
What's going on?!
What in the world happened?!
Get back here, meat!
Show him, Faracla.
You seem lively. How is work going?
Which way?! This way?!
Hey! Zoro! Hey!
Could you skip the formalities and
cut to the chase, Miss All-Sunday?
In my trade, screw up and you die!
Things are going great, obviously!
We did it, big brother!
Get up!
He got this trying to protect me
in the middle of a battle.
You imbecile! Imbecile! Imbe! Imb! Im!
A restorative!
Yes. I'll get right to the point.
Is it good, Chip? It's our first
food in 10 days! Eat it slowly!
Would you like to see the
medical wards and the graves too?
Yeah! Get started! Started! Start!
You're right. I'm sorry.
I can't believe we got meat!
Here, big brother!
Thanks...
T-That doesn't scare me!
--What were you doing?!
--Stuff...
--Un, deux!
--Ora!
But first, I'll need to introduce
you to our company's boss,
Yeah, we never even had
any in the Badlands!
--Un, deux!
--Krah!
He's still buried.
Towns've dried up, and many have
died 'cause the king stole the rain!
What the--? What kind of crazy
songs does this place play now?
Leave him be for now.
Where are the others?
whose face you still don't know.
Oh? You're from the Badlands?
They were gone when I came to...
As his secret proxy, I've been the
one who's had you work until now,
It made lots of my friends sick, too!
Song? No, I have a sonata playing right now.
Those coldhearted bastards!
From that rustic nowheresville?
It's all the king's fault!
But that's alright. We can
just follow their footprints.
--Who're you?!
--You can't have the food back!
I wanna fight, too!
but there is no longer any need for that.
There's no singing...
I'm not afraid of getting hurt or even dying!
I take it you understand...
--Un, deux!
--Ora!
At last, the time has come...
Then leave. Our opinions are too different.
Umm, footprints?
M-Move and you're dead!
Huh?
Say what?!
--Un, deux!
--Krah!
We're all afraid, and none
of us want to fight.
You're actually Crocodile?!
...for Operation Utopia.
Look at your fingertip with your nose...
Don't be stupid!
Then why do you fight?!
I'm generally not fond
of dangerous things, but...
--Un, deux!
--Krah!
Huh? We got separated?
It's not that we wanted to. We had to.
Keep with your fingernails!
Crocodile?!
You moron!
B-Big brother!
Have you shot for reals before?!
--Un, deux!
--Ora!
Why didn't we go after them sooner?!
This will be Baroque Works' final operation.
That's what the country wished for.
Before... being born...
That would be because of you!
Will it really shoot bullets?!
H-Hell if I know!
H-Hold on! I'm gonna--!
Whether you understand or not,
it has nothing to do with you.
Chopper! You smell things good!
It would seem you know who he is...
at least on the outside, anyway.
Lesson! Lesson!
I'm already trying. But
I don't smell anything at all.
Leave.
Stop!
I said leave, dammit!
This is no place for children!
Of course we do! But why one of
the Seven Warlords of the Sea?!
Love... and mascara!
Then we have no clues at all?
Which way is the wind blowing from?
Talk about a real big shot!
Wh-What happened?!
I don't know the direction,
but it's coming from our left.
Mascara with a nosebleed!
Play your dangerous games in moderation.
We've actually been the
underlings of a pirate?!
What was that about, Koza?
Left, huh? That at least
means they didn't go that way.
It's not like you to rant
and rave at children.
I'm self-made!
Good little boys should brush
their teeth before sleepy-bye.
You're our boss?
You're just makin' that up.
It was like looking at my
old self. It made me mad.
H-He bounced it back with a rock!
Shut up! Stay here if that's
what you want! Let's go, Chopper!
--So... Lesson!
--Lesson!
Dissatisfied?
I-I've never seen
anyone so strong before!
Yeah...
C'mon, wait for me!
Don't leave me behind!
Who're they?
Not exactly dissatisfied,
but the Seven Warlords are pirates
I haven't changed one bit...
--Lesson!
Oh, come my way!
with government permission to plunder.
I have a favor to ask!
Have we gathered enough weapons?
Why would you need to
own a company like this?
No, it's proving difficult...
And... smile!
There's someone I want
you to find and catch!
--Oh, the greatest!
--The greatest!
So hot...
Contact all the other towns.
What I want is neither money nor status.
Will be he all right?
If you catch him,
I'll pay you a million Berries!
As soon as we have weapons,
He's not the kind to
kick the bucket so easily.
Oh, come my way!
we launch an all-out assault on Alubarna!
Military might.
--Say.
--Yeah?
A million Berries?!
Military might?
I can't pay right away,
but I will pay it when I grow up!
Is pirate life always like this?
Sire! It's only a matter of time until
the rebel army attacks Alubarna!
Like what?
Allow me to explain in good order...
Always climbing snowy
mountains, crossing deserts...
Greetings!
Ain't that the truth?
We must take action first,
before it's too late!
Please! Find this man!
How are deux lately?
But we're just a little out of the
ordinary. Plus there's our captain.
Silence! I told you no!
You must be stupid.
This is not a children's quarrel!
Is retaliation what you want?!
...my true objective
I am not stupid, Paula!
I think I might've gotten on
board a not-so-good ship...
Scorpion-sama's ultimate weapon!
and the whole picture of
Baroque Works' final operation.
After all, I'm a dancer!
But, Sire! The country's
existence hangs in the balance!
What a coincidence. I was just
thinking the same thing myself.
One hit from this will
demolish that entire rock!
--One Octopar, please!
--Octopar?
So what?
Then, while Ace is buried under
the rubble, I'll capture him alive!
--Say.
--Huh?
Ever since the Dance Powder
incident, it has been clear
Gimme a break! An Octopus
Parfait! Everyone knows that!
You're the most veteran
crew member here, right?
that someone is trying
to destroy our country!
Okay! Light 'er up, Popo!
I guess, but there's not that
much of a difference between us.
--Oh, you guys can leave now!
--Right!
Are you suggesting
we destroy our countrymen
before learning who's
really pulling the strings?
Why did you join?
Don't get lazy with your dance practice now!
That would be the downfall of our country!
Darn it! It's meat, but it
ran away! I'll make it pay!
Why do you ask?
Right! Un, deux! Un, deux...
To me, since I just joined,
it seems like everyone's a maverick.
Listen! A country is its people!
Something like that really
exists in this country?
Huh? Fatty! Old hag! You're here?
However, this wire-puller has
not shown himself whatsoever!
Huh?
Why, you! Why did you do that?!
And we're going to steal the
entire country along with it?
Especially you.
Shut your trap, you! Pipe down,
you're hurting my back!
That's true. In my case, things
pretty much just turned out this way.
Taking action after this unknown
shadow devours our country
This is giving me such chills!
I'll strangle ya!
would be too late, Sire!
In short, these assignments of ours
Oh, right, right, right!
No. Please understand.
That reminds me, I hear even
Mr. 1's team is being mobilized!
are the final pieces of this enormous plan?
The others are the same.
Our real goals are different from his.
The king won't allow us
to take the offensive.
No!
That's right.
I've never met 'em for whatever
reason, so I just can't wait!
Every job you've performed
since Baroque Works was founded
We're trying to do what we want to do.
We can barely even appease
the soldiers at this point.
No! Hey, boy!
It's crazy. It's just like
someone said before.
If only Igaram-san were
here at a time like this...
Run!
has been a part of this operation.
If that blows up, it'll take
half of Alabasta with it!
On the outside,
we have no teamwork at all.
And those letters are your final orders.
Igaram says he's leaving
the country for a while?
Especially given our captain.
He's a real handful.
Oh! The night grows ever later!
At last the time has come for the
Alabasta Kingdom to disappear.
Huh?
No! It'll blow the
Grand Line to the moon!
As we speak, he and Vivi-sama
I think so, too.
are probably still hard at work,
trying to figure out who's behind this.
It's almost the appointed time of 8:00!
But, really, what is teamwork?
Once each of you has
fulfilled your mission,
I wonder where they are.
this kingdom of Alabasta will wreck itself...
Chaka-sama! Pell-sama!
Is helping each other and
protecting each other enough?
What is it?!
Karoo has returned!
Hey! Boy?!
...and, with nowhere to go,
the rebel and royal armies
Karoo has?!
Some people say so,
Yeah?
Oh, I'm bored!
but, sorry, that only sounds
like they're fooling themselves.
will tragically fall into
Baroque Works' hands.
Wh-What happened to the bomb?!
I'm so bored I spin around!
I think teamwork only begins
In a single night, this land
will truly become our utopia.
This?
when everyone risks their lives
to do what they can and then says,
No!
I think I'll take a spin!
Sire! Who is that letter from?!
Quit it! You're an eyesore!
Operation Utopia is Baroque Works'
last and greatest operation.
You're funny, old guy!
"I did it! You're up next!
If you can't do it, I'll kill you!"
What's your problem, hag?!
You wanna fight or something?!
It's Vivi's handwriting, without a doubt...
Hey, boy! Quit laughing and help me up!
If that's what you want!
Sire! Does that mean--?!
Failure is not an option.
When you think about it that way,
Come, now! Stop it, you two!
Karoo came to deliver
a letter from Vivi-sama?!
Upsy-daisy!
what's wrong with having
mavericks as companions?
We begin at noon tomorrow.
Understood!
Father. Everything written
here is true. It is fact.
That's my opinion, anyway.
I wish you luck.
Where?! Where is he?! Where'd he go?!
So that's what Usopp meant by,
"Just do what you can!"
I can't afford to be playing
around at a time like this!
I must ask that you hold off with
this Operation Utopia of yours.
It sounds like BS
when he says it, though.
Popo!
We're heading out to where he was!
H-Hey, now! What happened to you guys?!
As for why I still stay with him...
The person trying to bring
suffering and ruin to this kingdom
Why'd you come bursting back in here?!
N-No... It was him...
...being by his side all this time's
given me another goal to strive for.
My brother and I've followed
him out here from the Badlands.
is none other than Crocodile!
Oh. They're acquaintances of yours?
Another goal?
So, who is he?
Sorry. I dunno how to answer about it.
Scorpion. A bounty hunter.
They were acting suspiciously
in the desert, you see.
Bounty hunter?
Igaram is another who has
fallen at the hands of Crocodile.
Why are you guys
chasing a bounty hunter?
Don't worry. I doubt they're dead.
I found shade!
You seem to be on rather close terms,
Gum-Gum...
--Well...
--I have business with him, too.
Mr. 3. How did you get into
this secret underground room?
Crocodile! I stupidly believed
he worked for the government!
but worthless, cozy relationships
will only result in your downfall.
...Rocket!
Mr. 3! Where the heck did
you come crawling out of?!
A man in Yuba defeated Blackbeard.
His name was Scorpion.
I never would've imagined he
was trying to usurp this kingdom!
These men are my subordinates!
I'll get rid of you,
just like I was ordered to!
Stop, Mr. 2!
My reason for going
to Yuba is to meet him.
Igaram-san...
Wait, Mr. 2.
He gave his life for
Vivi-sama and this land...
Eh?! He defeated Blackbeard?!
Un, Deux, Krah!
Crawling out of? How rude.
Whoo!
This guy did?!
And now, there are people who
have given me unfathomable power.
Un, Deux, Ora!
I merely stuck by your side
since the Spiders Caf...
It's nice and cool!
I oughta chop you apart!
Oh! My bad! My bad!
...as I took a ride on Bunchi's car.
If I continue with them, we may
make a difference in this kingdom.
Huh? Where's Chopper?
Bold Change!
So, where are we going, old guy?
Un! Deux!
Oh! There he is!
Nice to meet you, Boss.
What's he doing out there?
Is he trying to act funny?
The light of hope is here!
Alabasta will be saved!
I've humbly come here
to ask for another chance.
You're a very lucky boy!
Yes. It was my fault. I'm sorry.
Please have faith, Father!
You get to witness me, the world's
greatest upcoming bounty hunter,
It was only natural that you
be sent to take my life, Mr. 2,
Geez! What was the point
of that conversation--
What the--?! He slipped through the wall?!
Vivi.
locked in battle!
after I failed to accomplish
the task given to me.
No! He shattered the wall?!
Hey. I didn't know
you were a comedian.
You're a bounty hunter, old guy?!
That is why I changed course slightly
I'm not!
It says you fought valiantly,
too, Karoo. You've done well.
It seems you want to die.
Don't be scared when I say
and headed for the Spiders Caf,
where we agents are stationed.
Oh! You're okay?
that I've been on many
a heart-pounding adventure!
Dammit! That hurts!
Hold it! That's enough, Mr. 1!
I've fought epic battles with
everyone from Double Barrel Danny
You're hurt? Let me see.
Failed to accomplish your task?
What are you talking about?
Don't stop me, Miss Doublefinger.
I'm going to kill him.
What is this place?
to Hellbattler Luther and they
always begged me for their lives!
At any rate, no matter what happens,
You know. H-How I let the Straw
Hats and Princess Vivi escape...
Wow! For reals?!
Stop! Let go of me, Fatty!
this thing on our left arm
is the sign of our friendship!
What's this?
Mr. 2! Cool your anger as well!
No, but someday it will be!
Chaka.
It's now 8:00. All the agents
that should be here are here.
Oh, someday, huh?!
Escape, you say?!
We know the enemy's identity!
Prepare the soldiers for expedition!
In any case,
I'm gonna beat Fire Fist Ace!
Are you saying they're still alive?!
And a letter with orders has
arrived at the Spiders Caf.
I will not let Vivi's resolve
and Igaram's death be for naught!
Everyone else but him would be a cinch!
What did you say on the Transponder Snail?!
You wanna beat Ace up,
old guy?! That's funny!
We're taking immediate action!
We're heading to Rainbase,
where Crocodile is!
Did you not say you took care
of the pirates and Vivi?!
We're to head to Rainbase,
the city of dreams.
Please wait, Sire! Rainbase is
too far away to be "immediate"!
Hey, now! Don't mock me, boy!
What is this?
The man we call boss, the man
whose face we've never seen...
When I do something, I don't kid around!
Transponder Snail?
What are you talking about?
Crocodile has the citizens on his side!
I never used a Transponder Snail
while on Little Garden.
Yes! Men live for big ambitions!
I have to show 'em that!
Even more so than you,
with all due respect...
What's something like this...
...doing underground?
What?!
Why are you down here?!
If we attack Rainbase,
...is waiting for us there.
--I used my arms.
--I'm asking why!
Huh? Show who?
Heya. You've called the Damn Restaurant.
You want reservations?
the rebel army will use that as
a chance to storm the palace!
--Just 'cause.
--You idiot!
With you down here too, we might
get separated from Chopper!
Here comes Scorpion, the gallant man!
And if that happens--!
So what if the rebel army
destroys this palace?!
Without him, we'll never meet
up with Vivi and the others!
This isn't good.
--Oh! That's okay!
--Why is that?!
So that's why the Unluckies
haven't returned from the island.
I've told you before! A country is its people!
Because Chopper was
falling down here too!
So, I assume you at least
got rid of one or two?
Even if our royal army falls,
as long as Crocodile is defeated,
See?
N-No, actually...
Oww...
the country will be reborn by the people!
What is this place?
B-But there was an
inaccuracy with the information!
But, consider if we clash
with the rebel army instead!
Heya. You seem to be alright.
She actually had four pirate escorts,
Zoro! Luffy! Where is this place?
I dunno, Ace. Did this Scorpion
guy really beat Blackbeard?
They should be on their
way here to Rainbase now.
Crocodile is the only one
who will have the last laugh!
and there-- and there was a
long-nosed man with them and--
No idea. But whatever it is,
it's definitely underground.
Damn you!
I'm not sure. The only way
to find out is to meet him.
Zero-chan! Come on,
explain what's going on!
I sent Bunchi to get them. I expect
them to arrive sometime tonight.
Underground?
Sire...
I'm exhausted!
Let's take a short break!
You're that dedicated to--?
A-Ace? You don't mean the real...
None of it makes any sense!
Even if by some chance
the rebel army doesn't stop,
Yes, Nami-san!
...Fire Fist Ace?!
we need only take out Crocodile!
C'mon! You're pathetic!
To think that you were
actually Miss Doublefinger...
Easy for you to say! You rode Lashes!
We gotta walk the whole way!
We're up against one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea.
I... I met them!
"Miss Doublefinger"
Crocodile is not weak of heart.
What is it, Ace?
Thanks, Lashes!
I don't remember ever saying that I wasn't...
This battle will not be without
sacrifices before its end.
Two people. And a bird?
I ran into these guys on my way here!
Vivi?
What?!
Have you found replacements for
the Billions wiped out in Nanohana?
Will Luffy-san and the
others know where to find us?
What is it?
Chaka! I'm holding a war meeting!
Assemble the officers!
--They're coming!
--Eh?
Him! Him!
I think they'll be fine.
We're on top of a hill. It stood
out clearly, even from far away.
Her!
Pell! Go on ahead and
conduct enemy reconnaissance!
I've finished assigning the replacements.
Him!
And him, right?!
Yes, Sire!
I hope so...
I've dispatched the Lizard Runners
to contact the new Billions.
It seems we've been severely
underestimating His Majesty.
And...
Say. How much further to Yuba?
There you are, Fire Fist Ace!
...this is Miss Wednesday,
who is this kingdom's Princess Vivi!
What powerful spirit!
Seeing as we made it to these ruins,
Meaning they were actually our enemy?!
We go to battle tomorrow morning!
I'm Scorpion! The indomitable hero!
we should be there by night
if we continue walking.
Yes, Sire!
Yes. They know my identity.
I'm sending all soldiers to Rainbase!
Close, at last...
I've come from afar to challenge you!
Let's fight, fair and square!
I see. Everything is progressing smoothly.
Oh? So these are ruins?
They will interfere with
the operation if left alone.
Yes. I believe they're
from quite an old era.
That's Scorpion?
Civilizations first began
here thousands of years ago.
Heya! Are you all here?
And Mr. 3.
Up ahead! I see a light!
L-Luffy!
It seems they have gained one person
and one animal, just as you say.
Wh-What are you doing there?!
Many kingdoms have risen and fallen.
Did we make it to Yuba?!
I can't really see with all this sand!
I see it...
Is that it?
Resettlement in search of water,
the occasional war...
Setting the pet aside,
it seems we can safely assume
I-It's really him...
Rainbase?
Ruins of such things remain
all throughout this land.
Oh! Are we here?!
This is Fire Fist Ace?!
that Vivi and the other four
are already here in Alabasta.
What's wrong, old guy?
Crocodile!
Many are full of mystery.
Eh?! N-No, uh...
Alright! Time to beat up Crocodile!
And time flowed on, leading to
the Alabasta dynasty of today?
Mr. 2. Make photographs of
the faces you just displayed.
So sorry! Your luck's run out!
What could that sound be?
B-But, Boss!
That's an epic story. A prosperous
kingdom, destined to disappear...
Your heroic saga that's
told on the sea ends today!
I swear that I will take care of that
crew and Vivi with my own two--!
The city doesn't look right!
Don't be stupid! He's the real one!
Quiet, you damn fool!
It's almost romantic.
Eh?
Sanji-kun!
Mr. 3...
This is so exciting!
Ace! It's a serious fight!
Sorry, Vivi-chan!
I didn't mean it like that!
Mr. 3!
Don't pull any punches!
It was just, you know, a figure of speech...
I wasn't planning to!
Do you know why I gave you your rank?!
But there's something
I wanna ask him, too!
It's all right.
A sandstorm!
I've often felt the same way as of late.
So this is Rainbase!
Move aside, Luffy!
What's wrong with me?!
Don't wimp out now!
In terms of fighting skill alone,
even Mr. 4 outclasses you, Mr. 3!
By the way, does Baroque Works
know we're in this country now?
The city of Yuba is being
struck by a sandstorm!
Just what is a country?
This is nothing!
I'm invulnerable! I won't die!
Even if the ruler of a land changes,
its people will keep on living.
Not as long as they're waiting for me!
It was because of the underhanded,
contemptible tenacity you have
Most likely.
Here I come, Fire Fist Ace!
We did run into Mr. 2, so we should
assume they know we're here.
Culture, lifestyle...
for accomplishing your duties!
If those stay the same even
when a country changes,
So what?!
You've really let me down!
I wonder if it's really necessary
to struggle to protect the country.
They know what we look like!
W-What is that?!
We can't do much of anything
while we're in Rainbase!
Take this!
H-He's drying up!
Certainly, there are other
things that need protecting.
Why not?!
If we get spotted first,
W-Water...
Ever since the sand pirates and the
town with the fake rebel soldiers,
Crocodile can probably deal
with us in all kinds of ways.
Water...
Have all the water you want.
I've been thinking that way a lot.
This can't be...
Assassination is their area of specialty.
W-W-W-What?!
I'm sorry! That's just me being strange!
Come out, Crocodile!
This is bad. It's almost no
different from that Erumalu city!
Oww! Hot! Hot!
Were you even listening?!
I haven't found the answers either!
In any case, no matter who we run into,
H-He sent that metal net flying back!
I'll protect Nami-san and Vivi-chan!
But I do know what we must do now!
Where's the water?!
Wasn't this supposed to be
an oasis city, Vivi-chan?
You two girls can call me "Prince"!
Baroque Works' scheming is about
to cause a meaningless war!
It's feeding time.
The sand has raised the ground!
The oasis has been swallowed up!
Prince.
Don't make me kick your ass!
We must stop it, at all costs!
It wouldn't be any fun if it were
that easy to stop Fire Fist Ace!
What is this place? Underwater?
--Prince... Water...
--Water...
What they're trying to do
is throw this land into ruin!
Shut up, you guys!
Water! Need water!
Oh? You seem to have some skill.
I don't care if it leaves a
dark splotch in our history!
I-It's almost like an aquarium...
Me too!
Are you travelers?
--Water! Water!
--Wait! Luffy!
Our hellish battle is just getting started!
I absolutely refuse to let
Crocodile have his way!
Take money with you!
A b-bananagator!
You must be exhausted from
your trek through the desert...
Popo! Compressed Extinguisher Gun!
Well, we should get going!
Sorry. This town is a bit dried up.
Usopp-san! Are you all right?!
That runt's caused me much trouble...
Are you kidding? I can't control
the strength welling up in me!
A compressed air gun filled
with extinguisher foam!
Captain Smoker.
But you're free to rest here if you want.
--Liar.
--Oh, shut up!
Why do you think the Straw Hats
will show up here, in Rainbase?
--Wh-What?!
--Extinguisher?!
He just doesn't know how to stay dead!
They'll stop in a second!
I'm gonna use this to fill you full
of compressed extinguisher foam!
I'll show you how gutsy Manly Usopp is!
Dunno. Call it a hunch.
There are plenty of inns here.
They are this town's pride, after all.
Listen, now! Take a good look at these five!
I'll never fall to my knees easily!
Alright!
--We can get water here, Usopp!
--Water!
They're bent on stopping the rebellion.
--What's the big idea?!
--You fell easily.
--Well, we should get going, Vivi.
Plus, something stinks about this country.
If we leave them alone,
eventually they will come to us!
Umm, we came because we heard
the rebel army was in this city...
Eh? But what about Luffy-san?
I get a strong sense that something
big is lurking in the shadows.
But, Zero-chan.
You're such a worrywart.
Even if she is the princess,
Old lady! Water!
What business do you
have with the rebel army?!
He says he's going
to kick Crocodile's butt.
do you really think she can stop
the rebellion at this point?
A barrel of water! No, five!
Five barrels of water!
Curse you! Don't tell me you're
hoping to join the rebellion?!
Once he has a clear goal,
you can let him do his own thing.
Then you think there
really is a connection
Sorry, but you never had a chance.
Unfortunately, the rebel leader
Koza and Princess Nefertari Vivi
--You know that!
--Yes!
between the Baroque Works criminal
organization and Straw Hat?
I expected as much. You lied about
beating Blackbeard, didn't you?
are apparently close childhood friends.
If you're looking for those fools,
they left town long ago.
You figured using his name would
get me to show up. Am I right?
--Here!
--Water!
My eyes've adjusted.
It's a swell of 700,000.
On closer look,
we're inside a giant dome.
All I know is that Straw Hat
is out to get Crocodile...
They what?!
Even if it can't be easily stopped,
That's right. Not too
shabby of a plan, huh?
--Built by people, no less.
--Huh?
--...one of the Seven Warlords.
--This water's great, you jerk!
No!
she can bring confusion to the rebel army.
A sandstorm hit the town just now,
but it certainly wasn't the first.
These are probably
ancient ruins or something.
I've already had many
Billions join their ranks.
It's great, you bastard!
How can you tell?
We've fought on even terms this far.
Now I'm gonna get serious!
Look at this. See all the
picture-like writing on this wall?
Let's hurry and take the others some!
The sand has dried up
after three years of drought,
The fact that there's
been no word from them
No more!
I saw it in a book or something before.
These are ancient letters.
must mean they still haven't
taken any direct action yet.
That's enough, Dad!
and sandstorms began to
frequent this town ever since.
--Eh?!
--Dad?
Whatever the cost,
Who cares about that stuff?
Vivi and the rebel army must
not be allowed to make contact
Little by little, the oasis of
the past was swallowed up,
It's so nice and cool in here!
before the operation.
"D-Dad"?!
leaving what you see now.
Stop this!
If you're right, then what is
this place doing underground?
--Miss All-Sunday.
--Yes?
With the town's flow of supplies gone,
D-Dip! Chip!
Given the circumstances, I don't
mind using Transponder Snails.
I need to take a leak.
I don't really know...
Dad!
not even the rebel army's protracted
struggle would have worked out.
Contact the Billions in Nanohana.
Stop! You don't stand a
chance against Fire Fist Ace!
Was it built underground, or did
it get buried after it was built?
Can we really count on them?
So the rebel army moved its base to Katorea.
Wh-What are you two doing here?!
Tell them to kill them on sight!
They can do little errands
just fine. Don't worry.
Either way, I get the feeling they
were trying to hide this building...
When did you leave the Badlands?!
Do not let Princess Vivi
and the pirates into Katorea!
I dunno. I bet they'll come back
with a bunch of trouble again.
Katorea?!
Dunno who did it,
but they sure worked hard.
Where's that, Vivi?! Is Katorea close by?!
Vivi and Koza must not be allowed to meet!
I'd do warm-up exercises if I were you.
In any case, it's none of my business,
and it doesn't interest me.
It's an oasis next to Nanohana.
--Run!
--Yeah!
Dad! Look! Look how big this potato is!
Yes. Right away.
--Got that barrel?!
--Yeah!
What we gotta do now is get the
hell outta here. Right, Captain?
Damn it!
We're going after 'em, Tashigi!
Gather the marines!
Katorea is the town where
I got lost and met Lashes!
Now you get going, too! You don't
want to be late for the party!
Oh! That is big!
Yes, sir!
Really? But it's cool in here.
Umm, how much do I owe you?
Just get up!
If you know those kids, you better
pay for the water they took, too!
No! No! Let's stay here a
little longer! It's hot outside!
"When you saved me..."
Our utopia is near at hand.
We're lucky we got to
eat another potato today...
Lashes says he was carrying
rebel army goods to Katorea!
Y-Yes! I'm sorry for the trouble!
Just once, I wanna eat until I'm full!
Why is the Navy here again?!
Okay! Time to get outta here!
We gotta meet up with the others!
--Why didn't you say so sooner!
--Why, you...!
You idiot! Don't tell Dad that!
How should I know?! Just run!
"Whatever!"
Dad gave up his dream of
bounty-hunting so he could support us!
So that's Zoro's comedy hole?
I don't want any further trouble.
Shut up!
Alright! Gum-Gum...
The Navy's chasing 'em again!
Why did we come all this way, then?!
Please leave it to us, Boss!
Yeah...
There's an incredible hero across
the sea on a big adventure,
...Pistol!
No way!
You can count on us!
Vivi?
So why are they running this way?!
Did you just say "Vivi"?
Go enjoy yourselves!
so I wonder if there's anything
that exciting for us, too...
Say! Tony-kun hasn't come back yet!
Wait, old guy! Vivi isn't the princess!
What are you doing?
Leave him! He'll manage!
Don't tell him that, moron!
Of course there isn't!
Darn it! I missed 'cause
the target's so small!
We're gonna live our lives
without anything interesting!
Hey, guys! The Navy's here!
I'm sorry for being so unseemly, Vivi-chan.
Vivi-chan? Is it you?
Even Dad threw away his dream for us!
You're the one bringing them here!
No, you're not unseemly at all!
You're alive! Thank goodness!
Catch 'em for sure this time!
We're going to spend our whole
lives in this withered land, too!
Well, we should be off!
Alright! Got it!
Oh, Luffy-kun. Take this with you.
It's me! Don't you recognize me?
Again, what are you trying to do?!
They're quick to run away, I'll give 'em that!
Wow! Water!
What kind of glum look is that?!
Quit complaining!
Just grab onto the boulder above the hole!
Water!
I suppose I can't blame you.
I did lose some weight...
You found some?!
This isn't a good idea!
Last night, just after you
fell asleep while digging,
Dad!
Baroque Works is gonna spot us...
Just you watch! I'm gonna
go back to bounty-hunting!
This is getting annoying!
Toto-ojisan?
...if we run through the city!
I reached a moist layer of sand.
Gum-Gum...
I'm going to challenge
that hero! Fire Fist Ace!
...Gatling!
That's right!
That water is the moisture
I managed to extract from it!
Then I'm gonna fight the world's
greatest battle and come back here!
I think it's too late for that.
Oh! That sounds kind of
complicated, but thanks!
Then it's decided! Let's go!
It can't be...
It's genuine Yuba water!
I'm sorry it's all I could get...
--Eh?!
--To where Crocodile is!
Right, Vivi?!
The world's greatest battle
is too much for you!
Yes! Do you see that
alligator-roof building up ahead?!
I'll drink it with care!
Well, Vivi-chan. This is goodbye for a while.
We came to get you, Dad!
That's the casino Crocodile runs...
Come visit sometime,
once the city's taken shape!
--Alright! All better!
--Are you crazy?!
Don't be silly. I'm the
world's greatest bounty hunter.
Raindinners!
What are you gonna grab on to
now that you broke that boulder?!
Okay, Toto-ojisan!
There, huh?!
So that's where Crocodile is?!
I've fought epic battles with
everyone from Double Barrel Danny
It's okay! I got an idea!
Luffy! What're you doing?!
Yuba will surely make this kingdom lusher...
to Hellbattler Luther and they
all begged for their lives!
--Huh?!
--Chopper. You should probably turn little.
It'd be best if we split up!
It looks that way!
Or so you plan, right?
--Huh?
--Gum-Gum...
Luffy?
Alright! See you later!
You found me out, huh?
What's wrong, Luffy-san?
I'm sure of it...
Yeah!
That's right. I'm a terrible
liar and a terrible father.
Oh, now I see...
Let's meet at the alligator house!
Grab on!
--They split up!
--Don't let 'em escape!
Just give it up. This is the only way!
But, there is one thing that's true!
I quit.
Okay.
Come and get me, Smokey!
Huh?
Here goes!
You got real guts!
Even the most insignificant person
Toto-ojisan?
You "quit"?
Don't think you can keep running forever!
can still challenge the world's
greatest hero if he tries hard enough!
Luffy-san... What do you mean?
Vivi-chan. I have faith in His Majesty!
...Spring!
White Vine!
C'mon, Luffy!
That's what I wanted!
We don't have time to put up with
your whims, you know! Get up!
I wanted to show you two a grand dream!
Gum-Gum...
Yahoo!
He's not someone who would
ever betray the kingdom.
Aren't we going back?
...Balloon!
Yeah.
Men need dreams burning
inside their hearts!
If we don't go back to Katorea the
way we came and stop the revolt,
Don't you agree?!
Even if it means struggling every day,
never give up! Stand tall!
How are we going to land?!
a million citizens here are gonna
clash and things'll get ugly quick!
Heck if I know!
Live every day with a laugh!
You don't mean--?!
That was close!
As long as you keep challenging the
impossible, life will be paradise!
I told you to just give it up!
This is for Vivi-chan! Now let's go!
Nobody mentioned this!
Damn!
Ahh! Much better!
But there's no way to show that
without putting my life on the line!
That's boring.
Say what?!
Where did everyone go?
Yes! If you stand up,
the path will always open!
That's Luffy's smell!
Vivi!
Yes?
That's Zoro's smell!
I wanna kick Crocodile's ass!
Sanji's goes that way!
D-Dad!
Now! Watch your father's
unconquerable spirit!
Successful escape!
What's going on?!
If we stop the people rebelling,
will that stop Crocodile?
Where'd they go?
Outta the way!
No, I won't lose!
Oh, there they are!
Besides, we won't be able to
do anything in Katorea anyway.
Not as long as I have an enormous
dream burning inside my heart!
I think I did choose
the wrong ship to ride on...
This rebellion is ridiculous!
Whoops!
We're pirates, you see. Things
are better off without us around.
Mr. Bushido! This direction, too!
We're on the same wavelength today...
Popo! The bazooka!
Those fools...
I was just thinking the same thing...
It's them! No doubt about it!
He can really get straight to the
point without thinking sometimes...
Kill 'em!
Fire Fist Ace! This is the end!
The Baroque Works Millions!
Despite being Luffy.
So what if it hasn't rained
for a mere three years?
Dad! That's enough! No more!
"Stuck between the devil
and the deep sea," huh?
Usopp. You're falling behind.
T-That's--!
Dip! Chip!
You want it so nobody dies in this fight.
Go on without me!
We understand! We understand
what you're trying to say!
I have faith in His Majesty.
Most of the country still does, in fact.
--Hurry!
--R-Right!
What happened to
showing how gutsy you are?
We stood up to hardship, too!
None of the citizens, and none of us!
I-I only said that out of spirit...
Usopp!
We'll live every day as hard as we can!
--Look after Nami-san!
--What?!
With you around,
we're filled with courage!
So many times...
Even when we're up against
a Warlord of the Sea
I'll hold 'em off!
So many times I tried to stop them.
Hang in there! Just a little further!
I'm sorry I complained!
I don't really care about food!
and a million people are going wild,
--Alright! You can count on me!
--Sanji-kun...
But they won't listen to anything I say.
--Go!
--We are!
you hope everyone will stay safe and sound.
Still worried?
I'm happy just being with you, Dad!
The rebellion won't stop.
Without that smoke freak around,
they're just small fries.
Oh, no...
--We love you, Dad!
--We love you!
It's written all over your face.
Their strength is at its limit, too.
Don't you think that's too soft-hearted?
I'm sorry. I do have faith in them, but...
My deepest condolences.
They intend to settle things
once and for all in the next attack.
I'm guessing you'll never
get over being a worrier.
Hold on, Luffy! At least show
some sympathy for Vivi!
Dip! Chip!
Their backs are to the wall...
Dad!
But that has its good points, too.
Wait, Nami-san.
But...
And what's wrong with thinking that?
--You people are amazing.
--Eh?
They're prepared to die!
What's wrong with not
wanting people to die?!
I've felt that way ever since Little Garden.
I hope Mr. Bushido will be all right!
Please, Vivi-chan! Stop those fools!
People die.
How can you have so much
faith in your friends?
How?
Is that all you got?
Try again some other time.
It's not something I'm conscious of.
I've never even thought about it.
Stop talking like that!
--Gum-Gum...
--I got this!
Say that again and I'll make you pay!
"Katorea"
Roronoa Zoro! We meet again!
That's what's amazing.
Having unconditional faith in someone.
Fire Fist!
That's exactly what
we're trying to stop here!
That's not very easy to have.
That voice...
Hmm. I'm not really sure,
but maybe it's because
I've been looking for you for a long time!
The rebel army, the royal army,
and the people of this kingdom
we all do what we can
as best as we can?
What do you think you're doing,
cutting down regular citizens?!
haven't done anything wrong!
So why do people have to die
when it's all Crocodile's fault?!
Look, I got my own circumstances, too!
--Where's our leader?
--Inside.
A while back, he said
something on the island I lived on.
Besides, I have no desire to fight you!
I don't know how to
use swords, you bastard!
We settled our match in Loguetown!
Dad! Dad!
I don't know how to sail the oceans!
We did not!
Dad!
I haven't even laid a single blow yet!
You all right?
Then why are you putting
your life on the line?!
I can't cook!
A-Ace...
She looks like her! Way too much like her!
--I can't lie, either!
--Hey, now!
Dad protected us!
I'm confident that
I can't live without help!
--Whoa, Luffy! You're going too far!
--Damn it, Luffy!
And quit it with that face, will ya?!
Hey, old guy. Did you die?
C-Come again?! Are you trying
to ridicule me yet again?!
I remember those words very well...
Don't worry, Toto-ojisan.
Just one look at this kingdom
and even I can tell...
You will pay for this!
D-Don't be stupid...
I thought,
"Oh, this is how these pirates are..."
Vivi-chan...
Dammit! She's the one
person I can't deal with!
As if I could really die and
leave my adorable sons behind...
Tell what?!
We will stop the rebellion.
Wait!
Alone, there's a limit to your strength.
...what most needs to be done!
Scorpion-sama is invulnerable!
Sometimes, things you really want
to do are too much for one person.
Bastards! Get back here!
You need friends.
Thank you for coming to get
this lowly father of yours...
No!
Yuba, you see, can't be
beaten by some lousy sand!
But it amounts to nothing if those
friends don't do what they can.
Thank you!
Let's go home. To the Badlands!
As if putting your single life
on the line is enough!
It's definitely them!
Yeah!
Whoops! Sorry that wasn't an answer!
Then what should I be putting on the line?!
--Thank you!
--I can't keep my thoughts
straight in this heat!
W-We did it!
Way to go, Usopp!
Look! Up ahead!
The entrance to Raindinners!
Well, then...
That answered plenty.
I can't let him get away with this!
Are you really leaving, Ace?
It's in the middle of a lake!
Yes...
Yeah.
I don't have--!
Seeing as Blackbeard isn't in Alabasta,
I have no reason to be here.
That may be one of this country's forms.
Well, Vivi-chan. This is goodbye for a while.
Is no one here yet?!
I don't have anything else
that I can put on the line...
Come visit sometime,
once the city's taken shape!
Alright! Let's blast 'em!
Hey! Hurry up!
--Oh.
--Where will you go next?
Start with those two!
Of course he gets energetic
when it starts to cool off...
The enemy?!
Scorpion says there's a man
who saw him in the west.
Okay, Toto-ojisan!
At least try putting all of our
lives on the line together!
We're gonna make an awesome city
Zoro!
Wasn't Vivi with you?!
Guess I'll check it out.
and make this kingdom even lusher!
Aren't we friends?!
Luffy.
What is it?
Yeah! Is she not here yet?!
The wind has changed direction.
I smell something!
Always hang on to that.
She might've gone inside!
--What?!
--No doubt about it! It's Nami's perfume!
Aren't we friends?
Bye, Vivi! Grow up to be a great princess!
Let's hurry, then!
Huh? It's just a scrap of paper.
--It's this way!
--Way to go! Luffy!
That scrap of paper will bring you
and me together again sometime.
Yeah!
--Luffy!
--Get back here!
We found Nami and the others!
In the sunset direction!
Oh, you can cry those kinds of tears...
Plume-Plume is with him!
Yeah?
Hey! Let's go! Run inside, guys!
--You don't want it?
--No, I'll keep it.
For reals?!
It's natural for a big brother to
worry about his bungling kid brother.
Hey! Guys!
We're going in?
He might be a bit much for you to
handle, but take good care of 'im.
Don't rush off on your own!
We'll get separated again, you moron!
He's in there...
...isn't he?!
Huh?
We will stop the rebellion!
Koza!
Luffy. When we next meet,
we'll both be top pirates!
Oh? Vivi and the pirates
are here in town?
I've contacted everyone in the other towns.
I know you actually hate this
and want to beat him up the most!
Yeah!
Yes. We just received
word from the Millions.
Come to the top!
Hey!
This is it. The time to strike has come.
Yes. We don't have nearly
enough weapons, however.
When I'm with them,
I start to see many things...
But there's no other choice now.
Go welcome the foolish rats.
Huh? Where's Ace?
Now tell me...
Yes, sir.
These people may have the answer!
The only ones who can
protect this country...
Well, he's gone.
...where Crocodile is!
Listen, Crocodile!
I'm going to kick your ass!
Fire Fist Ace, huh?
...are us!
We'll see him again!
Yeah. I'm sure of it!
I'm coming for you!
Like the adventurers
I dreamed of when I was a child
I continue on to the ends of emotion
I scoop up my hands, and the sand
and time that spills from them
I scoop up my hands,
and the sand and time
that spills from them
show me that this is what
I was born to do
show me that this is
what I was born to do
Let's continue swimming
at a near-tumbling speed
Until we wash up someday
on a white sandy beach
no one knows about
Ace-san certainly was
a mysterious person.
Crocodile! Come out! I came
to Alubarna to kick your ass!
Did we make it to Yuba?!
I can't tell with all this sand!
I want to kick Crocodile's ass!
Eh?! The Navy's chasing them!
Yeah, I suppose he was!
So why are they running this way?!
He really knows how to get
straight to the point sometimes...
The city doesn't look right!
Say! Tony-kun hasn't come back yet!
Oh! You ladies prefer mysterious men?
That's not gonna make him
come out! You're so dumb!
--This is horrible!
--Wasn't this an oasis?!
Despite being himself.
Leave him! He'll manage!
Vivi! You want it so nobody dies in this fight!
We're up against the kingdom's hero!
I'm enigmatic, too!
My left eye, for example!
The sand has raised the ground!
The oasis has been swallowed up!
The Navy's here!
You're the one bringing them here!
Are you gonna make these
customers our enemies too?!
--Don't you think that's soft-hearted?
--Hold on, Luffy!
This isn't good!
Baroque Works is gonna spot us!
And there doesn't seem to be any water...
Hey, what did he say?
Translate, Chopper!
But without Vivi,
we don't know who Crocodile is!
The rebel army doesn't seem to be here!
At least put all our lives on the line together!
I think it's too late for that.
--Hey! They're gone!
--Don't tell me they got separated?!
Huh? Come to think of it, where is Vivi?
I will stop the revolt!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Battlefront of Alabasta!
Rainbase, the City of Dreams"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy vs. Vivi! The Tearful Vow
to Put Friends on the Line"
"Ruins and Lost Ways!
Vivi, Her Friends, and the Country's Form"
"Spiders Caf at 8 O'Clock--
The Enemy Leaders Gather"
"The Trap of Certain Defeat!
Storming Raindinners"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!