Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Luffy, Zoro, Law, Kid, and Killer challenge Kaido.
Battles between the top officers
of the Animal Kingdom Pirates and
Can you carry...
the Straw Hats erupt one after another!
...the Land of Wano on your back?!
General Franky and Sasaki
are in heavy hand-to-hand combat.
Ple...
You fool! Of course I will!
Purgatory...
...Onigiri!
Beheading Claws!
It's my friend's country!
It's not over yet!
Luffy! You gotta move or you'll die!
Kong Gun!
As you wish, I'll show you how strong I am!
Thunder Bagua!
Luffy-dono...
What? You're already worn out?!
Punk Vise!
Sasaki-sama!
This is it!
Thank you...
Takt!
Well done rampaging!
General...
Let's get it over with now!
Hold him down!
Damn! I predicted the attack...
That's what I expected from idiots
who aspire to be the King of the Pirates...
Happy Mother's Blaze!
Heavenly Fire!
Gum-Gum...
But...
Foxfire Style Flame-Rend!
...you can't stop me anymore!
Counter Shock!
Take him down along with us, Sasaki-sama!
...Red...
Let's launch further
attacks on Kaido, Killer!
Bring him down at any cost!
...Roc!
God of Lightning Tenjin!
Of course I will!
Kin'emon's technique!
That's amazing, Zoro!
The wind that blows heavenward...
I stole it!
Otama uses her wit to make
up for the overwhelming
Linlin, get back!
I wanna see how strong they are.
...destroys everything...
difference in power against
the Animal Kingdom Pirates.
Big Mom fought back
and the scales have turned against Luffy and the others.
Dragon Twister!
I'm Monkey D. Luffy.
Gifters! Keep going and block the way!
I'm the one who'll best you guys...
Killer!
Beheading Claws!
You guys are already vastly outnumbered!
Three-Sword Style!
...and become the King of the Pirates!
You have no chance to win
unless the tide turns all over the island!
Straw Hat!
Hey, Linlin!
Purgatory...
Why didn't you get hurt by lightning?!
...Onigiri!
This is fun!
"The Battle of the Monsters!
The Three Stubborn Captains!"
T...
To turn the tide, I came here!
I was just thinking the same!
Because I'm rubber!
Everyone, please!
The cut is too shallow!
Hey, Kaido... What are you doing?!
How dare you hurt Zoro and the others!
Help Franosuke-kun!
Kaido!
I can't believe you got knocked down!
Blast Breath!
Got it, Master-sama!
Kaido!
What?!
We'll finish you off in one go!
Nami and the others inside the castle
start fighting back, too.
I guess you want your head
to be crushed this time!
Fire doesn't work either?! Why?!
Not again!
Lightning alert!
"A Barrage of Powerful Techniques!
The Fierce Attacks of the Worst Generation!"
My guts!
Your heart might get
paralyzed, so be careful!
Gum-Gum...
His attack worked against me?!
"Otama's Secret Plan!
Operation Kibi Dango!"
Thunder Lance...
...Tempo!
...Kong...
Big Sis!
You still say that?! You shitty brat!
Listen up, you guys!
Whoa-whoa.
...Gatling!
The Straw Hats and the samurai
brazenly made a raid on us.
Pay attention.
The King of the Pirates?!
You're in a fight with...
But we still haven't brought them under yet!
Hey, stop resting!
Gear Four!
Are you messing with me?
SPEED - A HEADLINER OF THE BEAST PIRATES
WITH THE HORSE SMILE FRUIT
"Kaido Laughs!
The Emperors of the Sea vs. the New Generation!"
That was just some squirt's weak punch!
To break the deadlock,
Queen-sama entrusted me with something great.
...me, right?
So that's the Haki
that the old man from the Land of Wano taught him...
Franken-Sword...
What was that Haki?
Punches can hurt Kaido?!
V-for-Victory Flash!
You're as hot as always, Speed-sama!
Ryuo...
Ryuo?!
Where is the thing?
The Haki that he wears
destroys his opponents from the inside...
This is it.
What?
Bounce-Man!
From inside, huh? I like that.
Just a dumpling?
"Sanji's Scream!
An SOS Echoes Over the Island!"
That's not it!
Yeah okay, I know why you doubt it!
There is a chance of winning!
More importantly,
there's something I have to say to Straw Hat-ya.
But lo and behold.
Roller-san!
It'll dramatically enhance curative power,
Here we go!
Hey, you brat!
and improve muscle strength...
Rolling, rolling, rolling, yes!
Do you have any idea
how influential the King of the Pirates is?!
Roller-san!
Here we go!
...significantly!
--What?!
--Are you sure?!
Rolling, rolling, rolling!
But...
Roller-san!
...it looks really delicious...
Here we go!
Rolling, rolling, rolling!
Roller-san!
Let me eat that dumpling!
Here we go!
What happened to him
after he took a pounding from me in Kuri?
It's an advanced version of
a game that is played with geisha!
BRISCOLA
A HEADLINER OF THE ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
WITH THE GORILLA SMILE FRUIT
Seems like you got beaten
very badly, Briscola.
Exclusively for you!
Shut up!
I need to avenge myself against
those annoying, shitty Straw hats,
Oh, I like that look.
otherwise, I'm not gonna be satisfied!
Everyone, come!
Gum-Gum...
He's whining about not being rolled enough!
How cute!
I'll let you eat it then.
If you eat one, it'll change everything.
Roller-san!
...King Kong Gun!
Sudden death!
Here.
All right!
Thunder Bagua!
How is it, Briscola-san?
Punk Rotten!
Oh no! This is...
Feels like it's working...
...too much!
Or maybe not...
No way.
You fool...
Oh, my dear boy.
You're not trying to say this dumpling
that Queen-sama made...
Are you tired?
Do you wanna go night-night?
Room!
That's enough...
...is a failure, are you?
Takt!
I'm satisfied...
Let me go!
What?! You've already gotten bored?!
Gulp!
Boing!
Then, let's play something more...
This little punk didn't even catch my attention...
Boing! Boing! Boing!
Wee!
...intense!
...at that time!
It's amazing!
I feel a surge of power!
Damn...
That's too intense...
I only know a few people...
That's awesome!
I want one too, Briscola-sama!
W-What the hell is this?!
...who are capable of fighting me.
Speed-sama! May I have that dumpling, too?!
This isn't my kind of game...
No more games...
I want one!
Two for us!
Be a good boy.
Are you suggesting you're as good as those guys?
Of course!
Black-Leg Sanji.
I have enough for all Gifters!
Gee...
Yay!
Straw Hat!
You're acting up. How cute.
They're like monsters!
You're strong but it's a shame.
It's good!
Bring it on! Let me see if you guys
are strong enough to become...
Are you suggesting you're capable of
fighting a deadly battle against me?
You beat the hell out of the men,
Once you finish eating, get ready to fight!
Don't waste your time!
but you can't even lay a finger on women.
...the King of the Pirates!
The Straw Hats won't wait for us!
You're still a fledging punk!
So you have no chance of winning.
Your life is in the palm of my hand now...
Gum-Gum...
You think you're that great?!
Now, call for...
A FEW HOURS EARLIER
Straw Hat!
...Nico Robin!
He did it?!
...Kong Gun!
This is Caiman Lady.
Master-sama.
Look at that relaxed smile...
Horselina-chan...
Let's go to hell together!
If you speak loudly to her,
You were gone for a while,
so I came to see if you're okay...
you'll be heard all over the castle.
Then I'll set you free.
Is something wrong?
It's Kaido-san's order.
What are you gonna do to Robin-chan?
Everyone's left for Onigashima.
Let's see...
Ow...
We'll gang up to catch her...
I know it's a dangerous place.
That hurts!
...and paralyze her
by grievously wounding her limbs.
I feel a tingling sensation on my skin!
I'm well aware of your thick skin!
No one allowed me to go with them...
But until the end of our little errand
which could take years to complete,
Kaido!
But I bet you can be crushed to death!
Kill them all!
Everyone and everything will be destroyed!
she won't get killed, so don't worry.
But...
Horselina-chan!
As you wish, I'll show you how strong I am!
I wanna go to Onigashima, too!
Damn you... Don't underestimate Nico Robin!
Punk Vise!
WIND
The Akazaya samurai got away from the rooftop
and went somewhere, it seems!
I don't wanna just wait like this
while they're fighting for their lives...
Hey, brat!
So...
Thunder Bagua!
Tra-guy! Move all of them downstairs!
Neigh! Leave it to me, Master-sama!
I'll get you a ship immediately!
They must not have gotten
that far yet, I think!
That's not bad, but it needs more mass.
Damn! I predicted the attack, but it was...
Find them!
...too fast!
This will finish you, Kaido!
Well done! You didn't take it directly this time!
Take care! Speed-sama!
Then I'm gonna add some.
What the?!
You suck, Kaido!
Catch all samurai who go against Kaido-sama
in one fell swoop!
Takt!
Trash should be burned!
Damn!
Prometheus!
Let me try and see if you're truly immortal!
Yes, Mama!
Get burned to dust!
GAZELLE-MAN - A GIFTER FROM BAKURA TOWN
WITH THE GAZELLE SMILE FRUIT
Heavenly Fire!
We managed to set sail!
That's what I'd expect from a man
who calls himself King-yoi.
You bastard!
You were gonna kill me too, weren't you?!
Of course!
Foxfire Style Flame-Rend!
DAIFUGO - A HEADLINER
VICE WARDEN OF UDON'S EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP
Because they don't know
that we ate Master-sama's Kibi Dango.
I followed up your half-assed attack
with a stronger one of my own.
What did you say?!
You can come out now, Master-sama.
Prometheus!
Jaggy! Tra-guy!
You guys are so cool!
Kin'emon's technique!
That's amazing, Zoro!
Sulongs!
Jeez, guys...
Oh, no!
Are you really okay without Marco?
Don't fight here now!
You guys are helpless.
Thank you all!
I stole it!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Lick!
No problem.
We're gonna take you down at any cost!
--Don't tell me what to do!
--I won't follow your orders!
Straw Hat?! When did you get hit?!
You hurt me!
But...
...even if we join the samurai and fight,
Don't lower your guard even a bit, Luffy!
I could've taken care of them
all by myself without you losers.
I like your high spirits.
He didn't get hit!
It's a by-product of that iron-ball-like technique!
the Animal Kingdom Pirates on Onigashima
have so many more soldiers than us.
There are two Emperors of the Sea!
But you'll be licked.
My attack harmed him the most!
He can't use Haki for 10 minutes or so!
Straw Hat's punches were so weak!
You losers better stand back!
If we clash head-on...
I see. Power with a risk.
Is this his ability?
What did you say, Jaggy?!
But if all of those attacks worked on him,
Whoa-whoa...
--The smaller the dog, the louder the bark!
--The same goes for you!
How annoying!
Wanda! This candy is dangerous!
it's our chance to finish him off!
We don't even have a
slight chance of winning.
Carrot!
That's enough for now, Kid.
That's right!
That candy will instantly
coat your whole body...
I have an idea!
Don't push your luck!
Don't lower your guard, Luffy.
Don't tell me...
Kibi Dango!
Okay!
Please stop... That's enough!
For each dumpling, we can make one new ally!
Tsk! But it's not settled...
...and seep into your system.
Women...
You can't breathe anymore, can you?
I'll make tons of these before we reach Onigashima
so we can let everyone eat them!
Women!
I know that it wasn't enough to kill him...
Luffy! You gotta move or you'll die!
Don't get fooled!
And when it's solidified...
Th-This is...
...a sweet corpse...
I love the idea, Master-sama!
...unmistakably...
...Candyman is complete!
What? You're already worn out?!
...heaven!
BANQUET HALL, THIRD FLOOR, INSIDE THE CASTLE
Well done rampaging!
Lick, lick!
Oh, that hurts!
I'll lick you up later!
Let's get it over with now!
Kibi Dango...
You don't need to go anywhere, do you?
It kills me!
Lick!
Kibi Dango!
Happy Mother's...
Cut it out!
Anyway, how could you cut my lovely face
over some crappy grudge.
I haven't felt such pain...
...Blaze!
Do you think I have time to stay here?
Kibi Dango!
Hand over Straw Hat to me!
I do!
You Minks are such a pain in the ass!
I'll stay here forever!
Bombs?!
...since those days!
No! This isn't the time for this!
Counter Shock!
Kibi Dan...
Let go of me!
I gotta go!
Goodbye.
Master-sama, I think you better stop now...
Untie me!
Yum-yum! I'm fully charged!
You may say so,
Luffy! Wake up!
I'm okay...
but you kind of like writhing too, don't you?
That Jaguar Mink who took
my right arm away...
Don't push yourself!
You'll fall sick before we get to Onigashima!
...really died for nothing after all!
What's the point of being in a hurry anymore?
Not bad, you little shits...
I have to make more dumplings...
Poor him...
Let's launch further attacks on Kaido, Killer!
Stay here forever.
That's what I expected from idiots
who aspire to be the King of the Pirates...
I can't bring down Kaido myself...
I won't go anywhere.
Okay!
I gotta get out of here now...
This is all I can do to help...
But...
...or not!
...you can't stop me anymore!
I'm gonna stay!
Momo-kun...
No! What am I saying?!
...will become a wonderful Shogun.
I have things to do!
But you actually wanna stay here forever, right?
Big Bro Luffy...
Let's have some fun.
...said he'd make the Land of Wano
a country where we can eat as much as we want!
There's no point
in going through all that trouble to get there now...
It's so sad...
Wanda!
I know you guys won't
last long either anyway.
And the samurai...
right?
Screw you!
...are all fighting for this country...
What?! No way!
I really need to get there...
...or not!
So...
I thought so.
...I'll do what I can to help!
Then why don't you stay here for a while
and answer my question...
Don't insult Pedro!
Once you guys die, I'll take everything!
The Land of Wano free of Orochi and Kaido,
that's ruled by Momo-kun!
He sacrificed his life
for the world to see the dawn!
That's what I want!
Which includes your crewmembers
who are here on this island!
Stop it!
Don't come any closer!
Killer! Watch out!
He made all this possible!
On top of that, I don't
wanna be hungry anymore...
I'm gonna go...
I won't let you do that!
Eleclaw!
...crazy!
I wanna eat...
Tell me...
Not just your crewmembers.
We'll take your treasure too!
...where are...
Okay.
Let's fight!
...your fellow crewmembers?
Yeah, let's do it!
The Ponegliffs.
I see...
Let's have a meal first,
then hide and wait for a chance!
I'm sure you guys have them with you.
Can't wait!
You softened the candy
with the heat of your electric attack...
--Okay!
--All right!
The wind that blows heavenward...
I wish I could stay in heaven!
I'll take your crewmembers
and treasure instead!
Sulong...
...destroys everything...
You Minks are really annoying...
And the time...
Farewell, my ladies!
Dragon Twister!
...has finally come!
Lick!
I shall return!
Whoever wins this battle
will be one big step closer...
I'm a swift runner!
I run at 200 kilometers per hour!
Killer!
Ready...
...to becoming the King of the Pirates!
Very funny.
But...
Start!
No! Don't run away!
...that power needs the full moon.
I'm the one who'll become...
Eat this!
...the King of the Pirates!
The moon...
Please, lady, don't stop me!
You've got to be kidding!
You better pay attention!
What?! It's good!
This is practically a natural disaster!
Candy Maiden!
Eat this!
Delicious!
Hey, you... Wait!
--Eat this!
--Delicious!
Zoro, thanks...
--Eat this!
--Delicious!
You little cheapskate!
Yeah.
Come on, eat it, Gifters!
Nice try!
A bunch of ladies,
I'm lucky but cornered!
Wanda!
Look! He's the vice warden
from Udon, Daifugo!
Focus, Carrot!
Take him down!
You have tormented us so much!
Sorry, my ladies!
Sorry about that! Forget it for now!
Wanda!
Until the next time,
Luffy!
see you again!
Whooacchoo!
Luffy!
Wee!
Oh, Daifugo-sama!
Thank you for your hard work!
I-I'm so...
Cut the boring greeting for now!
...thrilled now!
Eat this!
Demolition Gust!
I found them! I found them!
Eat this!
DEMOLITION GUST
The famous
"Whaddya say? That's naughty" bit!
I found the Akazaya samurai!
Wee!
Eat this! Become Master-sama's servant!
I get to... I get to...
Luffy!
I get to...
W-What the...
Whaddya say?!
They got away from the battle on the rooftop,
it seems!
That's naughty!
Whaddya say?!
Victory! That is our name!
Covered in blood!
That's naughty!
Damn samurai! Show yourselves!
But they're still alive, it seems!
Kid!
Getting cut by my sword
or trodden down by my giraffe feet!
I-I-I love it!
It was only made of metal scraps anyway!
No!
Go ahead and choose!
They're located at the
back of the castle tower!
Sexual harassment is never allowed!
The second floor of the Treasure Repository
at the second bailey!
Should we make him our ally, too?
Kaido!
Luffy!
Of course! The more troops the better!
They must've escaped from Kaido-san.
No matter how good a man you pretend to be,
I'm busy now.
Can someone else handle it?
Mm-hm!
Here we go! Special Attack!
You stupid King-of-the-Pirates pretenders!
you're one of those guys who abandon their women...
Millet Dumpling Star!
Whoa-whoa!
Go to the Treasure Repository right away
and kill all the samurai!
You bastard! Don't chomp on our captain!
Entertain me!
--Alright!
--You see that?!
...to chase their dreams.
Did you hear that, Black Maria-sama?
The samurai crumbled miserably!
I kind of feel itchy...
Do as you like...
Yes, King...
Loyalty to Oden alone...
...and use violence to dominate women.
A girl... Why are you here?!
I'll go.
...won't open the way to the future!
The second floor of the Treasure Repository
is connected to this floor.
Shake hands!
If you wanna leave, it's easy.
Master-sama...
She is the one I worship!
I should just finish the
Akazaya members, right?
Go ahead...
Yeah, thanks!
I will reign over the Land of Wano!
That's a foot!
...and kick me.
Kin'emon... They got beaten?!
But it went well!
With that leg that you're proud of
which is burning with a sense of justice.
Keep feeding them like this!
Wait! Don't go!
But be careful!
There are ten people in that...
Okay! Leave it to me!
Can you carry...
You realize it yourself, don't you?
...room!
It's dark so I can't see clearly,
You're actually having fun
when you kick someone, right?
...the Land of Wano on your back?!
but someone is trying to help the samurai!
Everybody, I'm counting on you!
Hurry up and kill them!
I...
Someone's...
...there!
I...
Hey, Apoo!
What's taking you so long?!
Take back the antibody already!
I see!
I...
That sword is where I sense the strange Haki!
Gum-Gum...
...would rather die than kick a woman!
...Kong...
KONG
I know!
...Rifle!
I like you, boy.
We'll back you up.
Very cute.
The situation remains the same,
we have a definite advantage.
How can you survive being so naive?
We can overwhelm them with numbers
in no time.
Alright! All we need to do now
is make a lot of them!
I guess you have wonderful friends.
Oniwabanshu and Mimawari-gumi, huh?
Three-Sword Style!
Wake up, Mr. Emperor of the Sea!
Black Rope Dragon Twister!
Okay! Let's make a fresh start, guys!
Let them know we're out of their league!
B-Boss!
I want you to tell me...
Guys! Don't touch me!
Here we go!
...about your wonderful friends.
Especially where the woman named Nico Robin is now.
Raccoon-san, how is it?!
SLAM
Stop them here at any cost!
It'll be ready soon!
Slam Gibson!
I refuse!
Do you think we can beat that many enemies?
Damn...
He cut his scales!
We have no choice!
I can't believe I'm dying here!
You didn't even hesitate.
There's no reason for me to hesitate.
I'm sorry, straw hat man!
I wanted to help you,
but I gave you trouble instead!
That makes me jealous.
That punk! He cut Kaido!
Tsk!
Room!
One after another!
No... Not yet!
Chambres!
I haven't paid back my debt
to Luffytaro-san and the others!
I'll ask...
If I'm gonna die anyway,
...your body about Nico Robin!
I've never seen
a diagram of a dragon's organs before...
Oh, that hurts!
I'll at least stop the enemies for them!
I see...
I don't like this!
Just as I thought, that sword...
Leave the front line to me.
Die, old man!
...but I guess your heart is around here!
How dependable.
Oden Two-Sword Style!
Don't lower your guard even a bit, Luffy!
Gamma Knife!
Reliable help has arrived!
Just a little more patience!
There are two Emperors of the Sea!
...is Oden's sword, isn't it?!
Chambres!
I'm gonna destroy you from the inside!
He competes against me using Dragon Twister...
What's wrong?
Boss Hyogoro...
He doesn't know his place!
Your body!
How annoying!
Oh yeah, he said...
...once our physical stamina runs out,
BANQUET HALL, THIRD FLOOR, INSIDE THE CASTLE
Okay, I must go and kill the samurai...
the effect of the flame will be gone...
Hey, Straw Hat-ya.
Tra-guy! You saved me! Thanks!
But before that,
I have to finish the job at hand quickly.
So you've learned how strong my body is!
Listen! We formed an alliance!
I guess you guys are not
just some ballsy idiots!
Hey! Luffy!
Allies must stand as equals!
Caiman Lady, are you ready
to broadcast his voice all over the island?
Oh, Zoro?
What are you talking about?!
This hard skin has been
a big pain in the ass!
So there's something I wanna say to you!
Yes, I am!
Black-Leg...
I...
I should just cut into the body, right?!
Could you call Nico Robin here now?
Look out for the big attack!
...was gonna move them downstairs anyway!
Boss Hyogoro!
We're all ready to go...
But you...
Scyther...
Dragon Twister...
SCYTHER SONIC
Tra-guy! Move all of them downstairs!
...Demolition Gust!
Around the entrance, multiple
layers of the sticky Hard Gum
...Sonic!
that never comes off once it sticks on you...
It was like...
...are all set up.
...I followed your order!
It's on the floor too,
so you'll get stuck once you step on it.
Why do you care about such a thing?!
I'm happy for you, Straw Hat!
It hurt you a little, didn't it?!
And my subordinates with tranquilizer guns
are waiting ahead.
You got yourself another subordinate!
Kaido!
General Left!
Indra!
A subordinate?! Who?!
All there is left to do...
Trafalgar...
I thought you finally became
Straw Hat's subordinate...
Killer!
N-No way!
...is for you to just call for her!
I don't care
if a loser subordinates another loser...
As long as you're under this sky,
Nico Robin!
there is no escape for you guys!
Shut up, loser!
Who did you call "loser"?!
You're the only loser here!
It's not over yet!
Come on, call for help!
They're more entertaining than I expected!
It can't be me!
Gee...
I have another task to do!
It's you! You! You!
They're such good friends.
Sasaki-sama!
Rhino Schneider!
Robin-chan...
You were freaking out before,
you damn silly monkey!
You were just watching in the back,
Jaggy, you jerk!
Let me... join your crew.
What?!
This is it!
I'm not a loser!
I...
General...
We never imagined our supplier would die,
Stop chewing the fat!
I...
Not bad!
and the banquet that we were invited to...
Hold him down!
I want to live!
...would turn into a battlefield.
Burn them all up, Prometheus!
Take me to the sea with you!
Yes, Mama!
CIPHER POL "AIGIS" ZERO
WORLD'S MOST POWERFUL INTELLIGENCE AGENCY
Heavenly Bon-Bons!
Tra-guy!
I...
Hey, come on!
Don't get in my way, you fools!
Move me up!
I heard it's a battle to win vengeance
for one who died 20 years ago in this country.
Okay, here's the deal!
Now you're telling what to do...
Even with your tremendous power,
you can't shake off this many of us!
The one who dodges her attack first loses!
I'm not your servant!
Orobi-chan! How does it taste?
We're the Gifters,
we were given special abilities!
Yeah...
No way, you idiot!
But when Doflamingo fell from power,
You always think of dumb games like that!
Foxfire Style...
Well, it tastes amazing!
We're no ordinary soldiers!
the clash between Kaido and the Worst Generation
became inevitable.
That's why you guys can't become big shots!
Orobi-chan the geisha is more amazing!
They're so strong!
All right! Then you guys are losers!
Blast Breath!
You're stubborn...
You don't have to be so patient...
King Kong...
God Thread!
Suit yourselves!
...Gun!
Take him down along with us, Sasaki-sama!
I'm not playing!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Why don't you run, you chickenshit?!
Flame-Rend!
Bring him down at any cost!
Oh, I can't watch...
It makes me cry...
Just dodge, you wimp!
Of course I will!
I think that man is trying to
protect his crewmate...
Hey, watch out!
Zoro!
He'll die without saying a word!
Franky!
One more time!
If he wasn't our enemy,
I would've fallen in love!
That must be...
Tra-guy!
Usopp! Nami! And Otama!
Why are you here?!
W-Wait!
I said stop using me as a tool!
It was fate...
This is not the time to ask that!
...that brought the samurai
and the pirates together.
Thank goodness!
Can you guys do something about...
Give me a chance to at least say a few words!
What are you guys doing?!
At the time when the world's situation
is about to turn over...
What the?!
Now who's gonna become the King of the Pirates?!
I bet he just wants to say something
like "Screw you" before he dies!
Dodge, Kaido!
If by any chance both of those Emperors of the Sea
get taken down...
That's not an ordinary sword!
Help!
Let's see...
One-Sword Style!
Stop! If you make her any angrier...
How am I gonna kill you?
They're being chased by tons of enemies?!
Robin-chan...
Linlin, get back!
I wanna see how strong they are.
No one can tell what will happen in the world.
I was already in trouble,
but now I'm in even bigger trouble!
I... I...
I...
Gifters! Keep going and block the way!
...wanted to see your smile again...
Why would you wanna see that?
But there's no worry of that.
Flying Dragon Blaze!
You guys are already vastly outnumbered!
Damn! You guys moved, didn't you?!
You have no chance of winning
unless the tide turns all over the island!
I didn't move!
Help me, Robin-chan!
What am I supposed to do?!
No, I saw both of you moving!
The number of enemies that invaded the island...
Don't get in my way, Hitokiri Kamazo!
T...
Why do I feel...
...is 5,400
To turn the tide, I came here!
What?!
...Oden's presence in his sword?!
He was actually ready to call for help!
There aren't that many people
who have such a weird laugh.
But 400 of them have fallen
Damn! I missed it!
I'm on the third floor!
Everyone, please!
On the other hand
The Banquet Hall!
Help Franosuke-kun!
I've been taken hostage! I'm sorry!
we Animal Kingdom Pirates...
You underestimated us too much.
Sanji.
Indra!
...have more than 30,000 troops
If Robin-chan doesn't come, they'll kill me!
Got it, Master-sama!
Onigiri!
But 3,000 of them have already fallen
What?!
Help!
Zoro!
The samurai did a good job.
What's that?! How pathetic!
Is that a member of the Straw Hats?!
You've got no place to run!
The difference in power means they can't even
reach the leader if they attacked head-on.
All right!
If I had these Punishers on at that time,
you would've died!
Whoa-whoa, it's echoing all over the island!
God of Lightning Tenjin!
Zorojuro...
The operation to launch a successful sneak attack
was brilliant.
Whew! That was close!
I don't think so.
Nico Robin is one of
the most important figures in the world.
But this battle won't end
even if they chop off the leader's head.
That went well!
I knew they would want her knowledge!
Damn! A "natural disaster," huh?!
What are you guys thinking?!
It's obviously a trap to capture Robin!
Sasaki!
Page One! Ulti!
A man shouldn't sound miserable like that!
(27,000) / (5,000)
They changed sides! Smack them down!
This is an all-out war, there's no refuge on the island.
Changed sides?!
If they leave Kaido's powerful top officers at large,
What do they gain by
siding with the samurai?!
those officers will take down 100 soldiers at a time.
They're so funny-yoi!
It's probably their ability!
The enemy is most likely a woman.
Isn't that right?!
Gee.
I guess you want your head
to be crushed this time!
Hey, Nami! That's where it's coming from!
Not again!
Beheading Claws!
Lightning alert!
Be careful!
If the Worst Generation can't stop the top officers...
Three-Sword Style!
--I saw one earlier! What is that eye?!
--You're my only hope!
Your heart might get
paralyzed, so be careful!
Purgatory...
Come quickly!
...Onigiri!
Thunder Lance...
Robin-chan!
...Tempo!
Straw Hat!
This game of Go will end
with all black pieces on the board.
Why didn't you get hurt by the lightning?!
Big Sis!
Damn! That hurts! Tsk!
It's a little too obvious which side will win...
Because I'm rubber!
She did it! That damn bitch!
I can't believe it.
I knew I couldn't take her down...
It should be more powerful lightning!
How dare you hurt Zoro and the others!
Crush as many of each other as you can...
I called for Robin-chan, so untie me now.
You pirates.
She used some weird trick!
Blast Breath!
The cut is too shallow!
Guys! Take them down!
They'll become a nuisance if we leave them be.
What?!
Aye-aye, Sasaki-sama!
Ma'am, someone's coming!
I won't let you! Special Attack!
That's very quick!
Millet Dumpling Star! Millet Dumpling Star!
Millet Dumpling Star!
I'm impressed with you!
I won't release you.
I gotta unleash Enma's power a little more!
Millet Dumpling Star!
You said you loved me.
What was that?
Kaido!
Everybody!
It's not business, it's personal from now on.
Follow me!
We'll finish you off in one go!
I wanna keep you as a pet like them.
Aye-aye, Master-sama!
What did you say?
Say that again.
I'll make your body unable
to live without me.
Fire doesn't work either?! Why?!
Gear Four!
What?! Hey! What's going on?!
I only love Black Maria-sama...
I've never seen him in that form!
Wait, Armored Division!
Whoa-whoa.
My guts!
Pay attention.
I wanna love all the ladies!
Gum-Gum...
You're in a fight with...
I forbid you to be unfaithful like that!
Punk Rotten!
Is that his Man-Beast Form?
I'll discipline you!
Wait! I don't wanna hurt any lady,
...Kong...
Hey, Linlin!
Room!
...me, right?
so my Color of Arms has been softened!
This is fun!
...Gatling!
Mil Fleurs!
Franken-Sword...
I was just thinking the same!
Gigantesco Mano!
They're...
Spank!
...like monsters!
V-for-Victory Flash!
Kaido!
Robin-chan!
A girl who wishes a better future for the Land of Wano.
Sanji writhes in pain from Black
Maria’s full-course torture!
The game-changing Kong Gatling blasts!
Black Maria plots to mesmerize
the bruised Sanji,
The great battle over the title of King of the Pirates!
Otama, who runs through the tumultuous Onigashima,
executes her plan with determination!
but Robin and Brook step
in to teach her a lesson.
Against the Emperors of the Sea who stand in their way,
the rookies use a triune technique!
Luffy's highly-trained
punches push Kaido hard!
There is only one condition that will set him free!
The Tobi Roppo member
becomes infuriated seeing
Turning over the most important
member of the Straw Hats!
The hand-to-hand combat becomes more intense!
Defeat Kaido! To take down his formidable enemy
and fulfill his dream of becoming the King of the Pirates,
To save her friends who are fighting unsupported,
the bond between the
members of the Straw Hats
Will he be able to take
him down in the momentum?!
will she be able to give them a chance to recover
and turn the one-sided battle against Kaido's army?!
The merciless evil lady forces
him to make a tough choice!
and the new battle with their pride on the line
erupts with the flames of anger!
He devotes his full strength to beat Kaido!
Luffy's all-out punch lets loose!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Spank Strikes! Sanji's Woman-trouble!"
"Otama's Secret Plan! Operation Kibi Dango!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sanji's Scream! An SOS Echoes Over the Island!"
On the next episode of One Piece! "A Barrage of Powerful
Techniques! The Fierce Attacks of the Worst Generation!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Kaido Laughs! The Emperors of
the Sea vs. the New Generation!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates![Events]
[Events]