Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Eluding the Marys' surveillance network,
The battle between Luffy's group, Kaido, and Big Mom
is getting intense.
The fierce battle continues on Onigashima!
Surprisingly, Oden appeared
in front of Kin'emon and the others.
The stalemate of the battle gradually ends.
Yamato and Shinobu defend Momonosuke for their lives.
Hyogoro, who is suffering from the Ice Oni virus
uses all his remaining strength.
This mature woman will go at it, too!
God of Lightning Tenjin!
How dare you hit my face...
Old fart!
You thought you could catch me easily
if you just lured me?
Luffy and the others' battle
against Kaido and Big Mom continues!
Prepare yourself!
Momonosuke's group doesn't know
about Oden's comeback yet.
How dare you hurt Zoro and the others!
When those two are side by side,
this place looks like...
Robin-chan!
Shinobu-san, this way!
Lead us to an out-of-sight path already!
Nice try, full-moon warriors!
Blast Breath!
Don't worry!
If we beat them all up, we'll be out of their sights!
...nothing but hell...
Meanwhile, Chopper is hurrying
to stop the infection...
Again, that's not what I meant!
So what?
Candy Maiden!
We're ready!
Hell doesn't bother me!
You guys need luck in weather to win!
Thank you...
Caution, we're too heated up!
All there is left to do
is clear the final problem.
"Oden Appears!
The Confused Hearts of the Akazaya Members!"
Kaido, finally in his extreme form,
stands in the way of Luffy and the others.
Wanda!
It's this cure's reliability.
Focus, Carrot!
I've been to hell many times...
RIGHT-BRAIN TOWER, INSIDE THE DOME
Zoro...
So...
...I'll try it myself!
--I need one minute.
--Yeah, leave it to me.
Your eyes always look vigorous!
Wanda!
Don't let that weird virus get the best of you!
There is a big space
between each floor of the castle!
W-Wait!
Let's see the Land of Wano's dawn together!
"No Regrets!
Luffy and Boss, a Master-Disciple Bond!"
Straw Hat!
No one'll see us there!
Okay!
We have the upper hand!
Momonosuke-sama! Just a little more patience!
Meanwhile, Kin'emon and his gang
reunited with Oden, however...
This...
Momonosuke-kun, are you okay?
Yeah...
Give me a chance to at least say a few words!
I bet he just wants to say something
like "Screw you" before he dies!
It's like the heavens have given me
a reward at the end...
Look! He's not even bleeding!
I am not okay...
I was imprisoned and only waiting to die,
but now I've made it this far...
Stop! If you make her any angrier...
I found them! I found them!
Damn, it's almost done...
Ashura!
I repeat!
But if I go on, I'll only risk your lives!
I wanted to see your smile again...
Young Master Yamato and the kunoichi...
Now it's clear that he's an imposter...
...are still on the run...
I'm sorry I assigned you in a tough role...
But do it for me!
Dr. Chopper?
...along with Momonosuke!
Help me, Robin-chan!
We all feel the same...
Dr. Chopper!
I wished he were the real one...
I'll leave the rest to you guys...
But he's an imposter!
I'm gonna fight it!
"Spank Strikes!
Sanji's Woman-trouble!"
I'll make a path for Momonosuke-kun!
So it's you!
Kanjuro!
As a doctor,
I'll make your body unable
to live without me.
I can't succumb to such an annoying virus!
Dr. Chopper!
Don't be silly! I'm Oden!
I wanna love all the ladies!
This mature woman will go at it, too!
I'm sorry, everyone! Hold out a little longer!
Don't tell me it's unsuccessful!
I forbid you to be unfaithful like that!
How's my drawing of Oden?!
That looks exactly like him, right?
You're strong, Shinobu-san!
I'll discipline you!
Wait! I don't wanna hurt any lady,
You, too!
Damn you! Kanjuro!
I'm glad you're here.
With you, I can defend Momonosuke-sama to the end!
so my Color of Arms has been softened!
I can't...
Mil Fleurs!
Hey, Denjiro!
I'm your lord, how could you defy me?!
Gigantesco Mano!
Spank!
Dr. Chopper!
You bastard!
How much more are you gonna taunt us?
This blue flame has to
draw out my physical stamina,
but my stamina itself is...
Black Maria-sama!
It's...
"The Worst Generation Gets Wiped Out?!
The Emperors' Deadly Attack!"
...running out...
Double Kunai Slash!
Yay! It's successful!
Fight it! Or you'll turn into an Ice Oni again!
We did it!
That was easy.
Shinobu-san, behind you!
I knew you would do it!
You'll run wild until your energy runs out
and you'll die this time!
We need a lot!
Everyone's waiting!
He's going after... Momonosuke-sama...
--Let's get on it!
--Okay!
Don't give up, young man!
Thank you! You saved me!
Get a hold of yourself!
I can't believe he used
a fake Oden-sama to keep us here...
If I was a little younger,
I would've fallen for you!
"All Set!
Chopperphage Nebulizer!"
How did you get in here?!
Raccoon-san is enduring the same pain as you
but is working hard to make antidotes!
It's unforgivable!
Momonosuke-sama, please put your mind at ease.
Yamato and I took care of all the enemies.
Kanjuro!
I can sprout anywhere.
We can't give up before he does!
B-Big Boss... Your appearance...
How dare you hit my face...
I'll wipe out the Kozuki Clan.
You thought you could catch me easily
if you just lured me?
I am not okay, I feel bad.
You don't look well.
We've got to go save him now!
I cannot do anything
except rely on others for protection...
Leave it to this old man!
Marco!
Robin-chan!
Oh, I think I heard this voice
from somewhere earlier...
I hate myself.
...saying Momonosuke-sama is with a kunoichi...
What are you saying?!
Is it about time to end this?
It's time to show them...
It's natural for us retainers to be your sword and shield
and defend you!
...a samurai's resilience!
That must be Shinobu!
Then we can get a connection!
I was part of an evil organization
for a long time.
It's not cool to chase a man who is dying.
Everyone is overrating me!
I won't let you get away!
Apoo-san, we can't fight anymore!
I... I...
The antibody is just past them,
but we can't break through their iron-tight defense!
What's so funny?!
Why should we suffer from Queen-sama's virus
even though we're on his side?!
If you mess with my friends,
I can't...
I am frivolous, stupid...
Bluebird!
...stop myself...
He's not gonna save you even if you whine!
...weak, foolish, and I am sick of myself...
The Akazaya members will meet their end here,
unable to do anything!
...from showing my devilish side!
Don't try to act tough, bird brain!
Just kill that raccoon and take back the antibody!
Momonosuke-sama, you're great!
I am not great at all!
Along with me...
Damn!
Even if you're small now,
Drake! That traitor!
I know you'll be big
and become a great Shogun one day!
Oh, excuse me! I cut you up
gathering the chill of the underworld!
Stop acting like a hero!
What?!
Let go of me!
Let's go out with a sensational bang!
Prepare yourself!
I'm gonna torment you to my heart's content!
Drake isn't the only obstacle!
You'll be a greater man
than Kozuki Oden ever was!
Brook!
The withered old man somehow recovered!
Ma'am, the tranquilizer gun unit
has been taken down!
I am not... I am not...
You guys!
Have fun, you idiots.
The Land of Wano's legendary great underground boss!
--The spider thread traps...
--...are all frozen and broken, too!
We're friends, right?
HYOGORO THE FLOWER
LEGENDARY GREAT UNDERGROUND BOSS
I am not great at all!
Hyogoro the Flower!
I'm gonna turn all the idiots and scum...
X. DRAKE - A FORMER TOBI ROPPO MEMBER
It seems like the spider thread
and the chill of the underworld go well together!
What?! An eel?!
...into Ice oni.
They've got those two monstrous gate guards...
Momonosuke-sama!
We can't approach the raccoon at all!
Why do you look like that?
This is what he becomes
when he gets excited.
Ghosts!
Why does he look like that?!
What?! I can't believe this!
Look who's talking!
He was just a little old man moments ago!
Oniwabanshu...
What? Could it be because you ate a Devil Fruit?
Thank you! You saved me...
He's back to the strong man he was
when Kaido was relentlessly recruiting him!
...and Mimawari-gumi...
Most of them are beaten!
No problem.
Yes, I did...
I'm sorry, but I'm gonna go help
Kin'emon and the others!
No... No way...
I'm shaking with excitement!
Daikoku-san!
Big Boss! Are you okay?!
Kazekage-sama!
I don't know why,
but I see no chance of winning here!
Captain Hotei!
Yeah...
It's quite cold...
No wonder.
Wait, Black-Leg! You'll be my pet!
But...
This is what the legendary yakuza is capable of?!
Ashura!
...I'm confident about my mental capability!
I won't let you go!
Get away from here, guys!
He resisted turning into an Ice Oni
but took advantage of its power!
Is that it?
Since I touched the virus by accident,
I now understand a little why the Land of Wano...
Go stop Kanjuro!
it's drawn out all the strength I've got
to the very last inch of my life!
That's your last words?
...has been so feared...
What are you doing?!
Get off of me!
Save Momonosuke-sama for me!
When it comes to this...
I'm sorry, Ashura!
You wanna die for that bastard
who sells out his friend?
You bastard! How could you get in my way?!
No, Black Maria...
Oden-sama...
You don't understand.
Momonosuke-kun!
Boss Hyogoro!
You look like...
Now, a Daimyo needs vassals.
Boss!
...my father!
Friends are wonderful.
Rather than being assigned with
some wise and sober men,
Sanji!
I want you guys.
Looks like Kaido's busy...
Thank you for relying on me!
Be my samurai!
It made me happy!
Boss!
Speaking of Kaido...
Oh, it's frozen there.
What are you waiting for, Yatappe?!
Oden-sama!
when the Navy caught him once...
With this last power...
Empty your mind!
there was a man-made Devil Fruit
which Vegapunk created...
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
Damn you! Get off of me!
Boss!
Thank you!
If I turn into an Ice Oni...
...by extracting Kaido's Bloodline Elements.
...in exchange for my life,
Don't sully Kozuki Oden anymore!
I will slice up...
The Government asked him to hand it over to them,
but since he viewed it as a disappointing failure,
I know! Just give me a second!
...all their key figures!
PERFORMANCE FLOOR, INSIDE THE DOME
Attention!
I'm gonna do it soon! I'm gonna do it now!
it was kept at Punk Hazard for a long time.
Momonosuke is in the Forbidden Storehouse!
Hey, you bosses!
Boss Hyogoro!
Yes, Big Boss!
Why are you bringing that up now?
Punk Hazard was detonated.
Someone's watching.
Of course it's hard...
What?!
That should be gone forever....
I may not have much time left...
He's like a father to us!
Is it you?!
I hope it was destroyed in the explosion,
Take this!
but Naval Base G-5 reported
that one facility was still in operation...
If Raccoon-san's cure can't make it
and I turn into an Ice Oni...
Tsunagoro, cut me without hesitation!
Why is smoke coming out of a mouse?
Before that happens!
Boss Hyogoro...
They're Marys,
the surveillance force of my father's army.
I'll join you soon!
Without hesitation!
I'm just really glad that it was a failure...
Just kill me!
They're cyborgs.
--Cy...
--...borg?
Otherwise,
They're animals
with mechanized body parts.
Ohmasa!
I'll indiscriminately...
Damn! Can't you make it in time somehow?!
Raccoon-san!
What?!
...slash and kill...
They're roaming around the island
without purpose,
...you guys and everyone here!
Raccoon-san! Isn't the cure ready yet?!
but they share their vision
with human Marys!
This whole floor...
No way...
But if Big Boss becomes an Ice Oni...
What?!
...and our friends will be taken over by Ice Oni again!
Momonosuke is in the Forbidden Storehouse!
Guys! You're badly beaten!
So what this mouse saw...
Yatappe! Do it!
I'm sure no one will be able to stop him...
Human Marys must've seen
the exact same thing...
Okay! I'm gonna... I'm gonna do it now!
Ashura-san...
I missed you all!
That means this place...
I'm counting on you...
I can't endure it anymore, either!
I have no chance to survive!
What?!
Damn... What a pain in the ass...
Just do it!
Hey, is it really this storehouse?
You've become quite old!
Alright then...
Don't make me...
No one enters this cursed place now...
...I, a former Mimawari-gumi member,
would like to see what he's got...
Boss Ohmasa!
I see no signs of anyone entering from here.
Don't make me hurt you all!
But they said this was the place!
O-Oden-sama!
I'm sure Young Master Yamato's here!
I mean, the next Shogun-sama!
You're a legend?
Ohmasa!
You're just a has-been swordsman, right?
There are a number of them.
Kanjuro!!
Queen-sama!
Get out of my way!
This place isn't safe anymore!
Queen-sama!
Old fart!
Let's run, Yamato!
Show us the way
that'll keep Momonosuke-sama out of their sights!
We're your subordinates...
Why do we have to die from your virus?!
Prepare yourself!
Those idiots in supporting roles
brilliantly performed in the tear-jerker!
Shogun-sama! Come on out!
Next is finally my turn in a leading role!
Or we'll break down the door!
TREASURE REPOSITORY
He's right! Why should we die?!
One, two!
I pretended to be a Kozuki...
You can't do this!
...and I'll eliminate the Kozuki, and die!
They'll break through soon!
--Sorry, Momonosuke-kun!
--What?!
You're irritating me!
That's the best way to bring the curtain down!
Hide in my clothes!
One-Sword Style of the Flower!
What?
My life is a beautiful show!
Whaaat?!
Did you think I was gonna die just like that?!
Shut up, you peons!
You fools are useless now!
At that moment, we were able to get away
because of Oden-sama's quick wit...
Listen!
Let's go, Shinobu-san!
If I have no use for you, you're garbage!
Flaming Hair of...
I told you to keep him out of their sights!
No, even garbage is better than you!
We didn't see what happened to him after that.
I know! If we don't take them all down,
they'll see him!
I can't stand people like you fools!
But...!
What's wrong, you guys?
...Holy Rage!
You people don't have much ability,
just waiting for handouts!
Why are you all making that face?!
That's not what I meant!
Damn you!
When you open your mouths,
all you do is complain!
Every time you say something,
I get the urge to kill you!
FLAMING HAIR OF HOLY RAGE
NEAR THE ENTRANCE, ONIGASHIMA
Oh, wait!
I wanna eat ganmodoki, too!
What? You've got shirataki noodles!
Ice Oni is my masterpiece virus!
People don't live only for shirataki noodles!
In fact, it's meant for you guys.
Nonsense!
What happened to your principles, Kikunojo?!
Let's overwhelm him with numbers! Go!
How could you do this to Wanda?!
Whoa-whoa...
Oden is like life!
I wanna cherish everything that's in it!
Hey, Pleasures!
Don't forget that we're all
fighting for our lives.
You've already lost the ability lottery...
Lick!
If I don't do it, I'll get beaten.
You're just cannon fodder who can only laugh!
Lick!
Hey, Oden...
--You took it!
--My life!
H-How could you say that?!
Shut up!
It's unnecessary to hesitate in life!
First come, first served!
Hey, Waiters!
I sometimes wished...
No matter how long you wait,
no more Smile fruits are coming!
Just like with the jaguar named Pedro
or whatever his name is,
How could you, Oden-sama?!
A leader shouldn't do that!
You guys lost your chance to gain powers!
you seem to like to hold grudges against people
for unjust reasons.
...that we had challenged Kaido
back in those days when we had so much energy.
He's right!
The forever Waiters.
As the name suggests, all you can do is wait!
Perospero!
Jack!
You bastard! Do you wanna fight again?!
I'll bring you down at any cost!
Oden-sama?
The only way you good-for-nothings can help
the formidable Animal Kingdom Pirates...
What a pain in the ass...
They tried to defend their kings...
With this Electro that
Pedro trained me to use!
...is to become an oni before you die,
Oden-sama...
You'll die for nothing, too!
and do something worthwhile
to close out your lives!
But Kin'emon and the others
executed a perfect raid!
No wonder you're surprised!
Just like that Jaguar!
What?! That's like... you're telling us to die...
I was sent to the future with Toki's special power!
Yes, I am!
I'll explain it to you later.
It's a long story!
These small fries stood in my way...
And...
We have tons of troops.
Oden-sama! That is why you are here!
...I landed an interesting disciple!
How annoying!
Candy Maiden!
How could you say that?!
We should've finished you off
in an earlier battle!
Kin'emon, I heard about everything!
That's terrible...
Thank you for protecting Momonosuke!
I gave you a chance!
That antibody could save some of you!
This time, I'll get you for sure!
Oh, please! That is more than I deserve!
Straw hat man, you have more potential.
And thank you all, too!
It must've been a struggle for 20 years!
Cat! Raizo! Just move on, everyone!
You'll get stronger and stronger!
Damn! I'm not gonna die!
Candy Armor!
And...
Don't forget. A moment of crisis...
...you must've been surprised to see
the drastically changed Land of Wano!
Slice up your fellow soldiers who turned into Ice Oni!
And the samurai!
Dogstorm...
...will reveal your true power!
Go get them!
Fight your asses off to survive!
Dog?!
I'm sorry for being late!
The candy is...
Their master-servant relationship
makes me sick...
But we can't rejoice in our reunion forever!
I'll take care of him-gara!
Let's defeat Kaido!
Yeah, it's so disgusting.
Hey, you damn samurai!
I'll leave him to you!
Let's go!
To face Kaido who we failed to take down that day!
You may think you're protecting something over there,
Everyone, save Momonosuke-sama for me!
Count on me!
With the Ryuo that you taught me,
Let's go, Kin-san!
--Of course!
--We'll come with you!
but don't forget that the raccoon is...
also a pirate!
I'll kick Kaido's ass!
Yeah...
Till we die!
Be sure to catch up to us, Dogstorm!
We'll be waiting for you!
I can't believe it.
That's been our wish from the beginning!
How could I get screwed by the Rabbit Mink?!
There is no lie or conceit in those words.
Queen...
Let's go!
Producing many antibodies
in just a short amount of time?
Yeah!
He'll achieve mastery of Ryuo
and become stronger...
This is it!
I knew you guys would say so!
That's impossible!
Are you gonna handle me all by yourself,
King of the Day?
I'm sure he just administered the antibody to himself
and escaped!
...and take down Kaido!
That's what I'd expect from my samurai!
You haven't changed!
We're both injured.
So we're a good match!
Wait and watch, Oden!
You're underestimating me...
He's different from you guys!
In the afterworld, Toki must be happy to know
that I'm alive.
Lick!
Are you gonna fight someone
who destroyed your country all by yourself?!
How can you be so sure?!
Pirates do cheat!
The Land of Wano...
...will see its dawn!
I stayed behind
not because I wanted to pay off an old grudge...
Boss Hyogoro! I'll follow you sooner or later!
I didn't want anyone to get hurt
by letting you go free!
Jack!
Don't be so hasty to follow me...
You can't see the moon from here!
Wait, you guys!
There's no poison gas, either!
Big Boss!
What's wrong, Ashura?
Killer! Are you okay?!
There's no way he's alive!
He must be an imposter!
Yeah, I'm all right...
What are you saying, Ashura?!
Goodbye...
They're running!
Kin'emon!
The enemy leader Momonosuke...
We both have to prepare for the worst.
This is what Toki-sama said!
...is getting away from...
...the Forbidden Storehouse!
Leave... to the future!
You guys are next? Let me have fun!
People can never...
People can never go back to the past...
I can't see Momonosuke!
But you can go forward into the future.
Wait!
But I have no doubt!
Momonosuke is with Young Master Yamato
and the kunoichi!
"People can never go back to the past"!
Toki-sama's ability was sending people to the future!
Oden-sama died that day!
MOMONOSUKE - LEADER
SHOGUN OF THE LAND OF WANO
Don't stop me, Raccoon-san!
We have no choice!
That fact wouldn't change even in the future!
No one can change the past!
I need you to wait! I'll save him now!
This place is small and it's hard to breathe,
but for whatever reason,
Don't forget!
I'm not a raccoon!
it feels as if I'm in heaven!
Boss! Swallow it!
Have you forgotten my face, Raizo?
How dare you do that to me,
you damn raccoon?!
No wonder... You're all badly injured!
Well done, you punks!
Yes! I made it in time!
You tried to take down Kaido on my behalf.
B... Boss...
Take this!
Shinobu-san, this way!
You've been waiting for an opportunity to take revenge
for a long time, it must've been painful...
You didn't just screw up my Ice Oni virus,
but you also struck me...
They keep coming!
Chambres!
Boss!
You're gonna have to pay for that!
Lead us to an out-of-sight path already!
Alright, it's working!
His body's gonna warm up!
It's nothing compared to the pain you suffered!
Using medicine
for the wrong purpose is unforgivable!
Don't worry!
If we beat them all up, we'll be out of their sights!
Let's take down Kaido!
Then we'll reconstruct the Land of Wano
and live together like we used to!
Again, that's not what I meant!
You're just a doctor
from a petty pirate group's ship...
What the?!
Hey, Linlin!
Who do you think I am?!
Everything will be restored!
Don't get in my way!
Don't worry! I'm not gonna set out to the sea
on my own again!
They're quite strong on their own...
Together they're too much to handle.
That looks bad!
So you can sleep well too, Izo!
Let me help you-yoi!
I like those odds!
Everyone was always desperate
to stop you from sailing away.
Hey, Luffy! Are you awake now?!
Boss Hyogoro! Are you all right?!
I repeat!
Guys, come to your senses!
Momonosuke, who escaped
from the Forbidden Storehouse,
We lost our lord,
and couldn't even achieve revenge
which was the only purpose of our lives,
Yeah...
Yep!
is with Young Master Yamato and the kunoichi!
and got beaten by Kaido!
I know why you wanna escape from reality!
Definitely!
It worked!
Raccoon-san, I knew you could do it!
Marco!
That broadcast again...
I'm all good now!
But Luffy-dono and the others are still
fighting for the Land of Wano!
Don't worry! We've got your back-yoi!
They're going after Momo and Shinobu-chan!
Young Master Yamato?
So we must face reality!
Oh, well...
Thank goodness!
Hey, which way is the Forbidden Storehouse?!
It worked?
Well done, Raccoon!
I-I'm not gonna tell you.
But maybe he is real!
Raccoon-san, give the cure to Boss Ohmasa, too!
Bring it on, you squirts!
I know!
It's near the entrance of the Skull Dome...
Miyagi, Tristan! Hurry up!
He's quite tough.
You fools...
Okay, Dr. Chopper!
But...!
I guess you really want me to kick your asses!
Kin'emon's group is at the
back of the castle tower...
BACK OF THE CASTLE TOWER
DOME ENTRANCE
Is that...
It's in the opposite direction
of the Dome's entrance.
Wake up, Kin'emon!
It's all set! Dr. Chopper!
You're gonna get your ass kicked instead, Queen!
Kin'emon and the others
are injured from the fight...
All right! Let's do it!
Momo and Shinobu-chan
are being chased by the damn Gifters...
Look! He's not even bleeding!
Whoa-whoa!
Which of them needs me?!
All our troops on the floor will be wiped out!
No way!
Dr. Chopper! Give us the order!
That way?! This way?!
Ashura...
A cannon?!
I thought you pledged to become my samurai.
Chopperphage...
We must put it out quickly!
Go to hell, geezer!
...Nebulizer!
Why am I still thinking?!
We need water! Bring more!
CHOPPERPHAGE NEBULIZER
The ones who need me are probably this way!
Be my samurai!
Phoenix Brand!
Shoot!
Ashura-san!
You better focus, Queen!
Ashura!
Marco!
You are...
I'm gonna teach you idiots a lesson...
That hurts! Was it a shockwave?!
You bastard!
Now it's clear that he's an imposter...
Orochi!
Inhale as much of the mist as you can!
You're in a fight with me!
No way! But you...
You should attack those samurai
after you chop off my head-yoi!
We all feel the same...
I wish he were the real one...
This is the most effective way
to save you from Ice Oni!
But he's an imposter!
Damn! How persistent he is!
Everyone, inhale!
How vicious!
Who's posing as Oden-sama then?!
If I inhale it, will I be okay?!
Go to hell already!
Yes! It's a virus that I made!
It's not him?! Damn!
Raccoon is right! Inhale it!
Okay!
A-Are you okay?! Ashura-san!
I trust Raccoon-san!
This mist saved Boss, right?!
But his behavior...
It looks exactly like Oden!
Lick!
Nice try, full-moon warriors!
I thought you were dead...
The one who can mimic him so well must be...
How come you're alive?!
Bluebird!
...one of us!
Everyone! Inhale the mist!
So it's you!
Kanjuro!
You guys need luck in weather to win!
How could you betray me, Kaido?
Don't be silly! I'm Oden!
Pedro...
Orochi-sama certainly...
How's my drawing of Oden?!
It looks exactly like him, right?
--Everyone's turning back!
--It's a big success!
Roger said, "Everyone has their own turn"!
...got beheaded by Kaido once...
Only you could do that, Dr. Chopper!
I'm gonna finish you off!
This is my turn!
But...
Your compliment doesn't make me happy, you fool!
I'll make him pay for it!
You son of a bitch!
Damn you! Kanjuro!
I'm gonna burn it all up!
Don't push your luck!
What do you think you're doing, Raccoon?!
I'm gonna turn Onigashima into a ball of flames!
Hey, Denjiro!
I'm your lord, how could you defy me?!
Crane Talons!
There's no escape in the air,
What have you done to my masterpiece?!
Listen!
You bastard!
How much more are you gonna taunt us?
so die!
You-gara guys must go forward!
I'll avenge Pedro at any cost...
It is my fault!
I'm gonna kill them all!
It's impossible to give the medicine individually
to thousands of warriors on this floor!
If I did not try to escape reality like a fool...
I'll make them regret crossing me!
No, it's my fault!
Not surprisingly,
it's quite hard to stall two with bounties of over a billion...
Avenge Pedro?!
That bastard deserved to die!
Ashura-san, I'm sorry!
So I crafted my own virus out of the antibody!
Because I failed to finish Kanjuro off, you...
What?!
Did you guys come to the Big Mom Pirates' territory
to have a picnic or something?!
A bad virus can be beaten by a good virus!
Even a sharp sword will become dull
when you try to cut your friend...
This way, everyone can ingest the cure
by inhaling the mist!
You bastard!
It must've been tough for you...
If you don't want your friends to die,
why don't you munch on grass in a forest?!
You're just a doctor
from a petty pirate group's ship...
Is this a drawing?! Where is he?!
Where did you learn such skills?!
We scattered all over the world
and trained ourselves!
That's what suits you. Lick!
I'm manipulating Oden from a distance!
It's too much to handle those two
at the same time.
Even my subordinates have recovered from Ice Oni!
Hurry up, Raccoon!
It's really exhausting though!
Yeah, we can't take it...
Now... I'm not thrilled about the alliance
with the Animal Kingdom Pirates,
How dare you?!
What? That's Marco over there!
Let's strike a blow, Kaido.
You shouldn't use a virus in a fight so casually!
Hey, Kiku!
Your blade did cut me!
but if that's what Mama decided,
I have no choice...
I wonder how many of those five will survive.
It'll surely get out of hand!
I'm seriously wounded, too!
I think I'm gonna die during this battle!
We must teach those punks...
...that the Four Emperors of the Sea
are on a different level from them!
But what keeps me going now...
He looks exhausted...
Why do I have to be taught ethics by a raccoon?
...is my grudge toward the Kozuki Clan!
Trafalgar! Can't you move either of them
downstairs with your ability?
Lick!
But before I die...
Who do you think I am?!
I'm gonna stab at the heart of the Kozuki Clan!
If I could, I would've done it already.
As Kurozumi Kanjuro!
Their Haki is too strong, I can't move them!
Dr. Chopper!
We're ready!
Then, let's tear them apart!
What?!
Thank you...
Pleasures?!
All there is left to do
is clear the final problem.
Is that...?!
Momonosuke-sama's in danger!
Why?!
It's this cure's reliability.
Hey, here comes a big one!
What are you guys doing?!
Get out of my way, you weaklings!
We need a guinea pig.
Momonosuke-kun!
Can you change back to yourself?
You're sticking out like that.
Yeah, since it was thrown together,
Shut up, Queen!
we can't administer it to patients
until we make sure it's safe.
Y-Yeah...
Our brothers were almost killed by you,
and were saved by Raccoon-san here!
So...
...I'll try it myself!
Instead of death due to a crazy superior,
we'd...
Stay still this time, Momonosuke-kun!
Both of you, monitor me closely.
I am sorry!
...rather die siding with the one who saved us!
We don't know what external changes may occur
as side effects!
Isn't that right, guys?!
It may not look it,
but I have gained better control over it...
Thank you, Raccoon!
When I first met Luffy and the others,
Raccoon!
I would turn into a dragon
every time I got surprised and felt sad.
The taste needs to be improved...
I hope your legs are not weakened yet, old bag!
Raccoon!
I'm astonished.
I wonder if it's similar to my father's power...
Who do you think you're talking to, brat?!
I'm indebted to you, Raccoon-san!
He finally revealed it!
If I could turn into a monster like he does,
I would be of some help to everyone...
Raccoon-san, thank you!
Are you scared?
I'm so impressed with Raccoon.
There is some difficulty in breathing,
Zoro...
Luffy is still fighting Kaido, right?
Raccoon! Raccoon! Raccoon! Raccoon!
but the pulse is generally
within the expected range.
--I need one minute.
--Yeah, leave it to me.
I wonder if he's okay!
I wanna take down Kaido too! As Oden!
Conquest of the Sea!
Raccoon! Raccoon! Raccoon! Raccoon!
Don't worry...
Luffy is getting much weaker...
How could he sleep in this situation?
This fever is a manifestation of the drug's effect.
Go to hell, Queen!
But somehow he is in good spirits!
It'll be gone soon...
He's a funny man!
That's good...
Pirate Hunter!
This can't be real!
What?!
You shitheads!
And Surgeon of Death, don't you think so?
No! We can't dodge it!
How can you tell, Momonosuke-sama?!
I just formed an alliance
with him and that's it...
What the hell is this?!
When are you gonna stop chatting?
That was impressive, Raccoon!
Do it!
You damn brats, don't disappoint me.
Thanks, Marco!
There's one more thing that I wanna say!
Raccoon!
Everyone's turning back into Ice Oni!
Rumble!
Th-The fire's gone...
Monster Point!
Let's see how strong that Man-Beast Form is!
Help me!
Get away! You guys!
Go!
I'll go!
What?!
The lives of Ice Oni are at their limits!
Don't ruin my fun!
I'm not a raccoon!
God of Lightning Tenjin!
Ohmasa! Are you okay?!
Yeah, thanks to the blue flame,
I'm good as new!
I told you. I'm gonna have some fun, too.
Oh, I'm sorry!
Take this!
How's Big Boss?!
He didn't get the blue flame!
Scyther...
What's wrong?
Are you getting tired of dancing?!
If you don't get away...
SCYTHER SONIC
Damn!
...Sonic!
we'll be wiped out!
Guys, think before you move!
You damn monster...
Zoro!
Shut up!
What's wrong?! It's not over, right?
Cutting into his flesh isn't working!
How can we defeat them?
Let's keep fighting!
His skin must've become even harder...
Bring it on, all at once!
I don't think our attacks are working.
Big Boss!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Let's go!
Okay!
They sure are the Emperors of the Sea...
Their skin is tough.
Can't they at least pretend
that it's working a little bit?!
Killer!
It's working!
After all this striking,
there's no way it wouldn't work!
Big Boss!
W-We Gifters are blocking this path!
Where are we...?
They're humans just like us!
Keep your spirits up!
You shouldn't go fight yet...
Gum-Gum...
What was that jolt?!
Ouch...
Shut up! Get out of my way!
Luffy... Zoro...
Don't let that weird virus get the best of you!
Kiku!
Bao Huang!
Are the Akazaya samurai still in the Treasure Repository?
Boss Hyogoro!
Kin-sama...
You did that earlier and it didn't work!
Think before you attack!
Let's see the Land of Wano's dawn together!
Are you okay?!
Yes. How's everyone else?
How can you say they're humans just like us
even when the distinction is so clear?
Hey... Are you guys all right?!
They're gone, but I can still hear them...
They're monstrous...
Yeah...
They are!
They got away from it... I'm impressed.
Someone treated their wounds,
You guys think you can't beat them,
and yet here you are?
You're right!
it seems!
Who healed us?
Zoro-ya, are you alive?
We're trying to figure out how to win!
I don't know...
I guess it's time...
Black Maria! Where are you now?!
But I think I saw the person...
We should pull one of them away from here.
I think so...
I'm still in the Banquet Hall.
No, I must've been dreaming...
Good job blocking it even for a moment...
Thanks.
I agree.
Alright, I'm gonna finish off the samurai!
When those two are side by side,
this place looks like...
It's impossible...
Where's Straw Hat?
Do it! I want this!
...nothing but hell...
Luffy-dono and the others are fighting Kaido for us.
Even if they're critically
injured, they're not weak enough
Kaido!
We should not be staying here and doing nothing!
to be killed by the Tobi Roppo!
So what?
Hell doesn't bother me!
It's like the heavens have given me
a reward at the end...
The battle on the island is still on!
You got it?! Don't do anything!
Caution, we're too heated up!
Let's go!
Jack...
I was imprisoned and only waiting to die,
but now I've made it this far...
We still have life left to give!
He's underestimating us...
But...
But if I go on, I'll only risk your lives!
...this works out well for me.
WOMAN TROUBLE
Gum-Gum...
Guys! You're badly beaten!
I'm sorry I assigned you a tough role...
...Red!
But do it for me!
I'd appreciate it if he did it.
You dodged it, Kaido!
I missed you all!
Must be because it hurts!
What is that?
What?!
I've been to hell many times...
I'll leave the rest to you guys...
Hey, Nico Robin...
You've became quite old!
Your eyes always look vigorous!
You will belong to...
This man, Hyogoro the Flower...
Ow, ow, ow...
...Kaido-sama.
Straw Hat!
I have...
No way. I'd rather die!
O-Oden-sama!
We have the upper hand!
...no regrets!
That's so cool!
Kaido and Big Mom overpower the Worst Generation
with their monstrous physiques
With a firm vow to his late comrade-in-arms,
His wild laughter!
The iron hammer with the strong Color
of the Supreme King will drag people to hell!
The hero of the Land of Wano! Kozuki Oden!
The Akazaya members
who witness Kozuki Oden's comeback find a ray of hope!
Boss Hyogoro the Flower
takes the final stage!
and warn them to prepare for the worst.
All covered in bruises, Luffy and the others
become single-minded in front of Kaido!
I, Yamato A.K.A. Kozuki Oden,
will talk all about his great life with Momonosuke-kun!
The conquerors of the sea unleash a furious attack
which would even make ogres cry!
Keeping his old, worn-out body going,
he cuts a swath through Kaido's army!
They failed to take down their sworn enemy Kaido once,
To launch a new era, they pull off a desperate feat
that stuns the Emperors of the Sea!
The samurai who has
weathered times of turmoil
The Four Emperors' special secret art will
destroy Luffy and the others!
Join us for the tales of Oden's spectacular adventure!
but now after 20 years,
they stand up again with Oden to finish the task!
entrusts his beloved homeland to Straw Hat!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Comprehensive Anatomy! The Legend of Kozuki Oden!"
"Oden Appears! The Confused Hearts of the Akazaya Members!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Supernovas Strike Back!
The Mission to Tear Apart the Emperors!"
"The Worst Generation Gets Wiped Out?!
The Emperors' Deadly Attack!"
"No Regrets! Luffy and Boss,
a Master-Disciple Bond!"
I'm gonna open the borders of the Land of Wano![Events]
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
[Events]