Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Hey! I'm gonna take everyone else
except you!
Luffy launched an all-out attack
against Kaido.
Okay!
But...
After Law and Zoro left the rooftop,
Luffy was defeated by Kaido
and sank into the sea.
Luffy and Kaido's one-on-one fight began.
"The Conclusion!
Luffy, Accelerating Fist of the Supreme King"
You seem to be enjoying yourself.
This is bad... Let's...
The higher the risk, the bigger the smile
and the bigger the smile...
Kaido-sama! We found Momonosuke!
...retreat for now!
Get out of my way!
--I'll be there soon.
--Okay!
I won't let you flee!
It's time to try your skill!
Show me what you can do!
"Luffy, Defeated!
The Straw Hats in Jeopardy?!"
Why?!
You're...!
I've got a bounty of 330 million!
Punk Gibson!
Fulgora!
FULGORA
And he's got a bounty of only 320 million,
which makes him a loser!
Meanwhile, Nami and Usopp
were defending Otama.
He infused himself...
With Big Mom's appearance,
the battle became chaotic!
Why should I carry him on my shoulder?!
...with the Color of the Supreme King...
Olin-chan!
Go away, Straw Hats.
I'm thirsty. I want sake.
Otama!
It's been so long!
This bastard...
Can't you see the situation?!
You must be sleep-talking!
...is my prey!
Otama! Make her go away!
Oh? I'm free.
Captain Kid!
You really were sleep-talking!
But the way he handled it...
Where's Mama?
Thing is... Olin-chan...
What?! What is it this time?!
Mama! Where are you?!
...was just awful...
Who is it?!
I'll be there! Mama!
Okobore Town?!
Damn...
How did it come to this?
They killed the people who helped me
when I lost my memory...
SEVERAL MINUTES AGO
Gum-Gum...
Hey! Momo! Shinobu-chan!
"The Animal Kingdom Pirates Trample Down!
The End of the Kozuki Clan!"
Captain Kid!
Kid! I mean, what?
Are you still trying to defeat me?!
Everyone...
Mama, where are you?!
Answer me! Let me help you!
This is fun!
Momonosuke-sama!
We won't let you through!
Everyone in Okobore Town
who was so nice to me...
Oh, what should I do?!
This is good for me!
Eustass-ya became weaker.
What am I supposed to do?!
I need more metal scraps!
What was it?
Kin-sama!
Big Mom went back to the castle...
Just get here already!
Is that what you're telling me?!
It'll be a pain if she returns
for that thundercloud.
--Kiku.
--Yeah...
I won't forgive you guys!
Momonosuke-sama!
I don't, however, need you fools!
--It's over...
--Don't kill us!
Kin-sama!
You couldn't be Joyboy...
This is perfect!
Oh, Shinobu!
I am glad that you are okay!
Hey! I'm gonna take everyone else
except you!
T-Take this!
I'll send the ladder down now!
Momonosuke-sama is...!
...either, I guess...
Run, Komachiyo!
Okay!
What?
--What?!
--Momonosuke-sama!
Mama!
Outta my way!
SECOND FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Where are you, Big Mom?!
What?!
Too slow! This is it!
No, Zeus.
Kid?
What?
Oh, crap!
You're no longer...
I switched us with some flying object!
Shut up!
...needed!
Black-Leg-ya?!
"Nami Screams -
A Deadly Death Race!"
Tra-guy? Mosshead?
It's not working!
I feel no pain, not even a little bit!
You fools...
Catch us!
Hey, Nami!
Your attacks can't hurt me at all!
What's this all about?
Even in the immoral world of pirates,
Where am I?! Where's Mama?!
You didn't really mean
I'm no longer needed.
there's supposed to be
humanity and justice!
I guess you can't keep it up anymore...
I'm on my way to help!
Right, Mama?!
Zeus!
Lick!
Where's Nami-san?
I thought you were working for her!
What are you talking about, Zeus?!
It's coming again!
The shower of candy arrows!
You left Mama in the lurch!
--Hey!
--Leave him be.
Take cover!
Why are you relaxing on my shoulder?!
Damn you!
No, I didn't mean to...
You have screwed up
so much until now as well!
You idiot!
At the very least, I'd like a girl!
I moved us to the right place.
Big Sis!
We're better off without you!
No, you didn't!
Where did you guys come from?!
Chopperemon-san!
The Rumble Ball's effect
will be gone in less than 10 minutes...
Mama!
I'm not obligated to carry
you scruffy guys! Get down already!
Are you listening?!
Even though the duration was increased...
Look after him, Black-Leg-ya.
What are you doing? We better run now!
You two, go downstairs!
I'll defeat him at any cost!
Hera!
What happened?
Eat Zeus!
What?!
Wait! Explain the situation before you go!
By consuming his soul,
you'll become even stronger!
"The Dawn of the Land of Wano -
The All-Out Battle Heats Up!"
That's not good enough!
Zoro-ya probably had
20 to 30 bones broken.
How could you say that, Mama?!
Tell that to everyone...
Three minutes of gigantification?
CONNECTING HALLWAY
FROM TREASURE REPOSITORY 2F TO CASTLE 3F
Splint up his body, put him on his back,
make sure he's conscious and breathing.
...for me!
What can you do in that short time?
What?
The Rumble Ball?
Not his situation!
I'd be happy to eat him!
Look at that formula.
Why don't you look after him?!
Mama!
You seem to be enjoying yourself.
I can improve that Rumble Ball!
I have to stop Big Mom!
You can at least tend to his wounds, right?!
Zeus-senpai! I'm gonna eat you!
The higher the risk, the bigger the smile
and the bigger the smile...
Five times...
Don't! Stop her, Mama!
--I'll leave it to you!
--Hey!
No, I can make the drug
10 times more effective!
I'm not a doctor!
And I don't have time to tend to his wounds!
But there'll be a side effect if I remain
as a monster for more than three minutes...
That bastard!
I'm sorry for always messing up!
A side effect?
If you don't wanna see me, I'll go away!
I have no choice!
So what?!
You only care about yourself?!
Hey! Stop moving!
Kiku, does your arm hurt?
And you call yourself a pirate?!
I swear I'll never show my face
to you again!
You don't ask such things of a samurai.
What?!
The enemies you guys will face hereafter...
Do you even know how to apply a bandage?
So please!
It's merely "itching"
until my life is extinguished.
...can't be beaten in three minutes!
Don't kill me!
It's the same as trussing a ham.
Just like my heart "itched"
on the day you disappeared...
That makes you a thief!
If you say
"Oh, I'm scared of the side effect,"
Am I a ham to you?
you can't even protect your dear playmates,
kiddo! Do you understand?
You're stealing a piece of my soul!
You're not that appetizing!
Oden-sama is gone!
Whitebeard's ship left the port, too!
Luffy!
Take a risk!
I was afraid of this!
Please! Take him down!
And?
Big Bro Izo...
Dog-chan and Cat-chan are gone, too!
If you're truly sorry, let her eat you
and become part of her power!
Kaido!
Don't cry, Okiku!
I...
Instead of fearing the worst,
let's look for them!
Who could hurt you like this?
I...
Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
--Okay?!
--Mm-hm.
...wanna help the others!
Kin-sama?!
Kaido and Big Mom.
Help, Mama!
Search! Search across the country!
Get the chemicals I ask for!
Shinobu! Is Momonosuke-sama doing okay?!
No wonder. I can't believe
you made it to the rooftop.
That serves you right!
The gigantification time
will be increased to 30 minutes!
He is, but we're getting
more and more attacks from the enemy!
Right, Otama?
Tell me Luffy is okay.
Hey! What's going on?!
I knew you would do this!
10 times longer than now!
Oh no!
We're now in a hidden room, but...
I think he figured something out...
You guys...
It will be riskier...
Do not lower your guard!
Kanjuro is after you guys!
Whitebeard!
He'll win!
I won't let you live!
...but you're not scared, are you?
Oden?!
I know that!
Let me on board the ship!
Stay alert! He will come to annihilate
the Kozuki Clan!
Of course not!
Oden-sama! I knew you would do this!
I'm a pirate!
Anyway...
Huh?
--Wait! Big money!
--I won't let you escape!
I won't let you go!
It's dangerous,
so stay out of the way for now.
I will be there to defend you!
That fool!
Otama!
I wanna leave you somewhere!
Let me come!
We're in a crawl space on the first floor
of the castle! Be safe!
Show me the world!
Black Coffee Beam!
Come back! You are the next Shogun!
I got it! I am counting on you, Shinobu!
Otama! You're awake!
Sangoro-dono!
Kin'emon!
Kappa! You guys are all right!
Great!
Momonosuke-sama!
Please be patient for now!
Big Bro-sama!
Stay there!
Scurrying around...
Now, how can Zorojuro-dono
sleep under these circumstances?
Onami-chan! Usohachi-kun!
I can still vividly remember that day.
He doesn't know when to give up!
They're bad pirates called the Straw Hats!
Sorry, sorry! Did it hit you?
Hey...
Maybe he got beaten by Kaido...
He seems seriously injured.
Well, if you're fine enough
to tease me, that's good.
What are you doing?
So...
Could you help me a little bit?
Don't worry.
This idiot won't die that easily.
...I'm gonna kill them!
I'm really sorry
that I disappeared without telling you...
We must get ready
to overcome this situation!
Well done!
You're the idiot...
No, I would've done the same
if I were in your shoes.
How's this then?!
Wait!
Gee! If you make a move now,
you'll risk Momonosuke-sama's life!
You're actually awake, aren't you?
Sangoro-dono, where are you heading?
It's more important to protect Oden-sama
than to warn the others of the urgency.
Hunker down for now!
Don't do it, Olin-chan!
This is the only way to protect you!
To the best of our poor abilities,
we'll help you.
They're my friends!
You and I would've died
if it weren't for Oden-sama...
And I must sort things out
with my old man!
I was gonna get to Momonosuke.
Luffy left this to me!
If we hadn't met him,
we wouldn't have lived to see today.
You weren't?
Together with you!
Kin'emon is heading for him,
so he'll be okay.
We're doomed!
I'll always be with Oden-sama!
Momonosuke-kun!
If you wanna help,
go to the Performance Floor.
Yeah! Let's do it one more time! Ready?!
Nami!
So this "itch" in my arm is nothing
compared to the pain of losing Oden-sama!
The Performance Floor?
What's going on there?!
Everyone! I'll leave the rest to you!
I'm sorry!
Back us up!
Don't just make a request
and then fall asleep!
You guys, why don't you give up already?!
For trying to kill you earlier!
Mm-hm.
Let's go to the Performance Floor!
So until Luffy defeats Kaido,
Izo.
Considering their strength, if we don't hurry,
the casualties will only increase.
Get this straight, Zeus!
If you hold back, I'll wipe you out!
If the Land of Wano is successfully opened,
how do you think it'll change?
He got on! The dinosaur guy!
I'm not gonna lose, either!
Yeah!
Go away!
Well...
I'm sorry, Nami!
Such a miracle won't happen!
Let's talk about it tomorrow morning
if we survive.
Usopp! Hit his weak spots!
Rest in peace!
I know!
Reality is cruel! Sadly!
I hate you!
That's a tall task!
We won't give up! We're not gonna die!
I'm done with you!
Now it is an all-out war!
It is win or die!
I'm a coward...
Stop dodging!
The temple!
There must be
a shortage of forces everywhere.
The chin!
Thunder...
...so I couldn't refuse Mama's order!
The Adam's apple!
...Bagua!
I can protect Momonosuke-sama
all by myself!
Damn you...
Hera!
Leave us alone, you damn lizard!
I didn't wanna die so I betrayed you
even though you were so kind to me...
Kanjuro will attack Momonosuke-sama!
How's this strangulation?!
Isn't it painful, Raccoon?!
The eyeball!
I will try to reach Momonosuke-sama
before him,
The nostril!
I'm a weakling and a coward!
I'm a reindeer!
and take him down with my own hands!
You guys, scatter and help the others out!
Just fall already!
BAM! WHACK! THUD! BONK!
Roger!
WHACK! CRACK! THUD! WHACK!
How many hits will you take before you fall?!
He's unbelievably tough!
I don't care!
I said I was done with you!
Come on, boy!
Okay, Kin'emon!
BAM! THUD! WHACK! BAM!
Cat, let's spread out!
Nami?!
I know you did!
But I got dumped by the other side too,
Shut up!
I'll do so!
You can do it, Komachiyo!
We'll be there soon!
and I'm all alone now!
Mm-hm! Good luck!
You insolent raccoon!
If we can get to the stage
on the Performance Floor,
Kin-sama!
Let me take care of Kanjuro!
I can give a command to the enemies
who were forced to eat Kibi Dango...
I know how you feel now.
Marys!
I'll get him this time!
I know I'm doomed to die soon...
Diffusion Mode!
...by Horselina-chan and the others!
...but I don't wanna die
with everyone hating me!
Kiku! Follow me!
And if they become our allies...
It's fun to punch someone
stronger than you!
You don't have to forgive me,
but watch me!
Okay!
I'm...
...no longer needed!
Announcement to all of Onigashima!
Like a kid, you're caught up in trying to
defeat the enemy in front of you!
If I can help everyone, I...
I'm gonna rebel
for the first and last time!
...don't care what'll happen to me!
The duel is over!
So get me to the stage!
The man with the highest bounty
amongst the enemies, Straw Hat...
Don't be silly, Tama!
Tama!
That's...!
Get a grip!
Until we take back the Land of Wano,
this fight won't be over!
Master Cat Viper!
Usohachi-kun!
I knew it was you-saru!
--Let's run!
--Mm-hm!
...has been defeated!
Gum-Gum...
Shishilian! Bariete!
Otama! Let's keeping fighting!
At least one person!
What?!
SHISHILIAN - CAPTAIN OF DOGSTORM MUSKETEERS
BARIETE - MINK RECON SQUAD
I wanna make it up to at least one person!
Chopperemon-san!
This young lady and this old man
will protect you at any cost!
Where are you dashing off to?!
And then I'll die!
...Red Roc!
We need your help!
Nami! Run!
Who did you call an old man?!
I'm only 19!
This is my way of life!
Straw Hat!
The thing is... Pedro...
It's all over...
Zeus!
Just like Big Bro Luffy,
Goodbye.
Kaido-sama choked the life out of him...
I wanted to help everyone!
I kept bringing down those people
who were said to be stronger than me,
But I'm...
What?
You hear that?
...scared and I can't take it anymore...
No way!
and I found myself
being called the strongest...
I'm already running out of energy...
What?!
But what do I see from here?
...and Straw Hat Luffy sank
to the bottom of the dark nighttime sea!
Is this for real?!
His soul is being extracted!
Pedro... died?!
It's boring to look at a landscape
in which no one is stronger than you.
Yes, in Big Mom's territory.
Even if you make the Gifters your allies,
it's no use!
Mama!
Good news!
Now eat him, Hera!
I think Luffy-kun's group wouldn't be here
if it weren't for him!
You stupid brat! Don't push your luck!
The child is scared!
You're lucky.
Did you hear that?
I see.
Because you don't have to feel this way.
He's such a doofus!
I don't care about that idiot!
Pedro...
I won't let you touch her!
You did a great job-meow!
Both the Kozuki samurai
and the captain lost!
The one responsible for his death
is here on the island?!
I'm sorry, Tama.
Here are Black Balls out of pity!
Yes, we need your help-saru!
Give up. You're different from me.
Eat them and run!
Usohachi-kun...
Who's next? Can anyone else win?!
It seems like Wanda and Carrot
are struggling against him!
I won't make you nervous anymore!
Zeus!
You can't change anything.
Oh, no! He's soulless now,
he's not even going for his favorite!
Kin'emon's group, too?!
Leave it to me!
The Kozuki Clan will be destroyed and the
Land of Wano will become New Onigashima.
Usopp!
Of course I was gonna help you!
Eat them, Zeus!
Big Bro Luffy!
Get ready, you damn lizard!
Wake up!
Kaido-sama will go downstairs
to start "cleaning"!
I'll still be the strongest and bored...
I'm gonna eat you! Zeus-senpai!
You long-nose shit!
Everything you do annoys me!
I can't believe she broke the castle
like this... Damn Linlin...
Master!
Zeus!
Special Attack Green Star!
Kaido-sama will accept your surrender!
The cat is flying!
What?! What are you doing,
you damn long-nose freak?!
Those who put their hands in the air
to surrender and obey...
The Kozuki Clan won't be destroyed...
Firework Flowers!
CRAWL SPACE, FIRST FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
...will be spared
and welcomed as subordinates!
PERFORMANCE FLOOR, SKULL DOME
The Land of Wano...
Momonosuke-kun.
Shinobu-san... Watch out for the Marys!
...will be free!
Screw that!
They're roaming around Onigashima
to do recon!
It's hot!
Luffy!
Watch it, Usopp!
Sorry! I don't have that many
close-range weapons!
They could be anywhere.
They could be watching us from somewhere now!
Anyway, I'll take him down!
And...
What? Where?! Where are they?!
This fool...
Special Attack Green Star!
I'm gonna become...
Don't worry! We got this!
...the King of the Pirates!
Do not tell me that is...
Way to go! Chopperemon-san!
Exploding Pine Cones!
It's you!
I thought so!
That serves you right, Queen! You bastard!
I'll use this to make myself a decoy!
You and I are targeted as a group.
So I'm gonna carry this and run!
The enemy will think I'm carrying you
and come after me!
You don't mind if I kill traitors,
do you?! Lick!
Come on! Usopp!
I did it! it was a direct hit!
And I'll hit them like wham!
Perospero! I don't need your help!
You two can stay hiding here!
How's that, you bastard?!
All right!
Doesn't matter if you don't.
I'll kick her ass right here!
I can see you're itching to fight.
Lizard extermination complete!
I'm just doing this for Mama.
Hey, Nami...
To me, Usopp-sama,
the Tobi Roppo is like nothing!
Momonosuke-sama! What is wrong?!
What are you doing?! We gotta run!
Go ahead, Yamato.
Whatever! No...
We're in contact with Kin-sama!
She'll get up again!
You know how tough those dinosaurs are!
Get rid of all the small fries!
That'll save me the trouble!
I'll protect Momonosuke-sama here!
Kin'emon!
Big Mom is behind us, too!
There's no path to victory for us!
I am here!
Uh-huh! Thanks! Shinobu-san!
Everyone, take shelter!
Hide behind something!
I must tell everyone!
Even if we run away,
she'll never stop chasing us!
Tell?!
That's a lot of arrows!
What do you wanna tell them?!
Hey...
Hurry up! Run now!
More than anything,
she even hurt Otama and that's unforgivable!
Oh, yeah!
Surrender, Land of Wano!
Momonosuke-kun,
you can hear Luffy's voice, right?
Run!
It's a losing battle!
Hey, you!
Hey, Tama! Stay with me!
Is he okay?
It's already over!
He got up again!
Mm-hm, I can hear it.
Otama, are you alive?!
Run! Hurry!
What's wrong with those
dinosaur power-users?!
Straw Hat...
It hasn't changed from before.
Komachiyo, run!
I know you're already up!
Just get up already!
...sank to the bottom
of the dark nighttime sea!
--He's gonna shoot'em!
--Hurry up and hide!
He became weaker, but he's fine.
But...
Go to hell!
...there are only two voices now!
This is a Mary, right?!
It's here which means...
Are you ready to be taken down by me now?
Damn...
What?
...we're in trouble,
aren't we, Kin-sama?!
That long-nose fool!
Apocalyptic Candy Shower!
Maybe the enemies know where we are!
I wish Kibi Dango worked against him, too...
Watch out!
It only works with Smile fruit eaters!
What should we do if he comes back?!
One on one...
Whoa-whoa, twirling a baton?!
Luffy and Kaido must be fighting head to head!
What?!
A loser like you is no match for Ulti-sama,
Cheerleader!
In any case,
let's get to the Performance Floor!
I gotta hurry!
We must fulfill Otama's plan!
Tornado...
Oh, no!
...Tempo!
ODEN'S TRAVEL RECORD
Are you okay?!
I never thought I'd meet you one day!
Wake up! Stay with me!
That's a good surprise-attack, Nami!
That brat!
I'm disgusted!
But...
Hey!
You'll have to do better than that!
On that day, I picked this up
at the river below Oden Castle.
How dare they do this...
Hey!
This voice...!
I, of course, give this to you.
I got you!
That was a hell of an attack!
Momonosuke!
I couldn't take down so many of them. Lick!
It's been a long time!
Repel!
What?! No way!
Shinobu, you're looking good too!
But that's fine.
I'll make him pay!
Don't worry-arinsu.
That means I get to enjoy it again.
I see... All the details of
my father's adventures are here...
When I finish with this tramp,
you're next.
F-Father!
Show yourself, Kid!
I'm determined to beat the shit out of
everyone who messes with Pay-Pay.
No, Shinobu-san!
Father! Father!
You're no exception, old bag!
Oh, no! Pardon me!
What?!
Do not look at him!
Raccoon...
What?!
Th-That was delivered to you after all this time
and contains everything about Oden-sama!
Just as Pay-Pay suffered...
Big Mom?!
Take this!
Father!
No, I'll make you suffer
100 million times more than him!
What?! Let go of him!
You fools!
It's a tear-jerking reunion of
a father and son!
Go ahead and read it.
Do you have any idea...
Mm-hm.
It's not!
Get back, Shinobu!
...what you have done?
Mm-hm, mm-hm...
What?!
He grabbed his head!
I'm Kozuki Oden!
I had heard so many stories about him...
I don't care about that brat!
You did it once and you're doing it again!
Should I have hurt her more?!
but to actually read them like this...
You're telling an obvious lie!
Hey, Kiku, what's wrong?!
Get that grim look off your face!
I'm sorry-arinsu. You're first.
It's me!
Shut up!
You fools!
How dare you...
Cat Burglar and the one with the long nose...
...kill Ashura-san...
I didn't like you from
the beginning-arinsu.
She's gonna kill us!
Damn you! Get off of me!
You're Straw Hat's peers.
After you ran like a rat,
Olin-chan!
you told that unfunny joke that your captain
would become the King of the Pirates...
Don't sully Kozuki Oden anymore!
Chopperemon-san is overpowering Queen...
Otama!
It's been so long!
But now,
How strong!
I finally get to smash your head in.
It's you, Otama!
Ulti...
I'm happy to see you again!
What are you doing
in a dangerous place like this?!
No, Kiku! What are you thinking?!
That's not the kind of breath I'd expect
from someone who's winning the battle!
Don't say my name with that appearance!
No...
Onami-chan...
Kanjuro!
Huh, Raccoon?!
Take this!
Why?!
--Hera!
--Yes, Mama!
I've never seen Big Mom like that!
--Prometheus!
--Yeah, Mama!
Gum-Gum...
Napoleon!
I've been worried about you, Olin-chan!
...Hawk Gatling!
Hey, Kiku. You've got to be kidding!
Yes, Mama!
I wonder how much more he can take.
You suddenly disappeared in Udon!
Let's go!
I took you and Izo into my care.
Lick!
THIRD FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Sorry...
But I've been worried about you, too.
I...
No.
Now, you two...
I'm not mad!
I'm happy to see you again!
We'll never flee or hide!
Where are your parents?
Gear Three!
Combine!
Bring it on from anywhere!
Uh-huh! Thank you for taking care of me
when I lost my memory!
Ow, ow...
Gum-Gum...
There you are, Young Master Yamato!
Come back without resisting!
I see... What's your name?
Maser Cannon!
Great! So you got your memory back!
Izo.
...Grizzly Magnum!
Kiku.
Mm-hm!
That's...
Okay!
Oh, no...
Momonosuke!
You two... Eat all you want!
She went into Mother Mode which she only enters
around kids under 10 every now and then.
Yeah, that cocky look in his eyes!
That insolent mouth!
Uh-huh!
Whoa... Whoa-whoa, Otama!
That sure is Kozuki's stupid son!
I-Is she your friend?!
Oh?
You're looking great in kimono!
He's not handcuffed!
Really?!
That's right. I'm not captive anymore!
I got a new hairpin!
Can you cut me?!
Otama! Make her go away!
I'm...
...Oden!
Let's smile more, Straw Hat!
Hey, the person who did my hair...
That meddlesome and poor woman
from Okobore Town...
I'm not enjoying myself at all, Kaido!
Just smile all by yourself!
Listen, everyone!
Oh, Otsuru! How is she doing?
I'm Kozuki Oden!
Then I'll make it more enjoyable for you!
First, it was Page One-sama...
I'm with my son, Momonosuke!
A-And now,
Ulti-sama was beaten by Big Mom...
You stupid swordsman!
CRAWL SPACE, FIRST FLOOR
I can't cut you...
Don't sleep and dream so peacefully!
SECOND FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Kin-sama... I can't...
I'll never forget how that small amount of
red-bean soup tasted!
Isn't she our ally?
Damn! You're heavy...
Kanjuro!
Father's logbook...
...and hard to carry...
It was so delicious!
It contains a series of his adventures
that I do not know of.
Can you get up, Nami?!
...and there's no joy in carrying you!
I wish I could eat it again.
That was crazy, but you saved us!
Let's run!
That's Black-Leg Sanji
with a bounty of 330 million berries!
Thing is... Olin-chan...
Mm-hm!
When he joined the Whitebeard Pirates
led by Edward Newgate,
That Okobore Town is gone now.
Take him down!
Kanjuro!
Komachiyo...
his journey began.
Sorry, Tama! We can't save him now!
Kiku!
Gone? What do you mean by that?
Let's come back for him later!
After we left for Udon,
What's this place?!
He was surprised and excited
by the world he had never seen before...
Look who he's carrying!
Okobore Town got attacked!
Zeus?!
Maybe that's Pirate Hunter Zoro!
Because you cut me before...
And...
Come to think of it,
We burned down
the mountain bandit's mountain!
who is that thundercloud?
What?!
But instead of seeking revenge,
The big money is carrying the big money!
Hey!
I'm critically injured too, Kiku!
...he fought, too!
We hit it off so well, Hera!
they keep stealing tons of food
from our farm!
Watch what you say!
He eventually met the great pirate,
Gold Roger.
The 330-million is carrying the 320-million!
I couldn't do that attack
with the stupid Zeus!
Do you guys have something to do with it?!
Kiku!
That's not what I meant! Damn...
No, that's because you got on
with me well, right, Hera?!
Kin-sama...
Divine Departure!
W-We don't know anything!
Can't you beat them more quietly?
I'm ashamed of myself.
Don't push your luck, you dummies.
I heard samurai are preparing to make a raid...
Is that why, maybe?!
I, Kikunojo of the Fallen Snow...
I just followed Mama's lead.
You're in my way, Mosshead!
Don't be so cold!
...can't live any longer...
The Final Island which is said to
hold a vast amount of treasure.
If so, we can't let them know!
PERFORMANCE FLOOR
I begged Mama for a girlfriend
and she created you!
But...
It's showtime!
What are you guys whispering about?!
...if the fallen snow is melting...
Father heard about it from Roger then he...
Your girlfriend? No thanks.
I will guide you!
Dance, Rac-Raccoon!
this country's dawn will
definitely come soon.
What?! But I even like that part of you!
White-Kichi-chan!
So do not hurt anyone!
I wanna go!
O-Otsuru-san!
Please allow me to go!
Guide me?
It's nice to have a girl in the group!
Do not be silly...
...went aboard Roger's ship.
Do you know anything about this?
Cloven Rose, Palm!
And he advanced toward
his desired island little by little...
Of course, it will!
You will see once you get there.
It is a little far though...
Prometheus...
The light from the dawn of the Land of Wano
will reach to the afterworld!
Yeah! The three of us should
work closely together from now on!
No, Otsuru-san!
You don't have to cover for us!
I found it!
Napoleon...
It's okay now! We just wanted to eat
as much as we wanted before we die!
This is where it was?!
Seems like you're gonna be
a better team than with Zeus.
So many people suffered
because of you!
Kiku!
Kikunojo!
What?
Hey, Mama... Who is that girl?
The writing is about a weapon
named Poseidon.
Give it some thought!
So it's you guys who did it!
I see...
Don't preach at me!
A predecessor sets
a good example for what not to do.
They lied about being the ones
who ate the food...
The way you fell
was very beautiful, Kiku...
Have you completed the train?!
Who is she?
You truly were a loyal retainer!
...which was actually eaten by
Samurai-san's group before the raid.
You mean the Sea Train?! No way!
I'm still designing it!
That's supposed to be my place...
Goodbye! Mr. Raccoon Dog!
Hey...
If it was a stage play, it would've been
the masterpiece of the century!
Am I gonna be all alone?
So Kaido's subordinates...
So long, Raccoon-san!
...burned down the town.
Toki! That's the Fish-Man Island!
Damn...
Now you're the next actor, Kin!
What?
How interesting... It seems like
the whole island is in a bubble...
That's Nami!
Olin-san.
--How is it, Oden?
--Well...
I'm gonna set the stage
for your final moments!
one of them isn't so important.
No wonder...
I once tried to kill her...
They're rebels! Don't let them get away!
It's an apology letter
from someone named Joyboy.
Another enemy?!
Chopperemon-san!
Burn them along with the houses!
Zeus!
I can't believe it!
He really can read the script!
It's you, Zeus!
Oh, Mama! I'm sorry to be late!
Yeah, by the way, do you have a weapon
to control the Neptunians?!
The poor man whose lord was killed
and who was betrayed by his friend,
The people of Okobore Town got...
Lick!
We have a new member?
What the?!
Otsuru!
Once every few centuries in this country,
and now he lost his comrade...
This is sweet red-bean soup.
Go ahead, Olin-san, try it!
It's reassuring to have a fourth member!
I came to help, Animal Kingdom Pirates...
a Mermaid who can talk to
the Neptunians is born.
What awaits him?
Four? No, Zeus.
How could you ruin my show?!
Is it a tragedy?!
So good!
What?
Or a comedy?
Maybe, that Mermaid is...
You're no longer needed!
It's delicious!
Just when I was gonna liven it up!
So your daughter will become the weapon
that will destroy the world someday?!
I'm glad that you like it.
Play your role, Kin'emon!
Thank you, Tsuru-san.
I never thought that Poseidon
was a Mermaid!
Decorate the stage
with your honorable death!
That guy's the one from
the Big Mom Pirates...
Then...
It's good to see you again...
...finally...
Kanjuro!
Okobore Town?!
Lick!
Now we've got all the Road Ponegliffs...
Oh, you're looking great, Olin-san!
Am I?
P-Pay-Pay!
Let's go, guys! To the Final Island!
That's so cute!
P... P-P-P... Page One-sama!
I want my hair done like you two!
Yeah!
I will do your hair
once you get a little older.
Was it you...
--Really?!
--I'll help that, too!
The Final Island
no man has set foot on for 800 years...
Are you still trying to defeat me?!
...who burned down Okobore Town?
Oh, gee!
This is fun!
Olin-san, you look beautiful!
That looks good on you!
Thank you all!
Hey!
That's it!
Hey, you...
Kaido's subordinates killed them...
...was named Laugh Tale.
How could you do that to my brother-arinsu?!
Please wait!
Destroy them along with the town!
Are you gonna take in a pervert like him,
Oden-san?!
What's the matter?
You're getting weaker!
Your brother?
Burn it all up!
Damn you!
Laugh Tale...
Forgive me already!
How many times should I apologize?!
I'll make you pay-arinsu! Big Mom!
--Shinobu.
--Yes.
Oden-sama, will you please elaborate on
how you feel today?
I think I must not die.
How dare you hurt Pay-Pay?!
She's coming!
Of course not!
Why are you saying that now?!
This ganmodoki is exquisite!
Okay, let's have Big Mom
beat that woman, too!
Yeah...
What's wrong with you guys?!
You're so creepy these days!
Big Mom's starting to...
The people who helped me
when I lost my memory...
What is it?!
Go after Momonosuke!
Who is it?!
...look like a godness!
Don't worry about me!
Hey!
What?! What is it this time?!
I missed you so much!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Olin-san!
Oh?
Is it over now?
That woman is bad!
What's wrong?! Stay with me!
Kanjuro!
She's the one who did the thing
that made you sad!
That's right!
Raizo runs with that kind of rhythm.
Everyone...
Whatever it is...
Shut up!
I think he has this kind of power...
Everyone in Okobore Town
who was so nice to me...
Cut the crap, Straw Hats!
Ninpo: Blindfold Jutsu! Guess who!
After that tramp, you'll be next!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
I-Is it Kanjuro?
I mean I know you're the only person there.
Clank.
Is that what you're telling me?!
Kaido-sama! We found Momonosuke!
Look out! Duck!
Ulti-chan! Beat her!
I won't forgive you guys!
--I'll be there soon.
--Okay!
Let's take down Big Mom together!
Shut up! Stay there!
After that old bag, you'll be next-arinsu!
Let the whole of Onigashima know, Bao Huang.
Hey! Stop the silly ninpo nonsense...
My battle against Straw Hat is over.
Are you okay?
--What?!
--Olin-chan!
There's no point in doing anything now.
It's over.
Run, Komachiyo!
What's the matter?!
In the end, this is your limit.
Get as far away as possible!
--It's over...
--Don't kill us!
If I need someone
to drop the curtain on my play,
Hey!
I said "Stay there"!
This is perfect!
it should be you!
Zeus!
You guys are cornered rats!
Zeus...
Ulti-Mortar!
Because on the stage...
I feel a surge of power!
The dinosaur guy's coming!
we were... best... friends...
Olin-chan! Kaido's subordinate
is attacking us!
He got eaten...
Kaido?
Go away! We're busy now!
Usohachi-kun! Onami-chan!
We must get away!
Komachiyo!
I've had it with chasing-arinsu...
Keep yelping until you die!
--Otama!
--Hurry up!
Run, Komachiyo!
Usopp!
You can still smile?! Interesting!
Hey, Big Mom!
Yeah!
Don't let them get past you!
Komainu...
Bring it on!
I'll knock you down again and again!
Your speed has given me nothing but trouble!
Did that break a few bones?
Otama, why are you running away?
Go, Komachiyo!
Hey, come here!
Komachiyo...
I won't let you go!
You're badly beaten, poor you...
I see...
Kiku! Kiku!
You're leaving me!
You asked for it!
Kin-sama!
The Marys have already found us here!
I hate those who leave me!
Too slow! This is it!
Just stay down there!
Let's leave before the enemies come!
Don't look at her!
What should I do about the ones I hate?
Damn...
Komachiyo!
Shut up!
Stop it!
I should kill them!
You fools...
Tama...
Komachiyo is my best friend!
What?!
Even in the immoral world of pirates,
Shut up!
Tama!
there's supposed to be
humanity and justice!
K-Kaido!
Otama!
Tama! You okay?!
So you were hiding here, brat!
Shinobu!
Take Momonosuke-sama and run!
I see... While I was unaware...
Otama! Stay with me!
O-Okay!
Hey, Nami! Carry her and beat it!
No, the outcome was obvious
from the beginning...
Damn you!
You're...!
You idiot!
Punk Gibson!
Let's flee for now!
Big Sis!
Get out of my way!
Samurai of the Land of Wano!
You sure did infuse yourself
with the Haki during the battle...
But such a strong weapon
made you cocky, squirt...
It's that way... Big Mom!
I will not!
I cannot let you get past me!
Hey, tramp.
That's Mama! Great! She's alive!
You just messed with my friend.
I'll get rid of you then!
Are you okay, Komachiyo?!
Humans don't give up hope...
No, they just can't give it up...
You hurt my brother...
You must get up!
You shitty lizard!
That's the problem...
How could you do that to Otama?!
Mama!
Are you okay?! Stay with me!
What?!
It's been a long time since I got
this worked up so I screwed up...
W-Wait, Nami! We gotta run!
No!
I should have chopped your head off
and declared victory...
I don't think I can forgive...
Kid!
...people who hit children!
Otherwise...
Captain Kid!
This bastard...
Go away, Straw Hats.
...they'll all keep the false hope
that you're gonna win, won't they?
Kin'emon!
This bastard...
I'll kick her ass right here!
...is my prey!
We can win this!
Momonosuke contemplates Luffy
and Kaido's battle.
Bearing the future of the Land of Wano on his shoulders,
Kaido's destructive power has taken
This is Kid!
We challenged
the Emperors of the Sea to a fight!
down Luffy along with his Color of the Supreme King!
The Animal Kingdom Pirates gain momentum
and upset the Straw Hats!
Luffy confronts the greatest obstacle of all!
Yamato heads out to the battlefield.
You guys should engrave our fierce battles
really far in your memory!
His limit-breaking special attacks
drive Kaido to the wall!
Top officers' fierce onslaughts
gradually drive the Straw Hats to the wall!
Ulti challenges Big Mom
to get her revenge.
Will they be swallowed
by the sea along with Luffy?
Their alliance cracks.
No one can stop the swell of the new era!
On top of that,
the vengeful Kanjuro attacks Momonosuke!
Can his all-out blow with a dream of
becoming the King of the Pirates...
Hate grows as rancor piles up,
and anger ignites a new phase.
After the captain fell, is there still any hope
left in the Land of Wano?
...break open the door to the new era?!
Hurry up, Kin'emon!
On the next episode of One Piece!
Or only despair?!
What is the fate of the Kozuki Clan?!
"A Comprehensive Anatomy! Fierce Fight!
The Five from the New Generation"
On the next episode of One Piece!
On the next episode of One Piece! "The Dawn of
the Land of Wano - The All-Out Battle Heats Up!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy, Defeated! The Straw Hats in Jeopardy?!"
"The Conclusion! Luffy, Accelerating Fist of the Supreme King"
"The Animal Kingdom Pirates Trample Down!
The End of the Kozuki Clan!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates![Events]
[Events]