iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
M-My friends who ate Kibi Dango!
In the castle where the fierce fight
still continues, shocking news has spread.
The news of Luffy's loss
discouraged the samurai.
Luffy was plunged into the sea by Kaido,
I need to ask you all a favor!
Momo!
Kaido-sama choked the life out of him...
but was rescued by the Heart Pirates.
Diable Jambe...
Momo!
Please side with Big Bro Luffy's group...
Luffy?
...and Straw Hat Luffy sank
to the bottom of the dark nighttime sea!
What the hell is this?!
...and Momonosuke-kun's group!
Momo!
Tell them!
M-My friends who ate Kibi Dango!
By Otama's order,
the Gifters who ate Kibi Dango...
On Onigashima,
Otama began to desperately address...
...go at Kaido's troops.
"Fight Against the Dark Night
...the Animal Kingdom Pirates members
who ate Kibi Dango.
Alright, the order's been issued!
The Commander-in-chief
of the Land of Wano Sounds Off"
Everyone!
Let's join the fight!
Luffy will...
Yeah!
Sanji!
The Gifters are acting strange!
...defeat Kaido!
Well done holding on, Chopper.
What are they doing?!
I need to ask you all a favor!
Lu... Luffy has...
Please side with Big Bro Luffy's group...
Master-sama gave a command!
Luffy!
The target is the Animal Kingdom Pirates!
...and Momonosuke-kun's group!
Don't cry, you fool.
Momonosuke's declaration reignited
the samurai's fighting spirit.
What are you guys talking about?!
Luffy!
But...
And take down Kaido with us!
I said,
How many times have we seen...
"Are you okay?" I'm worried!
However...
Luffy...
Have you really been defeated?
Yeah, thank you for your concern...
Straw Hat will defeat me?
Are you dreaming?!
I'm gonna be okay...
...miracles?
This is a mere side effect
of the Rumble Ball...
BABY GEEZER CHOPPER
(SIDE EFFECT OF THE RUMBLE BALL)
Meanwhile, to let Momonosuke flee,
Kin'emon fights Kaido at the risk of his life.
Then what should we...
Certainly, Master-sama!
Not just Luffy!
What should we do?!
We will surely defeat you people, too!
Alright, the order's been issued!
That's not "mere"!
Kaido!
Die gracefully, like a samurai!
Luffy!
Let's join the fight!
Yeah!
Stupid brat...
While all hell breaks loose in the castle,
Sanji clashes with Queen.
This order drastically
changed the tide of the war.
Everyone! Thanks!
Straw Hat's been defeated?!
Son of Judge!
Ripe-Ripe Jutsu!
There's no point in fighting anymore?!
This mechanical cyborg's power!
"A Dramatic Increase of Allies!
Straw Hats Fight Back!"
Bao Huang's announcement...
Watch closely!
...terribly upset the samurai soldiers who
were working together to take down Kaido.
Come to think of it,
I heard a rumor a long time ago...
It's always hard to believe...
You all!
Please side with Big Bro Luffy's group...
...that a member of CP9, the Government's
secret intelligence agency, escaped from prison.
"Nami's Lethal Attack!
Otama's Desperate Challenge!"
The straw hat man? No way...
...and Momonosuke-kun's group!
What about Momonosuke-sama?!
It's strange...
...that an intelligence agent
was imprisoned.
Luffy won't be defeated that easily!
...that you're defeated!
The escaped agent...
That's right!
Don't underestimate our captain!
And Momonosuke declares!
Yes, that's me!
The voice I heard from the sea...
Luffy is alive!
Jimbei learned about
Who's-Who's surprising past.
Side with?!
So that was you!
Big Bro Luffy!
I went through a lot.
Straw Hat Luffy!
He is talking to me
saying he will be back!
Big Bro Luffy!
Because of one single screw-up
13 years ago...
And take down Kaido with us!
Kaido?!
Didn't you proudly say...
So...!
So keep fighting!
...you're a member of the Straw Hats?
Maybe it's too late.
Hamlet-sama?! What's the matter?
Yes, I am the helmsman of the Straw Hats!
Even if it is painful and hard!
Don't say that!
Calm down!
Hamlet-sama?
Go under him and let him hang on the deck!
Straw Hat...
All right!
And then the flying Onigashima...
That name reminds me of my bitter past.
Aye-aye, sir!
I am sorry...
Master-sama!
...but fight as long as you live!
13 years ago,
Hurry up, hurry up!
a Devil Fruit that was being transported
on a Government ship was stolen.
Hurry up. Be careful.
Watch me in action!
"Believe in Luffy!
The Alliance's Counterattack Begins!"
...finally reaches the sky
above the mainland of the Land of Wano.
And two years ago, when Straw Hat Luffy
rose to prominence,
Yes, good job! Very nice!
ONIGASHIMA REACHES THE SKY
ABOVE THE MAINLAND OF THE LAND OF WANO
Hamlet-sama is going crazy!
I was shocked...
Momo!
Because that stolen Gum-Gum Fruit...
No, I'm not...
Rapid ascension!
I just woke up...
...was eaten by him!
Momo!
FOURTH FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
BIG CAT CAFE
Ever since I ate that dumpling from Speed,
I feel like I've been boosted!
Tell them!
Momo!
"The Pride of a Helmsman ?
The Enraged Jimbei!"
I will surely...
Here.
What the hell is this?!
It's tough, isn't it, Jimbei?
...defeat Kaido!
It's amazing!
Like I said, it's too late.
I told you not to say that!
We're gonna attack you
in greater numbers now.
Captain's not here
so we don't know what to do!
Please side with us!
I'm at my best!
Come on!
Let's clear his lungs!
Just give up already!
You guys have lost!
And take down Kaido with us!
One, two!
Komachiyo...
He'll be okay.
I don't know how,
You're right.
A child?
but you brought the strongest rookies
you could think of in the world now!
Move!
Hurry up, Horselina-chan!
What is she talking about?!
I got it, Master-sama!
She must be nuts!
Everyone!
They're not weak!
It's just that Kaido-sama...
I got you, Master-sama!
The Headliners and
the Gifters' insurrection was initiated...
...is too strong!
What?!
...by the command from the girl
on the Performance Floor.
Isn't that a little too violent?
There she is!
Should be fine.
Luffy will...
Ya-hoo!
Kill that brat!
He's rubber.
I won't let you do that!
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei!
Leave the spectators to me!
The Akazaya samurai and even Luffytaro-san
were defeated...
We'll protect Master-sama!
Okay!
...surely...
Not okay!
What's gonna happen now?
Beat the shit out of Who's-Who!
Maybe it's too late as I said...
Scorpion Death Needle!
Captain, help!
Poker! You...!
Look at yourselves! Prepare to die!
SECOND FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Let me help you, samurai!
I won't let you touch Master-sama!
I-It's... so... so...
...defeat Kaido!
Daifugo-kun!
So high!
No one but Straw Hat will win!
Leave Komachiyo to us!
Slicing Rounds!
Momonosuke-sama! I'm with you!
This is the second floor inside the castle.
The Gifters changed sides.
You sure?! Thank you!
Don't worry!
Count on my ninpo!
Kappa Style!
Both of you, Daifugo-kun and
Gazelle-man-kun, please be careful!
Ninpo: Great Kite!
RIVER OF RETRIBUTION
River of Retribution!
NIN
You're both...
Even if Straw Hat is dead,
don't give up until we defeat Kaido!
That's odd...
...precious friends to me!
I wonder what happened...
But...
Straw Hat's death isn't confirmed yet!
Ninpo: Great Kite is
one of the ninpo I'm best at!
I need to ask you all a favor!
Friends...
Master-sama!
But the hint of it
is enough to crush morale...
Please side with us!
All right!
Mm-hm...
Yeah, there's no way
to find out the truth!
Let's land somewhere safe first!
Kidnap the brat!
Make her undo the spell!
Master-sama gave a command!
How dare you all...
The target is the Animal Kingdom Pirates!
Wait for us, Komachiyo!
...think you're losing!
Here's a counterattack!
Momonosuke-sama,
Onigashima is heading towards the capital...
You heard him!
What are you guys talking about?!
Don't stop fighting!
Whoa-whoa-whoa,
are you gonna fight amongst yourselves?!
That was scary...
What an incredible ability.
I guess I managed to escape.
Oh, well.
Yeah, you can't usually make friends
on battlefields.
I can't ask for a better situation!
But...
Momonosuke-sama,
you're as great as I thought!
...what is going on?!
PERFORMANCE FLOOR, INSIDE THE DOME
Are they... Are they all okay?!
I'm truly impressed!
I'm gonna cut you into pieces!
I'm not gonna be worried.
Hey Nami, speaking of which,
You're the real Shogun of the Land of Wano!
Luffy!
Kiku! Kin'emon!
will you make me an attendant like before?
Everyone!
What are you talking about?! No!
What?!
Then, a servant is fine.
Luffy...
Aren't they the same?
Don't cry...
Then, a henchman?
You fools!
I don't need one.
You gotta fight, fight more!
Are you satisfied now, son of Oden?
Then, a pet. Meow, meow!
I'm impressed, Otama-chan!
Raccoon-san.
Not cute.
We barely succeeded escaping from Kaido...
Hey! Have you gone mad?!
Gah!
It can't be helped.
I was toying with you
because you were so high-spirited!
W-W-Where's Kin'emon?!
I did a bad thing to you.
He was just a loser
who couldn't even buy any time...
But if the island falls
on Flower Capital...
Your shepherd was killed
and you've become panic-stricken!
What should I do?!
...the Land of Wano could end.
Boss! What's going on?!
What can I do to win your trust?!
Are they taking sides with us?!
I have a present for you, sheep.
You know what to do.
Yes, it seems so.
Was her name Otama?
She did an incredible thing!
Lick!
Take her down!
Pay-Pay got beaten up because of you!
This is definitely as good as
a million reinforcements!
Get this straight, Zeus!
If you hold back, I'll wipe you out!
Didn't you hear me say "Stop"?!
Not that attack again!
Apocalyptic Candy Shower!
No!
You did it, Otama!
What?
I'm sorry, Nami!
Onami-chan.
The baton can do that?!
That was amazing, Tama!
Everyone heard your words!
Rest in peace!
Nami, use it as usual! I'll assist you!
Momonosuke-sama, are you hurt?
And they acted on them!
Her skin is too hard!
Kin'emon got...
But her insides are messed up
by Mama's attack!
I don't need a servant,
a henchman, or a pet...
Mm-hm! Mm-hm!
I can't take it anymore!
There's no escape!
It was well worth the effort, Otama!
We can take her down by a Lightning Blast!
Thank you, Onami-chan!
No! That's too destructive!
How about a partner?
You're the Commander-in-chief
of the samurai, right?
Mm-hm!
Nami!
You must give up too,
you cowardly monster!
The operation was a huge success!
You have to accept your death with dignity...
Yay! A huge success!
Otama will get hurt, too!
All right! Now the tide has turned!
Your meat looks so tender!
Black Kabuto...
Don't tell me that brat did something!
There they are! The Straw Hats!
I need your help...
Go away!
Diable Jambe...
I'm Nami's partner!
I'll kill you fools!
Special Attack Green Star!
There's no place to go.
Sargasso!
The last man of the Kozuki Clan
will die sinking into the sea...
I separated them! Do it, Nami!
Leave them to me!
Oh, no!
I'm gonna take them down!
Just like Straw Hat!
Weather Egg!
Come on out, thundercloud!
There is no hope!
Straw Hat will defeat me?
I'm gonna fight for Nami from today.
Okay!
And the Land of Wano will open up?
...Rotisserie...
Otama!
You've got yourself
an incredible power, too...
Zeus?!
Oh, gee! Run!
They'll all live happily ever after?
Not exactly!
...Strike!
Good luck, partner!
Are you dreaming?!
So Nami, give me a new name!
What?
I will...
She totally has him
wrapped around her little finger...
...surely defeat Kaido!
Go to hell!
Take down Kaido!
What?! What is it?!
The end!
Lead Master-sama
and the Straw Hats to victory!
Tell me now!
Not just Luffy!
We will surely defeat you people, too!
Ha...
Fluff!
No way!
Stupid brat...
About 2,000 have changed sides.
Collier Strike!
GUEST PARLOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa!
The number of troops who were blindsided
and taken down by them is 2,000!
Momonosuke-sama!
When we die, we die together!
Wait a minute!
I'm Zeus!
Lick!
That means the Animal Kingdom Pirates
that had 30,000
Nami's right-hand man! Prepare yourself!
Ripe-Ripe Jutsu!
at the beginning and then 20,000...
Let's go, Zeus!
...lost 2,000 to the other side
and another 2,000 to injury,
Damn you...
Damn you!
Son of Judge!
so their force shrank more.
Ulti!
The game of tag with you...
...will end with this!
16,000 vs. 9,000!
Don't ever say that name again!
Sanji!
Well done holding on, Chopper.
It was 30,000 vs. 5,400 at the beginning.
Were you a member of
the mad scientist team, too?
Lightning Blast!
The gap between forces
is much smaller now...
Lu... Luffy has...
You mean MADS?
That was a long time ago.
If the Gifters rampage more,
there'll be more white playing pieces.
Momonosuke...
Don't cry, you fool.
I don't care which side will win,
...fell, as well!
Yeah!
The enemy's de facto leader is dead!
but we have to make sure
to confirm that guy's death...
But...
No...
How many times have we seen...
Is it really him?
If we announce it to all of Onigashima,
This is it...
It seems so.
the damn samurai will lose their morale
this time for sure!
Either way,
the information that he stole is now old.
You're right! Let's crush their spirits!
No, it's not!
My job...
It poses no threat to the Government.
...is to hit my target!
Big Bro! He's alive!
...miracles?
No, it's not good to have the precedent...
Let's keep making for
the stage on the Performance Floor, Nami!
...that you can escape
from the organization and still live.
Look at my body!
Uh-huh! And she'll give a command there
to those who were forced to eat Kibi Dango!
Well, only if he can survive...
As a matter of fact,
Damn...
He's fighting against...
I'm a cyborg!
Damn...
Yeah! Then we can turn
the whole thing around! Right, Tama?!
...the mighty Jimbei.
Damn!
I noticed that a long time ago!
--Oh, no!
--Queen's Man-Beast Form!
What?
Uh-huh!
I'm just glad that Big Bro is alive!
Look after him.
What? Whoa!
Get back!
What? Sanji! What's this?
Luffy's doing his best!
We gotta do so, too!
It doesn't matter that you noticed
if you can't beat me!
Once he recovers,
he'll have the strength of 10 men.
You're a former CP9 agent...
Yeah!
I'm happy for Straw Hat!
Why did you become a pirate?
Of 2,000 men!
--Uh-huh!
--I'm happy for myself, too!
What?! Zoro?!
You saved me, Nami!
Chopper, will Mosshead be alright?
Are you insinuating I've fallen?
So have you.
What? Who is it?
Ulti-sama has been taken down!
I'm here!
What?!
You won fame as
a Warlord of the Sea at that time,
Mm-hm...
Don't tell me you're the Climate Baton?
He...
Leave the dinosaur to me!
Following Page One-sama!
but now you're working
under a brat like that.
He's gonna be okay... Sanji.
What's this?
Two members of the Tobi Roppo
have been defeated!
The Climate Baton...
Are you the one who did it?!
Hey, are you okay?
...talked!
Judge's son!
So you're holding a grudge against Luffy?
What?!
It's so cute!
Even your voice is trembling!
No way!
That's never happened before!
He doesn't stop fighting at all...
What did you say?
Because you failed to guard
the Gum-Gum Fruit 13 years ago,
Don't tell me we're losing!
Straw Hat will defeat Kaido?
Can you say that again?
His captain is dead...
Why does he keep fighting?
Bao Huang-sama,
all of Onigashima heard you!
Is that some kind of a joke?
I said,
and were imprisoned...
Do you care about
that rubber fool so much?
"Are you okay?" I'm worried!
Oh, no!
To be exact, I'm holding a grudge against
the one who stole the Gum-Gum Fruit from us,
I announced it by accident!
I just wanted to take him out myself.
Yeah, thank you for your concern...
which is "Red-Haired" Shanks!
That wasn't true! I take it back!
But if he fell into the sea,
I'm sure he's dead by now!
I'm gonna be okay...
So that one works as a transmitter!
That's why I like you guys...
Shanks!
BABY GEEZER CHOPPER
(SIDE EFFECT OF THE RUMBLE BALL)
This is a mere side effect
of the Rumble Ball...
That asshole screwed up my life!
Then...!
What?
WIND
Special Attack Green Star!
Damn!
Moon Walk!
After working together for a long time,
Devil!
That's not "mere"!
I have an odd feeling
he'll manage to survive.
Fang Pistol!
What?! What is it?!
Trafalgar!
Another one on my kill list shows up...
What's this monster?!
Son of Judge!
Shut up!
You guys are such nuisances!
This mechanical cyborg's power!
Hey, Tama!
You have no place in the new era
that I'm gonna create!
I don't know how it works
but that one is a transmitter!
The straw hat
that he was wearing at that time,
Watch closely!
Kin'emon!
You old-time pirate!
Your order will echo
throughout the island!
and the Gum-Gum Fruit
were inherited by that kid,
W-What did you say?!
Speak!
so of course, he became my target!
Uh-huh!
You got the wrong sow by the ear.
After what happened 13 years ago,
I got locked up and went through hell.
Dr. Chopper!
I've had enough, too...
Wait...
Meanwhile, he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Yes, I am Chopper.
How could you always disturb me
when I try to learn something or do something...
and was making a name for himself.
Wait!
A side effect?
I need you guys to go away!
So what?!
We're already in the new era!
I...
You only care about yourself?!
And he came to the Land of Wano
so nonchalantly.
I'm Otama!
Wait...
Trafalgar, are you here to interfere?!
You have to...
And you call yourself a pirate?!
Our enemy is Big Mom.
How could I not bother him?!
A child?!
What?!
...fight...
Grow up, Eustass-ya...
The enemies you guys will face hereafter...
Otama-chan?!
But he was just an overconfident brat.
Why's she here on Onigashima?!
...can't be beaten in three minutes!
...me!
He was defeated by Kaido-san easily!
There she is! Master-sama!
Let's form a temporary alliance.
If you say
"Oh, I'm scared of the side effect,"
you can't even protect your dear playmates,
kiddo! Do you understand?
Luffy will return.
I know he will!
I will not...
Take a risk!
He fought against Kaido-san.
There's no way he'll return!
You were so huge before...
...allow you to...
The Rumble Ball with a longer
gigantification time... How severe...
...lay a finger...
...on Momonosuke-sama!
Becoming a geezer and a baby
at the same time was unexpected...
What is a child...
I used it fully aware of the risk...
Don't die, Straw Hat!
...doing on the battlefield?!
I thought if I could fight in that form
for a while,
Momonosuke-sama...
He looks pale...
What happened, Bao Huang?!
I could take down Queen...
His pulse is weak!
Who are you?!
We gotta do something!
Drink up!
Sing!
FLOWER CAPITAL, LAND OF WANO
Raccoon!
Otama!
Luffy is alive!
Tama, get it together!
Rumble!
Monster Point!
If that's true, I'll just kill him.
Go!
After I kill you!
What?!
If you're gonna mess with our captain,
I'm not a raccoon!
"These are serious criminals
who rebelled against...
I've got to take you down right here!
...Shogun Orochi
and Supreme Commander Kaido...
That's...
That guy... I think there are still
tons of abilities he hasn't shown...
You don't complain even a bit, Jimbei!
...to overthrow the country..."
...my duty!
Why is a man of your stature
so devoted to him?
At first, it was 5,000 vs. 30,000!
The Land of Wano really
fell into Kaido and Orochi's hands...
You'll never understand!
Of course, you have many more men than us.
I know I can't fight you one-on-one.
That's my Sanji.
Have mercy on me!
You're seeing the situation clearly!
We were sent to the future
with Toki-sama's special power,
The way he fights fascinates me...
Take me with you!
I can help you for sure!
How annoying!
It's our job not to let you top officers
go unchecked!
Miyagi, how is Zoro doing?
and we're looking just the way Orochi
knew us, exactly as these posters.
I was arrested because
I objected to the war!
It's unbelievable!
He must have 20 to 30 bones broken,
but his breathing and pulse are steady.
I wanna save Ace-san, too!
So please!
They keep coming...
So the enemy could come get us
at any moment...
Let me die for him!
However, if he keeps on fighting,
it'll endanger his life.
I know that it's painful now, Luffy,
but you have to bottle up those feelings!
Their numbers won't decline!
That's not what I want to hear.
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
VASSAL KANJURO     KOZUKI MOMONOSUKE
VASSAL KIN'EMON     VASSAL RAIZO
Don't just think about
the ones you've lost!
Zoro! Leave it to me.
You can't get back what you've lost!
Momonosuke-sama.
What is it that you still have?!
No matter how desperately
you challenge us,
It's draining even to speak.
I still have my friends!
Let me humbly suggest you...
in the end it's a game of numbers.
Get on with it...
...call me...
That's what an all-out war is!
Hey, Jimbei.
..."Father" from today!
He fell asleep...
I guess any more stress
will cost him his life...
KOZUKI ODEN
Don't blame me...
It's gorgeous, isn't it, Otoko?
He can't fight anymore?
Mm-hm!
The Fire Festival is
for the repose of the deceased...
Call you "Father"?
We build a fire to reach heaven.
That is right!
Join...
Th-There they come, the Gifters!
There's one good drug
to inject him with.
...my crew!
I do not want them...
We're in trouble!
Dr. Miyagi!
I think Zoro-san should rest like this!
Let me bring up...
We're the elite corps of the Gifters!
KOZUKI ODEN
I do not want them to know
that you are Oden-sama's son!
...the rear!
I wonder if Daddy is looking at it.
Wait. Let's hear it!
Is it true that the Pleasures and Waiters
on this floor...
I'll pull it off and come back alive!
We, Minks, have...
They could come after you
at any moment now.
Yeah, of course.
...revolted against Queen-sama?!
I mean, there is a medicine
that's been handed down in Zou.
The sky is really clear...
Yes, it is!
Don't forget, Jimbei!
They said they were getting back at him
for sacrificing them with Ice Oni!
Please understand!
It's a drug that heals
even the most severe wounds in no time,
I'm your captain now!
Okay. I am counting on you, Kin'emon...
so it could be called a super-healer.
How stupid!
I won't stop the ship!
They're expendable,
why are they being so cocky?
Can he even return to combat?
I'm sure he's watching over you
and the fate of this country...
I'll be waiting for you at the Land of Wano!
Come at any cost!
Thank you, Momonosuke-sama!
Yes, temporarily...
Washed-up trash should be
beaten up and kicked out!
In exchange,
So call me "Father," Momonosuke-sama.
Get rid of the traitors on the floor!
the side effects later will cause him
to suffer twice as much as he does now...
Thank you!
Don't die no matter what!
I can do it, Kin'emon!
Twice?!
Still calling each other by "sama" and his name...
You two haven't changed at all!
I want him to fight...
But can his body take
that severe side effect?
Gorilla Punch Punch!
GORILLA PUNCH PUNCH
--Jimbei!
--Jimbei-san!
Uh-huh!
Boss!
Jimbei!
Damn! I've made it this far!
Oh, it's going to be so hard!
I don't know...
I can't administer it at my discretion...
Thank you for indulging me!
New ones?
Momonosuke, Momonosuke,
Momonosuke...
Oh, no! We're now in a pinch
due to unbalanced forces!
Just do it!
Luffy! I came back alive
as I promised you!
GUEST PARLOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
...sama.
Momonosuke, Momonosuke,
Momonosuke...
Were you listening?
Don't be afraid, Tama!
I'm glad I made it in time for the battle!
Even after they lost Straw Hat Luffy,
There's no time to debate.
...sama.
We got your back!
Momonosuke! Momonosuke!
Momonosuke...
Just give me the drug!
none of them surrendered.
I'm... I'm...
CIPHER POL "AIGIS" ZERO
WORLD'S MOST POWERFUL INTELLIGENCE AGENCY
...sama.
Are you sure?
Momonosuke! Momonosuke!
Momonosuke...
...gonna fight, too!
After the super-healing effectiveness is gone,
I'll fight.
Yes, the current situation is...
...sama.
you'll have to suffer
twice as much as you are now!
Momonosuke, Momonosuke,
Momonosuke...
Big Bro is getting hurt so much
and going through a lot of pain...
...a total of 5,000 men on both sides
incapable of fighting.
As the helmsman of the Straw Hats!
...sama.
Momonosuke, Momonosuke,
Momonosuke...
I don't care!
...but he still fights...
The Animal Kingdom Pirates had 24,000
fit for combat and the rebels had 3,000.
...sama.
Momonosuke! Momonosuke!
Momonosuke...
...for all of us!
...sama.
No matter what happens to my body later,
You are adding "sama" in an undertone...
Don't set the bar too low!
if I can't fight now, what's the point?!
However, all of the Pleasures and Waiters
on the Performance Floor...
I'll make it your everyday life!
...turned against Queen-sama,
By the time we leave this country,
I don't see any improvement!
The Headliners and the Gifters
who went over to the samurai army...
so 4,000 troops changed sides.
I'll make it a place where
you can eat as much as you want!
20 THOUSAND    7 THOUSAND
As a result,
the Animal Kingdom Pirates have 20,000,
Mo... Mo...
...number about 300!
It is so hard for me to say!
and the rebels have 7,000.
Looks like I overestimated you.
The order from the girl who got
on the stage at the Performance Floor...
I didn't expect to see the gap
between strengths diminishing now...
And everyone else...
Get it together, Kin...
Fang Pistol!
...is fighting very hard as well!
...very likely affected them
in some way!
The situation is totally unpredictable.
F-Father...
And we've already got information
that can change the situation...
Should I take that role?!
There she is!
That brat!
SECOND FLOOR - NAMI, USOPP, AND OTAMA
Father! I know it is hard,
but that is too terrible!
They came!
Usopp, hurry up!
How dare she use such a strange trick!
Maybe I'm too much of a genius
to realize it myself?!
If we kill her, will those
who are being manipulated wake up?!
Even with your Color of Arms,
you can't block them?
It talked!
The Climate Baton that I created!
Oh, no! They're after Tama!
That was a good decision.
They can chew up ordinary Color of Arms.
How dare they target a child!
They can't call themselves pirates!
No, can't you see?!
It's me! Formerly known as Zeus!
I didn't know you could
move so fast on land, Jimbei.
How did you become the Climate Baton?!
I'll defend Otama!
You were eaten earlier!
Onami-chan!
Even though you're a Fish-Man.
Usopp! I'll kick their asses first
so go ahead!
At that moment...
Father...
Nami! Run!
My goodness... Nowadays, it's out of style
to discriminate against the Fish-Men.
This is my way of life!
I'll do my best, too!
Here comes a headliner!
Zeus!
Scorpion...
Don't get so mad.
I'll... I'll...
Let's talk peacefully.
...Death Needle!
...fight along everyone!
What?
Poison!
Father...
--Poison!
--What?
I'm already running out of energy...
That brat! She's still there?!
I wanna ask you something.
What?!
You're doomed.
You guys are already poisoned.
Unfortunately, I'm not willing to have
small talk with you!
My spirit was leaving my body
before I knew it...
Hey, drag her down already!
Yes, sir! Leave it to us!
What if I chew up some of your limbs?
Now eat him, Hera!
--Let's go!
--Yeah!
Ow!
--You can do it, Otama!
--Go for it!
Daifugo-kun, thank you!
Will you answer me honestly then?
Father!
I was just about to be consumed
by the girl named Hera while in a daze...
Yay!
M-My friends who ate Kibi Dango!
Momonosuke!
Iron Body!
I need to ask you all a favor!
Master-sama!
Please side with Big Bro Luffy's group...
Here are Black Balls out of pity!
Keep living!
The operation was a huge success,
Master-sama!
You don't have to worry
about anything anymore!
Eat them and run!
Prepare yourself, Jimbei!
Now, get on my back!
...and Momonosuke-kun's group!
Horselina-chan,
thank you for coming!
Zeus!
Let's hope that everybody else
is okay, too!
Nami stretched out the Climate Baton
towards me at that moment...
Fang Flash!
You, too!
Thank you!
I'm exhausted from all the running!
Eat them, Zeus!
Now,
And take down Kaido with us!
Wake up!
let's keep living, Momonosuke!
I'm gonna eat you! Zeus-senpai!
What?!
Both of you, hang onto me firmly!
And it seems like when Hera bit me,
I was pressed into this Climate Baton.
Uh-huh.
Take me, too! If you can!
I'm begging you!
Master-sama!
And look!
Momonosuke... sama...
I was born again!
What?! My weapon is annoying me!
Gazelle-man-kun!
Fish-Man Jiu-Jitsu!
I just saw Komachiyo down over there!
Low Tide...
What the hell was that?!
Oh, yeah! She hasn't forgiven me yet!
What?!
...Shoulder Throw!
There's no way that
the Animal Kingdom Pirates...
Ulti-Mortar!
Of course not! You tried to kill me!
What's the point of stalling for time?
...will act on some brat's order!
Just get out already!
What's gonna change by fleeing?
But I can't get out of here
without Mama's power...
Komachiyo...
Water Shot!
Shave!
Run! Shinobu!
Certainly, Master-sama!
Please get away safely, Momonosuke-sama!
My pleasure!
Take down Kaido!
Ouch...
Oh, hey! There's the stage!
Momonosuke!
Gee... You're merciless...
A rebellion?
Damn you!
--Tama! Give a command from there!
--Okay!
Father!
Have you gone mad?!
Changing sides?
Announcement to all of Onigashima!
Briscola-san, what's the matter?
You must keep living.
Hey, you...
Let's beat up those traitors already!
The enemy's leader Momo...
Listen to me for a minute...
Bao Huang-sama,
the Straw Hats are behind you!
Kaido!
Die gracefully, like a samurai!
That's easily done, Master-sama!
I don't know what's happening...
Oh, Usohachi-kun!
Gorilla Punch Punch!
GORILLA PUNCH PUNCH
When I was behind bars, I heard this story.
--Ulti-Mortar!
--What?!
...but it's time to get serious.
For Master-sama!
FOR MASTER-SAMA
Usopp!
Alright, the order's been issued!
As I received severe punishment,
Daifugo! Gazelle-man!
I was mockingly told to pray for salvation.
In the end,
it's all because of this brat, right?!
Blade Pistol!
Let's join the fight!
Fish-Man Karate!
To the "Sun God" Nika!
Yeah!
Otama!
Because of her, our subordinates
betrayed us one after another!
Arabesque Brick Fist!
Leave it to me, Master-sama!
He is a legendary warrior of ancient times
who slaves believed...
The Gifters are acting strange!
Shave!
I can't believe
she even manipulated Big Mom!
What are they doing?!
She still got up
after taking that deadly attack?!
It's always hard to believe...
Tempest Kick!
...would free them one day.
Take down Kaido! Let's go!
I don't know if he really existed.
--Hera!
--Yes, Mama!
Guys, follow me!
--Prometheus!
--Yeah, Mama!
A warrior who would make you laugh
and put you out of your misery.
--Napoleon!
--Yes, Mama!
Imprisonment felt like forever,
Let's go!
Shave!
Our strengths!
...that you're defeated!
so I hung on to this strange legend.
We use them all for Master-sama!
Tempest Kick!
Thinking "I don't care who it is.
Just help me!"
And this is "Iron Body," right?
What does that have to do with me?
Kin'emon...
I heard that the Sun Pirates
you once led had members...
Combine!
That is the style of combat
the Government agents use...
Ouch!
Maser Cannon!
...who used to be slaves!
Everyone! Thanks!
...called the Six Powers.
Do not cry!
The history of the Fish-Men
is a history of slavery, right?!
Let's do it again!
Kaido!
Even if it is hard, get up.
Come to think of it,
I heard a rumor a long time ago...
Momonosuke!
You know something, don't you?
Pay-Pay got beaten up because of you!
Hang in there!
Tell me, Jimbei!
...that a member of CP9, the Government's
secret intelligence agency, escaped from prison.
Didn't you hear me say "Stop"?!
It's "Father" to you!
Yamato!
What? A frog?
The guard who told me about Nika...
It's strange...
I'm here to cut ties with you!
Momonosuke-sama! Why?!
What?
...that an intelligence agent
was imprisoned.
...was later executed!
The baton can do that?!
So you came to cut ties
between father and son...
I need to tell them...
Nami, use it as usual! I'll assist you!
How could you remember such an incident?
I thought I was in danger too,
so I broke out risking my life and I'm here now!
Her skin is too hard!
I need to tell them...
But her insides are messed up
by Mama's attack!
I can hear...
I can hear a voice...
We can take her down by a Lightning Blast!
Is it dangerous just to know?
No! That's too destructive!
That's laughable...
Luffy's voice!
I can't help but be curious.
What do you have?
Tell me what you know!
Straw Hat has sunk into the sea...
Otama will get hurt, too!
Momo!
Finger Pistol!
The escaped agent...
Momo!
So has Kozuki Oden's son...
Spots!
Yes, that's me!
Black Kabuto...
Luffy?
I need your help...
Do we know each other?
There, there, there, there!
If you have the will to fight,
you should've protected what you needed to!
Momo!
Tell them!
I'll kill you fools!
No, but I saw you once!
Neither Luffy nor Momonosuke-kun
is the one I needed to protect!
Special Attack Green Star!
You know a lot about slaves, don't you?!
When I was in CP9...
Sargasso!
Because you're a Fish-Man!
You were one of the Seven Warlords
of the Sea at that time!
I separated them! Do it, Nami!
They're...
Tell me, Jimbei!
Okay!
...the ones I fight alongside!
We both have
totally different positions now.
They're the ones who will take you down
and lead the Land of Wano to its dawn!
I'm happy with who I am now...
I am...
...Kozuki Momonosuke!
You snot-nosed brat...
...but I went through a lot.
That must be...
Are you gonna cut ties
and get out of here?!
Momonosuke-sama!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Because of one single screw-up
13 years ago...
Yeah! I'm gonna set out to sea with Luffy!
Fish-Man Karate!
Whose voice?
Shark Grip!
I was told that I was
as promising as the brilliant Rob Lucci!
I'm sure I heard a voice!
After I kick you out of this country!
Don't scare me! We're in the sea!
I am going to tell you...
Kaido!
I have nothing to tell you!
Kick me out?
That voice sounded familiar!
I think that has nothing to do with me...
...Luffy's words!
That's right!
You can pirate elsewhere, right?
Is he crying?
Let's just check... Head towards
the point where he heard the voice!
Shut up! Just listen!
But Luffytaro was defeated by Kaido...
Why did you get so pissed
all of a sudden?!
--Someone's there!
--What?!
Let me hollow you out! Fang Pistol!
Luffy is alive!
Someone's really there!
Fang Pistol!
Hey, isn't that Straw Hat?!
He is talking to me
saying he will be back!
How can you hear a voice in the sea?!
Who cares! Just rescue him!
It can't be elsewhere, Yamato!
Hurry up! Is he alive?!
So...!
I've never seen
the Six Powers like that...
So keep fighting!
What's going on?!
I feel pity for you,
but again, that has nothing to do with me.
I'm staying here
because this is the Land of Wano!
Fish-Man Karate Secret Art!
Even if it is painful and hard!
Damn!
That's not really true!
There's no way you can beat me!
Didn't you proudly say...
Where are you?!
Hey, my tail!
...you're a member of the Straw Hats?
I am sorry...
Demon Brick Fist!
...but fight as long as you live!
Become the Shogun of the Land of Wano,
Yamato!
Yes, I am the helmsman of the Straw Hats!
If it's Momonosuke-sama's order...
Straw Hat...
I refuse!
We'll fight as long as we live!
I know I can't beat you!
That name reminds me of my bitter past.
Mm-hm!
But...
...Luffy is the man
Kozuki Oden was waiting for!
13 years ago,
Momo!
a Devil Fruit that was being transported
on a Government ship was stolen.
Until he returns,
Momo!
You bastard!
If you wanna nose into history,
Kaido!
And two years ago, when Straw Hat Luffy
rose to prominence,
Tell them!
I'm gonna keep you here!
Momo!
you better be prepared for
what you're stepping into!
I will surely...
Don't expect me to go easy on you!
I was shocked...
Because that stolen Gum-Gum Fruit...
It's "Father" to you!
...defeat Kaido!
Yamato!
...was eaten by him!
I'm here to cut ties with you!
Endless resentment towards Straw Hat!
Samurai hold out
on the battlefield without Luffy!
To cut ties with Kaido,
Yamato unleashes his true power.
The all-out war between unbalanced forces!
Unexpected reinforcements!
Attacks from the Gifters who changed sides
due to Otama's power upset the Tobi Roppo!
Who's-Who unleashes a fierce attack,
mentioning his grudge against Shanks.
To find a way out of the close battle,
Nami's mighty thunderbolt blasts!
Kid stands up to Big Mom!
Franky intercepts Sasaki's tricky attacks
with the spirit of steel.
His provocations that trample on
the dignity of his friend sets off Jimbei.
Queen takes secret measures,
but Sanji and the others won't back down!
Law burns with an inner fighting spirit!
When elite troops of Kaido's army surge in,
When unwavering resolves come together
in the face of adversity,
Challenge the rampaging
mighty enemies boldly!
Otama's undaunted command echoes
all over the island and turns the tide of the war!
The changing tide of the war reignites
the samurai's flame of faith that was almost lost!
With his loyalty to Luffy and the pride
of the Sun Pirates at stake,
Extraordinary, super do-or-die
contests now begin!
a new power is born
that will break through the status quo!
his Fish-Man Karate unfurls!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Nami's Lethal Attack! Otama's Desperate Challenge!"
"Showdown Battles of the Monsters! Yamato and Franky"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Dramatic Increase of Allies! Straw Hats Fight Back!"
"The Pride of a Helmsman ? The Enraged Jimbei!"
"Believe in Luffy!
The Alliance's Counterattack Begins!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
[Events]