Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
The fierce battle continues on Onigashima!
Nami and Usopp run through the battlefield
protecting Otama.
"Clutch!
A Demon Incarnate, Robin!"
Dominate it by forcing its people to labor!
Hurry up, Horselina-chan!
Down on the ground, the resuscitated Luffy
is devouring meat and regaining his strength.
I got it, Master-sama!
Mari-Apprehend!
TOKAGE PORT, UDON
MARI-APPREHEND
Anyway, I can't believe
you had this much food!
There she is!
Ooaa-ay...
TRA-GUY
Kill that brat!
...iw aaiu!!
IS ALIVE!!
And Momonosuke asks Shinobu
to do something for him.
The Onigashima battle gets intense!
I won't let you do that!
I won't let you open the borders!
I have to take Luffy there!
We'll protect Master-sama!
Can you endure it?
So I want to go to Onigashima again!
Scorpion Death Needle!
What?!
Sparkle!
Meanwhile, Robin was fighting Black Maria
in the castle, however...
Why... are you saying
such a ridiculous thing?!
I'll never let you go
to a dangerous place like that again!
I won't let you touch Master-sama!
Mom...
Don't be shy. Come on.
Bulle-Triceratops!
Daifugo-kun!
Yes.
I might be able to become...
Come to me!
Leave Komachiyo to us!
I'm your mother.
...a bigger dragon that way!
Come here.
Illusion Mist...
You sure?! Thank you!
Damn you!
Sweet memories ruin you.
I am begging you!
I got you!
D-Don't do that, Momonosuke-sama!
Both of you, Daifugo-kun and
Gazelle-man-kun, please be careful!
General...
Please, Shinobu!
...Suplex!
Nice.
Are you my mom?!
With your Ripe-Ripe Jutsu,
Now, how should I torment you?
You're both...
If only Captain were here!
...precious friends to me!
make me grow older...
What else can we do?!
Straw Hat!
What an incredible ability.
Please... make me grow older...
Straw Hat!
I'm sorry I've left you alone
for a long time.
Yeah, you can't usually make friends
on battlefields.
Straw Hat!
Hey!
Make me grow older!
I'm a fighter.
The Animal Kingdom Pirates keep losing their
troops to the power of Otama's Kibi Dango.
Meanwhile, Robin and Brook
made remarkable gains.
I won't...
Tres Mano!
Freesia!
...go easy on women, either!
Demonio Fleur.
Meat!
Jimbei and Who's-Who fight a deadly battle
in one corner of castle.
There are the people who truly need me,
What?!
Give me meat!
How come the Illusion Mist...
As I received severe punishment,
and rely on me!
I was mockingly told to pray for salvation.
How come it didn't work?
And for those people, I would even...
"The Predator's Trap -
Black Maria's Temptation"
To the "Sun God" Nika!
I decided to live...
Oiran...
...Knuckles!
...alongside my friends.
OIRAN KNUCKLES
...turn into a demon!
He is a legendary warrior of ancient times
who slaves believed...
I've attempted to kill you
countless times,
...would free them one day.
It feels good to punch you!
"Slash the Nightmare -
Brook Draws His Freezing Sword!"
I don't know if he really existed.
and I've been struck down countless times!
Because you're so big!
A warrior who would make you laugh
and put you out of your misery.
She ran!
Grand Jacuzzi...
I became stronger thanks to you!
Imprisonment felt like forever,
...Clutch!
Go! Catch her!
What kept me on the island
wasn't only those handcuffs!
so I hung on to this strange legend.
Thinking "I don't care who it is.
Just help me!"
I was worried!
You should've told me
if it wasn't working!
It's great!
What does that have to do with me?
Thanks for caring, Brook!
You're beautiful!
I heard that the Sun Pirates
you once led had members...
If I don't fight for this country...
Very!
How dare they mess with people's memories!
What looks good on you...
...who used to be slaves!
...is blood makeup.
I...
I can't believe Black Maria-sama's
Illusion Mist didn't affect either of them!
I have nothing to tell you!
Now... Phrase d'armes!
...can't call myself Oden!
Nico Robin!
Orchestra!
I'll make you look more beautiful, okay?!
Let me hollow you out! Fang Pistol!
Oh, no...
Seriously?!
Your whole body is so tough,
She beat up her own mother...
I think you'll look
the most beautiful with...
but you got a cut on your stomach!
How wretched of her!
...a fractured face!
This will end you!
Go away!
Franken-Sword!
What's going on?!
I'm scared...
Oh? Are you running away?!
Fish-Man Karate Secret Art!
...of this place!
V-for-Victory Flash!
Welcome back.
Damn!
You let down your parent,
the people you owe, and your friends.
Robin-san.
Sea Serpent Snapdragon!
It's good to be back.
Do you privilege your own life that much?!
Thank you for...
Hey, my tail!
--No!
--Brook!
...waiting.
Demon Brick Fist!
Nice try, you stupid robot!
I'm a little... tired.
You're not affected by it, either...
MARI-CADE
Oh, yes!
Whoa.
That Illusion Mist thing is so cruel.
Mari-Cade!
This will end you!
Robin-san.
Meanwhile,
on the rooftop of the Skull Dome...
Where am I?
Who am I? Bones?!
Kaido!
The webs that barred your way...
Robin-san?
Black Maria-sama from the Tobi Roppo...
Robin-san!
...are flammable!
...is defeated...
Mari-Arson!
It's "Father" to you!
MARI-ARSON
...by Nico Robin from the Straw Hats.
Hey! You've changed a lot!
Yamato!
What?!
Damn! I'm not good with swords!
I was wondering whose bones you are.
Didn't you say
it'd be over before I knew it?!
I'm here to cut ties with you!
You're Brook.
Such an unpleasant name to hear.
Captain Yorky!
I'm sure that pirates will flock around her
to exploit her abilities.
You strutted in like a hero to cover up
Black-Leg Sanji's pathetic blunder,
You're Captain Yorky!
"Showdown Battles of the Monsters!
Yamato and Franky"
Yes, as you thought, I'm Captain Yorky!
and if you get beaten so easily,
Gather up all of the crew!
Time to ship out Binks's Brew!
Sea wind blows to where, who knows?
The waves will be our guide!
you'll make a fool of yourself
just like he did!
"A Spell!
Kid and Zoro Facing Threats!"
O'er across the ocean's tide,
the sunset is goin' wild
Try to bloom in this sea of flames!
To challenge the Animal Kingdom Pirates'
30,000 troops,
See the sky!
Birds singing in circles passing by!
the 5,400 Samurai-Pirate Allied Troops
made a raid!
If it's come to this,
I'll use the strongest game-changing...
Can flowers bloom in fire?!
Bid farewell to weaver's town!
Say so long to port renowned!
The gap between forces diminished...
Sing a song, it won't be long
before we're casting off!
...through Otama's Kibi Dango strategy...
No!
...and the samurai
and the pirates' valiant fights.
Cross the gold and silver waves,
changin' into water sprays!
Yamato!
How could you run?! Shame on you!
The enemy's tough top officers,
the Tobi Roppo, are all defeated!
You're strong!
Sailing out on our journey
to the ends of the sea!
Become the Shogun for me
without resistance...
Get fully warmed up with Mari-Arson.
Play it!
Onigashima, up above the mainland
of the Land of Wano...
You better listen to your parent.
Oh, no...
And die by flames!
I ended up close to the Performance Floor!
...will soon arrive at the Flower Capital!
Flex your strength all you want
as the Shogun of the Land of Wano!
I'm sorry that you can't move...
I can't let this guy reach it!
Dominate everything and do as you will!
This is payback...
Thank you for the meal!
...for punching my face earlier!
You've eaten it all!
I won't dominate anything!
My beloved Rumbar Pirates!
Mr. Straw Hat!
I won't be dominated, either!
I gave you a month worth of my food!
Bulle-Triceratops!
What a pain...
Do something about that!
They all died.
Otherwise, I can't go back!
All of those who said something like that!
It's ready!
It's great!
I know Luffy will come back!
Yeah, count on me!
How...
Gaon Cannon, Portable Version!
...beautiful!
Until then,
I'm gonna stall you!
Oh, come on!
What can you do now?
The problem is his stomach!
He can't even move properly like that!
Demon Child!
General Cannon!
Oh please, mister!
You don't know what's right
and what's wrong.
She is the child of a demon
and shouldn't be allowed to live!
Laboon!
I'm...
...Oden!
Your sin is being alive!
I'm gonna defend the Land of Wano!
Like I said earlier,
What?! He digested it all!
you're a burden to your crewmates!
Kaido!
The symbol of terror!
Wait for me!
The Animal Kingdom Pirates' Tobi Roppo!
Don't mess with us!
A tramp like you...
THIRD FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE,
ONIGASHIMA
He's smitten with you the most, Brook.
...is sought after by the biggest names
in the world...
I'll bring you down with me!
Mag... num-ceratops!
...only because of that brain
which can decipher Ponegliffs!
That's because he likes music!
It's ready!
They don't need your personality
as long as you're alive!
Why did you serve Kurozumi Orochi,
that hideous man?!
Franky Radical Beam!
You're nothing but a tool!
Fukurokuju!
Those hands and feet are also unnecessary!
We're a group of ninja
who serve the reigning Shogun to the end!
What else can you do?!
PERFORMANCE FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
NIN
You're in no position to lecture me!
Demon Child!
Raizo!
Go to hell!
You mean you would serve any Shogun?!
What?!
Brook!
She's a survivor of the Demons of Ohara!
Where did you go?!
Gee...
Kill her!
She shouldn't be allowed to live!
It really is cruel.
My skin's so hard, isn't it?
It hurts, doesn't it?
This is the power of a cyborg!
Ninpo: Clone Jutsu!
Yeah...
I realized again.
All you can do is use what you're given.
That my crewmates are all dead.
Dog-Dog Fruit!
It's the power of a pathetic fool!
That I'll never be able to see them again!
How annoying!
Mythical Type!
What?!
Punching such an annoying tramp...
Model Okuchi-no-Makami.
It's a valuable Mythical Type fruit!
...feels good!
What about the man you serve?!
It's a guardian deity of the Land of Wano!
He's a ghost!
Damn you!
No matter how much you try,
you can't beat me!
Are you talking about Oden-sama?!
I can't believe it was eaten by someone
who calls himself Oden!
What are you doing, Brook?!
Look! Because you disgracefully rampaged,
the fire is everywhere.
There's the real one!
Beam!
I'm in pain.
I'm sad.
It's all your fault!
Are you gonna ask that skeleton monster
to put it out again?
I'm sad.
There you are!
I'm in pain.
Go ask him to clean up the mess you made.
An extremely emotional man like you...
And it...
...breaks my heart.
Are you just gonna take it?
...will never make a good ninja!
It's nothing but a blunder.
You're really useless.
You're a damn lizard
who sparkles too much!
That's why I'm telling you.
Even though I no longer have a heart!
No matter how skilled you are
at ninja techniques!
Protect the Land of Wano for me.
Did they really call you Demon Child?
Sparkle!
As a guardian deity.
Oh, you're so pathetic!
Die!
Because of our emotions...
we're happy!
Shame on you!
That's not what I want!
I heard you say silly things,
Black Maria-san.
Technology that allows you
to fire laser shots in a row...
Song of Scratches...
That day, we...
Blizzard Slice!
Franky would want that!
If I were you...
...cried and laughed together.
I'll kill you!
I would get away from there!
Do you really want it?
Honestly!
We died with Oden-sama!
Do it already!
Damn you!
Stop cackling like you're in no danger!
Now we're just ghosts
who are trying to fulfill our lord's wish!
If you're gonna show me anything,
Take this! Beam!
at least show me your panties
rather than an illusion.
We don't consider it our job!
I think we're interrupting them...
Twirly Eyebrows alone
can't get us through here!
Because we're all servants with emotions,
Let's leave the two alone.
Orochi had a talent for exploitation.
Stop! I won't let you flee!
we're even happy to die in battle!
This country is a weapon factory!
Soul Parade! Ice Wall!
That's my Zoro...
How could she do such a terrible thing!
Today, the night called Orochi-Kaido will end,
All right! Prepare the injection!
I'm not okay but I'm...
Dominate it by forcing its people to labor!
and the bright sun will rise!
...okay.
Miyagi!
Oh, no!
Obtain informed consent!
With Momonosuke-sama as the Shogun!
Maybe even that skeleton monster
finally abandoned you.
For 50 years, in the mist,
Make sure you fully understand
the explanation before agreeing to it.
I kept wishing that the deaths
of my crewmates were a dream...
Don't worry.
I'll take care of you.
This medicine that's been handed down in Zou
will provide a super-healing effect,
I'll take my time...
I'm Kozuki Oden!
...and beat the hell out of you!
but it's only temporary.
In exchange,
the serious side effects later...
...will cause you
to suffer twice as much as you do now!
How great you've become...
Yeah, I'm okay with that.
I'll open the borders of Land of Wano.
I'm okay with that, but...
...isn't that needle too long?!
Zoro, hang in there!
Everyone!
You can do it!
I'll...
...free them!
Hey! Monster! Monster!
The samurai...
Geez... You really are a creepy child.
I saw visions every day...
...and this country...
Do you know how much bounty
is on her head?
...and felt hurt...
...will be unleashed on the world!
Hey!
She's a survivor of those demons
who planned the world's annihilation!
Too deep, too deep!
Oh! I'm sorry!
It'll be a problem if she's left at large.
She is the child of a demon
and shouldn't be allowed to live!
Blast Breath!
The bandages are too thick,
so I can't see your vein...
Namuji Glacier Fang!
We have so much in common!
Your sin is being alive!
That ability is so irritating!
Take them off first!
Every ordeal was for the present!
There're too many enemies...
to achieve my dream...
Yes, you're right.
No matter how many times you attack,
my stand-ins will take the blows...
Oh well, let's just do it.
I-I'm...
When did I ask you guys to rescue me?!
Come on, bring it on.
Are you sure? Hey!
I just want to... die!
Until you finish me,
I won't let you open the borders!
I'm so happy to be alive!
just accept your fate,
and curse yourself!
I'm not crazy like you are!
Laugh.
When you're having a hard time,
just laugh.
I will...
I am so very happy to be alive!!!
...send you to hell soon enough!
RIGHT-BRAIN TOWER, SKULL DOME, ONIGASHIMA
Of course you are.
What's this?
Go to hell! Old bag!
Robin-san!
Because today came!
You're annoying! Brat!
Robin-san!
I guess it's not just fog.
Hey, are you listening?
Leave the others to us!
I said...
Take down Sasaki!
...you need to learn to punch
just in case.
Iron Big Bro!
For my friends' sake,
I can't stay depressed!
Robin-san!
I don't like hitting people with my fist.
You guys came back to side with me?!
My spirit is unbreakable!
Can't it be slapping, Koala?
Is that all you've got?
They want to kill you!
Yeah!
Because I'm bones!
Don't mess with the Four Emperors!
Slapping is too weak!
Wanyudo Sleeve Swing!
M-My friends who ate Kibi Dango!
How about using the heel of your palm?
Hitting with your palm?
Oh, no!
I need to ask you all a favor!
Speed matters more than power!
That weird weapon again!
Even metal scraps are turning against you!
Throw it quickly
and pull it back quickly!
Please side with Big Bro Luffy's group...
Wham!
WANYUDO - PUG SMILE FRUIT
Say what you want!
Listen, Eustass-ya!
What?
...and Momonosuke-kun's group!
Shut up!
I won't let you get away!
Robin, do you want me to teach you
Dragon Claw Fist?
She is my prey!
It'll become your strong weapon.
Why did you come?!
I'm gonna teach her!
Get ready, Big Mom!
Did you say illusions don't affect you?
Doesn't matter who teaches her.
But you're still dreaming!
Certainly, Master-sama!
Then I will!
Hawkins!
No, I will!
How many stand-ins do you have?!
Leave it to me, Master-sama!
I'm more suited than you!
I'm a Fish-Man Karate assistant instructor!
Dreaming that you can defeat Kaido-sama!
Take down Kaido! Let's go!
There are only a few left...
I'm in trouble...
Whoa-whoa... Both of you,
don't be so obtrusive.
Spider Net!
Oh, Hack!
Guys, follow me!
She is strong enough
with her locking techniques.
I mourn those lives.
But once we part from her,
we can't protect her!
Who killed them?
Thank you!
I said she's strong.
Robin!
Our strengths!
We use them all for Master-sama!
The place is in flames!
With Fish-Man Karate,
she can make use of her specialty!
If you don't stop,
fire will spread throughout the castle!
Professor Clover!
Dragon Claw Fist
is better suited for that!
Are you worrying about our castle?
Saul!
Robin has her own way of fighting!
Thanks...
They're no longer your subordinates!
Then why don't you surrender yourself already?
Nico Robin!
Palms can be used
without special abilities like yours!
Bring it on, you little punk!
An application of Dragon Claw Fist
is good enough!
They're my...
...buddies!
Palms!
Neither of you are listening to me!
Super!
Robin-san,
could you keep holding me for a minute?
W... W...
Robin!
We still haven't heard you say it!
Wa...
If that weapon is a living thing...
Say you want to live!
Hey, Armored Division!
Soul!
I know you're manipulated by the enemy's
ability, but what you're doing...
Worms?
Cold Soul!
Help me, Robin-chan!
I know it's a long shot,
but I'll ask you anyway.
...is in fact treason!
It's cold!
When you get home,
I don't want you to tell anyone about me.
Wanyudo!
Damn!
I've never thought
that I want to become stronger...
Okay.
There are only a few left...
That was too easy. She'll definitely tell.
...for somebody else.
...but the important thing is...
If you leave it to me, it'll be alright!
I won't tell.
...whose lives are in them!
Being hot or too hot is prohibited.
That's a lie! There's no way
that a child can keep a secret.
If you leave it to me, it'll be alright!
What?!
I suddenly got stabbed!
Then...
What?
Damn you!
Can you teach me
the "palm" thing a little bit?
Hey, what happened to you?!
I won't tell
because I'm not interested in you.
Oh, no!
Soul Parade!
Okay!
Are you sure you want to teach that to me?
Don't tell me that straw doll...
You're really tough!
Of course I am!
"Dereshi"? What does that mean?
I think I delivered some deadly attacks!
Now you notice.
You are so precious to us!
What does it mean?
It's you who is tough and annoying!
It would've been entertaining to watch you
kill Kid without realizing that it's him...
Iceburn!
I'm just laughing.
That was so close. Thanks, Brook.
Robin-san!
You're laughing?
Why don't you...
This is...
...but it'll also be interesting
to see you...
...get out of my way now!
You don't know when to give up.
...a special move.
You're a funny girl.
It uses your palms, too.
Nico Robin!
...become helpless.
But it's a secret art of
Fish-Man Karate!
Don't you see?
You can only kill me...
You're cute when you laugh.
No matter how you look at it,
you were sold out by your friend!
...by killing your own captain.
I heard all of our subordinates changed
sides on the Performance Floor, too...
Black-Leg called you in front of me
knowing that you were my target!
Damn you!
Mil Fleurs...
You've grown.
Fish-Man Karate!
You monster!
I'm gonna kill you both!
I'm gonna go there
and kill everyone who stands against us!
Enjoy each other's company
in the afterlife, too!
Help me, Robin-chan!
Giganteum!
In other words,
Amazingly, you scored 100% on the exam
for the doctoral degree you took the other day!
since you're targeted
by such big names across the world,
From today on, you can introduce yourself
as an archaeologist.
Protect the Land of Wano for me!
you're a liability to your crewmates!
It's amusing...
...just to imagine you suffering
under that mask.
I recognize you
as part of our force, Yamato!
That's why he called you in so easily!
Professor Clover...
Looks like you've become
a fine archaeologist, Robin!
Where were you aiming?!
Help me, Robin-chan!
Now, do what you gotta do.
Don't hold back!
Certainly...
Certainly, my palms came in handy
so many times.
Parents don't say that to their child!
Black-Leg is the laughingstock
of the whole of Onigashima!
Are you... my mom?
Figure out where your enemy's core is!
You're disgusting!
His bounty is the second highest
in your group, right?
That Devil Fruit was hard-earned,
Figure out where my enemy's core is!
Move aside, Trafalgar!
and I wasn't gonna let you eat it!
Are you my mom?!
That shows how weak you guys are!
Listen carefully, Robin!
No one is born into this world to be alone!
I...
I'm sorry I've left you alone
for a long time.
...was hungry!
Go meet your friends!
Mom...
Live together with them.
What Sanji-san did...
I was shocked, too!
Yes.
...was very funny!
I'm your mother.
I wanna go out to sea,
but now I can't swim!
Come here.
Robin-san! May I leave her to you?
I've attempted to kill you
countless times,
Thanks! That's what I want.
We cannot give up the future
you young ones will live in!
and I've been struck down countless times!
Don't go, Robin-san!
Leave the other creatures to me!
I became stronger thanks to you!
Live, Robin!
Isn't it intriguing?! My cyborg?!
What kept me on the island...
But I'm scared of ghosts!
To sea? So you wanna set out to sea, too?
...wasn't only those handcuffs!
Are you hurt?
Show me your true colors already, Vinsmoke!
No.
No way!
Is that what she wanted to do?!
Yep.
He's so kind.
My mom has been busy with her
archaeological research all this time.
If I don't fight for this country...
Show me Judge's scientific capabilities!
But when she comes back
to this island next time,
You don't need to know...
...why he asked for my help!
I'm going to ask her
to take me with her to sea.
I can't call myself Oden!
Dammit! The fire has been put out!
He's a man worthy of being
one of the two arms...
So I studied hard and I was finally
able to become an archaeologist.
Where is she?!
...of the King of the Pirates.
An archaeologist?
When you're still so small?
You don't even remember
your mom's face, right?
Prepare yourself, Black-Leg!
Damn! This is going nowhere!
Right... but she's still my mom.
I'm gonna do it!
Just give up.
No matter what means you use,
You and I are two of a kind!
I can see right through you
most of the time!
Let's become friends, Vinsmoke!
I wanna see her.
Of course you do.
Gigante Fleur!
Don't call me that!
Say, Saul...
I'm gonna blow everything away!
Hmm... So that's what they call
a Man-Beast Form!
Do you know that the world has a blank history
of 100 years that no one knows about?
Don't lump me with...
Damn robot!
I'm gonna kick you out of my way!
...that crazy scientist!
I heard that my mom is traveling
around the world investigating it.
Diable Jambe!
What is that appearance?
Trick Mechanism...
...Screw Sword!
Concasser!
C-Could it mean...
A demon?
Blood will tell!
You're pissed off...
...that she's traveling in search of
those stones called Ponegliffs?
I didn't know
you could make yourself so huge.
I'm the cook of the Straw Hats!
That dangerous sword again?!
But looks like it's exhausting.
I won't move out of the way!
So you know about Ponegliffs?
Don't worry.
It'll be over before you know it!
Robin... Do you know your mom's name?
A demon!
Any more fighting will be a waste of time!
Shut up!
So what?!
Olvia.
Sea Serpent Snapdragon!
I don't know
if you're Demon Child or what,
Iron Big Bro!
I'm gonna cut up that leg
and your precious hands!
but you've never seen hell!
Olvia.
Let us help you!
You fool! I won't let you!
I'll destroy everything!
You...
Don't even try!
With the Oiran Knuckles and poison...
Sasaki, bring it on!
Come on!
Damn King!
Take this!
I got this!
I'm gonna show you...
You guys, go help the others!
...how gruesome my hell can be!
Saul?!
Whoa!
Robin is Olvia's daughter...!
I'm not gonna get caught
without putting up a fight!
Then could this place be...
an island called Ohara?!
That's hilarious!
So your real body gets hurt!
You must be glad those nuisances are gone.
Yeah.
In that case,
it's good that the target is big!
This is no time to be
sitting around talking! Robin!
Let go of me!
And has many arms!
Sangoro-san!
Seems like I don't have
any allies around here.
They're big, too!
This might shock you,
but listen to me carefully!
Hey, King! How dare you?!
You made a perfect decoy
so I just used you.
Oh, you noticed?
What?! That thing rotates?!
Navy battleships should be
headed to Ohara right now.
Poison barbs at the ends of my legs!
Demonio Fleur.
Maria-Nette!
Is that how...
Navy? Why?
What are you gonna do?!
...dinosaurs are?!
There are the people who truly need me,
In order to eliminate
the scholars on this island!
Yes, we are!
The price of betrayal is high!
Th-That technique...
and rely on me!
You're in danger! Run! Iron Big Bro!
And for those people, I would even...
Hey, you scum, formerly part
of the Animal Kingdom Pirates!
You idiots!
I'm gonna execute you all by flames!
Why don't you worry about yourselves?!
...turn into a demon!
Onigashima is moving farther away...
Heliceratops!
Robin... You fool!
You shouldn't be here.
What should we do?!
If it falls onto the Flower Capital,
the Land of Wano will...
Meat!
Are you... my mom?
Guys!
Are you my mom?!
Grand Jacuzzi...
Meat! I need more meat!
Where's Marco-san?!
Please do something!
...Clutch!
TOKAGE PORT
Meat!
Black Maria-sama has
way more momentum than usual!
What kind of move is that?!
Are you my mom?!
He reached his physical limit!
Is it gonna be an aerial fight?!
That tramp is finished!
We've got to do it!
General Left!
S... top... it...
I think you're confusing me
with someone else.
Sangoro-san!
Are you okay?!
"Hands and feet are unnecessary"?
Damn! It's hard to deal with two at once!
Straw Hat?
I'm Robin!
No! Not mine...
They're looking for Zorojuro!
I've grown, but don't you remember me?!
I was talking about yours!
I...
What is Mosshead doing?!
More meat!
...dominate the sky!
Hey, bring more!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
I've been waiting for you
to return all this time!
What did you say?!
He's already eaten
all the provisions on the ship!
Is it gonna take more time?
I don't think
we can find meat around here.
He was in critical condition
in the first place...
Saul!
Meat! I need more meat!
Chopper! Miyagi!
Anyway, his vitality is incredible.
If the drug's not working,
take that green mummy and get away!
This is it for me. I got caught.
Who can believe he's barely alive...
So that's how dinosaurs are...
Go! Set out to sea!
Sanji...
We've already injected him with it!
Luffy!
So cool!
No! There's no one on the sea!
Triceratops...
Luffy!
Hang in there, Zoro!
Listen carefully, Robin!
...is a dinosaur like this!
Who can stop them?!
You're alone now,
If nothing is done,
everyone on this floor will die!
Momo!
but you'll meet friends someday for sure!
--I thought you guys were on Onigashima.
--How did you get here?
Sangoro-san!
I didn't know...
Gee... There's no choice...
Friends?
You picked him up in the sea?
How's that for a miracle?!
The sea is vast, so someday, definitely...
What was that noise?!
...you'll come across friends
who'll protect you!
Black Maria-sama!
Is he gonna charge?
Well, we heard a voice in the sea...
At that speed?!
The ice is in the way!
Burn! Burn!
We turned in that direction
and found him.
That damn skeleton monster!
No one is born
into this world to be alone!
I'm gonna entertain you until you die!
All right!
Is something wrong?!
Luffytaro's voice?
Is that what Momonosuke-sama heard?!
Black Maria-sama...
Hey, dinosaur!
Find Roronoa Zoro...
Luffy! How lucky you are!
You are really alive!
When you're having a hard time,
I taught you what to do!
...and kill him!
Bring it on!
Black Maria... sama?
They gave him some strange treatment.
You came falling, too?
Don't let him recover!
General Shield!
Yeah!
Yeah, we got away from Kaido
with Shinobu's kite!
That's too small!
Saul!
Are you desperate?
Black Maria-sama got...!
I'm gonna let it crumble like a cookie!
After I have some fun with you,
Judge's son is next!
But Luffy...
A demon!
To let me flee, in front of my very eyes,
Kiku and Kin'emon were...
Thank you for lining up!
I'm here!
I knew it.
Kin-sama...
Now... Phrase d'armes!
Illusion Mist...
I'm ashamed of myself.
Sangoro-san!
Sweet memories ruin you.
Orchestra!
I, Kikunojo of the Fallen Snow...
Damn you!
...can't live any longer...
I will not move!
I cannot let you get past me!
I won't let you guys do as you like!
What's the matter, Robin?
Here I...
What?!
Come here.
I'll get rid of you then!
What?
Silly monsters...
I know. This is an illusion.
No way...
Kin'emon!
Propellers change the direction of thrust
depending on which way they turn.
The dust is so thick
I can barely see!
What a shame.
Welcome back.
This illusion is a mirror.
Robin-san.
He just had it rotate the wrong way...
A mirror that reflects my childish heart...
It's good to be back.
I'm gonna finish Vinsmoke Sanji!
Thank you for...
Save it for later!
You've always been like that!
...waiting.
But...
Lick!
That's why he went backward.
I'm a little... tired.
You're the commander-in-chief!
It's not over yet!
...when my friends are fighting,
If you had married Pudding...
Stop whining!
I can't just indulge in my memories.
Whoa.
Secured more space to run up.
we wouldn't have to work
with those idiots!
Forget about your friends.
Robin-san.
Until we kick Kaido's ass, it's not over!
Don't lie!
Shut up!
Luffytaro! Don't be so harsh!
The longer you run up,
the stronger the charge!
Do you guys really understand?!
I'm counting on you! General Shield!
I said stop crying, Momo!
I may forgive the others,
That's a month worth of my food!
You're the future Shogun!
Bulle-Triceratops!
but I'll never forgive you!
Make sure to return the favor,
or I'll be in trouble.
It's him, Master!
Saul wouldn't say such a thing.
TOKAGE PORT, UDON
I see...
Anyway, I can't believe
you had this much food!
My Swamp-Swamp Fruit power
is bottomless!
Lick!
Oh no! The launcher on my shoulder
will explode!
Good.
Go to hell, Germa's failure!
History is the treasure of mankind.
Straw Hat! What happened to
our captain, Bepo, and the others?!
It'll certainly light up the future
we'll live in.
I want more! Meat!
Let's step outside!
Ooaa-ay...
TRA-GUY
We told you we don't have anymore!
You people can't understand it.
IS ALIVE!!
...iw aaiu!!
All right! We're gonna go find some!
Goodbye!
"Iw aaiu"?
I am begging you!
Only you can do it!
Meat!
Damn you!
I got you!
I'm gonna avenge Pedro!
Yes, I can
but why do you want to do that?!
General...
Tres Mano!
...Suplex!
I want to grant Luffy his wish!
Straw Hat's getting weak.
Freesia!
His wish?
This is a bad sign, isn't it?!
I have to take Luffy there!
If he dies now,
I'll be in so much trouble!
How come the Illusion Mist...
So I want to go to Onigashima again!
I won't let you get away!
Cut it out! Caribou!
What?!
How come it didn't work?
I found Roronoa Zoro!
Don't be so mean...
Straw Hat!
Why... are you saying
such a ridiculous thing?!
Straw Hat!
Mister, you'll do it, right?
Kill him!
Straw Hat!
Yeah!
I'll never let you go
to a dangerous place like that again!
Come back to life!
POLAR TANG
ON THE SEA AROUND THE LAND OF WANO
Come back to life! Straw Hat!
They found him!
Shut up!
What should we do, Dr. Chopper?!
Listen, Shinobu!
Damn!
If nothing is done, the Flower Capital
and the Land of Wano will be annihilated!
You're gonna do the jailbreak thing, right?
If only Captain were here!
Protect Zorojuro!
His wounds were earned honorably!
His lungs have been cleared, right?
Yeah!
I beg you!
That is why I have to go there
at any cost!
What else can we do?!
Robin.
They're all wounded!
Finish them off along with Roronoa!
Mom!
Don't touch me!
Should we give him a pill?
Take me with you!
Live, Robin!
Please! So I need you to...
No, it should be an injection!
Momonosuke-sama,
listen to me very carefully.
Robin!
He looks pale!
If you don't win,
I can't get out of this country!
Take him and get away!
Straw Hat!
Say you want to live!
Wake up!
If I do that, you'll never...
Yeah!
What should we do?!
I wanted you to hold my hand...
Straw Hat!
...be able to turn back
to your current appearance!
Come on!
Straw Hat!
Keep up with them!
Hang in there, Miyagi, Tristan!
Straw Hat!
He's still gonna eat a ridiculous amount!
...and walk with me someday...
Straw Hat!
That means your mind
will remain that of a child...
Hey!
We have no choice. It'll take some time,
but let's go to a nearby town to get some...
Okay!
So I studied hard and
was able to become an archaeologist!
Straw Hat!!
...while only your body will be matured.
Hey!
I can read Ponegliffs, too!
If you do such a thing...
That is fine!
I bet this is what you guys want!
I might be able to become...
...a bigger dragon that way!
That's... a lot!
But I can't do such a thing!
Damn!
All this time...
Straw Hat! Thank goodness!
Momonosuke-sama!
I am begging you!
D-Don't do that, Momonosuke-sama!
Mom!
Mea...!
Momo!
King's here!
Please, Shinobu!
Mea?
Mea...
Take me back up there!
With your Ripe-Ripe Jutsu,
Mea?
Mea...
Transform into a dragon and fly me up!
Just wake up already, Mosshead!
make me grow older...
Live, Robin...
What?!
Please...
make me grow older...
Meat!
This is it, Roronoa Zoro!
What?!
I decided to live...
I'll defeat...
Give me meat!
Make me grow older!
...alongside my friends.
Kaido!
The Rumbar Pirates appear in the heavy mist!
Is this a dream or reality?
Black Maria's wicked verbal attacks
weaken Robin's spirit!
A vicious spell
that sees through people's minds!
Our friends and the Tobi Roppo
have an all-out confrontation!
Kind people who Robin met in Ohara and
her mother Olvia appear in front of her.
Killer agonizes when his slash to finish off Hawkins
cuts his partner Kid in the chest instead.
It evokes the voice of an old friend, Laboon.
Enjoy a full-course meal of fierce fights!
As she falls prey to a raging hellfire
and has both her body and soul burned to ash,
Seeing his old buddies confuses Brook!
The great battle of Onigashima!
Its intensity keeps increasing!
They shed a ray of light
on the young Robin.
Sanji faces the brutes
who come after Zoro by himself!
Their blades come to attack him!
will it be light or darkness that blooms?
Will their voices lead her
to the end of a tragic cycle,
Don't miss the series of bruising fights.
He is nearing his limit!
The roar that she raises for her loved ones
leads her to the black flower!
A tragedy that shouldn't be possible
terrifies Brook's mind!
Push yourself hard
and save your injured friend!
or the beginning of a lonely journey?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Recapping Fierce Fights! Straw Hats vs. Tobi Roppo"
"A Spell! Kid and Zoro Facing Threats!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Predator's Trap - Black Maria's Temptation"
"Slash the Nightmare - Brook Draws His Freezing Sword!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Clutch! A Demon Incarnate, Robin!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy's gonna become the King of the Pirates!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates![Events]
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
[Events]