Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"Rainbase"                 "Alubarna"
"Yuba" "Erumalu" "Nanohana" "Katorea"
"Spiders Café"
Three years have passed
since a single drop of rain fell
in the kingdom of oases.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people took up weapons.
The burning land is now
enveloped by a sad bellowing
and a mighty swell.
To stop the maelstrom of war
spreading throughout Alabasta,
Princess Vivi was in a rush
to talk with the rebel army.
However...
I wanna kick Crocodile's ass!
If we stop the people rebelling,
will that stop Crocodile?
At least try putting all of our
lives on the line together!
Aren't we friends?!
Now tell me...
...where Crocodile is!
It was at this moment
that Vivi made up her mind.
"The Battlefront of Alabasta!
Rainbase, the City of Dreams"
Everyone...
Luffy-san is exactly right.
I've made up my mind now.
Let's go to where Crocodile is!
Yeah!
That does seem to be
the quickest shortcut.
Meaning no more of this
annoying, roundabout traveling.
So, where is this damn Crocodile?
Let's see here...
This is the capital city of Alubarna,
where my father rules from.
And the rebel army is currently here,
preparing to invade Alubarna.
So we need to take care of
Crocodile before that can happen.
Crocodile is here. Rainbase.
Rainbase...
It's about a day's journey north of here.
C'mon, I told you to
quit moaning, you two!
Who're you to say anything
when you're riding the camel?!
Yeah! Let us ride, too!
You camel-woman!
--Nami-mel!
--Good one!
Chopper! You haven't collapsed today!
Yeah. I'm gonna try extra hard.
Vivi. Does Rainbase have water?
Yes, there's no problem there.
It's a gambling town, almost
completely detached from the rebellion.
Ooh! Gambling?!
Hey, now! What're you thinking?!
I guess even here in Alabasta
there are carefree cities.
Gum-Gum No Way!
No! No! No!
--Gimme some!
--Gum-Gum No Way!
C'mon! Just one sip!
That is why we have it!
That dry old guy spent all
night digging this water up!
We can't just drink it like
it's nothing! You dumbhead!
Wow! Sometimes you
can restrain yourself!
Of course I can! How rude!
You're rude!
Can't take another step... W-Water...
So?! How long until Rainbase?!
Luffy-san.
Thanks. I never would've been able
to make this decision on my own.
Then gimme food.
Eh?
After I kick Crocodile's ass,
gimme so much food I might die!
Okay! I promise!
"Rebel Army Camp in Katorea"
Please, Koza! Let me join the rebel army!
No.
Why not?! I have the right to
join the rebellion too, don't I?!
I despise the king! Let me fight with you!
Show him, Faracla.
He got this trying to protect me
in the middle of a battle.
Would you like to see the
medical wards and the graves too?
T-That doesn't scare me!
Towns've dried up, and many have
died 'cause the king stole the rain!
It made lots of my friends sick, too!
It's all the king's fault!
I wanna fight, too!
I'm not afraid of getting hurt or even dying!
Then leave. Our opinions are too different.
We're all afraid, and none
of us want to fight.
Then why do you fight?!
It's not that we wanted to. We had to.
That's what the country wished for.
Whether you understand or not,
it has nothing to do with you.
Leave.
I said leave, dammit!
This is no place for children!
What was that about, Koza?
It's not like you to rant
and rave at children.
It was like looking at my
old self. It made me mad.
I haven't changed one bit...
Have we gathered enough weapons?
No, it's proving difficult...
Contact all the other towns.
As soon as we have weapons,
we launch an all-out assault on Alubarna!
Sire! It's only a matter of time until
the rebel army attacks Alubarna!
We must take action first,
before it's too late!
Silence! I told you no!
This is not a children's quarrel!
Is retaliation what you want?!
But, Sire! The country's
existence hangs in the balance!
So what?
Ever since the Dance Powder
incident, it has been clear
that someone is trying
to destroy our country!
Are you suggesting
we destroy our countrymen
before learning who's
really pulling the strings?
That would be the downfall of our country!
Listen! A country is its people!
However, this wire-puller has
not shown himself whatsoever!
Taking action after this unknown
shadow devours our country
would be too late, Sire!
No. Please understand.
The king won't allow us
to take the offensive.
We can barely even appease
the soldiers at this point.
If only Igaram-san were
here at a time like this...
Igaram says he's leaving
the country for a while?
As we speak, he and Vivi-sama
are probably still hard at work,
trying to figure out who's behind this.
I wonder where they are.
Chaka-sama! Pell-sama!
What is it?!
Karoo has returned!
Karoo has?!
Sire! Who is that letter from?!
It's Vivi's handwriting, without a doubt...
Sire! Does that mean--?!
Karoo came to deliver
a letter from Vivi-sama?!
Father. Everything written
here is true. It is fact.
The person trying to bring
suffering and ruin to this kingdom
is none other than Crocodile!
Igaram is another who has
fallen at the hands of Crocodile.
Crocodile! I stupidly believed
he worked for the government!
I never would've imagined he
was trying to usurp this kingdom!
Igaram-san...
He gave his life for
Vivi-sama and this land...
And now, there are people who
have given me unfathomable power.
If I continue with them, we may
make a difference in this kingdom.
The light of hope is here!
Alabasta will be saved!
Please have faith, Father!
Vivi.
It says you fought valiantly,
too, Karoo. You've done well.
You're hurt? Let me see.
At any rate, no matter what happens,
this thing on our left arm
is the sign of our friendship!
Chaka.
We know the enemy's identity!
Prepare the soldiers for expedition!
I will not let Vivi's resolve
and Igaram's death be for naught!
We're taking immediate action!
We're heading to Rainbase,
where Crocodile is!
Please wait, Sire! Rainbase is
too far away to be "immediate"!
Crocodile has the citizens on his side!
Even more so than you,
with all due respect...
If we attack Rainbase,
the rebel army will use that as
a chance to storm the palace!
And if that happens--!
So what if the rebel army
destroys this palace?!
I've told you before! A country is its people!
Even if our royal army falls,
as long as Crocodile is defeated,
the country will be reborn by the people!
But, consider if we clash
with the rebel army instead!
Crocodile is the only one
who will have the last laugh!
Sire...
You're that dedicated to--?
Even if by some chance
the rebel army doesn't stop,
we need only take out Crocodile!
We're up against one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea.
Crocodile is not weak of heart.
This battle will not be without
sacrifices before its end.
Chaka! I'm holding a war meeting!
Assemble the officers!
Pell! Go on ahead and
conduct enemy reconnaissance!
Yes, Sire!
It seems we've been severely
underestimating His Majesty.
What powerful spirit!
We go to battle tomorrow morning!
Yes, Sire!
I'm sending all soldiers to Rainbase!
I see it...
Is that it?
Rainbase?
Oh! Are we here?!
Crocodile!
Alright! Time to beat up Crocodile!
So this is Rainbase!
By the way, does Baroque Works
know we're in this country now?
Most likely.
We did run into Mr. 2, so we should
assume they know we're here.
So what?!
They know what we look like!
We can't do much of anything
while we're in Rainbase!
Why not?!
If we get spotted first,
Crocodile can probably deal
with us in all kinds of ways.
Assassination is their area of specialty.
Come out, Crocodile!
Were you even listening?!
In any case, no matter who we run into,
I'll protect Nami-san and Vivi-chan!
You two girls can call me "Prince"!
Prince.
Don't make me kick your ass!
--Prince... Water...
--Water...
Shut up, you guys!
Water! Need water!
Me too!
--Water! Water!
--Wait! Luffy!
Take money with you!
Captain Smoker.
Why do you think the Straw Hats
will show up here, in Rainbase?
Dunno. Call it a hunch.
Alright!
--We can get water here, Usopp!
--Water!
Plus, something stinks about this country.
I get a strong sense that something
big is lurking in the shadows.
Old lady! Water!
A barrel of water! No, five!
Five barrels of water!
Then you think there
really is a connection
between the Baroque Works criminal
organization and Straw Hat?
--Here!
--Water!
All I know is that Straw Hat
is out to get Crocodile...
--...one of the Seven Warlords.
--This water's great, you jerk!
It's great, you bastard!
Let's hurry and take the others some!
I need to take a leak.
Can we really count on them?
They can do little errands
just fine. Don't worry.
I dunno. I bet they'll come back
with a bunch of trouble again.
I'd do warm-up exercises if I were you.
--Run!
--Yeah!
--Got that barrel?!
Damn it!
We're going after 'em, Tashigi!
Gather the marines!
Yes, sir!
Umm, how much do I owe you?
If you know those kids, you better
pay for the water they took, too!
Y-Yes! I'm sorry for the trouble!
Why is the Navy here again?!
How should I know?! Just run!
The Navy's chasing 'em again!
No way!
So why are they running this way?!
Say! Tony-kun hasn't come back yet!
Leave him! He'll manage!
Hey, guys! The Navy's here!
You're the one bringing them here!
Catch 'em for sure this time!
They're quick to run away, I'll give 'em that!
This isn't a good idea!
Baroque Works is gonna spot us...
...if we run through the city!
I think it's too late for that.
Then it's decided! Let's go!
--Eh?!
--To where Crocodile is!
Right, Vivi?!
Yes! Do you see that
alligator-roof building up ahead?!
That's the casino Crocodile runs...
Raindinners!
There, huh?!
So that's where Crocodile is?!
It'd be best if we split up!
It looks that way!
Alright! See you later!
Yeah!
Let's meet at the alligator house!
--They split up!
--Don't let 'em escape!
Come and get me, Smokey!
You got real guts!
Don't think you can keep running forever!
White Vine!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
That was close!
Damn!
Ahh! Much better!
Where did everyone go?
That's Luffy's smell!
That's Zoro's smell!
Sanji's goes that way!
What's going on?!
Outta the way!
Whoops!
Mr. Bushido! This direction, too!
It's them! No doubt about it!
Kill 'em!
The Baroque Works Millions!
"Stuck between the devil
and the deep sea," huh?
Go on without me!
--Hurry!
--R-Right!
Usopp!
--Look after Nami-san!
--What?!
I'll hold 'em off!
--Alright! You can count on me!
--Sanji-kun...
--Go!
--We are!
Without that smoke freak around,
they're just small fries.
My deepest condolences.
I hope Mr. Bushido will be all right!
Is that all you got?
Try again some other time.
Roronoa Zoro! We meet again!
That voice...
I've been looking for you for a long time!
What do you think you're doing,
cutting down regular citizens?!
Look, I got my own circumstances, too!
Besides, I have no desire to fight you!
We settled our match in Loguetown!
We did not!
I haven't even laid a single blow yet!
She looks like her! Way too much like her!
And quit it with that face, will ya?!
C-Come again?! Are you trying
to ridicule me yet again?!
You will pay for this!
Dammit! She's the one
person I can't deal with!
Wait!
Bastards! Get back here!
No!
It's definitely them!
W-We did it!
Way to go, Usopp!
Look! Up ahead!
The entrance to Raindinners!
It's in the middle of a lake!
Is no one here yet?!
Alright! Let's blast 'em!
Start with those two!
The enemy?!
Zoro!
Wasn't Vivi with you?!
Yeah! Is she not here yet?!
She might've gone inside!
Let's hurry, then!
--Luffy!
--Get back here!
Plume-Plume is with him!
Hey! Let's go! Run inside, guys!
We're going in?
He's in there...
...isn't he?!
Oh? Vivi and the pirates
are here in town?
Yes. We just received
word from the Millions.
Go welcome the foolish rats.
Yes, sir.
Listen, Crocodile!
I'm going to kick your ass!
I'm coming for you!
Like the adventurers
I dreamed of when I was a child
I continue on to the ends of emotion
I scoop up my hands, and the sand
and time that spills from them
show me that this is what
I was born to do
Let's continue swimming
at a near-tumbling speed
Until we wash up someday
on a white sandy beach
no one knows about
Crocodile! Come out! I came
to Alubarna to kick your ass!
That's not gonna make him
come out! You're so dumb!
We're up against the kingdom's hero!
Are you gonna make these
customers our enemies too?!
But without Vivi,
we don't know who Crocodile is!
Huh? Come to think of it, where is Vivi?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Trap of Certain Defeat!
Storming Raindinners"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!