Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"Rainbase"                 "Alubarna"
"Yuba" "Erumalu" "Nanohana" "Katorea"
"Spiders Café"
"Rainbase"                 "Alubarna"
"Yuba" "Erumalu" "Nanohana" "Katorea"
"Spiders Café"
"Rainbase"                 "Alubarna"
"Yuba" "Erumalu" "Nanohana" "Katorea"
"Spiders Café"
"Rainbase"                 "Alubarna"
"Yuba" "Erumalu" "Nanohana" "Katorea"
"Spiders Café"
"Rainbase"                 "Alubarna"
"Yuba" "Erumalu" "Nanohana" "Katorea"
"Spiders Café"
Three years have passed
since a single drop of rain fell
in the kingdom of oases.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people take up weapons.
in the kingdom of oases.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people take up weapons.
in the kingdom of oases.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people take up weapons.
The scorching land was now
engulfed in wails of grief,
The burning land is now
enveloped by a sad bellowing
Fanning the flames
of rebellion is Crocodile.
The scorching land was now
engulfed in wails of grief,
along with tremendous upheaval.
To stop his scheme,
and a mighty swell.
Luffy and company stormed
the enemy hideout in Rainbase,
along with tremendous upheaval.
Luffy and the others had been
caught in a trap inside Raindinners,
A fake King Cobra
appeared before the people
but they wound up captured instead.
"Nanohana"
At long last, Luffy's group reached
Crocodile's base in Rainbase.
Crocodile's plan was
finally being carried out,
What is the operation Crocodile speaks of?
and claimed to be responsible
for the lack of rain.
but as a result of Sanji's actions,
they were finally able to escape.
and Bon Clay, transformed into the false king,
Will Vivi's wish be swallowed
up by the burning land?
However, waiting for them there
Moreover, he destroyed the city
and persecuted its people.
had appeared in Nanohana.
Marine Captain Smoker, having
been saved by Luffy and company,
were marines led by Captain
Smoker of Navy Headquarters.
It just turned noon.
The operation is beginning.
then allowed them to get away.
Will Alabasta fall?
Unaware it was all a trap set by Crocodile,
Or will it find true peace?
A rebel army had also risen up.
the people's hatred exploded.
Moment by moment, the hourglass
of fate marks the final hour.
"Operation Utopia Commences!
The Swell of Rebellion Stirs"
The intense flames of rebellion
covered all of Alabasta.
Meanwhile, Vivi was escaping,
in order to tell Sanji about the peril
that Luffy and the others were in,
having been caught in
a trap within Raindinners.
"Merciless Mortal Combat!
Luffy vs. Crocodile"
While fending off the marines
and Baroque Works' Millions,
Don't hold suspicion, Koza.
Will Alabasta fall?
Ready for the final showdown,
the rebel army heads
to the capital city of Alubarna.
Luffy's party storms the Raindinners
Casino, where Crocodile is.
You know His Majesty's
character very well.
Or will it find true peace?
I see them!
However, Luffy and company still
remain in a Rainbase prison cell.
Moment by moment, the hourglass
of fate marks the final hour.
After them!
All you old people say that.
I didn't follow you here to
Yuba for the king's sake.
I'm... I'm Mr. Prince!
"The Terrifying Bananagators and Mr. Prince"
"The Trap of Certain Defeat!
Storming Raindinners"
The rebel army is over
100,000 strong now!
The rebel army is quickly approaching!
Yeah, I heard.
Captain, aren't you going after them?
I know you're in there, Crocodile!
Listen! We must protect
Alabasta by our own hands!
Apparently there've been casualties, too...
No. I'm too tired.
Do not fear sacrifice!
Fight to the utmost of your power!
You're too tired?
Get back here, you!
--Hey...
--Sir!
It's no use going after
those guys. Tell them to stop.
Shoot 'em! Shoot 'em!
It's nothing.
Damn, they're annoying!
Counter the rebel army!
Take up intercept positions!
"The Key to a Great Comeback Escape!
The Wax-Wax Ball!"
Just a little rain will clear him
of these strange suspicions. Yes.
And have everyone assemble here.
Contact HQ, too.
Tell them to have all
military vessels in the vicinity
Bring Alubarna down!
That quieted things a bit.
What on earth?!
of the Kingdom of Alabasta
gather here, to this land.
Tony-kun is a decoy?
--The canal's been destroyed!
--Who would do this?!
Yeah. He'll be fine.
You're calling for reinforcements?
Now we can't bring water to this town!
Let's hurry, Vivi-chan.
But Captain, I'm not sure
our superiors will be willing
Crocodile!
Explain the situation to me.
Are you okay, Koza?
to move those ships against
such a small number of pirates.
But Sanji-san, you were
shot earlier, weren't you?
Come out!
This is nothing!
It hasn't rained for over a year now!
At this pace, we'll reach
Alubarna by morning!
When did I ask for the
opinions of our superiors?
Erumalu is done for!
Me?
Let's continue our march at this speed!
Er, y-yes, sir! Right away!
Right!
Don't hold suspicion, Koza...
The decisive battle will be at dawn!
Hello?
Hey! Come back! Come back here!
I came all this way to kick your ass!
We've caught him! What should
we do with this strange man?!
I don't want to suspect you,
but people are dying of thirst!
Where are you? Tell me!
T-The front gate of a casino
in Rainbase, named Raindinners!
You may not be using it,
but you do have it!
What a coincidence. We're just
about to head to Alubarna, too.
--Crocod--!
--That's not gonna make him come out here!
No. Wait for natural rain.
Dance Powder summons misfortune.
We're dealing with the country's hero!
All right, nicely done.
That was a star performance.
If you'd like to come with us, then do so.
Are you trying to make these
patrons our enemies too?!
Hurry!
Just a little bit should be alright!
Now your boss will show up here.
Alright! What do we do, then?!
Or...
H-Hold on! Without Vivi,
we won't know who Crocodile is!
The rebellion might even stop
if there's at least some rain!
T-Thanks so much. So, can I go now?
Mm-hmm, this way. The scent of
Nami's perfume is getting stronger.
...would you rather save these people?
It would only result in a greater calamity.
Speaking of which, where is Vivi?!
That's--!
No, sir.
It is not as easy to use as you think, Koza.
The key to this cell?! Give it here!
Vivi! Crocodile! Where are you?!
Hey, we're not, by any chance,
just going to run all the way
to Alubarna like this, right?!
Yeah, guess not...
I can't stand to watch
towns dry up anymore!
Look, Chopper. His friends are
starting to crowd around again
That's right, Lashes!
Hey, now!
Where has Lashes gone?!
in the same place that
we were just running wild.
Assistant Manager! Some strange
people have come inside!
Now that you mention it,
Mm-hmm... Next,
it's whatever I can manage.
this town has a stable or something!
Have security take care of 'em.
Don't make such a fuss!
Let's get horses!
You haven't changed a bit
since the old days.
That's right.
But the marines are in town.
I'm counting on you.
Hey! Vivi and Crocodile aren't coming!
Not to worry. Look in front of you.
I have changed. I can fight.
Who are you?
Hey, guys!
I've got you now, Straw Hat!
M-My name is Mr. Prince.
I'm going to...
Huh? So then, you're the one
who did all this to my companions?
Smoker!
A crab?!
You think you can just
scurry all over the place!
Chopper!
I'm going to come here to take your rain!
That's a Moving Crab!
It's Smokey!
R-Run!
Looks yummy!
Whatever I can manage...
Damn! What's that smoke freak
doing here in Rainbase?!
My name is Mr. Prince!
A hole?!
I'd say he's taken quite a liking to Luffy!
Where is this country headed?
This building is surrounded by
a lake! There's nowhere to run!
My name is Mr. Prince!
Please stop, sir!
Where are we headed?
Government officials aren't allowed inside!
Awesome! Awesome! Awesome!
That's awesome!
Move!
It won't be too long before
their fight to the death begins.
Hop on board!
Where does the answer lie?
He's so stubborn!
We get to ride it?! Woo-hoo!
Get back here!
What is the meaning of this?
I can't deal with that guy!
The pleasure's mine!
Even if you hurried to Alubarna from here,
Its face looks kind of iffy, doesn't it?
who knows if you'd make it in time...?
And you've got yet another
amazing thing in tow, huh?
Just a minute, sir.
I have bad news, Koza!
To stop the rebellion, you'd need
to leave at once, Miss Wednesday.
I-It was a man,
calling himself Mr. Prince...
I must ask that you leave--
"Alubarna Palace"
He's Lashes's friend.
T-Terrible news,
Chaka-sama! It's His Majesty!
Or will you save these people instead?
W-What the--?!
What?! What are you saying?!
Huh? Did I just run into something?
Lashes was born in this town,
and has lots of friends in the area.
Though it doesn't help that I accidentally
dropped the key below the floor,
Him?!
He vanished!
That's absurd!
Have you searched everywhere?!
He is kind of pervy, though.
Yes! Not only the palace, but the
garden and storehouses as well!
into the bananagators' den.
Manager! This is terrible!
A strange group of people has...
Amazing! Moving Crabs are
always submerged under the sand,
Send them to the VIP room.
Could he have left
in the middle of the night?
so they're very nearly phantom crabs!
A bananagator!
Out of the question!
The king's security was top-notch,
Owner Crocodile's orders.
This guy's pretty fast, isn't he?
Bananagator?
Bad news! The bridge collapsed!
and he couldn't have escaped our eyes!
Whoa! What's that?! There's an
alligator growing from that banana!
Guys, hang on tight!
Stop!
Then... Then, why?
All right, let's go! We're off!
Why would the king hide himself
just before going to battle?!
W-What is that insanely huge alligator?!
Hey! Look there!
Thank you...
This room is underwater?!
...for coming!
Search! Outside the palace and the towns!
Right this way!
What a weird banana!
And that's more or less what happened.
Yes, sir!
You idiot! Look closer!
This is the VIP room!
It's an alligator with a banana
growing out of it! It's a weird gator!
Is Tony-kun all right?
VIP room?!
Yeah.
Could it mean, "Bring it on"?!
Pell excels in finding people,
but as luck would have it,
He has some tricks up
his sleeve, after all.
he's busy conducting
reconnaissance in Rainbase...
This guy gets right to the point!
Alright! Let's go!
Hey! What happened, Vivi?!
What has happened to His Majesty?
A bananagator swallowed
the key to your cell!
VIP?! What sort of connection
do they have with Crocodile?!
I can't afford to act recklessly...
What?! Chase it and make it spit it out!
I hear something happened
over at Raindinners.
What?!
Damn it!
Depending on that, all of 'em
could get sent to the gallows!
Stop, Chopper!
They say the bridge collapsed.
I can't!
Bananagators are so ferocious
that they even prey on Sea Kings!
But what's a VIP?!
You bastard...
Where did you go, Mr. Prince...?
It's him! Why, you...!
Get near one, and you'll
be eaten in one bite!
Hey! The path splits!
--VIPs go to the left!
--And it says pirates go this way!
I swear, I'm going to
find you, and kill you.
I apologize for clumsily dropping the key.
--Which way do we go?!
--Hurry and decide!
Plus, there's no telling
which one swallowed it.
VIPs, obviously! VIPs!
Hey! Luffy!
That idiot!
But we're pirates! Pirates go this way!
Luffy-san!
Just what are you planning
to do to Alabasta?!
What?!
--The water! The water!
--We're gonna die! We're gonna die!
Yeah! You got a point there!
I can't believe this guy!
You guys go on ahead!
I can handle this myself!
Damn! If we could just get out of here,
I could handle those reptiles!
Would you like to know the type of
people I look down on most of all?
W-Wait!
Once this cage is submerged,
it's all over for us!
You're so dumb, Zoro! We can't
get out because the key got eaten!
Straw Hat!
Hey, you stupid gator! Come and get me!
Huh?!
Hypocrites who treasure the
so-called "happiness of the people."
What in the world is going on?!
I know that!
What's come over you, Nami?!
Well, then.
You intend to kill my father?!
As if you could ever do that!
I can't believe we fell for this trick.
Make sure you deliver Vivi back
to her home! Make sure, now!
My "I Wind Up Swimming when
Falling in the Darkness" disease!
We must be going a little earlier than you.
I'm making that guy mad,
to get him to bite the cage apart!
There's no need to shout.
I have no such intention.
A trapdoor!
I get it! Great idea!
Also, this room will be destroyed
automatically in one hour's time.
Come and get me, you stupid banana!
You rotten banana!
He's not even worth killing.
This secret underground room I've
used as Baroque Works president
Where did everyone go?
No, that's wrong!
I told you, he's basically an alligator,
I'm going to let Cobra taste
humiliation far crueler than death.
Captain Smoker!
is no longer of use.
with a banana on his head.
It will soon fill with water and
be submerged in Rainbase's lake.
What?! Would you shut up?
Make sure, now.
Crueler than death?
For example,
there's the monkey dance, right?
That idiot...
You rotten banana!
Where could Captain Smoker have gone?
One million innocent citizens,
or a mere four pirates with no future?
Listen to what I'm saying!
Hey!
That's no way for a princess
of a kingdom to look.
He should be chasing Straw Hat, but...
Go, Chopper! Keep going, to Alubarna!
What?
For example,
there's the monkey dance, right?
S-She's with the Navy...
Only one choice can be saved,
though the odds are low for both.
I'll ask one more time!
Just what is Operation Utopia?! Tell me!
G-Got it.
A monkey is an animal,
but the monkey dance is a dance, and--
We're off!
Don't touch that!
Learn something, will you?!
Your feelings are your ante, Miss Wednesday.
Now, now. Do you realize where
you stand in this situation?
Hold on...!
Hey Zoro, are we leaving
him behind?! Hey, that's cold!
You eat both alligators
and bananas, don't you?!
Answer the question!
Do you like gambling?
Here he comes!
That's cold of you! From now on,
you've got to protect me, got it?!
You're a valiant princess.
But very well.
The operation has already begun.
With so many fools in this country,
this was such an easy job.
Where do you get off always doing this?!
Oh no! My glasses!
My glasses! My glasses!
I'll tell you about my plan
to end this country...
It's no use!
What a tough cage!
Luffy-san!
The juvenile rebels and the old man
digging in Yuba, for example.
It's all right, Vivi! He'll be fine!
Vivi! Please hurry!
About Operation Utopia...
Now what?! I can't do
anything without my glasses!
Hey, you guys...
I feel sorry for the other guys.
W-What?! You mean the dry old guy?!
Terrible news,
Chaka-sama! It's His Majesty!
After all, there isn't a single person
How can you keep so composed?!
What is it?! Did you find him?!
that Luffy has gone after before,
who has come out all right.
Yes, sir! He's apparently in Nanohana!
The information is certain!
You think up something, too!
Are you all right?!
Umm, have you fainted?!
A foolish old man who keeps
pecking away every day
How much do you guys know?
What exactly is Crocodile after?
Listen to me, Vivi. He will
keep Crocodile under control.
I see! That's a relief!
But... But, unbelievably enough...
Please, say something!
at an oasis that's long dead.
Sergeant Major Tashigi!
The moment that the
rebel army started running,
That woman who was at Crocodile's side...
C-Come again?!
He keeps at it,
despite the constant sandstorms.
Oh, here you are!
the time limit on this land was set.
She's had a price on her head by
the World Government for 20 years.
Yes! I'll be right there!
Oh! Umm--!
Once the royal army
and the rebel army meet,
Why, you--!
--Koza!
--Koza-san!
The price was over 70,000,000, as I recall.
--Wait!
--We're coming too!
Are these...
Tell me, Straw Hat Luffy.
Oh, you found them for me!
You're such a nice person!
this land, the Kingdom
of Alabasta, will be gone.
Why suddenly now?!
S-Seventy million?!
Do you think sandstorms can strike
towns perfectly time after time?
S-So what about it?
If you are the one and only
hope for preventing that,
Eh?
Has he fallen as far as he can?!
That's the same price that Crocodile has.
Thank you! Goodbye!
Don't hold suspicion, Koza.
The moment those two joined forces,
then you have to survive, no matter what.
Why would he do something
this nonsensical?!
this became more than just a simple coup.
--This way!
--Right!
No matter what might happen
to any of us here, from now on!
This can only develop into
a matter that the whole world
She's a world-class dimwit, that's for sure.
will get dragged into, if they're left to it.
What are you saying?
She said I'm a nice person!
"Nanohana"
Y-Your Majesty?
The whole world? What do you mean?
Being praised doesn't
make me happy, you moron!
B-But...
What did you just say?
Not to mention him.
That does seem a little far-fetched.
Just as you heard.
I am honestly apologizing.
What are you guys talking about?
Vivi-chan, this is a fight that you started.
I don't need any excuse
like that to kick his ass!
It was I, Cobra, the king of Alabasta,
who stole this country's rain!
A clever trap.
You're the one who ran out
of this land years ago,
Yeah. It wasn't our fault.
Yuba, you see...
We could have avoided it!
You did exactly what the enemy wanted!
and challenged this unknown
organization to battle.
I see...
Cobra-sama...
How can you joke like that?
...can't be beaten by
some lousy sandstorms!
So, how are we getting out of here?
I can't believe how stupid you are!
However...
Yeah...
Anyways, I'm suddenly out of strength...
It is no joke.
...don't go thinking that
you're fighting alone anymore.
I'll dig it back up as
many times as it takes!
It's up to my thighs!
I used Dance Powder to keep the rain
in the capital city of Alubarna.
How come? Are you hungry or something?
We're gonna die! We're gonna die!
As many times as it takes!
Luffy!
I'm kind of starting to lose my nerve.
As many times as it takes...
As li'l ol' king-- no, I mean, as a
respected king, I cannot go thirsty.
V-V-Vivi! Don't you wor-- wor--
don't worry! I'm g-gonna...
You did it?!
This is bad! This is bad!
Tough it out! Didn't Vivi say so?!
Luffy!
T-That may be so,
Luffy-san!
I-I-I'll fight you if you want, smoke freak!
but many have died due to lack
of food and water as a result!
Must be hard for you, huh, Vivi?
Vivi-chan.
I'm sorry, I know you
don't have time for this.
We'll be waiting for
you in Alubarna, okay?!
I once helped take down a bomb man!
Why would you allow--?!
I have faith in His Majesty!
I am aware of that, of course.
And that many oases have dried up.
Damn it!
Hiyaaa!
if only my swordsmanship were better,
this cage would be nothing!
Huh? I have no strength...
Just like when I fall in water...
He's not someone who would
ever betray the kingdom.
Yeah!
But some sacrifices are unavoidable
if we are to protect the country.
Try as hard as you can not to
make any noise at mealtime.
I-I'll kill you!
What have you done to Luffy?!
This is crazy!
At the tip of this jutte is a
material known as Sea Prism Stone.
You knew how miserable things were,
yet you only helped yourself?!
That's far too selfish even for you, King!
A strange type of stone that supposedly
only exists in one certain sea.
Bad Manner Kick Course!!
Water's leaking in!
Not much is known about it,
Is a mere cretin like you trying
to talk back to me, the king?
but it basically gives off
the same energy as the ocean.
The whole room's gonna be
flooded if we don't do something!
Vivi! Help! Do something!
I've come to Nanohana to
apologize for what I've done.
You can think of it as the sea in solid form.
I don't want only one hour to live!
So it makes Luffy weak?
Princess Vivi got away from us, huh?
Quit freaking out.
All Navy HQ prison cells are made of it.
What more do you want?
Are you crazy, Zoro?! How can
I not freak out at time like this?!
My brother died in Yuba, you know...
Either way, the Agents are
scheduled to gather in Alubarna.
We're gonna die if we don't do
something! Don't you understand?!
To prevent criminals with
Devil Fruit powers from escaping.
Contact them at once.
I have come all the way to
this city for one other reason.
The kingdom or my friends, you say?!
Then this prison cell is the same?!
I doubt you really plan
on giving anything back!
If it weren't, I'd be long gone by now...
As you know, Dance Powder is
outlawed by the World Government.
You've taken your nonsense
a little too far, Straw Hat Luffy.
You plan to take my life too
before I reach Alubarna!
...after making it so none of
you take to the seas again!
If word of its use is leaked outside,
Hey there.
I know full well that nothing
will end unless I beat you!
Navy Headquarters will take
action and destroy said country.
She tries, you see,
Been waiting long?
to help everyone she sees,
despite how weak she might be.
This must be avoided.
Prince!!
Wait! Wait! What good will
fighting in this situation do?!
However, you may remember that
large amounts of Dance Powder
Thank goodness.
You don't even know anything
Stop goofing around
and find the key already!
about this country's people,
history, way of life...
She can't bear to abandon anything,
so she's always in pain.
Besides, he's made of smoke!
Swords won't work on him!
Nami-san!
were found being smuggled
into this town two years ago.
L-Love me now?
She doesn't think that anyone
needs to die in this revolt.
That's correct. Give it up.
It is necessary to eliminate all
traces of that incident. Understand?
You don't know anything about it!
Yeah, yeah, I'm in love,
now hurry and open this up!
Nobody needs to die?
Okay!
There are many maudlin,
peace-loving fools like that.
You don't mean...
The guy is an interminable idiot, huh?
You're going to die together...
That's right! If we are to be rid
of that terrible incident forever,
Vivi! Way to go!
That's because they don't
know what a real fight is.
...so why not get along first?
we must be rid of this city and all of you!
You think so too, don't you?
Yeah.
--W-What?!
--That's insane!
Crocodile!
Here they come, one after the next.
We have to die just 'cause you ordered it?!
What?!
Go, Sanji! Pound them all!
Hey! King!
Vivi!
So it was all your fault!
Do something! Get us out of here!
But as long as you're around,
she's going to go at you, until she dies.
It's...
Luffy-san...
It's because you steal the rain that
all the towns are drying up, jerk!
Bunch together as much as you like,
and come get me, you damn bananas.
Finally starting to beg for
your life, Straw Hat Luffy?
Anyone with manners as poor as yours,
who would attack a lady,
So I'm going to put you down, right here!
But it's only natural.
Everyone is afraid of dying.
gets some table manners
beaten into them, but good.
If we...
That's worse than nonsense.
Sanji! There isn't any time for that!
If we die, then who's
going to kick your ass?!
You're the unsalvageable fool here.
This is a good example.
One-second strikes!
No, make that one-instant strikes!
You get close to someone,
and then die because of it.
I'm gonna avenge everyone...
Take out the third one who just came in.
Don't!
What? You can tell?
King...
I've forsaken tons of people like that.
Don't flatter yourself, small fry.
Are your ears just for show?
His growl is the same as the one
who swallowed the key, isn't it?
Men! Burn Nanohana to the ground!
You're the small fry!
So he's one of the Seven Warlords?
Then,
you're the fool, aren't you?
Yes, Sire!
Looks as despicable as I thought.
Well, this is your chance to
abandon them, Miss Wednesday.
Oh, you really are the wild dog
I've heard about, Smoker-kun.
--Koza!
--Koza-san!
What's so funny?
If you wish to stop the rebellion, that is.
You want to die, too, Nico Robin?
I can't really tell.
It seems you never once
believed I was on your side.
Smart thinking, collapsing the
bridge and buying time like that.
If you feel like it, go right ahead.
But, yes. You're correct.
Besides, didn't you promise
not to call me by that name?
Koza. It's been a while.
There are more of their friends here.
Smoker. I think I'll have you
die an "accidental" death.
Where are you going?
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
Was that to catch us off guard,
and get to the room?
I'm going on ahead to Alubarna.
It's so big!
I'll inform the government
that you fought well
Probably.
I can't figure that woman out.
Alright! Beat it, Vivi!
against the lowly "Straw Hat" pirate.
There it is!
That's crazy talk! It's too huge!
I don't know why you've
come to this country,
Vivi! Run! You can't beat it! But help us!
I'll give you three minutes.
The key to the cage!
but I assume you're on your own.
You're the one who's talking crazy!
Wait! Look out the windows!
The government would
never have sent you here.
I don't have time...
What is that?!
...to mess with you any longer than that.
That doesn't look like a key!
Because everyone trusts me,
as a Warlord of the Sea.
They're all waiting for their turn!
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
We're pretty much being treated as food!
Wax-Wax Ball!!
We're all gonna be in their
stomachs in an hour?!
So you're Crocodile?!
--King!
--Stop!
Release!
I came to apologize, as you can see.
Hey! You! Fight me--
What?!
Oh! W-Water! It's water! It's a miracle!
Quit screwing around! Shut up!
Peacock Str--!
Pay attention! Don't touch the bars!
Do you realize what you're saying?!
This is an incredible insult!
Straw Hat Luffy.
You've done well to come this far.
Hey, it's him!
I-It's fast!
I am the one who's been
using Dance Powder to--
Three! It's Three!
It took a chomp out of the stone
stairs in one instant! What a jaw!
I promise to get rid of you,
so wait a little more.
Mr. 3! What was he doing
in the belly of an alligator?!
I said shut up!
Our guest of honor has yet to arrive.
--Why are you so angry?
--Koza...
Guest of honor?
--Surely even you can appreciate...
--Sire...
Vivi!
I just sent my partner to pick her up.
Damn! These monsters are unstoppable!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
I'm alive again! I thought I was dead there!
--...that I...
--You asshole!
Oww...
Do you know how the people felt
as they died in the dried-up towns?!
That rotten Crocodile!
He may have tried to get rid of me,
--Vivi! Run!
--Get up!
Vivi! It's gonna eat you!
but he didn't try hard enough!
The moment I was swallowed,
They didn't have hatred or anger for you!
I squeezed out the last of my
power to create this Wax-Wax Ball.
"It isn't the king's fault!"
I can't afford to waste time
in a place like this!
"He's a great person!"
Even as they died, they all
said that, with faith in you!
I'll give you three minutes.
But what happens to them now,
Someone's calling.
What's this?
I don't have time to mess
with you any longer than that.
Hand that key over to us!
unless you at least lie
and say you're innocent?!
What?
You've put up quite the fight, Princess.
Hello? Hello?
It's you guys!
Can you hear me?
What? This key...?
Yes, I hear you. You're a Millions, yes?
I'd expect no less from
a former Frontier Agent!
Hey, does this thing work?
You don't mind, do you?
Hold on...
I've never used a
Mini-Transponder Snail before.
A room, forcefully leaking water...
No, that's fine.
Cobra...
Yes, everything is fine.
You can talk just as you are.
But don't you think it's time
you accepted your fate?
...an iron cage... and this key...
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!!
What do you want?
--Koza-san!
--Leader!
Hurry and state your business!
What happened?!
I have to hurry to the others!
Koza!
Oh, I've heard that voice before.
I know what's going on, now.
Well, I guess it's time!
Now come! The boss is waiting!
You're Mr. 3, are you?
Didn't we fight because
the kingdom-- no, everyone--
Heya. You've called
the Damn Restaurant.
You startled me!
Gum-Gum...
Don't touch me!
Are you Mr. 3?
Hand over the key, quietly.
...Stamp!!
wanted to know that answer?!
W-What the--?! What's that bird?!
Gleam!
Here comes a long throw!
What?!
A falcon?!
At the very least...
I should warn you, Straw Hat Luffy,
that no matter how hard you try,
Heya. You've called
the Damn Restaurant.
What is a bird doing with machine guns?!
The Damn Restaurant?
...that's why I fought...
there is no way that you'll ever beat me.
It's huge!
I don't know who you are,
but you appear to be on their side!
Oh, it sounds like you
remember me. That's great.
Shoot it down!
Gum-Gum Gatling!!
If you want the key, go find it!
However, whether or not you are able
to find it, I won't be responsible!
Heya. You've called the Damn Restaurant.
You want reservations?
You can't be serious!
Crap! The princess!
You bastard...
Quit fooling around, dumbass.
Transponder Snail?!
What are you talking about?
Pell! You came for me!
I never used a Transponder Snail
while on Little Garden!
It's good to see you again, Vivi-sama.
Here they come!
I'm certain we have all four
Straw Hat pirates inside that cell.
Listen here, Straw Hat Luffy,
you can continue
How is my father?!
A giant ship is about to crash! Run!
He's well. Both the king
and I read your letter.
these mosquito-like
attacks of yours forever,
All that's left is their pet.
Does this mean there are still others?
What if this person is able
to pick out the alligator
but you will never--
Gum-Gum...
That means Karoo made it
to Alubarna safely?!
that swallowed the key?
What is that ship?!
...Bazooka!!
--Hey, did you hear that?
-- "Damn Restaurant"? Could it be?!
Hmph, it wouldn't do any good.
Even if they were lucky
enough to get that key,
--San--!
--Wait, Luffy!
Yes. He's quite a duck.
The enemy doesn't know about him!
the real key is right here.
Let them struggle as hard as they want.
Thank goodness!
He was in his room when Mr. 2
showed up, so they never met!
Thanks to you and Igaram-san,
we know who we're fighting now.
You are bad.
Sanji-san...
It flew away, it flew away!
That's right! Sanji-san and
Tony-kun are still outside!
Mommy!
Yes.
That bastard...
Vivi-sama. Wait here a moment.
That was smart,
for coming out of nowhere.
I-It's toppling over!
--Pell?!
--Not Pell the Falcon?!
There's no time, Sanji-kun!
Just who are you?
Why, you... you... you...!
Did that smash you?!
That was a good-for-nothing thing to pull...
H-He's the strongest warrior in Alabasta!
Me? I'm...
You sand gator!
...Mr. Prince.
Just a minute, Sanji!
The Bird-Bird Fruit, Model Falcon!
For a final operation,
that sure lacked exertion.
Couldn't his wax-wax power
make a key to this cage?
I told you, that won't work.
I see. Mr. Prince. Where are you?
Only five types in the world are
known to have the power of flight...
You bastard...!
Have we ever had any
exerting work before this?
'Fraid I can't say!
No matter how hard a
rubber man like you might try,
...which you can savor now!
If I did, you'd come get rid of me.
S-Shoot! Shoot like crazy!
there is no way...
Indeed.
Though, setting aside whether
or not you can get rid of me,
We did it! Now light the
fires and let's retreat!
He vanished!
...you'll ever peat--
I'm not so stupid as to give
up information so easily.
"Peat"? What was that
you were just trying to say?
Yes, sir!
Flying Talons!
I just can't feel relaxed without this on!
Unlike you, Mr. 0.
Nicely done, candle man.
Prince! Help! We've been caught!
There's no time!
Koza! Say something! Koza! Hey!
Thank you! Now I have
to hurry to the others!
I think that is just about
enough fun and games,
--The royal army disappeared!
--What?!
--Come rescue me!
--Mr. Prince! Help me!
Really? Aren't you getting
ahead of yourself?
Let's get moving. There's little time.
Straw Hat Luffy.
How deux you like my kingliness?!
Yeah. I'm sure the first route
they took is toward Alubarna.
You've been a real thorn in our side.
I've been taking this
seriously the whole time!
That was great, Mr. 2, Bon Clay-sama!
Sounds like my crew's right by your side.
Miss All-Sunday!
But he's got me. I can't
slug him at all like this.
But there are still so many
bananagators that way!
It looks like our precious
employees are no longer usable...
In that case, I'm gonna--
He's too dry and grainy.
Put out the fires!
Aren't there any more?!
That wasn't enough!
The damn royal army lit fires and ran off!
There's a difference in the level
of pirate that you and I are.
Vice-President...
--Hurry!
--Put out the fires!
Troublesome bastard!
Who are you?!
Now to meet up with Mr. 2 outside town.
Desert Spada!!
Hello?
That was magnificent. I've never
seen someone who can fly before.
Looks like we needn't worry.
We've caught him! What should
we do with this strange man?!
And after I had that much
trouble with one of them...!
Alubarna's the finale.
But, are you stronger than me?
No, their strength is just abnormal,
so don't worry about it.
Sanji-san... No...
I look forward to it.
Vivi-sama. I take it these are
the ones threatening our homeland?
Where are you? Tell me!
Dammit, I can't go all-out,
soaked in water like this!
Vague! My favorite word is "vague"!
T-The front gate of a casino
in Rainbase named Raindinners!
Nicely judged.
Now whether or not the king
will stay king is vague!
I'd like to invite the princess
to our mansion. What do you say?
If you'd taken that, it would have
gotten more than an "ow" from you.
That useless moron!
That bastard better be alive!
The operation's a success!
Where's Bunchi?!
What?! The desert's been split!
He's west of town, Mr. 2, Bon Clay-sama!
Don't ask such pointless queries!
It's out of the question!
Sanji!
Depending on one's training and how
they're used, Devil Fruit abilities
Oh.
Huh? The king turned
into a weird ballerina...
Our hope...
Don't screw with us!
can become a means of
fighting as powerful as any.
The walls are crumbling!
Idiot, that's overdoing it.
I'm not like you other fools, who are
only preoccupied with your abilities.
It's no use! It won't go out!
This is great.
Princesses mustn't use such
uncouth words, Miss Wednesday.
Damn the king!
The passageway is crumbling, too!
Let's go to the front gate.
Out! We're getting out of here!
He was a fake!
You can regret defying me
as much as you want, now.
Is that wise? The Millions still
don't know who their boss is.
This is bad! Everyone's being tricked!
I have to tell 'em!
How dare you kill Igaram...?
I won't be going as their boss.
What a naughty little boy.
What do you think he's discovered?
Desert Girasole!!
Aside from the Number Agents,
no one knows who you and I are.
Igaram? Oh, Mr. 8?
What's so strange about Crocodile,
the owner of this casino,
That damn imbecile
made a careless slip-up.
Don't tell me you killed Igaram-san?!
Those small fry... They're going to pay!
What are you getting so worked up for?
going to see what has happened
in front of his building?
I'll kill them all, right now,
with my own hands!
Who're you?!
How was that any different from
what you did to our employees?
I take it there's no use in
asking you to stay quiet.
It's silly.
What?! What?! What?! What?!
Water! We need more water!
Wait! That's for my shop!
Can you pay for it?!
Vivi!
Not now, you idiot! The town is on fire!
--Put out the fires!
--Water!
What are you doing, Vivi?!
The sand! It's being
sucked into the ground!
What...?
It's no use! We can't
keep up with the fire!
There's still time before
this room fills up with water!
"Catch you later,
you damn gator. Mr. Prince"
We should probably run for it!
I'm going outside to get help!
Damn you!
Hang in there, Koza!
You're not the type to die like this!
Yeah! There's no way he
kicked the bucket just now!
Become sand of Alabasta!
If Vivi can just free him--!
You don't know about quicksand?
And Chopper's outside, too!
We might have a chance!
It makes for a handy desert coffin,
with no need for a tombstone.
Tres Fleurs.
Hey! Take Koza!
Look out, Vivi!
The sand is drawn down
into underground waterways.
Little boy! Say something!
This is terrible! Not even children are safe!
I am able to detect where those are.
Vivi!
Hey, you still alive, Luffy?
No one in the world can stand up
to me when fighting in the desert.
I-It's not...
Enough of your nonsense!
Pell!
What's that?! I'll stop
the bleeding! Don't talk!
Usopp-san, wake up!
Vivi-sama! You're all right?!
It's not what you think!
Everyone's being tricked!
Good grief, what are you doing?!
Swim, like you're supposed to!
I'm not about...
Hang in there, little boy!
Did it look like I killed this girl?
--Vivi! Wake up! Vivi!
--The gator's coming! Vivi!
...to let myself be buried alive in sand!
Koza!
Sheesh, you guys with your abilities
sure bear some hard risks, huh?
D-Damn you! What did you do?!
Let's... end this country.
Don't be so angry. I only teased you.
You bastard! Gum-Gum...
If you love your friends that much,
you can all die here together.
You have Devil Fruit powers?!
...Bazooka!!
Whoa, Smoker!
Contact all of our branches!
This will be our final battle!
Hey now, Zoro, what are you
bringing the enemy along for?!
That's right. I partook of
the Flower-Flower Fruit.
If I can't slug you,
then how about I catch you?
The water will soon turn this
into their feeding ground
Back off! I didn't want to.
He was this close to dying, after all.
Gum-Gum Finger Net!!
The power to make body
parts bloom like flowers.
and submerge the entire room.
O-Okay, but we don't
have nearly enough weapons!
I'll drag your cheeky Mr. Prince
here too, if you'd like!
This is my ability.
Whatever. Let's just hurry on ahead.
No, we do now.
Can't you learn anything? That won't work.
There is no escape from my body,
which can bloom anywhere.
Hopefully you don't mind corpses!
Know that ship that just crashed?
It was an armory ship.
We've lost quite a bit of time.
Vivi-chan, can we still make it?
Gum-Gum...
--I don't know.
--Nami-san...
...Whip!!
Escape?! Nonsense!
--Seriously?!
--Yeah! It was full of weapons!
Damn it!
I'm going to avenge Igaram-san
right here, right now!
Do you still have that perfume
I bought you in Nanohana?
Are you planning to keep doing that?
It's almost like divine guidance.
Huh? Yeah. Why?
I'm sorry. I'd like to play a
little more, but I don't have time.
Put some of it on.
Let go of me, you bastard!
Crescent Cutlass!!
Oh, really? A little pipsqueak
saw me? So sorry! So, so sorry!
Like this?
That's all right! This won't take long!
It makes me fall in love
to the ends of the world!
Oh! Owner Crocodile! Have you
heard what happened in Nanohana?!
It seems you still don't understand.
Come on, get going, seriously.
Sheesh. Now Mr. 4's team
just needs to do its thing...
M-My arm!
Seis Fleurs!
Roronoa!
Yes, I have.
The whole town-- no, the whole country--
is clamoring at the news
Fatty and Old Hag know
how to get things done!
Why did you save my life?
A submission hold?!
that the rebel army and the royal
army are finally about to clash!
Power. Speed. These mean nothing to me.
Kidnapping the king
will be nothing to them!
My arm...! My arm...!
It's turned into a mummy!
My arm has become a mummy!
I'm not surprised. The king does
let pirates attack cities freely.
Because of the sand.
Hear me, rebel army!
The hydration in your arm
has been sucked out.
Clutch!
The Alabasta of old is long dead!
I always thought something
like this might happen.
I could go on wringing the water
out of your whole body like that,
This is the final battle!
We're going to capture Alubarna!
Hey, look! It's Crocodile-san!
Pell!
until you shrivel up and die.
It really is him! He's so wonderful!
We're going to launch an all-out assault!
He rarely shows himself inside the casino!
Such is the essence of the desert.
He was the kingdom's greatest warrior?
The king must pay!
Y-You've gotta be kidding me!
Crocodile-sama!
We'll build a new country!
Hey, Zoro! Save him!
N-No...
I know! Water!
Huh?! He's our enemy! Leave him be!
You're as popular as ever.
Now, let us go.
"Meanwhile, at Alubarna Palace"
Nonsense!
This can't be...
If we leave him there,
he's gonna die, you know!
Cobra-sama would never do
such a thing! It must be a mistake!
Our boss and your friends are waiting.
He can't swim!
That was worthless.
Yeah, well, I know that, but he's...
Quit it with the gloomy look!
But the time between his disappearance
and his arrival fit perfectly!
Nothing worthless about it!
The dried-up old man
in Yuba spent all night
Curse you. When did you touch my face?
Excuses no longer hold any water!
Inside a prison cell in Raindinners.
preparing this water for me!
I was just following the captain's orders.
News of the Nanohana incident
have spread throughout Alabasta,
Luffy-kun, take this with you.
I didn't touch it! I punched it!
Have you forgotten, Musclebrain?!
Look at me, I'm Sanji.
I don't think you necessarily
have to thank me.
and rebel soldiers
everywhere have responded!
The old guy told me...
Not only that, the citizens
who had faith in His Majesty
It was one of his whims. Pay it no mind.
--What?!
--Oh? You wanna fight?
You the one who ate the meat?
Knock it off! Aren't there
others for you to fight?
have begun taking up weapons
out of hatred for him!
...Yuba wasn't going to give in to the sand.
-- "Collier!"
--Act like...
Their numbers are unknown!
--Here's Zoro! "Oni!"
--Act like...
Then, you'd have no gripes with me
carrying out my duties here, right?
Gum-Gum...
The entire country is infuriated
and heading for Alubarna!
You're no fun! Why do I have
to work with someone so un-fun?
Are you still planning to do something?
...serious prisoners!
There's no stopping things now!
See? Didn't I tell you?
That's what you get for saving a marine.
...Munch-Munch!!
How can you act like that in such
a serious situation as this?!
Fun or not, Alubarna has
finally come into view.
We can't get out,
so what else is there to do?!
Please, make your decision!
We will obey you!
Oh? Let me see, let me see!
Oh, there it is!
Don't go pulling ridiculous crap like that!
The fact we can't get out
is what makes it serious!
They're here? The Straw Hat pirates?
So that's Alubarna,
where the drama will unfold?
We might wind up dead
if we don't do something!
Yeah! Captain Smoker
is right there, with them!
And why are you sleeping?!
Where Zero-chan's ambition
will blossom as a desert flower?!
Die. You, along with the
indomitable land of Yuba.
How can this be?!
Let's go back him up!
Oh, is it morning?
Even the king's words from
yesterday are blurred now!
It's noon!
Vivi!
In what do I put my trust?!
All right, men! Full speed to Alubarna!
You're a high-spirited girl.
Your three minutes are up.
Like I said at the start,
T-They've always been there
to help me all this time...
Whatever! Go ahead and act
confident while you still can!
Where is Crocodile?!
Very well! We need only
fulfill our given duties!
I don't have time to hang
around with you any longer.
Once these guys get out of here,
We are the royal guards
of the Alabasta Kingdom!
Ah, they came around.
I refuse to just let them die...
Sables!!
they'll kick your butt and send
you flying above the clouds!
No kingdom should crumble
in the absence of its king!
Isn't that right, Luffy?!
Of course it is, you jerk!
Smokey! You want some of this?!
Protect the truth you see before you!
Protect this kingdom!
You seem to be quite the
trustworthy captain, Straw Hat Luffy.
Wah! It's Smoker!
Counter the rebel army!
Hey, Luffy, don't do it! Let's get out of here!
Yes! She got away!
Trust...
Just how serious is he?
"Rainbase"
The most unneeded thing in this world.
The sand is nice and dry.
Who does he think he is, insulting people?!
It's a sandstorm! I can see a
sandstorm in the sky to the south!
The water's broken through the glass!
This way! Hurry!
Q-Quit! You'll make him mad, too!
Take shelter!
Now we got less than 20 minutes
until this room's submerged!
Wait, the sandstorm isn't coming
this way! It's headed to the south!
What a horrifying plan...
Crocodile!
Captain Smoker, over there!
Well? Do you like it?
Vivi! You alright?!
Vivi!
The operation you once
participated in has now blossomed.
Go.
Everyone! Hang in there a little longer!
Welcome, Vivi, Princess of Alabasta!
No, Miss Wednesday!
But this is the only time I'm letting you off.
Vivi, what's wrong?
I will bring back help!
I promise I won't abandon you!
If you listen closely, you could
probably hear the howls of Alabasta.
There's a sandstorm over toward Rainbase!
I'm impressed you managed to evade
our assassins to come this far!
Next time we meet,
consider yourselves dead.
And they all think the same thing.
Yeah! We're counting on you, Vivi!
It's him.
I would go as far as it takes!
Because I want you to die, Mr. 0!
"Protect Alabasta."
What in the world is this?
Luffy...
"Protect Alabasta. Protect Alabasta."
If only you hadn't come to this country...
Including the employees just
done in by Pell the Falcon,
Stop it!
Wait! Vivi! Let us out!
There they are!
How can you be so cruel?!
it looks like all the Millions
in this town have been wiped out.
...Alabasta would've remained peaceful!
Listen here, Straw Hat Luffy.
Isn't it just heartrending?
The prevailing winds here
always blow from north to south.
What happened?! Hey!
Peacock String Slasher!
Love for the kingdom will be
what destroys the kingdom.
A-A man named Mr. Prince...
If this baby sandstorm of mine
were to catch one of them
Don't let them escape!
Come on, let's go. The marines are coming.
I thought you caught him? Where did he go?!
and grow as it headed south,
It's no use.
Which way is Alubarna?
where do you think the
larger sandstorm will hit?
Over there! Straight to the east!
He just now headed to
the south part of town...
Satisfied?
Just now?
South, you say?
As a citizen of this country,
you surely know
Hey, Luffy! Hurry! What are you doing?!
Him?!
Yuba.
that I have the power
of the Sand-Sand Fruit.
Yeah...
Small fry. Don't think you can escape me.
Why?!
Is he stupid? Did he not hear what I said?
Hey, you! What are you doing?! Stop it!
Why not forget about him?
Want to become a mummy?
Quiet. I've always killed everyone
who's made a mockery of me!
They won't get away this time!
He's definitely stupid.
But that's also why he's our captain.
Look. Little by little,
it's starting to head south.
A s-sand person!
Hey, you! Get away from Vivi!
I'll kick your ass!
That dried-up old man
has nothing to do with this!
You're not unlikable, you know?
Crocodile! I will kick your ass...
Sit.
Why, you...! Stop it, you!
Perfect timing. The party is just starting.
Stop, you bastard! Stop!
Whoa! An earthquake?!
Correct, Miss All-Sunday?
So many moves I've made
to make it this far...
Get going, already!
This is bad! The bridge into
Raindinners has collapsed!
Yes.
Party?
Give it up, it won't work.
Just out of the blue?!
The sabotage to instigate the citizens.
It just turned noon.
Operation Utopia is beginning.
What's going on?! What caused it?!
That sandstorm will pick up strength,
Directing the royal army's misconduct.
and obtain wind speeds
that even I can't stop.
Hey! What's going on?!
Operation Utopia?
Have you any idea why I'd go to
such lengths to attain this country?
What's an "Operation Utopia"?
You've gotta be yanking me!
--Now we can't get back to town!
--Aren't there any boats?!
Yuba is finished.
As if I'd understand anything
inside your rotten head!
What's going on?!
Don't let them get away!
Stop it! Right now! Stop--
You really are a bad-mouthed princess.
Hey!
The bridge fell!
Oh no! I can't go outside now?!
It's not about not going outside.
Vivi!
It will be this pathetic little
kingdom that dies, Miss Wednesday.
Now, now. What are you
trying to do, Miss Wednesday?
It's about keeping Baroque Works
from coming back in.
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Stop you!
Who do you think I am?
I'm going to stop you! There's still time!
It's all part of the plan.
If I can just get to Alubarna east of here...
All right, guys!
Head straight for Alubarna!
I'm going to wipe Alabasta
from the face of the earth!
Chopper's running around
town as a decoy as we speak.
If I can get there before the rebel army,
I may be able to stop them!
There are any number
of rookies like you,
We gotta hurry. The rebellion's begun, too.
All people, big and small,
will be sucked into eternal darkness
who are nothing but talk,
Sanji-san!
as they writhe in pain.
I absolutely refuse to let you have your way!
Straw Hat Luffy,
Think you could tell me
where they are, Princess?
here in the Grand Line.
Let Operation Utopia...
Vivi!
...commence!
Like the adventurers
I dreamed of when I was a child
I always wanted to talk about it
I continue on to the ends of emotion
I couldn't even say half of it
I scoop up my hands, and the sand
and time that spills from them
I'm by your side, I glitter
every time we share a dream
show me that this is what
I was born to do
The smile you gently gave me
was a very happy and kind one
Let's continue swimming
at a near-tumbling speed
Glory glory you're my shine
Until we wash up someday
on a white sandy beach
Because you're here, even
these tears turn to courage
I want to be strong,
I want to share with you
no one knows about
I'm sure I'll make it there
--Alabasta is going to die?
--What does he intend to do?!
Whoa! There's a whole bunch now!
It's Crocodile!
What?! The crab can't cross this river?!
What is that insanely huge alligator?!
Aah! He's come after us!
Wow! There's an alligator
growing from that banana!
He's a desert creature,
so he can't handle the water.
We're gonna die!
The operation has begun.
This country will fall.
I can handle him alone!
You guys go on ahead!
I'm suddenly out of strength...
But it's still a crab. Do something!
Don't be stupid!
That idiot!
Do something. Scissors-kun.
Hey, now! Endure it!
The alligator swallowed the key to our cell!
At the hands of the royal army,
the rebel army, and the people!
Let's keep on moving, to Alubarna!
Damn! If only I were a better swordsman,
this cage'd be nothing!
I know! Scissors loves dancing girls!
What?! What a troublesome gator!
We're leaving him behind?!
Luffy-san! We'll be
waiting for you in Alubarna!
What is that eyebrow freak
doing at a time like this?!
Will this do?
Heya! Been waiting long?
Love for the kingdom will be
what destroys the kingdom!
You're messing him up with this nonsense!
Hang in there a little longer,
everyone! I will bring back help!
Oh! Prince!
Yeah!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Dash For a Miracle!
Alabasta Animal Land"
"Operation Utopia Commences!
The Swell of Rebellion Stirs"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Key to a Great Comeback Escape!
The Wax-Wax Ball!"
"Merciless Mortal Combat!
Luffy vs. Crocodile"
"The Terrifying Bananagators and Mr. Prince"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!