Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"Rainbase"                 "Alubarna"
"Yuba" "Erumalu" "Nanohana" "Katorea"
"Spiders Café"
Three years have passed
since a single drop of rain fell
in the kingdom of oases.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people take up weapons.
The scorching land was now
engulfed in wails of grief,
along with tremendous upheaval.
Crocodile's plan was
finally being carried out,
and Bon Clay, transformed into the false king,
had appeared in Nanohana.
A rebel army had also risen up.
Meanwhile, Vivi was escaping,
in order to tell Sanji about the peril
that Luffy and the others were in,
having been caught in
a trap within Raindinners.
Will Alabasta fall?
Or will it find true peace?
Moment by moment, the hourglass
of fate marks the final hour.
I'm... I'm Mr. Prince!
"The Key to a Great Comeback Escape!
The Wax-Wax Ball!"
Tony-kun is a decoy?
Yeah. He'll be fine.
Let's hurry, Vivi-chan.
Explain the situation to me.
But Sanji-san, you were
shot earlier, weren't you?
Me?
Hello?
We've caught him! What should
we do with this strange man?!
Where are you? Tell me!
T-The front gate of a casino
in Rainbase, named Raindinners!
All right, nicely done.
That was a star performance.
Now your boss will show up here.
T-Thanks so much. So, can I go now?
No, sir.
Yeah, guess not...
Look, Chopper. His friends are
starting to crowd around again
in the same place that
we were just running wild.
Mm-hmm... Next,
it's whatever I can manage.
That's right.
I'm counting on you.
Who are you?
M-My name is Mr. Prince.
Huh? So then, you're the one
who did all this to my companions?
Whatever I can manage...
My name is Mr. Prince!
What is the meaning of this?
I-It was a man,
calling himself Mr. Prince...
Him?!
Bad news! The bridge collapsed!
And that's more or less what happened.
Is Tony-kun all right?
Yeah.
He has some tricks up
his sleeve, after all.
I hear something happened
over at Raindinners.
They say the bridge collapsed.
You bastard...
Where did you go, Mr. Prince...?
I swear, I'm going to
find you, and kill you.
--The water! The water!
--We're gonna die! We're gonna die!
Once this cage is submerged,
it's all over for us!
Hey, you stupid gator! Come and get me!
What's come over you, Nami?!
I'm making that guy mad,
to get him to bite the cage apart!
I get it! Great idea!
Come and get me, you stupid banana!
You rotten banana!
No, that's wrong!
I told you, he's basically an alligator,
with a banana on his head.
What?! Would you shut up?
For example,
there's the monkey dance, right?
You rotten banana!
Listen to what I'm saying!
What?
For example,
there's the monkey dance, right?
A monkey is an animal,
but the monkey dance is a dance, and--
Don't touch that!
Learn something, will you?!
You eat both alligators
and bananas, don't you?!
Here he comes!
It's no use!
What a tough cage!
Vivi! Please hurry!
Hey, you guys...
How can you keep so composed?!
You think up something, too!
How much do you guys know?
What exactly is Crocodile after?
That woman who was at Crocodile's side...
She's had a price on her head by
the World Government for 20 years.
The price was over 70,000,000, as I recall.
S-Seventy million?!
S-So what about it?
That's the same price that Crocodile has.
The moment those two joined forces,
this became more than just a simple coup.
This can only develop into
a matter that the whole world
will get dragged into, if they're left to it.
The whole world? What do you mean?
That does seem a little far-fetched.
What are you guys talking about?
I don't need any excuse
like that to kick his ass!
I see...
So, how are we getting out of here?
It's up to my thighs!
We're gonna die! We're gonna die!
I'm kind of starting to lose my nerve.
This is bad! This is bad!
Tough it out! Didn't Vivi say so?!
Must be hard for you, huh, Vivi?
I'm sorry, I know you
don't have time for this.
Damn it!
if only my swordsmanship were better,
this cage would be nothing!
Try as hard as you can not to
make any noise at mealtime.
Bad Manner Kick Course!!
Hey there.
Been waiting long?
Prince!!
Thank goodness.
Stop goofing around
and find the key already!
Nami-san!
L-Love me now?
Yeah, yeah, I'm in love,
now hurry and open this up!
Okay!
The guy is an interminable idiot, huh?
Vivi! Way to go!
Here they come, one after the next.
Go, Sanji! Pound them all!
Bunch together as much as you like,
and come get me, you damn bananas.
Anyone with manners as poor as yours,
who would attack a lady,
gets some table manners
beaten into them, but good.
Sanji! There isn't any time for that!
One-second strikes!
No, make that one-instant strikes!
Take out the third one who just came in.
What? You can tell?
Are your ears just for show?
His growl is the same as the one
who swallowed the key, isn't it?
I can't really tell.
Smart thinking, collapsing the
bridge and buying time like that.
There are more of their friends here.
Was that to catch us off guard,
and get to the room?
Probably.
There it is!
The key to the cage!
What is that?!
That doesn't look like a key!
Wax-Wax Ball!!
Release!
What?!
Oh! W-Water! It's water! It's a miracle!
Hey, it's him!
Three! It's Three!
Mr. 3! What was he doing
in the belly of an alligator?!
I'm alive again! I thought I was dead there!
That rotten Crocodile!
He may have tried to get rid of me,
but he didn't try hard enough!
The moment I was swallowed,
I squeezed out the last of my
power to create this Wax-Wax Ball.
What's this?
Hand that key over to us!
It's you guys!
What? This key...?
Hold on...
A room, forcefully leaking water...
...an iron cage... and this key...
I know what's going on, now.
You're Mr. 3, are you?
You startled me!
Are you Mr. 3?
Hand over the key, quietly.
Gleam!
Here comes a long throw!
What?!
I don't know who you are,
but you appear to be on their side!
If you want the key, go find it!
However, whether or not you are able
to find it, I won't be responsible!
You bastard...
What if this person is able
to pick out the alligator
that swallowed the key?
Hmph, it wouldn't do any good.
Even if they were lucky
enough to get that key,
the real key is right here.
Let them struggle as hard as they want.
You are bad.
It flew away, it flew away!
That bastard...
That was smart,
for coming out of nowhere.
There's no time, Sanji-kun!
That was a good-for-nothing thing to pull...
Just a minute, Sanji!
Couldn't his wax-wax power
make a key to this cage?
Indeed.
Nicely done, candle man.
Let's get moving. There's little time.
Yeah. I'm sure the first route
they took is toward Alubarna.
But there are still so many
bananagators that way!
Aren't there any more?!
That wasn't enough!
Looks like we needn't worry.
And after I had that much
trouble with one of them...!
No, their strength is just abnormal,
so don't worry about it.
Dammit, I can't go all-out,
soaked in water like this!
The walls are crumbling!
Idiot, that's overdoing it.
The passageway is crumbling, too!
Out! We're getting out of here!
Those small fry... They're going to pay!
I'll kill them all, right now,
with my own hands!
What...?
"Catch you later,
you damn gator. Mr. Prince"
Hey, you still alive, Luffy?
Usopp-san, wake up!
Good grief, what are you doing?!
Swim, like you're supposed to!
Sheesh, you guys with your abilities
sure bear some hard risks, huh?
Whoa, Smoker!
Hey now, Zoro, what are you
bringing the enemy along for?!
Back off! I didn't want to.
He was this close to dying, after all.
Whatever. Let's just hurry on ahead.
We've lost quite a bit of time.
Vivi-chan, can we still make it?
--I don't know.
--Nami-san...
Do you still have that perfume
I bought you in Nanohana?
Huh? Yeah. Why?
Put some of it on.
Like this?
It makes me fall in love
to the ends of the world!
Come on, get going, seriously.
Roronoa!
Why did you save my life?
Hey, Zoro! Save him!
Huh?! He's our enemy! Leave him be!
If we leave him there,
he's gonna die, you know!
He can't swim!
Yeah, well, I know that, but he's...
I was just following the captain's orders.
I don't think you necessarily
have to thank me.
It was one of his whims. Pay it no mind.
Then, you'd have no gripes with me
carrying out my duties here, right?
See? Didn't I tell you?
That's what you get for saving a marine.
They're here? The Straw Hat pirates?
Yeah! Captain Smoker
is right there, with them!
Let's go back him up!
All right, men! Full speed to Alubarna!
Where is Crocodile?!
Ah, they came around.
Smokey! You want some of this?!
Wah! It's Smoker!
Hey, Luffy, don't do it! Let's get out of here!
Just how serious is he?
This way! Hurry!
Go.
But this is the only time I'm letting you off.
Next time we meet,
consider yourselves dead.
There they are!
Don't let them escape!
Come on, let's go. The marines are coming.
Which way is Alubarna?
Over there! Straight to the east!
Hey, Luffy! Hurry! What are you doing?!
Yeah...
They won't get away this time!
You're not unlikable, you know?
Get going, already!
Don't let them get away!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
All right, guys!
Head straight for Alubarna!
I always wanted to talk about it
I couldn't even say half of it
I'm by your side, I glitter
every time we share a dream
The smile you gently gave me
was a very happy and kind one
Glory glory you're my shine
Because you're here, even
these tears turn to courage
I want to be strong,
I want to share with you
I'm sure I'll make it there
It's Crocodile!
Aah! He's come after us!
I can handle him alone!
You guys go on ahead!
That idiot!
Let's keep on moving, to Alubarna!
We're leaving him behind?!
Luffy-san! We'll be
waiting for you in Alubarna!
Yeah!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Merciless Mortal Combat!
Luffy vs. Crocodile"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!