(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
We all have different places we want to go
But first, we need
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
Sparks fly, no limit
This is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
Are your dreams still pure?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
Still, all of us
In the middle of an adventure
All of us, I tell you travelers
No such thing as a pointless fight
When random contexts
Start to make sense on their own
The threads of time are spun back together
The world keeps changing along with us
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
"Powers on a Different Level!
Luffy vs. Lucci!"
This is real!
Shaka revealed what happened on Ohara
22 years ago.
"The Will of Ohara!
The Inherited Research"
Look, Chopper! It's not a holoholo!
Luffy and the others met Vegapunk,
the world's greatest scientist,
Did it used to work?
MARINE HEADQUARTERS
Why are the Giants doing that?
OHARA, WEST BLUE, 22 YEARS AGO
The Straw Hats are at Egghead?!
and learned about astounding
scientific technology from 900 years ago.
Only technology of the future
could make it work...
It's been a while, Vegapunk.
Why?!
Isn't it too old?!
Dragon!
According to the report,
they seem to be siding with Vegapunk.
SEVERAL MONTHS AFTER THE BUSTER CALL
For example, if I said...
They know the value of the books.
there was an advanced kingdom
like Egghead 900 years ago,
See?!
Their captain is a strange man
with bandages all over his body...
Things are getting complicated again!
would you believe it?
He said, "Ohara saved their legacy
while sacrificing their lives,
CP-0's attempt to land on the island
There was some power in the past
seems to have set them off
on an interception mission.
that defies the common knowledge
of the world today.
and I won't let it be erased
from history."
Does that mean that Vegapunk
was aware of CP-0's purpose?!
"A Forbidden Piece of History!
A Theory Concerning a Kingdom"
We can't replicate
that iron giant perfectly
I will build an army that can fight!
even with our scientific technology.
Yes. That's why they forced their way in.
Good job protecting them.
Just you wait, Vegapunk.
900 years ago?
It's shameful...
You guys won...
I'm gonna change the world!
I feel it was fate
that brought you here today.
It's a victory for Ohara!
What are you talking about?!
I won't let Clover's death...
That's like a declaration of war.
Do you mean a futuristic city like this
existed that many years ago?!
and the will of Ohara go in vain!
I wish those brats had asked me first!
Later that year, Dragon teamed up
with Bartholomew Kuma
I need you to take me away
from Egghead-Quasar!
Anything else?
We already lost communication,
so we don't know anything more.
to create the Revolutionary Army
that now rocks the world!
It's just a theory.
Around the same time,
Cipher Pol "Aigis" Zero
Who is it and what is he doing here?
A man who once risked his life
for archaeology...
If Vegapunk has Straw Hat on his side,
was approaching Egghead.
The mystery of the world
that Ohara unraveled
That's...
shed light on a certain ancient kingdom.
we could lose
a tremendous number of forces.
Sea Beast Weapons...
They're like the gate keepers of Egghead.
lives on in my brain
and I've been working on that research.
And the manufacture of machinery which
has been discovered at a certain site
Pull it up!
Where's Kizaru?
Fire!
He's already on his way to Egghead
coincides with the reign of that kingdom.
The name of the Giant captain is...
The Giants?!
for the mission
we've been working on for some time.
Why are they doing that?
Was that machine built
during the 100-Year Void?!
Do they know
how valuable those books are?!
Saul, isn't it?
Tell Lucci to wait
until the Marines arrive.
He is hiding now.
How much do you know about that?
Yes, sir.
I must keep it a secret from everyone.
They want us to let them enter the port!
It's not good to have pirates here!
Robin! Do you know something?!
No matter what,
don't let him fight Straw Hat!
I bet you don't even want to think back,
The books...
What are they gonna do with them?!
EGGHEAD, NEW WORLD
Thank you, Vegapunk,
but 22 years ago,
It hasn't changed.
your birthplace Ohara was destroyed
by the marine's Buster Call.
Many intruders! Evacuate immediately!
for not letting the battle of
the people of Ohara be in vain.
Pythagoras, tell the ship
Your head is distinctive.
I recognized it at first sight.
Evacuate immediately!
to leave the Seraphim and go.
What?!
Meanwhile, Bonney ran into Vegapunk
at the scrap heap, and...
I'll carry her, Chopper!
Prepare to intercept! We'll deny
the World Government's request to enter!
Yeah, let's take her to Franky ASAP!
I believe...
Luffy, come with us...
that's because Ohara learned of
the existence of that kingdom.
It's rare that you're willing to fight.
Now change my father back!
It's been a while, Vegapunk.
If you say no...
MONKEY D. DRAGON
LEADER OF THE FREEDOM FIGHTERS (AGE 33)
The 100-Year Void...
Dragon!
contains the history of the conflict
between the advanced kingdom
What?
Your head has enlarged again.
Go ahead, guys.
and the Twenty Kingdoms.
Luffy!
"Preparations for Interception!
Rob Lucci Strikes!"
DR. VEGAPUNK
HEAD OF THE PUNK HAZARD LAB (AGE 43)
This is not good...
Enough about that!
Hey, look what you've done.
It seems like that person ate a failed
Devil Fruit I left at Punk Hazard.
Why are you here?!
That's my question, Vegapunk.
I don't give a damn.
The Twenty Kingdoms who won the battle
I knew the old man Clover.
Don't, Luffy!
This is not the time for quarreling!
I spent 20 years
and a lot of research money
later founded the World Government
and created the world as we know it.
She's injured!
What? You, too?
to create it
from Kaido's Bloodline Elements.
Well...
And to prevent anyone from inheriting
that ancient kingdom's ideology,
He used to be a rascal
traveling around the world.
You're right...
How about this robot?! Move it for us!
You know you shouldn't fight him, right?
Lucci!
Please leave!
they erased it completely from history.
The nonsense about him
trying to destroy the world...
Is this your creation?!
Don't do it!
I can't believe it!
is a ridiculous disinformation campaign.
No, it's not...
What?! What?! Is that true?!
This is the legendary iron giant that is
said to have attacked Sacred Marijoa
Yeah.
Are you wondering what they're doing?
What an exciting story!
200 years ago!
I can't let them take away
those valuable books!
It's too grand a story
for me to comprehend...
Yeah, I mean, "erase completely"?
"The Eccentric Dream of a Genius!"
They're not bandits.
I've already checked them out.
Guys, I'll leave you the rest!
Wait a minute, Vegapunk!
What?
Attacked Sacred Marijoa?!
If Ohara received a Buster Call
because of that,
They came from Elbaph.
Okay. I got it.
that means people who learn about this...
Once it wakes up,
it's gonna be big trouble!
They know the value of the books.
Clank.
Yeah, they'll be killed.
Nothing you say seems to help.
SCRAP HEAP, FABRIOPHASE
EGGHEAD
Their captain is a strange man
with bandages all over his body...
Is it a deadly weapon?!
Hey! We didn't even ask!
Why did you tell us about it?!
What should we do, Lucci?
In addition...
it was built...
Damn! I've heard it!
900 years ago!
We have no choice...
He said, "Ohara saved their legacy
while sacrificing their lives,
Everyone, get ready to abandon ship!
What?! No way!
I've heard it so...
It's a little hard to believe.
and I won't let it be erased
from history."
Let's forget it! I don't know anything!
Using the Seraphim S-Bear's power,
we'll fly to Egghead.
Oh, so you're quite something!
I didn't hear a thing!
I don't know anything!
-I didn't hear a thing! Forget it!
-Calm down a little.
How did you attack them?
Did you shoot laser beams?!
-I didn't hear anything! Forget it!
-I said it was just a theory.
As soon as we invade, this ship
Hey! Let me see it! Robonosuke!
This is horrible! I don't wanna die!
will fall prey to the Sea Beast Weapons.
I'm glad that you
and your World Government people
Please! Please! Please!
Now, Nico Robin.
didn't find out about this
and destroy the books.
You're hitting it too much!
You'll break it!
Yes, sir!
If Ohara was destroyed
because of this theory,
That's quite a risky move.
Hey, wait! I won't do that...
What did the iron giant
attack Marijoa for?!
I thought it was a joke!
People won't like you
if you're so impatient.
don't you think that means the Government
has admitted it to be true?
I can't believe you finally became
the Government's dog.
If you wanna be swallowed by the sea,
do what you want.
About that!
Oh, how scary.
After you turned down our invitation
to join the Freedom Fighters.
I don't know what it wanted...
Do it!
Vegapunk...
What?
Whose side are you on anyway?
Don't be a fool!
The scholars of Ohara continued to study
the valuable materials and made a theory...
Even with my wisdom and skills,
what can I make
in a poor army like yours?!
With a position as high as yours,
would the Government tell you?
I got it.
You're as honest as always.
No, they didn't tell me anything...
What's that on your wanted poster?
The World Government
is a huge organization.
The rule still stands.
While I am affiliated with the Government,
I'll be killed if I mention it.
There are people who listen to you too,
especially in the marines.
What was that?!
It came from the city...
Are you curious about it?
Of course I am.
Don't mistake your target, Dragon.
Maybe Kuma is on a rampage again.
I heard it ran out of power
so no damage was done.
Then I don't wanna know!
No, that explosion was outside the island...
I know, but...
This is like torture!
Get me out of here!
Seems like CP-0 is causing the commotion.
But it must have been quite a surprise
to the scientists of the time...
This incident hit me hard.
Then how did you find out
about the kingdom?!
Zero?
Harmless scholars who just questioned
the unreasonableness that is the law
They're those who work only on
the orders of the Celestial Dragons.
Because that advanced technology
was so out of place!
The books that Ohara acquired
from all over the world must be...
What's CP-0? It's not CP9?!
were crushed by violence!
The will of Ohara lives on.
It's even surprising now after 200 years!
They're superior to CP9.
I think it's better
if it just stays asleep...
That day,
the world was thrown into confusion...
I will build an army that can fight!
When they move,
it's said to be an omen of
a major historical event.
Ohara, an academic island with
the most advanced knowledge in the world,
But you despised war!
After all,
no one knows where this iron giant
came from and what it was trying to do.
Just you wait, Vegapunk.
I'm gonna change the world!
was destroyed overnight
leaving just one girl behind...
JOYBOY
I won't let Clover's death...
It's amazing!
The World Government ordered
its complete destruction,
and the will of Ohara go in vain!
DRUMS OF LIBERATION
What a futuristic city!
I feel it! Feel it! Feel it! Feel it!
Feel it! Feel it!
Ohara was accused of being
an evil group of scholars
I can't help getting excited!
but the curiosity of scientists
would not let that happen,
plotting to overthrow
the World Government.
Later that year, Dragon teamed up with
What's going on?!
Are they Cipher Pol?!
Usually, they're all in black suits.
Emporio Ivankov...
so here it is,
passed down to the present day...
Several months after the incident,
Why didn't they come
from the port as usual?
I visited Ohara.
and Bartholomew Kuma...
Even the Government
doesn't know it's here.
Hey!
Because I knew the late Professor Clover,
the archaeologic czar,
I heard two of the Sea Beast Weapons
were beaten up at the shore!
to create the Revolutionary Army...
that now rocks the world!
Don't tell me...
so I wanted to lay flowers.
they're intruders!
You knew him?!
Yeah.
He was obsessed with the 100-Year Void,
Hey, why don't you fix it?!
Shaka! CP-0 is on the island!
Damn Iva... I didn't know he was a founding
member of the Revolutionary Army!
I wanna make it my own robot
and operate it!
and went on adventures
to scour the world for documents about it.
They're here!
Luffy's dad is so passionate!
Don't be a fool!
That bastard is as annoying as always!
He was arrested by the marines,
and jailed ten times...
Wait a minute! Did you just say Elbaph?!
I hate him! Go away, Rob Lucci!
Anyway, I'm surprised you made it here.
I feel like my brain's gonna explode!
There he is!
The entrance to this place must have
looked like just a wall from the town.
Why did Kuma help us?!
And he became the most famous
archaeologist in the world.
I can't move!
Set us free already!
I am an officer of the Revolutionary Army.
Eventually,
scholars who were impressed by him
came together at Ohara,
I have a connection with them,
and I want to help them get out of here.
I won't let them touch Robin-chan!
Ouch!
Luffy!
and the island became
the center for archaeology.
Luffy vanished!
Why did you modify Kuma?
How did they come ashore?
I was in a hurry and senile at the time.
Is that... Luffy?!
Vegapunk!
You can say the tragedy occurred
because he was talented.
I didn't know Dragon-san and Dr. Clover
had such a relationship!
So that's
We wandered in here
while our brains were feeble!
the Warrior of Liberation!
The past belongs to all mankind.
Sorry to hear that.
The books of Ohara certainly
should not be found by the Government...
I see.
LABOPHASE
EGGHEAD
No one has the right to stop one from
wanting to know our unspoken history!
200 years ago...
This is gonna be fun.
Their ship has been
destroyed by the Beasts at the shore!
That year, Fish-Men were granted rights.
Yeah.
We asked them to leave,
but obviously they didn't comply.
That year, the Kingdom of Ryugu
affiliated with the World Government,
By analyzing the ancient
documents and some Ponegliffs,
In anticipation of our attack,
and was allowed
to participate in the Reverie.
But I went to Elbaph in secret
out of my own interest...
The robot attacked the Celestial Dragons.
I wonder who was behind it...
they probably
flew in by Paw-Paw Fruit power!
we eventually noticed
the existence of a country.
They used S-Bear.
If you're raided by that giant,
there would be no way to stop it!
They're willing to sacrifice
their ship to fight.
There is no trace of it left now,
I still can't believe it.
If that's what they want,
it can't be helped...
but what the documents brought to light
was the existence of a grand kingdom.
Are you saying this humongous robot
climbed the Red Line?!
Lucci!
Tell all researchers and workers
to evacuate!
Although it seems to have
boasted much power in the past,
Okay!
It would seem so.
And I read all the documents.
If you look closely, this robot looks like
the one that carried us here.
the information on this country
has obsessively been erased.
Yeah.
They probably sensed they'd be defeated
by the allied countries,
Vegaforce-01
was modeled after this iron giant.
later to become the World Government,
So...
Tell Atlas to get back to the lab!
Men are so stupid!
the mystery of the world
that Ohara unraveled
and so inscribed all the truth on stones
to pass it down to the future.
But there was something
I couldn't replicate
Get the Seraphim ready to launch!
What the hell is that?!
lives on in my brain
and I've been working on that research.
Luffy got bleached!
even with my scientific capability.
Let Sentomaru lead them!
Indeed, those stones are the Ponegliffs
that remain to this very day.
Something that even you,
a genius scientist, can't replicate?
That's it!
That's the Luffy who kicked Kaido's ass!
Energy-fill, start!
I see. That's a bold hypothesis.
It's the power source.
Can I ask you something?
The power source?!
96!
The white warrior!
It's true that the Ancient Weapon
would threaten the world.
There was some power in the past
97!
That strange man
with bandages all over his body...
98!
However, isn't it actually that
the World Government is more threatened
that defies common knowledge
of the world today.
99!
We can't replicate
that iron giant perfectly
Listen carefully, Robin!
Hey, Pigeon! Where are you?!
Signals all green!
You're alone now, but you'll
meet friends someday for sure!
even with our scientific technology.
by people becoming aware of
that kingdom's existence and ideology?
I'm going to open the confining walls.
It's shameful...
Let's fight more!
Seraphim, number one, three, and four.
I'm glad that Luffy and the others
are okay, but...
That captain of the Giants
who hauled out the books from Ohara...
The name of this once-prosperous kingdom
that holds the key to everything is...
who is that girl?
No one is born into this world
to be alone!
Your attitude is flippant as always.
That's Jewelry Bonney, a pirate!
Wait a minute! I thought it was
a little girl that we found at sea!
The name of the Giant captain is...
It annoys me!
Ohara has...
And look at Vegapunk's head!
Seraphim, number one.
come to know too much.
Is Bonney okay?
S-Hawk!
Saul, isn't it?
I think she'll wake up soon.
Give the attack signal.
I'll initiate a Buster Call!
He is hiding now.
Seraphim, number three.
I feel really bad for Bonney.
I must keep it a secret from everyone.
S-Snake!
You should, old man!
Get down on your knees!
You don't know a damn thing!
Seraphim, number four.
Thank you, Vegapunk,
S-Shark!
There is something...
I have to give to her.
for not letting the battle of
the people of Ohara be in vain.
Launch!
By the way, Straw Hat Luffy.
Straw Hat!
I'm well versed in all branches of study.
I feel it was fate
that brought you here today.
You're not the only one who got stronger!
If the World Government targets me,
it's only a matter of time
before they kill me.
It's the way of a true scholar.
CAT-CAT FRUIT, MODEL: LEOPARD
AWAKENED FORM
Fate?
And now, CP-0 is here
and I'm gonna pack up my stuff so
When I set foot on Ohara,
the place was an absolute disaster.
I...
What's that?!
I need you to take me away
from Egghead-Quasar!
Did Rob Lucci always look like that?!
take me out to sea-Quasar!
Don't say it like
it's a field trip or something, old man!
Stop, Lucci!
We haven't gotten permission yet!
What is it?!
Even the Tree of Knowledge
was burned to the ground,
If you disappear,
it would be big news worldwide.
and it seemed like everything
was reduced to ashes.
He's so fast!
The shoes are moving on their own!
It's so rare!
Your head is funny, so why not!
Typically, when a Zoan type Fruit awakens,
it robs the user of their personality!
But when I walked deeper into the island,
Is that the reason?!
I knew you would say yes!
I witnessed something astonishing.
I can't release you guys but follow me.
What are they?
Then, let's go up!
What is all of this?!
There's something I want to show you.
This place will be a battlefield.
A vast amount of books of all kinds
I want you to bring Bonney
to the Labophase above the clouds.
were submerged in the lake
at the center of the island!
Yeah, okay!
Perhaps the scholars stayed on the island
which was burning under the Buster Call,
You guys, take the Vacuum Rocket
from the Fabriophase!
Sea Beast Weapons...
They're like the gate keepers of Egghead.
Kiss my ass!
and died protecting the legacy
they were to leave for the future.
Vacuum Rocket?!
Sounds like fun!
SCRAP HEAP, FABRIOPHASE
EGGHEAD
Okay, see you up there.
The books that so many scholars protected
at the risk of their lives...
Meet me as soon as possible!
-Prepare to fire at any moment.
-Yes, sir!
Cool! Guys, look!
Even if ignorant soldiers found them,
they wouldn't know how valuable they are.
What?!
He vanished!
Wait, wait, Luffy!
Old Man Apple!
Think about your position!
This could cause a major uproar!
I'm like Sanji!
It's a victory for Ohara.
The future confuses me...
Do you like my invention?
When I saw it,
I couldn't stop my tears from falling.
Yeah! You're impressive!
Hey, look at that!
This is Cipher Pol.
There's a monster!
Allow us to enter the port of Egghead.
What?! Then he is the real Vegapunk?!
Please take care of Robin!
Please let my daughter escape
from the island at any cost!
Respond! This is Cipher Pol.
Shaka!
What?! No! What about you, Mom?!
Aren't you gonna come with me?!
Oh no!
Yeah! But...
Did the white warrior appear?!
Allow us to enter the port of Egghead.
What happened to your head?!
The real one!
Fire!
But he was just down there a second ago!
Olvia... What are you gonna...
It was bigger
and looked like a light bulb!
There's still something
that I have to do here, so...
I can't believe it!
My head?
It's no use!
Tell me! What is this transformation
Mom! I don't wanna be separated!
Guns don't work on it!
It had grown quite long so...
he underwent?!
I cut it.
Of course not!
I'll stay here, too!
Don't say it like you cut your hair!
We don't know much about it!
It's the Gum-Gum power, right?!
Robin...
Peashooters like those are powerless
against a creature beyond our imagination!
You're an Ohara scholar,
so you should know this very well.
Indeed, at the time I met you,
What badly trained pets.
One of the Devil Fruits,
the Gum-Gum Fruit!
I almost reached the height of a Giant!
History is the treasure of mankind.
I've always wanted to
fight something like you.
It'll certainly light up the future
you young ones will live in.
There was a sighting of Jewelry Bonney
heading to Egghead!
I'd heard rumors that it was big...
You look not of this world.
It was like a balloon.
She escaped repeatedly. What a nuisance.
There is no such Fruit
You're...
But the history we received
from the past will disappear
in the old Devil Fruit Encyclopedia!
You cut your head and are still alive.
How is it possible?!
a space monster, aren't you?!
unless we pass it on to the next era.
She is no longer of use to us, right?
We'll eliminate her once we see her.
-Put out the fire!
-Protect the books!
What?!
All right! Let's fight!
Save as many books as we can!
Well, actually I'm...
No, no! Even if you say that...
Throw the books out of the library!
Shaka, there's a Government ship!
He says "Gum-Gum."
a Brain-Brain-Brain-Brain...
Revealing the history isn't
what Ohara was trying to do.
Ow, ow, ow... I bit my tongue...
The Government?!
We just wanted to accept the voices
of the past and protect them.
I bit... my tongue...
They want us to let them enter the port!
It's not good to have pirates here!
How beautiful he is!
Are you okay, old man?
Tempest Kick!
Our research will end now,
but even if Ohara is obliterated
Well, actually I'm...
I knew it was fate!
I didn't expect to meet him like this!
Of course not.
What?!
We don't wanna get caught, either.
a Brain-Brain Fruit user and a Brain-Man!
Hey, if you know something, tell us!
we cannot give up the future
you young ones will live in!
Furthermore, for some reason,
they have CP-0...
I can memorize all kinds of knowledge
without limit,
This one is quite tough!
What happened to our captain?
I mean, Rob Lucci on the ship!
It's no use.
but my brain gets bigger and bigger
in proportion to the data capacity!
What should I do?!
This appearance of his...
What?!
It's a hologram.
I don't understand!
Lucci?!
He resembles a being in the old books.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?!
A data bank of unlimited capacity
You know a lot about this place, Stussy.
You will understand someday.
on top of the brain of a genius
with which I was born!
Why are you panicking?
Yeah, this place is nostalgic...
He resembles a god!
It has grown into the biggest brain
in the world and is still growing!
We can just turn them in!
Rob Lucci is an assassin, right?!
Now...
A god?!
When it comes to this,
Go, Saul!
It's Luffy! And he's an idiot!
I'm gonna see what's above the clouds
while I'm in the air!
Still? Is it somewhere else?
Hey! Release my feet now!
Are you saying
this is the appearance of a god?!
I'm sure Vegapunk will be there!
What are you talking about?
Are you sure about this?
-No! I don't like him! Didn't he quit?!
-Stop it! Let me go! Stop it! Let me go!
Yes.
Do you see those two lines
on the clouds, Lucci?
No! I'll stay here, too! Mom!
Yeah.
You cut your head, so you're stupid?
-Don't let him in!
-Stop it!
The Warrior of Liberation
who plays the fool
Don't mess with a genius, you little brat!
Lucci, that bastard! I'll fight him!
Mom!
Yeah.
and makes people smile!
This apple...
Once their enemy crosses past those lines...
Robin-chan, don't worry! I'll protect you
as many times as I have to!
Live, Robin!
is an antenna!
Also known as
An antenna?
Thank you.
The Sun God!
Look at the highest point of the island!
Shaka...
Nika!
"Punk Records"
is written underneath the giant egg!
Laser beams are activated.
Be proud, Robin!
Your mom is honorable!
Pythagoras, tell the ship...
That's my brain storage!
Someday,
pass down this island's history, Robin!
Kaku-san!
to leave the Seraphim and go.
It's called the Frontier Dome.
What?!
Isn't it too big?!
It's a defense system
encircling the Labophase.
Ohara fought against the world!
Even when I'm away from it,
there's no problem at all
Prepare to intercept! We'll deny
the World Government's request to enter!
because I'm connected to it
by brain waves through this antenna!
It's rare that you're willing to fight.
Nika? I've never heard that name before.
That's awesome!
So you better not underestimate
the world's greatest scientist.
Are you acquainted with medicine too,
Dr. Vegapunk?!
No wonder. It was erased from history.
What's the matter, Robin-chan?
Why didn't you tell him sooner?
Of course I am!
Hey! How dare you make her cry,
you helmet fool!
What?!
Hey! You're so mean, Stussy!
But as long as people yearn for it,
its existence will never disappear!
You guys met a girl earlier who identified
herself as Vegapunk, didn't you?
-Unforgivable! Vegapunk! I'll kick you!
-Gee! How insensitive you are!
Are you warmed up now?
So get these shoes off me, you bastard!
All things are brought into this world
because they are desired!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
-Get them off!
-Look at me, you damn helmet!
She punched me.
For example...
Who is it?!
She's one of my clones
and there are six of them on the island!
The Devil Fruits!
What?!
Are you a ninja?!
Kuma-san, you should not move!
Is it Shadow Clone Jutsu?! Nin, nin!
KAMABAKKA QUEENDOM
Vegapunk.
Who is acting more violently
You're still under repair!
The Devil Fruits...
Just as you guessed,
than me on Egghead?!
Each of them is an expert
in the fields I require!
are manifestations of the people's
aspirations for human evolution!
Ohara uncovered
the existence of the kingdom.
I'm...
I see. Then that's a fact.
Shaka is always calm and good!
gonna kick your ass!
Dragon-san! Kuma-san is acting strange!
"I want to be like this."
"I want to be like that."
01 GOOD (SHAKA)
Where are the books...
that were in the lake now?
Kuma?!
All the different powers represent
the diverse futures of humanity!
-Kuma-san!
-What's wrong?!
Who is that giant girl?!
The evil Lilith
is even willing to plunder!
I wanted to bring them back
to Punk Hazard,
Is that a hologram, too?
02 EVIL (LILITH)
Is he still being manipulated
by the marines?!
And so, that "unnaturalness"
but if the higher-ups heard about it,
it would all be over.
No.
comes with the punishment of being loathed
by the mother of nature, the sea!
An inventor, Edison!
That's Atlas.
03 THINKER (EDISON)
One of the Vegapunks.
Actually...
Atlas-sama!
The wise Pythagoras has an inquiring mind.
Beat them up!
I ran into those guys that day.
The power-users...
Please!
04 PYTHAGORAS (WISDOM)
Kuma-san! Where are you going?!
Yeah, leave it to me!
You're not even fully healed yet!
I see...
Atlas's job is to be violent.
are the ones
who live in different realities...
05 VIOLENCE (ATLAS)
So she's my prey.
"Eat Poop Sleep." The greedy York!
that someone dreamed up!
06 GREED (YORK)
What's going on?!
The six of them together
comprise my personality.
I don't know! It was out of the blue!
That is my theory!
He should have lost
all sense of himself by now...
But their work output
is six people's worth!
You don't even need to think about
whether or not there is a god!
Kuma!
Kuma-san, come back!
I'm gonna defend the peace of Egghead!
What are you talking about?
Once daily, they synchronize their
experience and knowledge via Punk Records.
What happened, Kuma?!
Where are you going?!
Isn't this world interesting?!
Their personalities
and missions are different,
Hey! Stop that cutie now!
Hey! There's no cockpit
on this thing, Chopper.
Do they know where they are?!
making each experience worthwhile!
Rob Lucci is a crazy guy!
-Kuma-san!
I know!
This isn't a playground
for the Government and pirates!
You all share the same brain?
It's beyond my comprehension.
Atlas! Wait!
We haven't checked under its jaw.
Stay here!
SENTOMARU
MARINE HEADQUARTERS SCIENCE TEAM CAPTAIN
Jaw?
You're no match for them! Retreat!
The Revolutionary Army's battle
is just beginning!
Ring, ring, ring...
Just think of it as us
using the same library.
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Okay!
Shut up!
Today is my day off.
General Franky has its cockpit
at the front,
I'm gonna teach
these evil intruders a lesson!
What took you so long, Sentomaru?!
but since this is so big,
it could be someplace we never imagined.
For example,
Hey! Old Man Punk! What should I do?!
Ultra...
if anyone in the world
could have access to my brain,
Wait!
I don't see anything from here...
Cipher Pol is our ally!
Pirates are our enemies!
I can't believe this idiot
is a Vegapunk clone...
Kuma-san!
All right, Chopper. When there is a robot...
Should I just fight alongside CP-0?!
it would be as if all humankind
had acquired my knowledge!
Yeah, we've got to do it.
No, it's not like that, Sentomaru!
Let's go!
We're not here to play!
The thing is I am CP-0's target!
Furthermore, if all humankind can mutually
update Punk Records continuously...
Combine!
Old Man Punk! What did you do?!
Pirates Docking Two!
Kuma...
Did you rebel against the Government?!
We're a robot warrior on a search mission!
I'm sorry
but I want you to drive CP-0 away!
...we can create a sea of knowledge
that far exceeds my brain!
Let's show everyone!
Our combined power!
Wait a minute!
That will make me a traitor!
SCRAP HEAP, FABRIOPHASE
EGGHEAD
All right! Rocket Booster!
Who are they?
...Mighty...
That one looks like Jimbei!
All humankind can share
the same brain someday!
Leave it to me!
What are they doing?
You're right. I must ask your opinion!
Pu...
Does that mean I can study medicine
all over the world?
-Where is the cockpit?!
-I guess you can't understand.
Of course!
n...
Cipher Pol!
Thank you for returning the Seraphim.
Sentomaru...
ch!
That's a dream come true for them.
You owe me a favor
I don't quite get it, but...
We deny your request.
Please leave the Seraphim and go.
for saving you
A dream, huh?
from poverty
Is there a door? I don't think it's here.
S-Bear can come home on his own
from there.
in the past!
But wouldn't it be inconvenient
if ideology were to enter into it?
Six King Pistol!
-What are you gonna do?
-You're pressuring me!
I can't find it either.
Please excuse the businesslike response
necessitated by our busy schedule.
It's not here?
Good guess, "First Son of the Sea" Jimbei.
Maybe it's on its back.
But if we worry about such things,
Please order S-Bear to return,
and with that, your mission is complete.
Yeah, let's get down then.
we can't advance science!
No, behind me there's...
Atlas-sama!
Thank you for your work.
He has no mercy.
Sorry!
Whoa-whoa, don't be so cold!
Don't move your head!
Sorry! I'll be careful!
That nature of yours is the problem,
Vegapunk!
Did they catch on?
Is he gonna fight us?!
It was a long trip!
Let us have a cup of tea on the island!
Didn't you hear what I said?!
They got three Seraphim.
You're willing to sacrifice everything
for the sake of scientific inquiry!
What?
It's cold, too!
This is gonna be tough!
Marine Branch G-14 is nearby.
Hey, S-Bear! Take one of them down!
That's why you
Please go there to relax.
Phew!
turned my father into a heartless weapon!
Don't move, S-Bear!
Oh, come on!
How could you be so cold?! Gee!
What did they combine for after all?!
There's no chance, Kaku!
We have a worse hand!
Are you Dr. Vegapunk?
Stop, Bonney!
That beam saber is a failure!
Yes!
S-Bear! Get rid of those officers!
The disappearances at Egghead
ring a bell with you, don't they?
Shut up! I've already tested it!
I guess there is no cockpit.
Atlas-sama got knocked out
by the intruder!
Relax, Bonney! Think about it!
Why does Cipher Pol behave so violently?!
Retreat!
Think how many people will
turn against you if you kill him!
They're supposed to be
on the Government's side! Why?!
What's that?
Ah! Maybe this robot is autonomous!
Who disappeared?
Everyone on the Fabriophase! Evacuate!
I don't care!
Two months ago,
one Cipher Pol No.5's ship...
Oh, one of those?!
Now change my father back!
I see...
If you say no...
We're in trouble.
A month ago, Cipher Pol No.7...
Maybe it'll react
if we say something to it!
-I repeat! Evacuate now!
-It's an evacuation order!
Yeah.
Sentomaru overrides
the Authority Chips that we have!
-Everyone, run into the factory!
-This is an enemy attack!
Two weeks ago, Cipher Pol No.8...
Turn off the switch, Bonney!
Like... Like...
I repeat! Evacuate now!
This is an enemy attack!
Move! Move, robot!
Are you begging for your life?!
Yeah. The Pacifistas follow
a hierarchy of authority
Not a single Government ship
that has visited Egghead
No!
and their priorities
depend on who issues the orders.
It didn't work...
That beam...
She's still alive...
I wonder what the magic phrase is...
in the past two months has returned.
Let's eliminate her first.
No! It must have a name!
We should call that!
Why?
First, the highest priority
is the Five Elders.
What's that?
Rocket! Rocket!
Move, Robonosuke!
Where is the rocket?!
Is that true? That shouldn't be.
That beam...
The second is Dr. Vegapunk.
Our records confirm
that all ships have departed...
Come to think of it, we don't even know
where to get on the rocket.
That's not it...
The third is Sentomaru.
What?
Let's call it by different names!
AUTHORITY CHIP
Yeah!
...attracts a lot of insects!
Hey, what are you talking about?!
How long will we continue to run?!
Authority Chip holders
like us are the fourth.
Move, Robomaru!
Do you suspect
we're messing with Cipher Pol?!
I wish we could have asked him
more specifically where it was!
Move, Big Robo!
No matter what we do,
Sentomaru's commands will be prioritized!
Move, Robotaro!
Screw you!
Lilith! Don't be aggressive!
Move, Miracle Robo!
If we keep running, we'll find it! Rocket!
Robo Ace!
Then we'll ask the Five Elders
to stop them!
I'll let you in,
so why don't you look through?!
Victory Robo!
Well, we've already done a lot of running!
It's no use!
Robo King!
-Don't do that either!
-Let go of me!
They must be commanded directly!
We have nothing to do with it!
Hurry up! Let's go up!
Even if it's the Five Elders,
Gee... What are you guys, kids?
Please leave!
the Pacifistas won't take orders
through Transponder Snails!
Via the Vacuum Rocket!
Okay. I got it.
There's no way
you could get it to work like that.
Clank.
And if you think about it,
Nothing you say seems to help.
it'll be the Government's loss
if we take down the Seraphim!
What should we do, Lucci?
Damn Lucci! He didn't even think ahead!
We have no choice...
What?!
What's this place?
Straw Hat.
Take you away from here?
Why? This is your lab, right?
I'll explain later.
The pigeon guy!
That's right!
This is the island
where the future is created!
Luffy!
Look at this.
I've used all the facilities as I want,
Are you okay?
extracted a lot of money
from the Government for research,
Yeah...
Luffy!
What was that?! The robot exploded?!
Good! They're all fine!
Rob Lucci!
and continued my research as I please!
Did they really come to
get rid of Vegapunk?!
No, it wasn't an explosion.
What are they doing?
Gum-Gum...
Egghead is amazing, isn't it?!
Then what just happened?!
Why are you here?! Pigeon guy!
Mole
Hey! Wake up!
Hey!
Even now, ideas are flowing
and I can't stop them!
Pistols!
Hey! Bonney!
Help me-Quasar!
There are so many ideas
that time, number of hands,
"Quasar"?
and funds are still not enough!
This is the Government's island.
Oh, no! I failed again!
Let's do it!
A great stag beetle!
S-Snake! Guide Straw Hat
and the others to the Vacuum Rocket!
Cut it out! Why don't you
worry about her passing out?!
Somebody, help me-Quasar!
You're right! We're the ones
who weren't supposed to be here!
Are you gonna make something
more awesome?!
Maybe space-time distorted
while I was warping!
So they can get to the Frontier Dome!
Do you guys want to see it?!
That doesn't matter now!
I do! I do!
S-Hawk, S-Shark! Hold CP-0 back!
Let's escape to the upper level
in a hurry, Luffy!
Was that old man there before?
The weapon she picked up was a failure
and that saved my life...
-I'm sinking! Hey!
-I don't think so.
I'm gonna change the future
with my own hands!
How annoying! The Straw Hats?!
My body's sinking!
But it's no wonder... No wonder...
Chopper! I can't believe my eyes!
And what are you gonna make?!
Somebody!
There's Jewelry Bonney, too.
All those darker-skinned ones resemble
the former Seven Warlords of the Sea!
Bonney wants to kill me.
Tell us!
It's nice if we can get rid of them
all at once...
All right!
I think she needs to rest for a while.
I don't know what's going on.
Old man, do you need help?!
With science,
I want to make a world like this someday!
But don't do anything, Lucci!
Yeah! They look like you all!
Since Straw Hat is an Emperor of the Sea,
A world where energy is provided
to everyone, free of charge!
I can't believe
they made clones out of us!
Oh yeah, you guys.
we can't fight him
without permission from the top.
I heard you were in the Land of Wano
until recently.
He's right.
The Four Emperors often have allies.
Help me-Quasar!
Our plan is screwed up!
Mm-huh.
You don't seem to understand much!
Is it true that another dragon appeared
besides Kaido?
What the... You're just like Kin'emon.
A skirmish could lead to a war.
Are you gonna give everyone something?
Report to the Navy now.
Yeah!
It sure would be great if it could happen.
Yes, ma'am!
It's Momo!
I know I shouldn't fight him...
Hurry up!
The resources that produce energy
It seems like that person ate a failed
Devil Fruit I left at Punk Hazard.
are always the seeds of war
as countries fight over them.
I'll get you out!
Thanks!
That's right! How stupid people are!
Muscle! Muscle!
Oh yeah?
Failed?
I thought so! It's him!
Energy...
That was a Devil Fruit
that I synthesized myself.
Take Bonney, Jimbei!
You can feel it!
It's here, there, and everywhere!
Thank you!
I spent 20 years
and a lot of research money
By the way, you're Dragon's son, right?
This world is full of energy!
to create it
from Kaido's Bloodline Elements.
Who are you, old man?
You...
But it didn't turn out to be
a fruit of the same composition.
I knew you were here. I'm glad you came.
And you're Bonney!
If we can convert it into tangible power,
That's why he could transform like Kaido!
What's the matter?
It wasn't a failure!
You've grown up.
we can eliminate one major cause of war
from the world!
He breathes fire and is strong!
He's a guardian of the Land of Wano now!
How awful!
Vegapunk!
I'm glad to see you doing well!
This girl...
So you created that! Impressive!
Hey! Ax!
We just saw her!
Old man, are you floating?!
Oh, if you're hungry...
I'm sure science can get us there someday!
What was the color?
You're wearing them, too.
It's an Automated Cooking Machine!
What was the dragon's color?
It's been a while!
What?
The leftover ingredients auto mode
is particularly handy!
Those Dom Shoes have a hover function!
Pink.
Straw Hat!
Don't talk to me cheerfully
calling me by my weapon's name!
What?! A hover function?!
You don't seem interested!
You aren't listening!
See?! It's a big failure!
No, anyone who tries to
make everyone happy is admirable.
How can we use it?!
We're enemies!
First, press the button on the side...
I'm not interested in
becoming a hero myself though.
Gee...
That doesn't matter...
Are you going to help Old Man Punk
get out of here?!
Chopper, check on her!
I see. He's a genius and a perfectionist.
Now, why do you wanna get out of here?
Oh, this one.
Okay!
And this lever!
The thing is
Yeah, he asked me! No problem!
Then...
the more I try to create
the energy I seek,
Push it further down!
I think this is more of
Franky's specialty...
I don't know if I can rely on you or not.
Like this?!
That's it!
How about this robot?! Move it for us!
I can't believe
you were named an Emperor of the Sea!
the closer I get to the power source,
the ancient energy
And that look of yours is ridiculous!
Is this your creation?!
that powered
this ancient mechanical soldier.
No, it's not...
Hey.
This is the legendary iron giant that is
said to have attacked Sacred Marijoa
And my nature as a scientist
makes me want to take a peek at it.
We've flown too far!
Did you do this to her?
I wondered what I would learn
when I unraveled the forbidden history!
200 years ago!
Help me-Quasar!
Stay out of it.
This is the Government's business.
In the process of carrying on my friend's
will, I went deeper and deeper into it...
I don't know what you came here for...
Hand Pistol!
THE MAN WITH THE BEST BRAIN IN THE WORLD
The man with the best brain in the world.
Ax!
A genius scientist, Dr. Vegapunk, appears!
But she gave us food to eat!
Vegapunk.
The commander just needed
to be eliminated.
That's how I went too deeply
into the forbidden history!
Seraphim, follow our orders!
The Government's gonna eliminate me
just like Ohara!
I'm here to eliminate you.
LEADER OF THE MARINES'
SPECIAL SCIENCE GROUP
How far I have run
Without knowing it, I counted scars
A treasure map in my head all along
Still looking for the future
The real promise
Lies much deeper in my heart
A dream
That no one can catch up with
That's all I hold on to
To you who smiles like the sun
I'll sing the same song as that day
This wish I don't want to forget
Even when I grow up
Until it reaches you
"Tell Me, Robin!
Chopper's I-Wanna-Learn-More-You-Fool!"
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
Hey, guys! I'm Chopper,
the ship's doctor of the Straw Hats!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
I'm Robin, an archaeologist.
Robin, I can't wait to learn as always!
Today we'll introduce this one! Kaku!
Today we'll introduce this one! Sentomaru!
Today we'll introduce this one!
Emporio Ivankov!
In this segment, we'll introduce people
to look out for from Punk Records!
Information can be a strong weapon.
Let's keep learning!
He is the captain of
the Marine Headquarters science team
He was the foreman of Dock One of
the Galley-La Company,
He's the ruler of Kamabakka Queendom and
and claims to have
the world's tightest defense.
the captain of Revolutionary Army
Grand Line Forces.
Today we'll introduce this one!
Monkey D. Dragon!
Yeah! Today we'll learn about this one!
a company of shipwrights!
He is apparently good at
repelling his opponent's attacks.
But that was only his cover.
He is a Horm-Horm Fruit power user
Jaguar D. Saul!
He's the Chief Commander of
the Revolutionary Army!
He was actually an agent of CP9,
the World Government's secret agency.
who can manipulate people's hormones
and alter their bodies.
He is a Giant and a former marine
Vice Admiral.
The Revolutionary Army is
He was born on March 10th and
likes rice balls and baked sweet potatoes!
an organization that seeks to dismantle
the World Government.
He and Kuzan, also a former marine
officer, were close friends.
He was born on August 7th
and likes bananas and sponge cake!
He was born on January 8th
and likes grilled organ meat!
He's Marine Vice Admiral Garp's son
and Luffy's father.
He was also working for
Marine Admiral Kizaru,
He was born on March 6th
and likes roasted whale.
He hid his true identity and
When he was being held at Impel Down,
he secretly created New Kama Land,
and cornered the Straw Hats
who assaulted a Celestial Dragon
successfully captured Robin,
the survivor of Ohara,
But they don't look much alike.
and Franky who had the blueprints
for the Ancient Weapon Pluton.
He was born on October 5th
and likes bocaditos!
on Sabaody Archipelago two years ago.
When he met my mother Olvia,
built an army,
and waited for the time to rise in revolt.
They're like sandwiches.
But he let them get away
due to Bartholomew Kuma's intervention.
he began to question
the marine's brand of justice.
After returning to Enies Lobby,
the Island of Justice, from Water Seven,
There he met Straw Hat Luffy
who showed up to rescue Ace.
He apparently saved Luffy's life once, but
Luffy didn't see his face at that time.
And he ran away from the marines
along with my mother.
he ate a Devil Fruit.
Later, he led an army of Pacifistas
Ivankov healed Luffy
who had been exposed to a deadly poison.
The Ox-Ox Fruit, Giraffe Model!
He washed ashore on Ohara...
He's from Goa Kingdom in the East Blue.
and cornered the Whitebeard Pirates
in the Paramount War,
It allows him to transform into a giraffe.
Then he met you!
Ivankov is an officer
in the Revolutionary Army,
The inequality in his home
and took down
the Luffy imposter Demalo Black.
Both its power and appearance
are shocking!
Yes, he protected me from the Buster Call.
was one of the reasons
he founded the Revolutionary Army.
so when he found out that Luffy is
their Chief Commander Dragon's son,
This country is an example of
how the world will be in the future.
his eyes popped out!
You're alone now,
but you'll meet friends someday for sure!
Straw Hat is not scum like you!
And in the Paramount War that he took
part in after escaping from prison,
There can be no happiness in a world
where the undesirables are thrown away.
I've become square with no blind spots.
he feverishly protected Luffy again
from Akainu of the marines.
Using the power,
he fought against Zoro of the Straw Hats
The sea is vast, so someday, definitely...
Keep your hands off of Straw boy!
Jet Pistol!
Someday I will change the world!
who came to rescue Robin,
After returning to Kamabakka Queendom,
you'll come across friends
who'll protect you!
Straw Hat...
but got taken down and
gave Zoro the key to Robin's handcuffs.
By the way, it seems like he is the one
who saved Sabo in Goa Kingdom.
he met Sanji who had been sent there
by Bartholomew Kuma.
No one is born into this world
to be alone!
He is using Haki!
I heard he went through a lot after that,
but now he's a member of CP-0.
See ya!
They had a good relationship
despite their bickering.
After the fall of the Donquixote family,
I think I'll see you somewhere again!
he summoned all leaders
of the Revolutionary Army.
Ivankov is a compassionate person.
A Marine officer and a pirate.
They're enemies,
CP-0 has a not-so-shallow connection
with the Straw Hats.
You were a prophet.
Let's see what he'll accomplish
as a member of the Revolutionary Army!
They infiltrated the Holy Land
but maybe he somewhat
thinks highly of Straw Hat.
There could be more turmoil.
and declared war
against the Celestial Dragons!
That's it for today!
Who is it?!
That threw the whole world in tumult!
That's it for today!
I took over this segment!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
That's it for today!
No!
See you next time!
The Drums of Liberation
echo throughout Egghead!
CP-0 makes a forced landing at Egghead.
A scientist with an inner passion
The amazing scientific power
of 900 years ago
is revealed in front of the iron giant!
and a young man with a fighting spirit
to start a revolution.
Facing Luffy's freewheeling Gear Five,
Lucci awakens the madness of a wild beast.
Fabriophase is confounded by the arrival
of the ruthless Massacre Weapon,
Vegapunk, who is fascinated
by the energy of a faraway antiquity
Vegapunk and Dragon's past
is revealed by Shaka.
Rob Lucci, and his team!
A wish for the future
quietly passed down from Ohara's scholars
To protect the people trembling in fear,
The clash between
creation and destruction!
and who is overflowing
with ideas and ideals.
Atlas now confronts the enemies
with her huge, raging fists!
The fateful confrontation
What lies ahead in the future
that he dreams of?
moves the hearts of the Straw Hats
from the next generation.
sends the Future Island
into a whirlpool of chaos!
On the next episode of ONE PIECE!
"The Eccentric Dream of a Genius!"
"Preparations for Interception!
Rob Lucci Strikes!"
"The Will of Ohara!
The Inherited Research"
"Powers on a Different Level!
Luffy vs. Lucci!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!