Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Indeed, tomorrow is a
day to commemorate.
How the Black Cat Pirates have fallen...
These are just in the way.
No!
Right?!
It's not a lie!
U-Us, feeble?!
--There it is...
-- "Cat Burglar"...
Pirates really are going
to come, aren't they?
You're nothing but the
son of a filthy pirate!
I'm not that great at the
One-Sword Style, but...
I refuse to let them enter the village!
Yeah. They're definitely gonna show up.
Zoro!
Straight north! Straight north!
But everyone thinks it's a lie!
Let's go, Butchie!
Thanks!
They're in big trouble
if they touch my treasure!
Okay! Let's do it, Siam!
Tiger Trap!
I love this village!
I want to protect everyone!
Dammit! What do I do?!
I can't climb up!
Filthy?!
Alright! We'll help you out!
Get up!
I feel for you.
These are Klahadore's
pirates we're dealing with!
Damn it! If I just had another sword!
You must truly hate your
great idiot of a father
Nami, you jerk!
Of course I'm scared!
What's wrong with that?!
for abandoning his family and village
because of his lust for treasure!
We ain't laughing!
Outta the damn way!
If I can just get Zoro his swords...
Klahadore! Stop this!
As if we'd risk our lives
because of sympathy!
I can't let you get past this slope...
Run away, Kaya!
Don't you dare insult
my father any more!
"Clash with the Black Cat Pirates!
Great Battle on the Slope!"
I devoted myself to you...
What do you need swords for?
Because I only lied, like I always do...
For so long!
So the village is going to have
just another ordinary day!
Yes, it was all so that
I could kill you today...
"Luffy, Back in Action!
Miss Kaya's Desperate Resistance"
So I absolutely won't let you go!
Damn you!
They're late...
They all know full well what happens...
...to those who upset my plans...
I'll slaughter them all!
If you hate getting hit that much,
I got a hundred more punches for you!
Only then will I inherit
her enormous fortune!
Alright. They're going to attack
from this shore at daybreak.
"Beat Kuro! Usopp the Man's
Tearful Resolve!"
But the only route into
the village is this one slope.
Hey, you guys! Don't attack that girl!
Everything else is cliff,
making it tougher to come through.
In other words, if we can
defend this slope to the death,
the village won't get attacked!
"The Terrifying Duo!
Meowban Brothers vs. Zoro"
Oh! That's easy!
--What was that?!
--What did he do?!
Talking about it is, but the
rest depends on our strength!
To think that these brats
have held you back...
It looked like his arm stretched!
--Get real!
--He sent Captain Kuro flying!
What can you guys do?
--Cut.
--Stretch.
How the Black Cat Pirates have fallen...
--Steal.
--I can hide.
You're gonna fight!
I'm just kidding! Geez!
Right... Jango?!
About time...
B-B-But... you said letting that kid
go wouldn't cause any problems!
Oh, Klahadore-san! Welcome back!
"Expose the Plot!
Pirate Butler Captain Kuro"
--How is she?
--She's resting now.
Y-You guys are that strong?!
I leave the rest to you!
She seemed quite exhausted...
I'm gonna get me some treasure!
Yeah!
But to think such a thing happened
while I was at the next town over...
What took you guys so long?!
Yes, I did say that.
You're the one who
got me stuck back there!
But so what? We knew he was
going to try to stand up to us.
That Usopp lad certainly
knows how to cause trouble.
--The Usopp Pirates have arrived!
That was an accident!
It couldn't be helped!
Yes...
And of all things,
he claimed you were a pirate...
It's better for one person to be saved
--You guys!
--Stay away!
The only thing I didn't count on...
than for two to stay down there...
Such a transparent lie!
Our captain's been gone a long time...
Say your prayers, butt-ler!
Then you should've stayed!
...was you guys' feebleness!
Luffy, too.
It's punishment time!
Seriously! How am I supposed to
know which way north is and isn't?!
It was a big shock for him...
Lousy pirate!
Disrupting this village's peace!
U-Us, feeble?
S-Stop!
Indeed.
He always watches the sea from
the shore when he's feeling down!
Who're you calling feeble?!
--Darn you!
--Take this!
What?! You're the one who ran
off first, all full of confidence!
Watch what you say, Captain Kuro!
You brats! What are you doing?!
What're those runts doing?!
What is this?
That was just because.
Yeah, you were strong before!
Oh, that seems to be a
present from her to you.
Stop that, you guys... Stop!
Night is long gone now...
But that was three years ago!
--Captain!
It's not like we partied while you
lived the easy life in this village!
It's your third year at this mansion,
He-- Captain Kuro--
has a short temper...
so it's a sort of commemoration.
Alright! We'll let you off with just that!
'As right! We've attacked lotsa
towns and sunk lotsa pirates!
Hey, men! Don't tell me those
two brats did you all in?!
Commemoration...
Huh? Wasn't Luffy with him?
Your current glasses seem to slip often,
Now Captain Kuro is really mad!
so she custom-ordered those!
--Captain!
Your point being...
She's such a nice, thoughtful person!
Where's Luffy?
Wasn't he at the shore with...
Those stupid brats!
You've done nothing for three years!
Listen! We don't have time
to be dilly-dallying here!
Captain!
There's no way you can beat
the Meowban Brothers of today!
I knew it! You were fighting, Captain!
If our enemy is strong,
we just need to be stronger!
Is he still mad about
his dad being insulted?
Why didn't you tell us?! That's unbare!
A commemoration?
Now watch this ring closely!
Indeed, tomorrow is a
day to commemorate.
No! You mean "unfair"!
S-Stop! Butchie! Siam!
Who knows?
On "one, two, Jango,"
you guys'll grow strong.
Who cares about that?! You guys
just gotta get out of here! Run!
No, that look was different!
Eh?
Your wounds will be completely healed,
Yeah, something must've happened!
and you will grow
stronger and stronger!
Why do you suppose he
looked so desperate?!
--No!
--We're gonna fight, too!
What're they doing?
You're not our captain anymore!
Hey, how do we get
to this shore of yours?
It's a crescent moon tonight.
The Usopp Pirates will
be shamed if we run!
It's hypnosis!
Sorry, but we're gonna kill ya!
Doesn't this smell like an incident?!
He's trying to convince
them to be stronger!
Huh?
Yeah, something must've
happened at the shore!
Nights like this make my heart race,
How ridiculous!
I think this calls for the Usopp Pirates!
Stronger... Stronger!
and my blood stir...
Alright, already!
How do we get there?!
One! Two!
K-Klahadore-san!
What are you doing to her present?!
You idiots! Get out of here, now!
Jango!
T-Terrible... news...
Oh, I'll be accepting a present, all right.
No way!
W-When did he get behind them?!
And those weapons...
But it won't be this--
it'll be this entire mansion!
Terrible news, everyone!
Pirates are going to attack!
W-What are you saying?!
Who...
There is no more need
to continue the act.
Who are you going to kill?!
Captain!
An accident is going to occur
in a few hours, anyway...
Tomorrow morning, pirates are
going to attack this village!
--He snuck...
--...behind us!
H-He gouged out the cliff!
Everyone, run away! Everyone...
What power!
They really did get hypnotized!
What are you all doing?! Everyone!
--Eh?!
--He's gone!
That hurt a bit...
It's truly been three long years!
With that many people that strong...
That's quite a strange
technique you have there...
Miss! Run away!
I take it you have Devil Fruit powers?!
There it is! The Pussy Foot Maneuver...
Go! Crush anyone who gets in the way!
Pussy Foot Maneuver?
Yep! I ate the Gum-Gum Fruit!
Alright, Usopp! Enough is enough!
You're gonna pay once and for all!
I'm a rubber person!
--What?! A Devil Fruit?!
--He's dangerous!
N-No, it's not like that!
--They really do exist?!
--I thought he seemed strange!
You're right.
It's the truth this time!
Shut up! All you ever
do is spout huge lies!
I see. A rubber person. So I didn't
hallucinate his arm-stretching...
You guys get back!
We'll handle this!
If you were as honest as Klahadore-san,
I do feel a bit of sluggishness.
then we'd believe you!
--Jango!
--Yeah?
Hey, Luffy!
He's handling them like kids,
I'll handle the boy.
You take care of Miss Kaya.
after they had the upper hand
against Zoro and his one sword!
No matter what he does,
it won't matter.
Luffy?!
That man's "Pussy Foot Maneuver"
is a silent movement technique.
Tomorrow morning, Jango.
Attack the village at daybreak!
As we planned, have her write a will...
...then kill her!
You got hypnotized too?!
Damn it!
Even a group of 50 assassins would
be killed before sensing him!
So he ignored me because
nobody'd believe me anyway?!
And those three little ants...
They're an eyesore!
There's no way we can escape his plan!
I'm on it.
W-What a simple-minded person!
And I got chills after seeing that
habit of his again three years after!
Are these to your liking?
Stop. I can't let you pass.
Gum-Gum...
They're the ones you custom-ordered
from the eyewear shop...
His odd way of lifting his glasses
to avoid cutting his own face
...Gatling!
Butchie!
...in the next town over.
with those Cat Claws...
Yes, they're perfect!
Clear proof that he hasn't
forgotten how to fight!
Cat...
I'm sorry for asking you
to go all the way there.
...astrophe!
Not again!
Damn you, Captain Kuro...
You were completely wrong
to think he'd have no effect!
It's a present, isn't it?
Yes. Tomorrow is actually
exactly three years since the day
These guys are no ordinary brats!
Klahadore came to this mansion.
He's always taken good care of me, so...
Klahadore-san will be delighted!
It seems I've grown
a bit good-natured myself,
Yes!
during my last three years on dry land...
Please, hear me out, everyone!
Pirates really are going to
attack tomorrow morning!
I'll give you five minutes.
If we believed every
story you ever told,
Where is he going?!
we'd have fled the village
hundreds of times by now!
If you can't take care of
things here in five minutes...
Please, believe me!
We gotta get out of here!
Captain Jango!
He's on a completely
different level than before!
They really are going to kill everyone!
It's almost daybreak!
Please wake up, Captain Jango!
...then I'll kill every last one of you...
Crap!
I swear it's the truth this time!
--Wha--?
--What's he planning to do?!
Kaya!
And we're gonna get you this time!
--Good morning, Captain!
--Good morning!
...with my own two hands!
You idiots!
My policy is to say "good morning"
with the morning sun!
Dammit!
Get him! Don't let him escape!
--He seems to be in a bad mood.
--He did just wake up...
Dammit...
Go! Luffy!
Five minutes...
Just look! The moon's still up,
and it's the middle of the night!
I'm out of strength...
Five minutes should be enough!
This is the place!
Our captain always heals
his emotional pain here!
He's gonna destroy the ship!
Dammit... Dammit! Dammit...
H-Him! If we just beat him,
we can get past this hill!
How dare you shout loudly!
It is nice here!
Our apologies, sir! We're sorry, sir!
D-Damn...
Alright, then.
Usopp Pirates!
That straw hat guy isn't here...
--Y-Yes, sir?!
No, he's not!
He's gonna crush us with that!
Listen to me!
We had the upper hand
against him just now!
We're not going to run!
Good morning, fellows!
It's pretty fragile here...
Not after they did this to you!
We'll cut him up in five minutes!
Please do something, Captain!
Good morning? That's the
opposite of what he just said!
We're going to avenge you!
We're counting on you,
Meowban Brothers!
Crap! Crap! This was
no time to be gawking!
--Nami. Don't fall now.
--Yeah.
You idiot! He's in a better
mood now, that's all!
Protect Kaya!
Oh!
Listen closely!
Quit bein' confusing!
On "one, two, Jango",
you'll get sleepy!
Zoro!
L-Look! There!
I'm giving...
Men!
I'm giving you the most
important task there is now!
--What the--?!
--There he is!
One!
--What?!
--H-Hey, you!
--It's the straw hat guy!
--And his butt.
Set sail!
Two!
Jango!
Now you're kicking my swords, too?!
Take Kaya and get away from here!
Where's my "thanks"?
Don't tell me you can't!
Yeah...
That was the reason we
formed our pirate group:
Luffy! How did this happen?!
Thanks!
--He fell!
--He's a goner!
Alright! Perfect!
to become men who protect
what's important to us!
So that's why our captain...
Now they won't be able
to climb up this slope,
It's no use!
Three swords won't help any!
Your skill's still the same!
thanks to all this oil
we've laid out here!
Usopp-san...
Quiet!
Tiger...
We'll let 'em slip and
slide on this slope,
then beat the crap out of
'em while they flail about!
That's... a direct order...
You don't get it, do you?
Oil, huh?
...Trap!
--Yes, Captain!
No matter what,
we will protect this slope!
This guy...
Hurry, Kaya-san!
Conversely, let's just hope
that none of us slip down there.
--This way! This way!
--This way!
Eh?! Klahadore the butler
went to the shore?!
Four minutes.
He sure knows how to talk all big.
It'd be like diving right
into an ant-lion pit.
He basically just told 'em to run away...
Yeah! And he had a
scary look on his face!
The woods are like our backyard!
I'm amazed you can
think up stuff this cheeky!
Just having three swords is different
Morning!
Is Kaya-san okay?!
O-Okay...
But of course!
Alright! Let's move out, Usopp Pirates!
from knowing the Three-Sword Style!
When it comes to
cheekiness and slingshots,
--Jango!
--I wound up gawking!
Hey! Quit sleeping!
I'm utterly confident!
The fools! They can't
possibly escape me--
But I should still be in bed...
This is no time to be sleeping!
He's strong...
It's almost daybreak.
We could be in trouble!
--Howdya like that?!
--Damn you!
They'll be coming.
Eh?
Go after them, you fool!
One hit...
I think pirates really
are going to attack us.
Y-Yeah, okay!
Our captain said he was lying,
but I think that was a lie!
How pointless.
I think so, too!
Usopp-san!
I know very well just
how weak Kaya is...
H-He beat the Meowban
Brothers in one hit!
Me, too! Something just wasn't
right about our captain yesterday!
She'll never escape Jango.
If you want to help her,
go right ahead.
Thank goodness!
I thought you might never come back...
If you can get past this hill alive, that is.
You don't think...
Don't worry!
You gotta run, Kaya!
They're gonna kill you!
I'll crush every last one of you
before your five minutes are up!
Eh? What?
Butchie!
But our captain used
to go through here!
You've been tricked!
That butler is really a pirate!
We're here!
You already lost to me once!
I told you not to get in my way!
Alright, men! Go ashore!
--No good! It's closed up!
--Let's look for another one!
Trash the village
and head for the mansion!
Move!
Captain! There are
two strange boats here!
Hold on. What kind of joke is this?
Three minutes.
What?!
Shall I check them out?
It's no joke!
I heard it with my own ears!
Leave 'em. They're not treasure ships.
Don't screw up our schedule!
You! How dare you make a fool of me,
I-I'll... slaughter him...
Understood!
Klahadore's really a pirate who
weaseled his way into your mansion
Get going, you guys!
so he could get your fortune!
insulting me for having
the blood of a pirate?!
He's been pretending to be a
butler for three years straight,
C-Captain...
Where are they?
so he could get your fortune!
Stop, Usopp-san!
H-Hypnotize me...
The sky's all bright now.
What's the deal?
What are you talking about, Usopp-san?
Maybe they overslept or somethin'?
P-Please, Captain!
No.
He said his crew's gonna storm
in and kill you at dawn tomorrow!
He's alive. You do sloppy work.
They'll definitely show up. Lot's of 'em.
His tough fat saved him, huh?
Say...
Maybe it's just my imagination,
but I hear, "Yaaah!"
coming from somewhere...
He's a really bad guy!
You gotta escape, quick!
I admit, he did say too much earlier.
Yeah, I definitely hear it!
Klahadore...
But lying like this...
N-Now that you mention it...
What?! What is it?!
It's not like you, Usopp-san!
Are you there, Klahadore?
There's a place just like
this to the north, too!
No, it's not a lie...
You don't suppose...
Klahadore?
Get 'im, Butchie!
You mean this is the wrong shore?!
This is where they had
their secret meeting,
It's the truth...
M-Merry!
so I just assumed...
It's the truth!
Merry!
More hypnosis?!
What's wrong?! What happened?!
Hey! Let's hurry!
They're gonna get into the
village! Where is this place?!
Open your eyes, Merry!
W-What's that sound?!
If you run straight north from here,
you'll get there in three minutes!
This guy means trouble! He could
already crack the ground apart!
--Please don't die!
--M-Miss...
Who knows? Ol' Jango is
probably tearing the place up.
Thank goodness, you're all right...
Why not go and see for yourself?
The terrain there is
almost exactly the same,
so we just need to
stop them at the slope!
Though it may already be too late...
Merry!
What happens when he's powered up?!
Don't worry! We'll do it somehow!
Oh, no!
Eh?! They're going to kill Kaya-san?!
Merry? W-who did this?!
The north shore is where our boats are!
Damn you...
Are they really going
to attack the village?!
Klahadore! He... attacked me!
Don't you even have a shred of pity?!
You lived with her for 3 years!
They're gonna take the treasure!
Yeah, that's what they said.
No question about it.
I'll be there in 20 seconds!
This is my chance!
Dammit! My brilliant Oil
Strategy was all for nothing!
I gotta wake him up while I still can!
No. I already told you,
He... he was a pirate all along!
Kaya is nothing more
than a pawn in my plan.
What is that crafty girl up to now?
--My treasure...
--Hey!
So what were you
sleeping down here for?
Once she's dead, then I'll
express some gratitude.
W-What are you talking about?
What're you doing?! Let's go!
Y-Yeah! We have to hurry--
That's the thing!
He got close to you so he
could get your fortune...
I thought I was up on the cliff...
Damn you...
What a helplessly evil guy!
--So how'd I get down here?
--I knew it! Klahadore's a bad guy!
Help! I'm falling!
Everyone's seriously hurt,
and he's just sleeping!
I don't plan to help him, though!
No... That's absurd!
It's no wonder he seemed so creepy!
--Let go, you moron!
--Sorry!
So that's why our captain ran to
the village with that intense look!
It's the truth!
Usopp!
Perfect!
Thanks, Zoro!
That's great, then!
Go to them!
Die!
Now they'll know, and
can run away beforehand!
We'll take over here!
Talk about stupid bad guys!
Sorry! The treasure's in danger!
Yeah, that's right!
We gotta run away, too!
Leave it to us!
Try to get back up somehow!
Then, what Usopp-san
said yesterday was...
Yeah! We gotta organize
all our prized possessions...
Get up!
--...and hurry!
That girl's gonna pay!
Nami! Look out!
Yes. Now that I think about it,
he tried his hardest to help us
when he learned the truth!
--Oh, no!
--What is it?
Two minutes.
We need to stock up on food
before the meat shop guy runs away!
I refuse to let them enter the village!
Yet, not a single one of us
even tried to hear him out!
But Luffy sure runs fast!
That's not the issue at hand here.
I can't even see him anymore!
Straight north!
Straight north! Straight north!
You gotta run, Kaya!
They're gonna kill you!
Tell me, Usopp-san.
They're in big trouble
if they touch my treasure!
You gotta escape for now!
What kind of story do you have today?
Get up!
We protected a real villain
and drove off that brave lad,
Nami! Look out!
Right. Hmm, let's see...
Oh? You can still move?
How impressive.
who ran about with desperate resolve,
There's someone at the top of the hill!
Split in two!
Alright!
Shut up...
This story happened when I was five,
Dodge it!
I refuse to let you... have your way!
You!
all for the villagers' sake!
when I fought a giant goldfish
living in the southern sea!
W-What the...?!
You went and betrayed the villagers'--
and Kaya's-- feelings...
A chakram! It wasn't
just a hypnosis tool?!
S-Someone help! Merry is--!
Goldfish? You fought a goldfish?
It's no use, Miss!
Yeah! It was so big,
Nami! How dare you stomp on my face?!
I refuse to let you
have your way anymore!
not even a fish tank the size
of this mansion could've held it!
My name is Captain Usopp!
The staff has been on
leave since yesterday.
I've been waiting for you all this time!
Oh, my!
Usopp!
What?! Then I'll...
What first shocked me was...
You mustn't get flustered!
...the immense size
and length of its poop!
I-I'm completely ready to fight!
D-Dammit...
H-He's alive?!
The incident hasn't happened yet!
I... can't... move...
Turn back now, if you don't wanna die!
It was so big that I landed on it,
Can't tell if he has bad or good timing...
You must think calmly about
what you need to do now!
thinking it was solid ground!
That sounds fake!
W-What the--? I'm the first one here?!
Yeah, it does, doesn't it?
If Klahadore's goal is
your fortune and mansion,
You really are a riot!
But he was running way ahead of me!
But it's the truth!
I betrayed them, you say?!
then just let him have it all!
L-Luffy...
Cut the crap! This was
all part of the plan!
They're not worth
protecting with your life!
So, first off, starting a bonfire to
dry off my clothes was a bad idea.
A kiddie pirate captain like you
has no place to talk all-knowingly!
Luffy!
--How come?
--Well, you see...
Oww...
--You're right.
--Cruel as it may be,
...the goldfish's butt caught
on fire and freaked it out!
Just stay on the ground there.
Ouch!
you are the only one who
can stop Klahadore now.
Oh, dear!
H-He's alive again!
Though, even if you did
catch up with Jango,
Though I guess I can't say I blame it.
Dammit!
--This is bad!
--Five minutes is impossible now!
Can you do it?
It was so close to
becoming a grilled goldfish!
What do I do?! I can't climb up!
you'd be no match for him anyway.
This isn't your responsibility, but...
This way is probably safest for you!
Nami! That hurts, you jerk!
Even if I am no match...
T-That wasn't me!
Even I know this isn't a
situation I can run from...
I'm in the village now! That's weird!
I... I loved them.
It wasn't me--
Even if I am no match for him...
I will protect them!
He said north, so I ran
in a cold-ish direction!
I understand that fully!
N-Nami! Did you hurt your shoulder?
I loved the lies you told...
I'm captain of the Usopp Pirates...
I'll talk things over with Klahadore!
I-It's nothing. I'm fine...
...and a brave warrior of the sea!
Yet, why are you saying this?
I've done everything I can for now,
so I leave the rest to you...
You're that boy who
overheard our plan.
I won't let you lay a
finger on the village!
It's not like that! I'm not
trying to get back at Klahadore...
What do you think you're doing?
I-I'm warning you!
Turn back now while you still can!
Why do you say it?
We absolutely can't
afford to lose this fight...
Or else my 100 million crewmen will...
Kaya... I'm...
Yeah!
...beat the crap out of you guys!
--What's with him?
--He's yellin' somethin'!
For the treasure!
Check it out, he's cryin'!
100 million?
Hey, now! That's even
worse than a kid's lie!
It'll all work out in the end!
What're you doing?!
What?! 100 million?! Wow!
Try hard! For my treasure!
Is something the matter, Miss?!
Hold on tight!
But these bars are slippery!
He's obviously lying, Captain!
Okay! That sounds like you, alright!
He's so naïve...
Climb over anyways!
Yikes! They saw through it?!
One minute.
He seriously thought
he could fool us, too...
Aren't you worried about Kaya-san?!
What's so funny?!
You gotta escape, Kaya!
How dare you trick me!
Oh, no! Someone's coming out!
Stop, Usopp-san!
You can't be serious!
Hide!
Luffy!
Not even Captain Jango
and Butchie-san...
Let go of her!
Captain Jango! Shocking news!
Me and Usopp are gonna chase
that hypno-freak! That a problem?!
--Really?! That's bad!
--No! It's not bad!
...can finish them in one minute!
Just trust me!
--It's Kaya-san!
--She's alright!
Nope! Hurry!
We found treasure
in those weird boats!
You gotta get out of this village,
T-Thanks...
An incredible amount!
Maybe 4, no, 5 million Berries!
before that butler gets back!
I'd actually be much faster by myself,
but they're inside some woods.
What?!
I'm gonna need your
directions to catch up to him.
F-Five million Berries?!
Hold it, you two. Who gave you
permission to pass this hill?
Why is there that much
money in those guys' boats?
It looks like something has her worried!
That's my treasure!
I did!
Butchie! There's no time to think!
Kaya-san, walking
outside all by herself...
--But you can have it!
--What?! You'll give us the treasure?!
Go! Zoro! Usopp!
Something's up!
Something's gotta be up!
Kill that haramaki bastard!
That's right!
And I'll handle that weird kid...
And another!
In exchange for that treasure,
I ask that you turn back now!
Stop!
Wha--?! You think you can
buy us off with money?!
Come on!
Gum-Gum Spear!
What a disgraceful guy!
I'll kill Straw Hat!
Darn! He disappeared again!
You fool. We're pirates, you know.
This'll all make sense come tomorrow!
We're obviously going
to take this treasure!
But you gotta escape for now!
Oh, well! They're past the hill, at least!
Looks like they're just about wiped out!
Please, listen to me!
It's about time for everyone to die now.
It's not good enough of
a reason for us to turn back.
Before fighting, I have
one thing to ask you.
I guess so.
Hey! Never mind that,
Luffy's trapped under there!
Why is an outsider like you butting
into this village's business?!
Y-You have a point...
He won't die.
Worry about your own
injuries or somethin'.
Alright, then! On "one, two,
Jango," you'll let us by!
Because there's a man in this
village I don't wanna let die!
You're pathetic.
How simple. Are you okay
with that being why you die?!
It's that weapon from before!
Damn that brat!
Huh? That bad butler is here too!
One! Two!
Now the plan's really screwed up!
Yep! I'm not gonna die, though!
Jan--
If Captain Kuro caught sight of this,
Quit saying stupid crap!
Isn't he...
he'd slaughter all of us, too!
Didn't he fall off that cliff and die?
I'll make sure you do!
Hey, Butchie! Come look!
This is bad stuff!
Get away from her!
No matter.
Oww!
W-Who's she?!
What the hell?!
Captain! This is no time to
hypnotize yourself and let people by!
Gum-Gum Whip!
No!
We still have a trump card!
Come forth, Meowban Brothers!
...and Pistol!
That boat's treasure is mine!
I won't let you have a single Berry!
Hold on to it!
I'll come take it back now!
Don't approach me...
You called, Captain Jango?
That hurt!
You're making me yawn!
Who said you could
give them my treasure?!
Why, you...
...from behind!
What's wrong with just
saying they can have it?!
Please, catch him!
You called?
He roughed up the lady of the house!
--Siam...
--...and Butchie!
Kaya!
What're you talking about?!
After I just saved you!
--How horrible!
--How could he?!
Together, we are the
Meowban Brothers!
Damn... He cut my mouth...
--Huh?
--I forgot to mention it,
but don't watch his ring
all the way through!
That straw hat guy's
insanely strong, and yet...
Why...
Butchie! Siam! We absolutely
must get past this hill,
He's a hypnotist!
...won't anyone believe me?
T-That's Captain Kuro for ya!
H-Hypnosis?!
So? Where's Luffy?
He ran here first, right?
--Get 'im!
--Hurray for Captain Kuro!
but as you can see,
an obstacle is in the way!
There he is! Get him!
Get rid of it.
--Captain Kuro!
--You're awesome, Captain Kuro!
U-Usopp-san! Are you okay?!
Dunno! He either
chickened out or got lost!
K-Kaya... What are you doing here?!
Don't call me that name!
W-We can't possibly do that!
He got lost, then.
I'm so sorry, Usopp-san...
Right, Butchie?!
Geez! Just when we need him, too!
Usopp-san...
Do you still not get it?!
Yeah, he looks strong!
I know you may not accept my apology,
I'll take command here.
Go kick their butts! I'll cover you!
Please pull yourself together, Miss!
This plan is so I can be completely
rid of the name "Captain Kuro"!
Huh?
but I just couldn't believe it...
And besides, we're just
supposed to guard the ship!
K-Klahadore, a pirate...
Eh?! Hold on, why me?!
Yeah! This isn't really
our place to fight...
There's no way I can take on that
huge army! I'm weak, you know!
N-Never mind that!
Why are you here?!
I'm tired...
W-What? They're not
their trump card?!
Don't underestimate me
just 'cause I'm a guy!
I-I told you to run away!
Devising plans everyday for you
men who only care about mayhem...
Thank you for coming, men.
I'm so scared my legs are
shaking like crazy! See?!
Your life is in danger!
But you're fighting!
It's truly been three long years.
Siam! Get going already!
Big deal!
Being relentlessly attacked by
government dogs and bounty hunters...
Eh?! M-Me?!
See, look! I'm so scared
I have tears in my eyes!
Once this plan succeeds,
Hurry!
Even after I treated you so horribly
and you've been hurt so much,
I intend to give you
all plenty of the take.
O-Okay, okay! I'll go!
Your eyes are bone dry!
I was absolutely sick of it all!
If you're gonna lie,
lie more realistically!
He's in tears! What's he trying to do?!
you're still fighting for me! So I...
I don't need you to tell me that!
At dawn tomorrow,
destroy the village
to your hearts' content!
Miss Kaya...
We don't have time to mess with them.
Why's he making him fight?
Hey, you! Get ready!
The navy, huh?
Why are you here?
Crush 'em and head
for the village, men!
I'm gonna scratch you
good with these claws!
This is the third time this week...
S-Stop this...
It can't be helped. We're doing
stuff that makes people chase us.
What am I supposed to do?!
H-Here they come!
Hey, you! Stop or I'll kill you!
Oh, yeah! I have caltrops!
Stop this, Klahadore!
Plus you've made quite
a name for yourself...
Oh! You do have some good stuff!
--If you can!
--What?!
Gimme, gimme!
Yes... That name is
what draws them to us.
Who are you?!
I'm Usopp!
A brave warrior of the sea!
Take this!
That's why I'm giving
up being Captain Kuro.
Caltrop Hell!
--What the hell?!
--You!
Merry told me everything.
I hear you've been unhappy lately!
You just underestimated
me, didn't you?!
I'll cheer you up with a story!
I'm impressed you could block that,
after my innocent cat act!
That's pretty funny. But it's no use.
Mind your own business!
Please leave! I'll call for someone!
Isn't that the girl from the mansion?
Now, now, don't sweat it!
I'm always meddlesome!
I think the navy'll keep
following you until you're dead.
You seem to have a little skill,
Meaning she's the plan's final target?!
but I wouldn't underestimate
Siam of the Meowban Brothers!
Damn that Nami!
She's gonna pay for this!
Then there's no need to
go to the village now?
When I was three, my meddling
even led me to save a sick whale!
We just need to kill her, right?!
I am going to die.
Missing something?
Don't look at me, though...
--Eh? A whale?
--You bet!
It would seem that
piracy just isn't for me...
Klahadore, please! If you want
my fortune, you can have it all!
It was huge, and had
a really sore throat,
I made it!
--There it is...
-- "Cat Burglar"...
so I went inside its mouth,
but it thought I was food!
B-But you're this ship's captain!
Just please leave
this village! Right now!
Give those swords back!
You can be captain!
Give them back?
But you already have a sword.
I will gladly accept it... but...
Tomorrow morning, Jango.
Attack the village at daybreak!
I'm sick of this tumultuous lifestyle.
W-Which way is the north shore?!
...there's one other
thing I want, you see...
Straight north!
Straight north! Straight north!
These are just in the way.
I'm... going to kill myself for all to see!
What I want...
Captain Kuro!
--Captain!
...is peace of mind.
How many vessels?
Alright! Now I'm much lighter!
Which way is north?!
J-Just one!
Oww!
Oh, hey, guys!
Peace?
What should we do, Captain?!
Should we blast 'em back?!
You're supposed to take good
care of other people's things!
Yes. I want simple peace.
Yes! We got 'em!
Yo!
Lower a small boat.
Now! Special Attack: Lead Star!
You're alive?!
--Huh?!
--A boat!
I find the villagers' trust that I've
fostered these past three years
Alive? Yeah, I just woke up!
Bastard!
to be nice and comfortable now.
This guy was asleep the whole time!
What?!
Way to go! Keep it up, now!
Anyways, Captain!
We heard everything!
What did you cut?!
Vice-Captain Jango!
Captain Kuro just--
I'm gonna quit fighting for a bit.
I can bend like a cat!
Yeah, I know.
So I want to have that
peace of mind forever...
Let's hurry and tell
everyone about the pirates!
You haven't even fought yet!
"Yeah"?! It's way too reckless
for him to go there by himself!
What is it?!
You're up, Butchie! Get 'im!
Don't tell me he's turning himself in?!
There are caltrops behind us too...
Tell everyone?
Right, Siam!
You moron! You dropped 'em there!
Cat...
You're pathetic.
Outta the damn way!
And I...
Shut up! All you ever
do is spout huge lies!
...astrophe!
And I will have that peace!
And your fortune...
Damn! He got away!
If you were as honest as Klahadore-san,
Hey! Hold him down, Siam!
Do you seriously think you can stop us?
In short, pirates will
come to the village!
--H-Huh?!
--The cannon fire stopped...
then we'd believe you!
My bad!
--What's goin' on?!
--This is creepy...
The bastard's way
stronger than I thought!
And...
Let's go, guys! Captain Kuro is waiting!
What the hell?!
...you will leave your will and die!
One hit from that'd turn every
bone in my body to powder!
Dock with their ship.
B-But...
These two things are absolute.
--Just do as I say, damn it!
--Y-Yes, sir!
--He's not getting away this time!
--'As right!
W-What the--?!
N-No...
Let go, you bastard! Let the hell go!
--Hey, get ready to fight!
--I see... So that's why...
Y-You're not...
I'm not that great at the
One-Sword Style, but...
Damn you! Take this! Take this!
I'm lying like usual, obviously!
Run! Run away, Kaya!
That damn butler pissed me off,
Hey, you.
I... can't...
There's no use talking to him! Run away!
Let's go, Butchie!
Y-Yes?! What is it?
so I decided to claim he's a pirate!
...let you get past this slope...
Okay! Let's do it, Siam!
Y-You're not Klahadore.
You're not Klahadore...
It was nice knowing you
for this short time...
--Pussy Willow March!
Oh!
Because I only lied, like I always do...
So you put the straw
hat guy up to it, too!
Kaya...
So the village is going to have
just another ordinary day...
Leave this village!
Hey? What's wrong?
So I absolutely won't let you pass!
I think less of you now.
Oh... You'd point a gun at me...
Oh, no! They got
Zoro on the defensive!
--Me too.
--Me too!
Damn kid! Shut up!
Even if that butler is a jerk,
Leave this minute!
I never thought you'd
lie to hurt someone!
What're you doing?!
Damn girl!
I see. You've certainly grown
a lot these past three years...
--T-The marines...
--They've been wiped out!
He's not gonna get anywhere just
blocking those two guys' attacks!
We really respected you, too!
Oww!
I'm gonna help him out!
Take this!
...Miss Kaya.
I was all wrong about him!
Are you--?!
Lead Star!
--Same here!
--Let's go home!
That's enough now!
Do you remember? So much
has happened in three years...
Yeah! It's suppertime!
Now, then...
Wonder what we're having...
Hey, you guys!
Gotcha!
Quit bothering with them
and get going already!
We spent so much time together,
Let's begin the plan...
Have you forgotten that
this is Captain Kuro's plan?!
even before your parents passed
away and you became bedridden...
Oww!
If anything happens
to throw his plan off,
Why're you attacking
a guy on our side?!
he'll kill every one of us!
Hey, now. Pull yourself together.
So much time...
No, it's not like that!
Do you understand that,
you dumbasses?!
I was kind enough to
leave you alive, you know...
It seemed like he let
it hit him on purpose...
--H-Hey, now...
--Yeah, hurry to the village!
So many memories...
Together we suffered...
S-Shut up...
Eh?! On purpose?!
Together we rejoiced...
I-I'm not gonna beg for my life...
Usopp, you dumbass!
There, all done!
K-Klahadore...
S-Stop...
Do you want to die?!
F-Finish me off, damn you...
Why did you tell them that?
Dammit...
I would visit the city with you,
Because I'm a liar.
Stop!
You don't suppose...
and whenever you had a fever,
I constantly looked after you...
Stop... Don't go to the village!
That's a good look.
...we're the ones who just got saved?
Shut up!
If you can howl that much with a
shattered jaw, then that's perfect!
They were never going to
believe me from the start.
You listened to my stories so happily...
Had you hit them with that slingshot,
I was too optimistic.
those two probably would've
come after us instead!
Even so, the truth is the truth.
I'm giving you, a nameless,
low-ranking soldier, a treat.
I devoted myself to you...
Stop! Please!
Please don't kill everyone!
He...
For so long...
But this is no time for that!
Pirates really are going
to come, aren't they?
Accept it gratefully...
Yes, for so long, I endured it...
I love this village! I want to protect it!
Yeah. They're definitely gonna show up.
The head of Kuro,
Man of a Thousand Plans!
Damn it! If I just had another sword!
But everyone thinks it's a lie.
Yes, it was all so that
I could kill you today...
Your name is Captain Kuro.
They think tomorrow'll be just
another normal, peaceful day...
This atrocity was your doing.
I'm gonna get his swords!
If I give 'em back to Zoro,
he'll win for sure!
One, two, Jango!
That's why I'm going to stop the
pirates at the beach tomorrow,
In that case, I'll do it!
My name is Captain Kuro.
This atrocity was my doing.
Don't push yourself!
You can barely even stand!
and make sure this stays a lie!
I, a man once known as Captain Kuro,
That's the only logical thing
for a liar like me to do!
W-What is this, Captain Jango?!
Nami!
And you're the man
who caught Captain Kuro.
Nobody mentioned guys
like them were in the village!
had to smile humbly
for some snot-nosed girl...
Even if I get shot in the arm,
About time...
Return to base and execute this man.
I went against my nature
and sucked up to you...
even if I'm driven off with brooms,
One, two, Jango!
this is my village!
What were those
unchallenging guys just now?!
I love this village!
Don't look at me!
I'm not satisfied, though!
I'm the man who caught Captain Kuro!
Damn you...
I want to protect everyone!
Nami! How dare you
kick me down there!
You're doing it again, Vice-Captain!
Do you understand these daily insults?!
Perfect...
You're one hell of a nice guy,
Usopp, you jerk!
With that fake gone, Captain Kuro
will disappear from the world.
pushing your henchmen away
and going into battle alone!
You didn't say which way was north!
Do you understand this man
once known as Captain Kuro?!
Nami!
What do you need swords for?
Just so you know, I have dibs
on all the pirates' treasure!
Who're they?
Alright! We'll help you out!
You guys... are going
to fight with me?! Why?
And when my plan today succeeds,
my goal will be fully achieved...
They're late...
There's a whole bunch
of bad guys, right?
Kuro!
They all know full well what happens...
"Scared" is written all over your face.
Money and peace of mind will be mine.
M-Me, scared?!
No! Uhh! I-I can explain!
Do you understand, boy?
I'm perfectly okay with lots
of bad guys or whatever!
...to those who upset my plans...
I cannot allow this plan
of three years to fail!
Come to think of it...
Because I'm Captain Usopp,
brave warrior of the sea!
...I still owe you for hitting me...
My plan will not be disrupted!
Night is long gone now,
They think they can
take their sweet time...
Usopp-san!
Dammit! Dammit! This isn't a show!
so it seemed odd that the plan
wasn't making any progress...
If they've already forgotten that fact...
You hit me with all
your might, as I recall...
These are Klahadore's
pirates we're dealing with!
Of course I'm scared!
What's wrong with that?!
C-Captain Kuro!
Seems you can do
more than just stretch!
...then I'll slaughter them all!
I don't want your sympathy!
You guys can leave! Leave!
W-We're dead!
That's right! I've toughened
myself up, to be a pirate!
We ain't laughing! We're helping
'cause we think you're honorable!
This can't get any worse!
You're "tired"?!
You're not fit to be a pirate if having
a name on the seas scares you!
As if we'd risk our lives
because of sympathy!
Oh... You guys...
It is Klahadore from the mansion!
My ambition is much greater than yours!
What is all this?!
If you hate getting hit that much,
I got a hundred more punches for you!
Why is he walking toward the shore,
this early in the morning?!
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
What the--?! Did they
have a falling out?!
Huh? Why'd Usopp
cover this slope in oil?
--Is this the place?!
--Damn you, Nami!
Usopp! You go save Miss Kaya!
Leave the bad butler to me!
Do you think Kaya-san and
the others managed to get away?
He's handling those two
like they're nothing!
Those three are with her.
She should be fine.
How dare you leave me down there?!
--It's his Oil Strategy.
--What a weird strategy.
I can't sense where damn Kuro is!
Crap! Zoro's really mad!
--What a helplessly evil guy!
--I don't plan to help him, though!
Yeah, huh? She won't get lost
like someone else I know.
But where are the pirates?
--Kaya-san! Look out!
--What's she doing here?!
Get ready to pay, Nami!
What?! They're at the north shore?!
I'm goin' after that hypno-freak!
I know! Get sleepy at the
count of "one, two, Jango"!
--Are you talking about me?!
--Who else is there?!
--Hey, where's Luffy?!
--Still asleep! Urgh!
Kuro! You're not cut out to be a pirate!
--I'll go on ahead!
--They're gonna take my treasure!
You wish!
What're you talking about?!
You used to bounty-hunt while lost!
--Get up already!
North, north! Which way is north?!
Hey, Luffy! Quit sleeping, you!
My ambition is much greater than yours!
I'll protect the meat shop...
Damn you, Nami!
Don't put it like that!
--Look at that guy's hand!
--Don't avoid the issue!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy, Back in Action!
Miss Kaya's Desperate Resistance"
"Beat Kuro! Usopp the Man's
Tearful Resolve!"
"Protect Kaya! The Usopp
Pirates' Great Efforts!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Clash with the Black Cat Pirates!
Great Battle on the Slope!"
"The Terrifying Duo!
Meowban Brothers vs. Zoro"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!