Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"North Block"
"West Block" "South Block" "East Block"
"Rainbase"                 "Alubarna"
"Yuba" "Erumalu" "Nanohana" "Katorea"
"Spiders Café"
"Rainbase"                 "Alubarna"
"Yuba" "Erumalu" "Nanohana" "Katorea"
"Spiders Café"
The feelings of those who are in anguish
are crushed by a dry cloud of sand.
Three years have passed
since a single drop of rain fell
are crushed by a dry cloud of sand.
Three years have passed
since a single drop of rain fell
The feelings of those who are in anguish
There are those who seek hope,
and those who cling to hope.
are crushed by a dry cloud of sand.
There are those who seek hope,
and those who cling to hope.
in the kingdom of oases.
There are those who seek hope,
and those who cling to hope.
Their feelings cross each other,
uncertain what to do,
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people take up weapons.
Their feelings cross each other,
uncertain what to do,
marking an era of history ending in sadness.
Their feelings cross each other,
uncertain what to do,
The scorching land was now
engulfed in wails of grief,
marking an era of history ending in sadness.
Having escaped from the trap at
Raindinners, Luffy and the others
There are those who would prevent war,
marking an era of history ending in sadness.
along with tremendous upheaval.
and those who would incite war.
set out toward Alubarna to plead with
a rebel army that numbered two million,
Though injured head-to-toe,
Karoo picks up Vivi,
Many different sensibilities
have gathered at Alubarna.
Zoro and the others take to
the Supersonic Duck Squadron,
but he was caught by a waiting
Crocodile, and they began a duel.
and they escape from an attacking Mr. 2,
acting as decoys, to draw away the
Number Agents of Baroque Works.
and run off between the battling
rebel army and royal army,
toward Alubarna Palace.
Among them, at this very moment,
were Usopp and Chopper,
However, unable to do
anything in the face
whose battle against Mr. 4 and
Miss Merry Christmas was unfolding.
of his overwhelming power,
Luffy fell before him.
However, Karoo falls after
being hit by a stray bullet.
Vivi sets out alone to try
to persuade Koza and company,
Will this situation continue to
deteriorate into a worst-case scenario?
but her voice is drowned out by
the cloud of sand surrounding her.
Mr. 2 closes in. Just then,
the supersonic duck squadron
Will Alabasta fall?
and Sanji appear, to rescue
them from their predicament.
Or will it find true peace?
Luffy, having separated
from Vivi and the others
"Dash For a Miracle!
Alabasta Animal Land"
Moment by moment, the goddess
of fate marks the final hour.
to face Crocodile alone, fell
before his overwhelming strength,
Meanwhile, at the southeast gate,
The battle between the rebel army,
which was attacking Alubarna,
and sank beneath the sands of Alabasta.
the battle between Chopper and Usopp,
and Miss Merry Christmas
and Mr. 4, had begun.
and the royal army, which was
defending Alubarna, had finally begun.
Although narrowly escaping,
thanks to Miss All-Sunday,
Luffy's life-threatening injuries
made his recovery hopeless.
"Big Opening Day Today!
The Copy-Copy Montage!"
"Alubarna Grieves!
The Fierce Captain Karoo!"
Don't you lie to us, you haggy old mole!
"Sworn on a Friend's Dream!
The Battle of Molehill, Block 4"
There's no way he can be dead!
Vivi-chan is in danger!
Usopp, you go help Chopper.
There's no way he'd be beaten
by that sand-gator bastard!
Meanwhile, as Vivi and the others
made for the capital city of Alubarna,
--Chopper?
--Get to the southeast gate!
I'd think you'd need
some grounds for saying
though hindered by the
vastness of the great land,
Look! T-There's so much!
that there's no way it could happen.
they were assisted by the
unique animals of Alabasta,
He's the man who will be
king of the pirates someday!
favorably speeding their journey along.
Vivi-chan, hang in there a
little longer, until I get there!
That's why there's no way he
can get his ticket punched here!
L-Look...
The water...
Vivi and the others are
trying to prevent a conflict.
K-King of the pirates?
The water is coming forth!
--It's a rebel soldier!
--They're here!
However, a rebel army,
two million strong,
"King-er-ates"? "K-rates"? "K"?
Rebel soldier? Me?
Didn't I say so, Luffy-kun?
was about to close in on Alubarna.
Ah, it's a royal soldier!
Don't make me laugh!
This land is strong.
Shoot him!
Hey, now, I'm neither
rebel army nor royal army!
Moment by moment, the hourglass
of fate marks the final hour.
Yuba still lives.
They're over there?!
I'm on the side of the ladies!
When did you have time to move?!
I wouldn't tell that foul story
in the Grand Line, ever again!
M-Meat...!
Yuba is going to die from
that one, final sandstorm.
That form...! I get it,
you're a Zoan type, are you?
Man, I'm glad he's dead!
"Alubarna - Southeast Gate"
He was a stupid bastard,
who didn't know his own place!
I thought you weren't just a normal person.
"Rebel Army vs. Royal Army!
Showdown at Alubarna!"
And then, the flame of anger in
the rebel army will burn even hotter.
A "ba"! He was a "ba"!
They've disappeared...
Are you okay, Usopp?
...all too quickly.
Thanks... you saved me...
This outdated consideration for others
Where are Mr. 4 and
Miss Merry Christmas?
is going to destroy this land.
So what if he did? Our advantage
over you hasn't changed a bit!
H-Hey, are you all right?
Listen up, Chopper!
Meat...!
And the same goes for you,
Straw Hat Luffy.
Let's go, Mr. 4!
Here we go! Off we go! Now we go!
You lunkhead! You l'ead!
A man...
If you had abandoned
your worthless feelings,
Meat...!
It's about time for
you to die, longnose!
you would have lived longer.
Meat? In your shape? What are
you talking about? Hang on.
She went underground again!
Molehill Highway!!
Usopp, you'd best consider yourself
done for if you stop moving.
W-What is this?
Just who are these guys?
...n-no m-m-matter how d-deathly
h-hideous his foe may be...
Water...?
I'll go get a doctor.
I get you. You mean, if we stop,
they'll fire dozens more at us, huh?
I doubt you still feel
indebted to this water, huh?
Who are you? You talk as
though you know everything.
See you in hell!
I'm going to make sure
Crocodile pays for this...
Let me introduce you
to our number-four batter.
Here they come!
Mole-Mole Impact!!
He made fun of Vivi...
and that dried-up old man...
Usopp!
...n-no matter...
...how slim a chance
he has at beating them...
You mean, you're still alive?
...and he's definitely gonna pay...
If I can just knock you flying...!
Who are you?
Mr. 4!
Number-four...
Wait up. If we don't have a batter,
the game won't be any fun, will it?
Look sharp! Take your batting stance!
Meat...
With your four-ton bat!
...batter...?
Here goes! Molehill...
Chopper!
It looks like that hurts. But you'll
be out of your misery soon enough.
Whew, I can do that.
Whatever I can do... Right now,
I should just do whatever I can do.
Why, you dirty mole!
...Intersection #4!!
I am... I am a pirate!
You bastard!
I see it! It's still far away,
but it's Alubarna!
Usopp!
Die!
Damn. If they keep running
away through these mole holes,
Bye, now.
Koza, we're less than 30 minutes away!
Princess Vivi!
then even if I use a Rumble Ball,
time will run out on it right away.
This desert will be...
Right!
Alubarna is near!
...your grave!
That was a waste of my time.
Raise your spirits!
Huh?
Un...
Huh...?
...deux...
Eh? Just where did that guy
with the long nose disappear to?
...ora!!
Karoo!
Chaka-sama! We've sighted the
rebel army, about 15 kilos to the south!
The weak are always weak,
no matter what they do! Take that!
They're right. Usopp is gone!
Their army, two million strong,
is bearing down on the southern gate!
I should warn you guys...!
No big deal. Once we get
through this sand, it will rain.
East, west, south,
southeast, southwest...
You bastards!
Hm, hm... Still, you're not getting away!
My goodness, I'm impressed
you could create all of these
Why, you...!
Defend each gate with your lives!
Just like always.
underground tunnels without it
becoming tiresome. Good work!
Oh, you want a go at it? That's perfect.
Do not let them set foot in the city!
Swan Dash!!
Then again, there can
be some literal "pitfalls"
We'll send you into the next world,
Yes, sir!
Keep coming! Keep coming as
often as you want, sandstorms!
just like we did that
cowardly punk with the nose!
when it comes to fighting
like this, you know?
Yuba will never give in to the sand!
I told you, you won't get away!
Come on, wait up, I say!
Where are you?! Where did you go?!
Shut up! Usopp...
--He wouldn't...!
--Yes!
Usopp is no coward!
I'm going to gobble you up!
You took the trouble to make
these underground tunnels.
"Alubarna - West Gate"
You're not the only ones...
...who can move around in them.
Hey, look over there!
The rebel army is coming into view!
Karoo...
There's so fabulously many of them!
Usopp...
You bastard! You were in one of the holes?!
The princess is quite a
nincompoop to try to stop them.
There are times... when a man...
You shielded me...
But then, is the nincompoop really coming?
...Pound!!
Then, that's when it happened!
That's when I said to him,
You're in no shape to be running anymore...
...must not run from a fight...
no matter what...
Or isn't she coming? Is she coming?
Or isn't she coming?
"You bowlegged bastard!"
That's when it started. Ever since,
It's so vague!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
No! If you go straight,
we'll be cornered on the stairway!
the crabs of the world have been
bothered about being bowlegged.
You're still...?
Are we sure about this?!
Like when... like when his
friend's dream... is laughed at...
Hold it, I'm telling you!
The princess and the pirates
are really coming, right?!
So that's why they walk sideways, huh?
Mr. 4!
The rebel army is going to
get here first, at this rate!
Uh-huh. Incidentally, at the time,
there was something
Let me off, Karoo! I'm going to fight him!
jumping up and down
behind him. It was a lobster.
Don't they want to stop them,
for crying out loud?!
Impossible! Your head was
knocked in with a four-ton bat!
A f-five ton hammer?!
There is a likely chance that
they don't make it in time.
So lobsters-- they're crabs, then?
You can't still be alive!
You can't still be able to get up!
Where does that kid keep
that kind of power?!
--Here... they... come...
--After all, they did lose a
good deal of time at Rainbase.
Hold on, that way is the cliff!
Yeah, they're crabs.
What trick did you use this time?!
Zoro, you're just wasting your
energy doing that, aren't you?
Hunh? That's ridiculous!
What?! They did?!
Well, supposing that
the rebellion starts first,
Luffy... isn't dead...
Shut up.
Just leave him alone, Nami-san.
what are we supposed to deux?
Five tons...!
He's gonna be...
king of the pirates someday...
Who are you?
If those guys aren't doing something,
they can't keep focused.
What is this?! That duck is scaling
the sheer cliffs of Alubarna!
We don't have to deux anything,
do we? Once the war starts,
They're not that adept. Especially...
Traveler of the world's oceans,
not even the princess will be
able to do anything about it.
I'm sure he will...!
crusher of notorious foes as I go,
That's the one thing...
We just need to get rid of
whoever we're told to get rid of.
and sinker of countless ships.
...that muscle freak, now that
he's had a taste of the level
...that's the one thing
I won't let you laugh at!
Can't you even determine
that much for yourself?
Out of fear, people call me
the "Dynast of Destruction."
the Seven Warlords have.
Ha! Looks like you still
haven't learned your lesson yet.
It sounds like you're just
dying for a taste of my kenpo!
Hey, you, what are you trying to say?
You dummy! Now, fall back down here,
One more time, Mr. 4!
Knock it off, you two.
Remember my name well.
Go ahead and spell it out.
and fall prey to my Ballet Kenpo!
Ah, you want me to say it?
Ah, my back! My back is aching!
Mr. 4, massage it for me!
Captain Usopp!
You're scared. You're worried
that maybe Luffy might lose.
They... 're... com... ing...
You think I'm gonna let that happen?!
Awesome! Awesome! Awesome!
Let me show you a transformation
point that I've been saving!
What?!
--That was awesome, Usopp!
--Yeah, thank you, thank you, baby!
Who, me?! Scared, you say?! Why, you...!
Why didn't you tell us sooner,
you dim-witted daruma doll?!
It's a sign of our friendship!
--Awesome! Awesome!
--Thank you. I'll be signing autographs later.
I've underestimated
your ability up until now!
--Fancy eyebrows!
--That does it! Now I'm mad!
Ducks...?
Hey...
You... moss head!
Oh, what are you crying about, Karoo?
Mr. 4 is...
Ducks? What do you mean,
Miss Merry Christmas?
What?!
You wanna go at it?!
He's not moving.
C-Could I have hit him that hard?
Their number has increased,
hasn't it? There are six of them.
Horn Point!
Leave it to us! Vivi is our friend.
Cut it out! This is pointless!
Usopp!
No, hold on. Either way,
this is my chance, huh?
There were four of them from the list,
not including Straw Hat, right?
She's strong!
Your determination,
at least, is praiseworthy,
but no matter how resolute you might be,
They are who they are.
Everyone's a bit worked up.
You, too, penguin!
You're wrong, Miss Merry Christmas.
you can't do anything in your shape!
Take this five-ton hammer!
Did you listen to what the boss said?
There's that Mr. Prince guy.
Now's the time for me,
the vice-captain, to...
C-Chopper...!
Take it easy, everyone.
Usopp Pound!!
He said there were more than one of him,
Get... b-behind... me...!
Luffy-san won't lose. I mean,
we promised him, didn't we?
so if you add two, the number matches.
What's going on?!
Tch, she got away! Where are you, penguin?!
That we'd be waiting for him in Alubarna?
You got it!
K-Karoo! That was amazing! You just flew!
No matter how many more there are,
our only target is Vivi.
Get ready, Mr. 4!
You seem more worried
than any of us, don't you?!
I told you, I'm a mole, you "ba"!
What are you so anxious about?
There you are!
Mr. 2 can't follow us
after we've come this far.
--Ow!
--You should just worry about the rebellion.
Pound!! Pound!! Pound!! Pound!! Pound!!
Mr. 1...
Take this! Special Attack...
Pound!! Pound!! Pound!! Pound!!
That was sassy of you, duck!
Here it comes! Molehill...
You say that Vivi is the only
one we have to get rid of?
Pound!! Pound!! Pound!! Pound!! Pound!!
Sorry about that, Vivi-chan.
Pound!! Pound!! Pound!! Pound!!
If you have to cover for us, we're done for.
...Smoke Star!!
Nothing is impossible for me!
Rubber band!
Well then...
Pound!! Pound!! Pound!!
Not with the relevé of my
kenpo's blood, sweat and tears!
All right, then, switch your
minds over to "Alubarna"!
...you can guess which one is Vivi!
Let's go, Pincers!
The rest... is up to you, Chopper!
They're all wearing the same cloaks!
Damn, you're all over the place...!
Ha! "Ba"! You "ba"! What's the point...
All right!
--What's that?
--A name for the crab.
What's more, those birds are
the fastest in all of Alabasta,
That kid took off his boots and got away!
...if you can't hit me?!
supersonic ducks!
"Pincers," you say?
What the--?! Hey!
--No good?
--Nothing wrong with it.
Let me inform you of something...
You must have heard that a good number
Why, those rotten...!
Molehill Intersection #4!!
How do we tell which one is Vivi like this?!
of Baroque Works staff have
been eliminated by us, right?
Me, go to Alubarna?
Stop! Mr. 4! It's me!
It's too vague, you know!
The truth is, that was all my doing!
We're chasing after the
Straw Hat pirates, right?
Or are we reinforcing the royal army?
--W-What?!
--And what's more...
Karoo, can you get
through this battlefield?
It's up to you.
I have 8,000 men under me!
We can't find Koza
in all of this confusion,
You decide what to do when you're there.
so we'll go to the palace, to find Chaka.
Let them have it, Mr. 4!
You don't mean that!
Exactly what is going on?
Really?!
Before the rebel army
reaches the center of the city.
You just follow your sense of justice.
Stay away from it!
--Five tons! Five tons!
--Wow, awesome! Wow, awesome!
Whatever happens, I'll accept responsibility.
Hey!
I caught up to you!
They dodged it!
Those birds are fast, huh?
--Five tons! Five tons!
--Wow! Awesome!
You guys look over here!
Captain Smoker, where are you going?
--Five tons! Five tons!
--Wow! Awesome--!
Special Attack: Uso-Cho Hammer Comet!!
Something sudden came up.
I'm heading out to sea.
Two of them broke off south!
They're splitting up!
Ee-yow...!
Be prepared to receive communication
from me at any time, Tashigi.
They're planning to go to the south gate!
What, just now?!
Whoa! He took a five-ton hammer,
too! He's a monster!
That's directly toward the rebel army.
Yes, sir.
Keep a close watch on
where this country ends up.
Which means that one of them is Vivi?
A stray bullet...!
He doesn't have the
slightest bump, does he?
Karoo!
Let us handle those two!
Vivi is our friend.
He took a direct blow to the
head by a five-ton hammer,
Let's go, Mr. 4!
Whether it falls, or whether it survives,
and he's uninjured?
something is sure to happen
to mark the start of a new age.
Special attack: Fire Star!!
It's no use!
Mr. 1, those two are breaking
off that way! That could be Vivi!
Sergeant... Sergeant!
They're planning to go
in through the west gate.
Papier-mâché?! Hey, that was fake?!
We did it...!
Your orders?
Why, those...!
Right...
Of course it was! You think
I can carry five tons?!
Usopp!
After them!
Keep a close watch on
where this country ends up.
I have to give up after 5 kg!
Un... deux!
This is a light, folding model I made
out of frying pans and a stick!
Karoo!
Okay, we're going to the southwest gate!
Whether it falls, or whether it survives,
something is sure to happen
to mark the start of a new age.
Usopp! Hang in there!
Karoo!!
They can try for three of
Alubarna's five gates from the west.
Don't you die!
Someone get a doctor!
We're going after the pirate
Straw Hat Luffy, and everyone under him!
They're going to split up
and come in that way, huh?
Why, you... You tricked me, didn't you?
A doctor!
Then we'll do the same!
We'll wipe them out inside!
That's you!
All hands, reinforce your gear!
Prepare to depart for Alubarna!
No more mercy!
"Alubarna - Southeast Gate Battle"
You're not getting away!
Yes, sir!
Mole art of escaping!
"Alubarna - Southeast Gate Battle"
"Winners: Team Usopp & Chopper"
Mole-fish!!
Straw Hat Luffy...
She's gone into the molehill again!
Hey, someone's coming up! Is it the enemy?!
I told you, it's no use!
What?! We can't cross
the river with this crab?!
No, wait!
Watch out for the holes!
They're the Supersonic
Duck Squadron! Let them in!
W-What's she planning to do this time?
Moving Crabs are creatures of the desert,
so they don't take to water.
But it's a crab, right? A crab!
Not a lobster! Do something!
All right...
--Are you okay?
--Y-Yeah.
You stay out of my way,
or I'll deal with you, too!
Hey, this is a problem. Not good.
Look here.
Koza! Are you all right?!
If we just blithely swim across
this river, as wide as a sea,
Where are you, you bastard?!
Where did you go?!
Stop!!
Y-Yeah.
we're not going to
make it in time! And look!
There's no way you're getting away!
You've still got that
bullet from Nanohana...
After we cross the river, there's
still dozens of kilos worth of desert!
Watch out for the holes, you say?
If this crab can't get to the other shore,
This is a battlefield.
Something like that doesn't matter here.
That won't do any good.
are we supposed to run from there on?!
Under the ground is like
a swimming pool to me!
We don't have any choice.
Never mind me,
There's no way we'll make it in time!
I'd like to get one
of their horses somehow.
It's absolutely impossible!
If we get down this street,
and through the center of town,
Y-You guys...
A pool?
we'll be at the north block,
where the palace is.
Thanks for following us all the way here.
The palace? What are you planning to do?
Uh-oh. Hey, the river!
What?!
You mean...?
Nice work, Captain Karoo. You're the man.
--I can see Sandora River!
--What?!
Demand that King Cobra surrender.
--Mole...
--Usopp!
Stop! Stop!
Do something, Pincers-kun!
...Banana!!
Don't be ridiculous! North block
is where the royal army's
I know! Pincers loves dancing girls!
You guys have good instincts!
That's right, I'm Princess Vivi!
Sanji-san!
Mr. 4! Lassoo! You guys take
care of the reindeer man!
main force, including Chaka and Pell,
will be! It's too dangerous!
You guys can stand down, too.
What are you talking--
er, talking about? I'm the real Vivi.
--Will this do?
--Probably.
Holy crap!
We haven't even mustered
all of us together yet!
You have a rebellion to stop,
right, Vivi-chan?
Show off your 400-swing punk knocks!
We can wait until reinforcements get here
Ah, he's looking this way!
I wonder if this is far enough?
from the other areas of town, right?
I'll take care of him.
It's already too late as it is.
We're accelerating!
Nami-san!
It's amusing how well you
folks have fallen for this.
Give me a hand!
It's no use! I can't take
an attack like this anymore!
Hey, Koza!
Now...
You've now messed up two
animals with all this nonsense!
It's all or nothing!
I'll have to use these three minutes
Let us show you who we really are.
All right, pervy power!
to think up a way to beat this guy!
Too bad, you guessed wrong!
So, what has this solved? Chopper!
Rumble!!
What?!
Are you the ridiculous transforming man?
Go!
Brain Point!!
You stay out of my way. Who are you?!
He did it!
Thank you, everyone.
Hey, now, this crab is incredible!
I don't believe it!
Halt! Are you with the rebel army?!
Go on.
I have to hurry. The rebel army
is already just right over there.
Scope!!
Look after Karoo.
Whoa, way to go!
There's nothing ahead in
north block but the palace!
It's a miracle!
Just stay on the water, and run!
Let's go, Karoo!
Run, run, run all the way! Go!
Understand me?!
You can make it! Keep going!
You can do it! This crab can do it!
If you're not here as part of the battle,
leave this area of town at once!
She's getting away!
Hey, are you listening, woman?!
This is no playground!
You've gotta be kidding me!
Hey, what's this?! Am I imagining
things, or are we sinking?
We are sinking, here!
You get to die!
I know!
Why don't I start by having you
return our sharpshooter's...
Princess Vivi!
Stop sinking, you crab!
It couldn't be!
No time to whine about it.
Keep moving forward.
Vivi and Koza must not be
allowed to meet, no matter what.
Is it really her?
...prized goggles to me?
H-Hold on a second!
What?
Where is my father? Where is he now?
Aren't there any boats?
How many kilos to the other shore?
I won't be done in like he was.
W-Well, the thing is...
You're in league with Straw Hat?
In that case...
About 50 kilos.
Who can swim that?!
Well, then, are you the fabled Mr. Prince?
...take me to where Chaka is!
There's something I want him to do!
A camel?!
Thank you!
And I know you from earlier!
Nope.
Thank you, Pincers!
My name is Sanji. I'm a
first-class cook of the sea.
Koza, where are you now?
This is no time to be
casually waving goodbye!
S-Sorry!
Go on, Zoro! Let them have it!
You keep quiet!
A cook? I happen to be a
super-first-class one myself.
What?!
--They got us.
--How much was that debt, again?
--Quite the farce, huh?
--You've already forgiven that!
Cooks shouldn't defy
underworld organizations!
There's not going to be a rebellion now.
What?!
That underworld organization
bit goes for both of us.
I'm a cook, and a pirate.
I'll stop them, at any cost!
If I don't stop them now,
then this will all be for naught!
An eye for an eye, is that it?
Deux!
That's what it is. You keep
your hands off of this country.
Un... deux...! Un... deux...!
It's a rare Sandoran catfish!
They're only very rarely seen!
"West Block"
Remember, the people are the country.
You don't have to explain that!
Father...
Also, humans are their favorite food!
You might tell us that first!
You still have a rebellion
to stop, right, Vivi-chan?
Go! Go! Zoro! What are you waiting for?!
Hurry up and pound them!
You want it so nobody dies in this fight.
You guys shut up and go hide somewhere!
Secure those cannonballs!
I don't want them rolling away!
Artillerymen, maintain your posts!
Would you guys make this fun for me?
Don't you think that's too soft-hearted?
Hey, let go! I can't see anything
in front of me, you know!
Keep your cannonballs under tight control!
You bastard...!
People die.
Chopper, let go!
Stop talking like that!
The ground is really rumbling, huh?
What a kick...
The enemy is a force of
two million angry men.
Imagine, him being able to
compete with my Ballet Kenpo!
If you are the one and only hope
for preventing the rebellion,
Go, Zoro! This is the only
virtue you've got, right?!
Even the earth shakes a little
before them. Do not shrink back!
Out of my way!
then you have to survive, no matter what.
Kung Fu Dugongs?!
I told you, if you want to get by,
you'll have to defeat me, first.
No matter what might
happen to any of us here.
They say they won't
neglect their senior pupil.
Well, it's not like we're
Luffy's pupils, or anything...
Just keep pushing your luck like that.
Hurry up and finish off...
those... ugly-looking...
Still, they saved us.
Day in and day out, lesson, lesson!
All right, just a little
farther! Hang in there!
You guys go on ahead!
It's okay, Karoo. You don't have to be here.
The dancer's kenpo I've refined will
not be beaten by the likes of you!
What do you think you're doing? Huh?!
Thank you!
We'll be waiting for you in Alubarna, okay?!
First rule of the guide to killing:
Eliminate the weaker targets first.
Bye-bye!
You could get trampled on.
Yeah!
Things have been going smoothly.
Can we make it?
Let us show you how a pro works.
It's no use trying to escape from my fists!
That's a tough one.
Even riding on Lashes-kun,
I'm not sure there's enough time.
M-Me?
Ballet Kenpo!!
What's more, he could
only carry, uh... two of us!
J-Just a minute! There's no
meaning in getting rid of me.
It will be...
And if Baroque Works is going to
attack us, it will be from here on.
My face and style might be
outstanding, but I've got no skills.
Please, Leader, listen to what I have to say.
...this pathetic little kingdom that dies.
Isn't there any way for
all of us to act together?
I'm a non-combatant.
Didn't we just say so?
Starting by getting rid of such
is the fastest way to work.
Damn, there isn't any, huh?
I'll stop this! No matter what I have to do!
Degenerate Swan Dance Recital!!
Well, sure! Of course, you're right.
I'd do the same, myself.
Everyone, stay together!
Charge through at the southern gate!
We'll knock out all the
others from the inside!
I'm not getting anywhere like this.
I'm gonna settle it right here and now!
Look over there!
Make ready your resolve!
What, is it the enemy?
A-A-Are they here already?!
I told you to shut up
and hide somewhere.
Chopper...?
--Collier Shoot!!
--Un!
N-No! That's...!
--Épaule!!
--Deux!
--Côtelette!!
--Ora!
Karoo!
Stop, rebel army!
This is the southeast gate
that Sanji meant, right?
And the Supersonic Duck Squadron!
Selle!!
This fight is a set-up!
Un!
It looks like the fight is over.
--Poitrine!!
--Deux!
You've come to get us, haven't you?!
--Gigot!!
--Krah!
Where is Chopper?
Please! Listen to me!
Ballet Kenpo!
Karoo!
Chopper!
Hey, Chopper! Wake up! Hey! Come on!
Mouton Shot!!
Chopper...
Swan Arabesque!!
Is this the time for you to be
concerned about someone else?
Usopp... Thank goodness
you're all right...
Don't be silly! Are you all right?
I told you, no more mercy, you "ba"!
Rebel army! Stop!
It's nothing serious.
I'll torment you as much as I like,
and turn you into desert dried fish!
So...
...this is what remains,
after the Mr. 4 pair left, is it?
And here, I came to help you out!
Mole Banana!! Here goes!
Hey, did you see a person there just now?
Meat!
That's too bad. I, the champion of
the seas, the world's greatest hero,
A person? This is no time for nonsense!
Captain Usopp-sama, wanted to
show off my fighting prowess!
Never mind that,
they're already shooting at us!
You can't go after that spot on a guy!
They're still around here,
somewhere. Be careful.
Quit your griping, you "ba"!
My Mouton Shot...
blocked by that bastard...?
What?! Tell me that part first!
There's a difference in the level
of pirate that you and I are.
What was that for?!
There's no visibility now!
Mole Banana!! Mole Banana!!
Banana!! Banana!! Banana!!
My Swan Arabesque, stopped by
that insignificant cook...?
Yuba is going to die.
What kind of dumb move
was that, royal army?
And then, the flame of anger in
the rebel army will burn even hotter.
Terrific!
You've got to be kidding me!
There are ruins of a wall over there!
You idiot! I haven't given
the order to fire yet!
If I keep dashing at this speed toward it,
Okay, fine! I mean business!
From now on, I mean business!
she'll hit the part of the
wall buried under the sand
Don't go acting on your own!
with a major crash!
T-Terribly sorry about that!
My hand slipped, and it just happened.
What on earth is that?!
Nobody's even there!
Try me.
Banana!! Banana!!
You don't know what
my ability is yet, do you?
They're under the ground.
Miss Merry Christmas
Come on, come on, come on,
come on!
What's amazing is the capacity
of my memory. If I use it,
Now bash your head open!
is a mole-woman,
thanks to the Mole-Mole Fruit.
A mole-woman?
I could make, say, this sort of montage!
The other one, Mr. 4, is a fourth-batter,
together with his dog.
When you see this, you will
laugh until you collapse.
Huh? That doesn't make any
sense at all. What do you mean?
First...
the world's most unusual hair...
Here it comes! Look out!
Don't back down! Charge through!
It's just a cloud of sand!
Then, the world's most unusual eyes...
Wha--?!
The world's most unusual nose...
No, everyone! Stop!
The world's most unusual mouth...
For the sake of our country!
Make the king pay!
Now, take a good, long look!
Grand opening, today!
Leader!
Usopp!
The Copy-Copy Montage!
Thank... you...
Leader!!
Are you okay, Usopp?
Why do you fight?
That was close! You saved me! Thanks.
What's the matter, Koza?
What exactly was that just now?
Like I said, Mr. 4 is a fourth-batter,
It's nothing.
You, who have the name of "D"?
Was it my imagination?
together with his dog.
90% of that was your own face, huh?
"D"...?
And I said, that doesn't
make any sense at all.
Usopp...
Who are you people?
Ah, it's him!
You've left yourself open!
Stop playing around, you dirty bastard!
Apparently, that was
a pointless question, huh?
Don't you have a heart?! You devil!
A dog?
Leader!
I don't have time to mess
around with your craft.
I don't have time for that.
The Rumble Ball will only
last for two more minutes.
Remember, this is our final battle!
I found you!
Craft? That's nothing!
Calling it a craft is nothing!
Usopp will be fine. It will take
more than that to beat him.
There was someone like this once.
What is that?!
Wait! Listen to me!
Right now, finding their weakness comes first.
A man who, through friendship,
made me powerless.
Where is Vivi-sama?!
My.
Otherwise, we're going to get beaten here.
"Mr. 4's pet gun Lassoo, the dog-gun"
Leader!!
--Love is everything. People have
to have love. Your love needs me.
--So that's it. I more or less get now...
Are you awake already?
"Mr. 4's pet gun Lassoo, the dog-gun"
"(has a slight cold)"
Yeah, it's just like Usopp
said, isn't it? Right now,
Now that I've got a handle on your ability,
O-Oh, no!
this won't turn out like last time!
I'll just do whatever I can!
...what you're going to do.
W-What?!
Go on, try to lay a hand on--
What?!
Don't overexert yourself.
You must be seriously hurt.
--Here it comes!
--Again?!
H-How could you?!
That was the face of your friend!
What do you take your friends to be?!
Here they come!
This works out perfectly.
Why don't you save that boy?
You have to run far away, Usopp!
Prepare to fire!
What are you, stupid? No matter
who you change your form into,
you're still you.
He is a courageous knight
I'm not the sort that's
caught up by such images.
who delivered your precious
princess to this land, after all.
Usopp!
A person is their soul!
Besides, the princess is safe.
She's on her way to Alubarna right now.
Are you all right, Usopp?!
I'm not sure about what will
happen to her later, though.
A person is their soul...?
Like I said, what exactly was that?
The situation is what it is, you know?
You're so...
It's a time bomb. It explodes
even if it doesn't hit anything.
...refined!
Got crushed, did you?!
You old penguin hag! Serves you right!
They can calculate the time
it will take, and then hit them.
Bring down Alubarna!
I'm embarrassed to have
been caught up by looks!
I told you, I'm a mole!
Or to put it the other way, they
don't explode until their time is up,
All right. Even if I were to,
say, set myself up as her,
Molehill Highway!!
so I thought I could catch the
bomb up and throw it back at them,
--Mellorine! Mellorine!
--or any of your other friends,
If I'm no match for her, then just
who will be able to protect Vivi-sama?
but that ball is as heavy as a wrecking ball,
--Mellorine! Mellorine!
--it wouldn't mean anything.
What are you doing?! Let me go!
and isn't the sort of thing you can catch.
Stop it! This is dangerous to do out here!
If you go too fast, you'll--
To be able to hit it with a bat,
especially at the speed that he does,
Mellorine! Mellorine!
Wah! In front of you! Look!
A wall! A wall in front of you!
Mr. 4's strength is extraordinary.
He's easy to read...
Can't you see that?! Stop it!
Mellorine! Mello--
Meat!
Really easy to read...
Mole-Mole Impact!!
--rine! Mellorine! Mel--
Huh...?
Seriously easy to read...
Lassoo!
Just you wait, Cobra.
We're going to defend Alabasta.
Just how many tons is that
bat that he swings around?
You're a fool.
I see it! I know your weakness!
We're not about to turn it over to you!
It's Vivi-sama!
--La...!
--Hey, Mr. 4! Mr. 4!
It's true! The princess has come back!
Karoo...!
"Royal Army" "Rebel Army"
You bastard, you! You 'tard, you!
Why, at a time such as this?
What are you just standing around for?!
Let them have it, already!
You... shielded me...
"The capital, Alubarna"
Come on, and let them have it!
Get on with it, and let them have it!
Hurry! Look lively!
Go on, and let them have it!
Let them have it!
Are you insane, Vivi-sama?! If we did that...
I'm so sorry... We've done so much...
but the rebellion has started...
Come on, get on, go on!
Have at it, you... you...
Stack it up higher!
"Ba"! You "ba"!
Ready cannons at the southern gate!
Stop dawdling around! Hurry!
If we did that, what?
This land would be finished?
I'm so sorry...
Now!
Bring more cannonballs over here!
There she is! The mole-woman!
But still, I will stop it!
She's a mole!
I haven't even transformed
yet, "ba"! You "ba"!
It wouldn't, would it?
This place isn't Alabasta, after all.
No matter how many times
I'm brushed aside,
Usopp!
Chaka-sama!
I can't let something like this
make all we've done be for nothing...
Usopp, can you get up?! Usopp!
Chopper, you'll have to take it from here.
The enemy's number is said
to be well over two million!
Bury my body at sea
when I'm gone, would you?
Get away from the mole, and her holes!
That's something I learned...
aboard the ship...!
The Kingdom of Alabasta...
You just got done saying you
came to help me, you dumb jerk!
What do you think of
His Highness's attack on Nanohana?
You don't have to tell me!
Now, look...
Not knowing when to quit!
I have served him for
ten years, so I was quite...
What is that dog-looking thing
over there?! You expect me to fight
Hurry!
What are those guys doing now?
against a mysterious life form
as inexplicable as that thing?!
Vivi!
Yeah. There's really no way
anyone could believe it.
I'm a human! Get it?!
So this is where you are!
I can only presume that something
must have happened to the King.
Usopp-san!
I'm a human, too!
We can still make it in time!
Hurry up and hop on!
Fool! You're a monster!
...is the people who are
hurting each other now!
And if so, it's all the more reason
why we must not lose this fight.
What about you, with that long nose?!
Right! Hold on, Karoo...
You shut up, bluenose!
That bird has had it!
It's because of them that this
place first became a country!
Now you've said it, longnose!
Do not flinch at the enemy's number.
Is this any situation for you
to be arguing like that? Eh?
If we can stop this war,
then that's good enough!
For the King's sake, as well as for that
of Vivi-sama, who has returned home,
We have to hurry! The rebellion
will only get worse! Hurry!
we are going to defend this country!
Please! If we can draw everyone's
eyes over here for a few seconds...
Sorry about that.
That... bird...?
Everyone who is not
involved in this battle,
His name is Lassoo.
W-What?
take shelter outside the city!
We cannot warrant your lives if you stay!
He's a gun that ate a dachshund
model of the mutt-mutt fruit.
...then I will come up
with something from there.
Let's go, Karoo!
Run! We're going to be
caught up in the battle!
I swear, I will!
A gun?!
Are you saying that
a gun ate a Devil Fruit?
It's a new technique in the Grand Line.
Things are finally starting
to become hectic, huh?
What's the matter? Hurry! This way!
Even things are able to eat Devil Fruit.
Destroy... this palace!
Hurry up and start fighting,
already, will you?
The molehill's weakness...
Ha! Don't be ridiculous! If he was
originally a gun, how could he move?
Things are so slow, I can't stand it.
Usopp-san, prove yourself.
...is that all of the tunnels are connected.
Devil Fruit doesn't have a will of its own!
And how does a gun eat
something in the first place?!
Oh, you doubt who I am?
Oh...
I don't care if he is the king,
or if he is the king,
Shut up! What good will it
do for you to learn that
...yeah...?
See?
if you're going to die here anyway?!
I can't take guarding him for too long.
It's not him!
Something can't help it if it moves,
you know, you "ba"! "Ba"! "Ba"!
Can't take it!
Can't, can't, for crying out loud!
Usopp! Hey, Usopp!
W-What are you saying, Princess?!
Isn't that right, Mr. 4?
Lashes, wake up!
This palace has a 4,000-year history!
I mean, sure, slipping
past the palace guards
Oh, Sanji. Good morning.
Listen up. You guys can't
escape this place anymore.
and kidnapping this guy is a mission
that only we could carry out,
Please don't go through with
this foolish idea, Vivi-sama!
--Right.
--Ah, how did our fight turn out?
Chaka-sama, don't let
your judgment go astray!
Not now that you've entered our territory.
but now that it's over,
nothing could be more boring than this!
The part of the mission where we
lured them away was successful.
The king is not present!
You'll enjoy this. The territory's
name is "Molehill, Block 4."
Right, Mr. 4?
We cannot allow you
to do this on your own!
And then...
You heard me, right?
It was over in two seconds.
One second each.
They're alive!
You are so slow when it comes
to answering me, really!
This is bad. My Rumble Ball's
effectiveness is already half gone.
Couldn't you hold out a little longer?!
Ah, my back is sore!
My back hurts! My back!
But then, Your Majesty,
the way things are headed,
S-She's turning into a mole-woman!
Chaka... Koza...
But Sanji, what are you doing here?
this country is in a mortal crisis!
You must not fight. You yourselves
are what this country is.
Your ducks came to get some
help for you! In any case...
So what if it is? Are you
saying we should wipe out
No more...
You must not overcome each other.
You let Mr. 2 get away, didn't you?
No more! No more!
We're gonna get killed!
the people of this land,
without even knowing the cause?
--A penguin?
--I'm a mole, I tell you! You "ba"!
Yes.
Usopp!
You've gotta be kidding me!
There's no way we can beat them!
Those who lament war...
That indeed would be the
destruction of this country.
Not those monsters!
They're still alive, after that!
Listen up. That degenerate's
transformations are perfect.
She went underground!
No, we can't run away!
Not from these guys!
We set out for Rainbase, where Crocodile is.
There's no telling when he
might pose as one of us,
Those who go to war...
Usopp!
and make an attempt on Vivi's life.
He's right!
Forgive me for saying so,
--All right, now's my chance!
--Wait!
but if we were to turn
against Crocodile now,
If you feel that any of us is
acting the least bit suspicious,
You can take it from here!
it would be like pouring fuel
on the flames of rebellion.
That was an insolent stunt for you to pull!
Go on, run away!
While we would be attacking Rainbase,
take off this wrapping, and
show each other your marks.
After going that far,
you can't just run away, you know!
Watch out!
the rebel army would come
against Alubarna Palace!
If they can't do that, they're a fake.
Those who incite war...
--It missed!
--A curveball?!
Usopp!
Whoa, having a two-stage plan is
uncharacteristically smart of you.
And so what if a rebel army
were to take the castle?
Those who know the truth,
and would prevent it...
No!
Ha! I guess if the captain is that feeble,
his crew must be wimps, too!
So does that mean you're
that degenerate already?!
It's above you, Usopp!
Even if we, the royal army, were to fall,
I'll cut you down!
Fly ball!
Ah, that's Zoro.
Ha, no big deal!
if we cut out the root of this,
the country will surely rise again.
Oh, it is Zoro?
I guess their cleanup batter
can't even hit .100, huh?
Each of their feelings are at odds,
as they clash in the
capital city of Alubarna.
It is not this castle that
we should be protecting,
Captain...?
I can avoid this one
with my eyes closed!
What about Luffy?
it is the people of this country!
You... are not Usopp-san!
If you mean Straw Hat Luffy, he got
killed a while ago, at the boss's hand.
Spin!
Remember...
Look out behind you!
...the people are the country.
"Port town of Nanohana"
Oh, dear...
The rebellion has begun, and all...
I wonder what gave me away.
If he was just fourth up,
he wouldn't be called Mr. 4!
You guys picked the
wrong people to mess with.
I thought I was perfect.
Vivi-sama...
The final revolt has begun, has it?
We got a report from Zero-chan
There was a ship.
Vivi-sama and the others
that you all had the same
mark wrapped up on you.
appear to have arrived in this land safely.
I shall do as you say!
Luffy... is dead...?
I must hurry. I do hope I am in time.
This is bad.
Don't you lie to us!
Vivi-chan is in danger!
I always wanted to talk about it
I couldn't even say half of it
I'm by your side, I glitter
every time we share a dream
The smile you gently gave me
was a very happy and kind one
Glory glory you're my shine
Because you're here, even
these tears turn to courage
I want to be strong,
I want to share with you
I'm sure I'll make it there
I see it! There's Alubarna!
That bastard! If he hurts
Vivi-chan, he's gonna pay!
They've gone into the molehills!
Watch out for the holes!
Luffy is dead?
Yaah! Why are they coming after me?!
Don't you lie to us, you haggy old mole!
Let's go! Everyone ready?!
What are they planning to do this time?
--Luffy... Luffy can't be dead!
--Usopp!
That dumb woman! Where did she go?!
The rebel army is all yours, Vivi.
Usopp! Behind you!
Chopper! Wake up!
If I don't stop them now, then all
that we've done will be for naught!
I have to think of a way to beat them!
This first-class cook of the sea
is nothing special, is he?!
Watch out! She's under the ground!
Hmph! You're a pesky
dancing bastard, to take me on.
I can't take any more!
We're gonna be killed!
Look, just go find somewhere to hide!
Let me show you my dancer's kenpo,
Please, listen to what
I have to say, everyone!
There's no way we can take them!
The Copy-Copy ability? Ha!
So what if your face has changed?
I have to stop this!
I can't let myself die here!
No! We can't get away!
Not from these guys!
developed during my daily lessons, lessons!
I thought I just heard a voice...
Am I imagining things?
On the next episode of One Piece!
Let's see what you've got!
"Sworn on a Friend's Dream!
The Battle of Molehill, Block 4"
"Alubarna Grieves!
The Fierce Captain Karoo!"
"Transformed into Nami!
Bon Clay's Rapid-Fire Ballet Kenpo"
"Rebel Army vs. Royal Army!
Showdown at Alubarna!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Big Opening Day Today!
The Copy-Copy Montage!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!