A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
"North Block"
"West Block" "South Block" "East Block"
The feelings of those who are in anguish
are crushed by a dry cloud of sand.
There are those who seek hope,
and those who cling to hope.
Their feelings cross each other,
uncertain what to do,
marking an era of history ending in sadness.
Their feelings cross each other,
uncertain what to do,
marking an era of history ending in sadness.
Vivi and her friends continue to fight in
order to save Alabasta from its crisis...
Nami engaged in mortal combat
Crocodile tries to get information
on where the Poneglyph is
with Miss Doublefinger,
who has Spike Spike Fruit powers,
As this was happening, at the southeast gate,
Sanji was toyed with by Mr. 2, a master of
ballet kenpo, and fought a difficult battle.
In addition to Usopp and Chopper's victory...
and announces that a cannonball
will be shot into the Palace Square.
and was overwhelmingly dominated by her.
Usopp and Chopper were taking on
However, Usopp's invention, the Clima Takt,
gradually began to show it's true power.
the mole-woman, Miss Merry Christmas,
...Sanji crushed Mr. 2 Bon Clay.
Will this be the end of Alabasta?
and cleanup batter Mr. 4,
in a life-or-death battle.
However, during the battle, he figured
out the Clone Clone power's weak point
Or will there be real peace?
Calling on their wisdom, Usopp and
Chopper finally defeated the pair.
and finally emerged victorious.
Meanwhile, Crocodile appeared at the palace
The sandglass of fate starts
the final countdown once again.
Meanwhile, Princess Vivi has
decided to destroy the palace
and finally began to reveal the
ultimate goal behind his ambitions
Meanwhile, Sanji and Mr. 2,
Bon Clay, were engaged
in order to save citizens' lives.
in hand-to-hand combat with each other.
in front of Vivi and Cobra.
Sanji faced impending danger
from the Copy-Copy Montage
However, as the countdown to the
explosion began, Crocodile appeared.
Meanwhile, Nami was engaged in
mortal combat with Miss Doublefinger,
put on by Mr. 2, Bon Clay.
"The Battle Is Over!
Koza Raises The White Flag"
who has Spike Spike Fruit powers.
"Secret Passed Down in the Royal Family!
The Ancient Weapon Pluton"
Take this!
H-How cute!
Tornado Tempo!
Out of our way!
Out of our way! Out of our way!
Oh, that's...!
"Nami's Cyclone Advisory! Clima Takt Burst"
"Transformed into Nami!
Bon Clay's Rapid-Fire Ballet Kenpo"
Luffy-san's dead...? You're lying!
Please wait, Chaka-sama!
What's he talking about?
What's Pluton? What on earth is he...
Hmm...? Who are they?
You're just what they mean when
they say, "he's nothing but talk!"
It's not a lie.
--What?
--The doves tangled up on me...!
You guys...
You don't even have the
strength left to get up, do you?
Straw Hat is buried in the sands
of Rainbase, Miss Wednesday.
I hear that one shot from Pluton
will completely destroy an island.
Kicking Claw Force!
Don't think I'm just going to
lie down and be beaten like this!
"Alabasta Kingdom Elite Guard Unit
Kicking Claw Force"
No matter how much you
might look like Nami-san,
If only he hadn't gotten involved
with you, he could've lived a long life.
you're still that idiot on the inside.
Don't do it!
The world's most disastrous weapon
from ancient times, also called a god.
You damn bastard! Don't get too cocky--
Stay away from this man!
There's no way he could be
killed by someone like you!
It should be sleeping
somewhere in this country.
Well, it's thanks to their sacrifice
that you're able to rant right now.
They broke the door!
It's the Kicking Claw Force!
An ancient weapon? Such a
thing exists in this country...?
As a result, Usopp's invention,
the Clima Takt, led Nami to win the battle.
Damn it! She's so cute!
--Just as you'd expect from the elite troops!
--Please save His Majesty and Vivi-sama!
Aah, I must say,
this country is too hot for me.
Give them your deepest thanks,
so at least the dead can...
And Father knew about it...?
Your Majesty! Defending you
to the death is our mission!
The only battle left was the one
between Mr. 1 and Zoro.
A secret passed down with the throne...
I just want to take all of my clothes off.
Where's Luffy-san?!
That's been my goal from the start.
We can't just stay away from him...
I'll help!
Why're you here?!
With it, I'll be able to build
the best military state right here.
Ballet Chop!!
When dealing with one of
the Seven Warlords of the Sea...
So basically, your body is hard as steel.
My eyes!
...we have to do whatever
it takes, even if it's unfair.
You fool!
Unless I'm capable of cutting
even steel, I can't cut you down, huh?
In order to achieve that,
all this time you've been...!
...rest in peace...
All four of us...
Kick Pointe!!
That would be correct.
...will fight together...
Once I become the king of this country,
...to set things right.
Smashing and cutting
attacks don't work on me.
it's easy to bring pirates in
this area under my umbrella.
It seems that you are very popular...
I see. This bites.
My influence will increase,
I'll spare you, so go home.
You're nothing but talk, are you?!
Since I'm not yet capable of
cutting steel, I can't defeat you now.
and I will eventually gain more power
than even the World Government.
--No can do.
--Hm?
You bastard...!
Humph... Then what're you going to do?
It'll be a dreamlike country.
Well, I'll sympathize with you.
There's a reason that we can't withdraw.
There's no way that the World
Government would allow that!
Mess with me, will you?!
What?
Mascara Boomerang!!
A reason?
They probably wouldn't. That's why
I need it... the powerful Pluton...
I've been waiting for a
difficult situation like this.
If you really are the ringleader
of this whole rebellion...
I've been thinking that it's about
time for me to go to the next level.
I'll see you in hell!
I don't know where on earth
you heard that name,
Oh, don't kick me.
When I defeat you,
but I don't know where it is
I'll be a man who can even cut steel.
and I'm not even certain such a thing
really exists somewhere in this country.
Those bruises...!
Don't tell me you guys...!
Have to catch my mascara, okay?
I see. What you say
probably isn't a complete lie...
"Secret of Powerful Swordplay! Ability to
Cut Steel and the Rhythm Things Have"
Playing with you is fun, but I can't
dawdle around too long, you know?
Shall I...?
I did think that that was also possible...
No, don't bother. They're worms.
I can hear the sounds of battle from here...
I do know, too, that its
very existence is in doubt.
It's my duty to kill the princess, after all.
So she wasn't able to stop
the rebel army at the entrance...
Humph... When you defeat me... huh?
They didn't...
I wonder if Vivi and the others are okay...
This might throw cold water
on that enthusiasm of yours,
I'm going to hurry up and finish this now.
Chaka! Something is wrong with them!
They're all... fighting with their very lives...
but ever since I gained Dice Dice powers,
Ha! Twirl, twirl, I'm twirling around!
In order to boost their
power temporarily... they...
And yet I'm...
I've never been given even a scratch by
those who call themselves swordsmen.
What noisy flies...
...they drank the water that
shortens their lives... the fatal fuel...
I heard that Cobra-sama has
been crucified by Crocodile.
What?! Blow up the royal palace?!
No swordsman can defeat me.
They only have a few minutes left to live...
Save Cobra-sama!
Yeah. Orders have come down
to blow up the royal palace.
Like I said...! I want a
more powerful weapon, too!
Ahh... I get the picture...
We have to do our utmost
to get inside somehow!
They can't be saved...
Oh, no...
...but you can store all those
old tales away in an album.
We're going to blow up the royal palace!
But we can't do anything because of
those hands coming out from the door!
Powerful weapon...? What's the
point in you becoming strong?
I thought as much...
I don't know how many swordsmen
you've fought in the past,
They can't be serious.
It's impossible unless we do
something about those hands!
The palace has a 4,000-year history.
It's true that I'm not a combatant,
I have a nice figure and I'm cute...
Challenging me at the cost
of your own lives...?
but we've never met before, so...
According to my plan,
Chaka-sama... Please forgive us
for doing this without consulting you.
the rebel army will reach that Square
within 20 minutes or so and start fighting.
--Huh? Say what?
--...but I still...
What can I say...
However, we have to make him
realize... this country's pain...
...wanna be at least strong enough
not to cause the others trouble...
It seems that at least your tongue is sharp.
...about this situation we are in?
After that... in other words,
at 4:30 pm, 30 minutes from now...
It's okay, I understand.
There was nothing you could do,
Thanks, baldy.
Especially this time, for Vivi...
except to intercept the rebel army.
...I've ordered that a powerful
cannonball be shot into the Square.
Igaram aside, you've done well
in suppressing the uprising
We'll see how long you'll last.
No, how long you'll last.
for over two years. But I was not wrong.
I met some true friends,
who are going to save Alabasta.
Are you insane?!
It's a special shell that can destroy
anything within a 5 km diameter.
You... idiots...
The view from here will
completely change, too.
You guys go on ahead!
I can handle this myself!
We have to make him...
realize this country's...
Usopp... You can understand
how I feel, can't you?
If you do that...
Make sure you deliver Vivi back
to her home! Make sure, now!
No one from either the royal army
or the rebel army will survive.
We're different from them.
Listen to me, Vivi. He will
keep Crocodile under control.
Hence, the battle will be ceased forever.
"Usopp Factory"
They're as strong as monsters.
...anger!
They can fight against any enemy
using only their own power.
The moment that the
rebel army started running,
Aren't you happy? After all,
you wanted to stop them so badly...
the time limit on this land was set.
But you and I are ordinary
humans with no power.
Once the royal army
and the rebel army meet,
Instead of doing things in a roundabout
way, like blowing up the palace,
Once the battle starts, we just
get flustered shamefully...
this land will be gone.
If you are the one and only
hope for preventing that,
it'll be quicker if we just
completely blow up both the armies.
We'll just be a burden to the others,
unable to even protect ourselves.
That's not smart...
then you have to survive, no matter what.
You should value your life.
How can you do such a thing?!
Oni...
No matter what might happen
to any of us here, from now on!
When we're like that, if we wanna fight,
What on earth did they
do to you to deserve it?!
Well, I guess it's too late, huh?
...Giri!
all we can do is depend on
powerful weapons... Right?
--You are... You are...
--Vivi-sama!
Who cares...?
Tiger... Trap!
All of you, who are willing
even to give your lives,
If you're gonna die anyway, I don't
even have to kill you myself, right?
Stop it! What good will it do?!
how are you faring now?
Vivi-sama!
The reason you frantically
work on inventing weapons
Vivi-sama...
Now, Mr. Cobra. Let me
ask you another question.
So you don't even bother fighting...?!
Over the two years that
I have not seen you,
you have become quite beautiful.
is that you wanna have pride that you
can fight just like the others, right?
Where can I find the Poneglyph?
Once we have seen this war through,
Me, too! I want to fight with
my own two hands, too, for Vivi!
I would sure like to hold a
grand banquet for those pirates.
Poneglyph... Why are you...
Chaka...
So help me!
If I tell you where it is...
Gimme food.
There isn't much time left
before we arrive in Alabasta.
Chaka... sama...
No... I'll show you...
After I kick Crocodile's ass,
gimme so much food I might die!
Yeah... Also, there's no way that
I can get strong just like that...
Daddy...
This is the very definition of stupidity.
Yes. I believe in you.
Luffy-san, you are all right.
Just what I'd expect from a wise king,
Cobra. You're a clever man.
I told you, didn't I...?
I'm sorry for being unreasonable...
I'm sure that you must
have defeated Crocodile.
Who said it's unreasonable just
because we don't have time?
You wicked fiend...!
Vivi-sama!
It's a little shocking that you
didn't even get a single bruise...
I can't... take this any more!
Chaka-sama!
What is it?
Are you saying that there's
something that Usopp-sama can't do?
You bastard!
Is it true that you are going
to blow up the royal castle?!
This is also the first time
my opponent is still standing
The soldiers are getting explosives ready!
when I thought my attacks were solid.
Chaka!
Then...
Chaka! Stop it!
Don't follow them to their deaths!
There must be some mistake!
...you're gonna do it?!
Oh, I love you! Thank you, Usopp!
Of course...
I am the one who gave the order.
...since we've never met before...
I see... A Zoan type...
Well then, let me get right to the point.
About the material cost...
Vivi-sama!
Please use as much explosive as there is.
Dog Dog Fruit, Model Jackal!
Thank you, really!
Hey, hey, hey... It's not like
weapons can be created for free...
In order to stop the senseless fighting,
and to save the lives
of the people of Alabasta,
Howling Fangs!
Well then, I'm counting on you!
No!
Hey, listen to me!
we will blow up the royal palace!
Listen, Nami. How you use the Clima Takt
comes down to your head after all.
You guys are off the hook now.
That's right!
So you're the type...
who'd die for others, too?
This guy's entire body is a blade.
Hang in there!
This is nothing serious, Usopp!
Nami-san...
Think frantically to survive the battle!
So his blades don't have a front or back!
You just shattered your femur, that's all!
That's our real weapon, right?
You may have busted your nose,
your humeri, and your clavicles,
Heat Balls and Cool Balls...
Sparkling Daisy!
but you lost only a little more
blood than should be fatal.
All I have to do is take full advantage of
their characteristics and combine them!
That's the power of the Clima Takt!
"Alubarna - North Block
In front of the Mehdi Assembly Hall"
Your blood pressure
may be at zombie-grade,
What am I doing... getting
scared by a noise like that...?
but there's nothing to worry about!
Th-This is...
Right now, I feel fantastic...
Dammit! I bled too much...
I see pretty fields of flowers...
I'll blow you away.
I guess I'm lucky that
the wounds aren't deep...
...when I grandly boasted
in front of Usopp like that...
You don't mean heaven, do you?!
Can you see heaven?!
But it does... hit me hard...
I'm prepared, aren't I...?
And one last thing... Tornado Tempo...!
This is the centerpiece of this weapon.
No matter how great a pirate you may be,
To fight for Vivi...
I wonder how the others are...
the end will still come for you...
Tornado Tempo...
No one'd better be dead...
As long as your enemy is human, they
won't be able to stand after being hit.
D-Don't die, Usopp!
Please, I don't want you to die!
I wanna know what's going on...
What?! I have to pair with Lashes?!
Farewell, Chopper...
I leave my vast treasure to you...
However, this is the very last resort
and you only get one shot.
That's right... Usopp kept his promise.
If you miss, consider it over.
In any case, I'll fight! If it's just
that woman, I should be able to...!
He's a camel, for god's sake!
If I miss, it's over...
15 gold and silver coins...
Become a good doctor...
Pay attention.
Don't underestimate how weak I am!
It was because you were unlucky
in the raffle! Just give up!
Usopp!
It seems that you have
an interesting weapon.
Open your eyes! There's something
I have to apologize to you for!
All right, then! Then promise me one thing.
But if it doesn't have practical
attacks, isn't it just a toy?
When we're in a pinch...!
This manju bun...
Make sure you save us, please!
Dummy. I only save ladies.
Whatever its purpose is,
you can call it... a weapon...
This is the manju bun that
you wanted, and I hid it.
When it comes to training,
I've done it more than anyone else.
If I knew you were going to die,
I would have given you half.
Usopp...
I've been a small, narrow-minded man.
Hey, Usopp. Why're you crying?
I've also been in many difficult
situations that had me on the brink.
It's no use running, girl.
...when it can harm people...
Who're you saying is crying?! Crying?!
Manju bun?!
Miss Doublefinger! What was that
spear-like weapon she just used?
If I don't hurry up, I'll be killed...
The last powerful technique...
When I defeat you, I'll be a
man who can even cut steel.
Manju bun...
The one who says someone's
crying is actually crying!
Tornado Tempo... I have to do it now...!
Does she also have Devil Fruit powers?
Uh, that makes no sense.
Confound that idiot!
Where the hell did she go?
But...
I've never been given
even a scratch by anyone.
That mole hag said... that Luffy's dead, so...
Do you get it now?
G-Give that back to me!
This is why I told her to
pipe down and hide somewhere.
You can't kill me with a toy like this.
She does nothing but slow
me down. Dumb woman!
I'm a spike person with
Spike Spike Fruit powers.
What is it that I lack...?!
I can release spikes from
anywhere on my body.
I... I wonder if it's true...
A sweater can probably produce
better electricity than this.
You guys believe that?
We won't know until I try! Give it back to me!
Spikes that can easily
pierce through stone walls...
Teacher...! Teacher!
Of course not! Are you stupid or what?!
That's it, I can't run anymore!
I'll have to fight!
If I get caught even once,
Hm?
she'll pierce my entire body with
those spikes, and that'll be it for me...
Me neither! I don't believe it at all!
Is it true that there're men in this world
who can cut anything, even steel?
Oh? Don't tell me you're going to fight me...
Think!
All right already! Then what we have
to do now is get to the palace ASAP.
All I have to do is get her to drop
her guard so that she can't dodge
That's right!
Impossible!
this one-shot attack,
the Tornado Tempo...! Maybe...!
Yes, it's true.
Stow your snot away until the
rumbling of this battle stops.
We're getting nowhere.
Sometimes, it calls forth clouds...
other times, it makes rain fall...
Something that I can do by using
Now, watch this paper carefully, Zoro.
the three kinds of air bubbles and the
extremely dry weather of this country...!
He's so impatient.
Yet other times, it produces wind...!
Don't swallow it!
I wish there were at least a little
more moisture in the air...
This miracle takt causes
catastrophes when it is re-arranged!
Moisture... That's right! If I remember
correctly, there's a rain technique...
Everyone... thank you...
Teacher, you didn't cut it.
Zoro!
It's too early to thank us.
Take this! My new weapon, Clima Takt!
Listen, Zoro.
He's right. Besides, if you
wanna thank pirates...
There're swordsmen out there
who are capable of cutting nothing.
Rain Tempo!
What... on earth...
The stone column! It split up lengthwise!
...you have to let us see some goods...
First, sunny weather! Fine Tempo!
Just what are you trying to
leach out of this country?!
Water tricks, huh?
Split? No, it didn't.
It was clearly a swordsman.
Sprinkler!
But they can also cut anything,
even steel... using the same sword...
Is Nami okay...? Did she get away okay...?
Wow, amazing! Doves flew out!
You're desperate, aren't you?
No! I have a plan!
"Alubarna - North Block
Behind the Mehdi Assembly Hall"
That's enough. I've had
enough of your party tricks.
That was stupid!
The strongest swordsmen are able to
protect that which they want to protect
Out of my way.
Ahh... They finally came off...
and cut that which they want to cut.
The party is at its height. Let's call it quits.
Are you... okay?
So this is what he meant by
a powerful one-shot attack...
You cut it, didn't you? With those arms?
Swordplay that harms whatever it touches...
A sea urchin?!
The first shot is often like this...
Sea Urchin Stinger!
I don't consider it real swordsmanship.
We start by getting the enemy's
guard down, right? I get it, Usopp.
That's quite an unusual body
you've got there, isn't it?
The wave of rebels is already
right around the corner...
Do you understand?
Indeed it is. I ate the Dice-Dice Fruit,
making blades of my entire body.
This time, it'll be the end
of you! Cloudy Tempo!
I'll make you Swiss cheese!
...though the situation has changed....
In any case, I should head to the palace...
You're him, aren't you?
Wow! What pretty flowers!
The swordsman who is said to have
cut down 100 men at Whisky Peak?
No way I can win like this!
Also, the pirate who, several years ago,
That's not what I'd call
Swiss cheese! It's even burnt!
turned down an invitation to
Baroque Works at East Blue,
What's going on with Vivi...?
The battle seems to have started...
What the heck is this?! Say something!
and cut down the Mr. 7 at the time...
In appreciation of your show earlier,
I'll show you something interesting, too.
Oh yeah, Vivi-chan. Just remember this.
...is you, isn't it?
Ha! There's a story that takes me back.
I don't know her situation...
but what a poor child...
Teacher, I'll be a swordsman
who can cut anything!
Now's my chance! Heat Ball!
After a battle... that guy eats tons...
That was your fault,
for not accepting my terms.
Zoro, were you listening
to what I was saying?
Yes...
We'll be waiting for you in Alubarna, okay?!
I told your scout man back then this:
Yeah!
"I will join, if you make me your boss."
Now, this will be the crucial point.
Hot air goes upwards
while absorbing moisture.
Such a funny man.
Don't goof things up!
Far from meeting my terms,
he took a slash at me.
When it collides with cold air that's
descending, it rapidly cools
Let's go! See you at the Alubarna Palace!
Humph... Hurry up and try cutting me.
Hurry up! Vivi-sama is in danger!
and the moisture gets frozen.
I just put him in his place.
Cannons! Bring cannons here!
Destroy the gate!
Would you like to try inviting me, too?
Then...
You can't cut my body down
if you just defend.
Right now, you guys are so ridiculous,
Spike Spike Doping!
Hurry up!
I wouldn't even accept
the position as your boss.
Unfortunately, I don't think I can show
you my valiant figure cutting steel...
I said pay attention, didn't I?!
Dieciseis Fleurs!
Stinger Flail!
You're making quite the fool of me, huh?
Chaka!
...because when I cut steel,
that's when you die.
You, a swordsman, from a
small-time band of pirates...
What the...
Being weak... is a crime...
In that case, who do
you think you guys are?
Makes sense...
Puppets, without volition of your own,
baited into creating a utopia in name only?
Vivi!
Or are you really just tin soldiers...
I'll cut... everything up into pieces!
Oh... these wounds are nothing...
...without any substance?
"Palace Square
25 minutes to the explosion time"
Miss Doublefinger...
"Swordplay that cuts nothing"... huh?
Everyone's fighting with their very lives.
You're going to tell me you
want to eliminate him, right?
Do as you please. And I'll deal with the girl.
Even if my arms get torn off
or my nose gets broken, I will...
I hope we can have some peace and quiet now.
If you talk too much,
you'll cause internal bleeding.
Hey, Nami!
She's gone!
I know!
So you're still alive for now.
Sanji!
Twirl, twirl! A finishing
320,000-spin grand fouetté!
Those wounds...
K... Koza!
How pointless...
So, how'd the battle with Mr. 2 turn out?
I'll cut everything up into pieces!
Of course! Here...
Can it be...?
Ballet Kenpo!
Memoirs of a Summer's Day!!
Ahhh! My goggles!
You... I see, you came through
the shortcut you used to use...
Swordplay that cuts nothing...
So you took them back
from him! Thanks, Sanji!
I see your weakness.
Cut nothing... but cut steel... I don't
understand what it means at all!
I've seen through your Copy-Copy Fruit.
Is something wrong with my eyes...?
You're such a... Ahh!
Hey, wait a sec! They're broken!
What a stubborn girl...
You bastard! This is the newest
model in the North Blue!
Thrust and Thrust... This is the
secret of powerful swordplay!
Don't you think it's pointless to
work so hard to dodge my attacks?
Do you know how valuable
these goggles are?
Atomic Spar!
Hey, look at that.
You have no chance.
Listen to me...
You're wrong!
Ah!
I came to persuade the Royal Army, but...
I'll just cut you up!
That must be the auxiliary
force for the rebel army.
According to the instruction,
there're tons more attacks!
I've seen through your Copy-Copy Fruit.
So there'll be more of them?
Chaka...
--Memoirs of a Summer's Day!!
--Joue Shoot!!
Looks like it. I guess Vivi-chan
couldn't stop the rebel army...
My Clima Takt!
The king is... about to be
killed by the country's hero...
When on earth... did you...
Ah, dammit!
It wasn't me. You dropped it here...
It's hard to believe what I'm seeing...!
Sure enough. No doubt about it.
Hm? Vaaa?
Give it back to me!
Hey, where have you been hiding, Lashes?!
Sure, I will. I'm not a magician, so...
You've seen through it,
you say? Through what?!
This has become interesting!
What part of my ability has
someone like you seen through?
Let's hurry to the palace. We might
still be able to help Vivi-chan.
And I do have enough power to fight
without depending on a thing like that.
You're in the middle of the battle right now,
and yet both sides' leaders
are facing each other here...
--Okay!
--Hey, Usopp! Let's go already!
You can't use your Ballet Kenpo
while in Nami-san's body, can you?
Y-Yeah...! Ah, hey, Lashes! Let me get on!
Now be a good girl and stay right there.
This war is now a fight to the death
Look! Can't you see these wounds?
between lizards whose heads are broken off.
Then I'll be able to kill you
without causing you much pain.
Crab... Grab!
It's true, I might not be able to attack you,
Lashes! Stop! Let me get on!
but the moment you attack me,
you always return to normal.
You still wanna continue
your fun magic show?
Looks like you're confused.
Well, that's just a natural reaction...
By touching your cheek with your left hand.
...but it's simple.
The weather forecast is thunder!
Thunder Tempo!
Just imagine the worst possible scenario.
Geez, at least you're a first-class
expert at running away...
Eh? What's that? I can't hear you at all!
Don't hold suspicion, Koza.
Thunder Tempo...
Thunder Tempo... Thunder...
Hey, I'm right, aren't I?
What an odious bastard...
Oh, yeah! The air bubbles!
S-So what if you are?!
Stinger... Finger...!
The feeling is mutual.
Yes, yes, without this limber
body that I've developed,
Let me tell you one thing.
Don't consider me a swordsman.
Do you like this country?
training daily in harsh,
demanding lessons,
It's formed! It's small, but it's still a cloud!
No!
I have many weapons
that can tear your body up.
I can't perform my Ballet Kenpo. So what?
What on earth are you talking about?
You're still plenty
black and blue, aren't you?!
Not enough...! I'll let it grow more!
Yeah! I was born here!
What's more, let me show you this.
The prima of Ballet Kenpo!
Cool Ball!
Spiral Hollow!
I'm the same way!
Heat Ball!
I'll just say this much about it.
My cheek is bleeding...
From your viewpoint, the left one is
the pen, and the right one is the cob.
That's enough!
Koza, listen...
If you're not a swordsman...
then an excavator?!
Ahh... I wonder if I'm gonna die like this...
Vivi! Who took the rain
away from this country?!
Who cares?
You bitch!
I'm an assassin!
I'm gonna die, aren't I...? I'm gonna die...!
Whether you've seen through
it or not, it doesn't matter!
Stinger... Flail!
Everything was...
If I die, I'm gonna curse him...
That long nose...! Long nose!
It was me, Koza.
Take this! Ballet Kenpo...
Sparks?! Just how fast is it spinning?!
Everything you thought
was the king's doing
...Bombardier!!
So, are you prepared to die yet?
Why didn't he make a
real good battle weapo...
was a "trap" by my company.
They'll be repelled!
How about you?
Hm...?
What?! That's the mark of his kick?!
Well, then... I'll kill you now... okay?
Over the past two years, you guys
played right into our hands...
Stop bluffing...
I can't do excavation... because
I'll drill and cut everything up.
The right choice!
Avoiding that was the right choice!
...when the royal family and army
were desperately chasing our shadows.
At the end of their bent
necks are steel beaks!
Crap!
Take that!
There isn't a single crack
around that hole!
She's standing on the underside
of the bridge...! Why...?!
True power,
when compressed into one point,
does not destroy anything needlessly.
You probably could've died happy
if you didn't know this fact...
Stinger... Hedgehog!
Consider one of my kicks to
be like a shot from a rifle.
That was close!
What a momentary misjudgment invites is...
H-H-Hey, hold on! Stop!
However, the bullet is
a bit on the large side.
I said hold on! Hold on a bit! A minute!
Would you give me a minute?! Hey!
I'm going to perforate you!
...death!
Don't listen to him, Koza!
Un!
Deux!
King...
--Collier!!
--Krah!
There's still things you can do!
I'll get caught if I'm in an open space!
That won't work!
Save as many citizens as you can!
You won't get away with this!
Damn! Too much difference in our reaches!
Within less than half an hour...
the Palace Square will be blown up!
This is it for you. Time to get skewered!
This fight is over, huh?!
What?!
No... thanks!
Flying, flying, I'm flying!
So you're still alive...
It'll be a fine day today
with stable humidity and wind
Ballet Kenpo! Memoirs of a Winter's Sky!!
as well as a high-pressure system.
Hurry!
However, in one particular area, you
need to watch for mirages and cyclones.
But the longer his reach is,
the longer it takes to recover.
You're still breathing...
If I can avoid his shot,
I'll have that much more speed!
Well, well...
Please be on the lookout for tornados.
I won't show my back to him...
Die, now!
It seems like she isn't a
total amateur in battles...
No!
Tornado Tempo... This is the
centerpiece of this weapon.
How're you gonna struggle
with your bare hands?
Vivi...!
This is the very last resort
and you only get one shot.
Hey! Move, Vivi! What're you doing?!
Too bad. How do you like this?
What was that...? I think
I read something ominous
If you miss, consider it over.
Hey, you've got something
stuck to your left cheek.
The Square will become a battlefield.
If it really gets blown up...
If I miss, it's over...
in these Clima Takt instructions earlier...
Really?
I won't... I won't let it become a battlefield!
You're not even a swordsman.
You won't understand even if I explain.
Basses Côte!!
Where was that?
The weather forecast is tornado!
That's it! I'm sure that if you use the
techniques I wrote up so far at parties,
I'll make it work... the last attack...
Humph... I'm not even interested.
Longe!!
You're still panicking!
...since I wanted to fight with
my own hands... for her...!
people will love them and
the party will really heat up!
Tendron!!
What do you think will happen
Spar... Break!
if they realize now that
the Square'll be blown up?!
--Flanchet!!
--Un!
You gotta be kidding me!
It won't just be a panic!
Nami-san... Don't die...
Also, I'll write the configurations
for battle on the back.
Deux!
Once that happens, the war will
no longer stop! No one will be saved!
--Ora!
--Quasi!!
The back?
At least try putting all of our
lives on the line together!
--Tendron!! Quasi!! Collier!!
Flanchet!! Cuisseau!! Jarret!!
--Un! Deux! Ora!
Aren't we friends?!
--Tendron!! Quasi!! Collier!!
Flanchet!! Cuisseau!!
--Un! Deux! Krah! Un!
Isn't that right?
Well... I wonder where you're
hiding this time, little kitty?
Well, well... what a clever judgment...
--Damn it!
--Deux!
--Collier!!
--Krah!
Die in peace...
Oh, you can cry those kinds of tears...
What we should do was
decided from the beginning...!
I have... bad luck with stones today...
--Jarret!! Collier!! Quasi!!
Flanchet!! Gigot!! Selle!!
--Un! Deux! Ora!
Which is to stop this plotted rebellion!
I know you actually hate this
and want to beat him up the most!
--Queue!! Jarret!! Collier!! Quasi!!
--Un! Deux! Krah!
I won't run or hide any more.
And you're the only one who can do it!
--Flanchet!! Gigot!! Selle!! Queue!!
--Un! Deux! Ora!
I may not look it, but during the
eight years of my life as a thief,
I survived life-or-death
crises... all by myself!
Un! Deux! Krah!
Un! Deux!
--Queue!!
--Krah!
I can't stand being treated
like just an ordinary girl.
Sometimes, it calls forth clouds...
other times, it makes rain fall...
Really... I'm sorry, then...
Yet other times, it produces winds...!
What's got you so
confident all of a sudden...?
The miraculous Clima Takt! I'll make it work!
Listen up, I'm gonna show
you my real ability now!
Vivi...
The last powerful technique! For Vivi!
The battle configurations of the takt!
First, understand the
characteristics of the three takts!
You guys! Make sure you
deliver Vivi back to her home!
And you think I'll just sit back and watch?
Each of the takts can shoot off
air bubbles by shaking or blowing.
Are you okay?
--Veau Shot!!
--Bombardier Arabesque!!
See you at the Alubarna Palace!
Your left leg has taken lots of injuries...
The first one shoots off hot air...
You can't actually keep
standing any more, can you?
...a Heat Ball!
Are they... all okay...?
What is this? It feels warm.
The next one shoots off cool air...
Chaka!
Sea Urchin Stinger!
...a Cool Ball!
I am... the Jackal, Alabasta's guardian deity!
Ah, it feels cool.
And the last one shoots off electricity...
The one who destroys the
enemies of the royal family!
...a Thunder Ball!
Oh, no... that tingled.
Why is he standing...?
After being cut so many times...
These techniques aren't complete yet,
so if you use them at parties...
This is... nothing...!
As long as I still live, I fight!
Did he dodge all those falling stones?
Then don't write them down!
It doesn't hurt at all!
That's what you call "stupidity."
Do you have any idea what
pain she's going through?!
Are you happy now?
Do as you want, both of you!
I can probably hold him back
at least for a few more minutes!
Compared to her pain...
I dodged... these stones?
Sewing Stinger!
Okay!
No...
...a leg or two, or three...
Please, something I can use! Not for
entertainment, but some techniques!
I could tell... the place where
no stones would be falling...
Chaka...!
I guess the leader of
Sand Sand Clan isn't all that strong.
I don't give a damn!
Take this... Tornado Tempo!
I'm sorry...
Now, what's the matter?
Swords...
Enough is enough.
There's one underneath
that stone... I can tell...
Stinger Step!
I-I give...
Ouch!
You astound me. You're still alive?
What's with you?! You're childish!
Take it easy on me!
What's he doing...?
What's the matter? If you turn
yourself into Nami-san again,
You're a pain in the neck.
I can't finish you off.
You're the one who asked me to train you.
Ridiculous... I can't move,
in the shape I'm in...
I've experienced this feeling before...
Oh, I get it! The Heat Ball and the Cool Ball!
What good will it do to avoid
the outcome of this?
When they stop spinning, the air bubbles
hit each other, create an air flow
You've won. Kill me.
It's awfully quiet around me...
and cause a tremendous wind!
This is incredible, Usopp!
I can hear my heartbeat very clearly...
I'm destined to be eliminated
by the organization anyhow.
What? What? What? What?!
The Cyclone Tempo is like
an ordinary boomerang.
Report from Guard Unit 2 to Headquarters!
The doves tangled up on me...!
If you go outside after
a party and play with it...
What are you waiting for?
Is this... precisely what it feels
like when close to death...?
Report from Unit 2 to Headquarters!
He doesn't seem to understand it himself...
Hurry up and strike the last blow...
Line 4... has been broken through!
But with this, I might be able to...
I sensed a hint from the falling
stones as if they're living things...
That was a good fight. We shouldn't
need any more words than that.
She uses a strange weapon...!
The rebel army is currently
passing through the Central Plaza
No, it wasn't a hint...
It was clearer than that...
and heading to the North Block!
They'll reach the palace!
Pay attention until one of us wins!
Rhythm...
Stones'... rhythm...
To show your back to your
enemy during the battle...
Ow...
This is, unmistakably, the testament
of friendship between rivals.
Aren't you taking a battle
to the death too lightly?
Trees have their own rhythm...
Raise the white flag to surrender!
Surrender right now...! Royal Army!
Soil has its own... Is that what it is...?
But I'm not going to cry...
Vivi-sama! What's she saying?!
Bye, now. I'll be taking back
our sharpshooter's goggles.
Surrender?!
Listen. There're swordsmen out there
who are capable of cutting nothing.
If we do such a thing, what's
gonna happen to this country?!
H-He did strike the last blow...
Hey, look! That's...!
It's Koza! Why is the rebel army's leader here?
Does "cutting nothing" mean...
know the rhythm...?
I changed the air density
by using the Cool Ball.
I've scuffed up another
couple of bones, there, huh?
An abnormal refraction of light due to
a considerable temperature difference...
Listen to Vivi! We no longer
desire victory, or to fight!
"Alubarna - South Block"
"Battle of Polka Street"
In other words...
That's... the ability to cut even steel...
A mirage...! Can't be...
when it was this close...
"Alubarna - South Block"
"Battle of Polka Street"
"Winner: Sanji" "Prize: A little camaraderie"
I want you to stop this battle!
You... what the hell did you do?
What?! What's going on?
After receiving such an enormous attack...
We can't win with power. At any rate,
survive by using your brain!
When you're bleeding that much...
I will let the rebel army know...
that this battle was pointless...
There's no way you can be still alive...!
That's how we fight, right?!
E-Everything here is ready!
...that there's no longer
a reason for us to fight!
If I use it efficiently,
even a miracle can happen!
We can ignite here at any time, too!
In order not to shed any more
pointless blood, wave the white flag!
Looks like this is a perfect weapon for me!
I can hear... the rhythm of his steel...
This castle has taken in
Alabasta's history for 4,000 years.
Please!
Now I've figured out the Clima Takt!
My will is flowing into the sword...
I did it... I did it! Usopp... Vivi...!
Just give up!
The king's head is close at hand!
"Alubarna - North Block"
Father!
Ahh! We can now see the clock tower!
"Alubarna - North Block"
"Battle behind the Mehdi Assembly Hall"
It has been a source of pride for me.
Let His Majesty go, Crocodile!
"Alubarna - North Block"
"Battle behind the Mehdi Assembly Hall"
"Winner: Nami"
But if we destroy the royal palace,
Hey, hey... You really think
that I'd agree to let him go
We're approaching the Palace Square!
the people will stop fighting,
and pay attention.
Fine... I'll completely finish
him off with the next attack.
Prepare to attack!
after going through all the trouble
to immobilize him like that?
I will be able to tell them
the truth in my own words!
Seriously... try and use your head...
Oh, yeah...
The only question left is...
Now I remember... your face...
It's in my fuzzy memory.
...whether or not I really
have the ability to cut steel...
If I'm not mistaken, you were a famous
bounty hunter in the West Blue... right?
I'm sorry, Vivi...
Okay, light them!
I couldn't make full use of the chance
that you risked your life to create...
It's hard to think that you can defend
my attack using only one sword...
H-Hold it!
Yes, ma'am!
Also known as an assassin...
But look at you now...
What do you fight for?
You're Crocodile's dog!
That's all right. I won't defend any more.
Father...
White flags?! The Royal Army is
waving white flags to surrender!
So you're now prepared. Fine by me!
Are you doing it in order to at least get
some nice scraps by licking his hand?
W-What is this?!
Good grief... Is this how a father and daughter
talk after being separated for so long?
You son of a bitch.
One-Sword Style... Lion Strike!
I'll show you... the difference in pride...
Anyway, Miss Wednesday...
Are you all right?!
Koza-san!
I-It's him...!
Atomic Spurt!
Don't call me by that name!
I-It's Koza-san!
What is Koza-san doing here...?
...between your swords and mine...!
Koza-san... What is Koza-san
doing here...? Why...?
Three-Sword Style...
We can't have that.
Let me tell you something first. I don't
intend to keep you and your father alive.
Bull... Needles!
The battle is over!
Everyone! Subdue your anger
and drop your weapon!
Spider...
When a kingdom dies out, it's just
natural for its royal family to die as well.
The Royal Army no longer
has the will to fight!
That was quite a treacherous thing
to do, wasn't it, Miss Wednesday?
Right?
However, before I take the throne,
Please stop...!
This is soon to be my house.
I give you my thanks...
there's something that I need
to ask you, the current king.
Crocodile!
I can become stronger still!
Your Majesty!
Father!
In fact, this is indeed my biggest goal...
So basically, your body is hard as steel.
He's indeed... become stronger...
during this fight...
It sure is nice to have a palace, huh?
Unless I'm capable of cutting
even steel, I can't cut you down, huh?
Cobra... Where is the Pluton?
That would be correct.
It's a fine place to look
down on the filth below.
Smashing and cutting
attacks don't work on me.
Are you... going to cut
diamond or something next...?
W-Where is Luffy-san?
I see. This bites.
Huh? You mean Straw Hat? That puny rookie?
Since I'm not yet capable of
cutting steel, I can't defeat you now.
How... do you know that name...?
Is that true...? Koza-san...?!
That would be a waste...
Humph... Then what're you going to do?
Yeah... the battle is now...
Well, I'll sympathize with you.
You win...
He's dead.
What?
I've been waiting for a
difficult situation like this.
I've been thinking that it's about
time for me to go to the next level.
"Alubarna - North Block"
When I defeat you,
"Battle in front of the Mehdi Assembly Hall"
I'll be a man who can even cut steel.
Koza!
"Alubarna - North Block"
"Battle in front of the Mehdi Assembly Hall"
"Winner: Zoro"
I always wanted to talk about it
Which direction should I run towards
to see a more wonderful tomorrow?
I couldn't even say half of it
I took the helm and opened the
miraculous map that I stored in my heart
I'm by your side, I glitter
every time we share a dream
I aimed for the sky and sought out
my dreams, though at times I got lost
It wasn't a dream; when I met you,
I discovered the wonderful person in me
The smile you gently gave me
was a very happy and kind one
With just a bit of courage,
I gained something grand
Now's the time for my "wish"
to become my "pledge"
Glory glory you're my shine
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
Because you're here, even
these tears turn to courage
Let's sketch out the tale of the future
I'll put all my feelings
in a brand new wind now
I want to be strong,
I want to share with you
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
A never-ending journey to be together
I'm sure I'll make it there
I'll chase after you
wherever you go, Shining ray
I swore on that day that
I would never lose again.
Why're you crying?
Wake up, Princess. You can't save the country.
Tornado Tempo! That's the
centerpiece of this weapon!
I hope Nami got away all right.
She can't match up
Because that mole hag
said that Luffy's dead...
But how large the wall standing
in front of me right now is!
to someone with those abilities.
If you miss, consider it over.
Nami, it looks like it's finally
time for you to use it, huh?
My voice no longer reaches anyone...
Is that true?!
I'll make the last technique successful!
You guys believe that?
When you can't even give me a scratch,
there's only one way left for you.
What is Pluton?
I've found you, girl.
Of course not!
If nothing is done, the country will...
Your new weapon...
It must be sleeping somewhere in this country.
Then stow your snot away.
Don't worry! Your voice is heard by us.
Usopp, stay with me!
Only death.
That's been my goal from the start.
There's no reason for you to fight any longer!
Take this, Miss Doublefinger!
What the hell do I lack?!
Luffy-san!
Such a thing exists in this country...?
Surrender right now...! Royal Army!
I'm gonna put an end... to all this!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Nami's Cyclone Advisory!
Clima Takt Burst"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Secret Passed Down in the Royal Family!
The Ancient Weapon Pluton"
"Secret of Powerful Swordplay! Ability to
Cut Steel and the Rhythm Things Have"
"The Battle is Over!
Koza Raises the White Flag"
"Where Vivi's Voice Gets Heard!
The Hero Descends!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!