Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
No!
It's not a lie!
Pirates really are going
to come, aren't they?
Yeah. They're definitely gonna show up.
But everyone thinks it's a lie!
I love this village!
I want to protect everyone!
Alright! We'll help you out!
These are Klahadore's
pirates we're dealing with!
Of course I'm scared!
What's wrong with that?!
We ain't laughing!
As if we'd risk our lives
because of sympathy!
"Clash with the Black Cat Pirates!
Great Battle on the Slope!"
Alright. They're going to attack
from this shore at daybreak.
But the only route into
the village is this one slope.
Everything else is cliff,
making it tougher to come through.
In other words, if we can
defend this slope to the death,
the village won't get attacked!
Oh! That's easy!
Talking about it is, but the
rest depends on our strength!
What can you guys do?
--Cut.
--Stretch.
--Steal.
--I can hide.
You're gonna fight!
I'm just kidding! Geez!
Oh, Klahadore-san! Welcome back!
--How is she?
--She's resting now.
She seemed quite exhausted...
But to think such a thing happened
while I was at the next town over...
That Usopp lad certainly
knows how to cause trouble.
Yes...
And of all things,
he claimed you were a pirate...
Such a transparent lie!
Indeed.
What is this?
Oh, that seems to be a
present from her to you.
It's your third year at this mansion,
so it's a sort of commemoration.
Commemoration...
Your current glasses seem to slip often,
so she custom-ordered those!
She's such a nice, thoughtful person!
A commemoration?
Indeed, tomorrow is a
day to commemorate.
Eh?
It's a crescent moon tonight.
Huh?
Nights like this make my heart race,
and my blood stir...
K-Klahadore-san!
What are you doing to her present?!
Oh, I'll be accepting a present, all right.
But it won't be this--
it'll be this entire mansion!
W-What are you saying?!
There is no more need
to continue the act.
An accident is going to occur
in a few hours, anyway...
It's truly been three long years!
Miss! Run away!
Captain Jango!
It's almost daybreak!
Please wake up, Captain Jango!
--Good morning, Captain!
--Good morning!
You idiots!
My policy is to say "good morning"
with the morning sun!
--He seems to be in a bad mood.
--He did just wake up...
Just look! The moon's still up,
and it's the middle of the night!
How dare you shout loudly!
Our apologies, sir! We're sorry, sir!
Alright, then.
Good morning, fellows!
Good morning? That's the
opposite of what he just said!
You idiot! He's in a better
mood now, that's all!
Oh!
Quit bein' confusing!
Men!
Set sail!
Alright! Perfect!
Now they won't be able
to climb up this slope,
thanks to all this oil
we've laid out here!
We'll let 'em slip and
slide on this slope,
then beat the crap out of
'em while they flail about!
Oil, huh?
No matter what,
we will protect this slope!
Conversely, let's just hope
that none of us slip down there.
It'd be like diving right
into an ant-lion pit.
I'm amazed you can
think up stuff this cheeky!
But of course!
When it comes to
cheekiness and slingshots,
I'm utterly confident!
It's almost daybreak.
They'll be coming.
We're here!
Alright, men! Go ashore!
Trash the village
and head for the mansion!
Captain! There are
two strange boats here!
What?!
Shall I check them out?
Leave 'em. They're not treasure ships.
Don't screw up our schedule!
Understood!
Get going, you guys!
Where are they?
The sky's all bright now.
What's the deal?
Maybe they overslept or somethin'?
No.
They'll definitely show up. Lot's of 'em.
Say...
Maybe it's just my imagination,
but I hear, "Yaaah!"
coming from somewhere...
Yeah, I definitely hear it!
N-Now that you mention it...
What?! What is it?!
There's a place just like
this to the north, too!
You don't suppose...
You mean this is the wrong shore?!
This is where they had
their secret meeting,
so I just assumed...
Hey! Let's hurry!
They're gonna get into the
village! Where is this place?!
If you run straight north from here,
you'll get there in three minutes!
The terrain there is
almost exactly the same,
so we just need to
stop them at the slope!
Don't worry! We'll do it somehow!
Oh, no!
The north shore is where our boats are!
They're gonna take the treasure!
I'll be there in 20 seconds!
Dammit! My brilliant Oil
Strategy was all for nothing!
--My treasure...
--Hey!
What're you doing?! Let's go!
Y-Yeah! We have to hurry--
Help! I'm falling!
--Let go, you moron!
--Sorry!
Perfect!
Thanks, Zoro!
Sorry! The treasure's in danger!
Try to get back up somehow!
That girl's gonna pay!
I refuse to let them enter the village!
But Luffy sure runs fast!
I can't even see him anymore!
Straight north!
Straight north! Straight north!
They're in big trouble
if they touch my treasure!
There's someone at the top of the hill!
You!
My name is Captain Usopp!
I've been waiting for you all this time!
I-I'm completely ready to fight!
Turn back now, if you don't wanna die!
W-What the--? I'm the first one here?!
But he was running way ahead of me!
Dammit!
What do I do?! I can't climb up!
I'm in the village now! That's weird!
He said north, so I ran
in a cold-ish direction!
You're that boy who
overheard our plan.
What do you think you're doing?
I-I'm warning you!
Turn back now while you still can!
Or else my 100 million crewmen will...
...beat the crap out of you guys!
100 million?
Hey, now! That's even
worse than a kid's lie!
What?! 100 million?! Wow!
He's obviously lying, Captain!
He's so naïve...
Yikes! They saw through it?!
He seriously thought
he could fool us, too...
How dare you trick me!
Captain Jango! Shocking news!
--Really?! That's bad!
--No! It's not bad!
We found treasure
in those weird boats!
An incredible amount!
Maybe 4, no, 5 million Berries!
What?!
F-Five million Berries?!
Why is there that much
money in those guys' boats?
That's my treasure!
--But you can have it!
--What?! You'll give us the treasure?!
That's right!
In exchange for that treasure,
I ask that you turn back now!
Wha--?! You think you can
buy us off with money?!
What a disgraceful guy!
You fool. We're pirates, you know.
We're obviously going
to take this treasure!
It's not good enough of
a reason for us to turn back.
Y-You have a point...
Alright, then! On "one, two,
Jango," you'll let us by!
It's that weapon from before!
One! Two!
Jan--
Quit saying stupid crap!
Oww!
W-Who's she?!
Captain! This is no time to
hypnotize yourself and let people by!
That boat's treasure is mine!
I won't let you have a single Berry!
Hold on to it!
I'll come take it back now!
That hurt!
Who said you could
give them my treasure?!
What's wrong with just
saying they can have it?!
What're you talking about?!
After I just saved you!
--Huh?
--I forgot to mention it,
but don't watch his ring
all the way through!
He's a hypnotist!
H-Hypnosis?!
So? Where's Luffy?
He ran here first, right?
Dunno! He either
chickened out or got lost!
He got lost, then.
Geez! Just when we need him, too!
I'll take command here.
Go kick their butts! I'll cover you!
Eh?! Hold on, why me?!
There's no way I can take on that
huge army! I'm weak, you know!
Don't underestimate me
just 'cause I'm a guy!
I'm so scared my legs are
shaking like crazy! See?!
Big deal!
See, look! I'm so scared
I have tears in my eyes!
Your eyes are bone dry!
If you're gonna lie,
lie more realistically!
I don't need you to tell me that!
We don't have time to mess with them.
Crush 'em and head
for the village, men!
H-Here they come!
Oh, yeah! I have caltrops!
Oh! You do have some good stuff!
Gimme, gimme!
Take this!
Caltrop Hell!
Damn that Nami!
She's gonna pay for this!
I made it!
W-Which way is the north shore?!
Straight north!
Straight north! Straight north!
Which way is north?!
Oww!
Yes! We got 'em!
Now! Special Attack: Lead Star!
Bastard!
Way to go! Keep it up, now!
I'm gonna quit fighting for a bit.
You haven't even fought yet!
What is it?!
There are caltrops behind us too...
You moron! You dropped 'em there!
Outta the damn way!
Do you seriously think you can stop us?
Let's go, guys! Captain Kuro is waiting!
W-What the--?!
Let go, you bastard! Let the hell go!
Damn you! Take this! Take this!
I... can't...
...let you get past this slope...
Because I only lied, like I always do...
So the village is going to have
just another ordinary day...
So I absolutely won't let you pass!
Damn kid! Shut up!
Damn girl!
Oww!
Are you--?!
That's enough now!
Hey, you guys!
Quit bothering with them
and get going already!
Have you forgotten that
this is Captain Kuro's plan?!
If anything happens
to throw his plan off,
he'll kill every one of us!
Do you understand that,
you dumbasses?!
--H-Hey, now...
--Yeah, hurry to the village!
S-Stop...
Dammit...
Stop!
Stop... Don't go to the village!
Shut up!
Stop! Please!
Please don't kill everyone!
I love this village! I want to protect it!
W-What is this, Captain Jango?!
Nobody mentioned guys
like them were in the village!
About time...
What were those
unchallenging guys just now?!
Don't look at me!
I'm not satisfied, though!
Nami! How dare you
kick me down there!
Usopp, you jerk!
You didn't say which way was north!
Who're they?
They're late...
They all know full well what happens...
...to those who upset my plans...
They think they can
take their sweet time...
If they've already forgotten that fact...
...then I'll slaughter them all!
It is Klahadore from the mansion!
Why is he walking toward the shore,
this early in the morning?!
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
--Is this the place?!
--Damn you, Nami!
How dare you leave me down there?!
Crap! Zoro's really mad!
Get ready to pay, Nami!
I know! Get sleepy at the
count of "one, two, Jango"!
You wish!
Hey, Luffy! Quit sleeping, you!
--Look at that guy's hand!
--Don't avoid the issue!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Terrifying Duo!
Meowban Brothers vs. Zoro"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!