A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
"North Block"
"West Block" "South Block" "East Block"
The feelings of those who are in anguish
are crushed by a dry cloud of sand.
There are those who seek hope,
and those who cling to hope.
Their feelings cross each other,
uncertain what to do,
marking an era of history ending in sadness.
Crocodile tries to get information
on where the Poneglyph is
and announces that a cannonball
will be shot into the Palace Square.
Will this be the end of Alabasta?
Or will there be real peace?
The sandglass of fate starts
the final countdown once again.
"The Battle Is Over!
Koza Raises The White Flag"
Out of our way!
Out of our way! Out of our way!
Oh, that's...!
Please wait, Chaka-sama!
Hmm...? Who are they?
You guys...
Kicking Claw Force!
"Alabasta Kingdom Elite Guard Unit
Kicking Claw Force"
Don't do it!
Stay away from this man!
They broke the door!
It's the Kicking Claw Force!
--Just as you'd expect from the elite troops!
--Please save His Majesty and Vivi-sama!
Your Majesty! Defending you
to the death is our mission!
We can't just stay away from him...
When dealing with one of
the Seven Warlords of the Sea...
...we have to do whatever
it takes, even if it's unfair.
All four of us...
...will fight together...
...to set things right.
It seems that you are very popular...
I'll spare you, so go home.
--No can do.
--Hm?
There's a reason that we can't withdraw.
A reason?
If you really are the ringleader
of this whole rebellion...
Those bruises...!
Don't tell me you guys...!
Shall I...?
No, don't bother. They're worms.
They didn't...
Chaka! Something is wrong with them!
In order to boost their
power temporarily... they...
...they drank the water that
shortens their lives... the fatal fuel...
They only have a few minutes left to live...
They can't be saved...
Oh, no...
I thought as much...
Challenging me at the cost
of your own lives...?
Chaka-sama... Please forgive us
for doing this without consulting you.
However, we have to make him
realize... this country's pain...
You... idiots...
We have to make him...
realize this country's...
...anger!
That's not smart...
You should value your life.
Well, I guess it's too late, huh?
If you're gonna die anyway, I don't
even have to kill you myself, right?
So you don't even bother fighting...?!
Chaka... sama...
This is the very definition of stupidity.
You wicked fiend...!
You bastard!
Chaka!
Chaka! Stop it!
Don't follow them to their deaths!
I see... A Zoan type...
Dog Dog Fruit, Model Jackal!
Howling Fangs!
So you're the type...
who'd die for others, too?
"Alubarna - North Block
In front of the Mehdi Assembly Hall"
Dammit! I bled too much...
I guess I'm lucky that
the wounds aren't deep...
But it does... hit me hard...
I wonder how the others are...
No one'd better be dead...
I wanna know what's going on...
What?! I have to pair with Lashes?!
He's a camel, for god's sake!
Don't underestimate how weak I am!
It was because you were unlucky
in the raffle! Just give up!
All right, then! Then promise me one thing.
When we're in a pinch...!
Make sure you save us, please!
Dummy. I only save ladies.
Usopp...
Hey, Usopp. Why're you crying?
Who're you saying is crying?! Crying?!
The one who says someone's
crying is actually crying!
Uh, that makes no sense.
But...
That mole hag said... that Luffy's dead, so...
I... I wonder if it's true...
You guys believe that?
Of course not! Are you stupid or what?!
Me neither! I don't believe it at all!
All right already! Then what we have
to do now is get to the palace ASAP.
Stow your snot away until the
rumbling of this battle stops.
Don't swallow it!
Everyone... thank you...
It's too early to thank us.
He's right. Besides, if you
wanna thank pirates...
...you have to let us see some goods...
Just what are you trying to
leach out of this country?!
Is Nami okay...? Did she get away okay...?
"Alubarna - North Block
Behind the Mehdi Assembly Hall"
Ahh... They finally came off...
So this is what he meant by
a powerful one-shot attack...
The wave of rebels is already
right around the corner...
...though the situation has changed....
In any case, I should head to the palace...
What's going on with Vivi...?
The battle seems to have started...
Oh yeah, Vivi-chan. Just remember this.
After a battle... that guy eats tons...
Yes...
We'll be waiting for you in Alubarna, okay?!
Yeah!
Now, this will be the crucial point.
Don't goof things up!
Let's go! See you at the Alubarna Palace!
Chaka!
Being weak... is a crime...
Vivi!
"Palace Square
25 minutes to the explosion time"
K... Koza!
You... I see, you came through
the shortcut you used to use...
Is something wrong with my eyes...?
I came to persuade the Royal Army, but...
Chaka...
The king is... about to be
killed by the country's hero...
It's hard to believe what I'm seeing...!
This has become interesting!
You're in the middle of the battle right now,
and yet both sides' leaders
are facing each other here...
This war is now a fight to the death
between lizards whose heads are broken off.
Looks like you're confused.
Well, that's just a natural reaction...
...but it's simple.
Just imagine the worst possible scenario.
Don't hold suspicion, Koza.
Do you like this country?
Yeah! I was born here!
I'm the same way!
Koza, listen...
Vivi! Who took the rain
away from this country?!
Everything was...
It was me, Koza.
Everything you thought
was the king's doing
was a "trap" by my company.
Over the past two years, you guys
played right into our hands...
...when the royal family and army
were desperately chasing our shadows.
You probably could've died happy
if you didn't know this fact...
Don't listen to him, Koza!
King...
There's still things you can do!
Save as many citizens as you can!
Within less than half an hour...
the Palace Square will be blown up!
What?!
So you're still alive...
Hurry!
No!
Vivi...!
Hey! Move, Vivi! What're you doing?!
The Square will become a battlefield.
If it really gets blown up...
I won't... I won't let it become a battlefield!
You're still panicking!
What do you think will happen
if they realize now that
the Square'll be blown up?!
It won't just be a panic!
Once that happens, the war will
no longer stop! No one will be saved!
Isn't that right?
Well, well... what a clever judgment...
What we should do was
decided from the beginning...!
Which is to stop this plotted rebellion!
And you're the only one who can do it!
Vivi...
And you think I'll just sit back and watch?
Chaka!
I am... the Jackal, Alabasta's guardian deity!
The one who destroys the
enemies of the royal family!
As long as I still live, I fight!
That's what you call "stupidity."
Do as you want, both of you!
I can probably hold him back
at least for a few more minutes!
Okay!
Chaka...!
I guess the leader of
Sand Sand Clan isn't all that strong.
Now, what's the matter?
Ouch!
What's with you?! You're childish!
Take it easy on me!
You're a pain in the neck.
You're the one who asked me to train you.
Report from Guard Unit 2 to Headquarters!
Report from Unit 2 to Headquarters!
Line 4... has been broken through!
The rebel army is currently
passing through the Central Plaza
and heading to the North Block!
They'll reach the palace!
Raise the white flag to surrender!
Surrender right now...! Royal Army!
Vivi-sama! What's she saying?!
Surrender?!
If we do such a thing, what's
gonna happen to this country?!
Hey, look! That's...!
It's Koza! Why is the rebel army's leader here?
Listen to Vivi! We no longer
desire victory, or to fight!
I want you to stop this battle!
What?! What's going on?
I will let the rebel army know...
that this battle was pointless...
...that there's no longer
a reason for us to fight!
In order not to shed any more
pointless blood, wave the white flag!
Please!
The king's head is close at hand!
Ahh! We can now see the clock tower!
We're approaching the Palace Square!
Prepare to attack!
H-Hold it!
White flags?! The Royal Army is
waving white flags to surrender!
Koza-san!
I-It's Koza-san!
What is Koza-san doing here...?
Koza-san... What is Koza-san
doing here...? Why...?
The battle is over!
Everyone! Subdue your anger
and drop your weapon!
The Royal Army no longer
has the will to fight!
Please stop...!
Is that true...? Koza-san...?!
Yeah... the battle is now...
Koza!
Which direction should I run towards
to see a more wonderful tomorrow?
I took the helm and opened the
miraculous map that I stored in my heart
I aimed for the sky and sought out
my dreams, though at times I got lost
It wasn't a dream; when I met you,
I discovered the wonderful person in me
With just a bit of courage,
I gained something grand
Now's the time for my "wish"
to become my "pledge"
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
Let's sketch out the tale of the future
I'll put all my feelings
in a brand new wind now
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
A never-ending journey to be together
I'll chase after you
wherever you go, Shining ray
Wake up, Princess. You can't save the country.
My voice no longer reaches anyone...
If nothing is done, the country will...
Don't worry! Your voice is heard by us.
Luffy-san!
I'm gonna put an end... to all this!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Where Vivi's Voice Gets Heard!
The Hero Descends!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!