A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
What?! A cannonball will be shot
into the Square in ten minutes?!
Who are they?
How is it from the sky, Pell?!
I searched every corner of the rooftops
of the buildings near the Square,
Let me tell you something...
That's right. The attack is scheduled at 4:30.
Kicking Claw Force!
4:30?!
but I saw no preparations
for the cannon anywhere.
You can't save this country.
We found you, Princess Vivi!
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
Then... it might be from
somewhere inside a building...
Goodbye, Princess...
I wonder how far I'll be
promoted if I kill you...
Those bruises...!
--I'll search all of them!
--Okay!
They drank the water that
shortens their lives... the fatal fuel...
--I'll go on ahead!
--On ahead!
Crocodile!!
I don't feel any anger against you...
You know why, Nico Robin?
They only have a few minutes left to live...
Luffy-san!
Ten more minutes...!
This is really the last chance!
Straw Hat...!
How silly... We were a team for four years.
The next ten minutes...
will decide... this country's fate...!
I knew you'd pull something like this.
You were skewered...
buried alive... and dried up...
Luffy's alive!
If you're gonna die anyway, I don't
even have to kill you myself, right?
Water?!
I'm gonna put an end... to all this!
If you get wet, a knife
can stick in you, right?!
Gum-Gum... Bazooka!
Even you, who stood back up after all that...
He dodged it! Where'd he...
...won't be able to survive this.
We don't have the slightest
intention of giving way to you!
Game over... The poison will
pass into your system soon.
You wicked fiend...!
Don't get in my way! Treinta Fleurs!
You don't understand anything!
I'll forgive you for everything, Nico Robin...
You can't turn into sand
once you touch water.
Strangle!
This is the very definition of stupidity.
Hurry! Hurry!
Sergeant Major! This woman... is Nico Robin!
You take rain away because
you're afraid of water, right?
What's going on?! The Navy helped us!
She's got a bounty and was talked
about worldwide 20 years ago!
Howling Fangs!
...because I've never... trusted
anyone... from the beginning.
Did you find the cannoneer?!
We haven't confirmed it yet,
but there's no mistake!
So you're the type...
who'd die for your country, too?
Now I can beat you up.
I must've looked at it many times,
but it was my blind spot.
My right hand dries out everything...
That's right... That place can...
The cannoneer is over there without a doubt!
Our fight starts now.
Special Attack... Red Serpent Star!
H-Hold it!
Nami-san! Vivi-chan!
"Sand Gator and Water Luffy!
The Second Round of the Duel"
Koza-san!
Why are you up there?!
Ground Death!
The battle is over!
Hey! I looked all over for you guys!
Everyone! Subdue your anger
and drop your weapon!
"The Nightmare Draws Near! This is
the Sand Sand Clan's Secret Base"
Zoro! You too?!
The Royal Army no longer
has the will to fight!
What're you doing there?!
Ribbit... ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit...
"That Looks Gator-ish!
Luffy, Run to the Royal Tomb!"
Is that true...? Koza-san...?!
Yeah... the battle is now...
Now, get up! Crocodile!
Crocodile!!
That was close!
His right hand is a problem...
Get up! Gator man!
"Magnificent Wings! My Name is Pell,
Guardian Deity of the Country"
Where are you?!
The lawn has turned into desert!
Koza!
What's with this place?
Where'd he go?
Baroque Works?!
You made me waste my energy...
It's falling apart!
We don't know. Where's the proof
that such a company exists?
We're ordinary citizens
of Alabasta, Mr. Marine.
"Where Vivi's Voice Gets Heard!
The Hero Descends!"
In the confusion of the rebellion,
are you trying to harm good citizens?
You missed...
Cro... co...
You...
Sergeant Major Tashigi!
What're you hesitating for?!
There's no mistake!
...lose again...
Koza!
The cannoneer must be in there!
I finally figured it out!
What?!
We're gonna make an awesome city
and make this kingdom even lusher!
Straw Hat Luffy... This is a good way to die...
If you wait until you have proof,
you can't prevent anything!
A cannonball will be shot
into the Square in ten minutes?!
Is he really in such a place, Vivi?!
That's right. The attack is scheduled at 4:30.
Discern the enemy with your own eyes!
--4:30?!
--What?
Yes ma'am! Our apologies!
If this dust devil is part of the plan...
For sure!
Within six minutes or so, this yard will
be blown up along with the Square.
At 4:30... We're running out of time...
...it should be a place where
they can still hit the target...
Sorry, but I'm in a hurry...
You just relax here and celebrate the
birth of a new king of the sand country.
The clock is...
Once it's shot, no one within
a 5 km diameter will survive.
And it also has to be an open space
where a large cannon can fit
D... Don't fight... Rebel... Army...
and yet can't be seen from the sky.
That's what Crocodile said!
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit...
Hey, listen, Mr. 7.
Within a 5 km diameter... Then...
Well...
Look! This place is
unexpectedly large, isn't it?
Both the Royal Army and the Rebel
Army will be completely destroyed!
I think this is quite an important mission.
--Koza-san!
Why don't we make this
place our secret base?
I should get going, too...
That's right, Miss Father's Day.
Yeah!
He said it's in the mortuary
temple to the west of here...
There's nowhere else I can think of!
That damn gator!
Koza-san!
I think perhaps we may be given
an incredible status. Ribbit, ribbit.
Wh-What the hell will we do?
How dare you shoot Koza-san?!
Okay! Hold on! Everyone's headed here.
So we'll leave a message...
Find the cannoneer.
What?
Get them!
We'll stop the attack!
I'm gonna go on ahead, Usopp-san!
Find the cannoneer?
What?! W-Wait, Vivi! W-Wait!
I hope that's the plan. I hope so.
I hope so, Miss Father's Day.
So how do we find him?!
In ten minutes?!
--Hurry!
--Ah, okay.
Baroque Works!
We don't have time to think, right?!
All right! The princess! We found her!
But a 5 km diameter means this guy's
aiming at least 2.5 km from here, right?!
After all, our plan is to shoot
a cannonball into the crowd
using such a big cannon! So I hope so!
Ahh! That was close! I thought I was a goner!
She led us right to her!
No, that's not true! The cannoneer
is probably near this Square!
You...! Why'd you shoot Koza?!
There're still some members
of Baroque Works...!
Urk! We signaled the enemy, too!
That bastard... He's gone now...
What?! Why?! If that's the case,
the cannoneer will also be blown up...
Ribbit! It's almost time, Mr. 7!
That's Usopp's signal.
I saw him flying that way!
But why is the palace that far?
So that's the kind of man Crocodile is...
Preparations to fire complete!
Rebel Army... L-Listen to me...
I won't let him get away! That gator!
He doesn't care if his own men die?!
Good, it's close!
"West of the palace -- The mortuary temple
(royal tomb)"
I wonder if they found the cannoneer.
Ahhh! What's going on?!
A sandstorm suddenly...!
They must have! Hurry!
What a crafty bastard...
Let's go, already!
Rebel Army...!
Usopp...! Noise...!
So this is the royal tomb... where the
bodies of generations of kings sleep...
They started shooting at us!
Those bastards...!
What is it that... you say I don't understand?
Yipe!
So this is... this is the...
We found you, Princess Vivi!
Where's the Poneglyph?
Now! Let's go, Vivi!
I wonder how far I'll be
promoted if I kill you...
Okay!
What's with this dust devil?!
Th-They ran away!
Stop!
We can't see ahead!
Billions!
Ten minutes minus how many seconds?!
Hey, we're wasting time by talking.
Hidden stairs!
Dammit! Those bastards...!
Two seconds!
The Poneglyph is deep underground.
--I'll go on ahead!
Gum-Gum... Gatling!
Normally, people aren't even
aware of Poneglyphs' existence...
Don't shoot carelessly!
1.5 seconds!
What's going on?!
Humph! There's nothing to wonder about,
Don't slow down, idiot!
What's happening behind the scenes is deep.
Same to you!
Even if countries belong
to the World Government,
since Baroque Works members
infiltrated both armies.
Let's split up! At any rate, we gotta
get out of this dust devil first!
it doesn't mean their kings know everything.
Don't you get it? You'll die soon,
You aren't to be blamed...
It took so long... to make it this far...
Ten more minutes...!
...since you probably didn't know
there was someone in this world
due to the poison that entered that wound.
Okay, hurry up! Let's go!
No!
Yeah!
Hey! Hang in there!
who can decipher them.
But the end... has finally come...
You can read Poneglyphs?
This is really... the last chance!
Your body is probably numbing by now.
Yes... That's why Crocodile and I teamed up.
This land is mine!
The next ten minutes...
will decide... this country's fate...!
Whether you win or lose, you'll be
buried under this sacred temple anyway.
Because of that, he can't kill me.
Surrender, my ass...!
It's likely that the Poneglyph in
this country tells where Pluton is.
Launching a surprise attack
by raising the white flag...!
15 seconds until the attack!
Is this how the Royal Army works?!
Isn't that right?
I don't know...
How dare they play dirty?!
Alabasta's royal family has been
obligated for generations to protect it.
The target is the center of
the Square. Ribbit, ribbit.
You think... you can defeat me...?
That's all it is to us.
Yeah... since you no
longer can turn into sand.
Ignite!
Protect?! Don't make me laugh!
Please! Stop, everyone! Don't fight!
Hey, Nami! What the hell
are you trying to do?!
I'm indeed impressed
that you figured it out...
...especially when you were close to dying...
We really don't have time!
If we fail, we'll die! Hey!
Look! I'm here!
But that is still nowhere near enough
to put you on the same level as me.
What an impressive-looking place...
I know that! Just stand there quietly!
I'm calculating right now!
S... Stop... Rebel Army... This battle is...
It's behind the doors in the back.
That's the level of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea.
Quietly? I don't understand
the point of this setup!
So what if you're one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea?
What the hell are you gonna do?!
Then, I'm one of the...
You'll know once I do it!
Indeed...
...Eight Warlords of the Sea!
Ready?!
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit...
Hey, listen, Mr. 7!
You...!
This is a rare occasion!
I wanna do a countdown!
I've cornered you, gator!
Who on earth is that man?
Are you okay?!
Is that your plan? That's good!
That's good! Sounds interesting!
He's a pirate. Haven't you heard?
Why are you alive?
Counterattack! Royal Army!
No matter how many times I kill you,
why do you stand up to me?!
Looks like the princess
escaped death once again.
The weather forecast is "typhoon"!
13 seconds until the attack!
Well?! Straw Hat!
Then he is the one... who brought
Vivi back to this country...
How... did he survive and come here...?
Cyclone... Tempo!
Who on earth is he...?
H... Hey! Cyclone Tempo is just a
boomerang game for after parties.
I won't... let you go...
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
How many times do you have to
come at me before you're satisfied?
It's no good if I dodge it.
Make for the clock tower!
Straw Hat...
Whether it's wet or not...
...my hand can absorb any kind of fluid.
Just how many times
do you want to be killed?
You still haven't returned...
what you took away...
Sh-Shoot! I forgot he still had that power!
What I took away...?
Stop...! Stop already...
Is it money...? Fame...?
What the heck...? They're coming up!
Nico Robin...
Chopper! Jump to where Sanji-kun is!
Trust...?
Please... Stop... Stop...
Lives...?
What?!
Don't tell me... Is she saying...
Rain...?!
I'll... capture you...
You told me, didn't you...?
...the plan is to jump
all the way up like this?!
Sanji-kun! You know the rest, right?!
We don't have time!
What do you want me to return?
Depending on how Devil Fruit powers
are used, you can become stronger.
You fought well, young lady...
There're so many things that I took away.
I think I get the gist of it, but...
But... your voice will no longer reach them...
Oh, heck! I just have to do it!
The country!
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
The country? You say funny things...
Sounds like we don't have time to think!
I'm counting on you, Tony-kun!
I'm just about to take this country...
by becoming its king.
Okay! Hang on tight, Vivi!
I see... that's what we're doing.
Shotgun!
Impertinent brat! Desert Spada!
Chopper! Get on my right leg!
Croco... dile...
When we got to this island,
it was already gone.
Got it!
That thing again?!
Looks like you were taken
down by that woman...
11!
So this is it...
Her country was gone...!
I never thought that you'd
follow me to this town... Navy...
There! They're coming, Zoro!
Okay! Good job!
That was close...
Where's your boss? Did that
smoke bastard run away?
Run, Vivi!
Gum-Gum...!
So all I have to do is throw them
to the top of that tower, right?!
I'm going to persuade the Rebel Army
Get away from that man!
You keep using the same technique...
Are you really trying to win?
10!
because I want no more shedding of blood!
Zoro!
Okay! Leave it to me!
Losers can't speak about justice.
We're in that kind of sea.
Yeah!
Totally!
Swords?!
Up until just recently, it was
a thriving city full of greenery!
You dummy! Don't be scared!
I'm using the back of the blade!
Go back to your base and just devote
your time to talking about justice.
--Get a good foothold!
--Ah, okay!
My goal was this from the start!
Time to get soaking wet!
No.
9!
Be careful, Vivi! There're weirdoes up there.
That's obviously what
you'd wanna do! Sables!
Please, Vivi-chan! Stop those fools!
Yes. They're familiar faces.
Hm?!
This dust devil... is your doing, isn't it?
No!
Miss Wednesday!
If this is really her country...
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit. I know that
she's a traitor to our company!
Not yet...
What's wrong... with not
wanting people to die?!
If I stop the attack that's
scheduled to happen in 15 minutes,
Crocodile!
They've noticed!
Barrel! Barrel!
What?!
Just one look at this kingdom
and even I can tell...
Wait a sec! We're in the air!
If they shoot at us...!
I can still reduce the number of casualties!
...what most needs to be done!
I'm certain that what you're
after isn't in this country.
You're struggling desperately,
Straw Hat Luffy...
If we do this, the rebellion will stop.
If we do that, the rebellion will stop.
You can't do anything
without that barrel after all.
You small fry...!
As if putting your single life
on the line is enough!
Isn't that right?! To achieve
someone else's goal...
What the heck are you doing?!
This isn't any different from our first fight.
What am I doing?! I'm trying to
put myself in Crocodile's shoes!
Wake up, Princess.
What's the point in dying over that?!
I don't have...!
Like, if I were him, where
would I shoot a cannon from...?
If you ditch a friend or two,
you can stay out of troubles.
I can't stand how annoying
your idealistic theory is.
I don't have anything else
that I can put on the line...
You're right.
Forget it! Just look for the cannoneer!
We've got less than five minutes!
It's no different like this.
Five more minutes! A million lives
will be blown up in five minutes!
You guys are total idiots.
At least try putting all of our
lives on the line together!
If you wanna talk about ideals,
you have to be able to make them real.
We gotta hurry...! We gotta
hurry up and find the cannoneer!
That's why I said you don't understand.
Chopper! Can't you find
the guy by using your nose?
Aren't we friends?!
I can't. The smell of
gunpowder is all over the town!
You're not qualified to do that!
Vivi...
Then, how about this?!
Then... listen.
Now, I'm not the same as I was.
Find the smell of "a cannoneer who may
be aiming at the center of the Square."
She tells others not to die,
If this is really her country...
she should be... smiling more!
I don't care if it's annoying.
Are you serious?
but she's the first to lay down
her own life to save others.
What kind of smell is that?
How should I know?! Try your best!
I won't give up on my ideals, either!
What?!
Water Luffy!
If we don't help her, she'll die.
You guys will kill her.
Ahh! This is bad! Water's leaking!
Even if you talk cool, when you don't
have water with you, what can you...
You could never understand!
I'm the princess of this country.
You're so dense.
A cannonball that can
blow up a 5 km diameter...
Is this brat... serious...?
That's why I'm telling you that
you can just ditch that burden...!
Wait. Then it must be big...
I won't give in to someone like you!
Bloated with water...
If it is to be shot from a cannon,
it won't travel very far...
We don't want her to die!
That's how friends are!
I guess I shouldn't drink this much water...
Then it should be closer
to the Square after all?!
You really have no charm...
That's why we won't quit fighting as long
as she doesn't give up on her country!
Ahh! I don't have time to go around!
I won't give up... I will...
Doesn't he get what's happening right now?
I'll take a shortcut!
This can't be... Kicking me without water...
How is it from the sky, Pell?!
I searched every corner of the rooftops
of the buildings near the Square,
Even if you guys end up dying?
I will... save this country...!
but I saw no preparations
for the cannon anywhere.
If we die, we die.
Then... it might be from
somewhere inside a building...
If only you hadn't come to this country...
Alabasta would've remained peaceful!
Stop messing around, you damn brat!
--I'll search all of them!
--Okay!
Adjust! Ribbit-Ribbit Gun!
This is an unexpected catch!
Isn't it just heartrending?
Vivi!
Adjust! Yellow Gun!
Love for the kingdom will be
what destroys the kingdom.
This is good! This is good!
They're perfect prey!
You bastards! How dare you
point guns at Vivi-chan?!
Dammit!
This is bad! They're a sniper pair!
Who's messing around?!
Chopper! I'll shoot you guys up anyway!
15 minutes until the Square is blown up.
Crocodile!
Wai...
I'll change the direction so
you do something after that!
My body...
Straw Hat!
More and more of the auxiliary
rebel forces will gather here...
Where did... the gator go?
I'm always serious! Gum-Gum...!
What?! Me?!
Seven seconds left!
Do something!
One after another, all without
realizing their own fate...
We've been warned that at 4:30 pm,
an explosion will happen
...Bazooka!!
Ready?! I'm gonna
shoot you up! Chopper! Vivi!
in the Palace Square where the
rebellion is going on right now!
Please stop it somehow!
A million lives are at stake!
Okay!
Could it be... you're using...
--Ready...!
--Smash!
Go!
...your blood...?!
Hey, listen. Our bullets are...
Losers can't speak about justice.
We're in that kind of sea.
Sand can be hardened
by blood, too, can't it?
Had you let the Royal Army know earlier
about the explosion on the Square...
...planned to crash and explode.
Go back to your base and just devote
your time to talking about justice.
...even if there had been a panic,
Zoro!
you could've saved thousands
or tens of thousands of lives...
Tell me! Where's the gator?!
That idiot! He took a direct hit...!
From Rainbase... to the palace...
and to the underground mortuary temple...
Stop! Please stop it, Crocodile!
How's that... sand gator?!
Ready, Vivi?!
With your all might, please, Tony-kun!
I'll reward you for your
persistence in challenging me,
In the end, your optimistic
ideas about saving everything
"5 seconds until attack"
even after living through hell twice...
Ribbit, ribbit. It's no use...
...dodging!
have resulted in the deaths of
all the citizens you love so much.
You bastard...!
Smash!
Who's that?!
Huh?!
...as a pirate...
"4 seconds until attack"
He went in the direction
of the mortuary temple.
It seems that you want to
beat me up no matter what.
From start to finish, everyone
in this country... amused me.
That way?! Thanks!
Where's Miss Wednesday?!
And I'll also admit that you're
an annoying enemy to me.
What happened?!
I can't believe it...! He beat the Crocodile...
Peacock... String...!
It came off! What the...
Who on earth is that boy...?
She's up there!
It's a poisonous hook.
"3 seconds until attack"
I see...
As a competent enough pirate,
you seem to understand
This is no time to be
impressed, right, Mr. Cobra?
Go!
What justice...
You did a fine job of spying on our
company for the past two years...
that a duel between pirates
is always a fight for survival,
Now, you show me the way...
to where the Poneglyph is!
and that there's no such
thing as "playing dirty."
It's me! Don't you recognize me?
I suppose I can't blame you.
I did lose some weight...
What in the world are you
going to do... by looking at it?
But when all is said and done,
you guys couldn't stop anything.
The hell with Navy Headquarters...
When the explosion happens up there,
this place will probably
collapse in one breath as well.
Don't ask pointless questions.
Even if you talk big,
your body doesn't respond, huh?
Stopping the rebellion...
Saving the kingdom...
All you have to do is show me the way...
This is the last time.
Let's settle it once and for all!
Your worthless ideals... only created
more unnecessary victims...
You look pathetic, Straw Hat.
Oh? I can't move well...
I wonder if your luck is running out...
There isn't much time left.
Slasher!
Let me tell you something...
This is strange... when I ate meat...
You can't save this country.
What's wrong...?
These are such small wounds...
Ribbit, ribbit! Sorry!
Go already, Nico Robin...
unless you wanna be dried up, too.
I wonder if I'm a little tired...
You missed!
Goodbye, Princess...
The smoke was in that direction, right?
"2 seconds until attack"
I'm losing... my patience...
No, was it this way?
Run Back!
What?! Marines?!
Nico Robin?!
Look! It's Roronoa Zoro!
All right!!
Dammit! I didn't realize that
the Navy showed up in this town...
Yes, as you wish.
When I don't have time...
I guess I can't help it.
I'll settle this in three seconds.
"1 second until attack"
You...! Why are you in a place like this?!
Listen up, Straw Hat.
What the heck are you doing?!
Every rock on the ground can be destroyed.
That's what I'd say!
Roronoa Zoro!
We knew you weren't good with directions,
but this is worse than we expected!
Go back! If you go north at the last
corner, you can get to the Square!
Did it tell you what you wanted to know?
Vivi!
Hey, you brats!
The grass is withering away!
Go back and turn right! Not this way!
You came in from the
shortcut again, didn't you?!
Are you stupid?!
Stupid?!
Ahh! It's the gatekeeper!
--Hurry up!
--Go!
--Ahhh!
--Run!
Wh-What?! What's going on?!
Chaka-sama. Pell-sama.
Please say something to those brats.
Ground Secco!
It can't be...
Hm...? Oh, I see... Hidden stairs...
Crocodile!!
Hm...?
Yeah...
What the heck...?!
Run! Run, Vivi!
Vivi-sama. Going out?
Usopp-san! I can't...
I'm falling...!
Yep! To our secret base!
Luffy-san!
Four... four more minutes...!
Wait! Hold it!
Okay. Have fun.
That was close!
That bastard! Water-Water Pistol!
Straw Hat...!
Where did Vivi-sama go?
Hm? I can't tell you. It's a secret.
What?! He swallowed it all with his hand!
The clock tower, huh?
You thought you killed
my powers, Water Luffy...?
Th-Tha... Thank...
But that's a mistake.
We'll assist you!
Please stop the explosion
of the Square. Now, hurry!
The true power of sand is drying. Look!
Aren't there any others?!
Is this all this country is hiding?
Thank you! Hurry, Usopp-san!
Ah... Yeah!
You're not satisfied? I kept my promise.
My right hand dries out
everything... with no limit...
All units! Continue to assist them...!
With all your strength!
Yes...
Yes, ma'am!
Me, go to Alubarna?
Just as you'd expect from a national secret...
We're chasing after the
Straw Hat pirates, right? Or...
No matter how desperately you search,
it can't be found unless you know where it is.
You decide what to do when you're there.
Was it stopped...?
So this is the Poneglyph, huh, Nico Robin?
You just follow your sense of justice.
Whatever happens, I'll accept responsibility.
That didn't take long...
It's strange, or how should I put it...
Were you able to decipher it?
Just in time.
Yes.
Good. Now, read...
the so-called Poneglyph...
Stones... and even stone
statues are becoming sand...
Luffy-san...! Pell...!
Kahira conquered Alabasta...
in Sky Ephemeris Year 239.
There isn't much time left
before the Square is blown up.
Hurry! Hurry!
The ground... is dying...!
In 260, Taymer ruled the Bitain Dynasty.
We wasted quite a bit of time!
Ah! My sandals dried up, too!
I don't know why they did,
but if the Navy hadn't helped,
it would've been worse!
Everything that's connected
to this hand... Dry up!
Everyone... is already down...
In 306, the Taff Cathedral
was completed in Erumalu.
In 325, the hero Mamdin of Oltia...
Ground Death!
My voice... no longer reaches anyone...
Hey, hey... Wait! Wait!
Is that what we wanna know?!
Oh... You're alive...
Wh... What happened to the attack?
Who cares about the history of this country?
At this rate, the country will...
Idiot! Don't look aside!
Hm?
Just tell me the location of the world's
most disastrous "military power"
If the attack isn't stopped,
the casualties will be a lot worse!
--What fell on me?
--Ouch!
that is sleeping in this country!
Don't worry.
Right!
Where is the Pluton?!
The attack can't be stopped by praying!
It's not written here.
--What?!
--History is the only thing written here.
Where is he?! Where's the cannoneer?!
In two minutes, are we gonna
be winners or dead bodies...?
What's the matter?
Is that true?!
We've only got eight minutes.
Pluton... I didn't see that
word mentioned even once.
They say something's wrong up there.
Your voice is heard by us.
If we have eight minutes, we can find him!
Vivi isn't showing her face...
We still have a minute and a half!
--Yes!
--You've got us all!
We'll stop the attack
no matter what happens!
Yes!
There's a problem! Everyone!
Or the lives of a million
people will be destroyed!
Yes...!
Vivi!
The cannonball has a timing device!
If we don't do something, it'll explode!
There they are! Vivi! Usopp!
Again, I'm saying that my injuries
are obviously worse than yours.
Nami-san! Tony-kun!
A cannonball that can
blow up a 5 km diameter...
What?!
What's going on?! The Navy helped us!
It has to be a big cannon!
Could it be inside a building?!
Well... I see... That's unfortunate...
You're a man, so stop whining!
My leg is injured! I can't stand!
Did you find the cannoneer?!
How despicable!
We haven't confirmed it yet,
but there's no mistake!
Ahh, I'm fainting. This is bad.
You've been an excellent
partner to me, but...
You're lying!
I'd like you to at least say I was
thoroughly prepared, Mr. Cobra.
Dammit!
I must've looked at it many times,
but it was my blind spot.
...I think I'll kill you here.
The cannoneer is over there without a doubt!
Wha...?!
But wait...! If Alubarna is completely
destroyed in eight minutes...
Operations should be carried out
considering unforeseen circumstances.
The agreement that we made four
years ago has been achieved here.
What?
...does that mean that we're all
going to die in eight minutes as well?
Be careful... Luffy-kun.
This is what you said then.
Even if something happens to the cannoneer,
We don't have time to be scared!
If I take you to where the Poneglyph is,
I ate lots of meat, so I got tons of blood!
the cannonball will explode on its own.
What?!
you'd turn over the information
on the weapon to me...
Look! That's it!
The clock tower...
Well, the time lag is just a few dozen seconds.
I see! From that place, he can
get a good shot at the Square!
Tsk!
Your work in Baroque Works
these past four years was excellent
C-Can we go up there... in eight minutes?
both in terms of brainpower
and command ability.
I wanted it to be shot into
the center of the Square...
If only Pell would get here,
we could stop the attack.
H-Hey!
That's enough for me... to say
that you were a useful woman.
...but it should still do more than
enough damage from there.
Pell...!
Ahh, dammit!
I won't...
...lose again!
But... you broke your word at the end!
You...! Are you from the Rebel Army?!
We don't have time.
How did he get out of that
quicksand with those injuries...?
If we do this, the rebellion will stop.
If we do that, the rebellion will stop.
The Poneglyph in this country doesn't
even show a clue on the Pluton.
I don't have time to waste on you.
If I'm not mistaken, the smoke
rose around here, but...
Go to sleep.
Or... is it that you weren't
planning to tell me from the start,
I can't stand how annoying
your idealistic theory is.
Luffy's alive!
That's it! That's it!
even if you found out?
Tony-kun!
Wh-Wh-What?! Luffy!
Let me tell you something...
Vivi's here, too!
This isn't it! It's got moss on it!
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit... Hey, listen.
See?! See?! I told you! I knew it!
However... I don't feel
any anger against you...
I just shot down a big bird
using this ribbit-ribbit gun.
Really?
You can't save this country.
You know why, Nico Robin?
You don't look like someone who knew!
How silly... We were a team for four years.
Usopp-san! Sanji-san!
Dammit! What the hell...! The attack
was stopped, but the cannonball...
I knew you'd pull something like this.
My blunder...
Ahhh! What the hell, Vivi-chan?!
You're hurt so bad!
Water?!
...has a timing device?!
I don't see him... anywhere...!
There's no sign of a cannoneer!
If you get wet, a knife
can stick in you, right?!
Usopp!
If it has power to destroy a 5 km diameter,
Nami-san... Mr. Bushido...
the Square and the town
won't survive after all!
He dodged it! Where'd he...
Why...? Why?!
Everyone's alive...
What's gonna happen?!
Who asked you to create a prop for parties?!
Seven minutes left...
Does this mean that it was
impossible from the start
I'll forgive you for everything, Nico Robin...
to stop the explosion in the Square?
Hey, you're standing!
Nami-san!
I'll stop it... I'll...
He made us come this far to look for it...!
It... It did have a powerful attack, didn't it?
He even announced the attack...!
I'll deal with you later!
...because I've never... trusted
anyone... from the beginning.
Just how far...
Vivi... So what's going on?
What's with this dust devil?
Nico Robin... Is that your real name?
...does he have to go to make fools of us?!
Yeah...
What if it is? It has nothing to do with you.
Hey, you jerk! Why is Nami-san
injured?! I'm gonna gut you!
Just how much does he have to mock us?!
I now know from Cobra's reaction
that Pluton really exists.
A girl whose name was known
throughout the world 20 years ago...
She's just fine, isn't she...?
Ahh... Chopper, I have a favor to ask.
I don't have to depend on the
Poneglyph. I'll find it on my own.
Why... are you here now...?
Crocodile!!
Will you bury my body in a wasteland?
Once this country becomes mine,
it's just a matter of time.
All you have to do is show me
the way to the Poneglyph...
He's already got fatal wounds!
Hm?! What's going on?! It's still too
early for the attack on the Square!
It must be you. What'd you do?!
What incredible timing you
have showing up now, Navy.
Well... nothing major...
That was...
Clear the way. We're in a hurry.
That bird guy...
This underground sacred temple is built
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
so that pulling just one small column
out will cause the entire balance
We can't! I heard everything
that's going on here in Alubarna
Sorry, guys. I lost against him once...
from a soldier on the ground.
to be disrupted and destroy the temple.
Pell!
Who do you think that person is?!
This place brings back memories...
The Sand Sand Clan's secret base...
You two... will die here with me.
So...
Well, I don't care who it is.
I hate people in the Government.
--Pell, listen! The cannonball
has a timing device
--Your unprecedented actions really gave us
As the 12th king of the Nefertari Family,
So...
--and is ready to explode at any moment!
--Your unprecedented actions really gave us
...I won't lose again!
I'll leave the rest to you!
If you don't get out of my way...
I can't give this sand kingdom
to someone like you.
lots of trouble all the time.
Go already.
We don't have the slightest
intention of giving way to you!
It's Vivi-sama! What on earth is she
doing in the ammunition bunker?!
Then I might have to kill you.
If you can't win...
Wait, Navy! Don't worry about me!
...who can?!
Hey, what happened?!
What was that explosion noise?!
We've been warned that at 4:30 pm,
a cannonball will be shot
into the Palace Square where
the rebellion is going on right now!
After we've told you so many times
not to go near the ammunition bunker...
Please stop it somehow!
I'm gonna put an end...
What...?! Seven more minutes...!
Where is it? Three minutes left...
Ah, Pell!
...to all this!
Pell-sama!
Yeah!
A million citizens' lives are at stake!
A cannon big enough to
blow up a 5 km diameter...
I wanted to make fireworks,
but it didn't work.
But...
There can't be many places
where such a thing would fit...
Then we'll save you and stop the explosion!
You see, it's the anniversary of the
day that you joined the army, so...
Everyone...
Why can't we find it when
we search this much...?
--Wait! This woman is...!
--Ready!
I still have... this many friends...
An open space where a big cannon can fit...
Don't get in my way!
What're you doing to the princess?!
Treinta Fleurs!
How many times do I have to tell you...
A stray bullet!
Strangle!
...not to come near this place?!
An open space...
Devil Fruit Powers...
You bastard!
I said I was in a hurry, didn't I?
Don't make me upset!
You! Do you know what you just did?!
Hey, no fair, Koza! You were
hiding in a place like this?!
Who in the world is he...?
Leader! No fair!
I'm gonna fire you! How dare you...?
Sergeant Major! This woman... is Nico Robin!
Wait, Igaram!
That's right... That place can...
Crocodile treated even our kingdom's
proud warriors like worms, and yet...
It's okay...
That's dangerous, you bastard! Smoke Star!
No matter how many times
you try, you can't even hit me.
There's no mistake!
As Captain Smoker asked,
I looked for her wanted poster.
It doesn't attract people's
attention and it's a big space.
What if you weren't just... injured...?
Idiot! Ahh! I'm not from the Rebel Army!
She's got a bounty and was talked
about worldwide 20 years ago!
Looks like you wanna be skewered again.
Usopp Hammer!
Usopp's Rubberband of Doom!
You were skewered...
buried alive... and dried up...
I remember the articles appearing
in newspapers around that time.
Did that teach you, you bastard!
Geez... who do they think I am?
More...! Higher! I said higher!
There was an incident where
six Navy warships were sunk.
Even you, who stood back up after all that...
Don't be surprised when I
tell you this. No, be surprised!
I am that famous Captain... U...
They said that a girl who was only
eight years old was responsible for it.
Vivi-sama! Please never tell
the king about this, okay?
...won't be able to survive this.
What? O-Oh, it's you, Vivi.
Did you find the cannoneer?!
Game over... The poison will
pass into your system soon.
The Government declared her
a first-degree risk factor,
I figured it out! It's gotta be there!
What?! Really?! Okay, then! I'll signal them!
You don't understand anything!
Because he sternly told me
not to fly with you riding on me!
and the bounty put on her head was...
believe it or not, 79 million berries!
In any case, I'll call everyone!
You're sure about it, right?
However, she suddenly
disappeared after that.
If you don't want to, that's fine.
I won't forgive you about today
Yes!
for the rest of my life.
Special Attack... Red Serpent Star!
Stop your rambling!
Are you gonna clear the way?
You're the one who said
you'd do whatever I tell you to.
Or do you all wanna die? Which is it?!
I wonder what happened...
It seems there's no point in having
many soldiers against this woman...
I don't see Pell anywhere...
Ahh?!
Gum-Gum...!
Say, Vivi. We can't go up that high
within a minute all by ourselves!
Oh?!
Who is that?!
Sergeant! Take everyone to the
Square and stop the explosion!
--Say, Pell...
--Yes?
Why do you train for battle every day?
Pell! Where are you?! Hurry!
But, Sergeant Major...!
Hurry up! There's only six minutes left!
Because I'm a guard. I do it
in order to protect this country.
In any case, we should hurry up, too!
Yes, ma'am!
I have to be strong.
We have no choice but to use the stairs!
--Where's the entrance?!
--Hey!
Who will you be fighting?
I don't know...
--Hm?!
--Nami-san! Vivi-chan!
Could he... possibly...?!
Now, let that man go!
Rather than fight, I'll protect...
...Buzzsaw!
Why are you up there?!
I said you're in my way!
Why? You left a message
under the smoke, didn't you?!
They're different?
They have different purposes.
Hmm... That's strange...
It said "clock tower."
That's why I came up here.
Boy, I slept well.
What should I do? Where's the cannoneer?
Huh...? Oh, that's right.
I feel proud from the bottom
of my heart that I was able
He's at the top! Top! Go up
from there and beat him up!
My body suddenly became
incapable of moving...
...so I decided to risk it and take
a nap since it couldn't be helped.
Hm? Hm?!
to serve you, the Nefertari Family.
Hey, I looked all over for you guys!
And now I feel fine, so...
Zoro! You too?!
What're you doing there?
Oh, yeah!
That's what I'd like to say!
Gator! I'll beat him up!
Well, Navy guys kept saying,
"go north," "go north,"
He hit Crocodile...!
so I came up here for now...
"North" and "up" are
totally different, you know!
But in any case, good job! Go up from
there and destroy the clock tower!
That hole...
That was close!
His right hand is a problem...
--No!
--What?
They can't go inside the
clock tower from where they are.
It looks gator-ish...
The lawn has turned into desert!
Other than entering from
the sky, the only way up
Well, well...
is the stairs in the back on the first floor.
Whoa... You're a model king...
Where'd he go?
But Zoro can destroy the tower wall and...
Are you trying to be buried alive,
taking me with you...
We don't know if the cannonball
can bear that kind of shock!
...for the country...?!
We have no choice but to
go up the stairs after all!
But... you can't kill me...
You made me waste my energy...
Wait, Vivi!
Hm?
I am Alabasta's guardian deity...
What?
I can change all the bedrocks
into sand and escape from here.
I've got a good idea!
You'll die in vain, Cobra.
Ribbit... ribbit, ribbit, ribbit...
It's now less than three minutes.
With the collapse of this sacred temple
and the big explosion of the Square,
Falcon!
You missed...
Get up.
everyone in my way will
be blown up in an instant!
Cro... co...
That time, the water that dropped on
your hand... the water I got in Yuba...
In that moment, this land...
will become my country.
Hey listen, Mr. 7. I know that this is
our last mission. Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit...
...taught me that you can't turn
into sand once you touch water.
You take rain away because
you're afraid of water, right?
That's the plan.
You... lose again...
According to the plan,
we have 30 seconds left.
Now I can beat you up.
Straw Hat Luffy...
What's that?!
The one who destroys
the royal family's enemies!
Our fight starts now.
Mr. 7! Miss Father's Day!
Crocodile!! Where are you?!
Which direction should I run towards
to see a more wonderful tomorrow?
I took the helm and opened the
miraculous map that I stored in my heart
I aimed for the sky and sought out
my dreams, though at times I got lost
It wasn't a dream; when I met you,
I discovered the wonderful person in me
With just a bit of courage,
I gained something grand
Now's the time for my "wish"
to become my "pledge"
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
Let's sketch out the tale of the future
I'll put all my feelings
in a brand new wind now
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
A never-ending journey to be together
I'll chase after you
wherever you go, Shining ray
This is a good way to die, Straw Hat Luffy...
Looks like more weirdoes showed up.
I've cornered you, gator!
Please shed no more blood!!
Crocodile! I'll beat you up this time!
Straw Hat... Why are you alive?
So if we take them down,
the attack will be stopped, right?
Dammit! There isn't much
time left till the attack!
--Why aren't they stopping?!
--Please stop fighting!!
Luffy! Don't lose against a guy like him!
Just how many times do you want to be killed?
Hey, Nami. What're you gonna
do by stacking us up like this?
Geez... You sure took your time getting here.
Where is this brat getting
all that strength from...?
What? Is the cannoneer really in such a place?!
You small fry...
Okay, then! I'll leave the rest to you!
Just shut up and do what I say!
What the heck are you doing?!
Yes! There's nowhere else I can think of!
Hey! Don't run away!
We're gonna look for the cannoneer!
Who the hell do you think I am?!
I'm trying to put myself in Crocodile's shoes!
We've only got 20 seconds!
Okay then! Everyone's headed here.
So we'll leave a message!
Forget it! Just look for him!
Sink or swim... But we have no choice...
I don't care who you are. I'll surpass you!
--Is he nearby?!
--There's no time left! This is the last chance!
I'm gonna go on ahead!
This is really... the last chance!
It will decide this country's fate...!
What?! Hey, Vivi! Wait! Wait for me!
We'll put it all on the line
in the time we have left!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Nightmare Draws Near!
This is the Sand Sand Clan's Secret Base"
"Sand Gator and Water Luffy!
The Second Round of the Duel"
"That Looks Gator-ish!
Luffy, Run to the Royal Tomb!"
"I Will Surpass You! Rain Falls In Alabasta!"
"Magnificent Wings! My Name is Pell,
Guardian Deity of the Country"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!