A world... Yes!
The world...
Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
Seek freedom,
And your world will stand stretched out before your eyes.
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
If the endless dream guides your spirits,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Conquer it!
Bear conviction behind your flag!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
I began my search,With a blast of water,
Heading towards a world without end
Toward a boundless,everlasting world
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
With this overflowing passion in my chest, I'll go anywhere
In search of light yet unseen
Seeking the light l've never seen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
When the summer-colored sun shakes the sall of my heart,
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
It's a sign the door to a new world has opened
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
Swaying between the waves, I can escape despair,
We head beyond the horizon
For the horize on the other side is what I aim for!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
I began my search, With a blast of water,
Heading towards a world without end
Toward a boundless, everlasting world
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
With this overflowing passion in my chest, I'll go anywhere
In search of light yet unseen
Seeking the light I've never seen
I am... I am... the man
who'll be King of the Pirates!
I'm certain that what you're
after isn't in this country.
If you want to continue adventuring with us,
"The Pirates' Banquet and
Operation Escape from Alabasta!"
I...
Isn't that right?! To achieve
someone else's goal...
That will be the last chance you'll have to jump on board.
What's the point in dying over that?!
Hey, Carue...
Oh... That compounding is amazing!
I WILL STAY HERE...
What do you want to do?
That's why I said you don't understand.
Please... stop fighting!
Unusual, I might say... Well, it's
indeed practical. It's wonderful...
Beginning is that day!
Vivi tells of her adventures!
Vivi...
What?
But if we ever meet again,
She tells others not to die,
Where on earth did you
learn those medical skills?
Will you still call me your nakama?
but she's the first to lay down
her own life to save others.
Tony-kun is a doctor from Drum.
The battle will end...
Why! Is that so? The Drum that used to
be the land of advanced medical care...
Igaram? I'm...
That's why I'm telling you that
you can just ditch that burden...!
--Ahh...!
--I see...
...going to become the Pirate Queen!
Their medicine is advanced as I thought...
We don't want her to die!
That's how friends are!
I've been a doctor for 40 years,
The rain falling right now...
but I didn't know such
techniques existed at all.
...will fall again as it used to...
--Ah...
--This is really wonderful.
Though you're so young,
I'm no match for you.
Beware her scent!
The seventh one is Nico Robin!
Vivi-sama...
...since our nightmares are... all over...
I feel proud from the bottom
of my heart that I was able
Shut up! Don't stare at me like that,
you idiot! Go away, you bastard!
to serve you, the Nefertari Family.
VIVI-SAMAAA!
"Well, have some tea and watch as much
as you like"... Can I take it that way?
Yes.
I sank one of the ships. The one belonging to the Baroque Works Agent, Bon Clay.
I think you can.
Oh, Igaram, good morning.
Well... really, you're outstanding!
What's wrong? You're sweating all over.
Shut up...
Hey, hey!
"A Farewell to Arms!
Pirates and Different Ideas of Justice"
But the other one...
Hubby, how dare you barge in here!
Come on, keep it moving.
I can only say I'm impressed.
Boy oh boy, you've got splendid skills!
Vivi-sama is dressing!
So they got away?
I am Alabasta's guardian deity... Falcon!
I was swindled by a cheap trick.
Go away! Shut up, you bastard!
Ah, that is- I mean...
Good morning.
They're pretty good at running away, huh?
Did you need something?
Ah- No...
Then get the blazes out of here, Hubby!
The nightmares are over...?
Hina-jou, watch out!
You can't be serious!
Hey! Do you have more lumber?
Honestly. Pisses me off.
There's no way what happened
was just "nightmares"!
The one who destroys...
the royal family's enemies!
Hina pissed.
I don't have enough, either!
Maybe I'm over-thinking...
What, your ineptitude?
That's right! We saw the king
attack Nanohana with our own eyes!
I've got some extra. Go ahead and use it.
Oh, thanks!
Oh, Your Majesty.
This country is sturdy...
That's right! Koza-san was
also shot by the Royal Army!
I didn't know you were there.
No. Not at all.
That's because the princess is cute.
Good morning to you.
How do you explain the Royal
Army's misconduct up until now?!
--That has something to do with it?
--It does!
Yes, good morning.
Dammit! House after house is penetrated!
Ah! So hot!
My, Terracotta-san is a frightening woman, isn't she?
The sheer power of the Ori Ori Fruit!
Ori - Cage
That's not good enough for
those who fell in this rebellion!
What's this hole? It looks as if
someone kicked and broke them.
WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN DOING!?
"Everthing that comes near me gets LOCKED UP!"
Urk!
That's right! That's right!
I don't have time to go around!
I'll take a shortcut!
"I Will Surpass You! Rain Falls In Alabasta!"
Say it!
Isn't this a little tight, Terracotta-san?
The catchphrase! Say it!
Whoa! This is terrible.
Hey, Usopp! Look!
There's something over there...
Clothing like this befits a princess of your stature!
Huh?
What the hell is this!? Iron shackles!?
The Square is already packed!
You piss me off, Smoker-kun.
Drop your weapons! Royal Army!
Really?
I'll improve my concentration...
We informed them that your speech would commence at 10 o'clock.
I'm aware of a lot of things I do that piss you off.
But they were so eager to hear it, they came early.
Well, I can understand how they must feel.
But...
Until I can bring out that power any time...
I can't consider myself stronger.
Chaka-sama!
When I told you the Straw Hat Pirates escaped,
They've been waiting for your Coming of Age Ceremony for two years now.
You almost sounded happy.
Chaka...
It was supposed to be held once you turned fourteen.
Ah. I did?
Hey, what's going on?
Whoa... They're all interesting books!
Is it really okay to take them with me?
You...
Why do you say that?
No idea.
But I haven't really... done anything.
Ma-ma-ma...
Yeah, that's fine, since I've read all of them.
And then, she said to me, in a ceremonial manner:
You don't have to say things like that.
You too, Rebel Army!
Thank you! Then I'll help myself.
Just show them how much you've grown. That will be enough.
"I have something very important to tell you, Papa. No, Father."
Did you not hear me say
I don't know?! Go back!
I... Igaram-san!
The Coming of Age Ceremony is to celebrate your transition into adulthood.
Squad Captain!
If you lie, it'll harm your country!
Sheltering pirates is a felony.
And I thought, as the King of this country...
And given the events that have happened,
--Hey, what's up?
--Hey.
Oh, welcome back.
Imagine how the King will feel.
"It's hard to stop being called Papa."
I think we were able to purchase enough,
--considering the state this city is in...
--Do you have any evidence
that pirates are here?!
Igaram...
What!? What's he talking about!?
Ah, that reminds me...
--Yeah...
--Do you have any evidence
that pirates are here?!
Vivi-sama's speech will be broadcast through Den Den Mushi and loudspeakers.
W-Well, that's...
I wonder if he woke up...
All of Arabasra will be able to listen.
If he wakes up, things'll get noisy, though...
Igaram-san...
I'm certainly looking forward to it!
Boy... I slept really well!
Pell...
Let us meet safely at our motherland.
I've received word that a battle has begun in the harbor.
I see...
Oh? My hat? My hat! Where's my hat?!
Unfortunately, there is no longer anything we can do to aid them.
I cannot accept your death.
That son of a gun...
I'm starving! Breakfast! Hey, breakfast!
Where's my hat?! Breakfast! My hat?!
That's the old pervert from Whisky Peak!
I cannot even shed tears.
FIRE!
FIRE, FIRE!
--So he was alive!
--Uhm, who's that?
He... protected the country...
You just woke up and you're already loud!
Why is this, Pell?
And it won't be breakfast.
It's early evening right now.
DAMMIT! SHOOT YOUR CANNONBALLS AT US!
Hey, can you talk?
Your hat is over there. A soldier found
it for you in front of the palace.
I CAN BOUNCE 'EM BACK!
Yes...
Goodness! Stop joooking around~!
That's the boy from Nanohana...
That's right... He's the kid who
was harmed by the Royal Army.
Oh, good!
If they keep hitting the ship with these iron spears,
I'm glad you got well, Luffy-san!
It's not true... They weren't
the ones who hurt me...
It's only a matter of time before we sink!
Got well? I've always been well.
FIRE! FIRE!
You dummy! You were in serious
condition with a high fever and stuff.
Here they come!
Everyone, listen! I saw it!
Vivi and Chopper attended you all this time!
Hey... This can't be happening...
Really? Thanks!
Oi! There's no way I can patch all these holes!
I just can't feel relaxed without this on!
Oh hey, Luffy! You woke up?
Hurry up and DO something you guys!
Hey, Zoro, long time no see!
"Long time no see"?
We can only protect one side at a time!
What is it, Toto-san?
You've been laughing ever since the speech ended!
Ahh, hey! You went out
training again, didn't you?!
It's vague!
Wait...
Jeez, did those sandstorms screw your brain up that bad, old man?
Going up against eight ships is too much!
What? It's my business, right?
Stop, all of you...!
No means no! I'm the ship doctor!
And don't take off the bandages, either!
That's right... This battle was
a plot from the beginning...
Sergeant Major! Watch out!
Even when we're stronger in hand-to-hand combat...
It's a secret!
It's hard to move with them.
I'm not telling you!
Don't move!
Even if we rush them or retreat, they won't break their formation!
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
"Long time no see"...? "Long time no see"?
--Koza-san!
--Leader!
Well, it's probably natural to feel
that way... since you slept for three days.
What...?
Look after yourself, Luffy-kun!
I will explain everything...
that happened to this country.
Three days?! Did I sleep
for three whole days?!
Come visit Yuba and drink our water again someday!
Tashigi...
The Black Cage Corps: Black Spear Squadron!
Yep.
Keep a close watch on
where this country ends up.
Everyone, drop your weapons!
I missed 15 meals...
You pipsqueaks won't beat us! Dorks!
How come you can calculate so
quickly when it comes to food?!
Something is sure to happen
to mark the start of a new age.
Now, what are you guys doing?
On top of that, in his calculations
there are five meals a day!
Oi, Hypnotist!
Go dig the well!
I thought you were a pirate!
Did I hear right that the captain is up?!
I got it!
Shut up!
It'll be dinner time soon,
so would you wait a little?
I have my own reasons for this!
I thinks I recognize that guy on the left...
--Wha...?!
--Oh hey, old tube-hair guy! You're alive?!
It may as well have been 100 years since we last met!
S... So you really were
into that sort of thing...
That impudent, harrowing cook and his buddies...
Vivi-sama!
No, everyone. She's Terracotta-san.
Chiisana koro ni wa takara no chizn ga
treasure map...
This is the day you sink to your doom!
She's Igaram's wife and is also
the head of the palace's servers.
Where's... everyone?
I've powered up, you see...
Thanks for helping
Vivi-sama and my husband.
Now...
Madness...
No way...! A wife could resemble
her husband, but this is too much!
Look closely at this ring.
atama no naka ni ukande ite
my head...
Why... aren't they stopping?
Hey, walk steady.
This is the day I prove to you that I ain't weird.
I heard you eat a lot.
Ahh... Well, listen... I'm coming down
with "if I walk more, I'll die" disease...
Would you have some fruit to
hold you over until dinner time?
Please...
itsudemo sagashita kiseti no basho o
es I'd always sought...
...stop fighting!
Oh my!
Okay.
Then stay there.
ONE TWO
Are you a magician?!
Please...
What?! Well, w-wait! Whoa! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Lady, I'm gonna eat
three days worth of food!
...stop fighting!
JAN...
Looking forward to it! I've devoted
my past 30 years to the job of serving!
Please...
Why're you pulling me by my foot?
shiranai dareka ni makenai you ni
from me by someone I'd never seen.
...stop fighting!
--Hm?
--Found him?
I won't lose against a youngster's stomach,
so eat to your heart's content!
BROTHER!
Please...
...stop fighting!
Who are you?
Usopp! That was you!?
Ahh... Thanks for carrying
that guy on your back.
...stop fighting!
Ima de wa
6&}And now...
Awesome!
They don't have a shred of dignity...
Please...
Y-YOSH! JUST AS I CALCULATED!
Meals at this dining hall are
supposed to be quieter than this...
...stop fighting!
He's one of ours. I'll take him now.
hokori darake no mainichi
re covered with dust.
That's what I can do when you rely on me!
Please...
Then you're the pirates who
brought Vivi back to this country?
Nose-chan, amazing! Good going!
...stop fighting!
So, it wasn't an empty boast.
But I won't lose!
Now the two ships to the south are gone!
itsu no hi ka
ut some day...
--Please...
--Vivi...
Eat quick or it'll be gone!
Full speed in that direction~!
Who are you, old guy?
Daddy!
subete no...
...I'll leave everything...
Hey, Luffy! You just took the
food from my plate, didn't you?!
BON CLAY-SAMA, A PROBLEM!
Please...
Everyone!
WHAT IS IT!?
...stop fighting!
Don't spit the food!
Ah, it's Vivi!
IT'S THE BLACK CAGE!
Hey hey, if you eat in
a hurry like that, you'll...
tokini mi o makaseru dake
t myself to the flow of time.
Please...
Daddy?
We've got a lot, so...
What's that?
...stop fighting!
Well then, wait and see, Luffy.
I'll put the Tabasco Star on this.
Black Cage Hina! The Marine Headquarters Captain who patrols this area of the sea!
Vivi-chan's father?!
Please...
Are you the King?
Moshimo seki ga kawarn no nara
hould change...
...stop fighting!
This is not good at all!
I prepared myself to die at
one point, but he saved me...
Hey, who was the Princess talking to anyway?
Let's get outta here super-quick!
Please... stop fighting!
Hey! When did you...?!
Aye, Bon Clay-sama!
Dunno. It doesn't really matter though.
What do you call that dish?
When his body was exhausted
after the fight with Crocodile,
nanimo shiranai koro no watashi ni
elf, when I was still innocent...
--Please... stop fighting!
--You dummy...
Looks like they've been weakened.
This is called konafa. You bake
noodles in the oven and...
I was just so happy to hear Vivi-sama's speech!
There is no ship that the Black Spear Squadron cannot bring down!
he carried two people
and rushed above ground.
We have to endure for her!
You guys! What're you
just standing there for?!
Delicious!
Don't get conceited.
Now, here's more!
Yes, that's right!
What unbelievable strength...
It doesn't matter if you have to
punch or kick! Just stop the rebellion!
tsurete itte omoide ga iro asenai you ni
never fade.
Underestimating people will get you bitten in the end.
Even us poor folk!
Off man, I diffn mow mu mere meh ming!
Now! Go!
Like you're poor!
Then there's no more need
to worry about the poison?
Ow!
Men mu're... muff... Mimi's mad, muh?
Once we get alongside their ship, you boys step back.
Reduce the number of casualties
as much as possible!
Right. It should be neutralized by now.
You'll only be in my way.
W-Well... we can talk after the dinner.
Hina annoyance.
But his injuries need to
be treated... Yours, too...
Meah, mu're might.
Aye!
What the hell are you guys doing!?
Can I have another mug full?!
Let's ruuun away!
Hey, we need some water here!
If we exit to the south, we can escape with minimum damage!
Just like we heard, Alubarna is on the verge of ruin.
What a noisy dinner table...
Please...
More importantly, Vivi, go already.
If we stay like this, we'll be done in for sure!
...stop fighting!
They're too vulgar to keep watching...
--What?
--Go back to the Square.
Then, we should go there.
Please...
...stop fighting!
But we need to get Yuba back on its feet. It's the Hub of the West after all.
Of course! The rebellion has finally stopped.
If you want to go, then go.
Please... stop fighting!
How can Vivi-sama just keep laughing...?
It wouldn't be proper if the king
or princess didn't say a few words.
We can't.
What do you mean you can't!?
Gotta fix all the canals from the Sandora River too.
BON CLAY-SAMA, PLEASE HURRY!
And the casino?
Yes... then I'll tell them about you, too.
LET'S JUST ESCAPE ON OUR OWN!
The place is closed.
Vivi-chan. You know how it is...
We made a promise to be at the eastern harbor at noon.
Let's get going!
Yeah!
There's no time to sail back.
Why's he getting special treatment?
We're notorious.
We have to press forward.
Really, that's the silly-silliest thing I've ever heard!
No idea.
We have no intention of
getting involved with a country.
But Vivi-sama said so. It can't be helped.
What kind of treasure could possibly be there that's worth your lives!?
I'm hungry.
And I hear he wants to join the Super Spot-billed Duck Squad.
We're going on ahead to
the palace. I'm exhausted.
Go ahead and die then!
Finally... the beginning is here...
We're going to see a nakama.
But he's a camel.
A camel, yeah.
The day that my enormous ambition starts...
Well, thank you. You took good care of me.
--Whoa!
--This is the palace's proud main bath.
This country is mine!
F-For a... friend?
Well, aren't you an impatient one.
We normally use this only
during the rainy season.
You should't even be moving with injuries like that.
Amazing! This is gorgeous! Gorgeous!
--I'll be the first to go in!
--No, I'll be the first!
Okay, see you.
You just understand this: Go straight to bed when you get home!
Are you guys enjoying that?
Okay, understood, Captain Smoker.
Well, I really enjoyed the dinner.
Yes, I understand.
We don't want her to die!
That's how friends are!
I'm coming in, Vivi.
Oh yeah, wait up.
Because of the current situation,
I thought we'd keep it simple,
Then Crocodile-san was...?
Okay. Come in.
You forgot this. Here.
but it seems that anything you guys
get involved with would become a party.
Vivi, about the speech-
Ah, thank you.
This guy was the ringleader for everything...?
That's why we won't quit fighting as long
as she doesn't give up on her country!
Good heavens... I can't believe it...
My! What a pleasant surprise!
Anyhow, you've got to rest quietly. Understand?
Hey Zoro, look at this! We can train here!
Hey, look at that! It's the Navy!
--Training! Training!
--What training is that?!
Leave your work to someone else.
I nearly mistook you for the former queen, Vivi-sama.
And eat a well-balanced, easy-to-digest meal three times a day--that's in the morning, noon and the evening-
So where's the women's bath?
Are you nuts?! Why would I tell you?!
Un, you've done more than enough.
Oh my goodness...
Vivi-sama's there!
Sit down, Papa.
Don't be so stingy!
We were told that a Baroque Works-owned
artificial rain-making ship
It's behind that wall!
Wow! Those guys are fast!
No...
King! You bastard!
was discovered with dance powder on it.
Father, Igaram.
It's more like we're losing speed.
Hey, old guy! You're not bad at all!
We're taking on water from the hole below deck.
This feels good! I wonder if a ship
with a big bath like this exists...
Sir Crocodile, president of the
secret crime syndicate Baroque Works
If those guys don't do something, we won't make it!
I have something very important to tell you.
and one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea...
BON CLAY-SAMA!!
I'm sure it does, since the sea is so vast.
Oi, Chopper!
Are there any boards left over there?
It's getting serious!
We saw giants... We saw dinosaurs...
Running away now would defy the way of Bon Clay!
CHOPPER!!
We also saw cherry blossoms
bloom in a winter land...
Where did the gator go?!
Friends who risk their lives to see another friend...
There's only three ships.
You... can't...
Guess we'll have to fight 'em.
There're more and more things in the
sea that are beyond our imagination!
Knowing that you have abandoned them...
Yosh! Let's go!
In the name of Navy Headquarters, an agency
directly under the World Government,
WHAT THE HELL!?
WILL YOU ENJOY YOUR BREAKFAST TOMORROW MORNING!?
Ah, those?
...defeat me!
Usopp asked me to keep them in case we could use them for somthing.
I hereby strip you of your
authorization to capture enemy ships,
--Well...
--It's my turn.
Listen up, boys.
THEY'RE IN THE WAY!
as well as all the titles and rights
bestowed upon you by the Government.
Thank you.
WE DON'T NEED THEM!
And the Straw-chan team as well!
Hm?
You finally manage to speak
and that's all you have to say?
I'll chuck 'em.
Hey, what're you all doing?!
All hands, battle positions!
Pay heed to my words!
Those idiots...
We attack in full force as soon as we're broadside!
That's a bluff that suits you well, a loser
who's about to die any moment...
It'll be 100,000 berries per person, okay?!
Hm?
Yosh! Let's get 'em!
Happiness Punch!
And it's even groundless...
Huh?
Hina-jou! The two ships have separated!
Nami-san!
Before it's too late...
The duck ship is heading south!
Full speed outta here!
The duck is the decoy, right?
Mellorine...
I am the man who'll be King of the Pirates!
No! In fact, the entire Straw Hat Crew is aboard the duck ship!
Now, Carue...
You can't make up your mind, can you...?
What?
Just wait and see...
The sheep ship is the decoy!
I'm thinking that we might
wanna leave here tonight...
Let's go home, to Alubarna!
What? Really?
Listen up, brat. The more
a man knows about this sea,
Because we no longer have
a reason to stay here, right?
Follow them! Resume battle formation at once!
The Navy is probably at the
harbor ready to capture us.
the less he'd make such thoughtless remarks.
Our ship will be in danger soon.
My adventure is over,
But now the challenge of restoring Arabasta lies before me.
I thought I told you that there're
tons of rookies like you in this sea.
Thank you...
Right now, Arabasta is like a small ship on the water, riddled with holes.
--You dirty old man...
--I'm not talking about that!
We've done an irreparable thing...
Three minutes.
I'm talking about the country.
The more you learn the level of this sea...
But, no matter what large waves should come,
Leader...
Prepare the bombardment!
We will never back down!
...the more you'll give up
on having such dreams!
I don't know what to say to them...
Here we go!
FULL SPEED AHEAD!
We'll keep pushing steadily ahead,
Could the Straw Hat Luffy you're looking for possibly be me~?
Hey hey, is it okay... for a
king to do such a thing...?
It's just natural to regret.
Without never losing our course!
That unbearable feeling is also natural...
This is a serious incident, Cobra-sama.
Not a chance!
Hina-jou! The sheep ship is escaping to the east!
A king shouldn't bow his head to anyone.
King...
Your Majesty...
Yes, just like that mysterious little boat...
What!?
Igaram... Authority is something
you wear over your clothes.
We lost so much and gained nothing...
You fell for it~!
But we're in the bath. There isn't
such a thing as a naked king.
My boys and I are masters of disguise~!
However, this is a step forward!
I am the man... who will surpass you!
As well as...
I'd like to thank you from
the bottom of my heart
No matter who you fought against,
the battle did occur and has now ended...
We'll see them again someday, won't we, Carue?
as a father and as a resident of this land.
...Straw-chan's friends!
King...
One may stray from the path of a man,
Thank you very much.
No one can make the past go away.
One may stray from the path of a woman,
I really appreciate it!
But there is no straying from the path of a HUMAN!
Overcome this war and survive...!
}All friends must scatter into the sky of truth, and blossom!
--Tonight?!
--That's right.
Leaving here?
OKAMA WAY!
Well, I think it's appropriate, too,
since we no longer have
a reason to stay here.
Yeah... I'm also worried
about the Navy's actions.
Smoker-san?
He truly is without equal...
Hey, little miss.
Okay, then. You decide, Luffy.
How are your legs feeling?
Okay! We'll leave after we have
some more Alabasta dishes again.
P-Please don't call me that.
- by Bon Clay
We're leaving right away, idiot!
Alabasta Kingdom!
--Idiot!
--You don't all have to...
What should we do, Igaram-san?!
We have to let them know right away.
The battle that will be
engraved in history and...
Yeah, of course. But...
this is becoming a big deal...
BRING IT ON!
I hope they can leave this island safely...
Thank you...
Hina humiliated.
How quickly they prepared...!
I've seen their new bounties.
Roronoa Zoro. His bounty
is 60 million berries!
The numbers suit them.
Do you know what his partner, the swordsman, did?
Monkey D. Luffy. His bounty
is 100 million berries!
...the battle that will never be told...
You mean Roronoa?
--Igaram-san...
--With bounties of this level,
He took out 100 bounty hunters at Whiskey Peak,
flag officers at Navy Headquarters
will surely start taking actions.
The scorpion's poison
should definitely be working...
...have ended...
And defeated Das Bones in Alubarna.
You can no longer go back, Luffy-kun.
Where is this brat getting
all that strength from...?
Das? The assassin?
You and your crew took down one pillar
of the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
That's the name we knew him by when he was a bounty hunter in West Blue.
But in Baroque Works, he was known as Mr. 1.
Bon-chan!
Well, it's impressive how many poweful and renowned figures Crocodile drew into his sphere.
The Mr. 5 duo was taken down?
Who the hell did it?
Bon-chan, we will...
Smoker-kun! What on earth is this rain?
But they all still lost.
Monkey D. Luffy? Never heard of him...
Don't tell me you used the Dance Powder?!
We'll set out again and continue pursuing the Straw Hat Pirates.
...NEVER, EVER FORGET YOU GUYS!
There must be a mistake.
You idiot.
There's trouble!
I do know better than to commit a crime.
What?!
Yes, Sir!
The Alabasta King kept
his hands off of this powder.
Are you saying they're still alive?!
The Marines aren't chasing us anymore!
Vivi-sama, where are they?!
Sir Crocodile...
What's the point in me going
against his morals now?
We shook them off, didn't we?
What is it, Igaram? What's the big hurry?
Those pirates are in this town...
Oh, excuse me. I apologize.
Scatter upon the water's surface, and grow where you may,
Where did Luffy-kun and the others go?
I can't believe the "White Hunter"
of all men would say something sweet.
My fellow blossoms.
To the sea... They're pirates, you know...
Hey now...
What's with the lifeless responses?
Oh, no...
I wonder if you've mellowed out a little...
You're just a brat who comes
from who knows where...!
WE MISS HER!
Listen, you guys. Pirates are scum.
That's none of your business.
"Navy Headquarters Sergeant,
Jango the Traitor"
Quit whining about it!
At any rate, you're really something,
using my elite unit just to look for a ship.
Who the hell do you think I am?!
If you didn't want to leave her behind...
Hey, what're you saying?
Don't you remember?
"Navy Headquarters Sergeant,
Iron Fists Fullbody"
You should've just taken her by force!
You used to be a pirate, right?
Ah! You neanderthal!
Very upset... I'm upset!
I don't care who you are...
Urk! That's right! You're exactly right, baby!
You suck!
Marimo.
And you don't know who the puppet master is!?
Santouryuu.
Santouryuu - Three swords
I'll surpass you!
Wait, Luffy. "Santouryuu" isn't an insult.
We joined the Navy in the
same year. Don't say that.
No. It is said to be a secret underground organization.
Wanna dance?!
Ahh! Yeah! Dance! Dance!
Youtouryu.
Youtouryu - Four swords
You always say that. I pity Tashigi
for the troubles you put her through.
Not even the company employees know anything about their Boss's identity.
No, you only added one!
Dance! Dance!
Listen, You know natto, right?
natto - Fermented soy beans
And they are the enemies of this country.
That could mean, like "You stink", okay?
If even the members know nothing, obtaining information from the outside would be impossible.
More importantly, take in
this artificial rain-making ship.
Looks like those two took down
the enemy ship and returned.
So we finally got away from the island.
Yeah.
Rather, an outside investigation would only endanger the country further.
It took them forever.
I wonder what they were doing.
Well done.
Why?
But, we've caught their tail.
And also, Tashigi will bring
Crocodile here. So take him, too.
I put trust in their ability and left the
ship we were attacking in their hands...
Here for revenge!? Bring it on!
Yes...
Eh...
Why are YOU here!?
Eh!?
Disappointed. I'm disappointed.
Give me a break! What makes
you think you can be so selfish?
Igaram, are you thinking what I'm thinking?
Take cover!
Have you finished deploying the ships?
N-No! Not at all!
Just fall along with this
sacred temple already!
Yes, ma'am! It's perfect!
E-Excuse me, I have to get back to work!
Who is she?
We've completely blocked
every harbor in the country!
It doesn't matter who she is!
Igaram!
She's a beautiful lady!
You must not! This is not a game!
Sables...!
--However...
--Hm?
That won't fix it, Igaram!
There's just one thing
I'm concerned about...
What is it?
Heads!
About the Straw Hats' ship that I
thought we confirmed in Erumalu...
I can't let this happen!
...Pesado!
Don't point those dangerous things at me.
It's tails. You lose.
It's gone...
Don't tell me they've
already left this country...
I told you that before, didn't I?
You're really selfish, you know that?!
No... I don't think that's the case...
How long have you been on this ship?
You haven't changed a bit since we
joined the Navy. I'm disappointed.
Then search for it... every corner of the coast!
The entire time.
These clothes are yours, aren't they?
Yes, ma'am! Will do!
I'm borrowing them.
--Geez...
--Miss Hina! Sorry it took so long!
What do you think you're doing, Baroque Works!?
That's fine. I'm well aware of it.
Please ask us why it took so long.
Monkey D. Luffy.
Ah, here they come again!
Why did it take so long?
You aren't forgetting what you did to me, are you?
GET OUT OF OUR WAY!
--We were picking flowers... for you...!
--Don't need them.
That's an order.
LUFFY!
Man your positions right away!
We'll take down the Straw Hat gang!
What the hell did you do to this beautiful lady!?
Look! It's Vivi-sama!
Sergeant Major! This is
a very rare opportunity!
Oh, Vivi-sama!
Princess Vivi!
WHAT- DID- YOU- DO!?
Everyone please disembark the ship at once!
S-Straw Hats?!
Once they come to, we won't be able to...
I can see her!
Gum-Gum...!
Vivi-sama!
Oi, you!
I will not allow you to lay
a hand on them right now!
Don't lie!
Hmmm... This is nice.
Your Highness!
I didn't do anything!
Desert...
Oh, how she's grown!
So this is finally farewell
to the sand kingdom...
Yes you did. You put me through some very excruciating treatment.
...Storm!
Vivi-sama!
Wh-Why?! They're all sitting ducks right now!
Hey, Luffy, when are you gonna stop eating?
Princess Vivi!
Take responsibility.
...La Spada!
The Alabasta dishes are great!
Sanji, make them sometime...
Vivi-sama!
Who is that?
"Excruciating treatment"!? What the hell did you do to her!?
What's going on?
O-On top of that...
Yeah. I was interested, too, so I got
some recipes from Terracotta-san.
Get out of here! I'll call the Marines!
What the hell did you do!?
In that case, Vivi-sama...
You'd better take responsibility!
Serious! Usopp is serious!
Some spices, too.
Allow me to ask you one question.
Leader... Are your injuries okay?
Nami, are you feeling sick?
I don't know what you're talking about!
It all began that day.
What do you want me to do!?
Nami, do you want one piece
of meat? Just one piece, though.
Have you made a resolution not to die?
You're not gonna die, are you?
Uhm, Toto-ojisan was... Yuba was...
Allow me to join your nakama.
Vivi... Looks like you're still
the worrywart as always...
Nami-san, you're thinking
about Vivi-chan, right?
I've had a little adventure.
HUH!?
SURE! }
I understand how you're feeling...
but thinking doesn't get you anywhere.
I don't know about Yuba,
but my stubborn old man won't die,
Oi! The Princess's speech is starting!
Hurry, use it.
I've been waiting.
no matter what happens.
Yeah, I know... you two were really close...
It's the antidote for Crocodile's poison.
She really is alive and well! Thank goodness!
--Leader...
--And I've got his blood in my veins.
But hey... chin up.
Even if he is buried beneath all this rubble, his rubber body may allow him to survive.
The ceremony in Alubarna has started!
It's two hours late. I wonder what happened.
As soon as I get treated, I'll head to Yuba.
I...
Back then you said...
I'll keep you updated... so don't worry.
Well now,
...that only history was inscribed there.
I hope this doesn't turn into a riot.
For Vivi's sake... I'm willing to give up...
Kohza! Hey, Kohza! Come outside!
Okay...
It's raining!
Vivi-chan's speech is starting!
Why did you lie?
...on the 1 billion berries...
Rain! It's raining for
the first time in three years!
Those loudspeakers are at maximum volume already.
--Of course you should!
--So it was about money?!
You can hear it from anywhere in town.
This rain will end the rebellion!
Ah! Usopp fell!
You knew?
Nami! Don't act misleading!
How naughty.
Our foolish sons will come back!
The history of this country is not inscribed on that stone.
What?! What're you guys worked up about?
It began... as a journey across a dark sea, in search of despair.
It's raining!
If it's about Vivi, it's no use
worrying about it, right?
All that is inscribed there are the details about the weapon your organization desired.
Hey! Usopp fell!
Leave him be.
Away from this country, the ocean was vast.
And of course, its location.
It was your fault!
And the islands in it had power that was difficult to comprehend.
If you had translated it for Crocodile, this country would currently be his.
Karoo! Where are you, Karoo?!
There were animals I'd never seen before.
It's no use, Igaram.
And scenery I could never even dream of.
Am I wrong?
Why? We should at least let them
know their current situation.
The music played by the waves... was sometimes peaceful.
I'm not interested.
Just how long are you gonna
stay so stubborn, old man?!
Unbelievable... There's so much
bedrock between here and the surface...
Since I had the Duck Squadron
take them, even Karoo can't catch up.
I don't care whether people and countries live or die.
Yuba is already finished.
What're you gonna do here by yourself?
Flowing calmly, enveloping all my smaller troubles.
I couldn't care less.
And it won't change anything...
I never intended to give Crocodile the weapon in the first place.
What won't change?
They'll be happy when they know it.
That's all. Nothing will change.
And at other timers it was violent.
Are you gonna die with the city? Old man!
Laughing loudly, ripping delicate feelings asunder.
I don't understand.
--But...!
--They'll be fine!
Then why did you come here?
Now, leave! I'm going to bed!
You have to get up early, right?
Hopes and expectations are two different things.
Look... Koza. The rain has fallen.
Amidst a dark, dark storm,
Ah... yes. That's right. We have to let
the entire country hear your voice.
What I wanted to find was... the Rio Poneglyph.
I suddenly came across a little ship.
Hey, look...! Look at that!
The ship pushed my back, saying:
Just three years... That's all.
I know. Come here, Karoo.
Let's sleep together.
Out of all the Poneglyphs existing in this world...
"Don't you see that light?"
It is the one stone that tells the True History.
Never losing its way in the darkness, that mysterious little ship...
Crocodile?!
That is the Rio Poneglyph.
Right... rain...?
--Hmm...
--Igaram-san.
The True History?
...rode the mighty waves as if dancing upon them.
Something's bothering me...
What is that?
What is it?
She's too calm... Hmm...
Enough.
It never opposed the sea,
The rain is no longer forced and
falls endlessly within the kingdom.
I've searched for 20 years...
Yet the continued to point forward, even when the winds blew against it.
Strange... There's something strange...
And this was the only lead I found.
This place was my last hope, and it was a failure.
And then it pointed a finger.
If I am to die here, that suits me fine.
"Look! There's the light!"
At this rate, so much blood will be shed
throughout the kingdom. It'll be a war!
It's quiet, isn't it, Karoo?
I'm tired of walking the road I followed here.
History will likely record this as an illusion.
We haven't had a quiet night
like this for a long time...
I can't just return safely! I need
to return as quickly as possible!
But to me, it is the truth.
The cook who fights with
the fridge robber is gone...
When all I want is to learn of a history,
What's she talking about?
If I don't make it in time, a million
citizens will kill each other pointlessly!
The swordsman who trains
every night is also gone...
A secret battle with the Marines!
There are too many enemies within my dream.
The navigator who throws her
pillow half asleep is gone, too...
And then...
Vivi-sama... You're still up?
They're all gone...
One further question, if I may...
Vivi...
Igaram...
Are you saying the threads of the history that cannot be told can be woven together?
You heard that speech, right?
That was Vivi's voice.
I see... Then all we have to do...
is beat up that Crocodile, right?
Transponder snail
communication? From who?
Can't sleep?
And that Poneglyph is the record of it?
It's the broadcast of that ceremony in Alubarna.
It's not that.
From someone named Bon-chan.
Bon-chan? Who's that?
I just don't want to.
So it's settled. She ain't coming.
If that is so, then why have we been...?
No one knows him.
But he insists he's your friend, so...
I just wanna keep watching this rain.
No! That only sounded like Vivi's voice!
Luffy-san...
Our friend?
She's definitely going to be at the place we promised, right?
Hello? Hi there!
Yeah. She is.
Yosh, let's get out of here.
Wait a second!
Let's go. It's past noon.
I have no reason to live!
It's me! Me! Uhm...
She has to be here!
Put me down and leave!
I don't know why he flew out
from such a place, but...
Let's get off the ship and look! I know she's there!
Why the hell should I listen to you?
Oi, we got problem!
What?! Shut up!
That's right! I knew it from
the start! But in any case...
The Marines are coming at us again!
Hey, it's you, huh?
What do you want from us?
Just how many damned ship do they have!?
Shit! We're moving on!
Oh? That voice must be Straw Hat, right?
Back then, you forced me to live when I wished to die.
About Pell...
Turning to starboard!
He won!!
You're strong! I was so surprised!
Give it up, Luffy.
That is your crime.
He is the most dignified and
strongest among the warriors I know.
She's from a different world.
I have no place to go or return to.
Oh, yeah... Don't call me Mr. 2.
If this signal is caught by
the Navy, I'll be in trouble.
So, are you going to let me stay on your ship?
Yes...
I get it.
I wanted to say "thank you" to him...
What does this mean?
You just said it yourself!
Guess that's that.
Okay.
Just tell us what you want!
When our enemy's already gone...
WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON!?
LUFFY!
Oh, yeah... I took your ship.
He'd be... greatly honored by that...
Don't worry!
Oi, show us your face, you phony princess!
She's not a bad person!
That's not funny!
You son of a bitch! This isn't a
joking matter! Where're you now?!
No! Captain Igaram!
Mellorine! Mello...
Where's the real Vivi-sama!?
On your ship.
Don't shed... any more blood...
Where's the Princess giving her speech from!?
Of all others, he...
No, no...! Gee...
Vivi-sama is actually...
We're friends, right?
Captain Smoker, Miss Hina!
Sergeant Major Tashigi has arrived.
Please stop fighting!
Welcome back.
Good shot.
It's been a while, Tashigi.
EVERYONE!!
He's at the upper reaches
of the Sandora River...
Hina-san...
Can we trust him?
Look at me when I'm talking to you!
Hello... I'm... a little tired,
so I'll go get some rest...
We became friends one time, but...
I want you to answer all of my questions truthfully.
In your case, you may be able to make
friends with him again, which is scary...
I'll ask you again.
Your full name...?
But we have no choice but to go...
He's right. He has our ship.
Oh, I'm Usopp. Nice to meet you. No, no, pleased to meet you.
VIVI!
If he tries to trick us,
then we'll just beat him up.
CARUE!
Captain Smoker, I've just returned!
Nico Robin.
Yosh! Nico Robin.
Yeah, thanks for your work.
Now that it's decided, let's get ready quickly.
And what's your occupation?
Vivi!
Koza!
See, she's here!
I'm an archaeologist.
Okay! Let's hurry. If we don't
get there quickly, our ship will...
Are you all right, Koza?!
VIVI-CHAN!
Archaeologist!?
I heard about what happened
with the Straw Hats.
Turn the ship around! Hurry!
I'm from a long line of archaeologists.
Say, everyone...
The Marines are almost here!
I'm sorry...
I helped the pirates and let our
opportunity to capture them slip away.
I see. From a long line, eh?
Say... everyone...
Do you get it...?
What the hell is this?
What?
And?
I'm here to say good-bye!
What... should I do...?
I know that my actions
were shameful as a marine.
I became an archaeologist,
And then I became wanted by the World Government at the age of eight.
What'd she just...?
Why do you apologize?
Didn't you follow your justice?
Carue, give me the receicer.
Listen well, Vivi. We'll give you 12 hours.
For the past 20 years, I've kept myself hidden from society.
I... cannot go with you!
"Current Location: Alubarna"
"Nanohana" "Sandora River"
Once we take our ship
back on the Sandora River,
No... that's not it...
Don't hold suspicion, Koza.
Since you were eight?
Thank you for everything!
we'll draw the ship near the eastern harbor
just once at exactly noon tomorrow.
"Eastern Harbor"
And you were alone that entire time?
Sergeant Major...
Is she talking to someone?
Not exactly.
We probably won't be able to anchor.
Impossible. Is that the Princess of this country?
A child can't survive on the ocean by herself.
If you want to continue traveling with us,
I just... didn't have any other choice...
The rain will fall.
She should be at her ceremony in Alubarna.
that moment is the only
chance to come aboard.
Over the years, I worked for various villainous characters as a way of protecting myself...
I want to have more adventures, but...
Losers can't speak about justice.
We're in that kind of sea.
If that happens, we'll welcome you...
though you'll become a pirate.
I can't because...
I love my country!
...and achieving my goal.
Since you're a princess of a country,
this is the best we can do to invite you.
Vivi-sama, where are you!?
Get outta here, Captain Igaram!
That's the story.
Come, Vivi! Definitely come! Come now!
Where did the gator go?!
And would you say Crocodile was just one of the those people?
We didn't come here to see YOU!
--Stop it, Luffy.
--Let's go.
Tell me!
The battle will end...
I would.
Why?! Don't you want her to come?
Way to go, Captain Igaram!
Even when I knew where the enemy was,
all I could do was tell him where...
In order to locate the Rio Poneglyph.
That's not the point!
It's something Vivi has to decide!
Do some more!
We came here to see Vivi-sama!
Rio?
It's given me a lot of experience in covert operations.
Even when I knew the time of the attack,
all I could do was assist them...
Rain...
That's why I cannot come with you!
I would be an asset to you.
Noon tomorrow...
Oh!
Hmm, you seem pretty confident about yourself.
There was... no justice that I could follow...
If it's the eastern harbor, it'll take
four hours to get there on Karoo...
I...
What's your speciality?
If I leave here at 8, I'll make it on time...
The symbol should be an !
Why?
Assassination.
'Cause we're pirates!
I've never thought of becoming a pirate.
AH, LUFFY!
But that means deaths to whoever sees it!
The interview has concluded that this woman is TOO DANGEROUS to hire!
The madness has stopped...
Those who you thought you
were on par with up until recently
If I miss this chance, I'll never have
such a choice for the rest of my life...
It's good. It should be an !
They've begun hesitating...
LISTEN TO WHAT I'M SAYING, DAMN IT!
are becoming more
notorious and rising rapidly.
Right, Vivi? It's cool, huh?
Yes! I like that!
Pathetic.
Look how easily you let her walk all over you.
Whatever, just draw them!
The air is clearing up due to the rain...
I've never thought that being
a princess was uninteresting,
That's not the point!
They know that in this sea,
they'll die if they don't rise up.
She was the Vice President of an enormous criminal organization until this very day.
and the country is still at a critical point,
though the rebellion is over...
Give me one good reason why we should let her join us.
I...
Go forward or die?
You may have fooled these idiots, but it won't work on me!
Please don't fight... any more...!!
Who decided to come to this sea?
If I go, you'll go too, right?
I...
If you ever try anything, I'm kicking you out.
This is prefect!
I WILL STAY HERE...
Say... Karoo...
Yes, I'll keep that in mind.
Excuse me... but I'll go rest a bit.
By the way...
What... would you like to do?
This is proof that we're nakama!
I brought along some of Crocodile's jewels.
But if we ever meet again,
I've been waiting, you guys!
Vivi's voice has reached everyone...
Will you still call your nakama?
OHH! I love you, Onee-sama!
Long time no see!
Oi, oi, oi, oi...
We're here!
Nami's down!
Okay, unload! Thanks, you guys!
That was dirty.
Everything's following right along with the enemy's pace.
Vivi-sama...
We have to say goodbye to you here.
You idiot...
It's Vivi-sama...
Have a safe trip back!
If you're frustrated enough
to cry, become stronger!
You hear that!?
Say hello to the King, the old
tube-hair guy and the others!
Vivi...
Ah, love!
Does the Princess have some sort of connection with the Straw Hat Pirates?
I thought the princess was absent...
Floating love!
Take care!
A princess the nakama of pirates? Impossible!
I am but driftwood laying my ebony-burned body down upon the flow.
I'll see you... definitely
see you again someday!
Anyti-!
BAKA!
DON'T ANSWER!
Treasure...
The Marines have seen Vivi already.
Driftwood, struck by your beauty called thunder: I am sent straight along the flow.
Hm? Wait a sec!
If they get any proof of Vivi's affiliation with us...
I will!
--What?!
--Don't "what" me!
Here is your snack.
That's not how you should
treat your friend, is it?!
She'll become a criminal.
Oh, thank you.
Hey, you!
That is without a doubt... that.
Let's just make this a silent farewell.
What do you mean "friend"?
We were enemies. You lied to us!
Yeah. He was a lost cause from the get-go.
I wish you guys had guts like that, too...
I didn't lie! I didn't know it, either!
And so...
Crocodile-san...?
The two of us are the last remaining bastions against her.
How come he fell into a place like this...?
Now, bring them to the ship!
But you see... who cares about it anymore?
Yes, sir!
Crocodile- "san,"  you said?!
Yes, those weak-minded fools have failed us all.
Baroque Works fell. We're no longer enemi...
Captain Smoker! You have a
communication from Headquarters!
I'll tell them what he did to this country.
Hm?
Oi, Usopp!
--Hey, move over...
--Oh, sorry.
This is Navy Headquarters.
Is this Captain Smoker?
Chopper!
Even if we're not enemies,
why are you on our ship?!
Wait a sec. Just stay here.
Speaking.
In regards to your subduing Crocodile,
--You stupid head!
--What'd you say?!
Listen! If I wasn't on this ship now,
Should I call you Robin-chwan?
it's been decided that the top
officials of the Government
Or Robin-swan?
what do you think would've happened to it?!
are going to give you and
Sergeant Major Tashigi a medal.
I can't decide!
It might've been taken by the Navy.
Oh, which would you like?
Subduing...? Hey, wait a sec!
It wasn't us who took Crocodile down.
--What?!
--It's not "might've"!
It definitely would've happened!
Do you know what's going on
around this island right now?!
Ah, this is such a joy~!
The rain falling right now...
will fall again as it used to...
She has a distinct, more mature beauty than Nami-san~!
It's completely blocked by
the Navy ships! It's blocked!
Were they really listening to the report?
Furthermore, each of you will
be promoted by one rank, so...
What?! Then you protected
the Going Merry from the Navy?!
...since our nightmares are... all over...
--Why?!
--How come?!
Hey! Listen up!
The ones who've been fighting Crocodile
and his Baroque Works all this time
Because we're friends!
From now on, whatever happens,
This is a nice ship.
This left arm is proof that we're nakama!
were the Straw Hat gang.
Is it always as lively as this?
It's no use, Smoker-kun.
Yeah, this is it.
Do we still have stuff to load?
The Government is probably
going to cover up this incident.
Nope. This is the last one.
Oh?
In other words, Mr. 2...
Everyone at the Government was
outwitted with regard to Alabasta's crisis.
You guys couldn't get off of the
island due to the Navy's coast siege,
This woman...
What's she plotting?
You think they can tell the world
that it was saved by pirates?
so you wanted to find allies...
Isn't that right?
Bon-chan!
Therefore, we'd like both of you to
attend the medal award ceremony and...
That's right... In a time like this...
Because it's a time like this...
I give you my thanks.
By the way, Miss Navigator.
Are we on course?
You can't be serious!
Gather! In the name of friendship!
No problems in wind or weather!
Smoker-kun! Accept it!
Let's unite our strength and fight together!
Everything's fantastic, Robin-nee-san!
If you disobey the top officials,
you don't know what'll happen to you!
Yeah!
You DEFINITELY took those jewels!
We took Crocodile down?!
No problem.
Geez...
Sanji!
Is it snack time yet?
Yeah!
My subordinate is in tears
because we couldn't do it.
Just wait one minute!
So, thanks in advance!
I'm hungry!
You were there?!
Me too! Me too! I'm hungry too!
Hey, you... Could you tell the old
geezers at the top something for me...?
ARITTAKENO YUME WO KAKI ATSUME
all our dreams,
Miss Hina! Miss Hina!
We found it! We found the Straw Hats' ship!
--Huh?
--Smoker-kun!
SAGASHI MONO WO SAGASHI NI YUKU NO SA
re looking for...
Near the upper reaches of the Sandora River!
"Go to hell"!
SET SAIL!
My... grave?
Prepare to fight.
ONE PIECE
Which direction should I run towards
to see a more wonderful tomorrow?
What course can I set that will lead me to a better tomorrow?
I took the helm and opened the
miraculous map that I stored in my heart
Taking the helm, I spread out the map of miracles I had shut in my heart
I aimed for the sky and sought out
my dreams, though at times I got lost
Aiming for the sky, searching for a dream, there were times when I lost my way
It wasn't a dream; when I met you,
I discovered the wonderful person in me
But this isn't a dream, I found a wonderful part of myself when I met you
With just a bit of courage,
I gained something grand
With a small bit of courage, I gained something large
Now's the time for my "wish"
to become my "pledge"
So now is the time to change my dreams into vows.
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
Shining Ray! Find your brand new way.
Let's sketch out the tale of the future
Let's paint a story of the future
I'll put all my feelings
in a brand new wind now
And put all of our thoughts into this new wind
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
Shining Ray! Find your brand new way.
A never-ending journey to be together
A never ending journey to be together.
I'll chase after you
wherever you go, Shining ray
I'll chase it anywhere, this Shining Ray!
The guy on your back is
one of ours. I'll take him.
Uhm, I'm Usopp, chief of
the party department.
Vivi will come, right?
Adventures are fun.
There's no way she won't come.
Thanks to all of you, we were able to
take down the detestable Crocodile...
Who are you, old man?
Give up, Luffy. Her case
is different from ours.
Everyone...! Daddy...!
Hm? Hey! Don't eat it yet!
D... Daddy?! Is he Vivi-chan's father?!
Well, when we think of it,
it was a tough battle.
Hey, this is bad! The Navy
is following us again!
--Vivi. Go back to the Square.
--What?
There's no way she won't come!
She'll be a pirate with us!
Okay, okay! Well then, everyone!
Eat, drink and party like crazy for now!
Of course! The rebellion has finally stopped.
Father... Igaram... I have something
important to talk with you about.
It wouldn't be proper if the king
or princess didn't say a few words.
Yeah!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"It All Started on That Day!
Vivi Tells the Story of Her Adventure!"
"The Pirates' Banquet and
Operation Escape from Alabasta!"
"A Farewell to Arms!
Pirates and Different Ideas of Justice"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!