A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
I'm certain that what you're
after isn't in this country.
Isn't that right?! To achieve
someone else's goal...
What's the point in dying over that?!
That's why I said you don't understand.
Vivi...
She tells others not to die,
but she's the first to lay down
her own life to save others.
That's why I'm telling you that
you can just ditch that burden...!
We don't want her to die!
That's how friends are!
Vivi-sama...
I feel proud from the bottom
of my heart that I was able
to serve you, the Nefertari Family.
I am Alabasta's guardian deity... Falcon!
The one who destroys...
the royal family's enemies!
"I Will Surpass You! Rain Falls In Alabasta!"
Pell...
That son of a gun...
He... protected the country...
Hey... This can't be happening...
Wait...
Stop, all of you...!
Sergeant Major! Watch out!
What...?
Tashigi...
Keep a close watch on
where this country ends up.
Something is sure to happen
to mark the start of a new age.
Madness...
Why... aren't they stopping?
Please...
...stop fighting!
--Please...
--Vivi...
Please...
...stop fighting!
Please... stop fighting!
--Please... stop fighting!
--You dummy...
You guys! What're you
just standing there for?!
It doesn't matter if you have to
punch or kick! Just stop the rebellion!
Now! Go!
Ow!
Reduce the number of casualties
as much as possible!
Please...
...stop fighting!
Please... stop fighting!
Finally... the beginning is here...
The day that my enormous ambition starts...
This country is mine!
We don't want her to die!
That's how friends are!
That's why we won't quit fighting as long
as she doesn't give up on her country!
You... can't...
...defeat me!
You finally manage to speak
and that's all you have to say?
That's a bluff that suits you well, a loser
who's about to die any moment...
And it's even groundless...
I am the man who'll be King of the Pirates!
Listen up, brat. The more
a man knows about this sea,
the less he'd make such thoughtless remarks.
I thought I told you that there're
tons of rookies like you in this sea.
The more you learn the level of this sea...
...the more you'll give up
on having such dreams!
I am the man... who will surpass you!
The scorpion's poison
should definitely be working...
Where is this brat getting
all that strength from...?
The Mr. 5 duo was taken down?
Who the hell did it?
Monkey D. Luffy? Never heard of him...
There must be a mistake.
What?!
Are you saying they're still alive?!
Sir Crocodile...
Those pirates are in this town...
You're just a brat who comes
from who knows where...!
Who the hell do you think I am?!
I don't care who you are...
I'll surpass you!
Just fall along with this
sacred temple already!
Sables...!
...Pesado!
Gum-Gum...!
Desert...
...Storm!
...La Spada!
Unbelievable... There's so much
bedrock between here and the surface...
Hey, look...! Look at that!
Crocodile?!
At this rate, so much blood will be shed
throughout the kingdom. It'll be a war!
I can't just return safely! I need
to return as quickly as possible!
If I don't make it in time, a million
citizens will kill each other pointlessly!
I see... Then all we have to do...
is beat up that Crocodile, right?
Luffy-san...
I don't know why he flew out
from such a place, but...
That's right! I knew it from
the start! But in any case...
He won!!
When our enemy's already gone...
Don't shed... any more blood...
Please stop fighting!
Koza!
Are you all right, Koza?!
Do you get it...?
What?
Don't hold suspicion, Koza.
The rain will fall.
The battle will end...
Rain...
The madness has stopped...
They've begun hesitating...
The air is clearing up due to the rain...
Please don't fight... any more...!!
Vivi's voice has reached everyone...
Vivi-sama...
It's Vivi-sama...
Vivi...
I thought the princess was absent...
Hey, you!
Crocodile-san...?
How come he fell into a place like this...?
Crocodile- "san,"  you said?!
I'll tell them what he did to this country.
Wait a sec. Just stay here.
The rain falling right now...
will fall again as it used to...
...since our nightmares are... all over...
I give you my thanks.
No problem.
Which direction should I run towards
to see a more wonderful tomorrow?
I took the helm and opened the
miraculous map that I stored in my heart
I aimed for the sky and sought out
my dreams, though at times I got lost
It wasn't a dream; when I met you,
I discovered the wonderful person in me
With just a bit of courage,
I gained something grand
Now's the time for my "wish"
to become my "pledge"
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
Let's sketch out the tale of the future
I'll put all my feelings
in a brand new wind now
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
A never-ending journey to be together
I'll chase after you
wherever you go, Shining ray
The guy on your back is
one of ours. I'll take him.
Who are you, old man?
Everyone...! Daddy...!
D... Daddy?! Is he Vivi-chan's father?!
--Vivi. Go back to the Square.
--What?
Of course! The rebellion has finally stopped.
It wouldn't be proper if the king
or princess didn't say a few words.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Farewell to Arms!
Pirates and Different Ideas of Justice"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!