A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
"The Fabled Pirate Hunter!
Zoro, the Wandering Swordsman"
I'm sick of this.
"The First Patient! The Untold
Story Of The Rumble Ball"
1,867... 1,868...
Simmer three nights and two days,
to take off the bitter edge...
When is this rain going to stop?!
1,869...
Nami-san and Robin-chan, just you wait!
This is a special breakfast!
Hey, Usopp, have you got anything fun?
Huh? I've got a firework we
could launch, but just one.
"A Recipe Handed Down!
Sanji, the Iron Man of Curry"
--Wanna do that?
--Yes!
Don't do it. What if there's a
hostile ship nearby, or something?
I got one!
I guess you're right.
Damn, it's like milk got spilled into
this fog. I can't see ahead of us.
--Look!
--Amazing!
We're going to drink up
every bit of liquor in this joint!
Luffy, do you see anything?
Ahh! I've got something, too!
Hey, now, Billy,
how many places are you going
to ruin before you're satisfied?
What's that book you've been
reading this whole time?
How should I know?
Hey, I see something!
This is big! This could be
the guardian fish for this area!
"Yosaku (several years ago)"
That man over there... has a
bounty of 5,000,000 Berries.
Luffy is showing interest in a book?!
Oh, no! There's a giant ship in front of us!
Huh? Something the matter?
Really?!
I... I can't breathe...
That's amazing!
5,000,000? What do you say we
back off on this one, Yosaku?
N-No, it's nothing.
"Johnny (several years ago)"
Stop it... Lashes...!
Sanji-kun! The helm! Hard to starboard!
The book is called "Rainbow Mist,"
or "Niji no Kiri."
Here, Nami-san! It's Sanji's
specially made love--
Hey, Johnny, if all we do is go after
small-timers, we won't get anywhere.
It's a novel, based on some
adventures this person had
All right!
This is the time when a bounty hunter
has to go after the higher ranks.
in an unusual region of the sea.
T-This is bad! We're surrounded
by the navy, aren't we?!
Adventures, huh? That sounds interesting!
I know what you're saying,
but when it comes to 5,000,000,
Everyone! Wake up! Wake up!
Unbelievable!
even we would lose by a hair.
Awesome!
Regardless of how bored he might be...
Not even the navy can move
around in this kind of fog, huh?
Good morning, Nami-san...
The sea sure is a strange place, huh?
--Guardian fish...?
--We can't eat that at all...
Give me your passionate morning kiss...
It might be best for us to escape
under cover of this thick fog.
Ahh! Shut up! You haven't even caught
a single fish yet! Don't complain!
Hey, I saw an island.
You're right. Keep heading forward.
Everyone, keep quiet.
Really?! Yahoo!
Okay then. Just watch.
I'm gonna catch a big one!
--Especially you, Luffy.
--Right!
What's with you guys?
Nami-san...
It's nothing.
Can you catch any?
I'm sure I will somehow...
Please, wait a minute.
You bastard! Don't give me
that disgusting face!
Nami-san!
Give me something to eat.
"I Will Make it Bloom!
Usopp the Man and the Eight-Foot Shell"
That's what I wanna say!
Got any money?
A child? I wonder what he's doing.
I brought you a tropical juice
that's great for your beauty
Not right now. However,
--You bastard!
--It's an island! We can see an island!
I'll be making some soon enough,
once I cut me up a bounty.
and makes your skin smooth!
Huh? An island?
It stopped...
Thanks!
An island!
That's not fair!
I want some, too!
Where's the island?
Then it's okay, right, Mommy and Daddy?
Smooth skin!
I can't let that go unanswered!
--Look out!
--Allow me.
Hey... what do you want smooth skin for?
Look over there!
I'll cut you down before you can get me!
Whoa... Whoa!
To get cuter!
The wind's fine. The current is fine, too.
He's okay now. The smelling
salts appear to be working.
It looks like we won't
have any problems today.
Don't go making me exert
myself so much. I'm hungry.
Something's taken the bait!
W-Where am I?
Okay, keep close watch on the ship!
You're on the ship of the Luffy Pirates.
Yeah, you got it!
Answer me one thing:
Is there a bounty on your head?
--P-Pirates?!
--Yeah.
Hey! There's a town!
Do you remember? You fell
overboard from a navy ship.
Won't you be surprised to hear?
I've got a bounty of 5,000,000 Berries!
Hey, wait up, Luffy!
What the heck is this?
You don't say. That's plenty.
It's huge!
What?
Hey, Luffy! What'd you catch?!
A town!
S-Stay back! You're planning
to attack the navy, aren't you?!
Doesn't this island have monsters?
I prefer big and strong ones.
What's with him? And after
we rescued him, too.
Don't step on it. Don't step on it.
Don't step on my life...
You can't blame him. He's a marine.
It may be a small town, but it sure is lively.
"Uprising of the Navigator!
For the Unyielding Dream!"
First, eat something.
I've earned some money.
Now give me something to eat.
There doesn't seem to
be anything suspicious,
I don't want it! I don't need any pirate help!
We should be able to procure
a few things here, huh?
Yes, coming right up!
and it looks like this is a small island, too...
Ha, you won't have any soup made
by the cook on a pirate ship, huh?
Look, Nami-san!
What a huge turban shell!
Usopp, are you going to do some shopping?
He's got amazing skill.
This is perfect for making
nonperishable food!
Hey, it's not actually a turban shell.
Good question.
It's not poisoned, or anything.
He's not on the wanted list.
It looks like this island has tons of these!
Hey, guys, get a load of this!
What're we gonna do with it?!
You'll settle down, once you've got
a little something in your stomach.
If he's a bounty hunter,
someone should know who he is.
I wonder if this is edible...
I see... Seems like it'd be a good idea to
collect them and load them on the ship.
You wanna eat it?!
What is it?
Don't tell me there are wanted
posters! No, that's not it, huh?
Could he be the pirate hunter
we've heard about lately?
Maybe cook it in its shell?
Hey, you too?!
This soup is amazing! Imagine,
consomm, as clear as this!
Looks like there're other plants
that can be used for food.
Oh, a firework festival!
And what's more, it's today!
I've heard he's one incredibly brutal guy.
No, word is that the pirate
hunter uses three swords.
This island seems quite
enjoyable for a cook.
--Yeah!
--Fantastic!
I haven't seen fireworks in a long time!
Okay. Then please go look for things
that can be used for food, Sanji-kun.
They say that one of them is a
famous sword, with a white sheath.
Well then, Nami-san, I shall be your escort.
Ahh... Boy, I thought I'd die! Hi, everyone.
Uh-uh, no thanks. Mind your own self.
What's more, they say
he's like a demon beast,
The remaining four of you will do this.
--Huh?
--What is it?
--Drawing lots?
Fireworks, huh? I can't wait!
who's taken the form of a man.
Who... are you...?
The three who draw the shortest lots
will spend all day collecting these.
He sure doesn't look like that.
If that's the case...
I haven't seen you folks around before.
Oh... Pardon me for not
introducing myself sooner.
The one who draws the longest one
will stay here and watch the ship.
Have you come to watch the fireworks?
...we can't just stand by
as our prey is taken from us!
Thanks, that was good.
With a single call, I'll cordially
deliver products to your town.
No, that isn't why--
Sure, you're welcome.
Why, are these fireworks that well-known?
I'm Tajio. I'm a probationary
cook for the navy.
Why are you the one giving us orders?
Hey, Johnny...
I'm Rice Rice from
Transponder Snail Mail-Order.
I'm Sanji.
Yeah. It's a famous festival on this island.
Right. Normally the captain
would give orders, but...
Hey, mister, if you're a bounty hunter, too,
Yeah, you're a cook, are you?
They've been holding it
for 400 years, after all.
Very nice to meet you.
Sanji-san, you're so good!
Oh, hey... they're all short.
then you have to abide by our rules.
Hey, why'd you draw three of them?
400 years? That long?
Too good to be a pirate cook
on a run-down ship like this!
Huh?
Transponder Snail Mail-Order? What's that?
Isn't the one who grabs
the most the winner?
We didn't want to make
any trouble for the pub,
Look. You see that tower up
on the mountain behind you?
What did you say?!
This ship is not run-down!
Well, I was in the process of
making a delivery with the Escar,
so we were waiting for him to leave.
Do you think this ship has a
captain who can give orders?
Yeah! This ship is from Syrup Village,
where I used to live--
The people who live in that house
have been making fireworks
We had first dibs on this guy.
He was our prey.
but I got caught in a heavy storm
No, it doesn't.
--Is it sweet?
--No, not like that. And there
was this girl, named Kaya,
for generations, since 400 years ago.
and got shipwrecked with the
waves throwing me to and fro.
Am I that great?
It's just an old man and a little girl
that live there right now, though.
--Now, now, now, take it easy...
--who gave us this ship,
so it's very dear to us!
Obviously you aren't!
--I see...
--You must've been shaken up.
Oh? Then, does the old man
make the fireworks by himself?
H-Hey, you!
I drew the longest one.
So I'll be watching the ship?
Didn't you hear me?! There are
rules among fellow bounty hunters!
Shaken and stirred.
Yes. Please look after the ship, Chopper.
Oh, no! He makes them
together with the girl.
As it happens, I...
Just kidding. You're quite clever, Miss!
Hurry up! Hurry up! Let's go already!
Let's go get fruits already!
Here, drink some water.
They bang them out all
year long, just for this day.
Hawk-Eye.
You're coming too, right, Nami?
Thank you for saving me.
It's really something.
Do you know Hawk-Eye Mihawk?
No, I'll spend all day today
measuring this island.
This isn't much, but as a token of my
gratitude, I'll give you these catalogues.
I spilled the curry that
they were having for lunch.
Why does it take a whole
year to make fireworks?
Mihawk? One of the Seven Warlords?
With a single call, I'll deliver
the products to you.
I'd like to put it on the sea chart.
I can't wait to put my skills in practice!
You're so dense! You see...
I'm sorry!
I'm on a journey,
with the aim of defeating him,
Oh, that's convenient. So you'll
deliver even when we're on the sea?
and becoming the world's
greatest swordsmaster.
You make it.
There's all sorts of reasons. If I
told you, you wouldn't understand.
See you later! Be careful! Have fun!
That, I can't.
You spilled it, right? So if
you're really sorry about it,
I do collect bounties, in order to eat,
Oh... really...
--Oh, okay.
--That's it!
Look after the ship, okay?!
It looked like we were
almost out of gunpowder.
but it's not as though I'm a bounty hunter.
then you make the curry again,
in time for lunch.
Yes... Our motto is safe, reliable and cheap.
The one who collects the most will win!
I wonder if they'd share a little with us.
The world's greatest swordsmaster?
Hmm... what a pain...
--Who knows?
--I'll be back in a bit!
Hey, did you hear that, partner?
Why do we have to take
orders from that woman?
No way! There's no way!
You must be dreaming!
The chef was right. No question.
--And our mission is...
--It's quite roomy inside.
Now, here I go! Measuring! Measuring!
Uh-huh.
Then again, I hope that nothing like
what went on last year happens.
So then, I've tried
making it again and again,
When I was a kid, that's what
I made up my mind to do.
Our company is, believe it or not...
Oh... How lively Nami-san is when she's
carrying measuring tools on her back!
--Ahh! What're you guys doing?!
--Wh-What's this?!
Yeah, really.
It doesn't matter what anyone else says.
but it doesn't turn out right.
Like what went on last year?
Even if it was your childhood
dream, there's no way you'll...
Tajio-kun, do you have
any experience cooking?
Nami-san! You're lovely!
Okay! This is what I'm going
to introduce to you today.
Yeah. Last year, at the fireworks festival--
I only started being a
probationary cook six months ago.
--Mellorine! Mellorine!
--Stop talking stupid and come already!
The Buru Buru Blade, which is
familiar to people by now.
Kadoyan! They came here
to have a good time.
I didn't know you had claim on him. Sorry.
Six months should be plenty.
No need to go out of your
way to tell them about that.
The Buru Buru Blade is our
company's top product.
You can deliver him to the navy.
The bounty is yours.
No, I can't! All I do every day
is wash dishes and peel things!
I suppose not.
Sorry, it's nothing. Forget about it.
And today, I'll introduce
you to this new model!
I'll be all by myself today.
I still haven't actually made any food!
--Y-You mean it?!
--However...
Oh, yeah! We should tell
Zoro and Robin about this!
When no one's around, the ship
looks really big somehow.
...my lunch here is on you.
What's worse...
I'm sure that many of you are already
using the old Buru Buru Blade.
Yeah! Let's go tell Robin-chan!
All of the ships' captains have a custom
Nah, maybe we should eat first.
of getting together once a week,
and having curry for lunch.
But the old model didn't, well, let you
change the weight load, which was bad!
How come?!
This week, it's my ship's turn to host it.
We did it, Johnny! 5,000,000 Berries!
We'll be able to eat for a while,
It was fine for fathers, but many wanted
small children to be able to use it.
How is my curry supposed to meet
the tastes of the navy's big shots?
without having to go after any bounties.
This is how a firework
of my making turns out.
Hey, what's the matter?
--I don't know what it is, but it looks fun!
--So, this new model lets you
keep a certain rhythm and...
Aren't you happy?
I'll show this to them,
and they'll be so impressed,
The navy's curry is famous.
Why...
I hear the chef on each ship
competes with all the others,
and say, "if you're skilled enough
to make something this wonderful,
...did you become a bounty hunter?
Listen, guys! I'll be the great
Captain Chopper from today!
This is fun!
then please, take as much
gunpowder as you like, for free!"
and each one has their
own flavor for their ship.
Huh? Why did I?
You know all about this one, right?!
This is the Abu Abu Slider.
Isn't it obvious? So I could eat.
Oh, yeah? That sounds yummy, huh?
I wonder if that will happen.
Our company's No. 1 product!
Hey, everyone! Look this way!
With six months' time in the galley,
The village where I
was born was really poor.
if you don't have any
confidence in yourself,
No!
Luffy! Don't eat others' food!
A new model has been
released! Give this a try!
then go back and apologize
to your chef again.
Even so, the bandits still
hit villages like mine a lot.
--How is "top" different from "No. 1"?
--Who knows?
Usopp! Work harder!
Whoa, what a face you've got.
Sanji! Prepare special dishes for me!
No way.
Are you really the head firework maker?
When they did, the bounty
hunters who were after
And, this is our best-selling
product! The "Golden Fish"!
If I tell him that, he'll put me off the ship!
You betcha! I'm Boss Odama,
the pyrotechnist.
Hurray, Captain Chopper! Hurray!
the bandits' heads came, too.
Does it have to be that ship?
This is recommended for people
who don't exercise much these days.
In any case, I'm begging you.
You can spare a little, can't you?
Is there any reason for that, or anything?
I'll offer these great weight loss
products together as a set!
Well...
You must have lots of gunpowder, right?
The All...
And, today only, I'll also add
Do you know about the All Blue?!
I don't have any gunpowder
to give to a greenhorn like you.
20 bottles of plenty sweet Mero Mero
Juice made in the West Blue,
Deep down in my heart, I wanted
to be just like those dashing men,
Now, be on your way, please. Goodbye.
a 26-volume encyclopedia set
that will definitely be useful,
The East Blue, the West Blue,
who challenged the bandits to fight.
J-Just a minute! Please, decide if I'm
a novice or not after looking at this!
the South Blue, the North Blue...
and a pair of binoculars that are
convenient for various things!
I thought to myself, someday,
It's where all the delicacies from
the four seas are gathered together.
This is a fairly decent--
How long have you been there?!
Being so quiet... How sneaky...!
How much do you think all this would cost?!
A pretty penny, to be sure!
I sure do hope that I can take
down those bad men like that, too.
"14th generation Odama"
As a cook, it's a sea of treasures
that I'd like to go to sometime.
So round! So huge! So white!
Just leave it to me!
L-Look! I still don't trust you!
It wasn't until much later that I learned
Today only, I present this as a token
of my gratitude for saving my life!
that they collected bounties
as their profession.
Who gave you permission to
come across my threshold?!
The senior cooks laugh it off as a dream,
Are you gonna give them to us?!
You were a Baroque Works Officer Agent.
Now that you mention it,
I wanted to be like them, too.
How about 23,800 Berries?!
Just take them, you thieves!
Hey, old-timer, is that real?!
That's papier-mch, right?!
but I believe in it! I'm sure
the All Blue is out there!
When I heard what that "world's
greatest" dude in there said,
You were a rogue, and mean, and stupid!
What would papier-mch be doing
lying around a fireworks master's home?
it reminded me of myself back then.
So you're selling them...!
If I'm aboard a naval warship, there's
a good chance I'll go there, right?
I won't accept you! Even if
Luffy accepts you as a friend,
I want them!
It's for real. So, "this is a
fairly decent" what, now?
Hey, what are you getting all
sentimental on me for? It's not like you.
You wanna buy them?!
So I... So I can't afford
to be put off the ship!
there's no way... I'd talk to you!
Shut up.
The All Blue? Isn't that...?
Oh! You carry kitchen knives, too?!
What is it?!
Her special skill is assassination,
right? I hear she's very smart, too.
Yes! You're talking about this, right?
Oh, nothing, really.
What's wrong? Has something happened?
This is one of the high-quality items
produced individually and carefully
Bandits! The Dick Gang is attacking
a ranch just outside of town!
I would like to get away from
here as soon as we can...
I have to be careful.
by a craftsman in High Mountain.
A three-gauge shell, huh?
It's pasted together a little loose,
Yeah, if we're spotted, and
they launch a salvo at us...
Dick the Bandit?
Look at this elasticity. And its
excellent sharpness will last forever.
but it's still pretty well put together, huh?
Here he is! Wow!
Then again, given the circumstances,
Why were you hiding it?
It would be a waste not to finish it.
A dozen table knives,
He's a big-leaguer-- 10,000,000 Berries!
Ah...
a pair of all-purpose kitchen
scissors that can cut anything,
we have to send this boy back,
don't we, Sanji-kun?
That's right, I went to bed after I
made ten Rumble Balls last night...
Huh? Who are you?
a paring knife, and an electric
whetstone! I'll add all these!
I'm Kodama, the granddaughter
of Grandpa Odama over there.
I'm just taking him back
to his ship, that's all.
If you act now, it's 2,980 Berries!
Snap it up, men!
I'll spend all day making another ten!
For you, Miss, here is a Smooth Skin Soap!
Huh? You mean,
Luffy, give us a hand.
you're the girl that makes fireworks
together with the old man?
Rumble Balls... I have to
make them when I can,
It can make your skin as smooth as an egg!
Gum-Gum Mooring Line!!
Yep, that's me.
I see... You do have everything.
since you never know when
you'll run into enemies...
I won't have you looking down
on me, just because I'm little.
They were hiding quite a bit, huh?
We got a big haul today!
Hey, Sanji, I've got hold.
I'm still pretty skillful, maybe even
as much as Grandpa here.
Yes. From mineral water to cannonballs,
there's nothing we don't carry.
Once noontime comes,
this fog will clear up.
But...
...this brings back memories of the
time the Rumble Ball was created...
Later than that, and it will be too
dangerous for us to wait around.
Ee-yow...!
You have living things, too?
Well, we don't.
Is that them?
Don't go getting carried away!
Hey, what do we do?
They're taking it all away, fast!
That's long enough.
What? You don't?
You were supposed to
contact the launch team!
We don't have what we don't carry, so...
How much are you planning to help him?
We're talking about the bandit Dick.
We're no match for him.
I did! They're going to be here
shortly to carry the shells away,
I'm just going to have
a little look for myself
Doctorine won't notice if these get
reduced little by little, will she?
Say, do you have paper?
at what the galley of a navy ship looks like.
It's not worth it if he takes
our lives from us, too.
so I thought I would
get them out, you know?
Huh? Paper?
Sanji!
Damn it!
That's right. Strong paper
that's big and hard to tear,
She always mixes this and this, right?
Before that, you've got
to prepare the mortars,
All right, hold on tight!
so that it'll take more than a
small sea breeze to get damaged.
and get the wagon ready!
All right, next one!
Take everything they've got!
Hm? Was it this one?
Yeah, yeah, you're right.
She didn't put this one, did she?
Okay, fine!
Then, please leave it to me.
Chopper! Do you know where
my medicine bottles are?
Transponder Snail Mail-Order
presents with confidence
They have important medicine in them.
They're all rare and valuable medicines.
What's with you?
What's with the people in this town?
They're such cowards.
the best paper, A-Thousand-Year Paper!
Don't just stand there, go give her a hand!
By the way, why did you come along, too?
A-Thousand-Year Paper?!
You wouldn't be playing
with them, would you?
How were you going to get back?
--Why?
--Just get going!
Don't they even have
the guts to put up a fight?
A-Thousand-Year Paper is manufactured
by using the A-Thousand-Year Tree
that naturally grows on Eight-Nine Island.
Well, just wait here, and behave yourself.
Well, maybe that's smart, in a certain sense.
This paper keeps away bugs,
and it's said that it won't fade
S-Sure.
Chopper!
There are those who take,
and those who get taken from,
for at least a thousand years,
even if it's kept exposed to the sun.
What was that all about? He tells me
to go away, then tells me to help!
and you're either one or
the other in this day and age.
"18th Fleet Galley"
This is the galley.
It's the best for writing family
trees or drawing treasure maps.
Being weak is a crime all by itself.
Yeah. Might as well have a look,
as long as I'm here.
I give up. I'm leaving.
Defiance is something only a fool would do!
Hey!
Paper airplanes, too?
Fixing to slack off? Help me out, here!
Huh...? That would be a waste...
Huh?!
So how much is it?
You're not here to become an apprentice?
So there is a fool here...
--You're gonna buy it?!
--Of course!
That's the navy for you.
This is expensive stuff.
I got a good scolding
from Doctorine then...
Of course not. I just came to
get some gunpowder from you.
I caught her purchasing desire!
G-Give back our food!
What's more, it's all in good repair.
That's something we all
worked very hard to store up!
I take it she's the type that price is
no object once she decides to buy.
You had your own firework,
so I thought for sure you
wanted to be an apprentice.
--What's that?
--It's coming from the ship's pantry.
Then, I'll just stir up her urge to buy as
much as possible and jack up the price.
Harry!
I just made that one for fun.
I wonder how Doctorine is doing now...
I hate to admit it, but I'm
not up to working pro.
Even if you're interested... it's a
valuable item in short supply...
You've got grown-up guts, at least.
Maybe I'll write her a letter.
That startled me...
Yeah... but it's true,
that is well put-together.
Luffy! What are you doing in here?!
Darn you...!
--Hm?
--They're called... Rumble Balls?
Sanji! Recon! I'm on recon!
Even if you order now,
You should hurry up and finish it.
Harry! Stop! You're no match for him! Harry!
I don't know if it'll be available
in five years... or ten...
A chance like this doesn't
come along every day, after all.
Come to mention it, you said
the same thing before, too, huh?
Let's go!
What do you mean? I thought
it was already finished.
Are you trying to uncover
the secret of the Rumble Ball
But isn't there some way you could
sell it to me? I'll pay any price.
Hey, take it easy, partner.
Even we would lose to him by a hair.
So, I'm just going to go do some more recon.
and then assassinate me?!
Do as you like, but if the marines
find you, they won't go easy on you.
Fireworks only become finished
when they blossom beautifully
What?!
Not a chance. I won't be taken
down by someone like you!
The Nami who would rather
count money than eat her meals...
And another thing...
That's not why. He's...
in the night sky.
Leave what you've stuffed
down your pants here.
The Nami who is a money monger...
Which is why all of the fireworks in
the storehouse are unfinished goods.
Rumble...!
Apples, right?
...will pay any price?!
Guard Point!
You guys're going too far...
...who I was that day...
These launching mortars, too.
This here is navy curry.
They're not finished until
they're used as equipment.
--Ow!
--Heavy Point!
Okay, then... If you insist that much...
He doesn't know how to compromise
or look out for himself yet.
There's something amazing about you.
Jumping Point!
A ream of 1,000 A-Thousand-Year Papers
It's like I told you. I won't have
you looking down on me.
Back when I was at a maritime restaurant...
normally costs 60 million Berries, but
how about a special price of 48 million?
He's me, back when I was still innocent.
So then, that ridiculously huge
firework earlier is the same way?
...the owner, Zeff,
never taught me anything.
48 million Berries...!
Horn Point!
It's still unfinished, right? I sure
would like to see that one go off.
Hey! Johnny!
Does that mean that it costs
48,000 Berries a sheet?!
You see the power of the Rumble Ball?!
There's more where that came from!
Day in and day out, all he ever
let me do was wash dishes.
Can't you drop the price a little more?
What do you think you're doing?!
I can see through your weak point!
Who are you?!
Well then, I'll make it a lot cheaper...
How about 47.5 million Berries?
Last year, we tried to
launch one just like that.
Brain Point...! Scope!
Just a nameless bounty hunter.
--2 million Berries!
--4.8 million Berries!
Hey, little brat!
Oh? There was another one like that?
Weak point...! Weak point...!
Where's her weak point?!
You have to do more than just your hardest.
What did you say?
--This sounds fishy...
--Can't you go cheaper?
Mm-hmm.
We'll buy it!
But it didn't work.
Our equipment was flawed.
Use your head, and think about
why I let you into my kitchen,
Sanji-kun...
What's funny?
You have the money?
You don't have to look so fierce, right?
Nope!
then had you do chores for the
last six months, or the last year!
You don't mean...?
But if we hand him over to the Navy,
we'll have that and change.
S... Stop it! Stop it! Stop tickling me!
My mommy and my daddy...
What?!
They died, a year ago today...
That's what Zeff told me, as I was
dripping with dissatisfaction.
--Stop it!
--How cute you are!
Sorry, Luffy. This is for Nami-san.
I like you.
I get it. Chef has me in here to
let me steal his cooking skills.
Wait a sec!
...when the launch of the
200-gauge shell went wrong.
Luffy...? Ahh!
Luffy... You mean... that Monkey D. Luffy?
C... Cute...?
Cooking isn't something that can be taught.
Give me a break! Even if you like me,
Yeah, that's me.
that doesn't make me happy or anything!
There's no way I'm happy!
You guys are bounty hunters, huh?
Are you after my head?
--Sanji! Whatever, just untie me.
--No, I can't.
Sanji-san, I'm going to try!
You jerk! You jerk! You jerk...!
Th-Th-That odious pirate with
a 100 million-Berry bounty...
What a pain. You're just a couple of hyenas.
--Well, then... shall we go?
--What?
That Monkey D. Luffy...?
What did you call us?!
--The water's gone, right?
--Ah...
Let's see... What was it Chef said...?
If you want money, then I
can give you some charity,
Come to think of it... that's a pirate flag!
This weather seems kind of weird.
if you don't mind small change.
I'd like to drink coffee... before I read.
The basic recipe for curry is
powder, soup, and ingredients.
--We don't want it!
--Huh?
I can't believe I missed
such important details!
Do you still hold the firework
festival if it's raining?
We just feel a little bit like
being champions of justice today.
What's the matter? You go draw
the water... since you spilt it.
His curry powder is delicately blended!
Mm-mm.
--I said untie me!
--No!
I guess it's no use, Mommy, Daddy...
Uhm...!
Ah, yes.
Eh? Hey, Johnny...
I just remembered that I have
an important appointment.
That aroma...
Champions of justice?
They take ready-made curry powder,
Goodbye!
and add in some freshly made garam masala.
--Thanks for everything!
--Hey, you forgot something...!
--Hey...
--Partner...
Would you let me be a man?
At least get things ready.
Johnny...
What's no use?
What's with him?
Don't be so lazy that you use
the powder that's already there!
Maybe he was scared of you...
Wanted man, Monkey D. Luffy.
Johnny, you mean...?
The flavor of a spice diminishes by the day!
All right.
If it clears up tonight, I'm planning
on launching the 200-gauge shell.
Geez... How could I feel like
working on such a fine day?
There's no such thing as
justice or evil in this day and age!
Really...?
It's the garam masala!
The mighty prevail!
That's all there is to it, am I right?
N-No! Fireworks aren't food!
Listen. I'm going to work now,
so don't interrupt me, okay?
We're serious!
What do you mean "work"?
Yeah! Just this morning,
His sense of smell is true, huh?
we turned in a bounty worth
5,000,000 Berries to the navy!
Whoa! There sure are a lot of them!
It's a secret.
That's not cute, you know...
Don't raise your voice, you dummy.
Leave it to me! I won't let anyone near
you until you're done with the work.
The navy, this morning?
S-Sorry.
But you can't launch something
as huge as that on your own, right?
But... what if the wind direction
suddenly changes or something?
You're the ones who did in Billy--
my sworn brother?!
That's all right. I asked the launch
team to help me out in secret.
Don't worry. Those clouds...
If they don't move, we'll have a fine
day today and there'll be no problem.
What?!
Even so, it already failed to launch
once, right? It's too dangerous.
Ahh!
He got me!
Come get me only when something
changes with those clouds.
That's okay. I want to do it.
That time, I thought... "This is it...
This is the end of Captain Usopp...!"
It's not okay!
Are you trying to get the launch
team folks caught in it this time?
This is huge!
Let's see...
No, of course not. They'll just be
setting it up, and then take cover.
I was attacked by a huge condor...
and I couldn't breathe...
In this fog...
...we won't be moving for a little while.
Sorry... Because of that, I couldn't
get even a single fruit. I'm sorry.
I'll take care of the launching by myself.
Things have been hectic
It'll probably clear up around midday.
and I haven't had free time since
we entered the Grand Line, but...
"By yourself," huh?
By the way, did you hear
about the customary luncheon?
That's okay. Don't worry about me...
Yeah, about how that
probationary cook Tajio is making it?
No, no, no! I'm telling your grandpa,
and putting a stop to this.
Little Garden...
Ugh...! I'm dead.
Drum Island...
I wonder just what exactly
he's going to feed us.
Have you finished the
sword I asked you to do?
Alabasta...
Why do I have to take orders from
that woman?! Seriously, how irritating!
Yeah.
No doubt!
I've written down all
the routes that we took.
What do you think you're doing?!
For the bullion, I can use
the ready-made stuff
I've stolen... no, obtained maps of the
surrounding areas from towns as well.
That's what I was going to say!
Three-Sword Style...
Don't go ruining my
Mommy and Daddy's dream!
that's thoroughly boiled.
...Dragon... Twister!
Now, it's time to prepare the ingredients.
Your Mommy and Daddy's dream?
You have exceptional skill.
I'll draw... my own world map...
my dream since childhood...!
That's right.
I put in a lot of work. You're too
reckless with such a precious sword.
First, I need to cut up and brown the beef.
Our family has been making
fireworks for generations,
If that were an ordinary sword,
it would have met the same fate
for over 400 years now.
--Hey, that's okay...
--Just let me!
as those two other broken swords of yours.
Apparently, we once had the technical skill
All right. I'll be careful.
to make and launch 200-gauge shells,
Ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
but at some point,
that tradition was broken.
There's a type of beef curry
where the beef's juices
It was my Mommy and Daddy's
dream to bring back that skill.
are sealed within the beef itself...
Guys! We'll make the deck spick-and-span
while Nami-san's working.
But from the mellow flavor of this curry,
The contour line should be like this...
That's why, tonight,
I'm going to finish their dream.
this isn't the type that keeps
the essence of the meat inside,
Okay!
Do your best!
it allows it to dissolve out into the soup.
The right ridgeline is 42 degrees, maybe?
I'm going to get stronger for her, too!
I understand how you feel, but...
You're gonna do it, too!
The love fever is also 42 degrees.
In which case, this kid is
messing it up right from the start.
--You traitor!
--No fair!
Hold on a second. Why would you
just blab something like that to me?
I'm going to get strong enough
that my name reaches to heaven!
--That's right!
--Then what about that woman?
Please measure the height of
my feeling towards you, too!
I'm going to be the world's
strongest swordsman!
Don't be ridiculous! She's a lady!
--You're in my way! Move!
--Ow!
Is something wrong?
Do you want to know?
How stupid! It doesn't matter
if it's a man or woman...
Just help us, Moss-Head monster!
Kid, cooking is not something
you should rush through.
You want me to keep
your grandpa occupied?!
Yes. The launch team folks will be
here soon to carry the shell away.
Ha ha, very funny,
Love-Love Machine goblin.
Thanks for your help. I'd like
to pay you something extra,
Remember, everything in cooking
depends on preparation.
but unfortunately, right now, I'm broke.
Just help us, or I'll beat
you up, you bastard.
While they're doing that,
keep Grandpa occupied inside,
I'm the one who's going to draw
the water... Why is she coming, too?
Don't worry about it. It's not often
I get to see such an item as that.
Go ahead. You think you
can beat the monster?
so he doesn't come out here. Please!
It's vital to take your time. That is everything.
It was a feast for the eyes.
You dumb fool! How can I help you
out with something so dangerous?
You say that because you
don't know my goblin power.
Not at all like this
good-for-nothing long sword.
What a fine day!
Oh, really...
What?!
Hey, didn't I tell you so?! Give me a break!
S-So what?!
"14th generation Odama"
Because my Mommy and Daddy's
dream is still only half-finished.
Nothing, really. It's a fine day. That's all.
Include garlic...
No matter how many swords you carry,
it'll never be enough like this!
...ginger...
I'm going to finish it for them.
I just... wanted to take a walk somehow.
Damn, I've done it again. Sorry,
I'll be sure to make it up to you.
...turmeric,
--I'll cut you down!
--Want me to gut you?!
I haven't felt this way for quite a long time.
and add some yogurt.
I'll cut you into pieces!
Go! Go! Fight! Fight!
That's that punk Dick, the mountain whale.
S-Stop it, both of you...
He's a 10,000,000-Berry bandit,
who uses a cannon.
Usopp! Don't just stand there and
watch. Let's stop them already..
I was constrained every day for a
long time, so... I never smiled, either...
A bandit with a price on his head, huh?
Don't be ridiculous!
Don't underestimate me!
Hold on a minute...
You know there's no way I can stop them.
Oh, yeah...
A prayer before launching?
A fine thing to do.
--Ah!
--Hm?
Wow...
But that isn't what you'll be launching.
You'll be doing smaller ones.
Didn't I tell you to be quiet?!
Water!
The launch team... Why did you tell him?
Mellorine...
J-Just one hit...
Watch what you say. They were
thinking of you when they told me.
Damn it!
For Pete's sake...
It's no use. He's too much
for those guys, after all.
Why?!
Why?! After all the begging I did?!
That takes care of the preparations.
Hey, Bellemere-san... Bellemere-san!
Sorry, Kodama-chan.
Next, I have to saut the onions.
But it's just too reckless.
That thing is sure to misfire.
What is this?
You don't know that for sure,
do you?! I'm not afraid of that!
--Bellemere-san...
--Hm?
Are you two really the ones
who took out my sworn brother?
Say, where does the wind come from?
If I remember correctly, you said you've
always been alone since you were eight.
Stop it, will you?!
Hmph! We were the ones who turned in Billy,
It's not as though they don't know
how those of us left behind feel.
but someone else beat him, you bastard!
--From the sea.
--Sea?
Yes... By following pirates,
I barely survived...
Then what are you bragging for?
I thought you were pretty weak.
That's right. The wind born on the sea
This isn't what it means
to carry on their wishes.
brings blessings by blowing
on Cocoyashi Village.
Shut up!
Not just wind. The rain, clouds, rainbows...
Smoking, where I'm preparing food?!
Kodama-chan!
Tell me... about this Doctorine person...
Ah, that's it...
As a cook, do you think that's okay?!
Everything comes from the sea.
Earlier, I said you were too good
to be a cook on a pirate ship,
What?
I see... Say... then where
does the sea come from?
Okay, well, we'll get things ready.
You were talking about that person earlier.
but I take it back!
Yeah, if you would, please...
My, my, I singed my hair.
She's a doctor, right? Is she your teacher?
--What?!
--Nami.
Don't give Bellemere-san such a hard time.
Y-Yeah, but Doctorine is someone
whom I'm deeply indebted to.
But... Nojiko...
Say, you're getting ready,
even with the rain?
Nami, you really are a curious girl.
Man, you are relentless.
People call her Dr. Kureha.
This rain will let up soon.
The wind is coming in from the east.
Dr. Kureha... What kind of person is she?
Nami...! Nami!
Remember, you first saut
onions over a strong flame.
She really loves alcohol. Although
she's a woman, she's like a pirate...
Kodama is the only one
who doesn't realize it.
Stop!
Keep them moving,
so they don't get scorched.
Hey!
Why, you...! You want to
die that badly, do you?!
Old-timer, has that structure
been there the whole 400 years?
And she's like a pirate, but she is a doctor.
Once the onions are soft, lower the flame.
I heard you did it again!
Go slowly and gently,
simmering over a low flame,
Yeah. What of it?
The lady at the bookshop
stormed into the house in a rage.
until they're golden-brown. Got that, men?
I hit upon a good idea.
Now, let's go home. The dinner is ready.
How about hearing me out?
Boss! We're done loading
all the loot into the cart.
Say, Bellemere-san...
What's beyond that sea?
Sanji-san was warning me
about the heat level...
I studied to be a doctor
under Doctorine for six years.
You're done? Then let's pull out of here.
These are graves? Wow, they're funky.
Who knows? I don't know what
lies beyond the Grand Line.
There's no sense in messing
around with these weaklings.
Even though you were a marine?
Yo.
Hold on!
I was, but the sea is too big.
"After mixing these three kinds
of herbs, grind them well"...
Mommy and Daddy, like I said,
if this long spell of rain ends,
I said hold it right there, wanted man!
I wanna see... what's beyond the sea...
We've turned in dozens--
no, hundreds of bounties by a hair!
Chopper! Chopper!
it means that I have your permission,
--Nami...
--I wonder if I can go beyond that sea...
Wow, this is high. The view is
completely different, all right.
Urk!
and that I can launch the 200-gauge shell.
Did you read the medical book?
The 500 pages that I told you to read?
If we let you get away, it will
shame us for generations to come!
You're a strong child. If you really want,
you can go anywhere you want.
So then, does this mean I'm wrong, after all?
What a waste. It's not worth it, is it?
Then I've decided!
W-Who are you?!
I'm gonna use my navigation skills
to travel to all the world's oceans
Humph! You were playing
with the medicine again?
I've been spotted!
--Hold it!
--I'm not holding anything!
Maybe we won't earn anything... but still...
I wasn't playing!
and make a world map of
everything I see. I sure will...!
"It doesn't mean you're wrong. Kodama,
That's the same as playing.
B-But...
if you launch your own fireworks,
we'd be glad to stop the rain."
Melt some pork lard...
...there are times when a man
has to stick to his beliefs, and fight!
But what?
That's right. I definitely will... some day...
I... I've been studying for three years now.
...add the flour...
I will complete my own world map.
I've also read 200 medical books.
Let me compound the medicine...
But then, Mommy and Daddy, your dream...
You guys aren't long for this life.
Gently, so as not to scorch it...
We knew that when we started!
Hey, Luffy! Watch!
It's still 100 years too early!
"Do you think that's all our dream is?"
I see.
Hey, men! Take care of
these guys, right away!
Put the curry powder in...
"You are our dream. Our dream
is that you will carry on for us,
Whoopie!
I-I've memorized all 200
books that I read! It's true!
...and add garam masala,
to enhance the flavor.
Amazing!
--Let 'em have it!
--Out of the way!
--Amazing! Amazing!
--Right?
and become a fine pyrotechnist."
I even memorized "The Seventh
Principle" by Dr. Alexandra,
Geez...!
"Kodama, take your time, and
make your own 200-gauge shell.
which you said was the most difficult!
Now, to bring all the ingredients together...
Ah... You've been working hard.
Are you done?
The TaboTabo bacteria start
dividing on the 7th day of culturing.
No... But what is this?
You have an unlimited
amount of time, after all.
After showing the sign of overreaction
Hey, what're you guys doing?
Add in the bullion...
"Kodama, if you can bring
back the 200-gauge shell,
mentioned on page 1,254,
chapter 7, section 2...
Cleaning.
This is pretty fun. Wanna do it, too, Nami?
What do you want?! Let me go!
They're in there fighting for me!
The tomatoes...
that will also make our dream come true.
Humph... So... wha...
What's going on? It's noisy.
If you feel like fighting...
"Let Grandpa take care
of our 200-gauge shell;
...think. What can you do
with the power you've got?
What?! The Smooth Skin Soap?
Add the onions...
you keep on showing us your
beautiful fireworks up in heaven."
Hey, it's dangerous.
It's okay! No problem!
Doctorine!
Then put the marinated meat in.
Are you okay?
Looks like I got a febrile disease
from the patient I saw the other day...
Luffy!
All right! I will!
And then, someday, I'll make my
own 200-gauge shell, you'll see!
--That idiot!
--Gum-Gum...!
This is a terrible fever!
Chopper, if you talk big like that,
try putting your medical skill to the test.
Bungee... Jump!
My, my, you poor guys.
Move away!
What?
Watch out, Nami-san!
"Thanks for understanding.
You don't have a spot on your
faces that hasn't been messed up.
I'll be your first patient.
Are you okay, Nami-san?
And now, as promised..."
I think it's about time to put an end to this.
I won't give you any advice.
Ah!
Ow, ow, ow...
It won't gain me a single
red cent to kill the two of you,
If you fail, I'll die...
It's not right...
It has no body.
but consider this your own twist of fate.
Ahh! My map...
Learn by experience that
medicine is a serious challenge
Oh, you were drawing a map?
The hard luck that comes from
having come after my head.
How? That's amazing!
Sure enough, I can't do it.
where patients' lives are at stake.
What? Map?
Just who are you?
So that's what your "work" was...
But relax, I'll send you into
the next world together, as pals.
Will the blue-nose reindeer be
able to win in a serious challenge?
Who, me?
That's right. It's the only map in
the world that recorded our journey
I'm a messenger, sent from heaven,
after entering the Grand Line...
Usopp Angel.
Take this!
Subtle flavoring...!
And yet...!
Usopp... Angel...?
Sanji-san!
Here goes!
My dream is to complete
my own world map!
That's so lame!
This apple...
Usopp Angel...
That's enough, don't you think?
This fight was over a long time ago.
Leave!
...thank you! I'll try my best, okay?
...sure is sweet.
--But...
--Just leave...
Nami...!
Sanji-san...
--What?!
--I'm sorry...
If "sorry" were enough,
there'd be no need for the Navy!
There's no mistake! This is
the pathogen of the Mondolin.
Thank you very much.
You...
What are you talking about?
That guy from earlier...
Now, leave already.
Forgive me, but I'm going
to swipe your prey from you.
What works for this
pathogen is... let's see...
I haven't done anything
you need to thank me for.
If you don't, you'll be fined 100,000 Berries!
This is it!
Sanji-san, you just pretended to stop by,
I've come into an urgent
need of money, you see.
but really, you were trying to teach me.
S-Sure...
--It's your fault.
--Why's that?!
Doctorine...
Okay.
Don't get the wrong impression.
--Well, I think so, too.
--I think so, too.
--Seriously, those guys
Over there! He ran over there!
--What?! You, too?!
--Now, Luffy, cheer up.
--always get in my way...
Don't die... Please...
How pretty!
Who is that?
Sanji! Let's go!
Ready, set...!
Hmm...
A-A white-sheathed sword...?
That idiot...
Hold it!
Gum-Gum...
I need to borrow your swords for a minute.
Let's see...
...Mooring Line!!
No problem, but what exactly are you--
You're not gonna ask what
medicine I compounded?
All right! I've grabbed on!
Three swords?! You don't mean...!
You think there're patients out there
who'd have enough composure
Tajio...
to ask doctors questions about everything?
The pirate hunter, Roronoa Zoro?!
Oh, this is coming off nicely.
I think it's out there, too.
If patients don't trust their doctors,
they won't recover from the sickness.
The All Blue.
Though I have to admit...
Hm? Smells like rain...
Ho, so this is the fabled pirate hunter, huh?
Sanji! Grab on!
By using the wheel on the
cart in the yard as a pulley,
Right!
So then, what's going on here?
How is it? Do you feel a little better?
he figured out the trick for dragging
that thing out of the storehouse.
You dummy. No medicine
would work that quick.
Sure, I've gotten noticeably stronger lately,
Who would have thought that the
tower that's been here for 400 years
Let me sleep a little.
but as soon as I use too
much of it, my swords break.
Hey, Tajio, there was a
suspicious-looking man just here, right?
was actually the launch
platform for 200-gauge shells...
I can't go overusing my strength so recklessly.
Where did he go?
There's a problem! Luffy! Luffy!
Huh? I don't know. Are you sure
you weren't seeing things?
No matter the sword,
I have to get to the point
Just who is this kid, anyhow?
where I'm able to get
100% of its force out of it.
There's a problem! The clouds...!
Keep looking! They must be
hiding on the ship somewhere!
Spiders have ten legs.
Find him!
No, they have eight.
Roronoa Zoro-san, even using three swords,
"14th generation Odama"
Hey, that doesn't matter! Wake up!
--Centipedes have 100 legs...
--Usopp! Sanji!
I don't think you'll be able to
defeat that many men at once.
Chopper!
Here goes the rapid fire!
Wake up! Zoro! Someone!
Why, you...! You have some
sort of grudge against me?
Not too bad, considering
your lack of experience...
There's a problem!
Sorry.
Using three swords is not the same thing
No, that face doesn't say "sorry"!
Nami...!
as using the Three-Sword Style.
That's why I'm sorry.
It was the first time that
Doctorine praised me.
You'll be fined 100,000 Berries!
I'm gonna fillet you...!
Three-Sword Style, you say?
Let's see it, why don't we?
Wh... What should I do...?
What's the matter, Luffy?
It was the only time during those six years.
Get him, men!
You've damaged the
Going Merry again, huh?!
Oh, Usopp, Nami, sorry!
Instead of acknowledging me,
she left her life in my hands.
Done!
The navy saw me, so we had
to come back in a hurry.
If I do say so myself, this is perfect!
Am I a genius or what?
That's Doctorine.
That's the kind of person she is.
Huh?! H-Hang on, what
do you mean by that?!
This is incredible!
What?
I won't forget... Some day, I'll become
a doctor that'll surprise even her.
This is a precious ship,
that we got from Kaya!
Yeah, outstanding.
Hey, what happened?!
Is it ready?
He did it! Incredible!
How many times do I have to tell you that?!
All set!
Outstanding!
--Nami!
--Hey! What were you doing?!
--Last one!
--Okay, last one!
We can't stand around like this! Usopp,
Sanji-kun, we're leaving immediately!
Right!
Watch out!
Why didn't you tell me
before it got this bad?!
Yes, Nami-san!
Oh, no... I said too much...
Urgh, I can't move...
Huh?!
Because... you said we'd
be fined 100,000 Berries...
We'd better get going or the sun will set...
Awesome!
You dummy...
I wish I had someone that I could
write a letter to... like you do...
Hey, you guys! How long are
you gonna keep sleeping?!
Here goes...
What...? Ah!
Ahh! What the heck is this?!
--It's a tornado! It's a tornado!
--It's obvious!
Serve it.
What was that shabby firework just now?
This is heavy...
Yes, sir!
--Luffy! Zoro! Fold the sails!
--Okay!
Huh?
Heavy...
That's how my first firework turned out, huh?
Usopp! Chopper! Secure the
stuff on the deck using ropes!
I told you, don't stand beside me.
Okay, Old Man Odama!
You're going to catch
a cold dressed like that.
Got it!
Sanji-kun! Turn to starboard!
People who catch colds are people
who let their mind's guard down.
Well, I wonder if someone
somewhere is spreading stories
Umph!
Point the bow of the ship away from the
tornado, or we're gonna get swallowed!
about Zoro, the pirate hunter.
Please, enjoy your meal.
I've never once called myself a pirate hunter.
Okay!
Then, who did give you
a name as cool as that?
So... why weren't you able
to get even a single fruit?!
Who knows? It doesn't matter to me.
--Hey, hey...
--Listen!
That's a good question...
If my precious map gets washed
away by waves or something,
That time, I thought...
Oh, this is good.
A huge king condor attacked me...!
It's just thick enough, and the spicy flavor
you'll all pay... dearly.
is spreading throughout my mouth.
Sorry, everyone... I tried
risking my life to get fruits,
The meat is so tender...
Another bowl, right away!
She really is scary...
but I couldn't... I'm dead.
--Tajio...
--Yes, Chef?
On the contrary, Zoro did a great job!
Make sure you clean up in there.
Keep up that momentum and stay
up all night tonight to get more!
O-Oh, crap! My flame!
Y-Yes, sir!
Oni Giri!!
The atmospheric pressure has risen
and the rain has stopped, too.
Oh... How lovely Nami-san is, even
when she efficiently gives orders...!
Mommy and Daddy's firework...
Thanks for your work. You can rest now!
Shut up! You lecher cook!
Okay!
So that... is the Three-Sword Style...
Well then, I'll go back to work,
so watch the clouds again.
To be able to make a firework like that,
Wanna fight?! Moss Head!
Mommy and Daddy really were amazing!
I was just kidding.
You're not done yet?!
Of course not! My goal is
to draw up the world map.
Sanji-san...
I wonder if I'll be able to make
a firework like that someday.
All right, they aren't broken.
But hey, today was the first
peaceful day in a while!
I've just finished the first one.
The real work starts from here.
I think it's out there, too-- the All Blue.
Thanks for the help.
What about you? What did you
do all day today on the ship?
Mommy! Daddy! Thank you!
She's really going at it...
Roronoa Zoro!
I like Nami-san that way, too!
Me? Nothing special...
I'm deeply impressed by your skill.
Would you let us join you?
I wonder if there'll be a
100,000-Berry fine again...
We are a bounty hunting unit,
Probably...
fearsome enough by a hair
to silence a crying child,
But it was a pretty good day.
Old-timer, can I have some gunpowder?
You've been reading all this time?
I'm going to work hard,
Yosaku and Johnny.
Now, unfurl the sails!
and someday, I'll be as good
a cook as you are, Sanji-san.
You dumb jackass!
Suit yourselves.
Full speed ahead!
I don't know anything about you.
Yeah!
So, I'll leave the rest to you.
Big Bro!
Hey...
Take as much as you want!
Ah, beyond the never-ending sky
The future that I once saw
is now starting to take shape
Which direction should I run towards
to see a more wonderful tomorrow?
I took the helm and opened the
miraculous map that I stored in my heart
I aimed for the sky and sought out
my dreams, though at times I got lost
There are days where I almost lose to myself
It wasn't a dream; when I met you,
I discovered the wonderful person in me
When that happened, there was
someplace warm I could go
With just a bit of courage,
I gained something grand
Now's the time for my "wish"
to become my "pledge"
The friends I took pride in
always, without fail,
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
pushed me onwards, didn't they?
Let's sketch out the tale of the future
I'll put all my feelings
in a brand new wind now
Ah, the stars are pouring
down underneath the sky
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
A never-ending journey to be together
I'll chase after you
wherever you go, Shining ray
This unique moment...
--Hey, do you know about the Navy's curry?
--Nope.
--Hey, Luffy...
--Huh?
Say, Sanji-kun... Please! There's
something I want you to buy for me.
You're going to catch a cold dressed like that.
Let's hurry and get off this island.
Wow, fireworks are great, huh?
They truly are pretty!
It's famous. I hear that the chef on
each ship competes with all the others.
Anything for you... Uhm...
these papers cost 4.8 million Berries!
It looks like there's going to
be nothing but trouble here.
People who catch colds are people
who let their mind's guard down.
I'd like to set some off sometime.
Huh? You'll let me?
I get the same whiff from that
old-timer that I do from you.
Oh, yeah? That sounds yummy.
Well, I wonder if someone
somewhere is spreading stories
Well, I wouldn't have that
much money, though...
The kid who fell from a Navy ship
earlier says he is a probationary cook.
I'm so happy! And what's more,
you'll let me set off that huge one?!
about Zoro, the pirate hunter.
Really? Then there's nothing
to worry about, is there?
--Don't be so cold.
--That's right. We do have money.
I've never once called myself a pirate hunter.
No, that's why I'm worried!
Oh, yeah. In exchange for this
guy with a bounty on his head...
It reminds me of my time
at the sea restaurant...
Wow! Then again, isn't that one too big?
Oh, yeah?
What?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Fabled Pirate Hunter!
Zoro, the Wandering Swordsman"
"Zenny of the Island of Goats and
the Pirate Ship In the Mountains!"
"A Recipe Handed Down!
Sanji, the Iron Man of Curry"
"Uprising of the Navigator!
For the Unyielding Dream!"
"I Will Make it Bloom!
Usopp the Man and the Eight-Foot Shell"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!