A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
You're the insolent folks
It's...
who didn't pay their taxes
at the harbor, aren't you?
...a trap! A trap by the navy!
Guys!
Usopp!
"How's Tricks? The Designs
of Zenny the Moneylender!"
Dammit, dammit, dammit!
"Zenny of the Island of Goats and
the Pirate Ship In the Mountains!"
How many times do we have
to be attacked by the navy?!
Sanji!
Geez, what are you doing?!
Sail on!
If you want to survive this,
keep rowing and stop complaining!
That's the Rainbow Mist!
Impossible! A pirate ship,
coming out of the mountains?!
Old man!
We're gonna die!
After them! Don't let them escape!
"Whereabouts of the Island Treasure!
Attack of the Zenny Pirates!"
Come on, come on, can't you work harder?!
You're not out strolling around, now!
Hey, Luffy! Give us a hand!
Professor, where are we?
Here I thought they were these great pirates,
Can't you put your back into it more?!
Ape's Concert.
No, I've got no strength...
I haven't eaten since this morning...
but these fainthearted guys are
just running away, aren't they?
Old-timer, you just sit there,
quietly! We'll take care of this!
Ape's Concert? It couldn't be.
W-What's that?!
Sergeant, let's be the ones who
bring in the Straw Hat pirates!
You're hungry now?!
Here, now, Gramps, get some rest.
A ship graveyard, where once
you enter, you can never get out.
We'll bring them in, for sure!
Would you like your shoulders rubbed?
Major! Major Pasqua! Please
report to the bridge immediately!
W-What is this?
Major Pasqua!
"Residents of the Land of Eternity!
The Pumpkin Pirates!"
So, why are you
intentionally building this ship
Major Pasqua!!
up here in the mountains, old-timer?
Come on! If we don't do something,
they really will hit us!
Aah... it's because it's not a ship.
Shut up, dumbass!
I'm too hungry...
This isn't a ship?
Is that...?
Me, too...
You did it, old man!
Now, look! If this isn't a ship,
then exactly what is it?!
You only have to say so once.
Hey, don't act so reckless.
Man, these navy guys are pesky.
I-I'm terribly sorry, Major.
His heart hasn't stopped, right?
It is my... coffin.
But we're engaging the wanted
criminal Monkey D. Luffy!
Hey, cut that out!
Haven't you caught anything yet?
Old-timer! Are you okay?!
What?!
It's not a matter of catching something!
Coffin?
There isn't a single drop of water left!
Hey, look! There's nothing but
sunken ships, as far as you can see!
Yeah. That means, this will be my grave.
At this rate, we're either going
to shrivel up, or die of starvation.
You sure took your time.
L-Let's give this up. It feels like a
ghost captain might appear at any time.
I see. So this is your grave, old goat man.
You almost missed this historic encounter.
Robin-chan, it's time for afternoon tea.
Don't pray over it! You'll doom him!
I'm finally out at sea.
Hmph. Hand me the binoculars.
Really? Ghost captain!
It's still too early for this!
Would you care for some
mille-feuille, as well?
You're over-preparing!
I really have become a pirate!
Don't call to them!
Thank you, mister cook.
Could Gramps be aware
that his life is almost over?
No doubt about it.
That's Straw Hat Luffy's flag.
Beyond the Rainbow Mist
is the world of the eternal.
I want a snack, too!
Yeah! This is no longer my coffin!
The final paradise remaining on earth.
Yes, it is.
Sanji, where the hell did
you have that hidden?!
It's the good pirate ship Zenny!
Isn't that right?!
What are you so startled at?
It's filled with treasures of gold and silver,
The dumbass...
Hey! You guys keep your mitts off of this!
Living on an island like this,
where people live forever
without aging or going hungry.
We've been firing warning
shots at them for a bit,
it's not unusual that I would
make my own grave, is it?
What's with the lack of a sense of urgency?!
but they've shown no signs of stopping.
That's what's written in this book.
Way to go, old man!
I am going to die someday, after all.
Major, if you would do "it," please...
I told you, that's nothing more than a legend.
We told you, don't egg him on!
"It," huh? If you insist.
He's a sick man!
Not just "someday," it's going to be really soon.
What are you trying to pull,
Zenny the Moneylender?
Is this any time to be laughing?!
I think I will.
Professor, you knew that this
place was a ship graveyard?
Nami, this sea looks even
more alarming than the navy.
Oh, here it comes!
The major's special technique!
Your profession is to extort
money from pirates, isn't it?!
It's not unusual for a grave to
be up in the mountains, huh?
Use your navigating skills and do something!
The one that has sunk countless
pirate ships-- the Finger Bomb!
Yeah. 50 years ago, I got a
short glimpse of this place.
But why have your grave be a pirate ship?
I gave up lending money long ago.
I know!
Right now, I'm Zenny the Pirate!
More fog?
If you knew it, then why come?
O-Old man!
I told you that, too.
I've been carrying on my research
Don't you sell the navy short, you old geezer!
W-Wait, old man!
Old man, watch yourself!
He's after your treasure!
C-Coffin, or g-grave, or whatever you call it,
We might be able to use this
fog to give the navy the slip.
in order to rescue my friends that
were swallowed up in this mist.
it's almost finished!
Don't go jumping the gun!
Oh? Lately, the navy has taken to
going after treasure on the side,
I even became Wetton's dog,
But this water is moving fast.
What's more, there are reefs everywhere.
Don't die yet!
Shh... He's just sleeping.
--Huh?
--What have you done, Major?!
and put up with the
finger-pointing, to that end.
in addition to capturing pirates, have they?
That's quite industrious of you.
--What was that?
--They shooting at each other?
--Nami, bring the ship over.
--Got it. Come on, everyone.
Hey!
So, you've found the
Straw Hat pirates, have you?
Why, you! Don't give Nami-san any orders!
Look at this!
Take that, navy rats! I predicted
this would happen from the start!
Sergeant Minchy!
The Straw Hats are on the move!
Yes, sir! I believe they have
landed on a deserted island,
This region of the ocean is designated
as a class-one danger zone!
Contact Captain Moore's fleet for backup!
as I reported earlier.
When did you predict it?
Shut up!
What's this?
Pursuing them any farther is impossible!
All right! As their formation collapses,
we'll use this chance to get away!
All right, ready to attack at once!
Isn't it awesome? There's lots,
lots more inside the ship!
"Justice"
We'll storm the island with all of our forces,
Rescue the men in the water
from the sinking ship!
and bring down the Straw Hat pirates!
Every last one of them!
I'm gonna go explore some more!
I told you, I'd give you your cut of the treasure.
Hey! Are you all right?!
Whether this is a paradise or not,
Please, wait, Captain!
The Going Merry is getting farther away!
If this keeps up, we'll be wiped out!
the "being filled with treasure"
thing doesn't appear to be
Silence! We've chased them this far!
In addition to those guys
with Devil Fruit abilities,
You understand, don't you?
We can't let the captain know.
--All right!
--There's nothing right about it!
altogether untrue, huh, Professor?
We've almost got them, you know!
we'll be facing the master
swordsman, Roronoa Zoro.
--My chance at a billion
Berries... no, my promotion...
--The wheel of fortune is starting to turn, huh?
Sergeant, let's finish this now!
Withdraw. Come about at once.
The way I figure it...
--...is getting away, Major Pasqua!
--Yeah. Everything is going as history leads it.
So what if we are? Are you losing
your nerve, Sergeant Minchy?
We've got orders from Captain Moore
Attend to the wounded! The fleet is
setting course for Luluka, as scheduled!
You're keeping your men hushed
up to take on this side project.
that once we spot the Straw Hat pirates,
we are to eliminate them!
Of course not. I just want to avoid
any unnecessary casualties.
Stop pestering me!
That must cost a pretty penny,
huh, Mr. Sergeant?
Then what would you have us do?
The captain is not in command
right now. I am. Understood?
If you do as I say, Captain,
then you will achieve
"Legend of the Rainbow Mist!
Old Man Henzo of Luluka Island"
Why, you dotty old coot!
Don't think you won't pay for this!
Those who would disturb
the rest of the dead...
a complete victory with only a few casualties.
Yes, sir.
Silence, boy!
W-What's that?!
You've got some nerve,
trying to swipe my treasure!
Leave the cargo, and depart at once,
Come and take it from me, if you can!
There.
or else, the curse of the dead shall befall you!
So that's how it's gonna be, huh?
Way to go, old man!
Yum! How did you make this cheese?
Where's the navy?
Looks like we gave them the slip.
I-I'm s-scared...!
Show them how a pirate fights!
Hard aport! Pull the sail 45° to the left!
They've been chasing us pretty hard lately.
From the island goats' milk. It will
give you lots of energy, old-timer.
Who's there?
When there are two people with
prices on their heads aboard,
Though at this point, it'll be
just a drop in the bucket.
There they are!
you can't blame the navy for going all-out.
We're out of the fog.
Okay, Gramps, it's your turn.
Hey, an island! I see an island!
Let's see... There, checkmate. That's the game.
"Nico Robin 79 million Berries"
Now, hand over the cargo, nice and easy...
"Monkey D. Luffy
30 million Berries
(actually 100 million Berries)"
I wonder if it has something to eat!
"Roronoa Zoro
(actually 60 million Berries)"
Or else...
Wait a minute!
No waiting allowed, Nami-chan!
Luffy...
Y-You got me. In return, play me again?
That was close! You rotten...
Watch yourself. It looks like there are
lots of hidden reefs under the waves.
--There!
--You idiot!
All right. Nothing beats playing
chess against a beauty like you,
What are you doing...?
while getting my shoulders rubbed!
Ghost captain...!
Why, you...!
If you're a pirate, then you won't mind
it when the navy kills you, right?!
We took in a great catch today!
Six people and one animal...
Come to think of it, does the old
man have any sort of weapon?
Sanji, make the old goat man
something yummy again, would you?
Doesn't matter how many
of you damn pirates there are.
--There's a harbor!
--What?! A harbor?!
There's nothing inside!
Yeah, I'm on it.
Just you watch this...
Show me what you've got! Take on
my class 10-ranked abacus skills!
Look! You can see the lighthouse!
They're... ghosts... all... right...!
Old man, if there's anything else
you want to eat, or have us do,
A harbor, huh? Which means
there'll be something to eat!
Get them!
don't be afraid to speak up, okay?
We'll do whatever we can!
But that arrow came from over there.
His abacus and...
Nah, I can die happy now.
What?
...the goats.
Maybe it's uninhabited.
Huh? It's not a lighthouse.
Luffy! Over there!
I'm in paradise... paradise...
What?! Oh, no!
That sure is a tall tower, huh?
There's someone over there!
Hey, listen to me, Luffy!
Don't say that!
Old man!
Even if the way ahead is short...
Who cares? Let's go get
some food to eat! Food!
Luffy, I say!
...you've gotta live with a positive view!
All right. Just wipe off that drool.
--A goat?
--M-Meat!
For as long as you live!
Oh, a bow.
That idiot! Luffy!
Meat! Meat! Meat! Meat!
Hey, doesn't it seem strange?
--What?
--The old man's only supposed
to have three days to live, right?
What are you guys, idiots?
What are you shooting at?!
Luffy! Watch out!
You there, hold up!
You shouldn't waste your
bullets like that! I'm right here!
That's right. Three days.
On the island of Luluka,
all ships that moor at our harbor,
Only three days to live.
Hold on! I don't care how hungry you are,
Let's go!
That's just the briefest moment, isn't it?
Luffy...!
or even along our rocks,
you can't just go after that cute little goat!
Why, you...!
must pay harbor dues!
Indeed it is. In just the briefest
moment, three days have gone by.
Harbor dues?
Apparently, the cute little goats
have taken a liking to us.
Whatever it is, we have to pay them money.
Special attack: Fire Star!!
Hey, why should we have to
pay a tax just for docking here?
You're right.
What are you doing?! They're goats!
You're taking on goats!
So then, how is it that
he's still alive and kicking?
It's because they're goats
that I can't do it, Sergeant.
Because it's your duty! Will you pay, or not?!
More than that, he's healthier
than he was before, isn't he?
Hey! The battle has already begun!
Hey...
More cheese.
Stop watching the goings-on from
on high, and come on down here!
It's a trap! We've fallen into their trap!
Don't talk like that to a lady.
Old-timer, here's today's medicine.
What?!
What's this?
We have no choice!
Make sure you take it.
--Akibi!
--Wait, Rongo!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Don't cut them, Zoro!
I don't need that anymore. It makes
all the food taste bad, after all.
These guys aren't bad! I can tell that much!
Food!
We know. Stand aside for a minute.
--Akibi!
--Take it easy, Rongo!
Food! Food! Food! Food! Food!
Relax, Chopper!
There, checkmate!
But...
Not again!
The old-timer is in no physical shape
to be doing anything so crazy!
Oh, you're just kids, aren't you?
That bastard...
Tabasco Star!!
I thought the old guy wasn't supposed to live
Are you all right?
Rongo!
for more than three more days.
Yes! I'm completely fine!
From the way he looks, he seems
good for another 30 years.
Akibi!
Come on, let's go. I want to get some
blank charts to draw some maps.
The goat kicked it back.
You idiot, stay away! Run!
Usopp!
You misdiagnosed him, huh?
I'll accompany you, Nami-san!
No. That can't be right.
I-I'm coming, too!
Wait! We're not going to eat
you or anything! I promise!
Still, if I did misdiagnose him,
that wouldn't be so bad, right?
--J-Just a minute! I'm coming, too! Me too!
--Hey, you there!
Gum-Gum...
That's not the issue here. If this is how it is,
...I'm Home!!
--Shoot them!
--Don't shoot!
But why did you all set a trap for us?!
then no matter what anyone else says,
I'm leaving the island.
Yo, thank you for that earlier.
You're welcome.
Yeah. This is no place for me to be
forever kissing up to that old man.
Huh? They were ordered by somebody to do it!
There's something I need to ask you.
Rongo!
A new kind of clown?
Somebody who?
I want to have some adventures at sea, too.
He might be a swindling salesman.
Now you've done it!
My boys are out of control!
Then, that settles it.
I'm neither one!
Stop!
Nami, we're setting sail!
That's enough!
You idiot! Keep out of the way!
Have you seen a rainbow-colored mist?
C-Can you wait a little while longer?
Watch out!
How long are you gonna goof around?
Quit playing chess, already.
Charge!
We are the Pumpkin Pirates,
and Ape's Concert is our territory!
Huh? Rainbow-colored mist?
Stop it!
I can't quit playing! I've lost so many times,
Ah, it's no use. He's an idiot.
Release my friends, and turn over
the cargo, if you want to live!
You're labeling me?
I ended up pawning the ship to Gramps here.
Hey, just a minute!
What kind of attitude is that,
after asking me a question?!
What?!
Hey, look! They're waiting for us in formation!
A bomb?
I wonder if you might tell me about it.
What are pirates who have lost
their ship supposed to do?!
Rapa Nui!
It's strange how they don't show
any signs of movement, huh?
Could it be...?
I'll get it back for sure, just wait!
I-It's a monster!
Hey, now, if you use that, you'll blow us all up!
We have to think up a battle
plan now, while we can.
Checkmate.
A weird old man fell out of there.
So, what shall we do?
Be the first ones to attack them?
We're all in the same boat!
We live, and die, together!
Stop, already!
Pops, hit me again!
Chopper, is this the man who
gave the goats their orders?
Earthquake!
Coming up! One more special!
If you keep this up, there's no
telling what else will be signed away!
--Don't be crazy!
--In any case...!
Another for me, too!
How about it?
Here's your special.
Right now, we have to
help the old-timer! Hurry!
They say yes.
If you want your ship back,
Hey, you've got money for this, right?
you'll just have to work here on
the island for as much as it's worth.
By the way, did we hit something a minute ago?
Oh, he's paying.
He must have thought we
were here to attack him.
--Let's go.
--I'm sorry, Rapa Nui. Rongo!
Whoa, I am?!
--Huh? Did we?
--Never mind! Hurry!
I'm telling you the secrets of the
Rainbow Mist. Of course you are.
Don't worry. We just want
some water and provisions.
By my reckoning, in total,
you'll have to work for ten years.
Captain Moore, there's no response
from Sergeant Minchy's ship.
Rapa Nui...? Is that you, Rapa Nui...?
How can I trust anything a pirate says?!
I'm not the one who asked you!
How's tricks with you?
What was that sound of
gunfire we heard earlier?
I'm telling you right now, there's no
treasure on this island, got it?!
Shall we advance?
And... Isoka, and Rongo... It's you, all right...
My name is Henzo.
No, not yet. Wait for Minchy to report in.
I am penniless!
--Nami-san!
--Nami!
I'm a genius, repeat, genius scientist
researching the Rainbow Mist.
You don't look very rich, in any case.
I'm sorry. I thought that if I got lucky,
Don't you know me? It's me, Henzo!
Where did you guys go?
Damn pirates! If that's how you
want it, I'll be a man about it!
I could get Gramps to tell
us where his treasure is.
We always used to play together,
on Cape Luluka!
You can't call yourself a genius.
Simmer me, bake me, do whatever you will!
Anyone who calls themselves
that is no honest fellow.
Are you still going on about that?
Henzo?!
Mister Henzo...
Oh, really? I'm a cook.
Simmering and baking are my specialty.
At this point, we'll have to leave
the old man, and run away.
You know them?
Call me "professor."
Enough out of you, already!
--That's all there is to it.
--Not me.
Henzo? You don't mean that Henzo!
Hey!
Wait! Wait! I was just joking!
You fiend! You scoundrel! You killer!
Professor, do you know this book?
What are you talking about, Luffy?
You idiot, there's no way...
It's a good thing for us that
Zoro noticed it, or we might have
Is that...?
That's enough of that!
I came across it in Alabasta.
Stay back! I-I'll blow us up! Stay back, I said!
spent the rest of our lives on this
island working for that old man!
So that's it. I thought I heard about
the Rainbow Mist somewhere before,
All right!
Would you figure it out, too?!
S-Stop!
but it turns out it's the name of
the book you're reading, Robin.
You can't have any adventures
around here, Luffy. Let's go.
I don't know who the author is,
--Nope.
--Luffy!
He's gone limp.
but the book was written over 40 years ago.
A stake is something like a promise, right?
The old man's grit is amazing,
but he's pretty fainthearted.
If so, I don't want to break any promises.
According to the book, the Rainbow
Mist is the garden of the gods,
Kaboom Mark III. I invented it, after all.
This is no time to think about appearances!
Oh, no! His heart has stopped!
or perhaps El Dorado.
Zoro, what do you say?
It's recorded as being the
entrance to the City of Gold.
It's just a gizmo used for bluffing.
--Zoro!
--You ogre!
The captain is the one to decide, right?
--How cruel!
--Mossy.
Luffy!
That's nothing more than a legend.
Now, hold on, it's not like that!
I said no, and I mean no.
Where's all that energy you had a moment ago?
Many adventurers have
been enticed by the legend,
Checkmate.
Zenny the Pirate, are you out of breath?
I'm a doctor! Let's hurry and
take the old man to his house!
and set off on a journey
to find the Rainbow Mist,
Hey, you've finally come forward,
you little miscreant.
T-That's...
but not a single one of them has returned.
Looks like we can get the ship back, huh?
Damn, it's a smokescreen!
You sure are a talkative bastard!
Yes, including my own friends.
What's all the racket...?
How about it, Gramps?
You're just now waking up?!
Huh? For that matter, who's the old guy?
You got me...
I was very nearly killed out there.
Hooray!
Well, it would take a bit of
time to explain it to you.
We can always count on you, Big Sister!
So that's why you're researching the mist.
You really can't drop your
guard around a pirate.
Now then, shall we get down to business?
How's tricks with you?
Sir...
Listen to you! You fainted all on your own.
Where is your treasure located,
Zenny the Pirate?
Just fine, thanks.
You'd best not take what
he has to say at face value.
Old goat man, did your
heart stop out of shock?
Hey, they're gone from over here, too.
Who was that just now?
How do you mean?
Here in the Grand Line,
there must be surprises every day.
I've lived for many years,
but I've never seen pirates
He's one of Mayor Wetton's dogs.
as interesting as you are. I really like you.
Dogs?
I'm surprised you've lasted this long,
with that faint heart of yours.
Yeah! He receives research
funding from the mayor,
Huh, Pops?
Big party tonight!
and lives the easy life! He's a flimflam scientist!
That's the truth!
Yeah, a feast, to celebrate
us getting the ship back!
Still, we're glad that you're life isn't in danger.
What's there to be glad about?!
What, Corporal?!
You've already scared the hell
out of me, and nearly got me killed.
Why didn't you report this sooner?!
I'm terribly sorry, Captain Moore.
What's more, now I can't chop
firewood, or draw any water.
T-The tax collection squad!
The tax collection squad is here!
Gramps, you're just like a great pirate.
I'm out a whole bunch, here!
--What's that?
--Hey, hurry and drink that!
What a sneaky stunt to pull!
That miserable Minchy...
Altogether, I've lost 50,000,000 Berries!
You can really put it away.
Nami-chan, are you calling me a pirate?
So that was what he was up to!
You're overcharging, aren't you?
At the most, it should be this much.
If you weren't, you wouldn't have
such first-rate glasses, after all.
Now you're being stingy!
Even with a huge discount, it's this.
They are indeed treasure-class, huh?
Why don't you spit it out, already?
You don't want to die yet, do you?
If you subtract Chopper's
consultation fee, it's this.
Ah! Nami, you're trying
to get the old man drunk,
Well, well, good citizens,
to find out where he keeps his treasure, huh?
All you young folks ganging up
to pick on an old man like me...!
are you having an enjoyable mealtime?
I do value my own life. I cherish it.
Don't spell it out for him!
Old goat man, do you really have a treasure?
You're heartless!
Henzo! Hurry on down!
We're not picking on you!
Let me tell you, I'm penniless.
What do you want me to spit out?
You there, you're drinking
some delicious liquor, yes?
I just said, don't go talking so openly!
Ah, I can't go on anymore!
I-I'm too scared!
When you drink liquor, you need to
pay the liquor-drinking tax, right?
Don't cry.
Don't be afraid over something
like this! We're the Pumpkin Pirates!
Some things do have their proper order!
I can't even manage any spittle.
All right, old goat man.
My treasure...
We'll chop your wood
and draw your water for you.
H-H-Hey, wait a minute!
Fine, then.
...is what I have shared
my joys and sorrows with
You're the reasonable sort,
aren't you, my straw-hatted lad?
A-All I've got in my wallet is my
wife and kids' living expenses!
ever since washing up on
this island-- the island goats.
As dinky an island as this is,
We have a deal.
It is a citizen's obligation to pay taxes.
it won't take much work to dig
it up from one end to the other.
What a great story!
Gotcha!
That old guy sure did seem
to dislike pirates, huh?
Those who neglect their obligations
have no right to live in this town.
Don't just say "gotcha," tell us what you mean!
Do you think he has
some grudge against them?
Who is this guy?
Okay, here's what it means.
They say the old man is
the only person on the island,
I have no further need of you.
Mayor Wetton's son, Flip.
For all the great pirates,
who traveled the Grand Line, I am...
and that it's been 20 years since
he washed up here from somewhere.
A disagreeable bastard, who extorts
all sorts of tax money out of us.
When I grow up, I'm gonna be a real pirate.
I knew it!
Why, you...!
...the moneylender who dealt with them.
20 years?!
But Rapa Nui, your father is a marine, right?
You're through!
We've met someone like that before, huh?
Moneylender?
Well, well, Professor Henzo...
Yeah. I'm Zenny the Moneylender,
not the Pirate!
Is he going to let you?
Father was looking for you.
Oh, where are you going, Zoro?
My pop is my pop.
You're not?
That's too bad, huh, Nami?
Huh? I'm going to go look
for something to eat.
He was wondering how
your mist research is coming.
I want to have adventures in places
that nobody has seen before!
Still, you must have some nerve,
lending money to pirates,
I doubt the old man is going
to share anything with us.
Same as always.
I seem to have broken your abacus.
Sorry about that.
Places nobody has seen before?
There's no telling when or where
the mist is going to appear, after all.
don't you, old man?
Oh, right! In that case, get some meat!
What the hell are you doing?!
Sure. There are still lots of things in
this world that nobody knows about.
Why's that?
Well, doesn't he? Do you think
pirates usually borrow money,
You think you can defy the
navy and get away with it--
Don't ask for too much!
My, my. Your research is supported
by the citizens' tax money.
then pay it back? Not to mention the interest.
I want to see them, too.
Me, too. I'll be a pirate, too.
That's right. You can bet everyone
bilked me out of their debts.
The Rainbow Tower over there was
constructed based on your research.
Put your back into it more!
Old-timer!
But we'll have to fight with
other pirates, too, right?
Can't you youngsters even
chop wood right these days?
You guys are late! I almost died, here!
Every damn one of those
pirates broke their word,
Do not forget that the
slower your research goes,
Someone as weak as I am couldn't do that.
Waah! I was so worried!
the more it puts everyone here out.
Henzo, you can invent all
sorts of things, can't you?
and betrayal was second nature to them.
I thought so. This cleaning is no good.
Smoke Star!!
You'll invent the gear that
we'll need for our adventures.
So Gramps, it's true that you hate pirates, huh?
Well, I will see you later.
Do this over, here!
That's far enough!
After that, get some grass to
the island goats, and fix the hut!
If I would've just sat back
and taken it from them,
Robin, this is where you were?
Hey, yeah!
Okay, I'll be a pirate, too!
my business would have been wiped out.
Old man, you can relax,
now that Captain Usopp is here--
Ah, I'm so tired... Don't just
stand there, rub my shoulders!
You're easy to convince, Henzo!
Well, well...
What happened? That bump is huge!
You there, you're eating a
heaping plate of spaghetti, yes?
Every time I went out to collect on a debt,
You might pay me a little mind,
without me having to tell you everything.
There's no pulse!
I had to fight against pirates,
Mm-hmm, I was hungry.
You people really are so
much trouble. After that...
Calm down, Chopper. I'm over here, over here.
at the risk of my own life.
I knew that! Here, take it easy, and lie down.
There's more?
Eating a heaping plate means that
you must pay a heaping tax, right?
We were so happy.
Playing as friends, and chatting...
That's a business where you have to be
Don't you die, old-timer!
He's paying.
stronger than the pirates, isn't it?
Damn it, which way is north,
and which way is south?
I am?!
You think I would die?
I spent the best days of my life with them.
Old goat man, were you that strong?
Every day was so bright,
it doesn't even compare to treasure.
I don't mean to brag, but I was weak.
But then, I had a dream.
What's that?
Why me, for pete's sake?
A dream?
--Aah, thanks.
--Cram it!
Until that one dreadful event occurred...
How are you feeling, old man?
You did, Gramps?
That's...
I feel fine, of course. I'm finally a pirate.
Now you understand.
If you don't want the people
in town to think ill of you,
I don't feel like dying anymore.
then stop hanging around with Henzo.
Thanks for the warning.
But that's not up to me to decide.
It's up to the captain.
Henzo!
What?
Pay back the money?
We just came to the island
on the sergeant's orders.
Henzo! Are you all right?!
I finally made it back.
I'm the man they call Zenny the Moneylender!
Yeah... well, I guess subordinates
can't go against their superiors.
Are you guys still at it?
I'd rather see you in hell than
have you run out on your debt.
That old-timer has been pushing
work on us, one job after another.
I've perfected the Kaboom Mark III!
Listen, our captain is pretty
capricious himself, you know?
We're all worn out.
Shall we head to the underworld together?
I'm so hungry...
W-Wait, Zenny! Here!
You don't say.
You idiot! Don't scare us like that!
Hey, don't go getting too chummy.
How's tricks? Well, goodbye.
You sure do have a lot of false alarms, huh?
Oh, no you don't! You give us pirates our due!
A pirate ship?
The ship was run down, but it
was definitely a pirate ship.
O-Old man, are you okay?
A-Are you still shopping?
Oh, but I am.
Who made it?
Of course.
Holy crap! The town is on fire!
Are you okay, lad?
The old guy is the only one here.
I have to buy some blank charts.
Why would the old-timer build a pirate ship?
If we run out while we're
at sea, we'll be in trouble.
Good grief, there's just no helping Luffy!
The town of Luluka is on fire!
Zenny! How dare you?!
How should I know?
You sure are buying a lot of
unrelated stuff, considering.
Your seizure has passed, so that's a relief, huh?
We just might be in luck here.
Much obliged!
Much obliged, Dr. Chopper.
Nami-san, I'd follow you into the
depths of hell to go shopping with you!
In any event, let's go have a look.
I may have been weak, but I had a dream,
Sorry about that. Old man, how's tricks?
You say it's at the top of the mountain?
so I fought desperately for it.
No, I managed to fight for it.
--What is this...?
--Our town...
Let's go see!
Old man, what was your dream?
There they are, Lake-sama! They're the ones!
Whoa, there's no need to run, right?
Just fine, thanks.
Ever since I was a kid, I wanted to be a pirate.
Hey, wait! It'll take too long
to get there starting now!
Dad! Mom!
You're the insolent folks
A real pirate. The king of the pirates.
Ah, right. Listen, Gramps,
you can tell us now, can't you?
who didn't pay their taxes
at the harbor, aren't you?
Rongo!
You're right.
That's why I first started
in the moneylending trade.
Damn, it was this close, in a straight line?
About your treasure?
But instead, I got hit with a sneak
attack by some damn pirates,
It seems creepy somehow, doesn't it?
Hey! Don't go giving any shocks to my patients!
taking their anger out on me,
I am Mayor Wetton's grandson, Lake!
Like a ghost ship in the mountains, huh?
and I ended up being washed
ashore for dear life on this island.
Old-timer, stay strong!
Burn! Burn!
Robin, don't say anything like that.
I'm the officer who seizes
unpaid taxes from the insolent!
Leave nothing of value!
That was 20 years ago now, was it?
For the love of...
Kill everyone that opposes us,
the Wetton Pirates! Got it?!
Have you been making that grave for 20 years?
Yeah, I guess you have done a lot for me,
I'm not exactly sure what's going on here,
What are those?
but if you're here to throw cold water
on our enjoyable little shopping trip,
Spirits of the dead! Didn't I tell you so?!
At first, I planned to build
the ship near the sea,
so maybe I can tell you.
Show the women and children no mercy!
They're fireflies!
you'll get no mercy.
but bringing the lumber down from
the mountain was too much for me.
That's more like it! Look,
the navy knows about it, and all,
so it must be an amazing treasure, right?
So, I didn't give up, no matter what,
but built it up in the mountains.
I did... have a treasure...
He used lumber from the local trees.
I had a hell of a dream I couldn't
calculate with my abacus.
The pirates who owed me signed over
a whole heap of treasure to me.
But it looks like he stopped midway through.
A hell of an adventure!
The old guy really did this?
Pirates!
But somewhere along the way,
my eyes were opened.
But then, thinking of buying a pirate ship,
and getting my pals together,
What's this, there are still some kids
who haven't run away, are there?
It doesn't look like it's here.
Before I knew it, I was too old
to set sail for the Grand Line.
Sanji!
What's not here, Nami?
Geez, what are you doing?!
I exchanged all of it for cash.
Treasure.
T-The moment I touched
his body, I got a shock.
Treasure?
Listen, guys, once we get to the harbor,
there will be ships there.
Cash!
If my guess is correct, that old man is,
in actual fact, a former pirate!
Thinking back on it, that's when my fate turned.
So much for my dream of being a pirate.
It's no use. That's what happens
to everyone who touches me.
We'll take one of them, it doesn't
matter which one, and get out of here.
A pirate?
But what about Dad, and the others?!
Dreams are just dreams, after all.
I told you last night that I was
attacked by those who had owed
--Electricity?
--I get it.
You idiot! Do you wanna get killed?!
He probably got shipwrecked,
He has the abilities of a Devil Fruit!
Go!
and I'll bet he's the only one
who made it to this island.
money to me, and I ended up
drifting ashore on this island, right?
Why did you give up, old goat man?
And so, he was building this
pirate ship to get off the island.
Well, naturally, I managed
to protect the money.
Age doesn't have anything to do with it.
After all, I'd risked my life for that
money in order to buy my dream.
Your own private generator?!
If you want to become a pirate,
then you should do it.
Yeah, but a former pirate disliking pirates
Dynamo Squad, increase output!
doesn't make any sense, does it?
Hey, now, Luffy,
That's just simple camouflage,
what are we going to do if the
old man takes you seriously?
to keep us from finding
the treasure he's hidden.
--Pirates need a ship,
--Sanji, give me another.
--Coming up.
Those brats...
When I came to, after
washing up on the beach...
--and the old man's ship is
a coffin in the mountains.
--Thank you.
I thought he was shady, right from the start.
So we just have to bring it down, don't we?
Somehow, this doesn't look good, does it?
Remember that furniture in the old man's hut?
Don't say it like it's so simple!
Yeah... there's still time...
He had some pretty valuable
things together there.
Have a good taste of the power
of my electroshock suit!
There, you see? The old man
is taking you seriously!
That's my Nami-san! Very astute!
No he's not. You're just drunk,
aren't you, Gramps?
The ships...!
Rolling Thunder!!
That can't be right.
--It was eaten?!
--Really?!
Those guys earlier must have sunk them!
There's no way that fainthearted
old man was once a pirate.
All of it?! They ate all of it?!
Yeah, I'm drunk, I'm drunk!
Over there! We'll get on that one!
That's right. Well, maybe
they left two or three bills.
Yeah, but he might have been
a famous pirate long ago.
Oh, he is?
Eh? That one?
This straw-hatted lad has got
me absolutely intoxicated!
There aren't any others, right? Hurry!
Huh? Was that thunder?
And above all else, there's this ship.
All right! Here's looking forward to the day
And so, like I told you,
these guys are my treasure.
There's a dense forest ahead, with no paths...
when the Zenny Pirates set sail!
...and a steep cliff to the rear.
That was close!
What are you doing to my ship?!
Nicely dodged. But that
won't happen this time!
All of my fortune may have been lost,
If he's going to build a boat to escape on,
Can we really do this?
but in return, I gained my friends.
why do it up here in the mountains?
Lure the Straw Hat pirates off
the island, all by ourselves?
Here he comes!
They don't betray me, or try to cheat me.
Chopper, look after Nami-san.
Why, Nami?
No matter how strong they might be,
Got it!
Now, I have friends at my side,
W-Well...
they're still a bunch of greenhorn kids.
Sanji-kun, don't do anything reckless, okay?
who don't do anything for selfish motives.
Damn it!
Depending on how this is done,
we have nothing to fear from them.
Yes, don't worry about me!
And so, I want to reward them for it.
It's not as though I'm going
to fight them. Now, just watch.
Uh-uh, those are what I'm worried about.
I've obtained the greatest
treasure in the world.
Oh, these?
Is the captain going to be able
to take the Straw Hat pirates?
S-She's the devil.
Good for you, old man.
Ker-splash!
It's all right. Not only will they not
get hurt, they won't even get dusty.
Why did you turn back?
A danger zone, you say?
That isn't any of my concern.
"Justice"
Yeah, it is good. I'm a man that
takes advantage of every situation.
While the bigwigs are off fighting for justice,
Do you think you can fear those,
and still preserve the navy's justice?!
we'll just be taking away the treasure.
You've got a real outrageous mayor here.
You all are ready to answer for this, right?
What a load of crap! Hey, Straw Hat!
This fight isn't over yet!
Corporal, I'm going to put you to work, as well.
He takes money from everywhere,
and says it's for taxes.
I'm terribly sorry. But it
won't be possible for them
And I will reward you handsomely.
Where does he get off calling it
a heaping tax? What a rip-off!
Y-Yes, sir.
to get out of that danger
zone so easily, either.
There's a pristine fleet over
there just waiting for you!
Sorry... everyone...
They couldn't have gotten too far away.
Don't think you're going to get away so easily!
Even Smoker, and Hina,
leader of the Black Cage Unit,
What are you apologizing for, Pops?
Don't go trying to act cool
when you're rolling around.
Didn't you listen to what
those guys were saying?
What is he, stupid?
let the Straw Hat pirates slip away from them,
Age doesn't have anything to do with it, huh?
Nope, not a bit.
You're the stupid ones!
All right, Pops here is in league
with those rip-off artists.
but we will stop them at
my hand, no matter what!
Do you think you can stand up
to a fleet of nine ships?!
Hurry, up there!
He went and said something to
make an old man like me dream.
They will be of no matter, once they
are within your grasp, Captain.
Everyone's money is being wasted,
on account of his weird research.
That straw-hatted lad is a nefarious boy.
Begin a search at once! Go locate
where the Straw Hat pirates are!
I'm not running away.
Do you really understand what's going on?
You think someone like you
can handle this axe?
--You're right.
--Robin-chan?
--Nope, not a bit.
--Look, Luffy, you've got your snails, right?
Tell them that if they want a fight,
to come straight at me.
Yes, sir!
--Nope, not at all.
--Hey, what's going on?
Don't get too cocky, kid.
--Uh, Captain...
--Let's go, Corporal.
Our captain also rescues people
who want to die, without asking them,
It's a ship! A galleon is arriving in the harbor!
Gum-Gum...
Yes, sir.
I'm not a kid! I'm Rapa Nui,
the leader of the Pumpkin Pirates!
and lets them live.
Hey, Luffy! A little bit higher!
--A galleon?
--I-It couldn't be...!
Are you glad he let you live?
Okay!
Sounds interesting! Let's go see!
Indeed... I'm not quite sure about that yet.
--Rapa Nui!
--It's all right! He's just one man!
Hey, wait, Luffy!
...Pistol!!
Why didn't you report
that island to the captain?
You're not sorry he did.
Let's all join our forces together,
and defeat him!
You saw it, too?
I can tell by your face. Robin-chan,
your life is just getting started.
Okay, direction is good.
Yes. I saw the island, not recorded
anywhere in that area of the sea.
Huh? Captain, are we setting sail already?
There's another one!
Let's keep that from the captain
for a little while. Got it?
But me... my dream will
remain at rest here, forever.
Ooh, it's huge!
Why? The Straw Hat pirates
are probably on that island.
You... disgrace to the navy!
It's quite an old ship, huh?
It's the Talielisin.
Huh? Who are you guys?
Allow me to let you in on something.
The Tali--? W-What? H-Hey, Pops!
The one who put down
Crocodile in Alabasta was...
--Take him away!
--Yes, sir!
What's the matter?!
Bad news! Everyone, wake up!
Yes, sir, Captain Smoker, hero of the navy.
You're such a dumbass.
I sure slept good. Time for breakfast?
This is Naval Captain Moore.
That turns out to be the official
statement, nothing more.
The navy! The navy is here!
That's awesome!
What?!
I have no interest in the island,
or in this man Zenny.
Then, who exactly was it?
What is that?!
Those Straw Hat pirates, apparently.
Cool!
My only goal is to bring you down,
in the name of justice.
The Rainbow Mist!
If we took those guys on,
Just one ship?
Slick! Awesome! I want one! I totally want one!
Hey, hurry and turn the helm!
They don't look like they're
about to attack, either.
no matter how many lives
we had, it wouldn't be enough.
If we get swallowed up inside there,
we won't be able to get back!
To show my gratitude for turning over
this misguided member of my fleet,
Yeah, knowing you, I knew you'd say that.
But, sir...
What on earth is it doing here?
The helm is busted!
Hey, don't believe everything
you hear from the higher-ups.
Hey, Straw Hat pirates!
I will allow you to choose where we fight.
I am Sergeant Minchy,
of the navy. It's a pleasure.
If we were to fight them head-on,
they'd wipe us out like it was nothing.
Why, you... You'll pay for this!
Come, bring your ship out.
A pleasure?
Rolling...
Listen, I'm terribly sorry about the other day.
Akibi!
Don't think you're getting
out of here alive anymore.
We were thinking of leaving pretty soon, too.
Never mind them, I need you to give
me a hand with something, Corporal.
If we had known better
who we were dealing with,
We'll be coming toward you right away.
we wouldn't have chased you around like that.
It's no use!
You need a hand?
I hope you accept our apologies.
Strange, isn't it? It's only natural
for the navy to chase pirates.
Here, old man, I fixed it for you.
Oh, I should have known. Much obliged.
--Sanji!
--Shopping bags!
He's being unusually hospitable.
Watch yourselves.
Don't mention it.
T-That's just stupid... I dodged it...
Let's get off this island, right away.
Everything is all set up through
supper. You just have to cook it.
Akibi!
P-Please! Don't get upset!
I understand that you're the ones
If this keeps up, that funny old man
Yeah, much obliged.
Your shoulder's dislocated.
is just going to keep slave-driving us.
who defeated Crocodile
back in Alabasta, aren't you?
You're the stupid one!
Rapa Nui!
--I'm staying here.
--Luffy?
Then again, lads, are you sure about this?
Sanji, it's the metal!
I wouldn't think of fighting
against pirates as great as you are!
The valuables are drawing
the electricity! Get rid of them!
You'll pay for that!
I want to eat! I can't fill up on just this stuff!
You're facing a fleet of nine ships, right?
Believe me. I mean, if we meant to attack you,
No!
Don't worry about it.
They were expensive!
I'm not just strong, I'm lucky, too.
You know what will happen
if you drop them, don't you?!
Ah! It's all gone!
would we come here with only one ship?
Why, you...!
What do you know?
The guy is afraid of us, isn't he?
Yeah, but... after taking an
electric current as strong as that,
Henzo!
--I had to go out looking for that food!
--For the time being, let's head back to the ship.
I can't keep up with you, lad.
a normal person would already be--
Henzo!
He's not normal, so no problem!
Old-timer, I made up a whole supply for you,
Even assuming we did risk
our lives to fight you,
Ah, Chopper, we're going back to the ship.
Go back! Turn the ship back!
so make sure you take your medicine.
it wouldn't earn us a single penny.
I'm going to stay by the old man's side.
We can't! The helm is busted!
This is bad... If my striking attacks
are completely useless...
Promise me!
So, what are you doing here?
Yeah, all right, all right. I'll make
sure I take it, don't you worry.
I can't just abandon one
of my patients, after all.
The Rainbow Mist... The Rainbow Mist...!
Oh, we're just here to investigate the island.
But he's gotten better. If you feel
sorry for him, there'll be no end to it.
It's a newly discovered island
that doesn't appear on our maps.
Rapa Nui!
Investigate? There's just an old
man and his island goats here.
Go on! Keep going! Don't worry about me!
There will be an end.
--He's running!
--Hey, hold it!
--Ah, Lake-sama!
What do you mean?
Now that you mention it,
where did the old guy go?
--It's been fun, Gramps!
--Take care.
Henzo!
An end?
I promise, I'll come after you later!
That old man's heart didn't
stop just because he's timid.
Now, while we can!
I see. Then Zenny is being
safely cared for here, isn't he?
--Hold on to my shopping bags tight!
--Right!
Guys, you take care of the old-timer!
I am a member of the
Pumpkin Pirates, after all!
If they're that important, why
don't you carry them yourself?
He's sick.
Zenny?
We'll see you later, out on the seas somewhere!
So by "there will be an end," you mean...?
Once our survey is done, we're
planning to return to our base.
--Is that wrong?
--No...
Yeah! Once I finish repairs to the ship,
I'm going to be setting sail!
There's no doubt about it.
That old man only has three days left.
Henzo...
You'd best set sail on out
of here as soon as you can.
Rapa Nui! Isoka!
What?
I wouldn't blame you.
Three days, you say?
Rongo! Pukau!
We'll be waiting for you, Zenny Pirates!
Naval headquarters is in a frenzy
to eliminate you guys, after all.
Ever since...
Akibi!
Everyone! Everyone!
Ever since, Rapa Nui and
the others have never returned.
So that's it. Sounds like
this is our chance, as well.
I'll go get the food.
Have to call Robin down, too.
To think that they actually
became pirates in a place like this...
I sure slept well.
Now, let's head back to
the island for a bit, shall we?
That smells good.
We have to fix the ship.
Yeah, but that happened 50 years ago, right?
--Good morning, old-timer!
--Breakfast is ready.
All right, everyone off. We're going back.
They were still just little kids.
Hey, Pops!
W-What is all this?!
It's...
The passage of time within the
Rainbow Mist appears to be different.
Gum-Gum...
Sanji is a noted cook, so this is delicious!
...a trap! A trap by the navy!
...Rocket!!
The island goats told me where the fruit is,
Y-Your arm...!
One day in here might be equivalent to a week,
and some points where the fishing was good.
Are we setting sail, Luffy?
Pops, let me have that boat!
or even a year, in the outside world.
There's good weather past the fog.
Y-You ate a Devil Fruit...?
Come on, hurry, hurry.
The waves are gentle, and we won't,
by any means, lay a hand on you.
Nami-chan, I'm warning you,
I don't have a penny to pay with.
W-What?!
Me? I'm a rubber man,
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
If that's true, we have to
find a way out of here fast,
Come on, go ahead.
You don't have to worry about that.
I go when I want to! You don't decide when!
I can't let you have that machine, the H-1.
or there'll be no undoing the damage.
Why not?
Something's fishy here. Way too fishy for me.
You are so dense!
The same thing that happened
If I were the navy, I'd fight
desperately against us,
Eh? Don't say that, let me have it!
There's a proverb about this, you know.
between those kids earlier and the
old man could happen to us, too!
even with only one ship!
"Beware of pirates that suddenly become nice."
Besides, something else is strange!
While we're in here, puttering around,
How did you know Gramps' name was Zenny?
Nami and the others we left behind
will become old men and women!
There isn't any poison in this, is there?
It looks like there were people
here just a little while ago.
We didn't say a word about it.
How rude.
What?!
There isn't a single person
anywhere on the ship.
It's only natural to be kind
to the elderly, isn't it?
W-Well, you see...
Hey, Pops, let's go back, quick!
I'm suspicious of what kind
of survey you plan to conduct.
Like he said, we don't know how to get back!
If you don't want any, I'll eat it for you.
This ship is one that went adrift 50 years ago.
You're not, by any chance,
after Gramps' treasure, are you?
Hold on! I'm eating, I'm eating!
--What?! Is that right?!
--So, there's no way back?
That's it, huh? I don't trust this guy!
--What have you been listening to, Luffy?!
--No... There must be a way
50 years ago?!
What's the matter with you?!
Age doesn't have anything to do
with becoming a pirate, huh?
I have a hard time believing that.
--They must have said it... three times now!
--to get out of Ape's Concert.
Old-timer, are you okay?!
They've caught on, have they?
--Hey, don't startle him!
--Sorry.
About the mountain of treasure
that Zenny the Moneylender
Oh, that many times?
No doubt about it.
My word, he knows how to get
an idea in someone's head.
had signed over to him to
cover the pirates' debts?
The ship is just as it was then.
Oh, so you've eaten a
Devil Fruit, too, have you?
Whoa, what are you talking about, Pops?
I knew it! Gramps does have a treasure!
Chopper is a patient one, too.
Geez, these guys are persistent.
Yum! It truly has been a long time
since I've had anything this good.
How many years will I need to
take this whole stack of medicine?
I smell gunpowder.
That weapon is a real problem.
W-What's that?
Old-timer, if there's anything we
can do for you, just ask us, okay?
Is it that bastard's cannons?
I-It's...
You shut your traps! I'll finish you off!
It's not just one ship's cannons.
Much obliged, everyone. Very much obliged.
It's from more cannons than I can count.
My radar is reacting! I've never
had a reading this strong!
Make sure you don't leave behind any regrets.
What's that there?!
If we had set sail, we would have been caught
Thanks to you, I think I can
tough it out a little while longer.
in a sneak attack by that fleet!
Nobody asked you!
If you like this kind of food,
I'll make it for you, anytime.
Mess with us, will they?!
I don't care if they are a fleet!
After all, my life as a pirate has just begun!
--Lake-sama!
--Are you all right, Lake-sama?
You will, huh? Well, thanks.
Wow, this really is good.
--Come and get me!
--W-Wait!
That's the Rainbow Mist!
L-L-Luffy...!
Damn, I can't go out into the open
sea in the H-1! What do I do?
Usopp!
This is terribly yummy.
This goes beyond yummy!
Guys!
Are you the ones who chucked that?!
Don't move! One move, and this guy is dead!
Oh, I know!
No, not us.
--I'm borrowing this!
--What?!
For that matter, wasn't he watching?
They already had a landing
party hiding here, did they?!
Nice going, inviting them into
the foggy reef area, Luffy.
He is wearing that thing, and all.
Don't go stealing our ship!
Well done, Corporal!
If you wanna go, take the galleon!
I asked you, was it you?!
Sometimes, you do use your head, huh?
Huh? I do?
What if we say it was?
Guys, hurry and let them know!
What's the matter, old goat man?!
The Talielisin's helm is still
broken, by Wetton's hand.
--Don't tell me...!
--It's happening already?!
Wait. If they leave now,
they won't make it in time.
"I do"...? That's what I was asking you!
All right.
--Oh, no!
--Hey, stay with us!
You're picking it up?!
But what else can we do?
This is Moore's Fleet, calling any
ships sailing in this area of the sea!
W-What do you mean, Pops?
How do you know that?
At this rate, the straw-hatted
lad and the others will be...
I have collected your harbor dues.
Whew! It was so good,
I rushed through eating it,
This is Moore's Fleet!
Request immediate assistance!
and got it stuck in my throat.
This is a mess.
I now formally welcome
you as a citizen of Luluka.
Because 50 years ago,
I was aboard the Talielisin.
What do we do?
Oh, your food got stuck in your throat, did it?
Geez, you are such a moron!
Gramps, you're a pirate, right? Do something.
I wish I hadn't complimented you! I take it back!
Don't scare us like that.
What?
That's crazy! Maybe I am a pirate,
but this ship is my coffin.
I was sure it was too soon for that.
Ape's Concert, you say?
It's not like he was thinking about that, huh?
Yeah. Some soldiers said
they saw your ship enter
Too soon for what?
--It's gone!
--The Going Merry is gone!
Pure chance. He was just
pointing his finger wherever.
It's up in the mountains,
and no matter what I do...
Hold on, what's going on here?!
N-Nothing at all! He means
you're eating too quick, old-timer.
the Rainbow Mist, no doubt about it.
Those guys from earlier must
have taken it, in place of the tax!
So we just have to bring it down, don't we?
From what the mayor says, it's
piled up with treasure in there.
Never mind him, have some of mine, too.
The wind that blows down
from the mountains...!
If that's the case, it's at the harbor!
And mine, too.
Help yourself to this, too.
Damn, that mossy bastard is good for nothing!
Prepare to set sail!
By the way, ship's doctor, how is it, really?
Really?! Much obliged, much obliged!
Treasure?!
What are you standing around for?!
Men, remove the chock planks!
They say that Ape's Concert
is a ship graveyard.
Gramps' condition?
Hey, are we really going in there?
Let's go!
The shipwrecks in there have
untouched cargo all over the place.
This really is good!
That's a place many
adventures have challenged,
That medicine controls his episodes, at best.
but none have ever returned from, right?
It won't keep him from getting any worse.
Drop your weapons, or else!
The mayor is after that treasure,
which is why he has a scientist,
We're going in.
His heart was fairly weak to
begin with, and as old as he is,
This is the reason why I've kept
up my research through today.
named Henzo, researching a way
to get into Ape's Concert.
--Usopp!
--Damn it!
His appetite is on the same
level as Luffy's, isn't it?
Guys! Hurry and get out of here!
sailing on a ship, let alone as a pirate...
Ah, the old man made
this electroshock suit, too.
Scared?
They're planning to finish us
all off, one way or another!
N-N-No way am I scared! I am he
who travels all over the Grand Line,
What do you think? Pretty damn slick, isn't it?
Does he really only have three days left to live?
You keep your mouth shut!
What are you talking about?
The old man said he wanted to
be a pirate, so we should let him.
Captain Usopp!
Damn you, cowards!
This guy sure likes to talk a lot, huh?
We don't even have to wait
for the captain to land,
Besides, once the old man sets out to sea,
it's all over now. Corporal!
We're charging into the Rainbow Mist!
Shouldn't he be content
with just getting the tax?
he may find an island that
has a cure for his illness.
We can't just stand around here!
Sure enough...
Here it is, Sergeant!
We're going in into that mist, too!
You cowards!
According to the records,
there was a man who fought
Maybe.
I can handle bullets just fine.
We don't have to worry about it too much.
Yes, sir, Nami-san!
against some pirates in that
area of the sea 20 years ago,
But we can't handle them!
That old man isn't going to croak that easily.
But once we go in there,
there's no coming out!
and hasn't been seen since.
I'll take the treasure of Zenny,
What good will getting scared do?
Our treasure is waiting for us!
I remember now. He was a guy
named Zenny, or something.
His weak heart notwithstanding,
he did have plenty of guts, after all.
along with the heads of the Straw Hat pirates!
Eh?!
Zenny?
It's time to send you to hell!
The bastard wasn't the
only thing that went missing.
No one is allowed into Ape's Concert
without my permission.
He's right, Chopper. We'll see him again!
A huge treasure disappeared with him.
Supposing he made it to that island,
--Grandpa!
--You bonehead!
Sail on!
Mm-hmm, sure we will.
and even if he has already kicked the bucket...
Grandpa...?
Professor, where are we?
You've got a poor memory.
Aren't I always telling you?
I-Impossible! A pirate ship,
coming out of the mountains?!
We'll be waiting for you, Zenny Pirates!
Ape's Concert.
Treasure doesn't have a
life expectancy, does it?
Ape's Concert? It couldn't be.
Attack of the Zenny Pirates!
W-What's that?!
You are to call me "Mayor."
You've already eaten too much!
A ship graveyard, where once
you enter, you can never get out.
Old man!
I'm just getting started.
You're awesome, mister!
W-What?!
"Mayor Wetton."
Awesome!
How's tricks?
Ah, beyond the never-ending sky
The future that I once saw
is now starting to take shape
There are days where I almost lose to myself
When that happened, there was
someplace warm I could go
The friends I took pride in
always, without fail,
pushed me onwards, didn't they?
Ah, the stars are pouring
down underneath the sky
This unique moment...
Can you believe that the old man
and those kids were the same age?
How long are we going to have
to look after the old man?
Oh, nice going! I've gotta give him more credit!
I was once a pirate, just like you are.
I'm not afraid of a place like this.
An island! I see a lighthouse, too!
My, how cold.
Then they've got something to eat!
--Is this any time for admiration?!
--Yeah!
Wow, it's incredibly tall, huh?
Is that really a lighthouse?
Hey, what are you doing, Luffy?
Whether he's a pirate, or has treasure,
it's none of our business, right?
It's not a good idea to show yourself,
when you're the one they're after!
You, a pirate? Doesn't look like it to me.
I was thinking that if we get the
ship going, we can get out of here.
Never mind about that, let's hurry
and get something to eat!
Should we be doing that without Nami?!
When I was young, I firmly
believed that I could do anything.
Gramps, let me take care of the treasure!
You should embrace a more inquisitive mind.
She's probably upset
about being left behind.
Huh? Who are you, Pops?
She might be a wrinkly
old woman by now, huh?
Our pursuers from the navy
are already that close!
But that young pirate still
lives on, inside your heart.
Oh, not another weird old man!
I'm not taking care of this one!
Naughty girl...
If something is dear to you,
fight to protect it, old man!
--Oh, are you scared?
--I'm not talking to you!
Don't say anything so chilling!
Tell me your story, old-timer.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Legend of the Rainbow Mist!
Old Man Henzo of Luluka Island"
"Whereabouts of the Island Treasure!
Attack of the Zenny Pirates!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Thoughts of Home!
The Pirate Graveyard of No Escape!"
"How's Tricks? The Designs
of Zenny the Moneylender!"
"Residents of the Land of Eternity!
The Pumpkin Pirates!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!