Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
These are just in the way.
--There it is...
-- "Cat Burglar"...
I'm not that great at the
One-Sword Style, but...
Let's go, Butchie!
Okay! Let's do it, Siam!
Damn it! If I just had another sword!
If I can just get Zoro his swords...
What do you need swords for?
"Luffy, Back in Action!
Miss Kaya's Desperate Resistance"
To think that these brats
have held you back...
How the Black Cat Pirates have fallen...
Right... Jango?!
B-B-But... you said letting that kid
go wouldn't cause any problems!
Yes, I did say that.
But so what? We knew he was
going to try to stand up to us.
The only thing I didn't count on...
...was you guys' feebleness!
U-Us, feeble?
Who're you calling feeble?!
Watch what you say, Captain Kuro!
Yeah, you were strong before!
But that was three years ago!
It's not like we partied while you
lived the easy life in this village!
'As right! We've attacked lotsa
towns and sunk lotsa pirates!
Your point being...
You've done nothing for three years!
There's no way you can beat
the Meowban Brothers of today!
S-Stop! Butchie! Siam!
You're not our captain anymore!
Sorry, but we're gonna kill ya!
W-When did he get behind them?!
And those weapons...
Who...
Who are you going to kill?!
--He snuck...
--...behind us!
--Eh?!
--He's gone!
There it is! The Pussy Foot Maneuver...
Pussy Foot Maneuver?
You're right.
I do feel a bit of sluggishness.
He's handling them like kids,
after they had the upper hand
against Zoro and his one sword!
That man's "Pussy Foot Maneuver"
is a silent movement technique.
Even a group of 50 assassins would
be killed before sensing him!
There's no way we can escape his plan!
And I got chills after seeing that
habit of his again three years after!
His odd way of lifting his glasses
to avoid cutting his own face
with those Cat Claws...
Clear proof that he hasn't
forgotten how to fight!
It seems I've grown
a bit good-natured myself,
during my last three years on dry land...
I'll give you five minutes.
If you can't take care of
things here in five minutes...
...then I'll kill every last one of you...
...with my own two hands!
Five minutes...
Five minutes should be enough!
H-Him! If we just beat him,
we can get past this hill!
We had the upper hand
against him just now!
We'll cut him up in five minutes!
We're counting on you,
Meowban Brothers!
Zoro!
--What?!
--H-Hey, you!
Now you're kicking my swords, too?!
Where's my "thanks"?
Yeah...
Thanks!
It's no use!
Three swords won't help any!
Your skill's still the same!
Tiger...
You don't get it, do you?
...Trap!
Four minutes.
Just having three swords is different
from knowing the Three-Sword Style!
He's strong...
One hit...
H-He beat the Meowban
Brothers in one hit!
Don't worry!
I'll crush every last one of you
before your five minutes are up!
Three minutes.
I-I'll... slaughter him...
C-Captain...
H-Hypnotize me...
P-Please, Captain!
He's alive. You do sloppy work.
His tough fat saved him, huh?
Get 'im, Butchie!
More hypnosis?!
This guy means trouble! He could
already crack the ground apart!
What happens when he's powered up?!
This is my chance!
I gotta wake him up while I still can!
What is that crafty girl up to now?
Everyone's seriously hurt,
and he's just sleeping!
Die!
Get up!
Nami! Look out!
Two minutes.
Get up!
Nami! Look out!
Split in two!
Dodge it!
W-What the...?!
A chakram! It wasn't
just a hypnosis tool?!
Nami! How dare you stomp on my face?!
H-He's alive?!
Can't tell if he has bad or good timing...
L-Luffy...
Luffy!
Oww...
Ouch!
H-He's alive again!
--This is bad!
--Five minutes is impossible now!
Nami! That hurts, you jerk!
T-That wasn't me!
It wasn't me--
N-Nami! Did you hurt your shoulder?
I-It's nothing. I'm fine...
I've done everything I can for now,
so I leave the rest to you...
We absolutely can't
afford to lose this fight...
Yeah!
For the treasure!
It'll all work out in the end!
Try hard! For my treasure!
Okay! That sounds like you, alright!
One minute.
You can't be serious!
Not even Captain Jango
and Butchie-san...
...can finish them in one minute!
Butchie! There's no time to think!
Kill that haramaki bastard!
And I'll handle that weird kid...
I'll kill Straw Hat!
It's about time for everyone to die now.
Huh? That bad butler is here too!
Isn't he...
Didn't he fall off that cliff and die?
No matter.
Don't approach me...
...from behind!
Kaya!
U-Usopp-san! Are you okay?!
K-Kaya... What are you doing here?!
I'm so sorry, Usopp-san...
I know you may not accept my apology,
but I just couldn't believe it...
K-Klahadore, a pirate...
N-Never mind that!
Why are you here?!
I-I told you to run away!
Your life is in danger!
But you're fighting!
Even after I treated you so horribly
and you've been hurt so much,
you're still fighting for me! So I...
Miss Kaya...
Why are you here?
S-Stop this...
Stop this, Klahadore!
Merry told me everything.
Isn't that the girl from the mansion?
Meaning she's the plan's final target?!
Then there's no need to
go to the village now?
We just need to kill her, right?!
Klahadore, please! If you want
my fortune, you can have it all!
Just please leave
this village! Right now!
I will gladly accept it... but...
...there's one other
thing I want, you see...
What I want...
...is peace of mind.
Peace?
Yes. I want simple peace.
I find the villagers' trust that I've
fostered these past three years
to be nice and comfortable now.
So I want to have that
peace of mind forever...
And I...
And I will have that peace!
And your fortune...
In short, pirates will
come to the village!
And...
...you will leave your will and die!
These two things are absolute.
N-No...
Y-You're not...
Run! Run away, Kaya!
There's no use talking to him! Run away!
Y-You're not Klahadore.
You're not Klahadore...
Kaya...
Leave this village!
Oh... You'd point a gun at me...
Leave this minute!
I see. You've certainly grown
a lot these past three years...
...Miss Kaya.
Do you remember? So much
has happened in three years...
We spent so much time together,
even before your parents passed
away and you became bedridden...
So much time...
So many memories...
Together we suffered...
Together we rejoiced...
K-Klahadore...
I would visit the city with you,
and whenever you had a fever,
I constantly looked after you...
You listened to my stories so happily...
I devoted myself to you...
For so long...
Yes, for so long, I endured it...
Yes, it was all so that
I could kill you today...
I, a man once known as Captain Kuro,
had to smile humbly
for some snot-nosed girl...
I went against my nature
and sucked up to you...
Damn you...
Do you understand these daily insults?!
Do you understand this man
once known as Captain Kuro?!
Kuro!
Come to think of it...
...I still owe you for hitting me...
Usopp-san!
You hit me with all
your might, as I recall...
If you hate getting hit that much,
I got a hundred more punches for you!
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Usopp! You go save Miss Kaya!
Leave the bad butler to me!
--What a helplessly evil guy!
--I don't plan to help him, though!
I'm goin' after that hypno-freak!
Kuro! You're not cut out to be a pirate!
My ambition is much greater than yours!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Beat Kuro! Usopp the Man's
Tearful Resolve!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!