A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
Pumpkin Pirates, charge!
Cradle setup confirmed!
Anyway, that sure was an interesting place.
"And So, the Legend Begins!
To the Other Side of the Rainbow"
Really? I've had enough of that ship graveyard!
Well, it's not like I wanna live there,
but I wanna visit from time to time.
Barco-hunter joint... completed!
The treasure we're after is on that island!
Whoever makes land first gets a reward!
--Was it really that nice?
--Hm? Rain?
Who the hell is invading my turf?!
--It's... not rain...
--Hail?
Hm? Oh, it's a monkey.
W-Wait!
No... something's fall--
What are you doing?!
Hurry and pick that up!
All right!
What?!
Wait for me! I'm coming, too!
Father, it's an even bigger
harvest than we anticipated.
Pipe down, would you?
Hey, what's all the commotion?
You can't.
They're coming for us.
We can go back to Luluka.
Take it! Take every last bit of treasure in here!
After all, you're a grown-up, aren't you?
What's this?! What is this thing?!
They're coming?! J-Just a minute! Hold on!
"Caught Log! The King of Salvagers, Masira!"
Let me out of here!
Charge!
--Hurry it up!
--Okay!
--Guys!
--Don't do anything crazy!
"Monsters Appear! Don't Mess
with the Whitebeard Pirates!"
H-Hold on!
Let me go, too, together with you!
This is the Pumpkin Pirates' territory!
Wait for me!
Are you planning to just
leave me here, all alone?
Until Rapa Nui gets back,
it's up to us to defend it!
Rapa Nui! Isoka! Rongo! Akibi! Pukau!
Hang on!! Hold on to the ship!!
Professor!
Are you going to let me starve
to death?! Come on, please...!
Don't leave me here!
Don't leave me all by myself!
I'm one of the Pumpkin Pirates, too!
I'll fight alongside you!
What?! What is it?! What is it?!
Bring me the key! Don't abandon me!
I'll help you out, Pops!
Okay, you got it.
--Professor!
--They got me!
Thank you! I owe you for this!
Dream! Yeah, this must be a dream!
I was dreaming...
You're concerned about your friends, huh?
Dream?! Goo--
How come you guys are having
trouble against those kids?!
You were calling out
their names in your sleep.
"An Inevitable Melee!
Wetton's Schemes and the Rainbow Tower"
Boss!! Boss!!
Hey! More stuff's falling! Be careful!
W-Wetton...!
He's still his same, young self!
What was it all for, exactly?
What is this?!
No, you see, I'm Grandpa
Wetton's grandson, Lake.
Turn the rudder! The rudder!
These last 50 years that I dedicated
to researching the Rainbow Mist?
Gum-Gum... Rocket!!
No way that'll work in these waves!
What is it?! What?! A continent?!
Luffy, protect the ship!
It can't take this any longer!
--Do I really look like him?
--Yeah, a dead ringer.
I don't know! I don't know!
I can't see anything!
Seeing Rapa Nui and the others
the way they were back then,
Got it! Hm? Usopp?
I can't see anything! This is a dream!
I am, huh? My grandpa was
as handsome as I am, was he?
it makes me think that I, at least,
have wasted all that time.
Cast aside your worries.
Calmly close your eyes...
A dream?! Really?!
Let me go, damn it! Let me go!
Phew, it's just a dream...
What's with him?
Stop it, Rapa Nui!
It wasn't wasted, right? You did get
to see all your old friends again.
He's a weirdo.
When you open your eyes,
a quiet morning lies before you...
There must be some mistake!
Oh?
You guys hand over your
treasure, nice and easy!
Henzo would never become
one of Wetton's men.
Were they all...
I'm not so sure...
If you refuse, I'll burn you to a
crisp with this electroshock suit!
This isn't something you can
just pass off as some mistake!
Watch out! He uses electricity!
--Bones!!
--You idiot! Don't throw it this way!!
Our town was burned down by Wetton!
Is the ship moving?
Heh! Electricity, huh?
...eaten along with the ship?
--More stuff's falling!!
--Bones!!
It shouldn't be...
Ahh! You don't have to spell it out!
And here I was just itching
to wreak a little havoc, too!
Burn! Burn to the ground!
You idiot! Don't throw it this way!!
I'll take your electricity, and cut
it clean in half with my sword!
If he has carried on, and not forgotten
that aggravation, and misery,
"Thoughts of Home!
The Pirate Graveyard of No Escape!"
--There's no doubt about it; the air
supply hoses are going into its mouth.
--Stop... saying... that...
Why the heck did a ship fall from the sky?!
No, electricity doesn't work that way.
then he'd die before doing
anything Wetton told him to do!
Forward!
How weird...
This will be interesting. Just try it.
Full speed ahead!
There's nothing in the sky.
Or have those feelings faded
over the last 50 years, too?!
Oh man, the Grand Line is a crazy place!
Hey, Luffy, are you sure
we're moving forward?
I was hoping you'd say that.
Yeah! Straight ahead!
First, we see a ship graveyard
inside a rainbow mist,
Luffy and the others were really eaten!!
What was 50 years ago for you
was not all that long ago for us!
--and then a ship falls from the sky!
--Ahh!
Where on earth are you headed?
What's wrong, Nami-san?
It was you who made them go
to the Grand Line's seabed!
Where? We're going out of the mist!
It's quiet, huh?
What're we gonna do?! Our Log Pose is broken!
Hold on, Rapa Nui!
Don't be ridiculous.
Yeah. Quiet.
You're only saying that because
you don't know anything!
You said it'd be okay even though you really
didn't have any idea, that's why they...!
Once you wander into Ape's Concert,
you never get out of it again.
It's stuck pointing upwards.
Do you think everyone's all right?
Do you have any idea what
Pops here has had to live with
That's not it. It was updated by
an island with stronger magnetism.
--Who knows?
-- "Who knows?"  You can't say that!
It's a fiendish region of the sea.
You're right.
Hey, didn't we see that
ship a little while ago?
for the last 50 years?!
Aren't you concerned about everyone?!
--What?!
--If the Log Pose needle is pointing upwards,
What...?
They don't need our concern.
He's had the people in town
criticizing him, calling him Wetton's dog,
that means the log has
been caught by the sky island.
Don't let it bother you.
Instead, I'm concerned about that
damn mayor coming back alive.
There are ships that look
alike everywhere you go.
I'm sorry!
Sky island?!
and yet he's put up with it, to continue
researching the Rainbow Mist!
No, this ship ran aground in the
very first place we dropped anchor.
You've got the right idea, but...
Huh?
What's that?
If Luffy and the others take
care of that damn mayor,
A floating island?!
Why?
D-Did that ship and those
bones fall from there?
I remember seeing the goddess on the bow.
then I won't be able to get him back.
Isn't it obvious? In order to save you!
Oh. I guess there is that.
D-Does that mean we've come
back to where we started from?
But I can't see anything
like an island in the sky.
--Coming?
--Yeah. Let's go.
It's all right. Rapa Nui, that had
nothing to do with you guys.
That's not it.
This is why I asked if you
were sure we're going forward!
Unless we cut the hoses,
To be precise, a sea is what's floating.
Gum-Gum... Rocket!!
we'll be dragged into the depths
of the ocean with the ship.
I've been watching!
We've been going straight.
A sea?!
Hit me, Rapa Nui! I forsook
my shame and my pride,
No!!
You can't see our way
straight in this mist, can you?
Robin! You're strong,
aren't you?! Do something!
I'm getting more and more confused.
What was that?
to live under the protection of
Wetton! Hit me, with your fist!
Yaay! There's a sea with an
island floating in the sky?!
It can't be...
I can't. That thing is too big.
Seis Fleurs!
Alright! Let's head there right away!
Hit me, will you? Come on!
Hey, guys! Turn the rudder upwards!
Whoo, we stopped.
C-Captain!
Okay, you guys, pull those
ropes and save our boss!
Upwards rudder full!
Y-You've got some nerve,
Show your pride and honor as Masira Pirates!!
In any case, you can't turn upwards, Captain.
Damn it! Why did 50 years have to go by?!
coming into the Rainbow Mist
without my permission!
Ooh, ooh, aah!
To be honest, I've never seen the
sky island, nor do I know much about it.
Our boss is still alive!
You have to pay the 50 million-Berry
"entering on your own" tax!
As bad as I want to, I can't
hit you, at your age, can I?!
Hey, what was that for?!
--No way.
--What?!
That's right! Our unity is
tested at a time like this!
We shot forward, but it came
flying in from behind us!
Yeah! It's impossible for an
island or a sea to float in the air!
Are you saying you won't
follow Wetton-sama's orders?!
Sure enough.
Space is being distorted.
Wetton? That's you?!
So the Log Pose really must be broken.
--Usopp!
--Yeah!
That's right. I am the grand, puffed-up
mayor of all of Luluka, Wetton!
No, Navigator.
What do you mean?
Cut the hoses to ensure our safety!
I remembered something
written in the book.
Our concern right now should not be the
Log Pose, it should be how we get to the sky.
Man, these guys are awkward.
The inside of the
Rainbow Mist is like a maze.
--Are you a devil?
--She's a devil!
What? You, who were once
a pirate, are now the mayor?!
That's better. You're friends, after all.
What, is that so wrong?
Even though 50 years has gone by,
--Gum-Gum...
--H-Hey, don't do anything crazy!
C-Captain! That's him!
He's the one who stole our ship!
No matter what weird situations
this ship gets caught up in,
What?! What's going on?!
you still understand each other in the end.
...Rocket!!
Henzo...
What?
It became night?!
or how panicked we get,
Rapa Nui...
Too late.
He won't necessarily return
to the same location.
we must not doubt the Log Pose.
This is an ironclad rule.
Y-You're that kid from back then?
Can't be! It's not that late yet!
You, the one who burned down
the town, are now the mayor?!
That idiot!
What we should doubt is rather
the common sense in our heads.
Then, what's going on?! Luffy!! Zoro!! Sanji!!
I don't accept it! No way do I accept this!
--Sorry!
--Luffy!
That idiot!
You shut your mouth!
No problem. The inside of
the mist loops, after all.
There's definitely an
island where it's pointing.
Rapa Nui!
How ominous...! This sudden night
is a sign that monsters will appear!
I get it. This is a strange mist,
where no matter how far you go,
They'll be back soon enough...
Kid, being the mayor is nice.
I'm able to stay at my desk,
you end up where you started.
...or maybe not, huh?
They'll sink our ship!
Hurry up and save our boss!
Oh, it's a "strange mist."
Now what do we do?
and rake in the money I swindle
from all the foolish citizens.
Are you sure you understand?
Let's look for them. There's no telling
what will happen within this mist.
The part about not being able
to get out of here, at least.
I don't have to wander the
seas in search of my prey,
What's that woman doing,
opening the coffin?!
Luffy!!
or get hunted down by the navy!
Every day is a carefree paradise.
He's such a pain in the ass.
We don't have to get out. It's fun in here!
Rapa Nui...
Luffy! What happened?! Are you dead?!
Yes, we do!
There's no other trade as easy as this!
Let's join up with Rapa Nui and the others.
--Can you learn something from that?
--I don't know.
Once you are reborn, you too
will obtain power, as I did.
You've got strange interests!
Zoro! Sanji!
With those kids?
Set sail! Hurry up and get out of here!
The best way to get ourselves
out of Ape's Concert
A pretty woman and the dead,
now that's an interesting combination.
There's no use going on being a petty pirate!
is to consult the ones
whose territory it is, right?
Ow-w-w...
He's crazy...
I'm glad you were safe! Yeah, let's
get away from that turtle anyway!
Hm? Where's Luffy?
Yeah, but where are they?
--Jump, Luffy!
--Okay!
Where is this place?
Turtle? No, there was a monkey in the sea!
Shut up!
What're they doing now?
Let's ask that boy over there.
He must be one of the sea animals.
Exploration, they said.
--Captain!
--Father!
He was getting along with Luffy for a while.
Oh, restoration complete!
--Hurry and pick me up!
--Right!
How did she find me?!
The holes here are man-made.
Since they're both monkeys.
It's no use hiding.
But when he saw this stuff
that we got from the ship,
Why, you...! What are you doing?!
I see... then this guy was
pierced there and died, huh?
Un Fleur.
Y-You've gotta be kidding me!
he suddenly started going on a rampage.
No, these are indications of medical treatment.
He went on a rampage like a gorilla!
Would you take us?
Run, Nami!
You don't know what a real pirate is.
To wherever your boss is?
His name's Masira, he's a salvager.
It's craterization, isn't it, Doctor?
Hey, do something! At this rate,
Nami-san will be devoured by--
What?
Yeah, in the past, they made holes in the
skull in order to constrain a brain tumor.
But it's amazing that you guys could
escape from that turtle's mouth!
Luffy...
We don't need power.
We pirates have a dream, after all.
Turtle? What turtle?
Sanji!
Impossible!
What do I care? That's what you get
for trying to get the jump on us!
But that's a medical
technique from very long ago.
Hm? Something's wrong with the turtle.
Henzo came back,
and he's an old man, you say?
That's right. It's been at least
200 years since he died.
A-A dream, you say?
But Grandpa, we can't get
into Ape's Concert, either,
His mouth's staying open...
Oh, that's why you could escape!
What sort of joke is that?
with that monster hanging around.
It's no joke.
I know. But there's nothing
we can do about that monster.
He was in his early 30s.
Whoa!! What the hell is that?!
He fell into the sea, in order to save us,
and we haven't seen him since.
My electroshock suit is invincible!
You cannot escape from it!
Hey! Get a clue!!
That thing ate you and the ship!
He fell sick while traveling
on the sea and died.
I'm gonna die! I'm gonna die!
Escape? Who, me?
I'm gonna die!
I promise, I'll come after you later!
I told you, I'm gonna cut that
electricity of yours in half!
Go on! Keep going! Don't worry about me!
Like I said, where's the sense
in trying to cut electricity?!
I know! Miss, use the safety gear!
Hm? Why's it nighttime?
The reason his teeth remained in good
condition compared to his other bones is...
He's still alive, in the outside world.
Luffy! Give me a hand! We're gonna set sail!
Shall I cut it?
The safety gear?
Henzo said that he's been
looking for a way to bring us back,
Take this! Rolling Thunder!!
Hold it!
It's something that Professor Henzo invented!
...because tar was rubbed onto them.
all this time, in Luluka, and that
50 years had passed, just like that!
He undoubtedly created it
for just this situation!
You punks!
This custom is characteristic of
some areas in the South Blue.
Huh? What's going on here?!
Don't think you can get away after
stealing treasure from my turf!
Professor Henzo? I don't know who you are,
That suit he's so proud of
doesn't seem to be of much use
So considering history, that was a ship
for an exploration party from the past.
50 years? That's absurd.
but please, help me!
once the plug is pulled.
Are you sure that old man
isn't playing a trick on you?
Damn it! How can this happen?!
Put it back! Put it back, you bastard!
Treasure?! There was treasure?!
A lifeline?
Why would he play a trick on us?
Here it is. The "St. Briss" of Briss,
a kingdom in the South Blue.
You jackass! That's no fair!
Yeah, there was a lot.
I wouldn't know why.
Crap! If that guy goes on
a rampage on the ship...!
Help me! I'm sinking! I'm sinking!
Ah, I can't open the top!
But if what Henzo said is true,
Nami-san!
It set sail 208 years ago.
Nami!
I wonder what's happened
to the town of Luluka.
That's the same ship as the one that fell.
Let me cut something...!
Come to think of it,
it had a symbol like that.
No, stay away!
Dad... Mom...
This ship probably wandered in
the sky for at least 200 years.
B-Boss...! Behind you!
There's no use in worrying about it.
A dream, you say? What is it? Tell me!
You'll know if it's true or not once
you go back and see for yourself.
You can find out all that
just by looking at bones?
Hm? What is it?!
Everyone knows what your dream is.
Dead people may not speak,
but they do hold information.
You know of a way to get back?
You just want to obtain
riches of gold and silver.
Of course I do. I'm the raiding captain
of the Wetton Pirates, Ian-sama!
That will come falling into your lap
on its own, if you have power.
If the ship was for an exploration party,
it should still hold various
records and evidence.
W-What?
A pirate's dream is to be
the greatest man on the seas.
Yeah... but the ship sank in the sea...
Tell us the way to get back
to the town of Luluka!
--What're you guys doing?!
--Luffy! Hang in there!
Sure! Just bring the key!
If you let me out of here,
What was that just now?
Help me!
Chopper! If you please!
then I'll take charge of you,
and return you to your homes.
I'm the man who will be king of the pirates!
Hey, everyone!
I did it!
Oh, okay...
Luffy...
W-What do I do?!
Rongo! Akibi!
I found something incredible! Look at this!
Damn...
Okay, I've caught it!
Don't let him fool you.
Here I go, into the mist.
Ah!
Ian just wants to get out of there.
When I give the signal, pull the rope back in!
A map of the sky island?!
No one has ever defied me and lived!
Saying that he knows a way to
the outside world is just a ruse.
--Skypiea...
--See? See?
I'll blow you away, right down to your bones!
You got it!
She's got guts, doesn't she?
Does this mean that there's
really an island in the sky?!
--Wait, Captain!
--Father, what about me?!
Huh? A ruse?
Yahoo!
Not a single person has ever
gone into the Rainbow Mist,
What do I care?!
You sure are a tough one, Isoka-chan.
Captain!
and then come back out of it.
Alright! The sky island exists!
It's a dream island!
I haven't forgotten all those
times you mistreated us.
She'll be back, that's for sure.
We can go to a dream island!
After all, Nami-san is the
best navigator in the world.
A dream island!!
Listen up, you tenderfoots!
What is that? What's going on?
Don't get so carried away!
This only means it might be possible.
Chopper, we're not letting
anyone lay a finger on that rope
Being on the seas means always
being side by side with danger!
until Nami-san has returned.
There're tons of fake maps out there.
If you want to survive, then follow the orders
Got it.
of the Wetton Pirates'
raiding captain, Ian-sama!
This should be interesting.
Monsters!!
Er... Sorry! It exists! I'm sure it exists, but...
Let's let her do this.
Rainbow Tower...!
It's collapsing...
We'll watch, to see if she
comes back out of there safely.
--Listen, Luffy! I'm telling you,
--Uhm, Nami, please treat
the ship with care.
It's amazing! That ship over
there is full of jewels, too!
--we don't know how to get there!
--Uhm, Nami, please treat
the ship with care.
All right, take it to the captain's quarters.
--You're the navigator! Figure something out!
--Uhm, Nami, please treat
the ship with care.
--What?
--The mayor will now change outfits!
--There are some things you can't
just "figure out," you know!
--Nami-san's cute when she's angry, too.
They also had all this food!
All right, take that to
the captain's quarters, too.
--I don't care! We're going to the sky!!
--Nami-san's cute when she's angry, too.
What's this?
Damn it, what's going on?
Sea serpent!
This is getting us nowhere.
He's abandoned us!
In any case, we can't move
the ship forward this way!
Flame Suit!
Wetton, you bastard! You're not
the captain anymore, dammit!
What we need now is
information, as Robin said.
--Commencing element filling!
Help!
If a huge ship like that really went to the sky,
--Help!
--Don't run away, face it!
Luffy!
Internal tank pressure rising!
--Rapa Nui!
--It's Rapa Nui!
then there's definitely a way
for this ship to go there as well.
Safety mechanism released!
R-Rongo!
No way...
He came back!
I'll burn you, right down to your bone marrow!
Let's somehow pull out whatever
records remain in that ship!
Thank goodness! Rapa Nui!
Rapa Nui!
No way can someone be that big...
He had me so worried!
But the ship has completely sunk.
Man, how big a pain can one guy be?
Man, the Grand Line is just
one mystery after another!
If it sank, then we'll salvage it!
Hold it!
Hey, just a minute! Where are we going?!
W-What's that?
--Alright!
--As if we could!!
Isn't that obvious? Back to our friends.
Today, too.
Take this!
We saw a huge galleon fall from the sky.
What's salvage?
--It can't be...!
--Professor?
Really? Do you know a way to get
back to where our friends are?
It means to pull up a sunken ship.
Ape's Concert was maintained in
a delicate balance to begin with.
The needle of the Log Pose
is now pointing to the sky.
But it won't work, since that ship is too big.
Nope, I sure don't.
A weird monkey appeared
and salvaged the ship.
If you set off a large
explosion in a place like this,
What's wrong?
Then, we're just running to wherever?
there's no telling what might happen!
Then, we saw a huge turtle
that ate the whole ship.
That's not true. I have a hunch.
What are you looking at me like that for?!
Looking at your gloomy faces
is making the food taste bad!
Well, well... You really
make us do reckless things.
Then night came.
That's called going wherever.
What is that?!
And, at the end, we saw huge monsters who
were dozens of times larger than the Giants!
And it's your fault for knocking
me out here in the first place!
The warping of space is expanding quickly!
Remember, it's only because I
happened to be aboard this ship
Er...
Nami-san! I'll be sure to find a clue to the sky!
At this rate, we'll be caught in it,
and all of us will croak!
that you've managed to stay alive up to now!
Sorry.
Yeah, those guys scared even me.
Apologizing won't fix this mess!
I'm finally reunited with Henzo,
What?!
I'm counting on you!
How could this happen? Rainbow Tower...
Worry not, there are no defects in my design.
You might at least say thank you,
but I don't recall ever getting
looks as critical as this!
and I didn't even get to
shake his hand, you know?
Huh?
...has completely sunk.
Beat it!
I'll never get back to Luluka now, either.
Then, I wish you... good luck!
Damn it!
What's that?!
Damn, as unfinished as it was,
it wasn't reinforced enough.
I'm going to die here in
this mist, just like my dad did.
But no matter.
Your dad?
He was drawn here by the
smell of the food, was he?!
My dad was an officer in the navy.
When I was still a little kid,
Now, my men won't be coming
after me. The treasure is all mine!
Oh, boy...
Guys, get outside!
This is Chopper. Everyone, please respond.
he left on a long journey to explore
some unknown area of the seas.
Whoa, wait! This is my ship! Defend the ship!
This is Luffy. There're tons
of monsters down here, over.
I'd been waiting, ever since,
for my dad to come back.
Is this a giant sea snakes' nest?
Your boat is more important
than everyone's lives?!
This is Sanji. Whoa! They looked this way!
In any case, those monsters were huge.
We don't need a leader like that!
Even now, Dad was off having
adventures at sea somewhere.
--Okay.
--Okay?!
Yeah... I don't ever wanna see them again.
They'll survive. Don't worry!
That's what I believed. But then...
--Chopper, hold the brake tight, okay?
--Okay!
Phew... I'm glad I didn't go.
The sky is falling in!
You know, Chopper...
There's not much time. An hour, maybe.
Hm?
--Salvage, salvage!
--Hm?
Dad! Dad!
This is bad! We have to get out of here!
If I went all out, I would've
been able to beat them.
I frantically searched the ship,
but I didn't find Dad anywhere.
But how?
Damn it! My ship...!
Really?!
Salvage, salvage!
The author of this book
once visited Ape's Concert.
I've beaten ten of them before.
We're better off without that ship.
We're not getting out of here alive, all right.
Ten of them?!
Our true departure is just getting started.
The way out must be written
in here somewhere, too.
--Salvage, salvage!
--What the heck is that?
We're going to be shut up
inside this mist forever.
What's wrong?
What on earth did you guys
go into the water for?
"Continued in the last volume."
Salvage, salvage!
We're all fed up with you,
always shooting your mouth off,
And where is that?
You don't have it?!
This stuff is all junk, and I don't see
any clues on how to get to the sky!
and only thinking about yourself!
Hey, where are you going?
--Salvage, salvage!
--Company, halt!
I guess you must hate me.
I told you, back to where our friends are.
What's that?
But what if I really do know a way out of here?
Huh? What's the matter?
But how?! We don't even know where we are!
Like I said, there was nothing!
Luffy, that light!
Salvage...
And yet, you're still going to keep
moving forward through this mist?!
That's the light of the sun...
the light of the setting sun!
Well... that's the truth, Nami-san.
Another transparent lie!
Go ahead and test me, to see if I'm lying.
Setting sun?
Aye, aye, sir!
If we don't keep moving,
Yeah. The light of the sun is
shining in through a crack in space!
we'll never get back to
where everyone is, right?
Is this the area where a ship sank?!
You're concerned about the town
of Luluka, too, aren't you?
Aye, aye, sir! Boss!
We followed that light, and got outside.
Once we get all of the dormant
treasures of Ape's Concert together,
By boss... they mean me!
R-Really?!
Hurry! That light could disappear at any time!
we can live without doing
anything until the day we die!
Prepare to salvage the ship!
It was clear that the ship
had already been plundered.
Unfurl the sails! Everyone,
man the oars as hard as you can!
We don't have to live as pirates
here in this hazy mist.
The sunken ship belongs to me,
the king of salvagers
Hey, you guys come on, too! Give us a hand!
Well? Come with me,
back to the outside world.
and the boss of the Masira Pirates!
We're getting out of here!
Or perhaps that there was some sort of mutiny,
Y-Yeah...
Our only leader is Rapa Nui.
None of us are going to follow you.
and they killed each other.
Oh, boy... weirdoes at a time like this...
My, my, there's no making headway with you.
Hey, you! What're you guys
doing there?! This is my turf!
Well, take your time and
think it over, Isoka-chan.
Hey, what are you doing?! Row right!
How's your end?
No good. I didn't see them anywhere.
Your turf?
We are, you know!
That's right. Every ship that sinks
in this territory belongs to me.
It's possible that both of them might
have been flung beyond the mist.
What's going on?!
Then, all the more reason
that we need information!
There's a ship coming!
You haven't touched anything
that's mine, have you, huh?!
All hands, prepare for combat!
Fortify our defenses!
You see, if we are to go to the sky,
What do you mean?
Rapa Nui isn't here anymore?
Looks like... he's going to salvage the ship.
How did they know where we are?
--Ah, they broke!
--What are you doing?!
that means what happened to
that ship could happen to us!
Damn, not good!
Quite possibly.
Yeah, that's what it sounds like.
Hey, this is bad! The light
is starting to disappear!
Oh, no...
Then what? Doesn't this work for us?
Is that...?!
So, this is the end...
We need information to stay alive,
and what'd you get?!
Quit mumbling! Answer my question!
Pukau!
You guys get off and push us from behind!
Rusty swords, dishes, and a live octopus?!
Don't be crazy!
That is a galleon, from 200 years ago.
No, if we all flutter kick, then maybe we...
We need stuff like a "journal" or a "sea chart"!
That ship is huge!
Excuse me! Can I ask you a question?!
We will not!
I've never seen that ship before.
If only we could get a tailwind to blow us...
You're asking me a question?!
That's fine. Ask me anything!
That's a wrecked warship, right?
It's possible that inside Ape's Concert,
What's that, Luffy?
Yeah. Right now, though, it's our hideout.
You just need the wind to blow, right?
It looks like you're going to
salvage the ship. Is that right?
the course of time itself is...
Armor.
Hold on! What are you gonna do?!
Hey! Guys!
Looks?
Blow up our ship!
You cowards!
How dare you hold Pukau?!
Whoa! She crushed the armor!
It was originally a navy ship, after all.
Hey... Do you find me that "monkeyful"?
What are you talking about?
I got pretty seashells for you, Nami-san!
It's fully loaded with
cannonballs. If we light those,
No more talk!
Oh, it's you, Nami.
I don't need them, you big dummy!
--Monkeyful?
--That means "handsome." Do you think I am?
it should give you a fairly powerful tailwind.
What do you mean, "oh, it's you"?!
Nami-san's cute when she's mad, too!
Release Pukau!
You can't!
And after I came all the way
here just to rescue you!
Wait, Rapa Nui! If you do that, what...
--Yeah!
--Oh, come on, stop it!
You'd better keep your
distance from her right now.
How rude of you!
...what will happen to you?!
But there isn't such a word, is there?
You aren't the least bit convincing.
Having a tough time?
It's only gonna get worse!
Really, they're all a bunch of idiots!
So, are you gonna salvage it?!
This is my treasure! Mine! This is
why I can't give up being mayor!
Pay no mind, pay no mind.
Of course! If there's a
sunken ship in front of me,
Now we can't get to our destination!
Huh? Who are these children?
Where did Luffy go?
I'll salvage it! I'm that kind of a man!
--Here...
--What?! An Eternal Pose... This...
What's the matter? You all look so glum.
If it's on the water, I'll sink it and
salvage it! I'm that kind of a man!
Has something happened?
There's no ship that we can't salvage!
Mayor! It's the Talielisin!
I took it from those monkey
people's ship earlier... just in case.
They're gone beyond the mist.
Oh, my dear old ship.
--Huh?
--Like I said, they're gone.
They're not here anymore.
Hey, our friends were
supposedly inside that mist.
Then... is it okay if we watch you do it?
What do you mean?
Hm? Oh, I see, is salvaging work new to you?
But Grandpa, why is this ship
coming back home now?
What happened? Don't tell me
you're the only one who came back.
You're the only one on my side!
Just what he said.
You weren't here for it, so there's
no way to explain it to you.
Hey, we've got an octopus!
Let's make some takoyaki!
--Yow!
--I told you to call me "Mayor"!
Okay, go ahead and observe it!
How about it?!
--Yes, sir.
--Look there.
Alright! Let's see how things
go for now, everyone.
Okay. We're withdrawing!
50 years ago, my ship
disappeared inside that mist.
It must be quite tough for you.
Be... Be careful!
Hey, hold it!
--Just a minute!
--What about Luffy?!
And, since the ship has returned,
I'm not sure what happened,
but there's no way he's dead, is there?
--Boss! There's trouble!
--What's wrong?!
it means that the doorway to
Ape's Concert has been opened.
Jaya...
The members who went into
the sea to set the cradle are...!
Just leave him be, no problem.
It must be their headquarters.
Come on, we're heading back!
Jaya? Are we going there?
In other words, it's now or never,
Did they get hurt by Sea Kings?
Is there a way to escape?
Rapa Nui!
if we want to get the
treasure inside there, right?
Well... it looks like they
were beaten up by someone.
That's your decision, you idiot!
Hey, guys! Where are you going?! Come back!
Of a sort.
That's right. But how do you know that?
That's just a rope, isn't it?!
We are the Pumpkin Pirates!
What?! Are you saying there's
someone down there in the sea?
We're friends, who swore we'd
stay together until we died!
Alright! Jaya rudder full!
You're the one who came from Luluka, are you?
Well, your grandson there told me so.
--Those idiots...!
--This isn't good.
Jaya rudder full!
Guys...
Then... Hey, you guys!
You bonehead!
Rapa Nui dove in to save you guys!
And after everything I said
about the treasure being a secret!
Ian!
Ah... well...
Who's this guy?
Don't let what he's done be for nothing!
There's someone in the sea! Be careful!
One of Wetton's buddies.
I'm sorry, Grandp-- I mean, Mayor.
--Nami, which direction would that be?
--Starboard!
What is that guy doing in here?
Are you all trying to get killed together?!
Er... O-Okay!
It sure must be trouble, having
dimwitted family members, huh?
Chopper, give me a hand!
We're not going to die!
Good thing he's an idiot.
Okay!
Guys! Hurry up and set the cradle!
Henzo, I promise, we're coming back!
Jaya speed ahead!
Mm-hmm.
Why don't you hand over that rope to me?
Ain't that the truth? And why are
you acting sympathetic toward me?!
Let's start salvaging!
No matter how many years it takes,
we're coming back to Luluka!
Why should I? If you want
to get out of the mist, too,
Hey, hold on a second...
Aye, aye, sir!
you can just come along with us, right?
If we go to that Jaya place,
For whatever reasons, now that you
know the secret of Ape's Concert,
Isoka...
Don't you care what happens to him?
D-Don't you go thinking that you
won't answer for striking the mayor!
won't the log be updated there again?
I can't afford you leaving.
In other words...
You're going to silence us, is that it?
--No, I don't.
--What?!
You'll have to pay the "hitting the
mayor" tax of 90 million Berries!
...we won't be able to go to the sky island.
No, you're going to pay the
"I found out the secret" tax
Who is that kid, anyway? I'm not
good-natured enough to help out
Are you okay with that?
What?!
It doesn't matter to me.
Stop Jaya rudder!
of ten million Berries.
a kid I've never even seen before.
Hey, Nami! What's the deal?!
Yeah, can't argue with that.
What?! You're the one
who decided to go to Jaya.
I'll just skip out on it, after all.
Is this a joke?!
What?! You jackass! I'll shoot him! I really will!
More to the point, that's too much!
What? Paying taxes is a citizen's duty!
Oh, yeah...
More to the point, what kind of tax is that?!
How is a pirate obligated to pay taxes?
But I didn't think this'd happen!
You murderer!
Are you saying you can't pay the tax?
Er, well...
It's your fault that you didn't think of it!
Do what he says!
Tax collection squad!
Sanji!
The Log Pose has always
worked like this, right?!
Who, me? That's silly--
The Rainbow Mist is disappearing!
Oh, yeah... Hey, listen up!
H-Hey, cut that out!
What?
I don't want to lose any more of my friends!
He's waving to us... Don't let him
notice the air supply, Usopp.
Since I'm the captain,
I'll decide where we're going!
What will happen to Luffy and everyone else?
You called, Mayor Wetton?
Please, do what he says!
I know!
I wanna go to the sky island!
Oh, Daddy!
Now, none of them can come back! Not ever!
Hey, you guys, imagine that they're pumpkins!
Nice, Isoka-chan! While you're at it,
attach that lifeline to the boat.
Daddy?
Okay, but how?
We're best off asking someone.
Take them to Rainbow Tower,
and condemn them to hard labor.
No matter how hard you guys try,
my power is unshakable!
Don't get nervous... just because
people are watching, okay?
--Yeah, let's ask in Jaya.
--Then, we should go to Jaya.
What's that?
Alright, then! Jaya rudder full!
Isoka-chan, why don't you come with me?
Aye, aye, sir!
That is Rainbow Tower.
With this much treasure,
we'll never have to work again.
Drop the cradle!
Wait! You're going in circles!
You are going to keep working
at that tower until you die.
Aye, aye, sir!
Don't get me wrong!
Rapa Nui is the only leader we have!
It's not as if a log can be
stored as soon as we get there.
Hellish, heavy labor, from morning until night.
So why don't we go to Jaya and leave
before the next log gets stored?
Watch out for the mysterious enemy!
I have no intention of following
a pantywaist like you!
You'll be off to the next world in no time.
Aye, aye, sir!
I guess we need some luck.
What?!
I wonder if they're doing this
out of pride or something.
Go on, Flip, take them away.
Okay, then, we'll do what you just said...
Run, Isoka!
Damn you!
They're trying to give us a show, I guess...
Oh, the Rainbow Mist has
appeared, hasn't it, Father?!
Alright, guys! Let's go to Jaya, "Land of Meat"!
Rongo!
Hm? What's that?!
Mess with me, will you?!
Get moving!
--What?!
--What the...?!
Yeah!
Stop!
Now is our chance to get the
treasure from Ape's Concert!
Aye, aye, sir!
Don't dream up stuff like that!
I wonder what kind of place Jaya is.
He just said everything.
Damn it, let go! Let me go!
Nami-san, Robin-chan!
Secrets aren't worth a damn to them, are they?
Your "Unprecedented takoyaki
just for ladies" are ready!
All three generations are patently stupid.
Hey, what's the matter?
You bonehead! Fine!
Sea Prism Stone...
What?!
Call in Henzo, and have him
investigate the Rainbow Mist!
--Right! Bring me the transponder snail, at once!
--Father, you're still pretty strong, huh?
Damn it!
Dammit! Who the hell are they?!
Yes, sir!
Hold it, you bastard!
Don't you dare miss!
Hey, calm down a minute!
Monkey kicking me like that!!
--Hurry up and shoot! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
--W-Wait, let me aim, let me aim, let me aim!
Shut up! You took Pukau hostage,
and forced him to tell you
where our base is, didn't you?!
I can't shoot, you know!
That would be disgraceful.
Burn! Burn!
The Merry!
Rapa Nui, I'm not a hostage!
Are those guys all right?
It's no use! I can't get out of the way like this!
Captain? Captain!
They just asked me to lead
them here, so I brought them!
What?!
Er... Is this really the right place?
Rumble!!
They threatened you, to make you say that!
Aah! My mansion!
The legendary cave where Captain John,
It's the truth! These people
aren't bad, I tell you!
All of my possessions are being carried away!
who did many cruel things
for treasure, hid his treasure...
Lake, there he goes!
Look, he doesn't get mad, even when I do this!
Electroshock Suit! Maximum output!
It's not true! This is all a strategy,
to get us to let our guards down!
Yeah, that's right. Be careful going forward!
You're not getting away!
Dragon Spark!!
You misunderstand.
Listen, guards and traps
often accompany treasure.
We just want to know how
to get out of Ape's Concert.
Chopper!
You shouldn't take your
eyes off your opponent!
If you let your guard down, you could die!
And once you find out?
We don't know what kind
of monsters will appear,
What is this?!
You're planning to take all the
treasures out of these shipwrecks,
Silver Barbecue!!
or if it'll be a bloody trap from hell!
--Guys!
--Nami-san!
B-Barbecue?!
and run off with them!
Damn, how can this happen?!
My precious ship...!
Believe me, Rapa Nui, these guys,
at least, wouldn't do that.
Shoot your mouth off, will you?
Oh, Sanji, long time no see!
Now let's put in another
hard day's work on the tunnel!
Nami-san!
You're an example of what we call
"not knowing your place."
How can I believe the words of a grown-up?!
What was that for?!
Oh, man, am I annoyed!
Okay, boss!
Of course they're out to get the treasure!
Why, Nami-san?
"Boss"
This is going nowhere.
Grandpa, it's pulling, it's pulling!
Oh? You guys must be new recruits.
All of the treasure she left
on deck got blown away.
Hey!
You mean, that girl is really
coming back from inside the mist?
Hm?
Look! Usopp's specially made lunch is ready!
Oh yeah, nothing like
workin' up a sweat, eh, Boss?!
Best not to get too close to her right now.
Yahoo! Food!
Umph! A pickaxe is a man's tool, right?
Hey, pull her back here!
You guys want some, too?
Right!
That's far enough, pirates!
Oh yeah, a pickaxe! With our sweat,
this will soon become a tunnel,
Can we?
--The navy!
--They're the same ones that were chasing us!
--Not yet.
--What?
I can't vouch for the taste, though.
--Hey...
--Hm?
I promised that until Nami came back,
and it'll change into people's smiles.
Look!
Who asked you?
no one was going to lay a finger on this rope!
"Justice"
Help us! These guys are terrible criminals,
Yum! Did you really make this?
That's right. And the alcohol
after work is really...
Don't make me laugh!
who have taken every last bit
of the mayor's property!
There's nothing I can't do. Hey, Luffy!
Don't eat those all yourself!
To hell with your promise!
You're just being petty and stubborn!
Is that how badly you want the treasure?!
This is the ring of Princess Illusia,
a treasure which was stolen
They're not as good as Sanji's,
but they are just regular yummy.
Why are you having me do honest work?!
We don't want that.
by pirates a hundred years ago,
and has been missing ever since.
--Oh, thanks. I lived alone for a long time and all.
--There are some children over there
who look like they'd like some.
Nami-san will be coming back,
you can count on it.
Why do you have this?
Hey, come on down, guys!
We're just guarding the spot
of her return with our lives.
W-Well, you see...
You didn't steal it, did you?
These are delicious!
--Oh, can we really?
--All right!
No, of course not! This was a treasure
that was resting in Ape's Concert!
So, Captain Buggy,
Captain John's treasure wasn't there.
Don't let them sucker you in with food!
Yes, yes, we just pulled it out of a shipwreck!
Joue Shoot!!
You idiot, Mohji! Show some consideration!
Have you forgotten your
pride as Pumpkin Pirates?!
I see. What you're saying is,
it doesn't belong to anyone.
It's obvious that Captain got the wrong island.
Rapa Nui!
This play at friendship disgusts me!
Are you trying to make him
go red with embarrassment?!
Cradle set, confirmed!
Pride won't fill your belly.
What?!
Major, we've discovered a large pile of treasure
Mayor! There's a boat coming back!
Who are you saying has
a huge red nose?! Huh?!
What's going on?!
Huh? You guys came from the East Blue?
that we believe was carried out of there.
All right, pull the rope. Lead it over here.
Hm?
All right, the navy will be confiscating all of it.
By the way, Captain... this is
no time for fooling around.
Yeah.
Hold it! You're not laying
a finger on that treasure!
Which means, you must have
gone past Reverse Mountain, huh?
You kids are idiots! You can just
live inside this mist forever!
What're we gonna do? The Straw Hat guys
are real pirates on the Grand Line now.
You've got guts!
That treasure is mine!
Any treasure without an owner
belongs to the World Government.
Yes, we've gone through
many adventures up to now.
Oh, it sure feels good, being under a blue sky!
What's that monkey?! What's that monkey for?!
Ha! You flashy idiot! Don't lose your head.
If it has been embezzled, it will
be considered an act of piracy!
We've dueled with giants, and sea
serpents that swallow whole islands,
We'll just let them be for now.
Oh, I see it, I see it! The town of Luluka!
Fine with me! I'm a pirate to begin with!
Oh, this one?
and even saved a country
from a secret society.
What?! What do you mean?
You see, they say that
when a witch eats a child,
Whatever I want, I take by force!
You have a discerning eye.
--Wow, really?
--Incredible!
I-Is that...?
Watch out!
You're right. This is no ordinary prow.
The only reason we got
through those predicaments
she first makes the kid nice and chubby.
I will take that as your confession.
is because we had my wisdom and bravery!
Launch Barco-hunter!
Do you get that?
Is that okay with you, Wetton the pirate?
That's not Nami...!
Out of reverence for that,
everyone calls me "Captain--"
What?!
In short, the more those Straw Hat
guys' bounty money becomes...
Aye, aye, sir!
W-Who are you?
Sorry to be away so long! I am Ian!
Oh, I see! When you beat them,
What was that for?!
your bounty will become greater than theirs!
Stop sputtering when others are eating.
Captain Wetton, you are
looking even better than ever!
You couldn't be...
Oh!
M-Me?
Whoa!
I am doing very well, yes.
"Justice"
Rapa Nui...
Yeah, exactly!
Ian? Ian, you say?
I see, that's amazing!
Captain, shall we have a party?
You're kidding!
The same Ian that was under me?
Rapa Nui, forgive me!
I promised that we'd come back, didn't I?
--Wow! Amazing!
--It's really amazing!
Why not?!
Huh? Captain, who is this geezer?
What is?
Forgive my shameful self! I spent
50 years researching a way
Isoka?!
Take all of Wetton's gang into custody.
It's no time to horse around, you guys.
Uh, well, see...
40 meters to the target!
I'm the captain! I'm Wetton!
to save you from the Rainbow Mist,
Yes, sir.
If you can't find out where Luffy is,
30 meters!
Eh? Then, who's this?
I've finally managed to get
myself inside the mist,
20... 10...!
My grandson, Lake.
how exactly are you planning to beat him?
His son, Flip.
You guys are all alive? B-But how?
Don't be so uptight, Alvida.
but thanks to my carelessness,
we can't get out.
You're kidding! You're that
bed-wetting pipsqueak Flip?
Nothing's wrong with having fun for now, right?
Barco-hunter joint... completed!
At the moment of the explosion,
we were thrown into the outside world, too.
I'm a failure as a pirate professor!
You've even got a kid of your own now?!
That's absolutely astounding!
Luffy, you say? If you wanna
see Luffy, I'll tell you where he is.
But I will endure my shame to ask you,
Alright, then! I'll start blowing air!
Stop laughing, I say! Stop laughing!
However, it was the world 50 years ago.
See? He'll tell us Luffy's whereabouts.
if you know a way, please tell me!
How do we get out of this mist?
Tell me, Ian, what it's like inside the mist.
Aye, aye, sir!
Sure enough, that mist warped
the axis of time, as well.
Y-Yes, sir.
What? No way...
And then, we can leave here,
together, and go back to our home.
Here, drink up.
Who the hell are you?!
Wow, thanks!
Then why didn't you come here sooner?
Oh, sorry for interrupting your party.
--Well?
--It's no use, I can't get through.
I was brought forth by the
quite appetizing smell of food.
In order to defeat Wetton, who
abused the mantle of his authority,
There is no way out.
Is he going to breathe into
that and lift the ship up?!
When the signal got through before,
And even if I did know of one,
I wouldn't tell you.
I thought we would need to use another
authority-- the power of the navy.
My name is Ace. Nice to meet you.
it must have been a temporary thing.
That's crazy!
Of all the bad luck.
Oh, no need to be so formal.
Nice to meet you, too.
I still don't trust you guys, after all.
To have a piece of jewelry with
a Sea Prism Stone in it there...
But in order to gain that high
a rank, it took me a little time.
Sea Prism Stone?
And you call yourselves friends?
I'm asking you what you're doing here!!
So that's it.
It's a sea crystal. It has the power
to cancel out Devil Fruit abilities.
What?!
I may be wearing the uniform
of the navy, but in my heart,
I don't care about your name!
What a flashy insolent attitude!
Never mind us, Pops here
is your friend, isn't he?
Aw, there's no point in
having this much treasure
I'm still a Pumpkin Pirate,
and Henzo, I'm your friend.
Captain! Captain, this guy is... "Fire Fist"!
Tell me, if you can't trust
your friends, who can you trust?
Air?!
if we can't even go outside of here with it.
You keep out of this!
For now, and forever.
"Fire Fist Ace"!
You're a navigator, right? Do something.
He's the captain of Whitebeard's second unit!
You expect me to just believe that
50 years have suddenly gone by?
Nothing I can do. This absurd
area of the sea is a first for me.
Rapa Nui...
The ship's body has risen!
Whitebeard?!
We've got no options, huh?
Believe it!
Oh? You guys know my boss? That's coo--
No, he'll be coming back.
No matter how much time has
passed, or how different he looks,
Now! Pull it up!
What for?
He fell asleep!!
Wetton's ultimate goal is the
treasure inside Ape's Concert.
Also, I forgot to mention this, Luffy Pirates,
Aye, aye, sir!
if he's one of your friends, who fell
in under the same banner as you,
No!
Send more air! On the double!
but you're under arrest, too.
you should know each other!
Why? This is a great opportunity
any way you look at it!
Now that his man Ian has returned alive,
The color of your flag may fade,
but friendship is forever, you know!
--What?!
--You're heartless!
Aye, aye, sir!
he'll be heading up a large
force and charging in here.
If we defeat Fire Fist Ace,
we'll become instantly famous!
Have you forgotten how you owe
me for feeding you, you jerk?!
You've gotta be kidding me!
I said no!
Let's fight! I won't hand over
this treasure to anyone!
As a member of the navy,
charged with upholding justice,
Listen to you...
Listen up, guys. Remember this flashily!
Oh, that's me.
I can't just let a pirate who has
a bounty get away. However...
If only Rapa Nui were here for us...
Okay, okay, I'm coming. Huh?
Boss! The crew that's in the water...!
No matter what happens, never mess
with the Whitebeard Pirates!
How can this be?! Right now, we have
to escort Wetton and his gang
Yes, hello?
What's the matter?! What happened, guys?!
What good does it do for you to answer?!
back to Navy Headquarters! But if we do that,
Whitebeard is a legendary monster.
Well, well, Professor Henzo?
the Luffy Pirates are going to
end up slipping away from us!
There's someone in the ship!
Huh? Who are you?
He's the only one who fought neck and neck
with Roger, the King of the Pirates.
Huh? Who is this?
But they're just too much for us to handle!
Hey, buck up! Hey!
Request assistance from
the naval base at once!
Damn!
--Luffy, is that you?
--Where are you?
He's now, without a doubt,
the world's strongest pirate!
It's no good! No matter how much we paddle,
No, it won't be until tomorrow or
the next day that they'll arrive!
You guys just took the ship on your own,
we wind up back where we started!
How dare they hurt my guys?!
Who the hell are they?!
He's the man closest to that
secret treasure, One Piece!
If they escape during that time,
that's the end of it!
It really is impossible.
We can't get out of this mist.
and put the rest of us in a big fix!
"Justice"
Aah, I give up! I can't do anything about it!
Huh? Is that you, Nami?
And, above all, Whitebeard never
forgives the killing of one of his own.
That's not so bad, is it?
You're connected to Nami and the others?
That sure sounded like a put-on.
--Nami?
--Hold on, if we can talk to her...
We're the only ones in here.
We can sleep when we want,
Never! He's that kind of man.
Well, we're not taking
pictures or anything, so...
and play when we want. It's our own paradise.
Are we connecting to the outside world?!
What?!
You know an awful lot about him.
We can't do any full-fledged repairs right away.
A land of freedom, a land of eternity!
Oh, he posed for us to take pictures...
Flip?! Flip, are you there?!
Boss! Help!
Rapa Nui!
Yes, this is Flip!
Those emergency measures should
at least keep the water out, though.
Of course...
We don't have to go home.
Let's make our own land, all on our own.
Professor Henzo, where are you?
Long ago... I met him in person,
here on the Grand Line.
I'm coming! Keep on working
on the salvaging operation!
I'm inside the Rainbow Mist.
Thank you, Luffy, and all of your friends.
I want to go home, back to our own town.
Aye, aye, sir!
What?!
The Rainbow...
I want to go home to Luluka.
...Mist?
Oh? You know my boss?
Now, the research that I carried
on all these years is at an end.
Currently, we are unable to get out.
We can't have that.
He's awake!!
I'm sorry, but could you come rescue us?
Dad?
There's no telling when the Rainbow
Mist is going to appear, right?
Someone's coming for us?!
Hey, you guys! Don't be shy!
It's a party. Let's have fun!
Dad... Dad!
We can go back to Luluka, right?!
With that thing out there,
we can't go out to sea in peace.
Isn't that great, Rapa Nui?
Uhh... He's right!
We were having a party, right?!
We want you to make us some gear,
There's no time. Tell Wetton to
equip the safety search gear
to help us avoid the Rainbow Mist.
What's that light?
Hey, you drink quite a bit! Drink more!
that I invented, and to come inside the mist.
Monkey punch!
That will be an easy task.
--Hey, isn't that...?
--An exit!
Oh?! You guys have a lion?
Come! Jump through this fire hoop!
Also--
It's coming up...
What are you doing?!
At last, my 50-year-old dream will come true.
That name you just said, Wetton,
Okay, show him, Rich!
is the same man who burned
down the town of Luluka, isn't it?!
The Rainbow Mist and this world
will be forever joined!
The Rainbow Mist is a land of eternity.
See? We're fine without the barrel.
Wait! I had to team up with that man,
in order to save all of you!
It has neither daytime, nor nighttime.
It's amazing that they pumped in this much air.
One never gets sick, or grows old.
But who is trying to salvage this ship?
Now it's all clear. You are not
the Henzo that we know!
The sea shines emerald, and the sky
envelops us deeply, like milk.
Something might have happened
to Nami-san and Robin-chan.
If you were one of the Pumpkin Pirates,
I've been calling them, but no response!
Where's the boss?!
there's no way you'd become
one of Wetton's pawns!
Boss!!
The countless ships that
become captives of this land
Who the hell are you, invading my turf?!
Rapa Nui...
--Hey, my gang! I'm right here!
--It doesn't look like he's around here.
had immeasurable treasures
resting within them.
Don't call me by that name!
Hm?
It was indeed the last
paradise remaining on earth.
--Hey!
--Let's go check over there!
You traitor!
Hello? Hello?
Oh, it's a monkey.
Aye, aye, sir!
W-What's that?!
What? Am I that monkeyful?
My, my, so they really are
inside that mist, are they?
Hey! Wait! Don't leave!!
We were the kings of that land of eternity.
Yeah, you're an imitation monkey.
What do we do?
We routed the pirates that came invading,
What kind of conversation is that?
Isn't it obvious? We go inside the mist.
and kept the peace in paradise.
Our name was the Pumpkin Pirates.
What do you mean?
By the way, who are you?
Just a minute!
I see... What can I say?
I would like to write down
the many unusual adventures
Do you really think so? You have a good eye!
I told you,
I wonder what kind of island Jaya is.
you aren't allowed to go into
Ape's Concert without my permission.
we went through inside the mist...
So who the hell are you?!
Like I said, it's a land of meat! A land of meat!
You keep acting on your own, and...
Everyone, grab onto something!
But you just wish it was, right?
...for the sake of the adventurers
who will visit this land hereafter.
Say, where is that safety gear
that he mentioned earlier?
Well, it's true that I'm tired of eating takoyaki...
Hey, underneath the ship...
W-What's that?!
--Oh, in here.
--Thank you!
Y-Yeah... there's something down there.
Then, don't eat them. Those were
for Nami-san and Robin-chan!
It's Rainbow Tower!
--No, don't mention it.
--What are you giving it to them for?!
Whew, that was a close one!
Thank you!
They said they wouldn't eat them,
so what's the problem?!
You fools! Seize them, at once!
Here's your hat.
The name of the adventurers belongs to those
--Give them back! Give us back the takoyaki!
--Shut up! Shut up!!
Thank you. By the way, what is that?
I see! You guys came from the East Blue, huh?!
Yes, sir!
whose debt we are in for
leading us back out into the world--
They're planning to invade Ape's Concert.
Shut up!
And here, I was about to make
a wisecrack about eloping.
Yeah. But really, you look just like a monkey!
the Luffy Pirates.
Huh? They who?
In any case, let's hurry. Everyone's in danger!
In any case, is there really an island in the sky?
Quit complimenting me!
Anyway, that sure was an interesting place.
Really? I've had enough of that ship graveyard!
We've experienced enough to know by now...
Go, Nami!
So, Wetton, you've come after all.
Well, it's not like I wanna live there,
but I wanna visit from time to time.
Yeah! Leave Luffy and the others,
and the treasure, to me!
that no matter how illogical
things seem, it's not strange,
Get going, men!
Was it really that nice?
--Hm? Rain?
--It's... not rain...
because it's this sea's logic.
Take every last bit of Ape's Concert's treasures!
Hail?
No... something's fall--
Nami-san!
So Jaya holds the key to go to the sky island.
What's this?! What is this thing?!
What?!
Ah, beyond the never-ending sky
The future that I once saw
is now starting to take shape
There are days where I almost lose to myself
When that happened, there was
someplace warm I could go
The friends I took pride in
always, without fail,
pushed me onwards, didn't they?
Ah, the stars are pouring
down underneath the sky
This unique moment...
Ahhh! It's a turtle!
This town looks rough.
Wetton is here!
Hey, guys!
What's wrong?!
But this is the mayor we're facing, right?
This is the sea! Of course we'll see turtles!
Oh, it's you, Nami.
--Yeah, because it's Jaya.
--Because it's a spring island as well.
Our Log Pose is broken!
It's stuck pointing upwards.
He has a lot of men under him.
What do you mean, "oh, it's you"?!
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
You don't make sense!
I've fought him all this time by myself,
And after I came all the way
here just to rescue you!
Shut up and be quiet!
I heard that this is a place for pirates to gather.
--What?!
--That's not it.
and I haven't given my heart over to him.
How can you be so calm?!
It was updated by an island
with stronger magnetism.
Sounds fun!
So, where's Luffy?
Hey, we came to gather information
on how to go to the sky island!
Aren't you forgetting about us?
You're not alone.
A galleon fell, and then a
weird monkey shows up!
He's not here.
--If it's pointing up, it's a sky island.
--Sky island?
He's disappeared beyond the mist.
Wh-What?! It's become pitch dark!
I won't let you defile the
paradise of the Pumpkin Pirates!
Don't you dare cause any
trouble here, got that?!
Then, that ship fell from there?
Wh-What's next?!
Huh? What do you mean?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Monsters Appear! Don't Mess
with the Whitebeard Pirates!"
"An Inevitable Melee!
Wetton's Schemes and the Rainbow Tower"
"Caught Log! The King of Salvagers, Masira!"
"Quit Dreaming!
Mock Town, the Town of Ridicule!"
"And So, the Legend Begins!
To the Other Side of the Rainbow"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!