A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
Cradle setup confirmed!
Barco-hunter joint... completed!
Who the hell is invading my turf?!
Hm? Oh, it's a monkey.
What's this?! What is this thing?!
"Monsters Appear! Don't Mess
with the Whitebeard Pirates!"
Boss!! Boss!!
What is this?!
What is it?! What?! A continent?!
I don't know! I don't know!
I can't see anything!
I can't see anything! This is a dream!
A dream?! Really?!
Phew, it's just a dream...
Oh?
Were they all...
...eaten along with the ship?
Ahh! You don't have to spell it out!
--There's no doubt about it; the air
supply hoses are going into its mouth.
--Stop... saying... that...
Luffy and the others were really eaten!!
It was you who made them go
to the Grand Line's seabed!
You said it'd be okay even though you really
didn't have any idea, that's why they...!
You're right.
I'm sorry!
You've got the right idea, but...
Unless we cut the hoses,
we'll be dragged into the depths
of the ocean with the ship.
No!!
Robin! You're strong,
aren't you?! Do something!
I can't. That thing is too big.
Okay, you guys, pull those
ropes and save our boss!
Show your pride and honor as Masira Pirates!!
Ooh, ooh, aah!
Our boss is still alive!
That's right! Our unity is
tested at a time like this!
--Usopp!
--Yeah!
Cut the hoses to ensure our safety!
--Are you a devil?
--She's a devil!
What?! What's going on?!
It became night?!
Can't be! It's not that late yet!
Then, what's going on?! Luffy!! Zoro!! Sanji!!
How ominous...! This sudden night
is a sign that monsters will appear!
They'll sink our ship!
Hurry up and save our boss!
Luffy!!
Luffy! What happened?! Are you dead?!
Zoro! Sanji!
Set sail! Hurry up and get out of here!
He's crazy...
I'm glad you were safe! Yeah, let's
get away from that turtle anyway!
Turtle? No, there was a monkey in the sea!
He must be one of the sea animals.
He was getting along with Luffy for a while.
Since they're both monkeys.
But when he saw this stuff
that we got from the ship,
he suddenly started going on a rampage.
He went on a rampage like a gorilla!
His name's Masira, he's a salvager.
But it's amazing that you guys could
escape from that turtle's mouth!
Turtle? What turtle?
Hm? Something's wrong with the turtle.
His mouth's staying open...
Oh, that's why you could escape!
Whoa!! What the hell is that?!
Hey! Get a clue!!
That thing ate you and the ship!
Hm? Why's it nighttime?
Luffy! Give me a hand! We're gonna set sail!
Hold it!
You punks!
Don't think you can get away after
stealing treasure from my turf!
Treasure?! There was treasure?!
Yeah, there was a lot.
Crap! If that guy goes on
a rampage on the ship...!
B-Boss...! Behind you!
Hm? What is it?!
Monsters!!
No way...
No way can someone be that big...
Man, the Grand Line is just
one mystery after another!
Today, too.
We saw a huge galleon fall from the sky.
The needle of the Log Pose
is now pointing to the sky.
A weird monkey appeared
and salvaged the ship.
Then, we saw a huge turtle
that ate the whole ship.
Then night came.
And, at the end, we saw huge monsters who
were dozens of times larger than the Giants!
Yeah, those guys scared even me.
Huh?
Beat it!
In any case, those monsters were huge.
Yeah... I don't ever wanna see them again.
You know, Chopper...
Hm?
If I went all out, I would've
been able to beat them.
Really?!
I've beaten ten of them before.
Ten of them?!
What on earth did you guys
go into the water for?
This stuff is all junk, and I don't see
any clues on how to get to the sky!
Like I said, there was nothing!
Well... that's the truth, Nami-san.
It was clear that the ship
had already been plundered.
Or perhaps that there was some sort of mutiny,
and they killed each other.
Then, all the more reason
that we need information!
You see, if we are to go to the sky,
that means what happened to
that ship could happen to us!
We need information to stay alive,
and what'd you get?!
Rusty swords, dishes, and a live octopus?!
We need stuff like a "journal" or a "sea chart"!
What's that, Luffy?
Armor.
Whoa! She crushed the armor!
I got pretty seashells for you, Nami-san!
I don't need them, you big dummy!
Nami-san's cute when she's mad, too!
You'd better keep your
distance from her right now.
Having a tough time?
It's only gonna get worse!
Really, they're all a bunch of idiots!
Now we can't get to our destination!
--Here...
--What?! An Eternal Pose... This...
I took it from those monkey
people's ship earlier... just in case.
You're the only one on my side!
Hey, we've got an octopus!
Let's make some takoyaki!
It must be quite tough for you.
Jaya...
It must be their headquarters.
Jaya? Are we going there?
That's your decision, you idiot!
Alright! Jaya rudder full!
Jaya rudder full!
--Nami, which direction would that be?
--Starboard!
Chopper, give me a hand!
Okay!
Jaya speed ahead!
Hey, hold on a second...
If we go to that Jaya place,
won't the log be updated there again?
In other words...
...we won't be able to go to the sky island.
What?!
Stop Jaya rudder!
Hey, Nami! What's the deal?!
What?! You're the one
who decided to go to Jaya.
Oh, yeah...
But I didn't think this'd happen!
It's your fault that you didn't think of it!
The Log Pose has always
worked like this, right?!
Oh, yeah... Hey, listen up!
Since I'm the captain,
I'll decide where we're going!
I wanna go to the sky island!
Okay, but how?
We're best off asking someone.
--Yeah, let's ask in Jaya.
--Then, we should go to Jaya.
Alright, then! Jaya rudder full!
Wait! You're going in circles!
It's not as if a log can be
stored as soon as we get there.
So why don't we go to Jaya and leave
before the next log gets stored?
I guess we need some luck.
Okay, then, we'll do what you just said...
Alright, guys! Let's go to Jaya, "Land of Meat"!
Yeah!
Don't dream up stuff like that!
I wonder what kind of place Jaya is.
Nami-san, Robin-chan!
Your "Unprecedented takoyaki
just for ladies" are ready!
Dammit! Who the hell are they?!
Monkey kicking me like that!!
Captain? Captain!
What?!
Er... Is this really the right place?
The legendary cave where Captain John,
who did many cruel things
for treasure, hid his treasure...
Yeah, that's right. Be careful going forward!
Listen, guards and traps
often accompany treasure.
If you let your guard down, you could die!
We don't know what kind
of monsters will appear,
or if it'll be a bloody trap from hell!
Now let's put in another
hard day's work on the tunnel!
Okay, boss!
"Boss"
Oh? You guys must be new recruits.
Hm?
Oh yeah, nothing like
workin' up a sweat, eh, Boss?!
Umph! A pickaxe is a man's tool, right?
Oh yeah, a pickaxe! With our sweat,
this will soon become a tunnel,
and it'll change into people's smiles.
That's right. And the alcohol
after work is really...
Why are you having me do honest work?!
So, Captain Buggy,
Captain John's treasure wasn't there.
You idiot, Mohji! Show some consideration!
It's obvious that Captain got the wrong island.
Are you trying to make him
go red with embarrassment?!
Who are you saying has
a huge red nose?! Huh?!
By the way, Captain... this is
no time for fooling around.
What're we gonna do? The Straw Hat guys
are real pirates on the Grand Line now.
Ha! You flashy idiot! Don't lose your head.
We'll just let them be for now.
What?! What do you mean?
You see, they say that
when a witch eats a child,
she first makes the kid nice and chubby.
Do you get that?
In short, the more those Straw Hat
guys' bounty money becomes...
Oh, I see! When you beat them,
your bounty will become greater than theirs!
Oh!
Yeah, exactly!
I see, that's amazing!
Captain, shall we have a party?
Why not?!
It's no time to horse around, you guys.
If you can't find out where Luffy is,
how exactly are you planning to beat him?
Don't be so uptight, Alvida.
Nothing's wrong with having fun for now, right?
Luffy, you say? If you wanna
see Luffy, I'll tell you where he is.
See? He'll tell us Luffy's whereabouts.
Who the hell are you?!
Oh, sorry for interrupting your party.
I was brought forth by the
quite appetizing smell of food.
My name is Ace. Nice to meet you.
Oh, no need to be so formal.
Nice to meet you, too.
I'm asking you what you're doing here!!
I don't care about your name!
What a flashy insolent attitude!
Captain! Captain, this guy is... "Fire Fist"!
"Fire Fist Ace"!
He's the captain of Whitebeard's second unit!
Whitebeard?!
Oh? You guys know my boss? That's coo--
He fell asleep!!
No!
Why? This is a great opportunity
any way you look at it!
If we defeat Fire Fist Ace,
we'll become instantly famous!
I said no!
Listen up, guys. Remember this flashily!
No matter what happens, never mess
with the Whitebeard Pirates!
Whitebeard is a legendary monster.
He's the only one who fought neck and neck
with Roger, the King of the Pirates.
He's now, without a doubt,
the world's strongest pirate!
He's the man closest to that
secret treasure, One Piece!
And, above all, Whitebeard never
forgives the killing of one of his own.
Never! He's that kind of man.
You know an awful lot about him.
Of course...
Long ago... I met him in person,
here on the Grand Line.
Oh? You know my boss?
He's awake!!
Hey, you guys! Don't be shy!
It's a party. Let's have fun!
Uhh... He's right!
We were having a party, right?!
Hey, you drink quite a bit! Drink more!
Oh?! You guys have a lion?
Come! Jump through this fire hoop!
Okay, show him, Rich!
Where's the boss?!
Boss!!
--Hey, my gang! I'm right here!
--It doesn't look like he's around here.
--Hey!
--Let's go check over there!
Aye, aye, sir!
Hey! Wait! Don't leave!!
I wonder what kind of island Jaya is.
Like I said, it's a land of meat! A land of meat!
But you just wish it was, right?
Well, it's true that I'm tired of eating takoyaki...
Then, don't eat them. Those were
for Nami-san and Robin-chan!
They said they wouldn't eat them,
so what's the problem?!
--Give them back! Give us back the takoyaki!
--Shut up! Shut up!!
Shut up!
In any case, is there really an island in the sky?
We've experienced enough to know by now...
that no matter how illogical
things seem, it's not strange,
because it's this sea's logic.
So Jaya holds the key to go to the sky island.
Ah, beyond the never-ending sky
The future that I once saw
is now starting to take shape
There are days where I almost lose to myself
When that happened, there was
someplace warm I could go
The friends I took pride in
always, without fail,
pushed me onwards, didn't they?
Ah, the stars are pouring
down underneath the sky
This unique moment...
This town looks rough.
--Yeah, because it's Jaya.
--Because it's a spring island as well.
You don't make sense!
I heard that this is a place for pirates to gather.
Sounds fun!
Hey, we came to gather information
on how to go to the sky island!
Don't you dare cause any
trouble here, got that?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Quit Dreaming!
Mock Town, the Town of Ridicule!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!