A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
Hey, Mister! We want to go to the sky island!
Gold bells and a bird...
Do you know anything about it?! If you do...
"Steer for the Clouds! Capture the South Bird!"
Do you suppose they
were symbols of old Jaya?
Take those two and beat it already
Dunno, but I think they were
part of some sort of model.
She said "sky island"!
--But the Log Pose is
definitely pointing to the sky!
--Give me a break!
What do you need to tell us, old guy?
while you're still alive, you small fries!
Now you're all out of money.
This here's called a South Bird,
and they still exist on this island!
Here. I'll start by telling you
everything I know about the sky island.
So then... wanna bet your pants
or something, brother?
Luffy!
Oh! Do they have weird calls?
The sky island exists.
You're lucky, in a sense.
None of it's certain, but it's up to you
if you wanna believe it or not!
Yep. Just like the logbook says!
Playing with Roshio, if you had won,
he would have made you pay for it.
Sailors have long used South Birds to...
Zoro, hold on a minute!
Zoro!
Shut up! I'm just taking him up on his offer!
Luffy!
--Yeah! We believe you!
--Geez, you're fast!
Sorry, but I'll be taking all your money.
There's a strange phenomenon
that occurs in these waters--
Oh, crap!
The new era they're talking about is crap!
What is it?! What's wrong?!
Let it go. I won this money fair and square.
Luffy!
sometimes it'll turn to night,
even though it's the middle of the day.
Go catch this bird! Right now!
Get outta this town!
The era where pirates have dreams
will be over, they say?! Huh?!
Why?! What for?!
Why do we need a bird?
Yeah! We saw that! Right?!
Luffy! Zoro! Forget the promise,
take care of them already!
Listen closely! The Knock-Up Stream
you're heading for tomorrow
You cheated just now, didn't you?
Yeah! Night came, and then
some monsters appeared!
Don't take them on, no matter what happens.
Ain't that right?
is located directly south of this cape.
People's dreams... have no end!!
What'd you say? When did I do that?
The giants?
How are you going to get there?!
You did! You cheated!
There's a story about where they
come from, but forget 'em for now.
Once you're on the open sea,
there's no way to get your bearings!
Don't make ridiculous accusations, you punk!
This sudden nightfall...
"Distinguished Pirates! A Man Who Talks of
Dreams and the King of Undersea Search"
That's right!
We're heading for ocean, not an island,
so we have no guide to rely on!
Sarquiss! Sarquiss!
"Legendary Family! 'Noland the Liar'"
Hm? What?
It's caused by the shadows
of extremely compact clouds...
So you'll use the bird's behavior for that!
You saw it, too, didn't you?
This guy just cheated.
Seriously... Seriously... Seriously...
You mean cumulonimbus clouds?
But it was too dark to be clouds...
Cheated?
I heard the sad tale of your
Montblanc family at the pub.
Seriously... that darn orangutan!
He wrecked the ship even more!
Yeah... That's right. He cheated.
Wow! You're so dumb, old guy!
It moved me, Cricket.
It gets cloudy on days
when there's lots of clouds!
I saw it, too. What a dirty cheat!
Look at them! They're still standing!
--Yeah! Cloudy!
--Cloudy!
Treasure someone else struggled to
get has a special flavor all its own!
This ship has really started to fall apart.
Maybe it's about time to replace it?
Shut up and listen!
Don't screw with me! You don't
know who you're dealing with!
Get those clumsy chickens!
There are clouds known as
"cumuloregalis clouds."
Don't you dare start saying
inconsiderate things, too!
Wanna know what people call me?
This town isn't for dreaming cowards!
Don't you dare!
They pile high into the sky but
produce no air currents or rain.
You know exactly how we got this ship, right?!
The Hyena!
Right?!
What's the commotion?
When they appear high in the sky,
even sunlight is blocked out,
I heard the Bellamy Pirates
are holding a public lynching.
I know, Usopp.
Complaining won't get us anywhere.
"Dreams Don't Come True?!
Bellamy versus the Saruyama Alliance"
Luffy! Zoro! Why are you
just taking this from them?!
--Going Merry is an important part of the team.
--You know exactly...!
bringing afternoon "nighttime" to the ground.
Fight them! Why don't you just beat them up?!
--You...! You...!
--So let's work hard and repair the ship!
One theory has it that cumuloregalis
clouds are fossilized clouds
--How we... How... How... How we...!
--Luffy... You're such a...
that have floated in the sky for
thousands and thousands of years.
It's no use, lady. They're smart.
They've realized that their
opponents are out of their league.
Whoops.
That's ridiculous! Clouds with no
air currents even after building up?!
You idiot!! Are you repairing
the ship or wrecking it?!
Not fighting a strong opponent...
it's a disgraceful move, though.
"Quit Dreaming!
Mock Town, the Town of Ridicule!"
You're free to believe they can't exist.
Well, I'm really trying to fix it, but...
I'm not asking you to believe me!
Whoops, it got broke again.
Here they come! Dodge!
I guess he has no dignity as a captain.
Luffy!!
They're mystery clouds, then?
Still don't see it, Usopp?
The Navy's generous these days,
We left Mock Town and headed east
by circling around the island.
Pretty much. There's still
no explanation for them.
No, I don't see it yet.
giving 30 million Berries for the
head of a worthless ass like him.
This Jaya island isn't that far, right?
You're awesome, Luffy!
We're almost here on the map.
Listen. If a sky island really does exist...
That man... what's his name again?
Yeah, since the weather has
been stable for a while now,
Zoro, don't take them on,
no matter what happens.
Montblanc Cricket.
...that'd be the only possible place!
we should already be
in the island's climate.
So that man who talks of
dreams lives there, huh?
Okay! Gotcha! Let's go above those clouds!
These praying mantises aren't normal!
Then, Jaya must be a spring island.
Why... are you both...?
--Get up, Zoro!
--Huh? Is it morning?
It feels nice and warm.
A-Amazing!!
--Our net!
--What's with this forest?!
The doctrine of nonresistance...
Sounds nice, doesn't it?
Get ready, everyone! Cloud rudder full!
That's his house?! That's a palace!
Spring weather's nice.
Thanks for filling us in, old guy!
Is this Montblanc Cricket guy mega-rich?!
It looks like the seagulls are enjoying it, too.
How many times do I gotta say
we don't know how to get there?!
--It's him!
--What do you mean?!
The South Bird is the bugs' control tower!
Idiots! Look closely.
In addition to being weak, you have no pride.
Now comes the real problem.
A dreamer, huh? He does seem to be vain.
Let me start by saying this...
Put your lives on the line!
Why is a bird controlling bugs?!
You can't get into a single fight.
We're already near death...
But your head is full of dreams.
The Knock-Up Stream is a
current that shoots into the air...
Ahhhh! They were shot!!
Why?
You're just like worms.
You can theoretically take it
into the sky. Understand?
Oh, let's make yakitori!
Right on!
What the...?! It's just a board?!
Shot? I didn't hear any gunfire.
They're here! Where's it coming from?!
It's a current that can send ships flying, right?
What?!
Look, I found a bullet! Considering
the direction that they were flying,
The actual house is only half of it.
The rest is just a veneer.
Oh! Then it just needs to
send us above the clouds!
the bullets came from the
direction the ship's facing!
I'm done here.
Are you saying that shots came from
an island that we can't even see yet?
He seems like a very cheap guy.
What's that? I hear something different...
A weak-looking shorty worth 30 million...
Yahoo!
That's impossible, Chopper.
What kind of dreams did he talk about
that would get him driven out?
--Up ahead!
--Huh? Boulders?
On a current?
I wondered what kind of man he is.
But I was watching them the whole time.
But wouldn't we just end up
smashing back into the ocean?
I don't know the details,
They're rolling this way!
This isn't just a letdown, it's boring!
Then what kind of eyesight, sniping skills
and rifle do you think this sniper has?
Is it dung beetle dung?!
but I heard that he said a huge
amount of gold rests in Jaya.
No! They're bugs!
Normally, yeah. The key is timing.
I've never met cowards like them before.
Ladybugs!
They were shot somewhere else
and just happened to fall now.
Gold?!
It's easy to talk about
being sent up the current,
They're huge! Oww!
Is that some pirate's buried
treasure or something?
Damn things!
Sanji, we got seagulls!
Well, I don't know.
but it's not gonna be as nice
a trip as you guys think.
Gold!!
Dig the ground, Chopper! Gold will appear!
There's no end to 'em!
Why is your mole cricket army attacking me?!
It will if I dig?
Poor thing... He must've suffered.
The Knock-Up Stream is a natural disaster.
Hey, get them out of my face.
Living alone in such a remote area?
You're in the way! Do you
think you can beat me?! Huh?!
Hello. I'm coming in.
It's something that should
normally be avoided!
I wasn't able to kill one of them instantly.
They're eyesores.
Couldn't you wait a moment?!
But that's also fate.
Hm? No one's here. Hello!!
I can hear it, but I can't see it...
How exactly does a water
current rise into the sky?
That's the result of how you lived.
S-Slug!
Look at them!
No answer...
We've never heard of
anything like that before...
--Salt! Throw salt!
--Sanji! Your Somersault Kick!
You idiot, wait! What're you
gonna do if this guy's dangerous?
Hey, everyone! No one's home!
--Alright!
--Not that kind of "salt"!
Yeah!
Hm? This is...
Naturally, we can only guess as to
how that monstrous current works.
Hey, you! Do you know who I am?!
I'm sick of running! Bring it on!
Luffy! Zoro!
...a picture book.
Huh? I don't know, you fool!
This is quite an old book.
No, Luffy! Bear-bees are really poisonous!
Hey, woman.
No one's dumb enough to
jump in and find out, after all.
How about I tell you, then?
I'm the Fighting Champion.
Hm? It's titled "Noland the Liar."
You won't be able to move forward
into the new era if you're with him.
The accepted theory goes like this!
--Fireflies!
--So pretty!
Wow, that's a cool title! Nice idea for a book!
Cockroaches!
How about I buy you?
Pigs!
Wow! Cool!
"Noland the Liar"?
What'll it cost to have you come with me?
Deep beneath the sea floor,
there are large cavities,
I see a neat-looking town!
You know it, Sanji-kun? But it says
it was published in the North Blue.
Hey, hey, doesn't it look kinda like a resort?
and low-temperature
sea water seeps into them.
--Resort?!
--Hurry up, Merry!
Yeah. I was born in the North Blue.
What was that? You're going to buy me?
The heat from the earth below
turns that water into steam,
Yeah, it makes me feel like
I want to stick around a bit.
Haven't I told you guys?
We gladly accept fights people pick with us!
and the resulting pressure causes
an explosion on the sea floor.
That's right. Join us. It'll be fun.
That's news. I thought you
were from the East, too.
Don't underestimate the Saruyama Alliance!
One big enough to send the sea flying
and create a current into the sky!
--I grew up there.
--Quiet, Chopper! What're you doing?!
Get 'em!
What?!
But is it my imagination, or do the ships
lined up in the harbor look like pirate ships?
"Noland the Liar"
Hate to say it,
Hand over your gold quietly,
or else you're gonna pay dearly!
This is a famous story in the North.
but I'm too good for a team
of small fries like you!
Silly Usopp, since when can pirate ships
just openly line up in a harbor?!
It's a fairy tale, but I've heard that this
Noland guy actually existed long ago.
For about one minute, the sea
continues to rise into the sky.
How do you figure?
One minute?! What size of explosion
are we talking about here?!
Y-You're right!
How stuck up!
This is a story from long, long ago...
Help me! He's gonna kill me!
The explosions change location each time,
What's with this town?
A story that took place 400 long years ago.
Their gang is nothing but dumbasses!
and occur five times a month.
O-Old man!
Monkey Punch!
They're hopeless!
You want us to be blown into smithereens...?!
What a weakling!
A man named Montblanc Noland
lived in a North Blue country.
But, y'know,
Hey, mister. You chose
the wrong guy to beat up.
describing a grand natural phenomenon
with words and logic is foolish.
Look at that symbol. He's one of Roshio's gang.
Noland, an explorer, always talked
about his incredible adventures.
S-So, basically, we gotta ride this current
that only appears five times a month
Take those two and beat it already
You've heard of him, right?
Roshio the Executioner,
while you're still alive, you small fries!
However, the villagers couldn't tell
if those stories were true or not.
whose bounty is 42 million Berries.
He's crazy, so you'd better be careful.
and hope the sky island shows up?
Yeah. And if you miss, you'll fall
back down, slam into the ocean...
One day, he reported to the King
after coming back from his travels.
Hey, don't ever come back!
What a reckless guy!
That wasn't a bogus game.
You know it's dangerous for kids
to swing stuff like that around!
"I saw a mountain of gold
on an island in the great sea."
But it's amazing that he beat up
Roshio the Executioner so easily.
...and then you'll all end up
at the bottom of the sea.
The sky island exists.
Don't you know? That's Bellamy.
The courageous king set sail to the
great sea to see if the story was true,
Well then, I guess we should
get this midnight show started!
A-Alright! Let's give up on the sky island!
That guy?! Bellamy the Hyena,
the one with a 55 million-Berry
bounty on his head?!
taking 2,000 soldiers along with him.
Spring...
It's impossible!
--Captain!
--Who did this?!
You gotta have the luckiest luck
that's ever lucked to make it there!
...Snipe!
After surviving great storms
and battling against monsters,
In any case, he needs a doctor! Hurry up!
Captain, please hang on a little longer.
The cherry pies here really are the best!
only the King, Noland and 100
soldiers made it to the island.
You're that guy...
We'll be fine! Let's go!
Why so angry, young lady?
How did I know?
"We'll be fine"? How can you say
such groundless stuff so easily...?!
They're the ones who won the fight.
However, what they found
there was just a jungle.
I mean, just look at the Going Merry now!
What?
In the end, he was sentenced
to death for the crime of lying.
It looks so pitiful!
Oh? You'll surpass us?
It can't stand up to a
gigantic disaster like that!
Noland's last words were as follows:
There're all kinds of people here.
That's true. Even in mint condition,
that ship wouldn't stand a chance.
We'll meet again when we
become distinguished pirates.
It looks like a fun town.
"That's right! The mountain
of gold sank in the sea!"
Way to go, Bellamy! Yay!
There's no way...
What?!
Speed, weight, strength...
You think those two can come
back without getting into trouble?
The King and the others were dumbfounded.
Your sharp retort was really something, too.
That boat'd be blasted apart in the explosion.
No one believed Noland any longer
Well, the town looks dangerous as it is.
What do you think of our captain's
"Spring-Spring Fruit" powers?
You've got nerves of steel.
It's next to impossible.
because Noland continued
to lie until his very death.
But... See! It really is impossible!
--That's right. They can't do that!
--H-Hey, Nami!
Speechless, huh?
Zoro!
Wait for me, Luffy! Zoro!
Luffy!
But don't you worry about that.
Clean up the trash! Take care of 'em!
This book is based on the North Blue
fairy tale "Noland the Liar."
I'll have Masira and Shojo
help take you there.
She went...
Only after we strengthen your ship, of course.
Well, she'll probably be okay,
since those two are with her.
The new era they're talking about is crap!
Montblanc Cricket is a descendant
of that Montblanc Noland?!
What? If Nami-san's going, then I'm...
Yeah! Just leave it to us!
So much for your Saruyama Alliance!
Don't you go!!
Thanks, guys!
The era where pirates have dreams
will be over, they say?! Huh?!
I heard that fairy tale a lot when I was a kid.
If you go, wh-what'll happen
i-i-if this ship is attacked...?!
Didn't even ask us...
You're just an old man and
a couple of overgrown apes!
There isn't anyone in the North Blue
who doesn't know the tale.
--Do you even understand?!
--Understand what?
What's going on?
Please don't go!!
We're all from the North Blue,
so we often got told
Fine! Let go of me!
For starters... Yeah!
Jackpot, Bellamy!
This is definitely it!
The most we can stay on
this island is one more day!
Then, guess I'll prepare
some tea and hold the fort.
that if we lied a lot, we'd be
sentenced to death like Noland.
People's dreams... have no end!!
Hm? Where's Robin-chan?
Oh! Would you look at that?
Wonderful gold bullion!
After that, the Log Pose will
start pointing to the next island!
Oh...? She's not here.
This is getting more and more interesting!
There's more! Wow!
Yeah! Yeah! We won't make it in time!
--Sanji-kun, about that tea...
--Make it yourself.
I never would've imagined that
Jaya was the island in that fairy tale.
This's a big haul!
Seriously, old man! You're not a psychic!
Isn't that right?!
In this town, I will...
And, after 400 years,
a descendant of Noland the Liar
I doubt you know,
but how many days will it be
You guys... aren't qualified to have that gold...!
--...not fight. I give my word!
--...not fight. I give my word.
Hey, hey...
is looking for the gold on this island, huh?
until the Knock-Up Stream and
the cumuloregalis clouds line up?!
What're you suddenly shouting about?
Good. This is serious, you two.
In order to clear the name of his ancestor,
Qualified?
No, no! How many months?!
No, how many years?!
What's this about people's dreams?
--Yeah...
What's with the weak reply?!
who was called a big liar
and laughed at until he died...
Is this qualified enough for ya?!
Outdoing others isn't easy!
If you cause trouble,
we'll have to leave this town!
Tomorrow afternoon.
If you're going, you better get ready!
Big Chop!
Has your brain melted?!
This family cracks me up!
We can't make it in that time!
If that happens, we won't be
able to go to the sky, got that?!
Oh? If you don't like it, then just quit!
You fool...
Yeah.
What's going on? I hear a ruckus outside.
Does he really think that
he can clear the name
Who's he?
Don't bother. Those guys might be goin'
on a rampage 'cause they're pissed.
Y-You're lying!
Look, he fell from a horse.
We're way stronger than you are!
of his 400 year-old ancestor by
bringing back a few pieces of gold?!
Yeah, he did.
This isn't right! We just met you today!
Aren't you being too nice?!
How much more qualified do we
need to be to steal treasure?!
How sad!
Sounds like he's weak in the head!
--Looks like he's in pain.
--Yeah, it does.
Plus...!
Well, old man?!
They can go ahead and laugh at us.
Hey you guys, sorry to bother you,
but please help me get up.
--Hold on, Usopp!
--Shut up, you!
Watch out, old-timer!
When you aim high, you sometimes
come across fights not worth fighting.
Tomorrow just happens
to be the perfect chance
Havoc Sonar!
You're not going to get up
by yourself, are you?
to go to this legendary,
unknown "sky island"?!
Isn't that right?!
--Luffy, get that side.
--Okay.
Alas, the liar died...
And you'll help strengthen
our ship and take us there?!
Well, thanks... I'm on the horse now.
Let's go.
Y-Yeah... Luffy?
That's way too convenient!
...before he could even become
a brave warrior on the sea.
I was born frail.
What exactly are you scheming?!
Bastard!
Wait, Sarquiss!
Plus you're Noland the Liar's
descendant! We can't trust you!
Now, let's go, Stronger.
Don't look at me! And don't add in a
heartbreaking sentence on your own!
I'll end his life.
The horse, too?!
Not that again... The power
of the Spring-Spring Fruit...!
Geez, what a pain.
Luffy!
Luffy fell into the sea!!
Thanks again.
Oh, looks like I interrupted you.
What're you doing?!
Old-timer! Dinner's ready!
Run, Shojo!
Who the hell are you?!
This isn't much of a reward,
but would you like some?
Are you in a hurry?
Move!
Spring...
You've got guts, relaxing at someone's
house without permission!
Nami-san! Dinner's--
You're too suspicious! We don't
want any, so beat it already.
I hope you can go to the sky island!
The sea in this area is my turf!
...Snipe!
W-What?! Are you gonna fight?!
--Hey, apples! Thanks!
--Hey, hey!
--Hey, Usopp! Go grab Luffy!
--Got it!
Shojo!
You're after the gold, aren't you? Die!
Whenever "midday night"
is confirmed in Masira's turf,
What?! What happened?!
cumuloregalis clouds appear in
the southern skies the next day.
Well, some guys were eating apples
that they got from a strange man,
Ah...
and then they exploded. Five of them!
And judging from its five-per-month rate,
the Knock-Up Stream will
probably be active tomorrow.
Oh, no...
--Sanji!!
--Sanji-kun!
Luffy! Spit it out! Spit out
the apple you just ate! Now!
Don't worry. It didn't hit me.
Hey, he might've known
something about the sky island.
It'll happen somewhere south of here.
I've already swallowed it.
Old-timer! We found gold! A bell-shaped ingot!
You bastard! What's the meaning of this?!
Hold on!
It's not a 100% certainty, but there's
a good chance it'll be tomorrow!
I wonder who he is.
Idiot... You shouldn't
underestimate your opponent.
I don't know... And it's not "he."
Well, he's all right.
Move! I'll handle this!
What? It's not "he"? Then what?
--That's going too far!
--It's a disaster inside.
"They," probably...
If you ate a bad one,
you would've died on the first bite.
I'm glad to have met fools like you.
What do you mean?!
Look! It matches what's listed
in the logbook! It mentions bells!
Do you mean there were
others with him? Where?! Hey!
Hey, what were you doing?!
You're...
I saw... bubbles coming out of the water.
Now, let's go and have some food!
Take it easy at my place today...
...lucky.
--This is awful...
--Hey, what the hell is this?
So I was looking in the water,
then suddenly a chestnut appeared.
...comrades!
Roshio the Executioner's grave.
The chestnut was actually a guy,
and he dragged me into the water.
Alright, let's go. Load the gold on board.
The drinks sure taste good today!
It looks as if a war happened here.
Grow up, old man!
--Food! Hurry, Usopp!
--Yeah! C'mon!
Hey, old guy!
Did they fire a cannon or something
in the middle of the town?
Who knows? Even people who
were actually watching it said
--Chopper! Go get Robin-chan!
--Right!
This "city of gold" is just a
product of Noland's imagination!
Bring more cold towels! Open up the windows!
that they couldn't tell what was happening.
If you wanna be a pirate
in the coming new era,
Looks like all we can do is try
our best to get into the sky...
All we know is that Roshio's
opponent was Bellamy.
--Caisson disease?
--Is this guy sick?
--Panel!
--Here!
then you need to realize
that dreams never come true!
Though in the end, it's up to luck...
Yeah, it's a sickness that divers sometimes get.
Oh, Bellamy the Hyena?
Nami. Am I miserable and cowardly?
--Nail!
--Here!
There's no doubt that he's got
the power of one of the devil fruits.
But it doesn't usually become
a longstanding condition.
You forgot "stupid."
The city of gold does exist!
--Panel!
--Here!
I know how you feel. Now go apologize.
Due to a lack of decompression
when surfacing from the seabed,
The pain...!
Hey, now! Don't go wild! It's a small house!
Here!
the nitrogen dissolved in the
blood gets released quickly
I'm sorry, old guy!
Here...
Seriously... I know I'm repeating myself,
but I'm not a shipwright.
and forms gas bubbles at that time.
Wait, kiddo...
What the...?! Yuck! Don't wipe your snot on me!
Since the gas bubbles expand
inside and outside of blood vessels,
they cause problems to
blood flow, muscle and joints.
But you're really handy with stuff, Usopp.
Aren't I?! That's the amazing thing about me.
So it's some bizarre phenomenon, huh?
Just what is up with this town?!
Today's booze is especially great!
We should just buy a new ship instead.
He probably kept diving
every day without giving time
Well, don't be so touchy, Nami.
Are you nuts?! Do you know
how we got this ship?!
A hatchling who doesn't have the
guts to pick fights with dreams...
Eat up, eat up! The saury full
course is just getting started!
You almost got killed for no reason, you know!
for those bubbles to disappear from the body.
Here!
Yeah, yeah, I've heard it so many times.
I guess it happens sometimes.
...is in no position to talk about pirates!
Gotcha, salvage bum!
That's a Tabasco Bomber!
It was given to you guys by a
pretty girl from your village, right?!
What for?!
I'll be damned if it does!
I don't know, but he's taking a risk.
What was that?
Why, you! Long-nose!
But still, it's dangerous to keep
traveling on a ship in this condition.
In some cases, caisson disease can...
Girlie! Come sit here!
That's why I'm repairing it!
Give us a hand here!
That guy again...
It's 100 years too early to
have Nami-san wait on you!
...cause death.
How many victims have there been now?
It's not like he's a famous
wanted man. Who the heck is he?
Repair? You call this repair?
You're just patching it.
Shut up!
Well, I don't even wanna know.
Hey, that's a funny face, Usopp!
In any case, we should stay away
from that Fighting Champion.
Oh, like this?
Shut up!
"I saw gold...
Oh hey, it's you, Masira. So you're alive.
Champion?
...in the skull's right eye!"
Oh, yeah... About tonight's dinner...
Why are you trying to compete?!
Gold?!
Alive? What're you talking about?
Shut up!
No luck. We couldn't even see a single one...
Never mind. In any case,
what was that gunfire about?
Ugh... I wonder if we can really
get information in a town like this.
--Oh, so you don't want any?
--Ahhh!
That tear-soaked sentence was
the last thing Noland wrote.
--Ahhh! We do!!
--Now, I wonder how the seagull
stock soup is coming along.
We saw one, but there was no time
for the bird, with all those bugs...
Exactly, brother! Do you think
something happened to the old-timer?
--We do!! Sanji-kun!!
--Now, I wonder how the seagull
stock soup is coming along.
Let's hurry! I'm getting all worked up!
--Please let us eat!!
--Now, I wonder how the seagull
stock soup is coming along.
"I saw gold in the skull's right eye..."
--How about this place?
--Hmm... This place seems quiet.
Sanji-kun!!
All we did was run...
Hm?
Old-timer! Are you all right?!
Yeesh! Seven people, and you get zilch?!
Get it together, you guys!
Noland was executed that same day.
Salvage, salvage...
Or rather, this place is lovely!
Even after coming to Jaya,
those words make no sense at all.
They've come to kill us!!
That includes you!
So although this is a rough town,
it has a place like this.
What're you guys doing here?!
--Salvage, salvage...
--Wh-What's with that ship?
I can't run any more!
"The skull's right eye..."
They have a vacation house on the sea, huh?
What did you do to the old-timer?!
Is it referring to the name
of a city that once existed?
In any case, there's no one here...
although I can smell tasty food.
What? We're looking after this guy
right now, so go somewhere else.
--Salvage...
--This song is...!
Or was it an allusion to his own death?
Idiot! They aren't really gonna hear us out!
The blank pages that follow say nothing...
E-Excuse me! Please don't
come in without permission!
--They're savages, you know!
--You know!
"You really think you can catch us? Idiots!"
So that's why we dive!
--Everyone, evacuate through the windows!
--You...
Th-This Tropical Hotel is currently
chartered by Bellamy-sama and his party.
We have a dream! On the sea floor!
What?! He came here to tell us that?!
...guys are so nice!
That's right!
Dammit! I'll shoot you good!
They're listening!
So we're asking other guests to, er... leave.
We're gonna fly!
Oh, this place was a hotel?
Not if you keep eating like that, we won't!
I-If Bellamy-sama sees you, it'll be a problem,
so please kindly leave immediately.
All I needed was to see one.
C'mon, what's wrong with just coming in here?
It's gotten quite late, but I see it, Bellamy.
Who's Bellamy?
Old guy! We caught a bird!
Hey, what's going on?
You guys live here, too?
Prepare to go ashore.
Who the hell are those shabby guys?
L-L-L-L-Luffy! Zoro!
Old diamond-head!
Well, the old-timer's house is the
headquarters of the Saruyama Alliance.
Dream-chasing fools deserve
more than a few lumps!
Masira!
Sarquiss-sama! Welcome back!
Well, this is just...
Why are you wounded?! What happened?!
Shojo!
Nami-san! Are you all right?!
But we sleep on our ships most of the time
What in the world happened?!
Never mind your excuses!
Just get rid of them already!
How much do you think we're
paying to charter this place?!
D-D-D-Doctor!!
because this house is too small for us.
Damn! Who did this?!
She's right. Now, go home, you dumb brat!
So check them out already!
It's because you guys are too big.
Ow...
--Hey! Gimme a hand!
--Right!
--Hey, can I beat him up?
--No!
Well, to those Giant guys you
look like a ball of earwax, though.
Look! The Going Merry...!
So, what kind of Moguera
monster did you fight?
Ha! You're going to beat me up?
What the hell?! Who did this?!
Dammit! Who was it?!
Why are they getting along so well?
What funny guys! At any rate,
those are rags you're wearing.
"The day I arrived on Jaya.
Entry for May 21, 1122."
They can probably relate to each other.
Pirates. But that's okay, it's all over now.
--Sorry...
--Old guy!
But it's amazing that you guys
kicked him off when you're so small!
Yeah.
Here! Take this money and buy
yourselves something you like.
Even if it's over for you guys,
it's not over for me!
Noland! Noland!
--Hey, old guy! Are you awake?!
--I'm truly sorry!
"Upon landing on the island,
we heard strange bird calls
Sarquiss, you're wasting money
by giving it to guys like them.
--Really? You can do it, too.
--Oh, really?
What's with you guys?! You're men, right?!
There's nothing we could do! We're pathetic!
and the sound of a very large
bell coming from the forest.
When someone provokes you, you should
just go ahead and beat them all up!
Yeah, you can because you're a monkey.
But... there's still time to
strengthen the ship before sunup...!
Maybe I should have thrown
it down the drain instead.
Luffy, he's come around!
Actually, better yet, why not just
blow up this whole annoying town!!
Oh? Are you sure?
He's awake?!
The sound from that huge
gold bell resonated far and wide,
--Let's go! This is unpleasant!
--Hey, hey, I can walk on my own.
So what was that stuff you said earlier?!
Wait, old guy! Tell us what happened first!
Hey, he's right, I can kick Masira...
Oh? You don't want it?
What's past is past!
Don't talk about ancient history!
almost as if showing off the
prosperity of a city long past!
No... It's okay. Don't worry about it.
Doesn't matter now...
Sarquiss! Lily! Don't tease them so much.
Hey old diamond-head!
I wanna ask you something!
Do you want me to floor you?!
Hey, what's she in such a mood
about when she's unhurt?
We thought we knew everything
after living for a few decades..."
Oh, that's where you were.
More importantly, you need to...
I don't know.
They, too, worked hard in their
own way to travel here. Here.
Sorry I caused you trouble.
Oh, yeah! Did you get any
information about the sky island?
Ah! Great! You caught yourselves a South Bird!
Noland! Noland!
I thought you were just
more idiots after the gold.
Sky... island...?
"...but experiencing the transience
of this civilization that flourished
Of course, compared to you
and Bellamy, they're trash, but...
Perfect!
What?! You have gold bullion?
Luffy!
Don't go after it.
Who cares?! All I did was mention "sky island,"
for a long time on the wide
open sea left us speechless!
For average guys, they're
doing better than others.
The gold... It's been stolen!
What is it that you wanna ask me?
Well, they probably won't be able to survive
in the new era that is about to start, after all.
Old guy, we wanna go to the sky island!
Please tell us how to get there!
and the entire bar broke out laughing.
The sound of the bell had
us stopped in our tracks!"
Did I say something funny?!
Still... I see, 30 million... for that greenhorn?
Sky island?
What's with them?!
Nah, it's alright... Forget about that junk...
Noland's so cool!
Ketchup Star!
Guard Point!
I'll show this to Bellamy.
You guys believe in the sky island?
Wow! A giant gold bell!
It's quite lively up there.
Why are you so upset?
You need to focus on...
Dammit! I'm really pissed!!
What do you mean, "junk"?!
Wait a minute, old guy!
You like Noland after all!
Hey, stop it! He's a sick person!
Oh! Welcome back, Robin-chan!
That's a shame.
It took you ten long years
of diving into the ocean
There's no sky island, old guy?!
Mock Town depends on pirates
who spend lots of money, after all.
Would you like to eat first,
or shall I prepare your bath?
--Look at this!
--Wow! Gold bells!
and torturing your body
until you found that gold!
Oh, Robin, did you go somewhere?
--You can't just...
--Quiet!
No one knows.
So poor pirates aren't invited, huh?
So, how exactly are those "giant"?
Yeah. I got some clothes and
information about the sky island.
I know someone who said there is.
Looks like there's no way
of calming you down.
These aren't that bell.
They're bell-shaped ingots.
It's alright... This's our problem...
That's right! You, Robin!!
But people call him a legendary big liar!
Here, this is on the house.
--Jumping Point!
--This all happened because you
started talking about that sky island!
We found these three on the sea floor.
Listen!
Since tough guys gather here,
there's lots of trouble.
His family became a laughing stock forever.
Ingots?
If they all work on it, the Saruyama Alliance
If it doesn't exist,
Oh! So there really is a city of gold!
But if you get bothered by it each time,
you can't get by in this town.
--Hey, Chopper!
--I'll send you to a watery grave!
It's not me!
can fix and reinforce that ship, no problem.
They don't prove that.
Ahh, leave her alone for now!
All you can do is play it safe
when dealing with people.
There's an old story that
most North Blue people know.
You could find that much gold in any old ruins.
I'll have 'em finish in time for morning!
Or rather, you'd better not get
close to her. Just don't rock the boat.
Here you go.
But this town is really unpleasant, you know!
"Noland the Liar" is the one.
There won't be any trouble
with your departure tomorrow!
But it does prove that there
was a civilization in this area.
That's probably how a
right-minded person would think.
Here, Captain.
Like I said, it's not me!
He's got a different name, right?!
Listen! We will send you
into the sky, without fail!
Oh! It's a treasure map!
Ingots are made to have standardized weights.
But unfortunately, right-minded
people are rare in this town.
Come to think of it, Noland's name is,
if I'm not mistaken, Montblanc Noland.
Hm? Isn't it just an ordinary map? Where is it?
Old-timer...
Which means they were used for trade.
Well, the log will be stored
within four days or so.
It's this island.
Could it be that you're Noland's...
So you should leave before you get into trouble.
The town drawn on the left is
Mock Town, where we are now.
Yes. And the strange bird calls
mentioned before that...
Hey, Luffy.
A descendant?! Could this place
be the island in that story?!
Four days... Then we can't stay even two days.
And you see an x on the other side, right?
Hey, Masira!
Hmph! He's my granddad's
granddad's granddad's...
Hey, mister!
I heard that a man who doesn't
blend in in Jaya lives there.
--Whoa! There's more?!
--This one's huge!
--Hey, old guy!
--Hey, buddy!
Bellamy's mark...
Hm? What's wrong?
--That's all of 'em.
--Wow! It's so pretty!
He's my distant ancestor... What a nuisance.
--This cherry pie tastes extremely bad! Hm?
--This cherry pie tastes extremely good! Hm?
Doesn't blend in?!
His name is Montblanc Cricket.
Want help?
Gold bells and a bird...
I doubt there's a drop
of his blood in my body...
No, I can do it alone.
Do you suppose they were symbols of old Jaya?
No, Luffy! Don't be stupid!
We set sail in only three hours!
A man who talked about dreams
and was driven out of this town.
You might have something
in common to discuss.
Although the Montblanc family
was driven out of the country then,
Dunno, but I think they were
part of some sort of model.
and has kept a low profile,
people continue to
denounce our family to this day.
Then, why don't we try going there?
--This drink tastes exceptionally good! Hm?
--This drink tastes exceptionally bad! Hm?
This here's called a South Bird,
and they still exist on this island!
If I run along the coast, will I reach
the town from this afternoon?
Hey, wait a sec, Luffy. I'm not sure
if we should go now because...
But no one in the family hates him.
Is there something wrong with your tastebuds?
Yes, you will.
Oh! Do they have weird calls?
Hey, Chopper, you saw it
earlier, too, didn't you?
Yep. Just like the logbook says!
Why?
Is there something wrong with your head?
Hey, kid! Where're you going?!
Because Noland was an
extraordinarily honest person.
Sailors have long used South Birds to...
Well, since I'm not the cook,
I don't care what you say.
Don't be a fool! Do you
know who you're dealing--
What're you guys doing?
But in that picture book...
I thought I was a goner!
Noland's last excuse in
the picture book is like this.
Oh, crap!
Hey, old guy! Give me 50 steaks to go!
Geez, you're such a pain.
If you wanna stop him, use this.
What is it?! What's wrong?!
But Nami was...
Buddy, give me 51 cherry pies to go!
"That's right! The mountain
of gold sank in the sea!"
This is bad! You guys! Go into
the forest! The southern forest!
What?! What about me?!
K-Kid...
You tryin' to say I'm some
simple-minded idiot?!
Wait, make that 52 steaks!
Huh?! What're you talking about?!
Are you crazy, old guy?!
A stupid-looking face is drawn in this book...
Sorry, I want 53 pies!
Go catch this bird! Right now!
--No, 54 steaks!
--55 pies!
I'll be back by morning!
...but he shed many tears
and died a regrettable death.
Big boss! Undersea preparations complete!
Why?! What for?!
--60 steaks!
--70 pies!
Why do we need a bird?
I'm empty now! That's every
last drop of water in my body!
--80!
--100!
Listen closely! The Knock-Up Stream
you're heading for tomorrow
The mic's ready, too!
He was sure that the island
he reached was Jaya,
You bastard! Wanna fight?!
Alright! Starting the search sonar!
What the hell are you fighting about?!
where he found the wreckage of a city of gold.
is located directly south of this cape.
Now I won't sweat a single drop!
Luffy, you promised, remember?!
He felt that there was no way
it was just an illusion.
How are you going to get there?!
Besides, we don't have enough
money to buy dozens of steaks!
This ol' drunk is broke and dry!
Just sail straight there, right?
We didn't come for shopping!
Noland insisted that the ruins had
submerged due to crustal movements,
This is the Grand Line, you know!
Are you a pirate?
Once you're on the open sea,
there's no way to get your bearings!
O, God of Alcohol, thank you for today!
Yeah, that's right.
but everyone thought he was
making excuses out of desperation.
What's the bounty for you?
That's right!
30 million!
We're heading for ocean, not an island,
so we have no guide to rely on!
30 million? For you?
Noland was executed in front
of the laughing onlookers,
But I guess there's no such thing...
Can't be true! It's gotta be a lie!
Then how do we go straight south?
and only the name "Liar" remained.
I'm not lying! That's the truth!
A newspaper?
Oh, I see! You're looking for
the city of gold on the seabed
You use that bird's behavior!
Stop it!
Let's see! What bad news is there today?
Hey, no fighting in the bar!
Some types of animals have
accurate, internal magnets
in order to clear the Montblanc family's name!
Take this and leave now! 50 cherry pies!
Oh, this isn't a newspaper.
It's a stack of wanted posters...
Don't be silly!
which allow them to get their bearings.
Usopp!!
I thought I'd die...
Honestly, this is a lawless town!
I'm sick of meeting new bad guys!
Then you're lower than an animal, Zoro!
How honest my distant ancestor was,
This is Utan Diver Number 27!
Sonar response confirmed!
Like you're anyone to talk!
or how great an explorer he was,
has nothing to do with me!
School of fish detected at 9 o'clock!
South Birds are the greatest of such animals!
From it's swimming speed,
we've determined that it's saury.
This is that spineless kid from this afternoon!
Can you understand how a kid would
feel being laughed at by strangers
Alright! We'll have them
roasted whole for dinner!
No matter how vast the land
or sea they're thrown into,
Boy, that sky island talk was a real hoot!
just because he's the
descendant of such an idiot?!
their bodies will always indicate
the direction accurately.
This is Diver Number 4!
Sonar response confirmed!
That's how I grew up!
Thirty million, I believe he was worth...
Small sailing vessel
detected traveling on the sea!
Is there a pirate with a straw hat here?
Anyway, without one of these birds,
you're going nowhere!
Hm?
But... yeah, over the past 400 years,
many set sail to restore our family's honor,
Crap! I had a little too much to drink!
What?! A vessel?
Determine the exact direction!
I-It's Bellamy!
You won't even get the
chance to go to the sky island!
Let's see...
1, 10, 100, 1,000, 10,000,
100,000, 1,000,000, 10,000,000...
Let's see... I'd say it's at 12 o'clock!
Eh?!
Why are you telling us this now?!
So, you're the 30 million bounty,
Straw Hat Luffy!
It's already close enough to see!!
though all of them went missing.
Quit fussing!
Yikes! I really did drink too much!
Stop the search and return
to the ship, Utan Divers!!
There's no time! Hurry! Don't dilly-dally!
What's this about?
I was ashamed of such a family.
Looks like he's got business with you, Luffy.
You want us to go into the forest
in the middle of the night?!
Isn't Bellamy the guy chartering that hotel?
I ran away from home and became a pirate.
1, 10, 100, 1,000, 10,000,
100,000, 1,000,000, 10,000,000...
You forgot these!
Oh? You're a pirate, too?
Did you hear that?
That shorty's worth 30 million.
We're gonna get started on your beat-up ship!
It's not that I wanted to become a pirate.
--He is?
--Is that true?
I just wanted to escape from Noland's spell.
Didn't take long for us to
come across something weird...
Now that I think about it,
there was no time to be partyin'!
Boy, I keep running into tall guys today.
...100,000,000!
But it doesn't look like the
same guys from before, Usopp.
And over time, I came to
have my own pirate group.
Give me your most expensive alcohol.
Again, why are you telling us this now?!
Three hours, Luffy!
And give this shorty what he wants as well.
Listen! Make sure you catch at
least one South Bird before dawn!
Well, whether that's a good thing
or a bad thing is another story.
At long last, I entered the Grand Line,
Okay.
and I spent all my time on adventures.
If we delay our departure any more than that...
Huh? This place is full!
In any case, we did see them! Right?
But ten years ago, my ship
reached this island by accident.
--It's pitch dark!
--Quit pulling me!
Yeah. As we thought,
that salvager is from this island!
What is this place? It's stinky and dirty!
It's not my fault! My hands
are moving on their own!
And cheap-looking rum
is about all they've got.
...you'll lose your chance to go to the sky island!
We saw his ship coming back!
Look. They're from earlier.
Strangely enough, only I,
I see... but I don't mind seeing him again.
My stomach's so full...
I don't think I can chase birds...
who continued to hate the Montblanc
family and Noland the most, made it here.
He must've done reckless diving day after day
You should offer us your seats, geez...
Hey hey, you guys! Quit mumbling over there!
Where are these weird birds?!
without letting those bubbles
disappear from his body!
The island didn't have a city of gold,
just like the picture book said.
What hopeless dumbasses!
Let's just catch one so we
can get back to drinking!
How did we wind up doing this so suddenly?!
Ha! Honestly, I got all worked up
wondering who you guys were!
As I stood on a cape of the island,
I felt that it was destiny.
That's him, Big Knife Sarquiss, right?
This is a duel with the man
who screwed up my life.
--You're in the way!
--Man! Couldn't he have told us during the day?!
There was no place to escape to.
Is he going to start a fight here or something?
Let's settle this, Noland!
No way...
Hey, where are the birds?
That's quite a reckless face
you've got! What species are you?
If we knew where they were,
we wouldn't be out looking for 'em!
"Deer"
The whole gang is here. There's
no way they just came for a drink.
Hell, no! Captain, we're not gonna have
anything to do with your family's problem!
Sorry! I'm truly sorry!
I'm human, you moron!
You punks! Don't you know Shojo-sama?!
Our only clue is that they have a weird call...
There's nothing we could do! We're pathetic!
Leave them be! It has nothing to do with us!
And they look just like that gold statue...
If you insist on searching
for the gold, do it alone!
He's the big boss of the Shojo Pirates
and the king of undersea search!
Bellamy sure is a curious one.
Are there really such dumb-looking birds?!
He sure is.
Damn him!
Don't make our big boss angry!
We're splitting here. Goodbye, Captain.
Plus "weird call" is way too vague!
How're we supposed to know?!
Well, have a drink.
Now, now...
Oh, thanks! You're actually a nice guy!
Looks like you're pirates.
He said we'd know once we're in the forest...
Those big apes were hilarious!
If it's there, that's fine.
If it's not there, that's fine, too.
Did you know that Crocodile, one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea, was defeated?
They had huge gashes all over
and had tears and snot dripping down
It's not that I want to prove his innocence.
A weird call!
as they cried, "Old-timer!"
That's it!
When you consider my abilities,
that post may come to me.
Alright!
At this point, we got no other choice!
This is a duel with the man
who threw a wrench into my life.
Darn! He did it!
If he's that important,
they should've protected him better!
We have three nets. Let's split
into three groups and search!
So I've been getting all worked
up waiting to be contacted.
Bellamy's nuts!
Right!
Right?!
Let's go! Let's beat up those weird birds!
Talk about lame!
I want to set the record straight before I die.
I see... Then you want to become one
of the Seven Warlords of the Sea?
Don't be like that.
You mean catch!
They couldn't help it; they were
up against you and Bellamy!
What's the meaning of this, small fry?
Well, in any case, the great part about me
After all, our captain is a major
rookie worth 55 million berries!
Why don't you tell me?
is that I haven't had my hair
cut in all my 25 years of life.
This is indeed a man's...
Don't worry! Whatever we run into,
I'll protect you, Nami-san!
Then, what about them?
Why are those monkeys, here?
Bad news!
Zoro! Hold on a minute!
Now, aren't you surprised?
Sanji-kun! What about me?!
What's the deal?! It's the middle of the night!
We haven't gotten any
information in this town yet!
There must've been an exciting drama
Hell if I care! Quit being insecure!
Shut up! I'm just taking him up on his offer!
Sounds stupid.
In any case, let's catch a bird
so we can get out of this forest!
spoken with the fists of men
committed to exploring the seabed.
This afternoon! Those guys in here, they--!
Whoa! I'm surprised!
Hey, watch your mouth!
Oh! Bellamy! You're still here?!
Let's start by listening closely
for that bird we heard earlier.
Those guys are fans of the picture book.
Now, now... What you say
really gets me all worked up.
Hm? So you got back up!
Fans?!
That's a quite simple connection.
You gotta get out of here!
You're in the most danger!
I think it was five or six years ago.
Listen. You will come out of the tunnel
that is my anger into a sea of blood.
--That bird call!
--Jooo! Come out! Joooo!
So you're ready to take me on, huh?
They heard a rumor about
me and barged in on me.
Bastard!
What're you talking about? Me, in danger?
They said, "We think
Noland's gold definitely exists!"
Whoa! They're gonna take Bellamy on!
What're you catching me for?!
Okay, whatever...
but there's a place we wanna go.
Go for it!
Oh, Nami! That's a cool thing
you got on! Where'd you get it?
Don't get beaten!
Shojo!
So move aside.
What?
Idiot! This area is my turf!
Are you ready to take me on
after suddenly kicking me like that?!
This isn't a fight, it's a test!
Hey, that's an outrageous
false accusation, Masira!
C'mon! Let's see how strong you are!
If you wanna pass through, pay the toll!
Spider!
Don't make me angry!
Huh? It's just a spider!
You poor thing... Come here!
Luffy, wait!
What's he mean by his turf?
He's talking like Masira.
Hey, Mister! We want to go to the sky island!
The sea around here is deep.
Spiders are yucky, you moron!
Toss it away somewhere!
In the dark, cold sea, you're
haunted by a deeper solitude.
Do you know anything about it?
Huh? Did Masira say stuff like that?
What? Masira?! What about Masira?
Get away, Usopp! I bet it's poisonous!
I just dived and searched alone every day.
They're falling from the trees!
What did that chick... just say?
We kicked him off our boat, but...
This is too gross!
She can't be serious.
K-Kicked... Kicked...?!
It's probably a species of tarantula!
They just came into my life
It's alright! They won't spit poison
as long as we don't do anything!
--Big boss!
--Kicked?! How dare you do that to my brother?!
and became my underlings without
my permission, and they romp around.
--This is revenge for Masira!
--Hey, hold on a sec.
I used to fight spiders a long time ago!
Single-minded idiots like them...
make me feel relieved, to be honest.
No, you can count me out when
it comes to creepy bugs like that!
We kicked him, but he's still alive!
Like I said, if you know how
to get to the sky island...
Same here! I totally hate them!
Totally! Hurry and throw it far away!
Sound wave!!
100 million...?!
Do you understand?
Havoc Sonar!!
I do. Yeah, real comrades give
each other strength and...
Oh? But those moths and
centipedes don't bother you?
60 million?!
She said "sky island"!
Give me a break!
That's right! Those two from this afternoon!
Well, putting the story
about those monkeys aside...
What?!
Their bounties are higher than yours, Bellamy!
But the Log Pose is
definitely pointing to the sky!
Then, don't ask! Clench your teeth!
You're dead meat!
Like I said... I wanna go
to the sky island, old guy!
I hate moths and centipedes!
Ahh! Don't leave me behind!
"The Log Pose is definitely pointing to the sky!"
The ship is...!
Are you serious?! Crap!
We laughed at the wrong people!
You're a hasty one!
I hear screams...
Log Poses get broken easily!
Yeah, I did tell you, right? The witness
to the sky island is that Noland the Liar.
Forget about 'em.
Think they remember what we look like?!
It's dangerous to stay here!
--So... what're they doing?
--Big boss!
If you have anything to do with him,
you'll be laughed at like me.
Hey, you got me there.
--Who knows? But it's amazing.
--If you use that technique on the ship, it'll...!
A centipede, huh? It's pretty damn big...
You guys believe in such an ancient
legend that there's an island in the sky?
--He's destroying their ship with his voice.
--Oh, no! He's blinded by anger!
What?! He's been to the sky island, too?!
I never met anyone with a 100 million bounty!
It's not nice to kill everything. Poor thing...
Now everyone! Stop gawking and
let's get through here while we can!
Unfortunately, this doesn't say he did, but...
That's what it gets for trying to attack me.
Just which era are you from?
A logbook?! Could it be Noland's?
Okay!
Unusual currents in the Grand Line
are being explained one after another.
--But...
--What?!
Hey, Nami's not a demon any more.
That's right.
That's the path we just took here.
Really?!
Hey, hey, hey! You fools!
Scared of a few scraps of paper!
The Knock-Up Stream is one of them.
Yeah, she should be calmer
after letting off that much steam.
Read around there.
Amazing... A logbook from 400 years ago...
I guess you probably don't know
something like that even exists.
That bird call... This way.
Do you have knotholes for eyes?!
You saw their leader!
Sea Ephemeris Year 1120, June 21st, Sunny.
H-Hey... hold on!
The ships that fell victim to this
current are pushed up high in the sky,
Watch out for that quagmire.
This isn't good! The waves
made it to this ship after all!
and then slam into the ocean!
We left Villa, a cheerful town.
Hey! Wait for--!
Made it!
The ship's starting to fall apart,
particularly the repaired areas!
Following the Log Pose, we should be
heading east-northeast from the harbor.
Without knowing this, sailors from long ago
Did you know that there were once pirates
The ship's body is worn out enough as it is!!
saw the strange scene where the
ships fell, and imagined sky islands,
who faked their own wanted posters
to make names for themselves?
Gotcha!
If we stay here, the ship will be torn apart!!
We got a rare item from a bumboat
that we came across during the day.
Look, Chopper! It's an Atlas!
thinking, "There must be
another world in the sky!"
Atlas?
Yup! Atlases and Hercules are
the most admired bugs in the world!
People'd see their bounties
and just curl up and surrender,
Full speed ahead! To someplace
out of his voice's reach!
It's a ski-like one-person boat called a waver.
How foolish! All phenomena have reasons.
It's a mysterious boat that can generate wind
and move even on a day without wind.
Really? Beetles?
even though they could've won in a fight...
These things that people dream
about will all be explained soon!
You never heard of 'em?!
They're super hard to catch!
Just like you guys now!
It seems that you need to get the hang
of it to ride, and I couldn't manage it.
Which is better, them or the One Piece?!
You saw how weak they are,
but look at you now! You're pathetic!
Hmm... That's hard!
Right now, it's become
a perfect toy for my crew.
Good grief! I thought I'd test you and
let you join my crew for the new era,
Luffy! There's something here, too!
No way! What's this? I want it!
Oh! It's a Miyama!
You're right! Boy, those
bastards had me scared!
Never mind that, keep reading!!
but you're such a delusional dumbass!
Catch it!
The power for this seems to be a
product found only on the sky island,
Bellamy's right-- someone
with a bounty of 100 million
Listen. The era where pirates
dream about things is over!
It flew away!
and I hear that many peculiar
things like that exist in the sky.
Why, you...!
has gotta be involved
with some pretty bad stuff,
The City of Gold, the City of Emeralds,
the big hidden treasure, One Piece...!
Speaking of the sky island, one of my
explorer friends showed me a live skyfish.
After it! Don't let it get away!
but then why hasn't he been in the papers?!
Those idiots who are blinded by dream treasure
don't notice the treasure around them.
A beehive! Run!
Definitely! I ain't heard of any straw hat kid!
I was surprised at how strange the fish looked.
In this era of oceans, those who should
be most capable of crossing the ocean
Skyfish?
Whew! Had me scared for a minute there!
To our ship, it's still an unknown area,
In any case, I was surprised.
are misled by those illusions and die.
but as a sailor, I'd like to go
to the sea in the sky one day.
Then this pretty woman says,
Alright! Back to drinking! Cheers!
"Tell me where this Cricket lives!"
And people talk about
those dead idiots, saying,
Montblanc Noland...
He said "the sea in the sky"!
"He was happy since he lived his dream!"
What's with this forest?!
It's just like Robin said!!
What a bold woman!
And it sounds like the sky island was a
pretty normal thing for people back them.
--Luffy! Look there!
--It's that bird!
That's just drivel from losers!
Bold? Well, she was strong!
Bellamy! Where are you?!
He dropped the beehives!
When I see idiots chasing after
dreams like that, I get disgusted!
She had these mysterious hands
popping out everywhere,
So it really does exist!
Alright!!
and they knocked down everyone
in the bar. It wasn't funny!
--Eh?!
--Huh? Did he say something?!
Hey, old-timer! How are you feeling?!
Luffy!
He said, "I'll kill you for invading this forest!"
Since there're weak pirates like you,
Couldn't be better!
Glad to hear it!
But what does she want
with old geezer Cricket?
Old-timer, this bastard...
it even makes us strong pirates look worse.
Shut up and listen. Do you like those guys?
The sea around there is the turf
of the big monkey brothers.
To think he'd call me out...
Why do you ask?
It seems like they wanna go
to the sky island at any cost.
Also, if you have something
to do with that old geezer,
Get outta here, you scum!
We can't enjoy our drinks!
Sky island... If they wanna go,
there's only one way to get there.
Bellamy's right!
Now, now, boy! Don't be making us mad!
you'll catch his stupidity.
Get out!
Hey!
That'd be a problem.
Get outta this town!
It's not nice to suddenly show up
at night and demand gold, kiddos.
If they try on their own, they'll get
killed immediately, old-timer.
What that woman's after is
gold bullion, no doubt about it.
Hey, Bellamy! Looks like everyone
here wants to see your show!
Exactly... so why don't we give them a hand?
--Gold bullion?!
--Yeah. I heard some gold
bullion was found recently.
Leave! We got work to do now!
I just heard the rumors about you...
That's no problem.
Really? Where?
Hey, guys...
You got business with me?
You're bodyguards, huh?
Luffy! Zoro! Forget the promise,
beat them up already!
Come to think of it, there was
a pirate named Cricket...
Bellamy!
Yeah! Give back old diamond-head's gold!
What did you just say about gold bullion?
I heard the sad tale of your
Montblanc family at the pub.
Zoro...
That Cricket guy...
I'd definitely like to meet him, too.
It moved me so.
Don't take them on, no matter what happens.
Treasure someone else struggled to
get has a special flavor all its own!
Wanna know what people call me?
Tell me all about him!
The Hyena!
Ah, beyond the never-ending sky
The future that I once saw
is now starting to take shape
There are days where I almost lose to myself
When that happened, there was
someplace warm I could go
The friends I took pride in
always, without fail,
pushed me onwards, didn't they?
Ah, the stars are pouring
down underneath the sky
This unique moment...
Hey, Luffy! Zoro! What's the matter?!
So this is, uh... what's his name again?
We can finally go to the sky! To the sky!!
Old guy! We caught a bird!
You said you were goin' to
a sky island. How'd it go?
W-What happened, old diamond-head?!
--Montblanc Cricket.
--This is his house, right?
It's no use. Once men decide on something,
you can't make them budge an inch.
I wonder what kind of place the sky island is!
I'm about to head into the sky...
after I beat you up!
S-Sorry!
Oh, there's a picture book!
It's titled "Noland the Liar"!
I'm so excited!
There's nothing we could do! We're pathetic!
No matter how cool they act,
it's all over if they die!
It's an adventure befitting me, Captain Usopp!
All you ever say is dream-like crap...
Wow, that's a cool name!
The gold's been stolen!
You guys come and help us!
If you want, I can make you
dream forever... in the afterlife!
But it'll be a life-threatening voyage.
Oh, that brings back memories.
I read it a lot when I was a kid.
It's alright! Forget about that junk!
What? Well, we also ran into a crazy guy.
Yeah, it'll be a life-threatening...
What? Hey, Luffy, let's forget about it.
--Do you know it?
--Yeah. I heard that he was a real person.
Bellamy's mark!
So long, Straw Hat!
I'll be back by morning!
You...!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Distinguished Pirates! A Man Who Talks of
Dreams and the King of Undersea Search!"
"100 Million Man! World's Greatest
Power and Pirate Blackbeard!"
"Dreams Don't Come True?!
Bellamy versus the Saruyama Alliance"
"Legendary Family! 'Noland the Liar'"
"Steer for the Clouds! Capture the South Bird!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!