A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
Give back old diamond-head's gold!
Everyone! Hold on tight
to the ship or get inside!
Gold?
The ship's going up!
What the heck...?!
It's a cloud road that looks like a belt...
You mean old man Cricket's stuff?
I just heard the rumors about you...
It's not an exit... It's an entrance!!
You got business with me?
Yeah! Give back old diamond-head's gold!
--Spread the sails! Right away!
--Eh?
--Oh, Nami-san, how pretty you are!
--It doesn't look like it was
created spontaneously.
If we're dealing with wind
and sea, I can navigate it!
Gold?
It's a sky island!
Who's this ship's navigator?!
There's no way this is spontaneous!
You mean old man Cricket's stuff?
You are, Nami-san!
So long, Straw Hat!
Heso!
Awesome! The ship is flying!
I'm sorry, I'm coming to a stop!
What could be up there?!
That's the exit! There's something written!
Let's plunge through
the cumuloregalis clouds!
Godland...
God's Land, Skypiea?!
Why should I give anything back?
I stole that stuff as a pirate.
Is everyone all right?
It's not an exit... It's an entrance!!
You're the one who crashed!
As a pirate yourself, you're in
no position to find fault with me!
It sure does require you to get the hang of it!
"Sail the White Sea! The Sky Knight
and the Gate in the Clouds"
Nami-san!! You're the coolest!!
Am too.
What's wrong?! Hey, Straw Hat!
Where're you going?!
They're my friends. So I'm stealing it back.
Whoa! This is incredible! I can't believe it!
Can't breathe...!
Why is she able to ride that thing?!
Where?
The sky!
"Godland, Skypiea!
Angels on a Beach of Clouds"
"100 Million Man! World's Greatest
Power and Pirate Blackbeard!"
Hey, where did Nami-san go?
"Take to the Sky!
Ride the Knock-Up Stream"
Father, I wonder if she's all right.
Yes, Conis-san, I'm a bit concerned myself.
I hate to ask, but can you fight?!
Do you know how to throw a punch?!
Why? What's the matter?
Here in Skypiea, there's a place that we're
never to step foot in no matter what.
Where the heck is he?! It's already morning!
Drat! They got away!
What can a coward like you possibly do?!
It's 46 minutes over the agreed time!
We're going to miss the current!
An island!
They're lucky...
It's a sky island!
You're pretty carefree, after our
prey just got away from us!
Never to step foot in?
It'll take him longer to come back,
because of all that heavy gold!
N-No doubt about it! That's him!
Why's that?
Do something, Captain! Let's go
after 'em and take 'em down!
I just know he didn't consider that!
Geez, you still got that?! Tear it
up and throw it away already!
--It's sacred ground.
--Sacred ground?
Hey... that sign... said Skypiea.
No, I don't think he ever
considered the time at all.
We call that place...
But if this wanted poster is real...
Don't fret, Burgess!
They haven't left this world!
Yeah! That's the same name as the one
written on the map that Luffy found.
Yeah, that's 100% certain.
Not even Bellamy stands a chance
against a 100 million-Berry bounty!
Do you suppose he was beaten in town?
...Upper Yard, the land where God lives.
We'll run into 'em soon enough!
As long as we're on the Grand Line!
By that Bellamy guy?!
Ridiculous! Just look at that runt!
Does he look nefarious to you?!
If he did, he'll have hell to pay
even if he makes it back in time!
That galleon that fell on us
really did come here...
Exactly.
"The Forbidden Sacred Ground! The Island
Where God Lives and Heaven's Judgment!"
All things in this world are cogs
that move in tune to strong desires.
I wouldn't put it past you...
They saw this scenery
two hundred long years ago!
That makes me suspicious of his
30 million bounty poster, too!
There's a God?!
Hey!
If you just stand there in
fear like this afternoon,
--See?!
--You're so right!
In a place where we're never to set foot in?!
you ain't gonna steal
nothing from me, coward!
It's him! Thank goodness! He's back!
--Yes.
--God... you mean that God?
This afternoon was different.
I did it!
God lives on the sky island?!
Luffy! Hurry! We're behind schedule!
That so? And just how is it different?!
Yes. Since Skypiea is God's Land,
What is this place?!
Check it out!
This time, I'll shut your
smart-alecky mouth for good!
You can really smell adventure in the air!
A Hercules! It took me forever to find one!
it's ruled by the Almighty God Eneru.
Ahhhh! You idiot! Wait!
--You were looking...
--...for a beetle?!
Your feet can touch the bottom.
The Almighty God?
It's collapsing!
I'll finish you in an instant!
Hey, you okay, Usopp?
Damn... What happened?! Is everyone here?!
God Eneru knows everything in this world.
Spring...
...Snipe!
Everything?!
He's also watching us all the time.
Hey, guys! Look outside the ship!
Whoa! Awesome!
Is this island made of fluffy clouds?
It's the Going Merry Flying Model!
--All the time?!
--Now, too?
Oh! Straw Hat flew, too!
It's fluffy, isn't it?
What is this place?!
It's fluffy!
It's pure white!
Of course.
It looks like it can fly!
What?! He's watching us now?!
--Clouds?!
--We're in the clouds?!
How are we staying on them?!
Doesn't it?! They did it for us!
Let's go ashore!!
Amateur trash...
Of course you can stay on them! They're clouds!
Humph. God, huh?
The sky island!!
No, you can't!
Oh, I'm coming, too!
You don't believe in God?
--Look at 'em go.
--Seeing that makes me feel uneasy...
I'm gonna go change!
Oh, no! Usopp isn't breathing!
What'd that runt come all the way here for?!
I don't know. Whether or not
God exists doesn't matter to me.
What?! Do something! CPR!
Hey, Luffy! What about the anchor?!
I agree.
Let's all sit back and enjoy Bellamy's "show"!
Okay! I'll give Nami-san CPR!
I couldn't care less from the beginning.
Even a pigeon would've
been better than a chicken...
There isn't seabed around here, right?!
But I don't intend to deny
those who want to believe.
--Moron...
--Usopp! Say something!
Who cares?
That's not the main issue here!
You're an idiot!
He talked all big, but now
he's just running away!
Yeah, who cares?
Alright! Let's set sail! Ready, men?!
So, have you seen that God who
lives in Upper Yard, Conis-chan?
Yeah!
Usopp!
--Forget about it!
Clouds... What?!
Me too! Me too!
Aye aye, sir!
Nothing's different at all...
These are clouds! No, there's
too many! What is this?!
No! God forbid!
Come down already! This beach is fluffy!!
We cannot step foot in Upper Yard. Never...
Basically, this is an ocean in the sky?
It's just like this afternoon!
Rolly, rolly, rolly...
An ocean... in the sky?!
Let me do it, too!
But look! The Log Pose is still pointing upward!
You're gonna steal the gold back?!
The sacred ground, Upper Yard, is forbidden.
It seems we're in the middle section
of the cumuloregalis clouds.
Still, this scenery is amazing.
You're just a weakling who's all talk,
who can't stand up to me,
Get on board already! There's no time!
We need to go even higher? How?
It's like something out of a dream.
Or are you plannin' to waste your
chance to go into the sky, you fool?
and can't do anything but
blather on about dreams!
That, I don't know...
So, the sky island has ground, too...
Yeah, it sure is.
--Did you call me a moron?!
--I forget.
And, look at how they're
getting all carried away...
Right! Thanks for the ship!
An ocean...!
They're hopeless...
--He's coming this way!
--Run!
Yahoo!
I see. A place that we're not
allowed to go no matter what, huh?
In Swimming Lane #1, Captain Usopp!
It's them you should thank.
So are you.
--You can do it! Good luck!
--Yay!
Ah! Your eyes...!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Sorry! I said, sorry!!
What're you thinking about right now?!
Hey, now! Don't be reckless!
This ocean's still a mystery!
Struggle all you want--
Listen good! "Never step foot in" means
there's no escape from my
Spring-Spring Fruit power!
Yeah! Thanks, you guys!
An ocean's an ocean!
you're absolutely not
supposed to go there, Luffy!
Finished already? Pathetic!
You can have my Hercules!
We brought the south bird with us, didn't we?
No way that kid can stand
a chance against Bellamy!
--Awesome!
--He's so brave!
--Seriously?!
--For real?! We can?!
Oh, I see... So there's a place
that we're not supposed to go.
We forgot to let him go.
It looks like there're people living here,
You're a nice guy!
so he'll probably be able
to survive without our help.
That didn't kill you, did it?
Anyways, let's hurry!
Get on board, before we're too late!
If he tries hard, he can go down to
the ground. He's a bird, after all.
I see. A place that we're absolutely
not supposed to go, huh?
There's so little resistance...
But it's hard to see anything at all...
We'll lead the way, so follow us!
Oh, hey, what about the anchor?
He got up!
--Luffy! Hurry!
--Yeah!
He's definitely planning to go there.
Oh! I'm going deeper and deeper! So easily...!
It hit bottom.
It's too early to kick the bucket!
Looks like those fluffy clouds
are the base of this island.
Hm? But if he's God, wouldn't he forgive you
My show's just getting to the good part!
That means that the island
is floating on the sea.
Usopp's so lucky! If only I could swim, too!
Spring...
even if you go someplace you're
not supposed to? He's nice, right?
This "city of gold" is just a
product of Noland's imagination!
I wonder if an island can actually stay in
the same place without being washed away.
...Hopper!
I bet it's so fun...
Well... But breaking God's
rules is blasphemous, so...
Well, all we can do is
take things as they appear.
You need to realize that
dreams never come true!
Actually, this is all hard to believe.
I see. Well, I guess it doesn't matter either way.
Hey.
Bellamy disappeared!
He's... not coming back up.
But, in any case, it's a fact
that this sky island's here.
That's because he intends to go
even if he won't be forgiven!
He did this when Roshio
the Executioner was killed!
They're your friends, huh?!
So, what happens if someone goes
into that forbidden Upper Yard?
I was just wondering... Do you
think this ocean has a bottom?
Saruyama Alliance!
Come to think of it, that geezer and
those giant apes are just like you!
See?!
--You don't mean...!
--Did that bastard fall from the clouds?!
I felt it with my body,
so there's no reason to doubt!
Th-That's...
Don't screw up, now!
Usopp!
You're a clan of natural-born
morons who believe in a fish story
That's...?
No matter what happens,
give everything you got for them!
Come down! Since your feet can touch
the bottom, you won't drown, right?!
The person cannot come back alive.
Everyone believes so.
That moron! I tried to tell him!
told by some guy 400 years ago!
Stretch your arm as far as you can!
A city of gold? A sky island?!
Yeah!
Cannot come back alive?!
--But I can't see down there!
--It's all right. Leave it to me!
What about you?
The era of dreams is over,
you pathetic excuses for pirates!
I-I'm worried about Nami-san.
Yeah, I'll go, too.
Ojos Fleur!
Alright! Let's go!
I hope she isn't near Upper Yard.
Do I know how to throw a punch, you ask?
The smell of adventure... huh?
It's time to set sail, guys!
--Nami-san!! Stay where you are
--In any case, let's go there, to find Nami!
Get 'im, Bellamy! That moron
isn't fit to live in reality!
--All right!
--Aye, Nami-san!
I've never thought of sailing or
going ashore as an adventure.
--and don't go anywhere!!
--Is your reason for going really to find Nami?!
So long, Straw Hat!
--Nami-san!!
--Isn't it really so you can
go to the forbidden land?!
Nami-san!!
For some reason, the sky island
makes me sleepy...
Kid! This is where we part ways!
--There he is!
--Eh?! Where?!
What's with the huge trees?
Yeah!
Hello, this is your Captain speaking.
There's one thing that's a definite fact.
I've never seen something this big before.
I'm having too much fun to figure
out what I should do first, over.
Veinte Fleurs!
How old are these trees?
Several hundred years?
No one in history's ever disproved
the city of gold or the sky island.
This is Usopp. Why don't we take
it easy for a while here, over.
All these trees...
Okay! Pull him up!
Take it easy? Sounds good!
I can't see the top of them!
You got him?! Okay!
Right!
--Denied!
--What?! "Denied" means no, you know!
There's no doubt about it!
People might laugh and call it
foolish logic, but it's enough for me.
The treasure should definitely be here!
Is he heavy?!
Look at these...
mysterious flowers are in bloom.
--He shouldn't be.
--Luffy! You can do it!
An extraordinary treasure is here.
That's what romanticism is all about!
You can do it!
Hey... Quit kiddin' around, Bellamy...
Romanticism...
We're very close, it's almost within our grasp!
I wonder if these flowers are also balloons.
Yes! He's back up!
Do they pop like that fish did?
C'mon! You're just joking, right?!
That's right!
There's someone there.
Say something!
The treasure is close by! Hurry up!
Things came with him!
They wanna eat Usopp!
Thanks for the gold...
This is very nice.
Hey! Bellamy! Quit acting dumb!
The navy won't be chasing us here,
so we can enjoy ourselves!
The voice came from over here.
It's nothing to be that afraid of!
Hey, Luffy! Let's go!
Don't be fallin' from the sky now, y'hear?!
C'mon, get up! Continue
your usual show! Bellamy!
Hm... Hold on a second.
We'll go after I finish these.
You're a major rookie with a 55 million reward!
What're you gonna do if
something happens to Nami-san
Hey, Chopper, look. I wonder what that is.
See ya, old guy!
Huh?!
while you're sitting around like it's nothing?!
Thanks for everything, Cricket-san!
That's right! Those two from this afternoon!
--Huh?
--Ah! I found a strange nut!
Just leave them there,
since we're coming right back!
I'm sure the city of gold is real, old-timer!
Hmmm... Hold on! This one, too.
I'm gonna try it!
Old guy! Don't overdo things!
Conis-chan, it'll be night if I wait for him!
What's this?
Their bounties are higher than yours, Bellamy!
This thing's hard!
Mind your own business!
Take me to that Upper Yard place!
Hey, Usopp!
What? B-But...
--What?!
--I've got a nut for you. Here!
S-See! I told you...!
Hm?
...we don't know if she was really headed there.
Hey, that hurt! Okay, stay right there!
It's morning already!
The old guy's gold. Give it back.
But it sure is hard to breathe here...
And...
Ahh! Robin-chan!
Well? See anything?
These are flowers from the
sky island. One for you...
This is one strange creature...
I'm not even sure if it's a fish...
...if we incur God Eneru's wrath,
we'll really be in big trouble.
Can't even see the outline
of the opposite shore yet!
...and one for...
Are they really going to a sky island?
That octopus was like a balloon!
Nami-san!!
God Eneru seems to be pretty scary.
Yeah, that's what they said.
Nami-san!! A flower for you!!
It's definitely an animal. It was moving.
It'll be tough to follow 'em,
so let's take care of 'em before that.
God Eneru... God, huh?
I can't believe things live in clouds...!
Whoa! This chair is made of clouds, too!
Perhaps we should think of this
as an ocean rather than clouds.
Straw Hat Luffy... A 100 million-Berry bounty...
I wonder if there's some technology
to make things from clouds, after all.
Man, they're tough!
What's this flat snake?
They got all beat up,
but now they're just fine...
But it's different from fluffy clouds.
A flounder! Because it's flat!
--It's puffy.
--Nami-san!! A flower for you!!
So this is a flounder?!
All right! It's currently 7:00 am!
I know Chopper tended to 'em,
but they almost seem immortal...
But why do I get wet in a sea of clouds?
We should arrive at the destination
area at around 11:00 am!
No one...
Hm? Oh, good timing.
...seems to be on that boat.
Dammit! What is it this time, Usopp?!
Like the old-timer said, the spot
the Knock-Up Stream shoots up from
Why didn't you go?
My pants! There was something in 'em!
Huh? What's with you?!
It's, "Don't fight! Do this! Don't go! Go!"
Usopp!
changes each time, so we need
to arrive beforehand and find it!
Sky island scary, sky island scary...
Sorry!
No! I mean, they beat you, too!
Huh? What the hell is this? A fox?
What an unlucky day.
Claw marks...! I wonder if it
was attacked by something.
Watch! Watch!
We're a little behind schedule, so...
These are skyfish! The odd fish
described in Noland's logbook.
Hmm? What's that sound?
There's no doubt about it!
Beat?
Hey! Are you listening to my explanation?!
The treasure should definitely be here!
They weren't really standing
in our way, you know.
They must have evolved to survive
in this bottomless sky ocean...
Hey, there's someone! Over there!
See! It faced forward!
An extraordinary treasure is here!
Fights that leave nothing
but sympathy are rough.
That guerrilla again?!
There sure are some weird birds out there!
We're very close...
The whistle! Where's the whistle?!
Let's ask him to save us again!
--Th-The seashell is talking!
--It's almost within our grasp!
What? Are you an idiot?
It's true! It can only face south!
This guy's like a compass! So neat!
So they turned all
balloon-like and flat and stuff?
--Th-The seashell is talking!
--The treasure is close by!
Shut up and get lost! You're in the way!
No, hold on. That's not a guerrilla. That's...
To be even lighter...
Hurry up!
I'm what?! You're the one who never listens!
This is a seashell, right? There's no
way there's a human in here, right?
The buoyancy here is weaker
than in the oceans below.
...an angel...
--Why do I have to listen to you?!
--Hey, now! Be careful there!
They have scales like feathers,
and weird carnivore-like mouths!
An angel?
What'd he say?
Are you guys insane?! This ship
is our treasure! Hey! I said stop!
He said he's going to face a
different direction to mess us up.
I tried sauting it.
Listen! If we keep a record like this,
it may become useful later!
--This is good!
--We're still investigating it!
Go ahead and try!
What're you guys thinking?!
Oh! It really is good! What is this?!
I've never had anything like it!
So this seashell can record voices!
Oh! He faced north!
Is it to your liking, Nami-san?!
I-I don't want to! I'm going back.
I got it!
Let's eat that big one, too!
T-That runt... It was a fluke!
Heso!
I-I'm scared! I can feel it!
I can feel God's anger!
That one looks like it'd be a lot of work...
Where is the sky island?
He doesn't feel right unless he's facing south!
Hey, you!
Stop! I'm still here!
Oh! A ship...
Hey, you guys! Don't get the big boss mad!
What's that noise?!
A ship! Hey, guys! A ship... and a person?
C'mon! Bring it on!
C-Can't be...!
It's God!
There's no way we can lose
to dream-chasing morons!
Eh?
It's all right! Their casualness
is getting me worked up!
What's wrong?! Hey, Straw Hat!
Where're you going?!
Eh?!
Hey. What's wrong, Chopper?
Heso?
Huh? What's wrong?
Where?
Did she just say heso, like belly button?
Is there a ship out there, Chopper?
There's no point in being anxious!
--Yeah...
--What did she mean by "heso"?
They were killed?
No, uhh, there was, but not anymore...!
Well, heso is heso.
The sky!
Huh?
Let's have fun!
--And there's a bull, and it's
running straight here, it's on...
--You're not making sense! Calm down!
By God?
Suu, come here.
And who put us behind schedule?
He's right! There's no point in
being tense for hours on end!
What's wrong with you?
Did you come from the Blue Sea?
Yeah, we flew up here from below.
I see! Alright, men!
Full speed ahead... while relaxing!
It's a person! Someone's coming!
Do you live here?
He's running on the clouds!
Yes, I'm a resident here.
I'm going back. It's creepy.
So these are the ones
who defeated Sir Crocodile,
Hey, stop! What do you want?!
It seems better to leave this area.
To eliminate you!
Welcome to Skypiea's Angel Beach!
--Looks like he wants to fight!
--Fine by me!
What nice weather!
one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea...
Would you like to drink what's inside?
What's going on?!
Monkey D. Luffy... and Roronoa Zoro...
Hm? Yeah...
Are we gonna be okay?!
A conush's skin is hard
like iron, so you can't bite it.
Three-Sword Style Technique!
Help!
Huh?! What's that?!
H-Hey! What's with you three?!
Three Thousand Worlds!
You cut it at the bottom.
The sky... is dark!
Help!
--Bad news, Boss!
--What's wrong?!
Here you go!
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame.
Night's coming from the southwest!
Cumuloregalis clouds!
He's gonna shoot us!
Admirable!
Sky island scary, sky island scary...
Yum!!
Seriously?! What time is it?!
What?! It's that good?! Let me try it, too!
Now, we're off!!
That is far enough!
10:00! It's way earlier than we expected!
Try to surpass me! Roronoa Zoro!
To the place we're not allowed to go!!
This is bad... Shojo! Can we make it?
Yum!!
Utan Divers! Into the sea
immediately! Look for currents!
My name is Conis. This is Suu, a cloud fox.
Ah! I'm sorry! There's a headwind right now.
So those kids've grown to the point
With this wind, going to Upper Yard
will take quite long! I'm sorry!
that they can shake up
the World Government...
If there is any way that I can
be of help, please let me know.
Those are cumuloregalis clouds?!
Well, you see... your gaze
is setting my heart on fire...
What?! Who's this now?!
What, now?!
--What?!
--Quite long?
--Oww!!
--Move it!
If this ship moved using dial energy,
it wouldn't take that long.
They appeared sooner than expected!
There are lots of things that we'd like to know.
But we don't even know
where the current is located!
To us, this place is filled with mysteries.
I am the Sky Knight.
I'm sorry.
How long do you mean by "quite long"?
Okay. Please ask me anything.
I don't know. Only the wind knows.
Hey, something's coming.
Reflected sound detected!
Large current at 12:00!
Oh, that's my father.
--I see... Quite long, huh?
--Old guy! Isn't there any other way
"Holy Land of Marie Jois"
Conis-san, heso!
--I'd very much like to go,
since I'm worried about Nami.
--Old guy! Isn't there any other way
Large creature detected at 9:00!
Appears to be a Sea King!
--I'd very much like to go,
since I'm worried about Nami.
--to get there quicker?
Yes, heso, Father!
--Even I, Usopp-sama, the hero...
--to get there quicker?
--We'd better hurry, or Nami will be back!
Hey, what're you guys saying?
...can't control the wind.
What? Red-Hair?!
Waves going against the
current detected at 10:00!
Hm? What's that thing that he's riding on?
Hey, Luffy! So that was why, after all!!
"Justice"
Yes. He is acting disturbingly...
I believe it's a giant whirlpool!
Oh, are you talking about the waver?
--"That"? Which "that"?
--You liar.
But I assume he didn't take action himself?
That's it! Head the ship in the 10:00 direction!
Wow! That thing is so cool!
No. He did so indirectly, using a messenger...
It's a sign of the explosion!
Catch the whirlpool! Don't draw back!
He's gone...
Waver...
But it's too dangerous for Whitebeard
and Red-Hair to make contact!
What the heck's going on?! Who was that?!
I'm sorry, I'm coming to a stop!
And what's with you guys?! You're
pathetic, losing three against one!
"World Government Supreme Authorities
'The Five Elder Stars'"
Yes, that is true.
What the...?!
But Red-Hair is formidable only when agitated;
--The waves suddenly got higher!
--We're gonna sink!
Thank you for saving us!
he is not the type to change things
about the world on his own.
Is everyone all right?
I have no choice. This one is on the house.
It's a pre-explosion earthquake! Get ready!
Let us be patient and watch.
You're the one who crashed!
Man... Talk about being worthless...
E-Explosion?!
Hey, Luffy. Didn't you bring back
something like that from the seabed before?
The Seven Warlords of the Sea
are more important now.
Navigator!
We must find a successor for Crocodile quickly.
I can't move well... for some reason...
What does the Log Pose say?
Yeah, I did, didn't I?
Do not underestimate his loss.
--It must be because of the thin air.
--Yeah, now that you mention it...
That's the boat I read about in Noland's diary...
It's pointing right at those clouds!
The collapse of the Three Great Powers
will fracture the world itself.
The boat that can be propelled without wind!
The sky island is up there?!
Are you Blue Sea people?
Are they your friends, Conis-san?
Balance must be maintained.
The wind's direction is perfect, too!
Blue Sea people? What's that?
Oh, yeah! Who are you?!
Yes, sir! That is why we have
called the Seven Warlords here,
The clouds are heading straight
for the center of the whirlpool!
Yes. We've just become acquainted.
Tsk! That son of a bitch! He took my prey.
I am the Sky Knight.
They said they came from the Blue Sea.
Hey, what's this "whirlpool"? I don't see one...
but who knows how many will show up?
I see. Then, there must be many
things that you're puzzled about.
"Blue Sea people" is the term for
those who live beneath the clouds.
Looks like we hit the
jackpot this time, brother!
They are pirates. They do as they please...
What's going on? I can hear noises.
The Sky Knight...
I'm sorry, this place is the White-White Sea.
In other words, did you come
up here from the blue seas?
Damn you, Crocodile. You've put
us in a dreadful situation...
What on earth...?
Yeah! And it looks like it'll be
a nice-sized explosion, too!
Oh, no need to apologize...
Excuse me for not introducing myself sooner,
but my name is Pagaya. I'm sorry.
Yeah! That's right!
Then that explains it. This is the
White Sea, 7,000 meters in the air.
--We can make it?!
--Yep!
Just give up!
We can no longer let this man
who beat you remain unchecked...
Oh, no, no... nice to meet you.
Father, were you able to catch some fish?
You should, too. He's mine.
Huh?
The White-White Sea even further
above reaches 10,000 meters high.
We'll take you to the inner
edge of the whirlpool!
Monkey D. Luffy...
Yes, I had a large catch.
Stay out of my way!
What do we do after that?!
Hoho! Same to you!
Oh, yes, why don't you all come to our house?
Ordinary Blue Sea people
can't possibly endure it here.
Get on the flow! If you can get to
the center, things should work out!
I'll prepare dishes for you
using the sky harvest.
Alright! I've gotten used to it!
Navy HQ to MaryJoa.
Hoho!
Yeah. I feel much better now.
Are you sure?! Then, let's go, let's go!
Don Quixote Doflamingo-sama
and Bartholomew Kuma-sama
The center of this huge whirlpool?!
Sky island cuisine?!
No, no, no! That is not possible!
of the Seven Warlords of the Sea have arrived.
Let me help you!
Anyway, why was that guy
speeding on top of the clouds?!
Wh-What on earth...?
Before we go, can I ask you a question?
"Warlord of the Sea Don Quixote Doflamingo
Former Bounty: 340 Million Berries"
Now, now. Hold on.
This boat doesn't have a sail,
and you weren't paddling, either.
I'm sure you have many questions,
but let's talk business first.
What's going on... in this forest?!
"Warlord of the Sea Bartholomew Kuma
Former Bounty: 296 Million Berries"
How did you propel it on the sea?
Business?
I am a freelance soldier-for-hire.
These seas are fraught with danger.
Oh, you mean you're not familiar with dials?
Hey! Stop! What are you doing?!
If you don't know how to fight
in the sky, guerrillas like that one
Hm? Dials?
No! My hands are moving on their own!
will come after you and turn
you into food for the skyfish.
Don't be stupid! This is no time for jokes!
I've never met any fools like you before.
I'm not joking! I can't control my body!
For a 5,000,000 Extol One Whistle,
I will help you.
Wh-What is this shaking?! I can't stop it!
I wanna go to the sky island, old guy!
The hell you can't...! I can't breathe!
There's finally a dangerous place we can go!
The gold... It's been stolen!
Knock it off! What do you think you're doing?!
What're you talking about, old guy?
I can't sit around and wait
till the wind changes!
Oh, no! Is he all right?!
What?! That is quite cheap!
I won't lower it a single Extol more!
I'll be back by morning.
--Are you trying to kill me?!
--It's not me!
Heavens! I'm sorry I let him use the waver.
Stop it! Where you do think you are?!
Hey Luffy! Could that be...
"Navy HQ Vice-Admiral
'Great Tactician' Tsuru"
See ya, old guy!
I need to earn a living too, you know!
Speaking of which, I wonder how
this sea treats those with powers.
What in the world is "Extol"?
And what's this "whistle" or whatever?
Doflamingo! This is your doing! Stop it at once!
...the old broken waver?!
Oh, yeah... This isn't an ordinary sea.
Prattling on about dreams...
You came here via the summit
of High-West, did you not?
Here I come!!
W-We're being sucked in!
So he just may float.
Then start talking already,
or I'll end this lousy get-together!
Then you must've passed an island or two.
--He sank.
--So he doesn't float.
Again, what're you talking about, old guy?
Nobody said anything about being sucked in!
That idiot!
Ahhh! This is terrible!!
Wait! You mean there are other
ways of coming to this sky ocean?!
This was obviously going to happen!
It's all right! I'll protect you and Robin-chan!
That was close! He was just
about to get through the clouds!
Help... me...
And "an island or two"? Does that
mean there are lots of sky islands?!
"Justice"
Hey! You idiot! Stop!
I've never seen such a large whirlpool before...
We had a late start because you
were making dumb comments!
What're we gonna do? He sank again.
Stop! Make him stop, Doflamingo! Damn you!
Don't tell me you came here via the...
Just leave him!
Geez, why did you have to jump in, too?
Enough!
This is bad! Let's turn back! Let me go back!
We rode the Knock-Up Stream.
Don't be fools! Did you
come here to start a war?!
The sky island is a scary place... a scary place...
Geez, you're such a pain!
My word! That monstrous current?!
Just accept it, Usopp! It's too late!
Someone else is already excited!
I'm sorry for letting a beginner use that boat.
So there still are people
gutsy enough for that...
"Navy HQ Fleet Admiral
(Naval Commander in Chief)
'Saint Sengoku'"
Let's go! Sky island!
So, this is your old waver.
The body of the waver is
made so light that its rudder
It wasn't a normal route, after all...!
can be taken over even by small waves.
This is really old.
We could've died, you know!
We found it in the sea in the world below.
Oh, pardon my late welcome.
Thank you for coming, scum of the sea.
Unless you know very well about the sea,
you can't handle it that easily. I'm sorry.
We could've done it more safely if
we had gathered more information!
Would you like me to take a look?
If it can be fixed, I'll fix it for you.
What does it matter now? We're already here.
I've finally become able to ride it recently.
Oh, my. Listen to the big-shot talk...
Sky islands scary, sky islands scary...
It's that hard?
You can fix it, old guy?
Did you lose any of your crew?
I'm a dial ship engineer.
Well, if you train, in ten years
or so, you'll be able to ride it.
Let us begin. I doubt any more will come.
No, we're all here.
That wouldn't have been
the case with any other route.
That's a lot of training!
Really?! Then, please fix it! Please...
Hey, she's riding it!!
Two out of six is better than I expected.
100 people head into the sky,
a few arrive, and someone survives.
This is so cool!!
...do it quickly!
Nami-san!! You're the coolest!!
I bet.
That is the gamble.
I didn't plan to come either, but my
island's business is going so well...
Whoa! This is incredible! I can't believe it!
But with the Knock-Up Stream,
everyone dies or everyone arrives.
Why is she able to ride that thing?!
Eneru...!
That's it.
It sure does require you to get the hang of it!
Not many can make that all-or-nothing bet,
Alright, you guys! The rest is all up to you now!
...that I came out of sheer boredom.
This is too delicate for you to handle, Luffy!
I see. That's disconcerting to hear.
especially these days.
I now see that you are capable
navigators with courage and skill.
Right! Thanks for the lift!
Nothing is as depressing to us
as a booming pirate industry.
Hey, Nami! We're going to the old guy's
house now, so get off already!
Hold on!
Gimme a break, will you?! I'm scared here!
Yes, I must admit it was
only because I was here!
--You stupid head!
--Don't take it out on her!
Let me go back, you jerk!
He's my prey!
You're quite in-your-face!
--You stupid head!
--You guys go on ahead!
While these guys were on their
knees crying and giving up on life,
This thing's gonna kill us instantly!
Oh? So you want to compete, huh?
Mister! Can I stay out here
a little longer and have fun?
Nobody said anything about a
giant whirlpool! This is a scam!
You betray the "Saint" in your name,
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
--I told them, "I will navigate us--"
--Hold on!
That's fine! Be careful!
I don't mind fighting with you...
It's night!
One blow of this One Whistle...
It's like a dream that there's
a boat I can ride at will like this,
...to kill my boredom!
We're being sucked into the whirlpool!
I hear dreary bickering...
without worrying about
the direction of the wind!
Ha! That's a joke.
Let's go back, Luffy! We can still make it!
I wonder if we can use it on the regular sea...
...and I shall come to your aid!
Do you want me to put your
body in this guy's stomach?!
Did I perhaps come to the wrong place?
Isn't it obvious?! Just this
whirlpool is enough to kill us!
Hey! Is that a construction site?
Normally, I would charge five million Extol,
Hawk-Eye!
Hohoho! Small fries crushing each other?
The sky island's just a dream within a dream!
The Navy HQ and the
Seven Warlords of the Sea.
but I will give you the
One Whistle as a present!
A dream within a dream? Yeah, huh?
That roundtable seems meaningless
for those two opposing powers.
That'll be a sight! Hoho!
Oh, that's a cloud-quarrying site.
Yes, Luffy! I don't think we can do this, either!
Wait! We still don't know your name!
You're the small fry!
It's a site where they quarry out
clouds to be manufactured.
Oh, my! A most unexpected man has arrived!
An island in a dream within a dream!
I am Gan Fall, the Sky Knight!
And this is my partner, Pierre!
You can cut clouds?
I'll regret it for life if I pass
up such a big adventure!
Don't tell me you're...
You took the Milky Road to get
to the White-White Sea, right?
I forgot to mention it, but my partner Pierre...
H-He's enjoying this...
No, I'm simply an onlooker here.
Milky Road? Oh, you mean
that winding sea path?
I'm a bit interested in some pirates
involved with the issue at hand.
That's a man-made canal.
...is a bird that ate a Horse-Horse
Fruit and gained its powers.
Hey! While you guys are
pointlessly trying to resist...
It's made out of the island clouds
that are quarried out here.
That's all.
In that case, I, too, am an onlooker...
Is that acceptable?
Yeah? What?
There're two kinds of natural clouds.
A bird?!
The ones your ship traveled
on are called "sea clouds,"
In short, he becomes a horse with wings!
We're being sucked inside it!
Well, I suppose I'm not exactly an "onlooker"...
Namely...
and the ones floating there that you
can walk on are called "island clouds."
No way! Wow! A Pegasus?!
Hurry, Nami-san! Come into my arms!
Who are you?! How did you get in here?!
Yes! A Pegasus!
Either way, they're not ordinary clouds.
But what a truly eminent-looking
group you have here...
We're falling!
How... unexciting.
Right. Their condensation nucleus
is different from other clouds.
I've come in the hopes...
May luck be with you, warriors!
What?! It disappeared?! How come?!
I've heard that a mineral called the
Sea Prism Stone exists in the Blue Sea.
What happened?!
T-That whirlpool was huge, too!
What's going on?!
That was a weird thing it turned into...
--Huh?!
--...that I be allowed to join in your meeting...
Sea Prism Stone? Is it something
to do with those clouds?
Wh-What?! What?!
Was there even a reason for it to transform?
Yes. When the corneous particles called
pyrobroine contained in that stone
Good question...
...if at all possible.
Hey! Help me!
In the end, he didn't tell us anything.
Let me ride with you!
are carried into the sky due to
volcanoes and gain moisture,
I do believe you have
stripped Crocodile of his title
No! It's already started!
You're right! Nothing at all!
Err... Ride with me? But this
is a one-person boat, so...
Now we're back to square one.
sea clouds and island clouds are formed
depending on the density of the moisture.
Eh?
and are now looking for a successor?
How do we get up there?!
The whirlpool only
disappeared from the surface!
I came here from another sky
island in search of treasure!
I know! Let's call that old guy and ask!
You...! Are you Lafitte?!
Oh, I see... that particle...
Y-You don't mean...
But I don't care about it any more.
H-H-Hold on, Luffy! This is only
supposed to be used in emergencies!
Oh, yeah, that one.
Lafitte?
Oh, you know my name?
Hold it!
Please!
We used to play with them a lot in
our childhood... corneous particles...
Can another person ride on this? I don't know!
What if that weird masked
guy shows up again?!
I'm quite honored!
There's no way!
E-Even if I had to kill you...
Hey, Zoro!
He was a well-known
peace officer in West Blue!
Well, in any case, there're
three kinds of clouds here.
Look!
For now, let's take our ship somewhere.
Sea clouds and island clouds,
which are natural,
He was chased from his country
for being excessively violent!
Guerrilla!!
Hey, look over there!
and man-made clouds
made out of island clouds.
That was long ago.
--What could that be?
--Isn't that a weird cloud?
I caught up to ya, Straw Hat Luffy!
Who I am is of no importance!
Now, this way, please.
It also looks like a waterfall...
What a great view!
Alright! It's decided! Let's check it out!
I've come to recommend a certain man
for the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
G-God...
Oh! We can see Nami riding the waver, too!
That's that guy from Mock Town...!
Hey, Luffy, what're you doing?
Who?!
I'm here to collect on your 100
million bounty! Prepare yourself!
Why can she ride it so easily?
Shanks... That name brings back memories...
--Sink!
--What are you, a kid?!
Ouch! I just bit my tongue, Sanji!
So this is a letter from him?
Hey, old guy! Where's the kitchen?
Yes. It appears to be important,
so he gave it to me to deliver!
Hey, who're they? Friends?
Son of a bitch! Is this Eneru's doing?!
Yes, this way.
Wait! Stop! Stop!
Dunno.
I see! Well done, then!
There are huge clouds in the way...
What do we do?
No, I'm still new to the Red-Haired Pirates...
They're floating in the sky ocean,
so they can't be ocean, too...
What's wrong?
Why's it dark out here?
"Red-Haired Pirates (Newcomer)
Rockstar
Bounty: 94 Million Berries"
Then what kind of clouds are they?
Well, this looked novel to me,
so I had a little taste,
My bounty? What do you mean, 100 million?
How dare you harm Vearth?!
If they were ordinary clouds,
they'd keep moving forward...
Though I was a pirate before that,
So you don't know!
but, how should I say it,
this blue sauce tasted intense.
Let's touch one and find out!
and I think I made a bit of a name for myself...
Gum-Gum Pistol!
There's a 100 million-Berry
bounty on your head!
Hey! You guys've heard of Rockstar, right?!
--It made my tongue numb.
--Oh...
It bounced off!
And Pirate Hunter Zoro!
You're worth 60 million!
Nope. Never heard of 'im.
I'm sorry, it's rotten.
Anyways, the Sea King tasted great...
Hey, don't keep stuff like this around!!
It's true! He has new wanted posters!
Look! I'm on it! I'm not sinking!
It's all fluffy, like cotton!
--I completely swallowed it!
--It sounds cheery over there.
Zoro! You have a bounty now!
--Pay attention to when stuff goes bad!!
--He's probably excited about
the sky food, since it's new to him.
Hey! What are you--?!
What?! Hold on! What about me?!
There's one for me, too, right?!
What is this?! What is this?! It's too fun!
Sending me a damn letter...
Miss, I don't mean to be abrupt, but...
When did that kid stoop
to being such a big-shot?!
Wow!
--Nope.
--Look closer!
--Now how does this work?!
--It's mysterious...
Would you tell us a little about
the dials you mentioned earlier?
Nope.
Me too! I'm coming, too!
Sure. Well... how should I explain it?
Me too!
Hey! Hold on, now!
I see! Your bounties went way up
after the Alabasta incident!
He acted like this was an important letter!
This feels great! It's warm and
makes me wanna sleep right here!
But 100 million...!
This is Red-Hair you're dealing with!
Are you sane in the head?!
Oh... this is a puffy chair.
It's even better than a freshly-aired futon!
100 million! Hear that?! I'm worth 100 million!
Hm? What? It's a seashell.
I'm Whitebeard!
60 million, huh? How disappointing!
Yes. Please say something to it.
Don't be happy, you!
Get some Water Dials now!
Captain. That's probably
enough alcohol for now...
But this means the ship can't go
through places filled with these...
Hey, you guys! Don't get distracted!
Okay! Hmmmm...
Put out the fire!
Fool! Something you drink when
you wanna drink can't be bad for ya!
Usopp is stupid!
"Angel Island Lovely Street"
Hey, why... why... why me?
My boss said this was an urgent letter!
Hey! Find a route that the ship can take!
Together now, salute!
Here it comes! The Knock-Up Stream!
Now, please press the apex of that shell.
I have a good idea what it's about.
Ace and Blackbeard.
Right! Okay!
Heso!
Hey, Luffy! There's something over here!
What's an apex?
Get ready!
"Captain McKinley
White Berets, Skypiea Police"
It's the tip of the shell.
--What is it?! What is it?!
--Hey! Where are you going?!
Quit playing around!
Heso, everyone!
Go tell that kid Red-Hair
that if he wants to talk to me,
Usopp is stupid!
That's the White Berets!
--Hey, why... why... why me?
--Ahh! The seashell made fun of Usopp!
What the...?
I wonder if something happened.
to come here himself,
and with some good booze, too!
Everyone! Hold on tight
to the ship or get inside!
--No, that's your voice!
--Now, please press the apex of that shell.
Everyone, please be careful!
--What is that?
--A gate?
The ship... it's going up!
Yeah! There's a big gate
under that waterfall thingy!
Whoa! That's amazing! It stored the sounds?
Illegal entrants have infiltrated
Skypiea through Angel Beach today!
Now go! I don't feel like talkin'
with snot-nosed runts, you buffoon.
So that seashell is a dial?
What?!
There are manmade objects
in a place like this?
Yes. This is called a Tone Dial.
It was reported that there are
a total of seven infiltrators!
It's a White-White Sea seashell
that records and replays sounds.
There could be anything in this ocean
and it wouldn't be surprising...
We, the White Berets,
are currently conducting a
full-scale search for these criminals!
"Strongest Man in the World 'Whitebeard'
The Great Pirate Edward Newgate"
We'll find out what it is
after we get through here!
Please watch out for suspicious individuals!
But the sea here is bottomless, right?
--Left next!
--No, right!
--It's to our left!
--No, our right!
Where do they live?
Please watch out!
The old man hasn't changed!
They live in the reefs of the shallows.
Let's call the old armor guy!
It looked like that man
was talking to someone.
Stop that!
But I can't believe that this
thing can move that waver.
This is no laughing matter, Boss!
Alright! Looks like we're through!
It was a guerrilla. He's just run away.
You're right. This is the kind
that powers the wavers.
Nah, I had an inkling this'd happen.
Hey, shut that dog up.
This is a small one,
He was probably begging for his life.
but it's fundamentally
the same as the Tone Dials.
Give me a little more time! I've never
been insulted like this before!
It's a gate, all right...
But what is Eneru-sama thinking,
taking care of that man by himself?
And look, that waterfall-like
cloud really was a waterfall!
Hey, now! What're you
planning to do? Forget about it.
Why were we...?
So, wind comes out of this one.
It's flowing over those
different clouds from earlier!
Thanks for your help.
You can come straight back now.
We probably ran out of time.
Let me try it.
What's this now? "Heaven's Gate"...?!
Oh, no! We're going to capsize!
Ran out of time?
This is called a Breath Dial. It lets you
store and blow wind as you desire.
B-But, I have my pride...!
Another group of illegal entrants
has already infiltrated this land.
That's unlucky! It sounds
like we're on our way to die!
Your life is more important than your pride.
Hm? Again?
Withstand it!
Y'know, maybe we already are dead.
Old lady Amazon informed us that it's a
ship with seven Blue Sea people on board.
Don't get thrown over!
There's nothing you can do now.
Sorry for all the trouble.
The capacity varies depending
on the size of the shell,
Ah! That would explain this weird world...
Seven Blue Sea people... Could he mean us?!
Go! Sky island!
but by attaching this to the stern,
you can move a light boat.
So, what're you gonna do, Boss?
Eep! We're dead?!
He said illegal entrants...
I'm going. Prepare to set sail!
Heaven, huh? This is gonna be great!
I finally get to go there!
That's the waver.
What the heck's going on?!
If you're going to the upper area,
The ship's going straight up a pillar of water!
To see Whitebeard?!
I see... So, it moved by blowing wind.
pay the entrance fee of
one billion Extol per person.
Get real!
Yep, that's right!
This is neat!
Do you think the government
will keep quiet if you do that?
What was that for?!
How is this happening?!
Your jokes aren't funny!
I wanna ride a waver.
That is the law.
Why did I get hit, too...?
This is no time for that.
Actually, there're various kinds,
like a skating type, and a board type,
Wind?!
Could it be because we
didn't pay the entrance fee?
Look! Over there! Someone's coming out!
Alright! Now we can go into the sky! Go, Merry!
It's no big deal.
No way!
although riding the waver
is as much as I can handle.
The government probably won't stay quiet...
The people who were riding that boat...
...but if they're gonna get in our way,
we won't stay quiet, either!
I wanna ride it. I'm jealous of Nami.
Too bad we have one but we can't use it.
...and, that man, too...
Hold on! I don't think it's gonna be that easy!
Men! It's battle time!
Look! She has wings on her back!
Because they entered illegally, they were...
W-What's wrong?!
You have a waver?
It's an angel! Is that what angels are like?!
Then, will the same thing that
happened to that man happen to us?!
Huh? Did we forget something?
Alright! Get some top-quality alcohol ready!
Yeah, we happened to
come across a beat up one.
She's like a pickled plum!
The hull's starting to float!
Eh?!
There's no challenge in taking
care of only seven people.
Well, to start with, it's 200 years old.
There's no way it works.
If this keeps up, we're gonna
get sent flying to our doom!
Teach?
Yes. The captain of our pirate crew.
U-Umm...
But what do you want us to do?!
We can barely even hold on!
Seven heads... We can't divide them by four.
We don't know that.
I am Amazon, the Heaven's Gate inspector.
Never heard of him.
Some random, unknown guy
Dials have always been made
from the shells of dead shellfish.
Sightseeing? Or perhaps war?
What just happened?
So, unless the shell itself is damaged,
they work semi-permanently.
What's that?!
would be no threat to other pirates.
I-I guess it's kind of like sightseeing...
Who the hell are they?!
A Sea King!
Yes, we realize that.
It's the one that got sucked in earlier!
And what is this place?!
See?!
We wanna go to the sky islands!
They're past this gate, right?
But you can't control it, right?
I'm jealous...
To that end, we are carefully devising a plan,
What do you mean by "war"?
Sounds like other kinds
of dials exist as well, huh?
See! It's only a matter of time
until that happens to us!
Is this one of them, too?
so I ask for a little more time.
Yes. It's a Lamp Dial.
It doesn't matter either way.
Hey, now! We're riding up
a powerful explosion!
Interesting! C'mon! Let 'em try, Sengoku!
If you're going to the upper area,
I have to tell everyone immediately!
This place is crazy!
Whoa! The seashell lit up!
pay the entrance fee of
one billion Extol per person.
In addition, there are
Flame Dials that store flames,
What can we possibly do?!
We are the Blackbeard Pirates.
Please remember that name...
That is the law.
I guess it is just a natural disaster!
O-One billion?!
Flavor Dials that store fragrance,
Vision Dials that store videos, and so on.
There's that "Extol" stuff again...
How much is one billion Extol in Berries?
Lots of stuff is falling!
Victims of the Knock-Up Stream!
How interesting! How interesting!
Well? Usopp, look at this!
Whatever it is, one billion
sounds really expensive!
Hey, did you hear?! Bellamy was beaten!
We're goners, too! We're gonna fall
and slam into the ocean and die!
People in the sky couldn't live without these.
Mine's finished, too!
Whoa! By who?!
One billion per person...
Seven billion for seven people...
Check out that art!
Don't they look just like us?
I see.
So, you could say that...
It's just to enter the country!
--Spread the sails! Right away!
--Eh?
Do countries usually charge
that much just to enter?!
That's amazing!
...sky culture goes
hand-in-hand with dial energy.
100 million...
This is the sea! Not just a pillar
of water! It's a rising current!
Just how does that look like us?!
In terms of ambitious spirit, I didn't
think he was even worth 30 million...
This old lady's trying to scam--
U-Umm, about the money...
What if we kinda don't have it...?
To think it was this high...
And the wind blowing from
below is a rising air current
This is what I think... of your art!
What's the plan, Captain?
produced by the geothermal
heat and steam explosion!
--You can pass.
--Are you serious?!
--While Nami-san could be in danger,
you're fooling around!!
--Stop it! How dare you?!
Hey, you! Don't just stand there gawking!
If we're dealing with wind
and sea, I can navigate it!
Or you don't have to pass.
--Take this! And this!
--Stop it! How dare you?!
--Don't take it out on my art!
Now, the food is ready!
I'm really ticked off right now!
Who's this ship's navigator?!
It's a hearty sky seafood
course with sky island fruits!
Shut... up!
--Can it be fixed?
--I've never seen these parts.
I am neither a gatekeeper nor a guard.
I simply ask your intentions.
You are, Nami-san!
Wow!
Please fix it one way or another.
Amazing!!
Alright, men! Do what Nami-san says!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
I'm sorry, but I can't say much
until I investigate it more.
Right!
Then let's go! To the sky islands!
I got no business with small-fries!
Catch the starboard wind
and pull the helm to point!
Yum!!
Anyhow, please try.
We don't got money,
but we're going through, old lady!
I was looking for a head
worth over 100 million!
and set out in search
of something to find
Align the ship with the current!
This lobster! How can I express its taste?!
I'll try disassembling it.
Yes, sir!
I see. The seven of you, then?
We're about to join the big leagues now!
Oh, no! The ship is about to leave the water!
Yeah. But how do we get to the sky islands--
ONE PIECE!
Old guy, what's that?
We're gonna fall! We're gonna fall,
Nami! Do something, Nami!
Hey, where did Nami-san go?
The time to hunt some prey has finally come!
No, we can make it!
She's out there on the sea, isn't she?
Compasses only cause delays
Captain! Weren't we supposed to
meet up with Lafitte in this town?!
--Eh?!
--What the...?! Something's here!
No, she isn't.
Then, she probably went a little far.
Don't worry about her.
We're flying!
You, suspicious ship over there, hold it!
The White Sea's famous Express Lobster...
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
"Blackbeard Pirate Helmsman
'The Champion'
Jesus Burgess"
Who're they?
Father, I wonder if she's all right.
Awesome! The ship is flying!
Seems we got separated!
But that's how luck is sometimes!
Yes, Conis-san, I'm a bit concerned myself.
It's moving!
Is this for real?!
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
It's a huge lobster!
Is it planning to go up the waterfall?!
Right, Auger?!
Why? What's the matter?
--We did it!
--Wow!
--Hold on tight!
--What speed!
Here in Skypiea, there's a place that we're
never to step foot in no matter what.
Nami-san! You're wonderful!
"Blackbeard Pirate Captain
'Blackbeard'
Marshall D. Teach"
And I love you!
Why the heck are they crawling?
When it comes to personal storms,
It's still a ways to the top!
That place is next to this island,
Go! To the ends of our unseen dream!
"Blackbeard Pirate Sniper
'The Supersonic'
Van Auger"
I don't know.
They're probably... weirdos!
so if you travel a bit by waver,
you can get there...
Precisely! Destiny always
measures a person's worth!
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
What?! So those are weirdos...
This is Heaven's Gate Inspector Amazon!
Everyone, halt!
It's huge...
Go!
"Blackbeard Pirate Doctor
'The Reaper'
Doc Q"
and pretend it isn't there!
What is this?
Attention, almighty God and His priests...
With this wind and current,
we can go as high we want!
Never to step foot in?
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
--Heso!
Seven illegal entrants
into God's Land, Skypiea...
Why, heso!
Why's that?
Hey! Nami! Are we almost at the sky island?!
H-Hey, what're you guys saying?
It's sacred ground.
and set out in search
of something to find
Sacred ground?
Give unto them Heaven's Judgment!
If it exists, it's on the
other side of those clouds!
Who're they?
We call that place...
Old diamond-head! I got your gold back!
Usopp said they're weirdos.
Above the clouds, huh?!
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
...Upper Yard, the land where God lives.
So you're the seven illegal entrants
who came from the Blue Sea?!
What could be up there?!
Hold on! I'll be there soon!
Let's plunge through
the cumuloregalis clouds!
Give unto them Heaven's Judgment!
We are, We are on the cruise!
What?
I'll humbly bring Heaven's Judgment upon you!
We are!
Ah, beyond the never-ending sky
The future that I once saw
is now starting to take shape
There are days where I almost lose to myself
When that happened, there was
someplace warm I could go
The friends I took pride in
always, without fail,
pushed me onwards, didn't they?
Ah, the stars are pouring
down underneath the sky
This unique moment...
What is this place? It's creepy.
Good! That's still only a 5th degree crime!
Gimme a break! I'm scared here!
Hey, guys! Look outside the ship!
Heaven is this terrifying of a place?!
It's not supposed to be like this!
There's a God... in a place
where we're never to set foot in?
That's not good! When it's determined
to be a 5th degree crime,
--What is this place?!
--It's pure white!
We're being sucked into the whirlpool!
Nobody said anything about a
giant whirlpool! This is a scam!
Luffy's definitely planning to go there!
in the name of God Eneru,
you'll be banished to the clouds.
Basically, this is an ocean in the sky?!
This isn't Heaven!
More importantly, don't you think
Nami-san's been gone too long?
Look! An angel's coming this way!
Banished to the clouds?
Let's turn back! The sky island
is just a dream within a dream!
Ahhh! Something's here!
Okay! Let's go look for her right away!
What's that? Being banished to
the clouds sounds kinda nice.
She's probably all wrinkly like the last one...
This is a weird creature...
Hey, Luffy! What're you
thinking about right now?
An island in a dream within a dream!
--Is it a fish?
--Ahh! Something's here!
No... It's the real deal this time!
No, it doesn't! It's the death penalty!
About that God... and Nami, too.
I'll regret it for life if I pass
up such a big adventure!
Now what?!
Looks like we're headed for trouble again...
Death penalty?!
It's a person! Someone's coming!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Already Criminals?!
Skypiea's Upholders of the Law"
"Godland, Skypiea!
Angels on a Beach of Clouds"
"Take to the Sky!
Ride the Knock-Up Stream"
"The Forbidden Sacred Ground! The Island
Where God Lives and Heaven's Judgment!"
"Sail the White Sea! The Sky Knight
and the Gate in the Clouds"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!