A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
I just heard the rumors about you...
You got business with me?
Yeah! Give back old diamond-head's gold!
Gold?
You mean old man Cricket's stuff?
Why should I give anything back?
I stole that stuff as a pirate.
As a pirate yourself, you're in
no position to find fault with me!
Am too.
They're my friends. So I'm stealing it back.
"100 Million Man! World's Greatest
Power and Pirate Blackbeard!"
I hate to ask, but can you fight?!
Do you know how to throw a punch?!
What can a coward like you possibly do?!
N-No doubt about it! That's him!
Geez, you still got that?! Tear it
up and throw it away already!
But if this wanted poster is real...
Not even Bellamy stands a chance
against a 100 million-Berry bounty!
Ridiculous! Just look at that runt!
Does he look nefarious to you?!
That makes me suspicious of his
30 million bounty poster, too!
If you just stand there in
fear like this afternoon,
you ain't gonna steal
nothing from me, coward!
This afternoon was different.
That so? And just how is it different?!
This time, I'll shut your
smart-alecky mouth for good!
It's collapsing!
I'll finish you in an instant!
Spring...
...Snipe!
Oh! Straw Hat flew, too!
Amateur trash...
What'd that runt come all the way here for?!
Let's all sit back and enjoy Bellamy's "show"!
He talked all big, but now
he's just running away!
Nothing's different at all...
It's just like this afternoon!
You're gonna steal the gold back?!
You're just a weakling who's all talk,
who can't stand up to me,
and can't do anything but
blather on about dreams!
--He's coming this way!
--Run!
Struggle all you want--
there's no escape from my
Spring-Spring Fruit power!
Finished already? Pathetic!
No way that kid can stand
a chance against Bellamy!
That didn't kill you, did it?
He got up!
It's too early to kick the bucket!
My show's just getting to the good part!
Spring...
...Hopper!
Bellamy disappeared!
He did this when Roshio
the Executioner was killed!
They're your friends, huh?!
Come to think of it, that geezer and
those giant apes are just like you!
You're a clan of natural-born
morons who believe in a fish story
told by some guy 400 years ago!
A city of gold? A sky island?!
The era of dreams is over,
you pathetic excuses for pirates!
Do I know how to throw a punch, you ask?
Get 'im, Bellamy! That moron
isn't fit to live in reality!
So long, Straw Hat!
Hey... Quit kiddin' around, Bellamy...
C'mon! You're just joking, right?!
Say something!
Hey! Bellamy! Quit acting dumb!
C'mon, get up! Continue
your usual show! Bellamy!
You're a major rookie with a 55 million reward!
That's right! Those two from this afternoon!
Their bounties are higher than yours, Bellamy!
S-See! I told you...!
The old guy's gold. Give it back.
Man, they're tough!
They got all beat up,
but now they're just fine...
I know Chopper tended to 'em,
but they almost seem immortal...
Why didn't you go?
Huh? What's with you?!
It's, "Don't fight! Do this! Don't go! Go!"
No! I mean, they beat you, too!
Beat?
They weren't really standing
in our way, you know.
Fights that leave nothing
but sympathy are rough.
What? Are you an idiot?
Shut up and get lost! You're in the way!
I'm what?! You're the one who never listens!
--Why do I have to listen to you?!
--Hey, now! Be careful there!
Are you guys insane?! This ship
is our treasure! Hey! I said stop!
I got it!
T-That runt... It was a fluke!
Hey, you!
Stop! I'm still here!
C'mon! Bring it on!
There's no way we can lose
to dream-chasing morons!
What's wrong?! Hey, Straw Hat!
Where're you going?!
Where?
The sky!
So these are the ones
who defeated Sir Crocodile,
one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea...
Monkey D. Luffy... and Roronoa Zoro...
Three-Sword Style Technique!
Three Thousand Worlds!
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame.
Admirable!
Try to surpass me! Roronoa Zoro!
So those kids've grown to the point
that they can shake up
the World Government...
"Holy Land of Marie Jois"
What? Red-Hair?!
"Justice"
Yes. He is acting disturbingly...
But I assume he didn't take action himself?
No. He did so indirectly, using a messenger...
But it's too dangerous for Whitebeard
and Red-Hair to make contact!
"World Government Supreme Authorities
'The Five Elder Stars'"
Yes, that is true.
But Red-Hair is formidable only when agitated;
he is not the type to change things
about the world on his own.
Let us be patient and watch.
The Seven Warlords of the Sea
are more important now.
We must find a successor for Crocodile quickly.
Do not underestimate his loss.
The collapse of the Three Great Powers
will fracture the world itself.
Balance must be maintained.
Yes, sir! That is why we have
called the Seven Warlords here,
but who knows how many will show up?
They are pirates. They do as they please...
Damn you, Crocodile. You've put
us in a dreadful situation...
We can no longer let this man
who beat you remain unchecked...
Monkey D. Luffy...
Navy HQ to MaryJoa.
Don Quixote Doflamingo-sama
and Bartholomew Kuma-sama
of the Seven Warlords of the Sea have arrived.
"Warlord of the Sea Don Quixote Doflamingo
Former Bounty: 340 Million Berries"
"Warlord of the Sea Bartholomew Kuma
Former Bounty: 296 Million Berries"
Hey! Stop! What are you doing?!
No! My hands are moving on their own!
Don't be stupid! This is no time for jokes!
I'm not joking! I can't control my body!
The hell you can't...! I can't breathe!
Knock it off! What do you think you're doing?!
--Are you trying to kill me?!
--It's not me!
Stop it! Where you do think you are?!
"Navy HQ Vice-Admiral
'Great Tactician' Tsuru"
Doflamingo! This is your doing! Stop it at once!
Then start talking already,
or I'll end this lousy get-together!
"Justice"
Hey! You idiot! Stop!
Stop! Make him stop, Doflamingo! Damn you!
Enough!
Don't be fools! Did you
come here to start a war?!
"Navy HQ Fleet Admiral
(Naval Commander in Chief)
'Saint Sengoku'"
Oh, pardon my late welcome.
Thank you for coming, scum of the sea.
Oh, my. Listen to the big-shot talk...
Let us begin. I doubt any more will come.
Two out of six is better than I expected.
I bet.
I didn't plan to come either, but my
island's business is going so well...
...that I came out of sheer boredom.
I see. That's disconcerting to hear.
Nothing is as depressing to us
as a booming pirate industry.
You're quite in-your-face!
You betray the "Saint" in your name,
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
I hear dreary bickering...
Did I perhaps come to the wrong place?
Hawk-Eye!
The Navy HQ and the
Seven Warlords of the Sea.
That roundtable seems meaningless
for those two opposing powers.
Oh, my! A most unexpected man has arrived!
Don't tell me you're...
No, I'm simply an onlooker here.
I'm a bit interested in some pirates
involved with the issue at hand.
That's all.
In that case, I, too, am an onlooker...
Is that acceptable?
Well, I suppose I'm not exactly an "onlooker"...
Who are you?! How did you get in here?!
But what a truly eminent-looking
group you have here...
I've come in the hopes...
--Huh?!
--...that I be allowed to join in your meeting...
...if at all possible.
I do believe you have
stripped Crocodile of his title
and are now looking for a successor?
You...! Are you Lafitte?!
Lafitte?
Oh, you know my name?
I'm quite honored!
He was a well-known
peace officer in West Blue!
He was chased from his country
for being excessively violent!
That was long ago.
Who I am is of no importance!
I've come to recommend a certain man
for the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
Shanks... That name brings back memories...
So this is a letter from him?
Yes. It appears to be important,
so he gave it to me to deliver!
I see! Well done, then!
No, I'm still new to the Red-Haired Pirates...
"Red-Haired Pirates (Newcomer)
Rockstar
Bounty: 94 Million Berries"
Though I was a pirate before that,
and I think I made a bit of a name for myself...
Hey! You guys've heard of Rockstar, right?!
Nope. Never heard of 'im.
Anyways, the Sea King tasted great...
Hey! What are you--?!
Sending me a damn letter...
When did that kid stoop
to being such a big-shot?!
Hey! Hold on, now!
He acted like this was an important letter!
This is Red-Hair you're dealing with!
Are you sane in the head?!
I'm Whitebeard!
Captain. That's probably
enough alcohol for now...
Fool! Something you drink when
you wanna drink can't be bad for ya!
My boss said this was an urgent letter!
I have a good idea what it's about.
Ace and Blackbeard.
Go tell that kid Red-Hair
that if he wants to talk to me,
to come here himself,
and with some good booze, too!
Now go! I don't feel like talkin'
with snot-nosed runts, you buffoon.
"Strongest Man in the World 'Whitebeard'
The Great Pirate Edward Newgate"
The old man hasn't changed!
This is no laughing matter, Boss!
Nah, I had an inkling this'd happen.
Give me a little more time! I've never
been insulted like this before!
Hey, now! What're you
planning to do? Forget about it.
Thanks for your help.
You can come straight back now.
B-But, I have my pride...!
Your life is more important than your pride.
There's nothing you can do now.
Sorry for all the trouble.
So, what're you gonna do, Boss?
I'm going. Prepare to set sail!
To see Whitebeard?!
Yep, that's right!
Do you think the government
will keep quiet if you do that?
This is no time for that.
It's no big deal.
The government probably won't stay quiet...
...but if they're gonna get in our way,
we won't stay quiet, either!
Men! It's battle time!
Alright! Get some top-quality alcohol ready!
Teach?
Yes. The captain of our pirate crew.
Never heard of him.
Some random, unknown guy
would be no threat to other pirates.
Yes, we realize that.
To that end, we are carefully devising a plan,
so I ask for a little more time.
Interesting! C'mon! Let 'em try, Sengoku!
We are the Blackbeard Pirates.
Please remember that name...
Hey, did you hear?! Bellamy was beaten!
Whoa! By who?!
100 million...
In terms of ambitious spirit, I didn't
think he was even worth 30 million...
To think it was this high...
What's the plan, Captain?
Hey, you! Don't just stand there gawking!
I'm really ticked off right now!
Shut... up!
I got no business with small-fries!
I was looking for a head
worth over 100 million!
We're about to join the big leagues now!
The time to hunt some prey has finally come!
Captain! Weren't we supposed to
meet up with Lafitte in this town?!
"Blackbeard Pirate Helmsman
'The Champion'
Jesus Burgess"
Seems we got separated!
But that's how luck is sometimes!
Right, Auger?!
"Blackbeard Pirate Captain
'Blackbeard'
Marshall D. Teach"
"Blackbeard Pirate Sniper
'The Supersonic'
Van Auger"
Precisely! Destiny always
measures a person's worth!
"Blackbeard Pirate Doctor
'The Reaper'
Doc Q"
Old diamond-head! I got your gold back!
Hold on! I'll be there soon!
Ah, beyond the never-ending sky
The future that I once saw
is now starting to take shape
There are days where I almost lose to myself
When that happened, there was
someplace warm I could go
The friends I took pride in
always, without fail,
pushed me onwards, didn't they?
Ah, the stars are pouring
down underneath the sky
This unique moment...
Gimme a break! I'm scared here!
We're being sucked into the whirlpool!
Nobody said anything about a
giant whirlpool! This is a scam!
Let's turn back! The sky island
is just a dream within a dream!
An island in a dream within a dream!
I'll regret it for life if I pass
up such a big adventure!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Take to the Sky!
Ride the Knock-Up Stream"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!