A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
"Upper Yard" "Lovely Street"
"Angel Beach"
Luffy and crew managed to avoid
the White Berets' demands,
Gum-Gum...
"Upper Yard" "Lovely Street"
"Angel Beach"
After a great adventure,
but a divine messenger suddenly
dragged Nami and three others away.
...Fireworks!!
Luffy and his crew finally
reached the sky island of Skypiea.
After a great adventure,
Luffy and company finally
reached the sky island of Skypiea.
However, Nami's group was taken
away by "Heaven's Judgment,"
So, they're saying that if we
want our friends and ship back,
and Luffy's group, on their way
to God's Island to get them,
However, Nami's group was taken
away by "Heaven's Judgment,"
we just have to come in from the front.
encountered trap after trap...
So that's our ordeal and... Heaven's Judgment?!
They defeated...
so Luffy and the others headed
for God's island of Upper Yard,
Gum-Gum...
...the White Berets!
with Conis leading the way, but...
...Bazooka!
Yes. In Upper Yard, four priests
strong beyond imagination await you.
Another group of illegal entrants
has already infiltrated this land.
Meanwhile, Nami's group,
which was taken to a sacrificial altar...
The Crow!
You fools!
Old lady Amazon informed us that it's a
ship with seven Blue Sea people on board.
You should've just behaved
and done what I told you to.
You can't be serious!
Oh, then it's easy.
Crows... aren't even waterfowl.
He has priests on this island too, you know!
To put it simply, all we have to do
is beat up those priests, right?
We, the White Berets, are the gentlest
upholders of the law in God's Land.
Seven Blue Sea people... Could he mean us?!
Anyway, we can't make God angry!
It's common sense, you know!
Your exit is Gate #2.
You're so simpleminded...
It will lead you to the giant Milky Road,
which connects to Upper Yard.
However, they are not as nice as we are!
Everyone, halt!
Sorry, but...
...I've never once prayed to God.
Y-You simply need to take that.
This is becoming fun!
You are now 2nd degree criminals!
--Heso!
And so, Zoro's group left Chopper
behind and entered the forest...
Why, heso!
--Hey. Conis.
--Yes?
No matter if you cry or scream...
H-Hey, what're you guys saying?
So you're the seven illegal entrants
who came from the Blue Sea?!
Why've you been shaking
ever since we left your house?
"A Trap on Lovely Street! The Almighty Eneru"
...you'll be judged...
I'm the one in the most danger!
Forgive me, Conis-san...
...by the priests of Upper Yard!!
I'll humbly bring Heaven's Judgment upon you!
Heso!!
It is our citizens' duty.
"10% Survival Rate! Satori,
the Mantra Master!"
Could you run away?
Illegal entrants?!
"Is Escape Possible?!
God's Challenge is Set in Motion"
--Hey! Luffy!
--W-Wait up!
I was the one who called
the Super-Express Lobster!
What is it?
"Already Criminals?!
Skypiea's Upholders of the Law"
Once we know someone's a criminal,
Where are you wandering
off to, all of a sudden?!
we'll be killed if we don't lead
them to the place of judgment!
What's their problem?
You heard Nami.
Where is this God, anyway?
We'll only burden Conis and
the old guy if we stay here.
More importantly, we were tricked!
Hm? Illegal entry? What's that?
I-Is that right?
If he's a god, he might have already
foreseen our actions long ago.
Yeah, but where are we going?
That old lady said it was okay to pass through.
There's no use making excuses,
Isn't it obvious? The sacrificial altar.
since Amazon, the inspector at Heaven's Gate,
sent us pictures taken by a Vision Dial.
How are you plannin' to get there?
And when we do, they say
we entered illegally?!
Things'd be a lot faster if he came to us...
That's fraud! I'll sue for this!
Oh, no! That can't be true!
Thank goodness! Conis-chan...!
I'd rather he not show up!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
Exactly...
Isn't that some sort of a mistake,
Captain McKinley?!
Quit thinking!
Of course, even if we were told,
"Don't pass through,"
The god on this island is horrible!
We just need to swipe one of those
ships and take the Milky Road.
They're not bad people like you say.
I know who you are.
we would've entered by force anyway.
What do you mean by illegal entry?
Shut up!
Do you see any ships we can swipe?!
Please come back...
Was the entrance fee
1 billion Extol per person?
In any case, you are in big trouble.
...God!
Since you've become 2nd degree criminals,
Oh, Lord... Please stay nice and peaceful...!
It's true that we didn't pay that.
I said quit thinking!
But that old lady said we could still
pass without paying, didn't she?
This isn't like the Blue Sea, you know!
we can't...
"Onward, Crow! To the Sacrificial Altar"
...help you.
Oh! And please let us find some treasure...
Why are you talking to us
from way over there?!
This old map doesn't give us details
about Angel Island's geography,
Yes, she did!
It's no use. Please stop
making excuses and admit it.
Well, what's the fuss?
Is that what you care about?!
and even how to get onto
the Milky Road is a mystery!
Is Conis gonna be alright?
We're used to being pursued.
Man, what a pain...
She tried to save us and
wound up as an accomplice!
Anyway, walking along the
river won't get us anywhere...
However, there's no need to get panicked yet.
More importantly, why did you come back?
She's gonna have hell to pay for sure!
"Illegal entry" is only an 11th degree
crime according to "Heaven's Judgment."
We should cross and check out the other side.
Everyone...
Huh?!
That old Sky Knight said
he'd hold on to her, but...
We were finally about to go to that place
that we're never to enter for a big adventu--
Yes.
Conis-chan! Did you come
all this way to see us off?!
But how? Use a vine to
swing across like before?
Once you accept your punishment,
Nah, that weird old guy doesn't seem bad.
err... no, to look for you!
you can become legal tourists on the spot.
Got no other choice.
My father asked me to help you on
your way to the sacrificial altar...
Or do we climb a--
Oh, you should've said so sooner.
You're really easy to figure out.
I wanna protect her, but we
can't take her with us, either.
I still don't like it, but just
what is this punishment?
Yeah, we probably are in
more danger than her...
Oh? Pagaya-san did?
What big adventure?!
It's simple. Please pay
ten times the entrance fee.
I told you, didn't I?!
What with a "sacrificial altar"
and some "ordeal" waiting for us...
I'll accompany you to the Angel Island docks.
Once there, I'll prepare an
appropriate boat for you.
You can say that because you haven't seen
If you pay right now,
we'll humbly write off your crime.
Damn! They're here, too?!
Wow! You're too perfect! Nothing
like a certain scatterbrain I know!
F-Forget it! I am not crossing this river!
how scary those people on that island are!
Geez, this thing is slow...
10 billion Extol per person, in other words,
70 billion Extol for all seven of you.
It's true that we don't know
if this guy is God or what,
Of course it is. It's many times
heavier than a waver. Don't be picky!
--That's for sure!
--I was referring to you!
We'd pretty much be feeding
ourselves to the skysharks!
but his supernatural powers are the real thing!
We'd be delighted to have you
accompany us, Conis-chan!
But there's no guarantee we can get across
S-Seventy billion Extol?!
I will never go back to...
even if we keep walking along the river!
S-So how much is one Extol in Berries?
...that island!!
Right, Luffy?!
Hey, look! What's that humongous forest?!
I said forget it!
Then, you can just wait here while we go.
Berry... That's the currency
in the Blue Sea, right?
If you're gonna go,
then you can go alone, Zoro!
Is that Upper Yard?!
Sure, we'll take you up on your offer!
Ten thousand Extol is one Berry.
Wow! Was there a forest like that on the map?!
No way, they're gonna come after me!
If you're that scared, you shouldn't
have come in the first place!
G-Great!
We have to leave this place!
No, there is a forest here,
but it's nothing like this.
Ten thousand Extol is one Berry...
Leave here?! Are you nuts?!
One, ten, hundred, thousand, ten thousand,
a hundred thousand, million...
Which is more important
to you, adventure or life?!
Say... This ground...
Ahh! How much would that be?
Life! Then money!
It's just a normal one.
Then, 70 billion Extol is 7 million Berries.
What about it?
People from 200 years ago had that map, right?
I won't let you escape!
Oh! Then, next would be me?!
That's expensive!! Do you realize how
much rice we could buy with that?! Hey!!
I'm going to send you to Upper Yard
to receive Heaven's Judgment!
It might've been an old map when they had it.
It's dirt.
Shut it!
Of course it is. It's ground.
But it's true.
After risking our lives coming up into the sky,
It'd take at least a thousand years
for such giant trees to grow!
Come to think of it, we were desperately
trying to reach this sky island,
why do we have to pay that much just to enter?!
This is a sky island.
so we weren't thinking at all
about how to go back.
--That's true...
--But they sure are big trees!
We can't agree to that!
You're right. It isn't all fluffy...
What are you saying? If that was the case,
Say, is there a way for us to go back safely?
Eh? Oh, right! Sky islands are
made out of island cloud...
I wanna climb 'em!
What's that?!
all you had to do was pay
700,000 Berries when you entered.
That's Lovely Street. Once we're there,
we'll be right by the docks.
Can we go back to the Blue Sea?
I'm telling you that's still expensive!
It feels like such a long time
since I've touched dirt like this...!
There is a way, though at this point,
I can no longer say it's safe...
--It's the entrance!
--Well, if we're gonna turn back,
now's our chance.
Consider this a forewarning,
Why is this island different?
but we, the White Berets, are the
unit directly under God's priests.
You ready, Usopp?
...if you go to Cloud End,
the farthest edge of the clouds.
Eh?! Well, if it's possible, I'd like to go back--
In any case, it's certain that
this is an unusual sky island...
Please be careful, as arguing
raises the degree of your crime.
--Let's go!
--You weren't planning to listen to me!
Cloud End? How do we get there?
Oh, whatever. Let's just forget this guy.
Looks like checking into
it might be worth a lot...
More importantly, we'd better
go find Nami-san. I'm worried.
Aren't they already headed for Upper Yard?
Cloud End is in the far east. To get there,
you need to go down to the White Sea first.
Do we really need to be this secretive?
She may be crying somewhere right now.
Fools!
All the Blue Sea people who've
come here have been the same!
Good! Then, we can go back down
to our sea from there, right?
At first, they talk all cool
about dreams and adventures,
I wanna go back...
A Level 2 Crime, huh?
Who do you take God for?!
No! I'm not going back!
but once they're in danger, they
suddenly cry and beg for their lives!
Hey, do you wanna stay here
and get sentenced to death?
Those guys earlier knew that
we came to the sky island,
Choose an ordeal... We shall
present it with our own hands...
In any case, if we stay here,
it'll cause trouble for Conis and her dad.
I'm so excited to go to Upper Yard!
which means something may be
happening to Luffy and the others, too.
Sin is living in ignorance.
Y-You could die, you know...
Oh, it's no trouble...
I have to hurry!
Well, even if we run away, we may
not be able to get away from them.
Yeah. Everyone dies sometime.
--There's things here!
--Well, it is a forest!
The means to attaining peace
do not lead into Heaven...
Okay, then! As soon as
the wind direction changes,
Yeah.
You're not concerned?
If that's the case, no matter where
we are in Skypiea, it'll be the same.
No, wait! Look around, you guys!
Nope! I'm excited!
we'll go out for an adventure...
no, to look for Nami!
"Swamp Ordeal"
Swamp!
Since they know our whereabouts,
we'd better leave here right away!
These are wrecked ships!
"Iron Ordeal"
--Eh?
--Quit laughin'!
Iron!
--It is a forest!
--Yeah.
H-Hey, Luffy!
W-Well, Usopp, what's wrong?
Now, everyone! Let's set sail!
Worry about Nami-san and Robin-chan, will ya?!
"String Ordeal"
String!
How are they related?!
No, no... I should calm down now
and somehow talk him out of it.
Plus they've all been sliced right in half...!
"Ball Ordeal"
And the Going Merry and
Zoro and Chopper, too!
Ball!
Conis! Mister! Thanks for everything!
Hmmm, you know, if Nami is just
taking a little ride around here,
Not again!
Choose an ordeal!
S-Sorry...
Forests are full of all kinds of stuff, you--
--Oh, yeah!
--Hey, Luffy!
she may come back soon.
No!
Hey, old guy!
Full speed ahead! All ahead full!
Paddle! Paddle, hurry! Forward!
So, what do we do?
If she does, you'll miss her.
Alright! Let's go with "Ball"!
What is it?
--Taking a little ride?
--But she's taking too long for that.
Huh? What's going on?
Can I take all the leftover
food from earlier with me?
--Why's that, Luffy?!
--It sounds fun!
Wow! This place is great!
Listen! Luffy's purpose
is to go on an adventure
Yes, of course.
That's your reason?! These are ordeals!
They're not gonna be fun!
Lovely Street is the only
downtown area on Angel Island.
Alright! Sanji, prepare some lunch boxes!
to the so-called "place where God
lives," rather than finding Nami!
A sickle monster!
No, but I agree with "Ball."
He's on the ball.
Don't let your guard down!
Another one's coming!
--That's right.
--He's planning to go there.
In that case, can I ask you a favor as well?
Check it out! The stores are floating!
It's the only one that
doesn't sound too violent...
Right? If we go to that place,
No... Not just one...!
They've been built using
the qualities of island cloud.
You're an engineer, right, old guy?
we'll incur God's wrath
and really be in big trouble.
I mean, "swamp" makes me think of...
Would you give me some
fixtures for the ship repair?
That girl told us that, remember?
Wow! Any yakiniku shops?
Then, what're we gonna do?
Paddle like crazy!
I'm sinking! Someone!
Sure, no problem.
Then, let's go to our house again.
We should just wait quietly for Nami
to come back without making a fuss.
I get the feeling that once you sink,
there's no coming back up...
Hey! Where're you guys going?!
It's Nami we're talking about.
She must have a secret stash with some
small amount like 7 million Berries or so.
Then what about "Iron"?
I'm gonna go get some food from them!
You guys go on ahead and prepare
the ship for our adventure!
What the hell is this?!
They're gonna hit us!
Actually, there's no way she doesn't.
They're here!
Denied! That sounds totally bad!
What have you been blabbering about?
Watch where you're going! Hit the brake, Luffy!
He's definitely planning to go there.
--Please, just go straight there...
--Just get outta here...!
Then what about "String"?
No, we're not gonna make it!
Take the wheel, Usopp!
Come to think of it,
it seems one person is missing.
It sounds easy, and not
too bad at all, but...
Gum-Gum...
Those guys're really scary!
Hey, Luffy! What're you doing?! Aim forward!
Who cares? I don't care either way.
In addition to the illegal entry,
Just keep moving forward!
--now there's suspicion of fleeing.
--Ahhh, h-hold on a second.
High up!
Don't take it out on me.
Is it just me, or is everyone avoiding us?
...Bazooka!
She'll be back soon. Then,
we'll pay the entire amount.
N-No! Its easy sound
makes it seem suspicious!
Chopper, you're on my side... aren't you?!
Can't blame 'em.
--Dodged it!
--That was close!
Word's probably already
gotten out that we're criminals.
So, please relax and wait calmly.
"Ball Ordeal"
--What?!
--Don't threaten him!
A huge ball!
Heavy Point!
This feels great! All of downtown to ourselves!
Luffy, you too! If you do something
stupid and make Nami angry,
There's still more?!
Squish!
you know what's gonna happen,
right?! Got that?! Just wait!
It sounds round and soft, but it's
the most likely to be a trick!
All the angels are avoiding me...
Hmm. Just a little bit, okay?
I was about to drop a rope ladder.
Now spears?!
--Sanji, you, too.
--Yeah.
We really need to think this over!
Oops.
--Usopp! Right!
--No, left!
You realize that there's no
persuading Luffy, don't you?
There's no time to be wishy-washy!
We're already there, anyway!
Then, guys, we break up for now!
--Which one?!
--Just dodge 'em!
Now, Robin-chan, shall we
have some tea over there?
Even if we all get together
and protest, he won't listen.
Let's go with "Ball"!
Sure.
Fine! Then, I'll stay here.
Phew... I somehow managed
things for the time being.
Hm? Go right ahead.
--They just keep coming!
--They're gonna get us sooner or later!
A-Alright! Guess I'll go with
Luffy's hunch on this one!
--Hey, Chopper!
--Hm?
Go right ahead?!
What a pain! All together! Gum-Gum...
Do you wanna go fishing or something?
Oh? There sure is a lot of weird stuff for sale!
Hey, I'll be killed by those creeps!
Then it's decided.
But don't let your guard down.
That sounds good! Let's do it!
...Pinwheel!
Conis! Is there any place
around here we can go fishing?
We're on God's Island,
10,000 meters up in the air!
Ah? Then so be it.
Ooh! If only I had money!
Is a treasure payment plan okay?
Yes, there's one nearby. I'll take you there.
Anything could happen here!
Made it through...
I sure hope there's no more of this...!
I can't wait to ride it!
Let's go! Ball!
No, no!
How dare you...?!
I hope it can be fixed.
Robin, why don't you
and I beat Luffy together?
Oh?
That waver looks broken.
If you're the ones who broke it,
That's impossible.
I guess we've got a better chance
taking on those creeps, huh?
Now what?!
that'd be a 10th degree crime, the destruction
of sky island property by Blue Sea people.
--We dodged it!
--No...
Those White Berets must be
gathering other members by now.
Hey, now! Don't shut your eyes, driver!
--It's coming back!
--Dodge!
No, no! I'm sorry. They had
this one from the beginning.
This must be a dial shop!
Even when they're open, it's pitch black!
He's right! This is mine!
I wonder if the Going Merry
could speed along like a waver
Come after you? How foolish!
Say, there's other stuff like this, right?
From the beginning? That's suspicious.
That damn Super-Express Lobster
just deserted us here...
God and his priests are as
immovable as a mountain.
--Like what?
--You know how there were four entrances?
if it had two of these big Breath Dials?!
Wavers shouldn't exist in the Blue Sea.
Maybe one of them was the right one,
and the others were wrong?!
They simply wait on the sacred ground
for those to be judged to come.
Where exactly are we?
If this was something stolen on the sky island,
"God"
Eh?! What?! Don't say that now!
What's for certain is that it's
the interior of Upper Yard...
When you weigh anchor, your ordeal starts.
the degree of your crime will further increase.
What happens if we chose the wrong one?!
You'll be led...
Shut up! I'll beat you up!
If it's the wrong one... Hmm...
Luffy! This ain't the time to be foolin' around!
It's almost as if this is a sacrifice altar...
--Hm?
--Beat me up?
...to the forbidden sacred ground...
Sacrifice... altar?
Nami-san and the others
are gonna be sacrificed!
Maybe we'll fall off the sky island?
H-He didn't say anything!
Are you even serious about saving 'em?!
Come with us, Luffy!
Don't be stupid! We can't fall off!
Nami. What's a "sacrifice"?
Upper Yard!
Save them? They're gonna be fine!
Zoro was caught with them!
They're only Blue Sea people, and yet
they insult even the White Berets...
It's 10,000 meters to the Blue Sea, you know!
It means being offered
to God while you're alive.
Oh, that's all? I thought it meant
being boiled alive or something...
You could reflect on your life
multiple times on your way down!
Like we can really count on him!
How foolish they are!
I just hope the ship isn't any more damaged,
Even falling has it limits!
Excuse me, I'd like to discuss
something with you all.
Hot!
This is nice! This puffy chair sure feels good.
Quit bein' idiots!
That's obviously not gonna happen--
but things've been so crazy lately...
Hmm?
Actually, it's something like that...
Huh?! There's something
in the middle of the street!
Eh?
Whatever the method, your life is given to God.
What a strong pull!
Eh?! Does that mean we
are going to be killed?!
Don't let it get away, Usopp!
So there's a special cloud current that
can take us down to the White Sea?
Ahhhhh! It's trying to pull my rod away!
What a weird face! What is this? A seal?
--Luffy! Hurry!
--Hm? Oh! Leave it to me!
Yes. By getting on the cloud, you can cross
the vast ocean and go to the White Sea.
Chopper!
Looks like a weird mud figure,
but it's probably a religious statue.
Geez!
And you can also get to
Cloud End without getting lost.
Morons! This is art! I can tell!
Really?!
It's "Vearth." The people of
the sky have forever admired it.
As long as you get on the current,
no one can chase after you.
No! You gotta be kidding me!
--We got it!
--It's a big one!
Yahoo!
If we don't tell Luffy and get
the Going Merry on that current...
Vearth?
Eh?! You guys admire this thing?
You must be crazy...
What is that?!
By the time he notices, it'll be too late, huh?
A shark... in the sky... A skyshark?
But that doesn't mean he'll give up on it.
Yes, I'm sure it must be difficult
for Blue Sea people to understand.
Zoro! Zoro!
I can guide you to the entrance
of that current riding a waver.
Oh, the docks are this way!
We're alive...
Eh?! We're already leaving town?!
Ow, ow, ow... What the heck is this?
Now all we need to do is
keep that fool from noticing.
I seriously thought we were
gonna fall 10,000 meters...
What're you talking about?!
This isn't our destination!
What a weird fish!
We'll take care of that part.
It tried to eat Conis!
C'mon, can't we hang around a little more?
Then please weigh anchor and wait for me.
Is this another one of the skyfish?
Can't see much...! Where the hell is it?!
It's all because you said
misleading stuff, Luffy!
Uhm... I'm sorry.
Okay. I really appreciate it, Conis.
Hm?
That was scary! I thought I was gonna die!
Thank you very much for saving Conis-san.
No problem.
--Looks like it worked...
--They went straight to the docks...
Father, look...
We're saved!
Hmm... We're in trouble.
Still, what is this place?
This is good!
Well, well, well...
Hey, don't eat our lunch!
They're balls...
This skyfish is so rare that
it's forbidden to capture it.
I'm way out of my element! I can't
move as well as I can on land...!
There's a lot, so don't hold back.
Your action was a violation
of the protection law,
You're the one who should hold back.
and it's a 9th degree crime.
They're small "island cloud" balls...
--Conis, give me some tea!
--Do it yourself!
Why is it a crime?! Zoro saved Conis!
Awesome! It's like big snow!
Oh? Conis-chan's not here.
Oh!
Looks like she went to bid a
fond farewell to the others.
What a weird place! It's so neat!
So many boats!
Zoro, did you kill it?
I just smacked it.
I brought some tea, if you'd like some.
There are all kinds of boats anchored here.
I see. Then if we release it, there
shouldn't be any problem, right?
Damn! Damn! Damn!
The Milky Road leads above the trees...
We dodged it!
From hotel ships where you can stay the night
So, you're the shipwright for that ship?
But what part of this is an ordeal?
All right! It's very much alive!
It's coming back!
to speed-oriented boats
loaded with giant dials.
Hmm? No, I'm not. I'm a sniper.
Who knows?
Oh! It looks yummy!
It'd be great if there's nothing at all,
but I doubt that's the case...
Oh, that's wonderful!
Hey, wait Luffy! Don't eat it!
I'm sick of this place! You couldn't
have enough lives to survive this!
There are many other kinds that--
Ahh! Spin, spin, spin...!
Right? Our ship still doesn't have a shipwright.
Maybe we got the right entrance?!
I'm going back, I don't care what anyone says!
Whoa! Check out this gondola!
If you eat it, you can't even give an excuse.
No! Usopp!
Shaddup! I'm captain of the Crow!
I bet if we chose the wrong one,
we'd be in trouble right about now!
That's theft, an 8th degree crime.
Well, how should I put it? Since I'm
almighty and skillful in everything,
--Since when?!
--Since now!
It's so cool! Let's take it!
--This is hard. It's too hard to eat!
--Ahhh! Never mind that
and come over here, Luffy!
Even if we do go back, there's no
guarantee we'll return safely. See?
--Y-Yeah! You might be right!
--Right?!
everyone depends on me!
Look behind it! This one can
move on its own, like a waver!
Hey, skyfish! Go back to the sea now!
Don't get caught again!
Idiots, don't let your guard down!
It's a lot of work.
Would you really let criminals get
off free?! Give things some thought!
That ship just wouldn't function without me.
This could turn into a fun gondola ride!
It's coming back!
You idiot! We're rescuing Nami-san
and Robin-chan! Get serious!
Alright, you! Gum-Gum...
Although I'm a sniper,
it's like I'm also co-captain.
There might be traps like earlier...
--That's it!
--Get it, Luffy!
Oh, your boat is over here.
Stay sharp!
I kept quiet and listened to all your
nonsense about crimes and such, but...
And, everyone calls me, "Captain Usopp"!
I can't think of anything.
--Right!
--Eh?!
Let's just keep moving...
Oh, boy! What kind of gondola is it?!
Just dodge! Our only option now is to run!
I'm thirsty! Let's have some tea!
Oh, dear! This color arrangement
is clearly done by a professional!
--...if you don't cut it out, I'll...
--Wait! Wait, Zoro! Don't be hasty!
Huh? Yes, let's! Open up
the rice crackers in your bag!
Oh, yeah! Arranging food is art.
This is now far beyond arguing.
Ooh, good idea!
His speech and behavior just now
are unmistakably extortion.
You guys!
See you later, Conis!
--C'mon, just one rice cracker!
--Yeah! Let's eat, let's eat!
So, that's a 7th degree crime!
Heso!
Zoro wasn't extorting! He was about to say,
No! Listen! I'm gonna keep steering.
We managed to dodge it...
The Crow!
"if you don't cut it out, I'll laugh!" That's all!
I can finally see rays of hope.
But this is bad! Now we can't even go back!
You guys keep watch on both sides!
For a while there, I was worried.
That's his signature gag! A gag, you know!
You can't be serious!
We've come a long way from the entrance...!
But I wonder if there really is such a current...
Crows... aren't even waterfowl.
--Wanna get off here?
--Don't be stupid! I'll die!
That's not right! Isn't he twisting
what we do into crimes on purpose?!
What?
It took us really high up at some point...!
Yeah, probably.
If such a convenient current existed,
I used it until just recently,
when I learned how to ride wavers.
Chopper! Don't you go
making things worse, too!
But it's strange...
you'd expect to see more survivors
from the sky island in the Blue Sea.
But we can't do anything like this!
There are four priests, so I assumed
each entrance led to one...
It's not fast like a waver, but it does
have two Breath Dials on board!
Can't do anything? Oh, yeah!
What was that?! A snake?!
Don't be silly. Since it's difficult for
people to come up here in the first place,
A lamprey. A "sky lamprey," I guess?
All we have to do is do nothing.
Let's take a nap.
Please feel free to use it!
...but I guess not.
One that big'll do more than suck a little blood!
Now, take a nap! Take a nap now!
it's just natural that not many
people escape here safely as well.
Hey! Usopp! Pass!
No... I'm not going.
It's possible that quite a lot of the
people who tried couldn't escape
Okay! I got it! Pass!
What a neat forest!
Neat, my butt! If this is our
"ordeal," I've had enough!
I told you to keep watch!
because they were too slow.
That's right. Not knowing when
to back off can cost you your life.
But we just entered the forest.
We're in for big trouble if we stop
or dawdle on this Milky Road...
Hurry up and get ready to set sail.
Weigh anchor quickly.
A snake!
They're producing tremendous
noises at divine Angel Beach.
You jerk! Get outta here!
Chopper, use your Heavy Bonus
now and start on the heavy lifting.
Looks like our only choice is to keep moving!
You all... if your action falls under
destruction of the environment,
Err... I told you, it's Heavy Point.
--What?!
--N-Nothing.
a 6th degree crime will be added as well.
That was a shock! Why...?!
--Now, wake up Zoro.
--That's impossible.
Hey, we can't even snore?
No... I'm not going.
Sanji! Look out! A cloud!
Don't worry. I can do it alone!
Ahhh! How annoying! I'm gonna
beat up this beret-wearing old guy!
Kick it far away!
We'd better hurry up, or Conis'
kindness will be wasted.
Dammit! Are all these
floating things snake eggs?!
Just as I expected! He shows
his true colors at the last minute!
--Shall we do it?
--W-Wait! Hey, stop it!
Heavy Point!
There's no one in this world
who doesn't value his life!
Oh, no... There's already someone there!
I prefer that one instead.
I wonder if they're with
those guys from earlier.
Please don't do anything stupid, everyone!
He was just being selfish?
What happened to you, Zoro?!
Don't be so hasty, Luffy, Zoro!
I put this one here... Hm?
No, this is in the wrong place.
--Listen. You know snails, right? They're...
--Hold on a second!
Y-You don't like it? I'm sorry. But...
This isn't good...
I put the red one there, and put the
emerald green broad beans here.
Ah! Nami-san, you're all right!!
You damn ingrate! Apologize!
What's the deal with these balls?!
Luffy! Don't give them any trouble!
Apologize to Conis-chan from the
bottom of your heart! You scumbag!
Now, they look more delicious than before.
But they...
Pay no attention to his selfishness!
--There he is!
--Zoro!
This one is for Nami-san and Robin-chan.
There's no telling what will come out!
Nami! Go ahead and pay
them the 7 million-Berry fee
The skyshark is beating Zoro!
--Sorry!
--N-No problem...
Wow, they don't look like food!
for our illegal entry using your secret stash!
--No, thank you. I'm sorry.
--I've never seen such a pretty lunch before.
These clouds are called "surprise clouds"!
Good! We can still get by with a fine, then?!
Really?
Surprise clouds?!
This is for you, Conis-chan.
7 million Berries, he said...?
Oh?! You made one for me, too?!
--Heso!
--Who're you?!
Of course! The title of this lunch is...
H-He went under again!
Zoro isn't coming back up!
What?!
Thank you for choosing my "Ball Ordeal"!
"Skypiea Priest
Satori of the Forest"
"Love is a dilemma. Lunch for the falling angel."
That's too expensive!!
--Oh...
--Well, once they're in your stomach,
Your exit is Gate #2.
Do you think... he got eaten?!
Who is this dumpling freak?
they're all the same.
It will lead you to the giant Milky Road,
which connects to Upper Yard.
Zoro was eaten!
Oh, shoot! Because they demanded such an
unreasonably high fee, I unintentionally...
Don't say stuff that tears down my hard work!
If he was eaten, the clouds would turn red.
Y-You simply need to take that.
Listen up. With food, presentation comes first!
Hey...
How can you say something
so scary so calmly, Robin?!
C-Captain!!
Really?
Hey, mister, thanks for letting
me use your waver. It was fun.
See? Now they're the same.
I'm sick of you!
You're just chowing down
without looking at them!
--Hey. Conis.
--Yes?
No, no. I'm sorry.
--Really?
--Umph!
Why've you been shaking
ever since we left your house?
More importantly, you all are in big trouble!
They're the same after all. They taste the same.
Like I said, enjoy them with your eyes first!
--Captain! Please hang in there!
--Everyone, let's get out of here!
--Your wound isn't deep!
--How did this happen?! Captain!!
--Why? I thought you started a fight.
--Don't be rude! Not even
I can eat with my eyes!
--Hmm?
W-What the hell is he saying?!
Don't tell me he's a priest?!
It's dangerous to have anything to
do with this God thing. Seriously!
That's not what I mean!
--But I've eaten with my nose before...
--Don't do that!
D-Does it seem that way?
By the way, what crime would that be?
...though I didn't mean to.
You're the ball ordeal?! A ball?!
I think it's probably a 5th degree
crime for obstructing official duties.
Quit dancin'! Who the hell are you?!
This is bad...
Yeah. It's like you're afraid of something...
Now we'll just wait until Luffy
and the others come back.
Good! That's still only a 5th degree crime!
Doesn't look like swimming
outta here will do us any good...
That's not good!
No! She wouldn't!
You punched that shark!
I thought you were a swordsman?!
Wow, he seems dumber than I expected...
When it's determined to be a 5th degree crime,
You're so strong, Zoro!
Didn't Nami and the old guy
say they were really strong?
in the name of God Eneru,
you'll be banished to the clouds.
Conis-chan! You're worried
about us! That's so touching!
What happened to your
so-called "swordsman pride"?
--Okay!
Banished to the clouds?
Will you quit nagging about everything?!
What's that? Being banished
to the clouds sounds kinda nice.
Hey! Dumpling!
Nami-san and the others are safe, I hope?!
Still, are you guys gonna be alright?!
No, it doesn't! It's the death penalty!
There wasn't just one!
There's a whole swarm of skysharks!
D-Death penalty?!
Do you mean the sacrifices?
Chopper! What just happened?!
Everyone in town is plainly avoiding us,
If so, I wouldn't know. Even if they're
left alone, they're going to die!
We'll be here all night if we try
to take on every single one.
yet you're lending us your boat
and even giving us directions...
Even if they manage to escape,
they're still going to die!
Can't get even get to shore like this...
Though we can't just sit here, either.
--Say what?!
--You should worry about yourselves.
Doesn't that make you our accomplices?
Just so you know, you'll of course
need to beat me to continue ahead!
That giant lobster brought us
to one hell of a place...
Say, you're looking pale, too...
He's completely out of it.
Do you suppose starving us
here is "Heaven's Judgment"?
You should've told us if you were that scared.
But the death penalty in
God's Land? That's harsh.
Okay! Here he comes, Luffy! Get 'im!
We would've come on our own...
Would God really do something so bland?
What's going on?!
Alright! I'll shoot him down!
I wonder if we're already on that current.
No. I'm...
But it's the truth. It really exists!
I don't know. I've never met him before.
Gum-Gum...
Hey! Something's wrong with the ship!
Oh, you're going to stretch?
It's a punishment where you,
together with your ship,
This is bad... We can't set sail
with the hull like this.
What?!
are put on a cloud that you can't escape from,
What's going on, Usopp?!
...Pistol!
and you keep wandering
until you become bones.
Look at that! The ship's rocking!
Try to fix the ship somehow, Chopper.
A party? No fair, having a party without us!
It's not what you think!
Eh?! Me?! Okay.
It's the death penalty!
I see. That's why that ship fell from the sky.
Ah! Nami-san!
Fix it? Are you planning to do something?
She wouldn't!
I'm gonna get into this forest somehow.
What?! What're you talking about, Robin?
Why...
Don't say anything you shouldn't!
Why is she wearing a t-shirt?
We should probably make
this our base of operations.
Remember that galleon that fell
from the sky? The St. Briss, was it?
It's strange, isn't it?
I'm sure Luffy and the others
are headed here in search of us.
Just where the heck is your mind at?!
--No way!
--Luffy!
Explaining the route to your "ordeal,"
guiding you here myself...
They might have received that
punishment 200 years ago.
Ahh! The ship started moving!
It's like they say, "If you get lost,
stay where you are."
What?! Why?!
It's like I want to lead you there,
despite saying how terrifying it is...
Especially you!
What're they doing? Where're they going?
Whoa! It's moving backwards!
That's incredible!
Stop it! Don't say anything foolish!
Luffy?! Hey! You're alright, right?!
Hey, you!!
That's not it! They didn't set sail!
Regular hits don't work on you!
Do you realize what you've
done to the Captain?!
Huh? What was that?!
Huh?
Hit?
--What did you say?
--Ahh! Sanji-kun, hold on!
Say, Zoro. You said you're gonna
go into the forest, but what for?
Look underneath the ship!
It is a bit different from a hit!
Why, sure, Nami-san!
Don't be upset like that. That was by chance.
I'll show you different!
By chance?!
Hold on! What is this? What's going on?!
God's on this island, right?
I'm gonna go meet him.
An upper kick with the right foot...
W-Well, how should I put it, I unintentionally...
Collier--! What?!
I'm telling you, that's a bad idea!
What if you run into those freaks?!
Unintentionally?!
Don't tell me they're all...
Only the well-trained are
given the power of "Mantra"!
Uhm, you know... it was like an accident.
An accident?! An accident, you say?!
Did we get on that current
thing earlier than we expected?
Dunno. Depends on how they act.
Impossible! He predicted my movements?!
That's right! It was an accident! An accident!
No, it doesn't look that way.
Zoro... You seem even mightier than God...
'Cause it's hard to control
and ride a waver, right?!
He has priests on this island too, you know!
Wh-What the...?!
On top of that, I rode it today for the first time,
We can't make God angry!
It's common sense, you know!
Why?! There's no need for that!
They're different...
Ahh...! That's...
so I made a little mistake
while turning the handles.
I'm clumsy, aren't I? I guess beginners
shouldn't push too hard, after all,
...the famous White-White Sea
Super-Express Lobster!
Why do I need to guide them?
They're already headed for Upper Yard...
Sanji!
should they?
Sorry, but...
Yes, if that were the case, I wouldn't
force this horrible job on you...
It is different from a hit!
She wasn't having troubles riding it,
she looked like she was having lots of fun!
...I've never once prayed to God.
What?!
Impact!
Hey, Luffy!
So cool!
It's trying to take us somewhere!
--Oh, no, Luffy!
--Nami's trying to fool them into
thinking that it was an accident.
But most of the people we've
seen haven't been that way.
Don't believe in him, either.
So I got no obligation to him.
The shock destroys the body from the inside!
--That's impossible!
--Don't say anything unnecessary.
Hey! Everyone off the ship! There's still time!
Oh, really?
Once the initial excitement wears off,
Uhm, I'm sorry, but I thought it'd be
better to treat Captain McKinley first.
Oh, Lord! I have nothing to do
with him! Please don't punish me!
What about the ship?! If our ship is taken...
everyone values their life more
than dreams and adventures...
D-Dammit! Sanji! Usopp!
Don't worry. I'll stay.
I'm sorry.
C'mon! What can you do by yourself?!
Th-That's right!!
--Captain McKinley!!
--Then, let's carry him over to my house.
We must lead them to the
very end... To Upper Yard...
You're so awesome, Zoro!
Yeah, I'm alright... But
what the hell was that?!
I'll pull it off somehow!
We appreciate your assistance!
Heso!
No idea at all...! He's mysterious!
Damn... I wish this would end already...!
All seven of you, don't go
anywhere! Understood?!
Forgive me, Conis-san...
My name is Satori!
This is just a warm-up!
It is our citizens' duty. It is his will.
Captain!
I am one of the priests of
the almighty God Eneru!
Supposedly, there are neat-sounding
priests waiting for us ahead!
They're crawling again?
I own the Vearth in this Illusion Forest!
Why can't they just carry him normally?
So, what, you're saying none
of this was part of our "ordeal"?!
So, it doesn't work...?
I know you're not bad people.
Illusion Forest?
Yes!
There we go.
Yeah, I doubt it. You saw that
attack back at the docks.
So, please use this chance
to get away from here!
This forest!
Could you run away?
H-Hey!
And...
Alright, this'll work!
Let's do as she said.
I dunno how it works,
but that's some incredible power.
Unfortunately, it seems that won't work.
...your boat will be lost in its illusions!
I saw it with my own eyes.
An island with these scary guys on it!
I'm sorry!
One hit from that and you're a goner.
Come on board!
The boat is taking off!
Yeah...
So you did go to the place they
call forbidden sacred ground.
Your boat will now speed along
this forest's Milky Road at random
This "God Eneru" is mysterious.
--Stop!
--What are you saying?!
What'd you say?!
Even if that works, it looks like they'll just
move right on to their next move. Look.
"The place you're never to step foot in."
Seems like he's been keeping
constant watch over us...
I was the one who called
the Super-Express Lobster!
and eventually leave through
this forest's only exit!
"Scary guys"...
What?!
Do you think God was in that town?!
Ah! Don't listen! Don't look! Don't talk!
I'm sure you realize it,
but losing a dial boat
The thing that took Nami-san
and the others?! You called it?!
He'd have to have been,
to attack so accurately like that...
God... guerrilla...
That place is no good for sure!
is the same as losing your
way to the sacrificial altar.
Large skyfish are following us
with their mouths open.
No, not necessarily. We are
talking about God here!
In any case, we're leaving! We're leaving!
While you weren't on board,
He might be able to foresee everything!
Ahh... It's heartbreaking to
be apart from Conis-chan,
So you must find and board
the boat before that happens.
We can't jump off the ship and escape now.
He might even be watching
us at this very moment!
but if that's what Nami-san says...
I lied to them about a current
that leads to Cloud End
Even if we could defeat them,
another batch will probably arrive soon.
When did you become such a believer?
You're not even from here!
Of course, these countless surprise
clouds and I will not allow that.
If we stick around, those two
may also get in trouble.
and had them raise the anchor.
There's nothing we can do.
It's probably already started.
That's right! Those guys will just
make them out to be our accomplices!
That's not the issue. God is great, right?
Welcome to the sacred ground of Upper Yard!
Heaven's Judgment, huh?
You gotta bow to great people,
even if you don't mean it!
So, if we make it so that
we run away on our own,
So, instead of sending people
after us, they're bringing us in.
That was the signal for the
Super-Express Lobster...
it shouldn't cause any trouble for them.
Then you can worry about other things!
What an impudent guy...
I guess, but there are un-great
gods in the world, too.
Right?! Okay, that settles it! Let's go!
This is the Illusion Forest Ball Ordeal,
with a 10% survival rate!
Then... I'm going back to that island?
Like the gods of poverty... and pestilence...
10% survival rate?!
What're you doing, Luffy?!
Luffy!! Usopp!! Sanji-kun!!
Who're you referring to?!
Foolish girl! Do you want
to die?! This is our duty!
Why are we running away?
All that said, looks like our
next guest is here to see us!
Because we'll be in big trouble!
Once we know someone's a criminal,
We're always in big trouble.
we'll be killed if we don't lead
them to the place of judgment!
Like I said, it's not just us, but those
two may get arrested, too, you know!
Not another one!
Those two have done nothing wrong.
Stop it! Do you realize what you're saying?!
The one who arrests them is wrong.
Zoro! Nami! Robin!
That vine looks usable.
--You're blaspheming against God!
--Stop her!
I know that's true, but...
You're right. Good idea.
This is our citizens' duty...
Don't leave me all alone! Please come back!
Mind if I join you, Mr. Swordsman?
Please... hurry up...
Are you serious?!
Huh?! No, but don't be slowin' me down!
I'm sorry!
Who'll save me if I'm suddenly attacked now?!
It's all so strange, isn't it?!
Hold on! Where are you going, Robin?!
There's no place for them to escape to.
Look at this.
Don't be stupid! You didn't
have any choice, right?!
How long will you two be
arguing? Come up already!
At least a thousand years have
passed since this altar was built.
How many times do I have to tell you?!
A thousand years?!
If we stay here, we'll be in big trouble,
and so will those two!
Why...? Why a t-shirt...?
Historical things like this
make my body tingle...!
You're still talking about that?!
Then...
Either way, we're in big trouble.
This is all because Luffy wanted
to go to the sky island...
Hey, Luffy! This is terrible!
What will we do?! What will we do?!
Please run!
...why are you telling us?!
--Hurry!
--Oh, darn!
Where there is great history, there
should be just as many old relics...
Where'd they go?
I'm sure Luffy and the others
are headed here in search of us.
You shouldn't, Miss.
Where?! Of course...! Err...
If you say something that defends criminals,
So where?
Your life is in danger!
I'd wager even a few jewel
fragments would help out our ship.
Oh, yeah! Luffy and the others are coming!
you two are also going to pay.
--It's all over!
--We're too late!
--Where...
--...did they...
--...go?
As you know, those people are felons
--Stay away from the girl!
--The judgment is coming!
I'm coming, too!
who should be sentenced to be
banished to the clouds as punishment
The Super-Express Lobster
is a messenger for God.
Oh! Then I just need to endure it until then!
Eh?! After you were so scared?!
for their 5th degree crime, caused by
all their abusive language towards us
What it transports is always an offering to God.
It's for historical investigation!
I just need to play it safe and
wait for Luffy and the others!
She has Berries in her eyes...
So, it's headed to northeast Upper Yard...
along with their obstruction
of our official duties.
In the meantime, I'll fix the ship!
Zoro did ask me to!
...to the sacrificial altar.
--How's that?
--Perfect.
Like I said, it was an accident!
Alright!
Sacrifice?! Nami-san, Robin-chan, and the rest...
--C'mon, already!
--Arrest them!
--The rest?!
--...will be sacrificed?!
Please get out of here!
They're beyond your power!
For that darn God?!
When Luffy and the others find out
I'm handling the ship fine alone...
Fire! Milky arrows!
That son of a bitch!
Don't mess with us!! You bastard!!
--Arrows?!
--You go ahead, Nami!
What is that? A catchphrase?
Hold on a second, please! But, I'm sorry.
Okay!
That's not the case!
What're these?! Clouds?!
--What?!
--I've heard that although it's called sacrifice,
in Heaven's Judgment, there're two kinds
of punishment that criminals receive.
No good! It's too big!
The hammer!
Go, White Berets!
Robin is amazing!
I-I have to go get it...
Sacrifice and an ordeal.
She did it so easily...
They're currently hostages,
so to speak, in God's hands.
But...
I'm kind of high up...
It's about 50 meters. Mess up and you die!
Hostages?!
So, the ones who are
actually being judged are...
Could you please not say that?!
You'd better hurry before the boat
goes deeper into the Illusion Forest!
...the three of you.
What?! What's going on?!
Hey! We gotta go after the boat
before we lose sight of it!
Huh? What do you mean?
I really am a goner if I fall!
Let's go!
If we had some sort of map...
Oh... I have a map of Skypiea with me.
If we lose it in this forest,
finding it again'll be tough!
Nami...
Alright, fine! I'm going!
Is that what you want?!
It's so fluffy that it's hard to run!
Wait, Usopp! The same is
true if we get separated!
This one is very old, too.
Luffy! What about you?!
But the shape of the island seems correct.
You guys stop the boat!
Watch out!
How foolish... to think you
could get away from us!
I'm gonna take care of the ball guy!
T-Too fast! I can't stop!
Are you all right, Conis-chan?
In your dreams! I'm filled
with good fortune and pride!
Yes. But...
Don't worry.
See, you have guts.
What was that?!
I see... Those're the skating type.
It's them we're talking about. They're fine.
I guess we do need someone
to stop that potbelly freak!
What just happened?!
I apologize for the inconvenience.
That's neat!
How can you be so sure?
--Luffy!
--Conis-chan! Hey! Where'd you go?!
--Not at all.
--That's what you get for not going, "Aa-aa-aa!"
Don't do anything reckless!
He's got some weird powers!
This is where you are right now.
You guys have fun stuff!
The sacrificial altar is in the
left upper direction, northeast.
--We'll come back once we stop the boat!
--Right!
Luffy! Conis!
Is that the issue here?!
It's no use...
The almighty God Eneru sees all...!
Hold it right there, Ball!
This certainly is a big forest...
There's only one way to get there.
Grabs a branch...
Okay, Chopper! You're in charge of the ship!
--What?!
--What is he?!
They are both safe.
You take the Milky Road that leaves this island
--We're counting on you!
--We'll be back soon!
What?! His arm... His arm stretched!
Gum-Gum...
Right! Be careful, everyone!
Come back safe, now!
by using a dial boat,
Oh, my...
The same as before.
...Pistol!
and go across to the forest
where the priests await you.
Gum-Gum...
It's Gan Fall-san!
Can't be...! Devil Fruit?!
I guess Nami is okay,
since she has Zoro and Robin...
Oh! That weird old man!
"Weird"?
I'm too scared to go...
...Fireworks!!
No, I am the Sky Knight!
This one is on the house!
Well, old guy, instead of taking the trouble
of going through the middle of the island,
Everyone is so brave and amazing!
I wonder if I'll be brave, too, someday?
all we have to do is go around
the island by boat, right?
Thank goodness! Conis-chan...!
That lobster went to Upper Yard
that way, too, right?
Leave this girl with me. I will
not allow Eneru to harm her.
Anyway, I'll do everything I can now!
What's wrong? I thought you
were going to take care of me?
Well... even if you can go ashore nearby,
you can't get to the altar on foot.
Being all alone and in charge of
the ship in this dangerous forest
I said I will... and I will!
Right!
You now know this land's true nature,
as well as "God's" power.
is proof that everyone trusts in me!
The big difference between this
map and the current Upper Yard
I gotta do my best!
What will you do now?
Yeah! I'm all alone in this dangerous place--
I won't miss this time! Gum-Gum...
is the Milky Roads that are
stretched all around the island.
This land is none of our business.
A fake punch, followed by a kick...
Our friends are on "God's Island"!
The cloud canals that you mentioned, huh?
...Whip!
Yes. I hear that there're several hundred
Milky Roads, large and small in size, over there.
I see... May luck be with you.
Again!
I'm the one in the most danger!
By the way, Nami!
Hmm... I see...
What's our financial situation?
Gum-Gum...
That's why entering the island by boat
We have 50,000 Berries left.
A lamprey!
50,000? We're that poor?
Hey, do you think that huge thing
would taste good roasted?
and taking the Milky Roads
within the island is the only way.
Normally, that'll last a day or two at most.
--What about them?
--They have chosen their course.
Forget it. This is no time for cooking.
Why are we so poor?
I see...
It is no fault of yours.
So no matter where we go ashore,
the canals will block our way.
As your captain, I gotta say this.
Darn. Gum-Gum...
I know who you are.
You should think more about
how you use money and...
...Pistol!
That's right. By the way, there're
man-eating fish in the canals.
I am the Sky Knight.
It's because you eat so much!!
Alright! In any case, the "Formation B"
that I instructed them to use
No, we all know. Please come back...
Man-eating fish?!
They've really covered all their bases.
during the fight was successful!
Really?!
...God!
So, they're saying that if we
want our friends and ship back,
They defeated...
Sky islands are scary... Sky islands are scary...
...the White Berets!
we just have to come in from the front.
Wanna get off here?
Normally, up here the athletic abilities
of Blue Sea people decrease.
Are you stupid?! You're asking me
to die! I'm scared! Gimme a break!
Get on! I'll give you a strong push out!
So that's our ordeal and... Heaven's Judgment?!
You're comin', too!
Now there's a giant!
Yes. In Upper Yard, four priests who are
strong beyond imagination await you.
You fools!
Where is it?! Where'd the Crow go?!
We gotta catch the boat, quick!
Alright, let's go to Upper Yard!
No. That's a statue!
You can't go back now!
Oh. But it's a total dead-end!
--Hm?
--You should've just behaved
and done what I told you to...
Oh, then it's easy.
No, there are four entrances!
No...!
To put it simply, all we have to do
is beat up those priests, right?
Dammit! Can't see from down here!
We, the White Berets, are the gentlest
upholders of the law in God's Land.
Don't tell me they each
lead to different places?!
The bastards actually left...
With no hesitation or uncertainty at all...
You're so simpleminded.
Alright!
"Swamp Ordeal"
However, they are not as nice as we are!
"Swamp Ordeal"...
"Iron Ordeal"
Watch yourself, Luffy!
These priests are no ordinary people!
"Iron Ordeal"...
"String Ordeal"
This is becoming fun!
"String Ordeal"...
"Ball Ordeal"
You are now 2nd degree criminals!
"Ball Ordeal"...
Let's find the boat ASAP
and get the hell outta here!
Are we allowed to go in any one?!
No matter if you cry or scream...
Is God trying to play games
with us or something?!
U-Urgh... I-I'm stuck...!
...you'll be judged...
Four ordeals... Which do we choose?
...by the priests of Upper Yard!!
How stubborn.
Heso!!
Ah, beyond the never-ending sky
Even if we're far apart
The future that I once saw
is now starting to take shape
I don't want you to forget
That on those days when
you're brought to tears
There are days where I almost lose to myself
You have a friend here to share the pain
When that happened, there was
someplace warm I could go
That far-off feeling we refuse to concede
The friends I took pride in
always, without fail,
I won't let it just be a dream
pushed me onwards, didn't they?
The eternal brilliance that
everyone is searching for
We will surely embrace it with our own hands
Ah, the stars are pouring
down underneath the sky
This unique moment...
We were tricked!
Conis, why are you shaking like that?
Crap! At this rate, we're
gonna lose the boat!
Is Conis gonna be alright?
What do we do? Which do we go in?
All we can do is count on the old man!
Ball! Ball! It sounds like fun!
What's the fuss? We're used to being pursued.
Oh? You think so?
What are these surprise
clouds and this ball guy?!
We gotta save Nami-san and Robin-chan now!
These are ordeals! They're not gonna be fun!
Now that I look closer, you look pale, too.
Alright, then! Get ready for an adventure!
Sky fights are strange!
Whatever, it's decided.
Just don't let your guard down!
--There are two others.
--Huh? What's that?
--I...
--You look like you're afraid of something.
He's definitely planning to go there!
This is no time for crappy ordeals!
--Aaah! Aieee!
--Is it "God's ordeal"? Shut up!
--Would you please run?
--What?
Hey, something's wrong with the ship!
We gotta save Nami-san and Robin-chan!
What is this place?!
Once we know someone's a criminal, if we
don't lead them to the place of judgment,
It seems there's nothing we
can do. It's already started.
--Balls! Balls!
--How is this an ordeal?!
Zoro! Nami! Robin!
Just keep moving forward!
we'll be killed, so...
Heaven's Judgment, huh?
Please let me go home!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"10% Survival Rate! Satori, the Mantra Master!"
"Is Escape Possible?!
God's Challenge is Set in Motion!"
"A Trap On Lovely Street! The Almighty Eneru."
"The Ordeal of Spheres!
Desperate Struggle in the Lost Forest"
"Onward, Crow! To the Sacrificial Altar"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!