Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
T-There it is!
--Jango!
--Y-Yeah?
I'll handle the boy.
You take care of Miss Kaya.
What the...?
Those're cannonballs!
Hmm?
Huh? That was way off!
As we planned, have her write a will...
Who do you take your friends for?!
Whew, that's heavy!
What are you guys doing?
W-What is that?!
...then kill her!
Cannon practice!
I found it in the storeroom!
There they are!
Foolish pirates.
Those're cannonballs!
We finally got a cannon,
so I thought I'd do some practice!
You'd knowingly attack
the invincible fleet
Awesome! You hit it on your first try!
U-Usopp Pirates!
Then just leave it to me!
commanded by Captain
Usopp-sama of the Going Merry?!
Whadya think?! I'm awesome when
it comes to aiming! Impressed?!
"Anger Explosion!
Kuro vs. Luffy, How it Ends!"
I believe it was when I was three
that I jumped on a cannonball
Attack them, men! Attack!
Protect Kaya!
flying my way and traveled
halfway around the world!
It's settled! You're our sniper!
Luffy!
--How do you work this thing?
--Listen!
Come out, you damn pirates!
Me and Usopp are gonna chase
that hypno-freak! That a problem?!
Hmm? That voice...
Hey, Zoro! Do you
know how to work it?!
What the... What the... Who are you?!
He's been fast asleep all this time.
Nope! Hurry!
"Sea"
Are you nameless pirate
wannabes trying to kill my partner?!
He's no fun.
Tired?
C'mon, you guys. Show some
interest in other people...
A little further to the south is a
reef that'd make a perfect target!
What?!
The Out of the Back Attack does
have lots of unnecessary movement.
I dunno what's going on,
but stop breaking our ship!
All done!
For reals?!
Don't get cocky.
Let's go! Let's go!
T-That's Captain Kuro for ya!
L-Lost by a hair...
--Let's go there!
--Hey! You're gonna fire
a cannon without me?!
Look! A pirate flag!
Everything so far has been playtime.
--Get 'im!
--Hurray for Captain Kuro!
Now that Usopp's joined
and we have four people,
People used to call me Cannon
Master Usopp, you know! Listen!
--Captain Kuro!
--You're awesome, Captain Kuro!
we need to have our own mark!
You get the special treatment.
Don't call me that name!
"Famous Cook!
Sanji of the Sea Restaurant"
That's our mark?
I'm going to let you taste plenty
of fear, then slowly cook you!
This plan is so I can be completely
rid of the name "Captain Kuro"!
"The Three-Sword Style's Past!
Zoro and Kuina's Vow!"
Whadya think? Nice, huh?!
A pirate flag is a symbol
of death. A symbol of fear!
I'm tired...
Devising plans everyday for you
men who only care about mayhem...
Out of the Back Attack!
I do sense fear, though...
Fear of your talent.
Say, where're you taking me to today?
Being relentlessly attacked by
government dogs and bounty hunters...
Wish you would've told me first!
To the most wonderful
restaurant in the world.
Don't forget about me,
the gifted artist!
Don't tell me... there's one
in the middle of the ocean?
Gifted artist?
I've drawn graffiti on walls
for 50 years straight!
When it comes to painting,
I'm in a league all my own!
W-What?!
Hey!
Here's to your beauty...
Awesome! 50 years?!
Hey!
That means he's an old man now!
Just try your foot technique now!
I'm here to challenge your dojo!
Not only that, he must have
5 or 6 grandkids by now!
Damn you! Get away from me!
You're "tired"?!
Someone strong, come out! Fight me!
That's awesome, too!
Well, just wait until you see it...
You're not fit to be a pirate if having
a name on the seas scares you!
Now your plan of three
years is a complete failure!
Hey!
Dojo-challenging is
certainly rare these days.
What?!
Alright! Behold this work of art!
He caught Captain Kuro!
Hmph! Don't take me
lightly just 'cause I'm a kid!
Tadah!
My ambition is much greater than yours!
I'm unrivaled in the next village over!
Hey, if he wins, that means
we won't get killed, right?!
Who told you to make your flag?!
Very well. I accept.
If I win, I get your dojo!
I guess that's more like it.
"Protect Kaya! The Usopp
Pirates' Great Efforts!"
Now you die!
Wow, it's pretty good!
--And if you lose?
--T-Then, uhh...
Hey, if it isn't Johnny!
Oh, no, you don't!
Yeah! It's good! I like it!
I'll become a student here!
What?
So this is our mark...
Alright! Usopp!
Draw one on the sail, too!
That will be fine. Now, then...
B-Big Bro Zoro!
You damn kids!
Kuina!
Right!
Wh-Why are you on
a pirate ship like this?!
Is that hypnotist still behind us?!
Yes, Father?
Alright! All done!
Looks like you're one
step too late, Haramaki!
What?! You're not gonna fight me?!
Nope, I don't see him!
Let's lose him for good!
Is something wrong?
Yosaku isn't with you?
I wouldn't say so!
Now the Going Merry
pirate ship is all set!
Kuina is a girl, but she's even
stronger than the adults in the dojo.
Well...
Like he can really catch
us inside this forest!
Yes! That branch was in the way!
What? Does Zoro know that guy?
Don't worry, Kaya-san!
We will keep you safe!
I say this, even as her parent...
What's going on?
What?!
Usopp-san...
Yeah! In the name of the Usopp Pirates!
Fine!
"You're the Weird Creature!
Gaimon and His Strange Friends"
Then please come inside.
Get 'im, Rubber Guy!
Y-Yosaku is...
Thank you...
Kick Captain Kuro's ass!
I can use any I want?
Get away!
I'm pooped...
To your heart's content.
You guys have no right to cheer me on!
He's sick?
All right, then! Let's begin!
Although he was full of life
up until a few days ago,
Is this the right way?
It seems kinda dangerous...
Eat this, hypnotist!
Alright! Bring it on!
now he keeps getting pale
suddenly and then fainting!
What?!
Usopp-san!
Wait.
Bow before the gods!
--Captain!
I have no idea what's causing it...
--What's he doing?
--He's ridiculous...
Let go!
That's it! That's the place!
No doubt about it!
Gum-Gum...
Bow to each other!
In the end, his teeth fell out and his old
wound opened up and started bleeding.
Begin!
Do you see something neat?
Special Attack: Exploding Star!
The legendary Treasure Island.
I didn't know what to do any more...
The legendary Treasure Island?
I've heard of that before!
--My plan will not be disrupted!
--...Bell...
Not there...
so we were on a rocky island
letting him rest quietly. But then...
Yeah! It's a famous
island among pirates!
Where are you, you runts?!
Don't think you can escape me!
As are the weird stories about it...
Weird stories?
That whoever gets near the
island incurs a god's wrath...
I can shave this whole
forest bald, if you'd like!
D-Damn it!
...a cannonball came
flying from this ship...
Whoa! He seems really mad!
W-Were the rumors really true?!
Is this the god's wrath?!
He's not just a hypnotist?!
You've studied Two-Sword
Style techniques before?
That sounds kinda neat!
No! Today's the first time I've
ever held a bamboo sword!
--W-We're sorry!
Luffy! You're not thinking of--
We sure are!
Where did you run off to?
Today's your first time?
Sorry doesn't cut it...
This way!
Damn it! I'm strong!
And I'm gonna get even stronger!
Let's go! Treasure Island!
Isn't that right, partner?
I refuse... I refuse to lose to this girl!
Big Bro... Is he going to die?
Oww...
Why doesn't he dodge?!
H-He beat him...
Where are you, you runts?!
H-He beat Captain Kuro!
--Are you all stupid?
--What'd you say?!
Match over!
Not even the navy was a match
for Kuro, Man of a Thousand Plans!
He's like a boar.
Hey! East! East! I said east!
Come now, Kuina!
But he really beat him!
It's 10 years too early for an
amateur to use the Two-Sword Style!
--Wh-What're you doing?!
--Ouch!
Just who are you?!
Like I know where that is!
Tell me left or right!
If you mock my partner's
death, you'll pay for it--
--Then turn right!
--That's the opposite way!
What?!
Monkey D. Luffy.
Luffy! Usopp! Remember we
have limes in the storage?
What? We can fight
another match, if you want!
Kaya-san!
I'd never lose to a pirate who ditches
his name and runs from the sea.
Are you listening?!
Bring them here. Now!
I'm sorry... You run on ahead...
--Y-Yes ma'am!
Damn it! A loss is a loss!
--Out of my way!
The only time a pirate should
abandon his name is when he dies!
Yes. It's good to accept
defeat gracefully. Then, you'll...
What are you saying?!
Our mission is to protect you!
Yeah! I'll become a student here!
Got a problem with that?!
L-Luffy?! Yeah, I never
heard that name before!
This is one creepy island!
Oh, no! She's got a really bad fever!
None whatsoever.
Remember my name for
the rest of your lives!
Yeah?
Eh?! Hang in there, Kaya-san!
I'm going to train lots and lots and lots
It's said that an extraordinary treasure
rests somewhere on this island.
A doctor! Get a doctor!
I'm the man who's gonna
be King of the Pirates!
It's scurvy.
You idiot! This is no time for that!
Someone's trying to kill her!
Scurvy?
and then I will beat you!
If we weren't too late,
he'll be fine in just a few days.
Supposedly, lots of pirates
have landed here in the past,
This guy's...
But it's dangerous for
her to run any more!
R-Really, Big Sis?!
Remember that!
But...
but they've all fled in terror
before they could even look for it.
Take him and leave!
Where are you, you runts?!
Big Sis, is he really...
That day'll never come.
Stop... calling me that.
In terror?
Never come here again!
In the past, it was a hopeless disease
that accompanied sea journeys.
Supposedly, one pirate's face
suddenly changed into a boar's face,
Run!
Thank you...
I'm happy that you helped me...
and another's mustache stretched
out and strangled him like snakes.
--Here, drink it. Drink a lot.
--Here... drink more. Drink more.
Just the thought is enough for me...
But the cause was simply a
deficiency of plant-derived nutrients.
Run away, all three of you.
That's not real, right?
Though I'm sure the stories
are exaggerated somewhat!
Where did you run off to?
Ships in the past
didn't carry fresh fruits
Well done...
It's no use running! Come on out!
--Hurry!
--Raise the anchor!
and vegetables since
they weren't storable, so...
D-Don't scare me like that!
Okay, now. Put them all in his mouth.
I'd expect even you to collapse
after all you just went through...
Now he'll be fine.
Say.
If we leave Kaya-san and run now,
we'll probably survive, right?
You're amazing! You're like a doctor!
I'm hungry.
What were you mad about earlier?
Well, I always thought you were good.
I'm going to sleep.
Yeah, probably.
I hate them. They're wrong.
Plus our captain always said to run
with your tail between your legs
How can he sleep in
a creepy place like this?
Yeah, you're right. She is.
Yeah. What kind of
nerves does he have?
if you think you're gonna lose...
You should know at least that much!
You could die if you don't!
That's not how friends should act.
Damn brats think they can mock me!
What're you talking about?
Of course it's not.
Pirates aren't the lovely things
you make them out to be.
Wha...
--Yaay! Yaay! Yaay!
I'd say Captain Kuro's
more standard than you.
What are you doing?! Don't scare me!
All those nutrients revived me!
N-No, I just thought I'd do
a little dance to liven things up!
All right, partner!
Our captain is a liar!
I want some meat.
There's no way you can
recover this quickly!
See? See? See?
You're unbelievable!
Match over!
The winner is Kuina,
with 2000 wins and 0 losses!
Even he went and fought!
He tried so hard to protect us!
Stop that, Luffy...
Sorry for not
introducing ourselves first.
D-Damn it...
My name is Johnny.
You're still as weak as ever, Zoro!
Can you keep everything that's
just happened here a secret?
I'm Yosaku.
I won't let Kaya-san die!
You're so pathetic. Especially for a boy.
The pirate bounty hunter duo!
Eh?! A secret?! How come?!
Alright, then! Prepare
yourselves, Usopp Pirates!
W-What is this?!
--Alright!
--Let's fight him!
We used to be
colleagues of Big Bro Zoro.
Yeah! After we just fought
for the village's sake!
No! You're still just children!
You mustn't die for my sake!
Hey! Zoro isn't weak!
Glad to make your acquaintance.
Everyone'll change their
opinion of you, too!
Leave...
He's the strongest one
out of all the guys!
I never thought that
I'd see you guys here...
He's even beat grownups!
You could be the village hero!
--Who's there?!
--Leave!
But he's weaker than me.
We're not gonna die.
We're gonna fight to live!
--Yeah! Yeah!
Where's it coming from?!
But again, we're surprised...
Usopp-san. You need to clear up
everyone's misunderstanding...
Even with two swords,
a weakling's still a weakling.
As our captain always said.
We never imagined that the pirate
hunter Zoro became a pirate...
I am this island's protective god!
Leave this island at once
if you value your lives!
--Yeah!
Misunderstanding? I was only
called an exaggerator, like always.
You losers'd do good to stay quiet.
Your howling makes you pitiful.
Yeah, I know...
Protective god?
Big Bro...
You guys're pirates, aren't you?
There's no need to scare everyone
with something that's already over.
--Yeah.
--Pirates, just as I thought.
You brats...
Why would a god ask
something like that?
H-Hey, partner?!
Aside from things like this,
Listen! Just try taking
another step into the forest!
You lost again, Zoro...
no pirates will show up to attack
a remote village like this one.
The instant you do, will you
receive my divine punishment
Even after you've grown so strong.
T-That guy...
and meet your doom?!
Sensei! Are you
giving her secret training
I'm just going to pretend
that nothing ever happened.
He broke Captain Kuro's "Cat Claw"!
How should I know?
Why are you asking me?
'cause she's your daughter?!
This is a lesson.
It was all a lie.
--What's the deal?
--This guy seems kinda weird.
Don't cheat!
Yeah. There're pitfalls like this
That leaves only five more
of those weird swords!
No, no. I do no such thing.
What did you say, straw hat boy?!
when you travel on
the sea for a long time...
Zoro did indeed grow stronger.
Which means on the ship,
we have to consider
I won't force you to, but...
But Kuina has grown stronger as well.
No, I can do it! If it's for
the best of the village!
the distribution of nutrients
using limited kinds of food...
W-What are these things?!
It's okay! He can still fight plenty!
--Zoro?
When we think about it carefully,
it's a necessary ability...
Me, too!
Me, too! I'll never say a word, ever!
Humans I completely transformed
when they came to look for treasure.
I'm gonna wash my face.
Yeah! He still has the other claw!
Scratch him up and
kill 'im, Captain Kuro!
Kaya...
A necessary ability, huh?
Will it be hard for you?
Hey! That name is taboo now!
Then you really are a god?!
Okay, then! A seafaring cook!
Damn it!
I think his name in this
village is Klaha... something.
--What?
Look at all these weird things...
Why can't I beat Kuina?! Why?! Why?!
Let's go find a seafaring cook!
No.
Is this a lion?
Kla-san, then!
Aha! Then we'll be able to eat
yummy food even on the ship!
Are you sure it's not a pig?
I'm gonna be the strongest
man in the world! So why?!
--Kla-san! Get 'im!
Where is Usopp-kun this morning?
Exactly!
Oww! Oww! Oww!
W-What exactly are you?!
Be quiet, you!
It throws everything off for some
reason... I can't get motivated...
If you're looking for a cook like that,
there's a perfect place for that.
Tonight... I'm gonna fight her again!
I'm a rubber person!
I ate a Devil Fruit!
Mommy...
Devil Fruit?! Don't be absurd!
All right! Where's it?
I'll come exterminate
every one of you later...
Is the liar guy not coming today?
I heard rumors about them long ago
when I used to be a pirate, but...
But this place is close
to the Grand Line, and...
A mere year since he became a pupil...
That damn exaggeration-spewing kid...
When you used to be a pirate?
Zoro's improvement is
nothing short of spectacular.
Jango too, of course!
Where is he today?!
N-No! I'm not reminiscing
about old times at all!
you hear rumors there about the hawk-
eyed man you've been looking for...
He trains incomparably
more than any of the others.
Do you think maybe I was
too harsh yesterday?
W-Why us?!
No, I don't want to
hear about old times!
Please stop joking around, Captain Kuro!
He'll be back to his old tricks
come tomorrow! I'm sure of it...
What're you talking about?
You're the one who said it!
So I suppose it's only natural.
We'll head...
Are you really a god?!
It's still not too late for us
to attack the village, right?!
But... it seems he's still
no match for Kuina-san.
north-northeast!
Shut up! If you won't leave,
then receive my divine punishment!
And if Captain Jango gets her to
write her will, the plan should work!
Yes!
All right!
Female swordsmen are
faced with immense walls.
Thanks!
I wouldn't have been able to protect
the village without you guys!
You need not worry about this plan;
As she is now, I cannot
let her inherit the dojo.
What're you talkin' about?
your corpses will be enough for
me to place the blame on you...
If you hadn't done anything,
I would've done nothing!
Now you've done it, God!
--Father!
--Kuina-san!
H-How are you all right?!
Our destination is...
Me, too!
--There you are!
--Don't move!
It's not nice to eavesdrop, Kuina.
I never intended to let you
leave this village from the start...
Who cares about that?
I got me some treasure!
I told you not to move!
I will become the world's
greatest swordsman! You'll see!
I can't have people who
know I exist stay alive...
...the Sea Restaurant...
...Baratie!
--That can't be!
--Hey, God or whoever!
Kuina. As a girl...
You can't be serious!
Pistols don't work on this guy!
Then you planned to kill
us from the very start?!
--Whoa!
But they surprise me,
so I don't like 'em!
...you can never be
the world's strongest.
What do you think, everyone?!
This incident has helped me
finally come to a decision.
M-Monster!
Whoa! It's a huge fish!
That's right...
O-Over there!
--How lovely!
--That's pretty funky!
Since three years ago, when I
was still known as Captain Kuro...
Here it is. His pistol.
Right?! Just like I told you, right?!
It was all...
...all part of my plan!
Wh-What the...
Where'd he go?
At a place like this...
Man, you guys're dumb.
A Navy ship...
You're such an uncool pirate group!
--What is this?
--This is a god?
Zoro?!
"Uncool"?
What're you doing out here?
S-Surely they're not gonna
shoot at us, are they?
Captain Usopp! What did you
want to talk to us about?!
Pirate groups are nothing more
than a collection of social outcasts!
That's my line! What are
you doing here at this hour?!
It's moving!
Hmph! What an unpleasant
bunch we've run into...
You guys fought well against
those Black Cat Pirates!
Without plans, what
can they possibly do?!
Wh-When did they...
Every last one should just
shut up and follow my plans!
I'm here to challenge you
to your 2001st fight!
As captain, I feel very proud!
I plan to make this
my last fight with you!
Crew members are loyal
pawns of the captain!
Stand me up, already!
I said stand me up!
Y-You're too kind...
I've never seen that pirate flag.
We're nothing compared to you...
He's a person!
I'm going to end this!
Neat! Is he a scrub brush?
Whether my men live or die is all
up to my orders as their leader!
Fight me with a real sword!
You're embarrassing us!
Darn it!
No, you really did great!
What's so god-like about you?!
You thought you could trick us!
You have a real one, don't you?!
We're not pirates!
No matter how powerful the obstacle,
You were scared to death,
but you managed to keep Kaya safe!
they simply need to stand up
to it and die for my plan...
Shut up! Stand me up, I say!
Against me?
I'm Iron Fist Fullbody,
Lieutenant at Navy Headquarters!
Don't act all big after
you've fallen over!
We overcame our biggest and
greatest battle since we formed
I-I'll let you go for today!
Sure.
Hey, who's your captain?!
Come out and state your name!
Wait!
the Usopp Pirates five years ago,
when you guys were just four!
I'm Luffy!
--Yes!
Huh?!
I'm Usopp!
So, I know this is sudden, but I've
decided to set out to sea by myself!
We just made our pirate flag
the day before yesterday!
And I'm the one who drew it!
This is how pirates are!
Huh?!
The Wado Ichimonji...
--Hey! Luffy!
--Luffy!
Don't you talk down to me, traveler boy!
I'm gonna be a real pirate!
Hmph! Oh, you're just... Hmm?
You two over there,
I remember seeing you before.
No matter how many hundreds
I had always been unsure if I
wanted to stay here forever or not...
If I remember correctly, you're a bounty
hunter duo going after small fish.
or thousands of men follow
you as their captain...
But, once I saw them,
I finally made up my mind!
Wh-What?!
So you finally got caught by pirates...
...you'll never be better than Usopp!
I feel that, as a man, I must
set out onto the vast ocean!
W-We are...
What?!
So I'm leaving this village!
That's a laugh.
You're saying I'm inferior to a kid
pretending to be a pirate captain?
C'mon, let's get going.
Okay.
You think small-time bounty hunters
would go after these guys?!
That's right!
There's but one reason:
the pirate flag is calling me!
You're hilarious!
Don't get cocky just because
you snapped one of my claws!
There. You're all set.
Hmm?
How exactly is he better
than me?! Let's hear it!
Captain! You're lying, right?!
Now, let's go to the restaurant.
You're a pretty popular guy, God...
You're lying again, right?!
They're an eyesore. Sink them.
So you used these guys
It's way too hasty to do that!
Don't you love this village, Captain?!
to scare off everyone
who came to the island?
--Yes, sir!
Character.
What'll happen to the Usopp Pirates?!
What?!
But I've never seen a person stuffed
inside a treasure chest before!
You don't know what a true pirate is!
He ignored us.
Are you a boxed and sheltered son?
You've been great to me, guys...
Next time we see him,
we'll have to shut him up!
Yeah. I've been overly pampered
since I was just a little boy...
What is this...
I plan to leave without telling
the villagers. Give them my regards.
Of course I'm not!
They're wanted pirates, Big Sis Nami--
I can't get out of this box!
--No...
--I don't want to!
I've been alone on this island
and in this box for 20 years now!
Don't go, Captain!
In other words, if we defeat them,
we'll get the reward money.
H-He...
20 years?!
He kept up with the Pussy
Foot Maneuver's speed!
Do you remember this place?
A very profitable business,
don't you think, Big Sis?
Two real swords are heavy, huh?
This is where we first met.
How insulting...
It seems you still lack strength!
You've been all alone on
this island for 20 years?
S-Shut up!
If you want to know about
real pirates that much,
My hair and mustache
are just as you can see.
W-We're in trouble.
They're aiming at us!
Even my eyebrows got connected...
It's also been 20 years since I've
conversed with anyone like this.
--All done!
--Liar guy!
then I'll show you that terror...
Can you understand how painful this is?
Who're you guys?!
Don't treat me all buddy-like!
The terror of a pirate who's been
face-to-face with death many times!
Leave it to me! Gum-Gum...
But you're famous!
--It seems ridiculous.
--What did you say?!
Yeah, you're a famous person...
My 2001st win.
I see!
Slingshot!
Oh, here you are...
So, people've finally started to
respectfully call me Captain Usopp!
You were asleep this whole time,
even after all that happened?!
Hey! That stance! Is he--
Everyone calls you Liar Usopp!
Damn it...
He's gonna use that technique?!
--But he's only fighting one guy!
--But that's definitely it!
Damn it...
Alright! From this day forth,
you're members of the Usopp Pirates!
He's planning to use the
Out of the Back Attack!
This sucks...
--Eh?!
Don't give me that!
W-Who's this guy?!
Notice sooner.
Isn't it bad for us to be
here?! He'll get us, too!
He's a guy stuffed in a treasure chest!
A lot's happened, huh?
I'm the one who should be
crying out of frustration.
Ow...
He plans to kill us, too!
He even said so earlier!
Are you a boxed and sheltered son?!
A Cerberus! Scare it away!
Yeah. I've been overly pampered
since I was just a little boy...
Eh?
Please stop, Captain Kuro!
Anything but that technique!
You see, when girls grow up,
they get weaker than men...
A dragon! Capture it!
Of course I'm not!
We'll do anything you want!
Don't do the same stupid gag twice!
Please, Captain Kuro!
Zoro! Gimme a hand!
Flour Star!
Even you'll catch up to me soon...
You're amazing, Captain!
What's the big deal?
Ouch! Ouch!
What are you doing?! Stop it!
You're pulling my head off!
He's only wobbling back and forth...
But of course!
I am a brave warrior of the sea!
You're always saying you're going
to be the world's best swordsman.
--Don't do it!
--Captain Kuro!
You're right! You can't get out!
We don't wanna hear
about the old days!
Don't be crazy!
Because of my lack of
exercise over the years,
My father told me that
a girl can never be that...
Yeah! We don't wanna hear about that!
this treasure chest fits
together with my body now!
Owner!
This isn't like you, Captain!
Why are you saying this stuff now?!
Are you all right, Head Chef Zeff?!
If you try to break it,
my body'll get destroyed, too!
Owner, are you all right?!
I know...
I know that! But... But it's frustrating!
He's a strangely annoying guy.
It's almost like you're...
But who are you guys?
Hmm? What happened?
Is our reservation okay?
You're so stupid, Captain! Stupid!
You're lucky, Zoro. You're a boy.
You're nothing like any of the
other pirates who've come here.
I want to be the world's
greatest swordsman, too!
I'm Luffy! The man who's
gonna be King of the Pirates!
Head Chef Zeff, are you really okay?
My breasts have even
started to grow out now...
I'm saying it's not okay!
W-What?!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates
and get the One Piece!
What are your ambitions in life?!
If only... If only I had
been born a man...
Never mind, just get back to the
restaurant already! Get to work!
To run a pub!
The One Piece?!
Don't tell me you're seriously
planning to enter the Grand Line?!
To be a master carpenter!
B-But Owner, you're...
Don't be whining like
that after you beat me!
To be a novel writer!
We even have a chart of the Grand Line!
You idiots! Do you
want me to get angry?!
That's not fair! You're my goal!
T-Then swear here that you'll
continue on each of your paths
Don't take it lightly!
That place is Hell, or a graveyard!
Feeding customers is a cook's job!
--Zoro...
--Boy this, girl that!
I once saw pirates who'd managed
to escape from the Grand Line!
and never let the fires
of your ambitions go out!
Are you fools trying to put
my restaurant out of business?!
Are you gonna say that stuff
too when I beat you someday?!
You act like none of it is skill!
They looked almost like people
who had died and lost their souls!
As of today...
You're insulting all the hard
training I've been doing!
Please stop, Captain Kuro!
Something incredibly
horrific must've happened,
...the Usopp Pirates...
We brought him in.
So don't say that stuff!
or they must've run into
monsters or something...
Out of the Back Attack!
He's the one responsible.
Not a single one of them
even tried to speak.
Promise me!
I-I-I-I'm very sorry!
Someday, one of us will be
the world's greatest swordsman!
On top of that, rumors about the
One Piece spawn even more rumors,
...are disbanded!
so there's no telling what's true or not!
We'll compete to see who gets there!
Ahhh! Your leg...
Some 20-odd years since the
start of the Great Pirate Era,
Idiot!!
"Food"
What a small haul...
the One Piece is already a dream
within a dream beyond a legend!
I thought they'd have a
little more treasure than that...
Well, we've eaten.
We should get going now.
You dummy. You're so weak...
Let's see, is the fight over by now?
Yeah...
So which is the Grand Line?
--Here you are!
--Hey, Miss!
--It's a promise!
Huh? Everyone's stopped... Is it over?
Dunno. Don't you know,
old scrub brush guy?
Are you alright, being out of bed?
I can't read sea charts one bit.
Yes...
Oh. Then we're the same.
This didn't happen just now.
My sickness this past year
That's not a pirate conversation!
O-Oh, then it was like
that from the beginning...
was caused by the mental dismay
from having lost my parents...
Whoa...
Anyways, even if we do
enter the Grand Line,
T-There it is!
She's gotten even stronger than before!
And Usopp-san really
cheered me up, too...
earning as much money as we can,
then escaping, is the best idea.
Why over there?!
But you gave me
bruises all over my body.
I can't stay coddled forever!
I will find the One Piece!
I have good luck!
The medical fees and the repair
charges for the ship will cost you a lot!
Not again!
You've done so much for me. Thank you.
Where does all that
confidence of yours come from?
Gotta get stronger! So I can
hold lots of swords just fine!
Now it's the wall!
I will get it! You'll see!
I've prepared a present for you
from the bottom of my heart!
If two's not enough,
then I'll use three!
I won't ask you to reduce the charges.
Whatever you say...
Oh?
But...
You're the same...
Please stop, Captain Kuro!
Please accept it!
I don't have money!
You're just like me; you even
look like me, like we're twins!
It's no use! He attacks at random
using his Pussy Foot Maneuver!
What do you guys want?
You talk very candidly.
Because of his speed, not even
he knows what he's cutting!
How in the world
does he look like you?!
Kuina...
Well, if you don't have money, you
have no other choice but to work here.
I understand! Achieving
your dreams someday!
So many crew members
have fallen victim to--
Kuina's dead...
We used to think the same way!
Yeah, I'll make proper amends.
All packed...
Hey!
You'll do chores unpaid for a year.
We?
We were willing to put our lives
on the line to search for treasure!
Okay! Chores unpaid for a year!
Guess it's farewell to this house, too!
It was that zeal that
changed my entire life!
I'll let you off the hook with that.
W-What's happening?!
People are suddenly being cut!
A-A year?! A-A year...
You mean a year?!
W-Wait. What do you mean?
Apparently, she slipped and fell
down the storehouse steps...
It was 20 years ago. My fellow
pirates and I landed on this island.
Storehouse?
Seems she was looking for a sharpening
stone for her beloved sword.
To find the treasure that
was said to rest here.
What would she need that for?
I don't know...
Alright...
She was just a child, too...
Show yourself, butler...
What's taking Luffy so long...?
What?!
200 men have searched for
a month now, but it's no use!
There's just no understanding people...
Yeah...
No one knows what's
just around the corner...
Maybe they'll make him do
chores for a month or so...
All we've found on this island
is this one empty treasure chest!
What the...? I can't get out!
He should've made it the Navy's
fault instead of being foolishly honest.
We're leaving, men!
Darn it!
What're you doing, Gaimon?
We're going on ahead!
Who do you take your friends for?!
Yeah.
Did anyone look up there?
The captain stayed down
here the whole month...
Luffy...
I'll check it out one last time!
Hey, look. Just as I thought, the man
sitting there is Lieutenant Fullbody.
A caravel!
--He's a lieutenant at Navy Headquarters.
--Huh?
Can we really have this?!
I couldn't believe my own eyes!
He's gorgeous. How elegant...
Yes, please use it!
I-I found it! It's up here!
It's amazing. Everyone's looking at you.
It's a slightly older model,
but I personally designed it!
Hey! Guys!
Well, they're admiring you.
A carvel-make caravel, with lateen
sails and a central stern rudder...
Found you!
This is good!
Bastard! You should've let
yourself be cut like a good boy!
...the Going Merry!
Th-This flavor...
That's when I got stuck in the chest!
Hmm... This scent...
Look! Thanks to you, my adorable
men are left alive and in agony.
Let me explain the running rigging!
When I came to, my crew
was already far out to sea.
This may be the scent of the soil
of Micquo of the North Land...
First, about the Kruger
net yard adjustment--
Bitter with plenty of body, a tad sour...
No, no! You can explain
the ship stuff to me!
It would've been better for
them to die in that attack!
Crap!
Wait a minute! Does that
mean that fortune is all mine?!
This wine is...
What a good ship! Especially
this front-- it's so cool!
Iturutz Burger Stein!
I can't climb up like this!
We've loaded it with everything
you might need on a voyage.
Now what? You look like
you have something to say...
Aren't I right, waiter?!
I can't get out! I can't get out!
Thanks! It leaves nothing to beat tired!
That's... damn wrong, sir.
Yeah...
I will never be...
That's "leaves nothing
to be desired," you idiot.
Hey! Come back!
Your soup is getting cold.
Please eat it while it's hot.
...a man like you.
Even after all this time,
Not "will."
the fortune I only saw for an
instant has never left my mind.
Stop this thing!
Usopp-san!
What's he doing?
Someone like you can't be like me!
By the way, I'm Sanji, the Sous Chef.
Pirates have come to this island
in search of treasure countless times,
Let's just stop him for now.
He's on a collision course with the ship.
but I used these guys
to scare them all away.
All the waiters ran off as of yesterday.
People are such fragile things, Zoro...
That's how I've protected
the treasure for 20 years now!
T-Thanks...
Sure thing.
Especially since
you're going to die here,
It's mine!
So you are taking to
the ocean, Usopp-san?
Kuina... She was a very
competitive girl...
You really shouldn't laugh.
Yeah! No question about it! It's yours!
But he looked so confident...
while you writhe in agony as
I hack you up like raw fish...
Yeah. I've decided to get going
before I start to change my mind.
Alright, Gaimon-san!
We'll get the treasure for you!
She practiced in this dojo
since she was little,
Do you know a lot...
and achieved strength
that exceeded even adults.
...about wine?
--R-Really?!
--Yeah!
Don't stop me, now.
I'm going to painstakingly
carve you up as a special treat!
Well, yeah...
I won't. I could just tell somehow.
Don't tell me you're gonna...
Because of this,
she became a bit self-conceited...
...although it seems my sense of
taste isn't working well today...
Aren't you a thief who
only steals from pirates?
That's kind of sad, too!
How rude!
Hey, what's going on?
The next time I come to this village,
But then that's when
you appeared, Zoro.
Even I know what's
appropriate and what's not!
I'm sure I requested the owner to serve
us that wine when I made a reservation.
I'll tell you adventure stories that
seem even more lie-like than lies!
Oh, no, you don't!
Out of the Back Attack!
I thank you.
Okay! I look forward to it!
You grew ever stronger, so she
started to practice even more,
You guys take care, too!
Let's meet again sometime!
so as not to lose to you.
What do you mean by that?
Please reduce it to a week.
--How come?
--Huh? "How come?"
So as not to lose to a boy...
Man, you're antisocial...
Come out, you brats!
You talk very candidly.
I'm gonna be a pirate too, so we'll
meet on the high seas eventually!
I know you're hiding there!
Give yourself up!
And she had begun to break down
the walls of female swordsmanship...
Two weeks!
Hey! You wrecked my restaurant and
injured me, the Head Chef, seriously.
What're you talkin' about?
Get on already.
...but I'm an ordinary parent, too.
Eh?!
Here?
You can't settle that with just
one or two weeks of unpaid work.
We're friends now, aren't we?
We surrender!
We'll give you Kaya-san!
I haven't been here for a while, myself.
Come over here!
We'll take you to her!
I've decided! Three weeks!
When I look at you now,
I feel pained, too...
Don't talk so...
The time has finally come!
Today is a great day!
Like I'll really fall for that!
I can't trust what a bunch of brats say!
I...
...candidly!
I'm counting on you, Straw Hat!
I get to be captain, right?!
Alright! Gum-Gum...
Don't be dumb! I'm the captain!
Huh?!
...Rocket!
We got him! Now!
Sensei...
--No!
--Hmm?
Let me have... that sword...
Take this! Pepper Attack!
I've patiently waited
ten years to become a pirate.
Yes!
I definitely don't want to
be stuck here for a year!
Kuina's sword?
Hmm?
W-Well?! Is it there?!
I'm going to get stronger for her, too!
Okay, I've decided.
I'll get you to let me off the
hook in a week. So I've decided.
I'm going to get strong enough
that my name reaches to Heaven!
What's he doing?
I knew it! They were...
they were lying from the very start!
Oh? If you value time so much,
There goes the captain...
Luffy!
I'm going to be the world's
strongest swordsman!
Yeah. But he's with those guys,
so I feel less worried now.
--Hey! Luffy!
--What the heck's going on?!
I'll tell you what you can
do to settle it quickly.
--Push...
Yeah. I've never seen anyone
as strong as them before.
I promised her...
I found 'em! Six treasure chests!
Ow!
--Hyaaah!
Leave one of your legs here.
I...
Guess it can't be helped.
W-Well done!
He always talked about
how he wanted to be a pirate.
The villagers'll probably be
sad when we tell them, though...
Oww! Oww! Oww!
No!
I finally got it!
The treasure! The treasure!
Ha! You sure talk very candidly!
It's all so sudden, plus he
livened things up all by himself...
Toss my treasure down here!
Yes. You can have it.
Tap, tap... tap...
End of the line, hypnotist!
--Hurry! Hurry!
--No.
What?!
Yaay! Yaay! Yaaaaay!
I just had an idea!
I leave Kuina's spirit
and dreams... with you.
No! I don't wanna toss it down!
--What is it?!
Don't get cocky!
What nonsense is this?!
Quit joking around!
They were certainly pleasant people...
Yeah! That treasure belongs
to Gaimon-san! Toss it all down!
--Merry...
--Yes?
Darn it! We failed!
Lying hurts...
You made a mockery of me.
But I am a pirate...
Are you referring to Klahadore?
No...
Quit clowning around, you!
--Onion!
You mean how you really wanted
to stop Usopp-kun from going?
You pretend pirates have
interfered a bit too much...
It's all right.
--It doesn't matter anymore.
--Of course it does!
Yeah! You've guarded that
treasure for 20 years, Gaimon-san!
Miss, the villagers once told
me a story from his childhood.
Where are you hiding, Miss?!
I'll start by executing these three.
Straw Hat. You're...
Waiter!
...a great guy!
You can reflect on your foolishness
to meddle in a real pirate fight
Hmm?
Shortly after Usopp-kun's
father left the village,
What do you mean?
in the next life.
I had a slight inkling
that might be the case...
his mother passed away.
Didn't I tell you that I'm not a waiter?
I tried to avoid
thinking about it, but...
Pirates are here!!
But my, how beautiful you are!
They're empty, aren't they?
There you are.
Pirates are here!
Eight years since then...
Say, Miss, would you like to have
some wine with me over there?
Yeah. They're all empty.
Dad's pirates are here!
--No!
--Run, Kaya-san!
H-Hold on, Usopp!
You mustn't shout!
You're finally going to set out, then?
That's terrible... The treasure
he guarded for 20 years
Run!
Hmm?
Yes, Sensei.
Hey! Do you serve soup
with bugs in it to customers?!
Dad came back for us!
was just empty boxes...
--Hey!
--Yeah! That's them!
To fulfill our promise.
It happens all the time with
treasures that have treasure maps...
D-Don't be silly... Usopp...
They're the other way?!
Bugs?
What the hell is this bug?!
Please stop this!
You go to look, but
someone's already stolen it.
But he said he'd take us with
him when you get better, Mom!
Leave them alone! I'll write my will!
Hmph! This will make this
restaurant's reputation drop sharply.
That's how much of an ordeal
treasure-hunting is for pirates.
N-No!
I'm sorry, sir, but I don't know...
You'll be killed if you write it, Kaya-san!
Your father won't be coming back...
You can wait all your life, or lose
your life, and never touch treasure...
...since I don't know much about insects.
Zoro!
But... I'm proud I married him...
There are more pirates like
that than you can count!
I'm sorry...
Take care.
Fool. Don't try to make a deal with me.
Don't be so upset, old guy!
T-There's a legendary medicine!
It can cure any sickness!
It's a good thing we
came after 20 years!
Captain Kuro told me
to get rid of everyone.
Huh? That was way off!
30 years later and you
might've been dead!
You're so silly... You dream too much...
You can't be serious!
What are you guys doing?!
Straw Hat...
Cannon practice!
Don't mess with me!!
I don't care if I'm silly!
I do dream! I am the son of a pirate!
--Luffy...
--He's...
But they sure don't fly good!
You've made this much
of a fool of yourself!
I'm telling you, let me try!
All you got left now is the One Piece!
If you don't do as I say,
then you won't get to kill me!
Judging from the last flying distance...
Come be a pirate again with us!
Grow up to be a brave
man like your father...
This should do it.
You're... inviting me?!
I won't write my will, either!
Fire!
H-Hold on! Don't act hasty!
Awesome! You hit it on your first try!
No one's even tried to talk to me
before when they saw me like this!
I absolutely must get
you to write that will!
I really hit it...
You could've eaten it if you
took that bug out, couldn't you?
Whadya think?! I'm awesome when
it comes to aiming! Impressed?!
K-Kaya-san!
How many years it's been
since I trusted someone!
Pirates are here!
Yeah! Yeah!
It took three full days to
cook it, skimming the scum...
It's settled! You're our sniper!
Alright! I'll let the brats go!
Perhaps out of his loneliness,
What?! I don't get to be captain?!
he continued to shout it out
after his mother's death.
Though they're really
in no condition to run...
I'm the captain!
Aren't you acting a bit
too big for your britches?
Thank you...
In the hopes that one day his father's
pirate ship would be at the shore,
Well, whatever! I'll humor you for now!
But if you do anything too cowardly,
I'm taking over immediately!
I'm a customer! I'm paying you!
in the hopes that one day
he would come back for him...
Yeah, that's fine.
But anyways, I was thinking, there's
one other position we need to fill
Here!
Please stop, Fullbody-san!
Shut up!
before going into the Grand Line!
You're really gonna stay
on this island, old guy?
Don't forget to sign your name!
F-Fullbody-san...
The villagers say that lie
of his also contains his wish.
Yeah! We have a fancy kitchen, too!
If you pay me, I can do it!
I know...
Yeah, Straw Hat.
Even if there is no treasure,
Can money... satisfy your hunger?
there's something else I want to protect.
An important necessity
for long trips, right?
Pirates!
D-Darn it...
What'd you say?
Yeah! All pirate ships need one, huh?!
--Eh?
--Something you want to protect?
I'm asking, "Can it...
satisfy your hunger?!"
As someone who lost his
own parents in this village,
A musician!
"I leave my entire fortune
to Klahadore, my butler..."
I've shared hard times and happy
times with these guys for 20 years.
Are you an idiot?!
he probably couldn't ignore you,
seeing as the same happened to you.
What do you see voyages as?!
Excellent! This is your will, all right!
I can't leave them now.
Just when it seemed you were
gonna say something smart...
That saved me the trouble
of hypnotizing you!
You will need to grow
stronger now, too!
But pirates sing, you know!
No!
No! No!
You promise not to kill them, right?
To live up to everything
he's done until today!
Don't think that you can survive in
this world by repeating "No," kid.
Come out, you damn pirates!
Now that I know there's no treasure,
I somehow finally feel free.
Don't worry.
What the... What the... Who are you?!
Yes!
I may not look like it, but I'm
known for being an honest man.
I think I can really
live a life I want now.
Shut up! Who I am
doesn't amount to crap!
No!
Plus, I've actually grown
a bit fond of being in this box!
So candid...
Cheers to our new ship and crewmate!
--Kaya-san!
Oh! That's too bad, then!
You're a neat old guy, too!
How many are there?
There they are!
One... I think?
--There they are! There they are! Stop!
--Ouch, ouch! I've been cut there, you know!
So the weird creatures
are your true friends...
Then leave it to him.
They said they were
fighting to live, not die.
He's the weirdest creature
of them all, though!
"Sea" Then leave it to him.
Over there!
"Sea"
We've taken the heads of many a pirate!
Say what?!
F-Fullbody-san...
--Alright, I'll be back!
--Hey!
"Sea"
Are you nameless pirate
wannabes trying to kill my partner?!
Usopp-san's lies always
spoke about the joy of living.
Sanji...
Are you nameless pirate
wannabes trying to kill my partner?!
That's far enough, hypno-freak!
Sous Chef!
Hmm?
They cheered me up
and told me to live!
That voice...
He followed me here?!
What do you mean, "partner"?!
A fight?
Indeed.
I dunno what's going on,
but stop breaking our ship!
See ya! Take care!
Here we go!
Are we really gonna do this?!
Bye!
You bet! We're following
in our captain's footsteps!
Looks like I better finish this quickly!
L-Lost by a hair...
Straw Hat...
--Ready...
Don't... waste food.
Strive for your dream, for me.
What's going on?
Hey! Is that you, Johnny?!
--Pirates are here!
You, if anyone, will surely get
At sea, provoking a cook is
Who's saying my name all familiar-like?!
the legendary treasure,
the One Piece!
the same as committing suicide.
Remember that.
You know what, Merry?
I'm going to be a doctor!
And then... buy the world!
B-Big Bro Zoro?!
It is you, Johnny!
What are you doing here, Big Bro?!
That's a wonderful goal to have!
Where's Yosaku? Isn't he with you?
What now? What now?
You guys know each other?
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Hey, Zoro. When did you start
using the Three-Sword Style?
Hey! This island gives me
the creeps! Let's go back!
I wonder if Luffy's working hard.
I guess we need a cook, huh?
All finished here! The rest is up to you!
They say there's a "Sea Restaurant."
I bet he's causing trouble.
Oh, it--
Treasure-hunting, huh?!
That sounds exciting!
I won't lose to someone who ditches
his name and runs from the sea!
You're so dumb! Zoro would
never tell anyone about himself!
--A navy ship's firing its cannons!
--Alright! Leave it to me!
Yeah, he doesn't seem a helpful hand.
Watch out! There's something here!
Remember my name for
the rest of your life!
The restaurant's that way, you idiot!
--Actually...
--One sword is different
from the others, right?
What'd you say?! That's not nice!
--What're you so mad about?
--I hate him! He's wrong!
What's with this guy?!
He's totally suspicious!
I'll go apologize!
Hey, have you found a
cook who might join us?
What's taking so long?!
--He just couldn't get a full set!
--Hey!
Let's check it out and get some food!
Says he's the protective
god of the island!
That's how pirates are.
It's just some ordinary old sword?!
Yeah, I found him! It has to be him!
--Huh?! A fight?!
--What's with him?
That's not what friends are like!
Neat! A scrub brush!
Shut up, you guys!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Famous Cook!
Sanji of the Sea Restaurant"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Unwelcome Customer!
Sanji's Food and Ghin's Debt"
"Anger Explosion!
Kuro vs. Luffy, How it Ends!"
"You're the Weird Creature!
Gaimon and His Strange Friends"
"The Three-Sword Style's Past!
Zoro and Kuina's Vow!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!