A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
"Upper Yard" "Lovely Street"
"Angel Beach"
In pursuit of Nami and the others,
Luffy's group entered the Illusion Forest,
and were greeted with a rigorous
Ball Ordeal by the Priest Satori.
Say... This ground...
With Wyper leading the charge, the Shandians
Having entered Upper Yard's Illusion Forest,
--It's dirt.
--Eh? Oh, right!
take the fight to Upper Yard,
taking advantage of the fact
Impact!
Sky islands are made out of island cloud...
Luffy and the others faced the rigorous
"Ball Ordeal" of Priest Satori.
that the priests' eyes are focused on Gan Fall.
Why is this island different?
No matter what, head for "God's Shrine"!
Looks like checking into it
might be worth a lot...
Don't fear Eneru!
Meanwhile, Gan Fall is defeated by Priest Shura.
Sanji!
The Great Warrior Calgara is
our one and only Preserver!
This is the Illusion Forest Ball Ordeal,
with a 10% survival rate!
Life is suffering.
Sky Knight!!
You're still alive? Impressive indeed!
Now, for the other two!
Yeah!!
You'd better hurry before the boat
goes deeper into the Illusion Forest!
Well, then, as a reward, I'll give
you my prized finishing blow!
'Kay, let's do this! Center of the ship!
Hey, Nami! See anything?!
So you've come, Shandians!
Hey! We gotta go after the boat
before we lose sight of it!
I'll put it on the main mast,
so if anyone's in trouble,
This means you declare war on God Eneru!
Meanwhile, Chopper, who was looking
after the ship alone on the sacrificial altar,
they can get the whistle from here and blow it!
After defeating Satori, Luffy and the
other two headed for the sacrificial altar.
I'm gonna take care of the ball guy!
Now it's fair!
Shut your mouth! Or the flavor will escape.
was attacked by Shura, one of the four priests.
Don't do anything reckless!
He's got some weird powers!
This is... a love ordeal!
The wounded Gan Fall,
and drowning Chopper...
A-All right! Good thing this was here!
--We'll come back once we stop the boat!
--Right! Gum-Gum...
Is this guy an idiot, too?!
Believe it or not, the one who rescued them
was a bird that was also found in Jaya.
...Pistol!
Huh? You're the only sacrifice I get to kill?
No!
Concasser!
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
Offer your life... to God!
"Light the Fire of Shandora! Wyper, the Warrior"
Again!
There's a bunch of South Birds... But why...
N-No!!
Gan Fall, the former God, went into Upper Yard.
Why are they this huge?!
Die!
"Chopper in Danger!
Former God vs. Priest Shura"
I doubt Eneru'd leave him alone.
So you're the ones that saved us?!
Dammit! Can't see from down here!
Is Gan Fall trying to fight Eneru?
Sorry to have kept you waiting!
What?! He's God?!
Sky Knight!!
No way... It's hard to think
that he'd be that determined.
Watch yourself, Luffy!
These priests are no ordinary people!
You probably came here knowing this, but...
Around that time, Nami, Zoro and Robin,
who reached the seashore,
Let's find the boat ASAP
and get the hell outta here!
...you're already a criminal!
discovered the shocking
secret behind Upper Yard.
What do you think? Don't they look amazing?
Ahh, I'll show you what I do
to aggravating fools like you!!
"The Ordeal of Spheres!
Desperate Struggle in the Lost Forest"
This is the other half of the island that
was ripped up. This was part of Jaya!
Huh?
This year's pumpkins are very good.
"Knight"
The "city of gold" that once existed
on the ground and was seen by Noland...
String Ordeal!
What's the matter, Aisa?
Yes...
I don't know what to say
to express my gratitude.
...didn't sink into the ocean.
--Two voices disappeared.
--What'd you say?!
Don't be in such a rush! Stay for a while!
Hm? Is that your Mantra?
I'm sorry. Now I am staying with you, as well.
"Profound Mystery!
Ordeal of String and Ordeal of Love?!"
For 400 years... this part of Jaya has been...
Yeah... Just now...
If they decide that your daughter
let those straw hat fellows escape,
...flying in the sky all this time!
Your Mantra is saying so, Aisa?
they'll consider you an accomplice.
So you'll be in danger as well.
"Jaya, City of Gold in the Sky!
Head for God's Shrine!"
You can't hear two voices
anymore... Is that true?!
This time is on the house...
Now then, where are the other two?
I won't let a single one escape!
Eneru's Mantra does not reach this far.
There's no mistake about it.
You all know that since she
was born, she can use Mantra,
a mysterious power, which enables her
to sense people from even far away.
How are things on Angel Island?
Here we are!
Ah! That's...!
Yes?
Come out! Ball Dragon!
I'm referring to crops.
How are this year's crops coming?
So you can't hear two people's voices anymore?
Oh, it's just a bunch of
surprise clouds put together.
Yes... They disappeared
around the same time...
Hey! You see it, Usopp?!
Yes, I hear they're coming along quite well.
I think it's Gan Fall and one of the priests...
Is that right? I'm glad to hear that.
Are we supposed to be surprised by that?
This is juice made from the
pumpkins that I grew in my field.
--Killed each other simultaneously?
--Well done, old man.
I'll have you know, it's made up of surprise
clouds containing explosives or sharp objects.
Now there are three priests left.
It tastes good.
This works in our favor.
Yes. I'm sorry. Thank you.
Looks like Heaven has answered our prayers.
--Found it!
--Gimme directions!
What?! Then that means...!
Straight ahead! Climb up
the tree after the next one!
Conis-san, have some, too.
You touch the fire-bomb ball
somewhere on its body and it's over.
Yahoo! Thank you, God!
This is our chance to crush the priests.
You can jump onto it from the branches!
One explosion will cause another,
Got it!
Yeah!
and its gigantic body will
instantly cause a huge explosion!
I can't believe that the sky island we reached
after all this trouble was the city of gold!
We'll launch a full-scale attack
on Upper Yard immediately!
Young lady, are you aware that there are
those called pirates in the Blue Sea?
Surprise Balls! Go, Ball Dragon!
Yeah!!
This must be a reward for
behaving myself, right, God?
You've never been comfortable
around Wyper, have you?
No.
Gum-Gum... Pistol!!
Hey, I thought you were
scared of this island's God?!
They are criminals who travel on the blue sea.
--Now, out of my way.
--Ow!
No! Wait, Luffy!!
Hm? God? Oh, what's the big deal?
Their ships all fly a black flag with a skull on it,
although each pirate's flag is different.
Yikes! It's him! What's he up to?!
--Hey, Laki, wait!
--What is it?
Is he worth more than gold?
Go!
The priest wasn't defeated by Gan Fall.
But, you just said, "Thank you, God!"
Look out, Sanji! There's a ball headed your way!
Whatever you do, don't touch that thing!!
There're other people there, and they did it.
If you lay even one finger on it,
She's not making any sense!
What?! What's Luffy doing?!
Those straw hat fellows
are probably pirates, too.
we'll be blown to bits!
Other people?
You mean the Blue Sea people
who entered Skypiea?
How are we gonna fight it if we can't touch it?!
My word! Are you saying that
they were already criminals?!
I don't know, but they're definitely scary!
Exactly! Forget about fighting that thing!
So...
Our only option is to run!
Well... It is probably true that they
do not live by the rules of the Blue Sea.
Surprise Billiard!
...be careful.
In any society, there are always
those who don't blend in.
Okay... Aisa, give me your bag.
Usopp!
So we just keep running?!
Right now, how are you any different?
He was aiming for me!
How should I know?!
What?! No! This is my secret bag
and I have my treasure in it!
It's useless.
Here it comes!! Jump!!
Who can say for certain that society is right
and that those who don't blend in are wrong?
I know.
It's gonna explode!
"Pop"?!
I'll get some for you, too.
Sometimes it's not so clear-cut.
Why'd we hafta land here?!
A dud...
--Really?!
--Yeah.
To put it in extreme terms, a "hero" in wartime
is simply a killer if he lives in a different time.
You're quite the stubborn ones.
Idiot!
He's finally stopped his blabbering.
I also have a pirate friend.
It's the same result either way!
Bastard! Mocking us with
a bunch of stupid tricks...
But if you died before you
experienced the power of Ball Dragon...
What's with these guys?
How'd he know our attacks and stuff?
He came here when I was still
God over twenty years ago.
Hey!!
Hey, what is this place?!
He was quite the big-hearted
and pleasant fellow.
...it wouldn't be fun!
Luffy! Sanji! I found the boat!
I'll bet that this is the next ordeal area.
Hurry up! Or it'll leave the forest!
I hated to say goodbye.
Another priest will appear. Be careful!
Hm? Oh, Usopp was okay.
Aw, man... Come on, one ordeal is enough!
Right now, though it doesn't
look it at first glance,
Hey, he's saying the boat's leaving!
Skypiea is a land of endless battles.
Why, you...!
Oh, crap! It's almost on the
route that exits the forest!
What is it gonna be?! String? Iron? Or Swamp?!
A land where battles between
those of us from the sky
Gum-Gum...
It looks like an ordinary grassy plain.
...Gatling!
and Shandians, also known as
guerrillas, rage continuously.
Hey! Hold on to my body!
It's not ordinary! Open your
eyes and take a good look!
--To your body?!
--Here goes!
Those sticks all have skulls on them!
Usopp Aa-aa-aa!
The Shandians are still challenging Eneru.
Stop, Luffy! Don't hit those balls randomly!
Your attempt to coexist with the
Shandians when you were God
Aisa!
Oh, you're right! What the heck?!
Where have you been?
All right! I got it!
offered hope that the several-hundred-year war
What the--?! What the--?! What the--?!
Ah! Kamakiri!
Yahoo! You're the man, Usopp!
Upper Yard again? That's
Vearth in your bag, isn't it?
Another one of those monstrous
priests is gonna show up?!
Oh, no! Too late!
would end in peace.
Ouch! That hurt! Are you trying to kill me?!
Yes... I was very close to succeeding,
I'm excited! I wonder what kinda ordeal it'll be?
Look out! They're coming from all directions!
--Just got a little carried away!
--Man, you threw my back out!
Are you nuts?! If the priests win, we'll
end up like the heads on those sticks.
Don't go there too often...
but my status as God was taken away by Eneru.
Whoa! You can fix it that easy?
You people are fun!
Nothing is impossible for me.
...or you'll lose your life.
There's no doubt about it!
I'm sorry. Everything went
down the drain because of that.
You can be pretty cool sometimes!
Yeah! You underestimated me, didn't you?!
Don't worry! We're not gonna lose!
Bahhhh! Don't tell me what to do!
Wh-What're you saying?!
There's no need to apologize.
Huh?
Huh? Huh? Hey! Hey, hey!
You haven't even been able to beat Eneru yet!
Something's coming this way.
H-H-H-Hold on a second!
What're you doing?! Hey, let me go!
What?! Iron, String, Swamp...
Are they all coming together?!
Spears! Crab!
Oh, Sanji-kun. If we're gonna
die, let's go together.
In Skypiea, there is this legend
passed down from long ago.
M-Me, too?!
That would save us a lot of time.
That damn brat!
Four at once!
Long ago, on the day that Upper Yard,
the sacred ground, was born,
--A chance?
--That's right.
Ahhh! Here they come!!
For some reason, Gan Fall entered Upper Yard.
the island's beautiful singing
voice enveloped Skypiea.
That old geezer thinks that he can
settle everything in Skypiea peacefully.
No biggie...
What the--? Another dud?
Or should I say, I hit the jackpot?
I'll get you for this!
That's when the battle between the
Shandians and those from the sky began...
It would've been better if I stretched myself.
He's got it all wrong.
You dirtbags! Gum-Gum...
...as if that voice was a cue.
Win or lose... Those are the
only two outcomes in a battle.
I freaked out for nothing!
In any case, we're now getting
out of the Illusion Forest.
So, when we hear the "island's singing voice,"
...Balloon!!
Huh? You want me to sing, too?
Okay! Listen in awe to the one
known as the Singing Pirate!
the legend says that this battle will end.
The Great Warrior Calgara said,
"Light the fire of Shandora."
"Wyper Shandian
(a warrior of Shandora)"
The island's singing voice?
What was that?!
We'll follow those words.
Paramythia! He probably has the
power of the Super-Power Devil Fruit.
Here goes!
That's right.
It doesn't matter who we have to fight--
the former God Gan Fall, or Eneru.
The sacred ground will sing again...
Hey! I haven't sung yet!
Oh, yeah... I can't swim.
Wyper, are we gonna fight them?!
...someday, for sure.
So long as they reign as "God,"
No, don't bother!
no matter what their differences are,
That guy...!
Sky Knight!
to us they're the same!
Oww! Hot! Oww!
Hey, you! What're you doing?!
You ready to take us on?! You bastards!
That weird bird, too.
They all have to be eliminated!
Water! Water! Water!
Oh yeah, he has a Devil
Fruit power, just like I do.
Oww! Hot! Oww! Oww!
--Wyper.
--Hm?
So you were the Blue Sea
people acting up in Skypiea...
A rebel against Eneru
appeared on Angel Island.
Dammit! I couldn't... save them.
River!
I heard it's a young woman.
It's been six years since Eneru started reigning,
What's the matter?
Hey, Luffy. That guy's the masked
guerrilla that we saw on the White Sea!
Oww!
and this is the first time.
Please look after this place. I've got a job.
So what?
What's wrong with you?
Let's go, Pierre!
Since Gan Fall saved her from judgment,
He's running on the clouds!
Eneru now has a reason to
judge even the former God.
Oh, no... I feel... faint.
Hey, stop! What do you want?!
I went through!
--To eliminate you!
--Looks like he wants to fight.
Gan Fall has never harmed any of us,
Luffy! Don't fall into the river below!
There might not be a bottom!
--Fine by me!
--What's going on?!
So, Satori has fallen.
not only as the Sky Knight,
but also as the former God...
What a novice, disturbing his Mantra!
Eh?!
They're scary! Sky islands are scary!
If I'm not mistaken, the illegal
entrants this time are Blue Sea people.
...nor has he tried to directly
confront Eneru, either.
If you don't want to die, go back
to the Blue Sea immediately!
It seems they're no ordinary people.
That very man finally stepped into Upper Yard.
The sacrifices are moving about freely as well.
If you've got any funny ideas about
doing something on this island...
Yikes!
However, even if we leave them alone for now,
And if he and one of the priests
kill each other, that'd be great.
they probably won't find a way off of this island.
...we'll eliminate you along with Eneru.
Or do you mean to say that
Gan Fall is no longer our enemy?
More importantly, we have to...
So they're trying to kill Eneru?
"Skypiea Priest
Sky Punk Gedatsu"
Then does that mean the
guerrillas and God are different?
When men have a common enemy,
they get deluded into thinking
that the one next to them is an ally.
They're not priests?
Then let's leave them alone,
Are you stupid?!
Usopp Hammer! Usopp Hammer!
Usopp Hammer!
and get through here quickly, Luffy!
Do you sense the voice of
a sorrowful warrior, Holy?
If you have doubts,
then stay out of the fight, Laki!
Rubber Band! Usopp Hammer!
What'd you say, you dirtbag?!
C'mon! I'll beat you up!!
No matter how many times we fight,
the result is always the same.
Father, what tasty pumpkin juice this is!
You'll only be in our way!
Shura defeated Gan Fall,
but the "Ball Ordeal" was broken.
Ahh! Stop it! Please stop!
Yes... I'm really glad...
I'm coming over there, so stay put!!
Aisa!
What a turbulent day today is!
...that you can enjoy it.
I'll pay you back for earlier with interest!!
Yahoo!
What?! I didn't go to Upper Yard!
I won't let them through here. It's insolent
for them to even try to see God.
Don't go into the tent yet.
Although the sun will soon set,
I told you, "Go back."
Yahoo!
it seems that Upper Yard will now become...
Wyper, or rather, the man descended
from the Great Warrior Calgara, is angry.
Whether or not you have the
ability to go back is another story.
"God"
"Skypiea Priest Sky Breeder Ohm"
Oh! I didn't think of that!
Now I can finally try it out!
...a little rattled.
"Skypiea Priest Sky Rider Shura"
Yeah, that's scary.
I don't care about the escapees anymore.
Now, offer your life to God Eneru!
It seems some opponents who
should face my anger have appeared.
Got any ideas, Usopp?!
He's scarier than God.
What's their story?
Well, we learned that they're enemies
with God Eneru and us as well.
I sure do! I'm known as
the greatest pirate inventor!
Help... them?
Us?
I'll show ya my latest weapon!
Dammit...! What's with this island?
Yes, that's right.
Fire...!
Usopp Aa-aa-aa!
Let's try to create a way for
them to escape somehow.
We're gonna move on.
Why do you struggle?
There's no way that you can escape death!
My "Can't Go into Jungles" disease is...
--Uhh, what?
--Just watch!
Oh, I'm hungry.
Die gracefully!
How could you be hungry? I've had it!
What?!
There it is! On the river straight ahead!
Oh yeah, Luffy, let's sing Sanji's
song to bring our spirits up!
Listen up, everyone!
I can make it! Set up!
# Take my hand... #
Upper Yard is rattled right now!
No, it goes like this!
This is the opportunity of a lifetime!
--The ship is...!
--Hmph! So he's gonna get big...
No matter what, head for "God's Shrine"!
I can't tell what they're doing... Amazing!
Don't fear Eneru!
The Great Warrior Calgara is
our one and only Preserver!
What is he up to?
I no longer think that I can
negotiate with your group!
Darn it! Come on!
Yeah!!
I'll cover you!
Ha! You're as soft as ever!
Alright! Now it's just a
straight line to the Crow!
Hey, hey! Why do you care when there
won't be anyone to get on board?!
--Braham!
--Yeah!
Save our comrade!
Kamakiri!
If it goes any further in,
we won't be able to get it!
--Genbou!
--Yeah!
What is this fight?
Now!
You and your friends cannot escape death.
I can't let this chance go!
--Laki!
--Yeah!
Come back safely! We're splitting up here!
Wow, not too shabby! Watch out for the balls!
Who the hell are you?!
Stop it! Don't harm them!
I ain't gonna screw up!
You can call me King of the Jungle!
Heaven's Judgment...
We vow to the Great Warrior Calgara
to light the fire of Shandora!!
Then... offer your life instead!
Here goes!
That young woman did something foolish.
Usopp Aa-aa-aa!
Yeah!!
We are never to... anger God Eneru.
No!
So you've come, Shandians!
Something's gonna happen!
Something's definitely gonna happen!
There's no way that we can
get through this safely!
Don't tell me... this island is...?!
Stop it! Stop it!
We've got zoro, er, zero chance... zoro...
Here goes!
Don't harm the ship! Just don't harm the ship!
Usopp Aa-aa-aa!
I wonder how Zoro's doing.
Please come back...
Alright! Go!
...God!
Dammit!
I got you.
What was that?!
Yes! Perfect! Get on board and stop the boat!
Is something wrong, Gan Fall?!
It's an explosion.
What did you do?!
I heard some earlier,
but this one seems different.
Why...?! Why can't we move?!
You won't need the answer...
More importantly, we have to move on!
...when you're dead!
Umph! What's the big rush, Nami?!
We've come quite a ways, haven't we, Sanji?
You've been acting strange. What did you see?
You bastard!
Haven't we, Sanji?!
Did you see God or something?
What're you doing?! Get on already!
Yeah, and that grassy plain
earlier turned out to be nothing.
You bastard! Stop it already!
No, that's not it!
Yeah... about that...
Even if I explain,
you probably can't understand...
I-I'm in charge of this ship!
Now that we've come this far,
I hope we can keep on going safely.
I forgot that the rope is attached
to the belt, so I can't get down...!
They asked me to look after it.
Yeah! We can! We definitely can!
Profound mystery... String Ordeal!
Dammit! I keep slipping! Why is
it so hard to walk around here?!
What is it this time?! What the heck?
You can enter Upper Yard, but you have to
face difficult ordeals from us, the four priests!
Well, what should we do, Fuza?
You're the one who said
this way would be faster.
Look, Usopp!
"Thirty-foot Bird Fuza"
Just spit it out already! Just what did you see?!
This is fun!
Don't think they can be beaten so easily!
Crap! Crap! Crap!
He says not to harm his friends.
Is there any point in winding the canal?
No questions. Just follow me!
He says not to damage the ship.
We have to get to the seashore somehow.
He says he doesn't want to die.
God Eneru is...
Hey! Give me a hand!!
I'm getting dizzy!
What a dilemma.
Shouldn't you be the one in front
if you want us to follow you?!
...someone who is glorious and distant.
"Skypiea Priest Sky Rider Shura"
Such a damned selfish animal!
--Seashore?
--That's right.
He really irks me!
In any case, we have to get
close to it to check it out...
--This is fast!
--Or rather, we're falling!!
Yahoo! Hey, Usopp!
You seem to be havin' fun, too!
That's right. The sacred
ground will sing again...
...because I still can't believe my own eyes.
...someday, for sure...
I need a word with you two.
--I, too...
--Hm?
Sky...
I, too, have something
that's been bugging me...
Sky Knight!!
Milky roads are fun!
...although I don't have any proof.
If this theory I dreamed up
turns out to be true...
Oh... I feel sick.
Got it? I'll forget what just
happened, so do as I say!
Gan Fall...
...it'd be interesting. It'd be interesting.
--Yes! I'm sorry!
--I'm sorry...
Maybe my goal in life is still attainable.
Forget about the boat for right now.
All three of us are gonna attack him at once!
It's only a theory, though.
I don't care if he is a priest;
if we all attack at once,
I've gotta save him. I've gotta save him!
There're skysharks here!
we should be able to find a way to beat him!
The Sky Knight'll be eaten by them!
Hey, we've come really far.
Beat me?!
Ha! Think of it as Eneru-sama's anger!
I wonder if it'll be like this
the rest of the way to the altar.
B-But how can I save him?
The sun will set soon.
Oh?
I can't swim... and I'll be
eaten by the skysharks, too.
I'm alive?
Where'd he go?!
I can't see the sunset because of the clouds.
He says not to harm his friends.
Ouch!!
So they have twilight on the sky island, too.
He says not to damage the ship.
He says he doesn't want to die.
Sky Knight!
Doctor! Doctor! Oh, that's me!
Hey, Nami! Get a move on!
What a dilemma.
Such a damned selfish animal!
Impact!
Shut up! Don't talk to me right now!
He really irks me!
Good... He's still alive.
If you want to live so much,
then why are you so weak?!
What'll you do if I fall?!
Sanji!
Wyper! Kamakiri and I will fight here!
Damn you!
But this is strange.
Help them over there!
Got it!
I thought we sank in the river.
I wonder who pulled us out.
Life is suffering...
Sky Knight?! Hah! You were forced out
from your position as God, you old fool!
Now, for the other two!
Hm?! Who is it? He said God...
--In the end, you were no
match for us, the priests.
--Ahhhhh!
Who just spoke?!
Sky Knight!!
Hey! Are you all right?!
Yeah...
Ha! You're a Zoan, aren't you?!
Chopper!
...somehow...
Where are you?!
What? What? What?!
Are you stupid? You can't even swim!
What happened, Chopper?! Say something!
What?!
My apologies... for troubling you so often.
Hey, the Merry's mast is gone.
No problem.
Why...?
What kind of changes did he make?
Oh, yeah, you're a Zoan, too.
--We're close to the sea.
--Hm?
You can't be serious! The ship was attacked!
I can hear waves now. Listen...
How inconvenient...
Chopper! I'm sorry it took so long!
What's wrong? Did you see God or something?
It's safe now to come out!
You're there, aren't you?!
Why don't you follow your master?!
You're right! We're almost there!
No... a well.
Stop hiding and say something, Chopper!
A well?
--Now, let's go! Hurry up!
--Like I said, what's there?
I wonder if he was torn limb from limb.
The ship... your friends... and yourself...
Stop saying scary things!
Have you lost it?
Ahh, how absurd!
I hear noises mixed in with the waves as well.
You don't want to lose any of those?
I can't stand how weak they all are.
Hey, Chopper! Are you there?!
Did something happen?!
Yeah, sounds just like a battle.
If this was a bottomless river,
there'd still have been some hope.
Say something!
If you want to live so much,
then why are you so weak?!
But unfortunately,
this river does have a bottom.
No--
Stop it! That spear burns things!
The sound of many people charging...
No--
Let's see... I wonder if those three
escapees have already been hunted.
Nothing scary happened!
Thanks!
I heard enough of that in Alabasta.
I wonder if things are all right.
Okay, okay... You're strong.
If you mean Chopper, don't worry about him.
Is that well that strange?
Stop it!
So tell us everything that happened.
When push comes to shove,
he can take care of himself.
Dammit!
Yes. It's unbelievable that a well
would be stuck underneath a tree.
--No, I meant our captain and the others.
--Luffy?
You creep!
The balance between civilization
and nature here is off.
I doubt he'd just sit by after we got kidnapped.
Wha...?!
Are you trying to live...
without sacrificing anything?
Well, in any case, unless we come up
with a way to cross this cloud river,
Yeah, he wanted to come to
this island to begin with.
Whoa! We're going up
another tree! This is a big one!
I don't know what this God person is up to,
--Hey, did something move over there?
--Dunno.
we can't walk around this forest.
What is this guy?
but he probably wouldn't
just let them through.
It's as if he can predict my moves.
Hey, this is no time for idle chit-chat, Luffy!
And now, a totally different fight is going on.
Say, did you see anything, Robin?
We're far from meeting God.
The civilization couldn't
estimate the growth of this tree.
What is this? What's this feeling?
No, nothing at all...
The situation has gotten a bit complicated.
For someone to live, another must die.
Don't you think there's gonna
be something at the end?
You sure it wasn't just a monkey?
Yeah, it certainly has.
I've never seen a case like this before.
But, well, they're probably okay, since
they're used to being in all sorts of trouble.
A monkey? I guess so...
The priests might be waiting in surprise
for us at the end of the milky road.
Hey, Nami! Can you see
anything from up there?!
That's how life is.
Getting worked up over little
stuff like this gets us nowhere.
Say. Do you think we should
check out the other shore after all?
This thing is so tall! I'm so excited!
You're right.
No way! What if we get
attacked by sharks again?!
Did you know that this is a sacrificial altar?
Ahhh... Ouch...
The island where God lives... Upper Yard...
Geez! You're hopeless...
Y-Yeah! I heard something like that.
Are we gonna spin around again?!
It's true. The rest of your group
is desperately trying to get here.
Hm? There're something there.
Hey! Say something! Did you find God?!
There they are! Are they priests?!
I can't get near it like this...
No, they're skysharks!
Oh, just skysharks, not priests.
I promised Zoro I would fix the ship...
Hey, Nami! Hey!
I wonder if she saw something.
There are four separate areas
that we, the priests, govern.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, seriously?!
Alright! I'll do my best, too!
Ahhh! They're huge!
We're gonna be swallowed!
"Swamp" "Iron" "String" "Ball"
This is how you gotta do it, Usopp.
Alright. Hey! It's about time you woke up!
This island... Can't be...!
The rule is that when the
targets are in one area,
Just don't let them notice you!
Gently... Gently...
Gum-Gum...
Hm? Is it morning already?
the other priests aren't supposed
to do anything to the targets.
Gently... Gently...
But this sacrificial altar doesn't
belong to any of those areas.
You're pretty much dead.
Hurry up and rest in peace.
"Swamp" "Iron" "String" "Ball"
"Sacrificial Altar"
That's just like Zoro!
...Gatling!!
Pay attention, you idiots!
I'm a priest. There's no way you can win.
In other words, it's a free area.
We don't even know what's going on
with Nami-san and Robin-chan.
So it doesn't matter who
strikes the ones at the altar.
I did it! Now I can fix the ship!
Uhm, and Zoro and Chopper...?
I-I can't go on anymore!
My heart can't take any more surprises.
There're three more priests.
But it should be after those who're
receiving the ordeal in some area die.
There may be other ordeals waiting for us.
We're soaking wet!
Soon, you'll be out of options.
This is... a love ordeal.
Oh! Hey, look!
We found it! The Going Merry! That's the altar!
Your boat has nearly reached this forest's exit.
What?! Then, Luffy and the others are...?!
In any case, we have no choice
but to get to the altar quickly.
Don't freak out. My coming here doesn't
mean your friends' death... unfortunately...
When that happens, it's all over!
--Yahoo!
--Ahhh! Nami-san! Robin-chan!
--What do you say?!
--Yes, I'm sorry.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
So long as you can't fly like birds,
I've overcome the love ordeal to come here!
I came here for a different reason.
you won't be able to get out of here.
I wonder what made her suddenly take off.
Aw, was that it? That was the ordeal?
What?! A different reason...?
Geez, she got all energetic
as soon as she saw the sea.
Were you guys scared?!
Ah, but does that mean we can also
get out of here if Luffy and the others
You'll wander around in this
forest and die of exhaustion!
Now that Captain Usopp is here, you'll be safe!
So I really did see it!
come to rescue us?!
Looks like they're okay, too.
Yeah, that's right...
Phew, I'm relieved.
This is...!
That won't...
Hey, Nami! That's enough.
It's about time to tell us...
...if you can get out of this free area.
...happen!!
It will!
What...?
Surprise Balls!
But, hold that thought.
There's no need to explain,
is there? Look at this.
The reason I came here is because,
although those are the normal judgment rules,
Ball Dragon!
Now, it's show time!
The mast is... gone...
You recognize this, right?
U-Uhm... Usopp... I'm sorry.
I fought really hard...
Which one is the fire-bomb ball?
when there's an exceptional situation,
the rules change a little.
It's not actually even a
matter of recognizing it...
Touch it, and there'll be an
astonishingly huge explosion!
Exceptional...
The whistle...!
Yes. For example, when three of the sacrifices
...since we were looking
at it until this morning.
...but a lot of things got burned.
Are your wounds okay?!
escaped to the forest over there
without permission using vines...
What?
Good, now's the time. We can still make it!
What's going on?!
One blow of this One Whistle...
Yes.
Why is something from the ground
up here? It's the same thing, right?
I'll leave things here to you, Luffy!
I see... that's an exceptio...
What a scary guy, using a
spear that can burn things.
--No, it's not.
--What?!
...and I shall come to your aid!
God's on this island, right?
I'm gonna go meet him.
Hm?
I'm glad that it wasn't you that got burned.
This is the other half of the
one we saw on the ground.
Oh? You're gonna climb up that tree to escape?
The other half?!
Normally, I charge five million Extol,
We'll think about the ship later.
It's been bugging me all this time.
Why can he read my mind?!
This ground is something that
shouldn't exist in the White-White Sea.
but I will give you the
One Whistle as a present!
Don't follow me!!
Wait! We still don't know your name!
It was a mystery to me from the start that
this island wasn't made of "island clouds."
Wh-What?!
He's the culprit!
I am Gan Fall, the Sky Knight!
And this is my partner, Pierre!
Oh, I see!
In other words, this island called Upper Yard...
It was controlled by this string.
What's with her, wandering off on her own?
I'll become a more dependable man!!
I'll take care...
May luck be with you, warriors!
...was originally on the ground.
What a selfish woman!
...of this thing!
Hey, Chopper! How did you
get rid of one of the priests?
I thought that house was strange,
I don't think I could take
being called selfish by you.
I can't control Ball Dragon anymore!
because it had a second floor,
but there were no stairs to go up.
So how do we get up there?
I used the whistle.
The Sky Knight came to rescue me.
What impudence!
I know! Let's call that old man and ask!
Huh?!
Just hang on and come to me!!
Because of you, I feel that I've gone through
so many hardships that I wouldn't have had to.
Oh? Where's that weird old guy?
H-H-Hold on, Luffy! This is only
supposed to be used in emergencies!
Also, there wouldn't be any reason
to build a house on a cliff like that.
"God"
Err... really?
That seashore was "a split in the island"!
What if that weird masked
guy shows up again?!
Hey, don't hang on with the other hand, too!
Someone has to die to atone
for the others' crime of escaping.
A... Amazing!!
Idiots! Look closely.
Sacrifice is a fact of life.
Here! I'll hold on to this whistle!
A dreamer, huh? He does seem to be vain.
So he fought this hard, even though
he gave us this whistle for free.
Any objections?!
Especially if they are to come back,
--Yes!
--Yes! Yes! Yes!
--Why?
--What the...?! It's just a board?!
in order that they can more
deeply realize their own fault
If it wasn't for the Sky Knight, both
the ship and I wouldn't have survived.
How can you say that?!
I'm the weakest girl here!
when they see their friend's death...
There're many things we'd like to ask him,
It's only natural that I hold onto this whistle!
This is the other half of the
island that was ripped up.
but we'll wait until he wakes up.
I wanna blow it!
...offer your life... to God!!
You just wanna try it out, Luffy! Forget it!
Thanks to you, too.
This island was part of Jaya!
I wanna call the old man here!
No!!
There it is!!
So I was right! There's no doubt! That's the exit!
Let me hold on to it! I'm the weakest!
Then, the island was split
into two a long time ago,
You wish! I'm the weakest!
Of course! Why didn't I think of this sooner?
Luffy!!
and one half rose into the sky.
What?! Quit screwin' around!
I'm clearly the weakest!
We fell from such a high place.
Die!
Since the ship is in this
state and the sun's setting,
No, I am!
It's natural that the exit is at the same height!
But how could something like this...?
it looks like we won't be able to head
back to Angel Island until tomorrow.
Don't downplay my hopelessness!
Now that I know where the exit is,
the boat rule doesn't matter!
There's a bunch of South Birds... But why...
In any case, let's head to the
forest and camp at the lakeshore.
What a strange argument...
I have to hurry. I'm worried about
that huge explosion earlier.
Why?
The ship will get destroyed if
we have to fight here, right?
Why are they this huge?!
They'd better be okay!
Sorry to have kept you waiting!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
'Kay, let's do this! Center of the ship!
Use your head!
Sky Knight!!
It had to be that monstrous current,
Also, it's probably a little
easier to fight on the shore.
I'll put it on the main mast,
so if anyone's in trouble,
although it may sound silly.
Hmph! Looks like a surprise guest showed up!
they can get the whistle from here and blow it!
--Yay!!
--Yay! Alright! Camping! Party time!
That was close! What an unbelievable idiot!
Now it's fair!
What? Hey, wait! We're in enemy territory!
--Alright.
--Got it.
No, he might've been
determined to take me with him.
So you're the ones that saved us?!
Oh, and none of you are allowed to blow it!
You wanna camp?!
This isn't good. I'm still insufficiently trained!
Alright! Then, let's start by
barbecuing those skysharks!
Gan Fall!!
Huh? But I wanna call the old man...
He took control of the pace for a second!
What?! He's God?!
If I can't stay calm over a little thing like this,
Blow it and I'll kick you
to the ends of the earth!
Sky Knight!!
Yes, we'll be careful.
it'll hinder my Mantra!
You're right!
He is quite good. He is a worthy opponent.
That was close!
Let's get rough with him, Pierre.
Ah! You're still alive?!
A-All right! Good thing this was here!
Ahhh! Get off of me! You idiot!
Yeah, this is yummy!
What's that old previous God doing here?!
Now if anything happens,
the Sky Knight will come save me!
Geez, you'll eat anything.
My name is Montblanc Cricket.
Don't stick to me, you weirdo!
Shall we play with him a little, Fuza?!
Hey, this is pretty good.
I said get off of me, now! You idiot! Idiot!
But the whistle is a last resort!
Quiet! We're in the middle of reports.
Just keep barking!
--Don't let him go, Luffy!
--Get off of me!
Sorry I caused you trouble.
All right! I'm going to work hard
and watch over the ship!
We don't need two Gods on this island!
Don't ever let go of that doughboy!
I thought you were just
more idiots after the gold.
We encountered Satori from the Illusion Forest,
a priest who uses surprise balls.
--You...!
--Oh, Sanji! You're alive?!
Then there's no sky island?!
I almost died because of you!!
I know someone who said there is.
While the surprise balls made
the fight tough, the toughest part
Pay more attention to others!
But he's a legendary liar!
Go!!
Well, in any case, doughboy...
was that he predicted our movements using
a technique called Mantra or something.
No, it's not me!
What's that?
"Noland The Liar"
Noland The Liar...
The priest Shura, who appeared out of
nowhere, uses a spear that burns anything.
"I saw a mountain of gold
on an island in the great sea.
You keep saying "ordeal this," "ordeal that,"
but frankly, it's got nothing to do with us.
Also, he seemed to predict my movements, too.
The courageous king set sail
to see if the story was true.
Although I tried to attack him
many times, he dodged each time.
However, we accept that stupid sky ordeal...
However, what they found
there was just a jungle."
...because two helpless ladies are
waiting for me to come to their rescue.
The bird he was riding blew flames
and burned the main mast.
Huh? You're the only sacrifice I get to kill?
The Sky Knight was defeated, too.
A stupid-looking face is drawn in this book,
In other words, yes...
but he shed many tears
and died a regrettable death.
You guys had a really hard time.
But we discovered that this
island is the other half of Jaya.
...this is... a love ordeal!
He insisted that it had submerged
due to crustal movements,
Is this guy an idiot, too?!
Ahh! I said get off of me!!
The city of gold didn't sink in the ocean,
but it flew up into the sky!
but everyone thought he was
making excuses out of desperation.
Y-You! You! Dammit! Let me go!
This is a duel with the man
who threw a wrench into my life.
Cobblestones...
You guys play dirty, attacking two on one!
We might find more clues if we follow these...
Alright! Well, everyone, thanks for your reports.
That's why you kept diving
until you became sick.
You creeps kidnapped our friends.
Sky... Knight...!!
Based on your reports,
we've learned many things.
It's not that I want to prove his innocence.
Say, what do you think that sound was?
You made a cute angel cry and tried to kill her.
"The bird blows flames!
The spear burns things!"
"The sky island is actually part of Jaya, which we thought sank in the ocean!!"
I want to set the record straight before I die.
However, the biggest discovery is this!
Dunno. Stay right there.
You have no right to say we play dirty.
Believe it or not, this island is the city of gold,
He's right.
This is indeed a man's...
It's amazing that you can
predict our movements.
Let's settle this, Noland!
the one that the Saruyama
Alliance was searching for!!
But even if you can predict them,
Really?!
We need to give him one
more push, Pierre. Let's go!
it doesn't mean anything if
you can't avoid them, does it?
I already said that, didn't I?!
So, what is this Mantra thing?
I-Idiots! Stop it! I'm one of
the priests that serve God!
I don't know. Maybe it's like
an intuition or something.
I'm sick of you things!
Intuition, huh?
Let me go! Hey, are you listening?!
You son of a bitch!
Hey, Chopper! Should I ground more?
Not being judged by a priest is
a 1st degree crime in Skypiea!
Yes. Make it so that he can swallow.
You probably came here knowing this, but...
His digestive tract is a little damaged.
What an unlucky day.
Now listen here! Attacking me means you
declare war on the Almighty God Eneru!
...you're already a criminal!
You gotta be careful.
T-Thanks...
Ahh, I'll show you what I do
to aggravating fools like you!!
Shut your mouth! Or the flavor will escape.
Gold, huh? I've been waiting
for an adventure like this!
I can't wait!
For example, when you want to produce
the supreme mignonnette from pepper...
That's what I wanted to hear!
This simplifies things!
String Ordeal!
Hey, hey, Luffy. Have you forgotten
the guerrilla's warning from earlier?
Usopp!
...the important thing is to, strongly, roughly
God's gonna get angry. He's scary!
and without hesitation, beat it to a pulp.
That sounds fun.
Well, as pirates, we can't back off
when there's treasure close by, can we?
Then, the wonderful flavor
confined inside will be...
--# Take my hand... #
--Don't sing!
We've got enough enemies.
It's gonna be a survival game.
Ahhh! Ahhh! Stop it!
You're still alive?
Sounds fun!
Impressive indeed!
Ahhh! Stop it! Stop it!
You guys... Shouldn't you be
at least a tiny bit afraid of God?!
The "city of gold" that once existed
on the ground and was seen by Noland
Well, then, as a reward, I'll give
you my prized finishing blow!
It's gonna hurt! So stop it!
I'm not responsible for this.
You'll be punished, seriously!
Concasser!
didn't sink into the ocean.
This part of Jaya has been...
...flying in the sky all this time!
Surprise Balls! Ball Dragon!!
Alright! Let's do it! Gold hunting!!
Even if we're far apart
I don't want you to forget
That on those days when
you're brought to tears
You have a friend here to share the pain
That far-off feeling we refuse to concede
I won't let it just be a dream
The eternal brilliance that
everyone is searching for
We will surely embrace it with our own hands
Whoa! What a fight!
Phew, it's finally quiet. What's the next ordeal?
Head towards the sacrificial altar!
Oh, I can't wait to see the treasure!
We're in huge trouble, aren't we?
You bastard! What did you do?! I can't move!
Yeah! Everyone, we're on our way!
Yeah, it's one thing after another!
Don't be so hasty. At any rate,
we'll start in the morning.
After a love ordeal is,
of course, a romance ordeal!
Hey, you two! We're not going on a picnic!
So we can't save you yet, Chopper!
We'll start after eating dinner and breakfast!
Don't be so touchy. Let's enjoy the trip!
Sky Knight!
Follow me! We have to
somehow get to the seashore.
Eh?! I'm in big trouble!
That's what you always talk about!
Ah! What's this?!
He's right! Look, some cheerful
people're headed this way.
If I'm not mistaken,
it's in the shape of a bell, right?
It looks like things're gonna get crazy!
You already got a strong ally on your side!
A golden bell? How gorgeous!
This is our chance!
Idiot! Thosere guerrillas on the attack!
I've finally caught him!
Sanji, give him a good pounding!
Eh?! O-Oh, right! Sky Knight!
--Alright! We'll get the gold!!
--Yeah!!
Today we'll definitely crush the
priests and take Upper Yard back!
Whoa!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Jaya, City of Gold in the Sky!
Head for God's Shrine!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Profound Mystery!
Ordeal of String and Ordeal of Love?!"
"Festival on the Night Before
Gold-Hunting! Feelings for Vearth!"
"Chopper in Danger!
Former God vs. Priest Shura"
"Light the Fire of Shandora! Wyper, the Warrior"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!