A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King
of the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
Heading towards a world without end
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
The horizons everyone
dreamed of were separate at first
but now they can be seen
through a single telescope
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
A bitter compass of destiny
is leading your heart astray
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We head beyond the horizon
We can surely smile despite that
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Tears shed trying to achieve
your dreams aren't for naught
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
Precious in my life
In search of light yet unseen
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
"Upper Yard" "Lovely Street"
"Angel Beach"
"Upper Yard" "Angel Island"
In an attempt to obtain gold,
the crew split up into Nami's escape
team and Luffy's search team.
Nami's group on the Going Merry
headed for the eastern shore
Laki!
They agreed to meet again on
the eastern shore, then departed.
What are you doing?
Though I guess there's nothing
you can do, hanging there like that...
If you don't want to die, go back
to the Blue Sea immediately!
in order to escape from Upper Yard.
Luffy's team ventured through
the unsettling forest
After the campfire ended...
If you've got any funny ideas about
doing something on this island...
This is that important to you, huh?
as they headed for ruins in the south,
Usopp had a mysterious experience late at night.
Meanwhile, Shandians headed
for God's Shrine to defeat Eneru,
but they were attacked by a giant
snake and wound up separated.
...we'll eliminate you along with Eneru!
but encountered Priest Shura,
and a great battle between
him and Wyper took place!
Meanwhile, Ohm, Gedatsu, and Shura
were called to God's shrine...
This isn't good...
Who're they?
Laki!
I returned to our course,
but no one is coming...
Did I get separated?
Kamakiri!
Oh, no! I got separated! Huh?! Huh?!
H-Help! Where is everyone?!
Why would you throw your shield
and gun away?! Are you a fool?!
So he fought this hard, even though
he gave us this whistle for free...
Yeah, just thought I'd start hauling
the wood for the ship's repairs...
...where God Eneru made an appearance.
Where are they? I look away for
a second and this happens...
No, he wouldn't...!
--You planning to swim across?
--Huh? Yeah.
Oh, well. I'm sure they'll manage somehow.
As pirates, we can't back off when
there's treasure close by, can we?
Those big sharks are in there.
If you want a shoulder, you can have one.
I got most of the map memorized,
anyway. It's to the right.
We've got enough enemies.
It's gonna be a survival game.
Tomorrow, I will let you enter
all areas of Upper Yard.
See! This is how Jaya looked 400 years ago!
Yeesh, where'd they all go? Am I lost now?
Oh, well. Guess I'll go ahead
and wait at the ruins.
An Impact, huh?! Such things can't defeat me!
You can set up your ordeals wherever you like.
--Whoa! It's a skull!
--It looks like a skull!
Alright! Let's do it! Gold hunting!!
She said "straight south,"
and south is in a warm-ish direction!
No, it's ten times the energy.
You can also ignore the rules
and go as wild as you want.
Well?
Kamakiri... Your wounds...
This way!
Reject!
"Festival on the Night Before
Gold-Hunting! Feelings for Vearth!"
I can still fight!
Wyper! Are you trying to die?!
Tell me, Merry. Who was that?
I can still fight.
Meanwhile, Wyper and the Shandian warriors
Try using the Reject Dial one more time!
Your body'll be blown apart!
headed for God's Shrine to defeat Eneru.
You're right-- now is the time
to take down Upper Yard.
However, Eneru, who uses Mantra to see all,
--Let's get going!
--Yeah!
let his priests use the entire island
as locations for their ordeals
With Satori gone, we put up a
good fight during today's battle...
So what about my body?
Isn't that called "resolve"?
to begin a game of survival.
Those beasts are problematic.
So let's attack again tomorrow, Wyper!
"A Giant Snake Bares Its Fangs!
The Survival Game Begins"
These guys can't be beaten
without any sacrifices like this!
Can't we draw them away somehow?
Alright! I'll try!
"The Deadly Reject!
War Demon Wyper's Resolve"
"Enter God Eneru!! Farewell to the Survivors"
I'm going on ahead!
C'mon, Zoro! Just for a second...!
When I first met you, I said one
reason I became a soldier-for-hire
Hey! Where are you going, Zoro?!
I'm not goin' with you!
Fine! Do what you want!
That's the wrong way! West is this way!
You're such a whiner! If you're scared,
then hold it until morning!
was because Blue Sea people
cannot handle sky combat.
At least pray for everyone's good luck!
Geez! Your horrible sense
of direction is such a pain!
I would if I could!
Sky combat? What's that?
West? That's east!
Alright, guys! Watch yourselves out there!
Hmm. In that case, place that barrel there.
Just go pee by yourself.
C'mon, Luffy! Why don't you
ever listen to anyone?!
Two... Three...
Let's meet at God's Shrine!
Barrel?
You're so cold-hearted, Zoro...!
It's the "skull's right eye," so we
gotta go right! Are you stupid?!
--Watch...
--What're we doing this for now?
I think they both are...
We're heading south, so could
you tell them it's this way?
At present, one has dropped out
of the Upper Yard survival game,
You will see.
Try crushing that shell with all your might.
You got it!
Gently now, Sanji! If you smash a
hole in the deck, you're gonna pay!
and eighty remain!
He must not have had God's divine protection.
Luffy! Zoro!
Urgh...
Hit it with all your might.
Laki!
What are you doing?
Quit saying whatever you want
when it's not your ship!
South, huh? Why didn't you say so sooner?!
Though I guess there's nothing you
can do, hanging there like that...
Meanwhile, four of the Straw Hats
set out to search for gold.
What's that sound?!
Alright, if that's what you want...
Their goal: the ruins of an ancient city
where a vast amount of gold rests!
This is that important to you, huh?
Wait! Wait! You don't need
to swing it that hard!
They head straight south
from the sacrificial altar!
Luffy! That's a nice stick!
Hey, what're you doing?
Straight... south...
Laki!
I know I told you to hold back,
but you didn't even crack the barrel...
Isn't it? You can't have it! Go find your own!
Run, Kamakiri!
There shouldn't be anyone with the ship...
You're so lucky! Stick...! Stick...!
No, I hit it as hard as I could. I was
ready to put a hole in the deck...
I owe you one, Kamakiri...
It's hard to see through all this fog...
What about sticks?
I thought this forest would be a
scarier place, but it's not so bad!
Hey!
"Fierce Midair Battle!
Pirate Zoro vs. Warrior Braham"
Kamakiri!
Yet, it's almost like this
shell absorbed the shock...
Dammit!
Wyper! Kamakiri's been hurt!
Now, point the dial's holes at the empty barrel
Chopper! You're strong today?
--Wait!
--What do you want?!
What?!
and press the back tip of the shell.
No, I have nothing to say, nor do I
want to hear any of your garbage.
That's right!
You know how to press it, yes?
Dammit! And we were so close!
I feel so reassured when I'm with these three!
I simply want to eliminate you!
But it really is a let-down, to be honest.
How do you figure that?
Click...
Once night falls, we'll have
an even greater advantage.
There was nothing in the
forest yesterday, either.
Oh! That's nice and easy to understand!
We didn't run across a single priest.
I know how you feel, Chopper.
Right?!
Assist the wounded!
We're pulling back for now!
What odd people. Do you want
an accident to happen that badly?
Meet back at the outer island!
That is an Impact Dial.
I won't let you escape!
It can absorb and freely
release shocks given to it.
Wait, Ohm!
What is it?
Normally, they're affixed to the
palms using gloves or bandages.
Huh? Those big roots have a weird pattern...
What's his deal?
God Eneru wants to see us.
The priests and guerillas here all
use strange fighting techniques.
He goes to take a piss, then falls
asleep out here. He's hopeless...
They're powerful enough that a direct
hit can kill your average person.
It's moving!
Might be dangerous to use my
swords from the usual distance...
What's moving, Chopper?
O-Oh, nothing! It's nothing at all!
G-Ghost... G-G-Ghost...
Usopp... This is...
But if I need to defeat enemies
from a distance... I do have that.
If I said I saw roots moving,
they'd all laugh at me for being afraid.
Quit dreamin'!
Yeah... This is what that dumpling priest used!
Ghost! A ghost...!
What is it?
I'm supposed to be strong today!
I bet it was my imagination!
Those sounds seem to be getting farther away.
Hawk Wave!
Yeah. The guerillas and priests are
probably going home for the night.
The other one might work
against small fries, but...
I sense something strange...
We are...
We better hurry and get back, too.
It is different from a hit!
Impact!
Chopper. Why do you keep
looking behind you?
--Wait for me, Zoro!
--Hurry, or I'll leave you behind!
But why couldn't you have said so sooner?!
Hey.
That freaked me out, you geezer!
N-No reason at all!
You don't know the way back!
I hear there existed even more
powerful dials in ancient sky islands.
What are those big roots with a weird pattern?
Must be hard to talk while
you're biting your lower lip!
You see it, too?! I knew it was strange!
Now-extinct "Reject Dials" that
could release ten times the energy
Why are the roots moving?
You see it too?! Actually,
I noticed earlier, and...!
of these Impact Dials...
Still needs work...
How careless of me.
But they were a double-edged sword,
But I guess I'll try it out...
I'm telling you, Eneru-sama summoned
us because you let Wyper go!
as the excessive shock from using
them put the user's own life at risk.
A flying slash!
--W-What the...?!
--What the...?!
Though, naturally, it seems
they were hardly ever used...
There's no need to get worked up.
However much they struggle,
mere Shandians cannot escape us.
Man, this is boring!
Who told you to stare at it?!
Such is their fate!
There're shells that dangerous?!
Those're practically weapons!
Your only job is to put the distilled
water that collects in the container
That's nothing but an excuse!
into the canteens, so that we'll
have drinking water for tomorrow!
I thought dials were more
common, everyday objects...
The wind's good! The helm's good!
Had Eneru-sama left it all
to me from the very start,
Yes, they are.
Truly comfortable! What a perfect cruise!
But what seems useful can
always be used for evil as well,
Still...
But this thing sure is slow!
Hey, navigator! Do something!
everything would have
been taken care of today,
Sanji! We got lots of things!
I'm afraid I can't, Captain Usopp!
Oh! Good work! What'd you find?
and his mood wouldn't have been spoiled!
Say that again...
depending on who uses it.
Walnuts, aloe, bananas, and garlic!
--I'm afraid I can't!
--No, not that part!
And rats and frogs.
Dials are extremely useful,
Gedatsu. It would be
impossible for a fool like you.
The Milky Road has intense ups and downs,
Great! Toss it into the stew!
so our only choice is to rely
on the dial ship's power!
Shandians!
but that makes them all
the more powerful in battle.
Hold it! There were some
weird ingredients just now!
Divine Soldiers!
You can do it, Crow!
What?!
Oh, and Sanji. Be at my guard at all times!
You're right! How careless of me!
I'll warn you two now.
For example, even a
Heat Dial used to warm food
No garlic?
The captain is afraid of this forest...
Know your place,
No! I wasn't talking about that!
can turn a spear into a controllable,
high-temperature "Heat Javelin."
or else you'll lose control of your
Mantra and end up just like Satori.
What's wrong, Navigator?
Shut up! Then quit acting
like a big-shot captain!
Wow! Robin! What's that blue thing?! A gem?!
You're the one who needs
to know his place, Ohm!
And just so you know, I'm only
going to protect Nami-san!
A flame-storing Flame Dial,
placed inside a bird's mouth,
Pretty, isn't it? But no, it's not a gem.
Oh, yeah! It's time for the
Weird Knight's medicine!
Oh, a salt crystal, huh?
That's a great find, Robin-chan!
Where did Chopper say he put it again?
can create the truly rare "fire-breathing bird"...
My name is Gan Fall. Gan Fall.
Don't start acting haughty just
'cause you beat ol' Gan Fall, Shura!
I...
I found it on the lakeshore.
I thought it would be useful to have...
Yeah, Chopper did mention stuff like that!
...should never have come!
Oh, the medicine's on a
barrel next to the fridge.
--And that's "sky combat"?
--Yes.
It sure would! Salt is vital to
surviving in the wilderness!
Amusing!
Thanks, Nami-san!
Blue Sea people unfamiliar with dials
cannot ascertain our techniques.
Okay!
Looks like you've gotten a lot better, old man!
I'll take half the garlic and aloe!
God. The priests have arrived.
Yes. I thank you all.
I can use it to make burn medicine
and antiseptic for the Sky Knight!
The same is true for our
many types of artificial clouds.
If you're gonna thank anyone,
thank our ship's doctor!
Open the door.
The warriors of the sky
are trained to master them;
Yeah?
Chopper's medicine works real wonders!
--What about the frogs?
--No frogs.
The forest has become quite lively...
Hey, Zoro!
those with no knowledge of
them do not stand a chance.
Oh, but you tried to save Chopper, right?
You're not doing anything. Help out.
This is a house away from the city.
Then is there some reason
behind the "Mantra" thing
Then you're both even!
As expected, it's been swallowed by the forest.
You know, my swords aren't
meant to be used like this...
that lets them read our
movements ahead of time?
Not again...
What are you doing?! You're so hopeless...
I wonder if the ruins of
the actual city are intact...
Old man?
Quiet! Disobey the cook
and you'll go without dinner!
Mantra, huh...?
I'm unable to use it myself,
so I can't explain it very well,
Shall I talk a little about this land's history?
Quiet! It's only because
these guys drag me down
Eh?! We're eating rocks, too?!
Are they any good?
but it is said that "Mantra"
is a listening ability.
that I can't use my powers to their fullest!
Until six years ago, I was God...
A woman!
Get real. This is stone stew.
This route leads to God's Shrine!
Going any further would be insolent!
Supposedly, just by living, people
give off voices from their bodies.
The heat from the cooked stone boils the stew.
Did you hit your head, old man?
I would fare much better if you let
me handle the entire island alone!
Oh...!
Stew is great! You get all the
ingredients' nutrition without any waste!
--Voices?
--Yes.
Get down from there!
By listening to them, one can allegedly
tell what a person will do next.
That's some mighty big talk there!
As you know, it is said that
Upper Yard appeared in Skypiea
You don't seem to realize the
historical value that ruins have!
--I see!
--Ah! We're having stew...
I'll show you just how "skilled" you really are!
With further mastery, you can hear
voices over an even wider area.
Don't open it!
some 400 years ago.
How impudent!
Sanji! I'm hungry!
Do you have business with me?
What do you want?
The priests can hear all throughout Upper Yard,
Until then, Skypiea had
been a peaceful sky island...
It's not even cooked yet!
Simple! By God's orders,
On the sorrowful path of
enlightenment... The Iron Ordeal!
Besides, didn't you just roast
and eat an entire skyshark?!
and Eneru's powers extend
across this entire land.
I'm to chop the Shandians
and you Blue Sea people
Items from the Blue Sea that
sporadically rode up the Knock-Up Stream
Yeah... but that was just to tide me over.
And those powers are all too mysterious.
into pieces with this Axe Dial!
Your worthless ordeal is nothing but pathetic!
Geez, what kind of stomach does he have?
were rare and valuable to the sky people.
Because of them, the people of this
land have no time to feel at ease.
How uneconomical...
Seis Fleurs!
All the Vearth on the sky islands
came into the sky in this way.
My swamp is the supreme ordeal!
Want to give it a try?
Have they reached the bottom yet?
What're you doing, Usopp?
Dinner's almost ready.
Twist!
Gedatsu-sama. That must be tiring.
Yes. They are already waiting eagerly.
Yeah, just thought I'd start hauling
the wood for the ship's repairs...
But Vearth the size of Upper Yard
was an unimaginable miracle.
To cross your arms, you need to
put your hands under your elbows.
There are the three priests' ordeals,
on top of Commander Yama's
fifty Divine Soldiers...
--You planning to swim across?
--Huh? Yeah.
--How careless of me!
--Come! That is enough!
Those big sharks are in there.
God. You're waging all-out war.
Is such severity really necessary?
Just awful.
You are in God's presence!
Naturally, the sky people were
overjoyed and worshipped it
Presence? I don't see him anywhere!
I can fix it tomorrow! Let's get dinner, Zoro!
as holy ground bestowed by Heaven.
We're only dealing with a few
Shandians and Blue Sea people.
I thought he called us here?!
That'll teach you, Divine Soldier!
Yeesh...
Where is Eneru-sama?!
However, indigenous people
lived on this Vearth,
Festivals are more fun the livelier they are.
They've killed many of our allies!
and a battle over its ownership began.
Alright! Finished!
Damn! These Divine Soldiers mean trouble!
Plus, you're making light of the
underlying power of sky combat.
Ladies first. Got it?
Got you!
Those people are the Shandians...
Yeah.
Right. Right. Right...
Alright! Everyone in your seats!
--You mean the guerrillas?!
--Yes.
I'll come around and serve it,
so eat before it gets cold!
Underlying power?
Is that one of the Blue Sea
people Wyper mentioned?!
Yes, that's right.
They'll show you soon enough.
So they originally lived on
Jaya in the world below?
Alright, guys!
He must be eliminated!
Let's begin our strategy meeting
to decide what to do tomorrow!
Yes. They were sent into the sky
with the island, against their will.
Ooh! Looks great!
Banana.
A guerilla!
Guys! T-Thanks.
Yet, you guys kicked them off the island?
Seems he wants to fight!
Now, then. We have fifty
Divine Soldiers and three priests.
We can do this while eating, so listen!
I am God.
Die!
Yes. The sky people stole their
homeland, due to their own greed...
--Right!
I dunno what brought this on, but...!
See, I'm right here.
Oh! Heart-shaped carrots!
Including me, that makes 54 people.
Train some more. You're all too weak.
Currently, there are twenty
Shandians heading for the island,
Even after 400 years,
You're really meticulous, Sanji!
Who the hell are you guys?!
Surely you don't wish to wind
up as pathetic as Satori did?
the war between the Shandians
and the sky people has not ended.
there are four Blue Sea people in the forest,
and four attempting to escape.
How is it, huh?! Do you like my love stew?!
The Shandians are simply trying
to take back their homeland.
What is this?!
Please, forgive me! I give up!
No, make that three. I doubt
the old man can fight now.
What a horrible prank!
Eh? What?
That's... kind of heartbreaking.
I give up! I lose! Please don't kill me...!
You called us here just to tell us that?!
Everyone ready?
81 people, altogether!
This will be a battle for survival.
First, let's review Noland's picture book!
Then doesn't that make you the bad guys?!
I was bored.
It was 400 years ago when Noland
first discovered the city of gold.
Yes... You're right.
Have a seat.
But when he returned to Jaya
years later, the gold ruins were gone!
Shall I guess how many will have
fallen three hours from now?
Another one?!
You don't seem to have taken much
notice of those Blue Sea people...
Hey, you! If you ain't a priest,
don't be attackin' me!
Honestly... You're so quick
to make things into games.
Oh, my medicine. Thank you.
This stew sure is good! Just like--
Eneru-sama. If you're referring to Satori...
I'm in a hurry here!
Oh, come now!
He was simply too inexperienced.
Hey, you guess.
Hey! Are you listening?!
Eh?! M-Me?
I'm sorry, Nami-san! But he was...
With his lousy "Ball Ordeal" and all...
These sky island boxed lunches are great, too!
No, I have no understanding
of such things, so...
What about Eneru?
As I said, you're weak, Shura.
Who is this "God Eneru"?
Back to the story!
Huh? What's with you? Don't be a
party-pooper. Just use your hunch.
Gan Fall is still alive.
Basically, during those few years,
this island, which is part of Jaya,
Impossible! I finished him off myself!
came up into the sky!
When I was God,
Okay, then. You guess!
You mean it rode up the Knock-Up Stream?!
He's not in tip-top shape...
he suddenly appeared from
some sky island, leading soldiers.
Y-Yes...
Yeah. That's the only possibility I can think of;
He made a heavy blow to my
"Divine Squad" and to the Shandians,
Well, the three priests are powerful enough,
But he seems to be friends with the
Blue Sea people for some reason...
Bastard! What the hell
are those flashing pistols?!
Cricket-san said the sea floor
explodes at different places each time.
then took control of Upper Yard.
but the fifty Divine Soldiers
are all quite strong as well...
He's such a stubborn old man!
I could see an island flying
after an explosion like that!
This was six years ago.
What exactly are the Blue Sea people after?
Where'd he go?!
So I doubt many of them
will be defeated at all,
Most of the Divine Squad is now
being forced to work hard by Eneru.
But it's hard to believe that forest
on Jaya is the same as this one...
but the enemy is also strong enough
to compete with the priests...
Their aim is gold.
Given three hours, I suspect
thirty people will fall.
I do not know the details.
That's probably due to the
composition of sea and island clouds.
But to the Shandians, who God
is doesn't change the situation.
Gold...
Therefore, about fifty will survive...
How do they know about that?
It appears the environment
around this sky island
This island was originally part of the Blue Sea.
They simply want their homeland back.
allows animals and plants
to develop unusually quickly.
I see! Fifty, huh?
That also explains the civilization
that was swallowed up by this forest.
It's not strange for Blue Sea
people to know about it.
If these Shandians just
want their homeland back,
But don't you think that's
a little too optimistic?
You're pretty tough.
I apologize. I underestimated you,
Blue Sea person.
why'd they attack us the
instant we came to the sky?
So dejected...
You're underestimating this battle, you know...
Naturally, they will make their move tomorrow.
Say, the South Birds that saved
us at the lake were this big!
And the Shandians will attack again.
Then, what do you predict, God?
The rules are that you each
run an area of Upper Yard,
Yeah, they probably got
bigger over those 400 years.
No, I should apologize.
But it's strange...
All right, allow me to answer straight-out.
but you're not allowed to
interfere with one another.
I had you pegged as a small fry.
Why did those huge South Birds save you?
Tomorrow, I will let you enter all areas.
In three hours, only five of the 81
people on this island will be standing.
Yeah, I'm not really sure. But they
all called the Sky Knight "God"...
You can set up your ordeals wherever you like.
Members of the Divine Squad
sometimes escape via ship.
You can also ignore the rules
and go as wild as you want.
God?! Does that mean we
should beat up this old man?!
Of course not, you stupid loudmouth!
Why this, all of a sudden?
Naturally, the Shandians see them
as enemies and try to eliminate them.
Alright, that's enough! Sit down, loudmouth!
Actually, I've almost completed the Maxim.
--Yeah! Sit down!
--Who's this "loudmouth"?!
--It's you!
Perhaps they mistook you for them.
So let's put an end to this island
and set forth for the world of dreams!
Anyways, remember what Noland's
log said about the city of gold?!
We were almost killed because
of a mistake? That's too much!
One reason I became the Sky Knight
I know! He saw gold!
Obviously, you loud loudmouth!
Quit sayin' whatever comes to mind!
was so that I could help those
escapees flee to other islands safely.
I recall there being a giant gold bell,
and that there were South Birds...
As criminals, they can't stay here,
where Eneru can observe them.
There was an incomprehensible
line on the last page of his log.
What the...?!
From the sound of it, "God Eneru"
is almost like a king of terror...
My body!
Just before he died, Noland wrote a passage
Hey, now! Watch what you say!
The almighty God sees all!
W-What the...?! I can't move!
that said he saw gold in
the "skull's right eye"...
To think that these people defeated Satori...
That's it! Look at this!
Hello there, Shandians.
Since when did you become
a native Skypiean?!
They've made themselves
complete enemies of Eneru...
I matched the size of Robin's
Jaya map with the old Skypiea map!
Looking good.
D-Didn't you hear what he just said?!
And the Shandians won't
overlook this chance, either...
Forgive my rude welcome.
It's just an approximation,
Terror, huh? No, it is worse than that.
but when you put their locations
of the beach house together...
Shura!
Yes, yes. I know my name.
I don't need you all to tell me.
Damn you, Eneru... Just what is it you desire?!
See! This is how Jaya looked 400 years ago!
Eneru establishes outsiders
like yourselves as criminals,
--Whoa! It's a skull!
--It looks like a skull!
He didn't even step toward me!
then has the denizens of Skypiea
lead them to their "judgment."
It's unfortunate news for you...
--Well?
--Awesome!
...but Upper Yard's layout has changed
from how it was until last night.
--Way to go, Nami-san!
--We did it!
They said there's all kinds of wavers...
What this brings about is the
citizens' "awareness of sin."
Then, the "skull's right eye" is...
Are those skate things just another type?
Can't move, can you? That's just fine.
We did put up a good fight...
Right here!
A person becomes his weakest when
he senses sin in his own actions.
Noland was referring to the
shape of the entire island.
He's using blasts to make himself float!
Today, we will break into God's shrine!
The survival rate is 3%...
And those pistols that flash each time he shoots!
But only half of it is left now,
so nobody could solve the mystery!
...here in the String Ordeal!
Eneru knows this.
Because of those, I lose sight of him every time!
He creates his own "lost sheep"
and controls them.
I see! So that's why...
And then, Eneru will be--
Where'd he go?!
Interesting...
He is truly playing God. He's a powerful man...
--Treasure!
So we just need to go straight to this spot!
See! It's just like I said! Someone was here!
--Tiger...
--Three swords?!
We can't leave the boat, though,
so let's split into two teams tomorrow!
We thought we found a paradise
when we arrived at Angel Beach...
...Trap!
The String Ordeal?!
No doubt about it!
Boy, were we wrong...
I would say watch out,
but it's too late for that now.
There's an enormous amount
of gold waiting for us here!
Bastard!
This is one hell of a place the
old city of gold flew up to...
The Going Merry's been repaired!
Oh, that reminds me.
This "gold" you've been
fussing about since last night...
I saw it! It wasn't a dream, after all!
String Clouds?!
What exactly is it?
A Blue Sea swordsman who
can't even use wavers or dials...
Eh?!
Indeed. I'm impressed you could tell.
Anything you do is useless!
What covers my area are String
Clouds so fine they can't be seen,
The mast was completely
snapped off, but now it's all fixed!
Know what this is?!
but are so strong in bunches that
they can stop even grown men.
What the...?!
Wyper...
Yes. Just standing this heavy thing
up must be hard work by itself!
Genbou! How are Kamakiri's wounds?
A Milky Dial!
They're tending to him over there right now.
So you've appeared again...
And you pulled them all in yourselves
from the island's entrance.
Still, I hate to say it, but...
Aerial combat ain't just
jumping around desperately!
Are they deep?
Yeah.
Leave, old man!
...it sucks.
It's hard to believe he would be beaten...!
There sure are nice people out there!
Stop it, Wyper! Gan Fall is here to negotiate!
Look closely. You're covered in strings.
Ohm really is formidable...
A-An eel?!
There was someone here! I saw him!
I-I'm sorry...
This is what they mean by,
"You reap what you sow!"
Negotiate, my ass!
Move aside, Chief!
But who'd fix our ship for us out here?
Do you expect us to agree to a
compromise between two old men?!
It's...
It's my fault!
Except...
The only people besides us in
Upper Yard are our enemies...
...for one of you!
Listen, Gan Fall!
We're not budging a single inch!
I bet this'd make good eatin', broiled...
Let's go, Fuza!
But it's not the flying model anymore, Usopp.
If you insist that fighting is
pointless, then give it all back!
Wyper!
What a meal!
Do you know what you've done
to us Shandians for generations?!
Don't assume you can match me in mid-air!
--We get gold tomorrow!
--That's right!
Yeah. That's got me wondering...
So why do you want "coexistence" now?!
Do you think tomorrow'll be sunny, too?
Watch out! It's a Heat Javelin!
Well, we are above the clouds...
I cannot return everything.
It's gotten pretty late. We need
to put out any unnecessary fires.
How did the person know what
the Merry originally looked like?
The power of Upper Yard's Vearth
is essential to Skypiea now.
They'll only reveal our location to the enemy...
I-I really screwed up! Am I an idiot?!
Why would you throw your shield
and gun away?! Are you a fool?!
How'd they know it didn't have
a crest or wings or a tail?
How foolish! Did you hear that, Usopp?!
She wants to put out the fire!
They are all grateful for its blessings.
I'm already dealing with a
nimble enough bastard here...
No, he wouldn't...!
Who did you see, Usopp?
I cannot possibly take that
away from innocent people!
It's not her fault.
She's lived in darkness until now.
It really sounds like it could
only happen in a dream...
If you want a shoulder, you can have one.
...but then I get my leg shot up!
You're saying the sky people are innocent?!
Isn't there anything I can do
about those flashing pistols?!
She just doesn't know.
What're you loafing around for?!
Maybe so, if you live in peace and never fight!
That's it!
What do you mean?
We have lots to do, you know!
An Impact, huh?! Such things can't defeat me!
Those are some mighty nice
weapons you got there!
You're always supposed to have a campfire!
Should we get people outside your
"Divine Squad" involved, too?!
No, it's ten times the energy.
You're not curious, Nami?
Don't be foolish!
The desire to have a campfire
when camping at night,
But too bad! Look! I have goggles!
About what?
If you wanna undo your sins, take a risk!
even if you're on your last legs,
is what makes one human!
About who fixed the Going Merry...
Reject!
Sacrifice 100 people who don't
wanna die, and bring their heads here!
Your flashing pistols
won't work on me anymore!
You're the stupid ones!
Maybe if someone wrecked it, but
since it's fixed, what does it matter?
Will you cut the crap already?!
You know how dangerous this forest is!
I cannot do that!
So just give it up!
Or do you wanna find the
person and thank them?
They don't look like sunglasses to me...
Then our negotiations
have broken down! Leave!
--Do not!
--There are priests! There are guerrillas!
No, but...
He saw through it!
Unless you want your head
removed where you stand!
You don't seem fond of these Flash Guns.
And even without them, forests
at night are dangerous anyways!
How did they know?
Wait, Wyper!
Close distance is vital to a swordsman.
You're no match for me.
Who knows? There could be wild
animals or monsters out there!
Monsters?!
Sky islands are scary, sky islands are scary...
I don't know what you guys are here for.
Don't be saying my name so freely...
Tell me, Merry. Who was that?
Hey, Luffy!
Is this wood pile good enough?
But as long as you are here,
you're still our enemy.
You guys are serious about this, too?!
The Upper Yard survival game...
I...
It's all right, Nami-san.
Wild animals are actually afraid of fires.
One has dropped out. Eighty remain...
Now die already! Your leg
must hurt pretty bad, too.
...love pumpkin juice.
Behind you! There's already
something behind you!
The first battle ends in a great upset...
Shura has been defeated.
Mind your own business. It only grazed me.
Okay! Watch as I, President of
the Lowering-the-Merry Company,
I'll kill you!
Wait, Wyper!
M-My word! Shura-sama has?!
Getting shot while gawking at
an eel is proof I still lack vigor.
use my greatness to get the ship off the altar!
Men! Stop Wyper!
He underestimated sky combat, too. The fool!
What are you doing?!
Kamakiri! Braham! Not you, too?!
I'm Vice President of the
Lowering-the-Merry Company!
Hey! It's saying something! C'mere, Chopper!
Well then, this is the perfect
situation to try out that technique...
Eh?
I'm being relied on!
But is this not cause for distress?!
"You outsiders are being too damn loud!
Get to bed, you dumbasses!"
Shall I give it a try?
Two priests, undefeated for six years,
suddenly fall in under two days!
What're you planning to do, Usopp?
Aisa certainly cries a lot, doesn't she?
--Say what?!
I'm not the one saying it!
No. It can't be helped that they were defeated.
"Don't tell me you bastards are
thinkin' about trashin' our turf!"
Yes. She always cries when something
scary happens in the village.
Alright!
They must not have had
God's divine protection...
No, we were brought here against our will!
--Chopper!
--Right!
Is it because of Wyper...?
"This is our land! Who said
you jerks could cook here?!"
Alright, men! We're up against twenty
Shandians and seven Blue Sea people!
Uh... Sorry!
Fire!
"This forest is ours!
The trees, the grass, everything!"
It's okay, it's okay.
Go!
Trying to run away?
I'm not sure. Though he always is
in the center of any trouble there is.
This will be easy. There is no need
to trouble the priests with them.
Eyes, ears, nose, tongue, body, mind...
Go, and wreak havoc to your hearts' content!
Yes! Alright!
I won't let you have our treasure!
Those six roots of man
have good, evil, and peace...
"The 50 Divine Soldiers of Skypiea"
Why do you think it's him?
Chopper! Full speed!
Awesome! You're awesome, Usopp!
Hey, look! Things seem even
worse now! What do we do?!
What are you talking about?
I'm afraid of him, too...
Those who can step over comrades
and keep moving, come with me!
And each of those has pure and impure...
--Do something!
--Me?!
After all, he's almost like a demon...
36 worldly desires in a lifetime...
"Forget it, guys. You ain't no
match for them, even as a pack..."
Today... Eneru's head will be mine!
I now have the barrel of
a cannon pointed at you.
"Girlie! You pack a mean punch! I like ya!"
That didn't really work, Usopp...
Once we defeat Eneru, we won't need
to revere a single bag of Vearth.
You have pistols, I have a cannon...
Don't worry, Chopper!
Distance and power-wise,
my weapon is superior.
I figured this might happen,
so I devised a secret backup plan!
The Vearth!
Did we just work things out?
You've done well...
Wyper!
Seems that way.
Really?! What is it?!
...but now you die!
Then let's all have a campfire together!
I told you, that's Aisa's treasure!
There are huge skysharks here, right?
Stop.
Yeah!
A single bag of Vearth...
Braham!
There sure are! Swarms of them!
A cannon?
Don't assume we'll get another chance!
Have you gone mad?
Where is this weapon of yours?!
I won't let this opportunity go!
There is a way we can utilize their power...
Let's get this party goin'! It's the
night festival before gold-hunting!
Those who aren't prepared,
stay here. I won't blame you.
Have you ever seen a flying slash?
The skysharks' power?
Yeah! They got lots of power!
I can guarantee that!
Wyper! Are you trying to die?!
Nonsense!
C'mon, Wyper! We're always prepared!
What is this?! It's delicious!
Try using the Reject Dial one more time!
Your body'll be blown apart!
So, Chopper... I got a little job for you...
Single-Sword Style!
Did you guys make this juice?
It's delicious! More, please!
Are you prepared to abandon
anyone who falls during the fight?
Anything you say! I'm being relied on!
I'll do anything at all!
Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
Great!
Yay!
So what about my body?
Isn't that called "resolve"?!
Those who can step over comrades
and keep moving, come with me!
Well said!
These guys can't be beaten
without such sacrifices!
What is this?! It's delicious!
Let's get the treasure!
Today... Eneru's head will be mine!
--Gold!
U-Usopp! Don't tell me I'm being used as...
Hungry skysharks are gonna try to bite you!
They even tamed the cloud wolves...
Sorry.
Run! It's a giant snake!
I'm bait?!
No one else living on Eneru's land
would have such a wild party...
Nothing personal, but I ain't the
type of guy who'll die when told to.
No! No! No bait! I don't wanna be eaten!
Oh, you're awake!
Should you be moving about?
That bastard!
I apologize for trying to help
but causing trouble instead...
What're you standin' around for?
What're you talking about? You helped a lot!
What size! Is this also a result of
the sky island's environment?
Braham!
I accept this survival challenge!
Thanks! I hear you saved Chopper and our ship.
We're behind enemy lines now.
Let's all split up.
Now, Sanji!
There are still two priests out there.
--It was nothing...
--There's still some stew. Would you like some?
Seems they've changed
the locations of the ordeals.
No, no. I thank you, but I'm
afraid I can't right now.
We don't wanna all get caught
in the same ordeal again.
You're like a catfish! I'll chop you into chunks!
Oh! You're up, weird old man!
Thanks for your help!
There's no reason to be that stupid...
--Let's dance!
--Let's dance, Sky Knight!
I'm going on ahead!
You're supposed to be a doctor!
Alright!
Fine! Do what you want!
How the hell can something
so big move so fast?!
Old man! How is Conis-chan? Is she all right?
At least pray for everyone's good luck!
Yes. She and her father
are at my house. Fear not.
Darn it...
Come on, skyshark!
Alright, guys! Watch yourselves out there!
Really?! That's great! I was so worried!
Let's meet at God's Shrine!
I lost all sense of direction...
That's great! They're both safe!
Guys!
Alright! Let's all toss Chopper into the air!
Luffy! Zoro! Robin!
No!
What for?!
Don't move!
Am I going to be left here to die?
Move!
Poison!
Will I go to heaven if I die?
Will the doctor be waiting for me?
I think we should run away...
Definitely.
Who're you?! What have you done?!
Yikes!
No, I can't think like that!
--Heso!
--A Divine Soldier?!
I heard you talking earlier...
I'm a doctor! I can't think
about death so casually!
Indeed! By God Eneru's orders,
Don't touch the poison! You'll die instantly!
--So this island was originally known as Jaya?
--Yes.
we've been sent to clean out all of Upper Yard!
I take it you don't know why this
place is now known as holy ground?
But I wonder what heaven is like...
Accept the fact there is no escape
from us fifty elite Divine Soldiers!
All right!
Wait, isn't this heaven?
--Hurray! We did it!
--Way to go, Usopp!
Hey! Poisonous snake! Over here! Follow me!
Huh?!
Taste the wrath of the Axe Dial,
which does not exist in Skypiea!
Piece o' cake!
Things turned all ruin-ish at some point.
Your food's running away!
I wonder if the others are here!
I guess I really am great!
Out of the way!
It's stuff like this that
causes distractions in battle!
Robin! Look out!
Even deeper! Even sharper!
Oh! Could I be the first one here?!
Yeah! My nose must've helped!
Are you here to get in our way, Laki?!
Cinco Fleurs!
Axe Dial!
Too bad!
I feel truly sorry for Kamakiri...
Yay! I'm the first!
Robin! You're incredible...!
No!
Shields have no effect!
We're up against priests!
If we lack any strength in battle,
we'll never make it to God's Shrine!
A raccoon dog...
Alright! I should be behind its tail now...
Now, then. Here's the map.
I know apologizing won't fix everything!
The search team will go
this way, straight south...
But give that back! It's Aisa's treasure!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
This "right eye" should
have some sort of ruins,
I promised I would get some Vearth for her!
Crap!
so watch out for enemies
and bring some gold back!
--Shut up!
--Forgive me! Don't throw it away!
You make it sound so simple...
I'd love to investigate the ruins!
This way! Over here!
Kamakiri... Your wounds...
# The islands in the south are warm... #
Huh? You keep talking about
the gold, but you're not coming?
That doesn't work on me at all!
I can still fight.
No way! It's scary!
# Pineapple-ple, head all warm,
what a dummy... #
You want the gold, but without any danger!
You're right-- now is the time
to take down Upper Yard.
You're so weird, Nami! Weirdo!
Gum-Gum...
You saying something?
A goat? Was that a goat? Where is it?
This isn't good...
...Balloon!
With Satori gone, we put up a
good fight during today's battle...
I returned to our course,
but no one is coming...
Meanwhile, we'll leave the island in the Merry.
Did I get separated? Should I
go ahead and wait for them?
So let's attack again tomorrow, Wyper...
A goat in a forest?
We'll be in danger, too, you know.
We'll head for the beach ruins
area as fast as possible.
Oh, no! I got separated! Huh?! Huh?!
H-Help! Where is everyone?!
Let's meet up there, and then
escape from this sky island!
Why, you...
For you Blue Sea people, the ground
here must seem quite natural.
Aww, man! Jerk got my hopes up!
And I was all excited to see a goat!
Where are they? I look away for
a second and this happens...
...bastard!
Then we'll be super-rich pirates!
We can buy whatever we want!
Oh, well. I'm sure they'll manage somehow.
Yeah.
Sanji-kun!
Hurray! I can eat all the meat I want!
I see.
I got most of the map memorized,
anyway. It's to the right.
Second verse!
# The islands in the north are cold... #
Escape, huh? Sounds good to me!
But this is something that does
not normally exist in the sky.
Sanji!
No bait!
Yeesh...
Sanji!
# All chilly-like, head all shivery,
what a dummy... #
Look! It's nice weather today!
Island cloud does raise plant life,
but it does not give birth to it.
Where'd they all go? Am I lost now?
We are above the clouds.
Oh, well. Guess I'll go ahead
and wait at the ruins.
Okay! Let's meet safely on the eastern shore!
--Sanji-kun!
--H-Hey!
Neither greenery nor soil is
naturally found in the sky...
--Alright!
--Let's get going!
Say something, Sanji!
She said "straight south,"
and south is in a warm-ish direction!
Yeah!
Oh, it's you!
This way!
Hey! What happened?! Sanji!
What are you doing here?
We call this "Vearth."
It seems the Shandians have started to move...
I warned you to leave this island!
Shut up! I can do what I want.
And the Blue Sea people
have split into two groups...
It is the very object of eternal
admiration for those living in the sky.
No, you can't. This island
belongs to us Shandians!
Hey! I can't hear his heart!
And then split up even more... Solo, huh?
No way!
Eh? It does? I thought it was God's...
Once we defeat Eneru, we won't need
to revere a single bag of Vearth.
Today is going to be a lively day.
Just how many people will survive?
Really? Well, pardon my intrusion.
What a foolish man. And I didn't
even come here to bring you harm.
Right, Wyper?
Third verse! # The eastern-- #
Well then, let the survival game begin!
--Wait!
--What do you want?!
Will it be the Shandians who are
welcomed by my String Ordeal,
No, I have nothing to say.
Then why are you here?!
We're going back. To the 400-year-old
homeland of the Shandians!
or the Blue Sea people?
We're now heading for God's shrine!
What a cold-hearted hello...
Nor do I want to hear any of your garbage.
Don't stop, no matter what happens!
I simply want to eliminate you!
It's truly been six long years,
Former God Gan Fall...
This is perfect weather for
the festival about to begin...
We're after only one thing... Eneru's head!
Oh.
Yeah!
That's nice and easy to understand, then!
Racing full speed ahead as always
A to Z, we run through it
Even if we're far apart
We all have worries and fall many times
But we just need to rise to the top someday
I don't want you to forget
What could be beyond the sea
in which the morning sun rises?
That on those days when
you're brought to tears
Let's go little by little toward
the brilliantly shining sun
You have a friend here to share the pain
I never treat you "bad"
How many times did we fall?
That far-off feeling we refuse to concede
It's all right, we're definitely
pointing at tomorrow now
I won't let it just be a dream
Smile! Come back to you, friends
The eternal brilliance that
everyone is searching for
Come back to you, friends
We will surely embrace it with our own hands
Alright! Let's set out for the gold!
Right, right, right...
Gold-hunting, at last!
I can't believe Sanji-kun is dead...
How many will survive?
Why is it just you and the old
man here?! I can't rely on you!
I, Usopp-sama, am president of
the Lowering-the-Merry Company!
Where the hell did Luffy and the others go?
I'm counting on you! Once we get
the gold, we'll be rich pirates!
Where is everyone?! Help me!
Who're you?!
That's my line!
--Hold on, President!
--President!
If you want a shoulder, you can have it!
I should never have come!
Straw Hat! I'm going to eliminate you!
Things're finally getting interesting!
--There is nothing I can't do!
--Just get working, President.
They get lost so easily when I'm gone!
The forest has become quite lively...
It's no use! Your bazooka doesn't work on me!
Bring God and the guerrillas
and everything else on!
Eneru's head will be ours today!
But now you're complete enemies of Eneru...
I ain't the type of guy who'll die when told to.
I feel reassured with you guys around!
All right! I'll try hard, too!
Wretched pest! Don't mock sky combat!
Only five will be standing in three hours' time.
I accept this survival challenge!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Enter God Eneru!! Farewell to the Survivors"
"A Giant Snake Bares Its Fangs!
The Survival Game Begins"
"The Deadly Reject!
War Demon Wyper's Resolve"
"The Roaring Burn Bazooka!!
Luffy vs. War Demon Wyper"
"Fierce Midair Battle!
Pirate Zoro vs. Warrior Braham"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!