Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King
of the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
The horizons everyone
dreamed of were separate at first
but now they can be seen
through a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny
is leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve
your dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
"Upper Yard" "Angel Island"
With one hour left until
God Eneru's declared time limit,
Impact.
God only knows.
Nami's group was planning
to escape from Upper Yard
there currently remain 25 survivors.
when God Eneru appeared
and demonstrated his might.
Burn Blade!
Cien Fleurs!
Nami's group headed for the
eastern shore to escape Upper Yard,
Stop!
Meanwhile, the four search team
members wound up separated,
but Eneru appeared, charred Sanji
and Usopp, and then vanished.
It's too late for that now...
I should never have come!
and Luffy was confronted by
the Shandian warrior Wyper.
Can't breathe...
After defeating Yama and
discovering Shandora, the city of gold,
Did you think you could
move faster than lightning?
Get down from there!
Gum-Gum...
My name is Hotori!
Impudent Blue Sea woman! I'll chop you up!
Burn...
Robin found something even more surprising.
My name is Kotori!
Seis Fleurs!
Run! Wyper!
As if taking his place,
Twist!
--...Bazooka!
Could it be?!
Satori's twin brothers Kotori and
Hotori showed up, bent on revenge.
No!
The Poneglyph I searched the
world for, but could never find...!
Their voices... are disappearing!
Just awful.
I have to protect them!
In which case, the grand belfry
located in the center of the four altars
Whoops. It seems the electricity
traveled along the Milky Road.
Meanwhile, the four who headed
south for the ancient ruins
might contain the "text of real history"...
Fools...
Nami's group then encountered a new enemy...
ran into a giant snake and wound up separated.
Have you ever seen a flying slash?
Don't play dumb! My name is Hotori!
The Rio Poneglyph!
"A Mystical City!
The Grand Ruins of Shandora!!"
Descendants built this after the city fell...
My name is Kotori!
Single-Sword Style! Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
You guys killed our brother!
"0% Survival Rate! Chopper vs. Ohm,
the Sword Wielding Priest"
Shandora... That was this ancient city's name...
--Amazing!
--You're incredible, Nami-san!
And Chopper, after losing his way,
encountered Priest Gedatsu.
Who's there?!
It's all yours now!
Where did you go?!
Where am I?!
Yes, thanks!
Yikes!
I love it! It's so much faster!
Nothing personal.
I accept this survival challenge!
Yes. Jet Dials went extinct
hundreds of years ago,
"The Ordeal of the Swamp!
Chopper vs. Sky Punk Gedatsu!!"
"The Roaring Burn Bazooka!!
Luffy vs. War Demon Wyper"
How careless of me!
so I was shocked that the waver
you left with me had one onboard!
Is this guy an idiot?!
They each encounter enemies
and are drawn into battle.
But, what do we do now?
Among them, Chopper fought
and defeated Priest Gedatsu.
Damn him! He... He... killed Sanji...!
Just a little more...
We planned to lead you all
to the end of Skypiea, but...
Everyone will be so surprised
if I find the gold first!
Cloven...
Yeah.
...Cross!
For now, we need to get the ship
to the coast we agreed to meet at.
It's no use! His heart isn't
beating at all! Hey! Sanji!
I really think they're all right...
Sanji! Sanji!
Though, with those four together,
no one can stop them!
"Unbeatable Powers!
Eneru's True Form is Revealed"
Ruins up here, too...
Dammit! If only Chopper were here...!
There's no four-person group on the island.
Wait, Usopp!
Eh?
That's his right side!
At most, there's a two-person group.
The heart's on the left!
Oww!
A memorial for the very city itself...
If there were four people
moving together, I'd know!
"Right Side"
What's with this place?!
The ground's all crooked...
Yikes! It's beating!
I'll go around that way.
It's Mantra... The thing
God and those priests use?
Descendants built this after the city fell...
You alright, Kamakiri?!
Thank goodness! He came back to life!
Don't worry about me!
Pay attention to your surroundings!
I was born able to use it!
But he's seriously injured! He could die!
Gold! Gold!
What?! Oh crap! This is bad!
Shandora... That was this ancient city's name...
That's why I'm afraid...
Look!
I can see the cloud-covered Giant Jack!
You have no idea how scary
it is hearing voices disappear!
Wait. Wait, Holy.
Holy! Wait!
Are you gonna cry again?
The ruins of Shandora are near!
402 S.E.
I am not crying, you stupid Blue Sea person!
Eneru...
The city flourished over 1,100 years ago,
Eneru is at the top!
There's no need to be indignant.
It's been so long since we last met.
Her waver broke down, and we passed by
and it was 800 years ago when it fell.
just as a skyshark was about to attack her...
I got too carried away! I should've
just gone back! I'm going to die!
Why don't you cheer up a bit, Gan Fall?
What were you planning to do?!
That matches the "Blank Century"
that's missing throughout the world.
I don't know! But I can't just
sit around doing nothing!
You called?
You're the third one to make it here today...
This island might know
about the "unspoken history"
I'm right here.
Laki... Everyone...
H-Hey! What the hell did you do to Sanji?!
Eh?! Who're you?!
that's gone from the world below.
That spider-head is so careless!
Do you want something?
J-Just try something else! My 8,000
subordinates won't sit by quietly!
You killed Gedatsu, didn't you?
This is a complete map of Shandora...
I hope everyone's alright...
Warrior of Shandora, Kamakiri...
Perhaps I'll find more clues
about the "unspeakable history"
He means that guy from earlier!
Eneru! Damn you!
H-Here. If you run away now,
I'll forgive you. What do you say?
in the center of the city...
No, it's all right. Being rid of a
fool like him is best for the world.
Who do you think you're talking to?
Who's there?!
Why, hello there, cutie-pie.
I am God, you know.
Wouldn't you agree?
Are you another of God's henchmen?!
He... ran...?
You seem absolutely baffled
as to why I've appeared here.
Henchmen?
Watch your mouth.
Man, this is no good...
I am Yama, Divine Commander for God Eneru!
My bag's on the outside, and the
trees are all rotted and fruitless...
Mantra?!
So, what brings you here, Divine Commander?
Huh? I tripped over--
Damn you!
I don't need that to see what's
written all over your face!
I was so looking forward to
that boxed meal for breakfast...
Enough talk!
What a weird cave I wound up in.
I can't find the exit anywhere...
Though, I don't blame you.
Don't be so afraid. That's my
pet dog Holy. He won't bite.
Remain silent... and I will do nothing...
Normally, I wouldn't need to
bother doing anything personally,
but I happen to be a player in
this survival game, too, you see...
I wonder if everyone's
at the city of gold by now.
B-But this guy is lying here, all torn up...!
Got that?
I bet it's pretty, all made out of gold...
Plus, I will soon be leaving this land.
Holy is well-trained, so he
won't bite anyone recklessly.
Where did you disappear to?!
That reminds me, I once heard at
a bar that gold stew tastes great...
In fact, I just finished
saying goodbye to Gan Fall.
Good.
Eh?!
A concealment technique?!
I cut that man up.
Who is this guy?! What did he just do?!
Oh! His eyes are rolled back in his head!
You think this is a game?! Like hell it is!
That's even scarier! Who are you?!
That's so scary!
Just what are you thinking?!
You look like you really want to get rid of me...
--Who are you?
--My name is Ohm.
--You're scary!
--Just be silent!
Your men that I captured when we
invaded this island six years ago
Sure.
--He's too scary! I don't like him!
--I am saddened by the frailty of man.
Gedatsu-sama! You cannot see the
enemy with your eyes rolled back!
I've walked a long way.
Guess I'll have that lunch...
I will reward you for all
your hard work as a warrior,
Eh?
How careless of me!
are working very hard for me.
Why do people fight and rot,
despite knowing the transience of life?!
Is this guy an idiot?!
as an act of God's charity.
An enemy?! I guess so, huh?!
Are you... a priest?!
Not too shabby!
My Divine Squad...
Hmm... how does five minutes sound?
Who's there?!
What, now?
They're also very strong.
Truly great talent, they are.
I will sit right here for five minutes' time.
They're born to be happy, and
they desire happiness in life,
What?!
only to die in battle!
What's that supposed to mean?
Don't tell me you're after my food?!
I will neither dodge your
attacks nor strike back.
But it appears that their six years
of hard labor is nearing its end.
Indeed, I am! Heso!
My name is Sky Punk Gedatsu!
In which case, it would've been
best to do nothing from the start...
Go ahead and do your worst.
Well, forget it!
Such is the dilemma of
man's nature... It's so sad...
Priest of the almighty God Eneru!
Quit lookin' this way!
And as I'll no longer have any need
for this island once they're done,
Why, you...!
I am in charge of Upper Yard's "Swamp Ordeal"!
But, there is one path to salvation!
But, once those five minutes are up...
I thought I would come to
bid you farewell. That is all.
...you will come to learn what God is
from the bottom of your heart.
Say something, you jerk!
Everyone just needs to die!
What scary stuff is this
guy saying?! Unbelievable!
Quit following me!
Gedatsu-sama! He cannot hear you
unless you speak out loud!
Damn you!
Listen! I just ate all my food!
I don't got any more!
What have you come here for?
However, the denizens of
Skypiea are all ignorant fools.
How careless of me!
Is that something you normally forget?!
Time to die, Eneru!
Oh, I'm just looking for gold--
I wouldn't give you any, anyway!
Got it?! Now get lost!
Greed begets strife.
They only view this island
as a clump of Vearth, you see.
Eh?
Allow me to save you.
You had best watch your step!
This area is already my territory!
Walkin' all weird-like...
Which way are you even facing?!
You'll save me?
What do you mean?!
Damn you!
The reason we forcefully took this island away,
You wanna take me on?! Huh?!
We are surrounded by Swamp Clouds!
You missed!
Once you're caught by one,
there is no way to escape on your own!
Once dead, you will do-- and desire-- nothing.
the reason the Blue Sea flies
stepped foot onto this island,
Stop!
In three hours, only five of the 81
people on this island will be standing.
The survival rate here is 50%--
He doesn't plan to save me at all!
I said stop!
and the reason the Shandians are
intent on returning to their home
How careless of me!
--Nope!
Swamp?!
The "Swamp Ordeal"!
are not at all different.
Only one hour left until
the time I proclaimed is up...
You're sinking?!
In other words... there is but one
thing everyone seeks on this island!
I said stop it!
Current number of survivors... 25.
Fool! It has no effect on me!
They're unconscious!
Why?!
--So what?!
Swamp Cloud...
Why is everyone charred black?!
--These guys killed our brother Satori!
--Killed!
This can't be! What is God Eneru doing here?!
...Milky Dials!
It was because everyone desires
the great relics of Shandora,
They must pay!
It's almost as if they've been hit by lightning...
He's going down!
the legendary city of gold that
prospered in the Blue Sea long ago!
Why, you...!
Wow! Awesome!
Got an Impact!
Kamakiri...!
He's shooting stuff out of his feet to fly!
Gold? What is that?
Impact?!
Kamakiri!
Twenty-four left.
Peeyew! What is this...?!
L-Laki...?
So cool!
That's what I mean by ignorant!
Yes!
I stored farts in a Flavor Dial!
No one living here knows of gold, or its value!
Something came out of his hands, too...
Go... Go, Laki...
A single raccoon dog will be no trouble at all.
I see. So they have four types of dials...
Oh, my. You're nothing but talk, Missy...
But, Kamakiri!
Funnily enough, this game is the final battle.
Take this!
Wyper... is headed... for God's Shrine...
The winner of this survival game
will make the bountiful gold his own.
That's right!
Swamp Cloud Burger!
Axe! Flame!
Stomach Mountain!
Impact! Flavor!
With the weight of a cloud,
and the properties of a swamp!
But... Eneru isn't there!
Got those memorized?!
Once you touch it,
there is no hope for survival!
You can still stop him...
There's no way to distinguish us!
Which is Hotori, and which is Kotori?!
Can you hear it?
The sounds of the lively festival...
Gedatsu-sama! No! I'm not the one you're--!
Stop Wyper...
Which hand has what? It'll be fun to find out!
A runic statue!
All right! I understand! Save your breath!
Veinte Fleurs! Calendula!
Surprise Dial Illusion!
As a matter of fact, I'm a
participant myself, so I must be off.
We know what they have!
We cannot waste time!
No one... can beat him...!
He can't get it off!
I don't give a damn who's who!
I am lightning.
I see! It is a cloud! If you try to lift it,
your hands will just go through!
Wait, Eneru! The Divine Squad...
Are you going to free them?!
Here comes a typhoon!
--You missed!
How long are you going to keep
protecting this withered old city?
God only knows.
The more you struggle to get it off,
the deeper you're dragged inside...
He's... invincible...
Now, what dial is on my right hand?!
Wait, Eneru!
You don't seem to have any respect
for the vestiges of our ancestors.
He's lightning... which people have
feared as God... since long ago...
He disappeared...
Yet another fart! Dummies!
--I have to help him!
--There you are, raccoon dog!
Did you expect flames?!
Those are from my right hand!
I have no care for the past!
Usopp!
Swamp Cloud Burger!
Thank goodness! His heart
is still beating somehow...!
Fools always say that.
I'll stop Wyper! Wait here!
He's going to ignite the gas!
I'm going to leave Aisa's bag with you!
Yikes! If one of those hits me, I'm dead!
Who do you take me for?!
Weird knight!
Punch Mountain!
Hey! Are you all right?! Hang in there!
Fool! He got sent flying!
I need to move away from the ruins
Hey!
before this simpleton destroys it all!
Breathe!
Don't die!
Eh?!
No one... can beat him...!
He's... invincible...
Gum-Gum...
Thank goodness! You're alive!
Kamakiri is so strong...
yet his will has been broken!
That sounds like something a fool would think.
...Balloon!
I owe you my life...
You underestimated me...
The Rumble-Rumble Fruit!
Kotori!
To think that Eneru has the
powers of a Logia-type Devil Fruit,
Being saved by an enemy... Pathetic!
Back then, I thought my goal had been lost
the most powerful kind of all...!
Come back!
with the underground temple of Alubarna...
Uh oh!
I have to stop him quickly!
And you call yourself one of the 50
Skypiean Divine Soldiers who serve God?!
Cyclone Tempo.
Having lost everything,
I decided to travel with Luffy.
Try all you want, it's no use!
Not even cannons or guns work on me!
I think I recognize this place...
Or not... No, I do...
How dare you speak that way?!
You'll pay! I'll never serve you again!
But these ruins could hold clues
about the unspoken history
You... Girl...
that's been lost to the world below!
Apparently not.
Or not...
Finish him off with my gauntlet down below!
I'll make you prey for my Axe Dial!
So I'll change the style!
No, I do.
Weird knight! Did your wounds open?!
Does it just look similar?
Alright! We can do it! Let's fight together!
Never mind me! He'll be back soon!
Gauntlet?
Hey, you! You don't scare us!
Gauntlet... Gauntlet... Gauntlet?!
Did you laugh just now?!
Hey, what's a gauntlet?!
Very well. Jet Punch!
What? You're the one who
came along just to get food!
Whoa, it's heavy!
How far are you going to run?
It is made of Blue Sea iron.
This is what you get when you're
with me! Got a problem with that?!
There is an Impact Dial inside it.
Use it just as I explained.
Peeyew!
What's this smell?!
I think I understand, but I can't
use this thing, it's too heavy...
Gas is stored inside the
Breath Dial of this weapon,
You'll pay!
You idiot! Hey!
which is called a Burn Bazooka.
Hey...! Wait! There's no more food in there!
Guess this is no time to be worried about that!
The bluish flames that ride on the
expelled gas burn prey to a crisp!
The destructive Jet Dial!
First big brother Satori,
then little brother Kotori...!
Let go! Hey!
If you accelerate your punch with it,
Where are you flying off to?!
your opponent doesn't even
have time to feel his own defeat.
Not even praying will save you now!
He's the flame guy, right?
This is a crazy place I wound up in!
Though the fact that it
rips clothing is a problem...
He's sopping wet, plus the air is full of moisture!
Exit, exit, where is the exit? The exit! Hey!
This is a priest?!
Cool Ball!
Is this as far as you run?
I have to run with
everything I've got... or I'll die!
Huh? That's just cold. Is that it?!
Yep, that's it! You use fire, right?
Yes.
A dead-end?!
It's too late now.
What the...?! It went right
through that giant tree!
You're mocking me! Are you trying
to use this against my Flame Dial?!
No, stay off the clouds!
There are Swamp Cloud traps!
Too late?
You can't be serious, I walked all this way!
Even if you repent, I won't forgive you!
Huh?! He disappeared!
I gotta go on top of the ruins
and into the forest!
I'll burn you up!
Bastard! Where is he?!
Wait...
You won't forgive me? You certainly
do adore those shabby ruins.
Could it be a trick door?
Ah! I might be able to go
forward if I bust through it!
Where do you think you're going, raccoon dog?
Hot air flowing above collected
cool air causes moisture to condense!
Especially when they
don't even belong to you...
That's right. The ruins belong to no one.
Jet Punch!
Gum-Gum Bazooka!
Yes... It becomes fog!
Rumble! Jumping Point!
I don't feel like talking with you anymore.
Fog Tempo!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Don't worry. You won't have to anymore...
What the...?! Fog!
Rumble Balls last for three minutes!
Huh? It didn't even budge...
If I don't escape within
three minutes, I will be killed!
I can't see! What is this?!
...because you're going to
be crushed to death now!
So you have Zoan-type powers!
Gum-Gum Stamp!
Drop Mountain!
What... the...?!
You! What are you--?!
I can go all out here!
It's no use! Jet Punch!
Pardon me a sec!
Treinta Fleurs!
Impact.
Heavy Point!
What's going on?!
All you can do is rush forward like a bull...
Swamp Cloud Burger!
It's that!
Realize the weight of
the history you destroyed!
Guard Point!
Owww!
Hang!
My arm's coming off!
You insolent little...!
How could you make me
use this, you weird knight?!
Brain Point!
That was close!
He weighs so much!
It won't hurt for long.
But you did wonderfully, girl!
Scope!
Gum-Gum...
A weak point! Some sort of weak point!
...Spear!
Anything at all! I gotta find
an opening and escape!
Jet Punch!
Urgh...!
But... Yes! We protected the ship and crew!
Take this! 10-Axe Combo!
Axe Mountain!
If it's a bazooka you want,
you can't beat mine!
I even had my guard up...
Straw Hat!
Gum-Gum...
Burn...
Uhh, do you mind if I call you Aisa-san?
He's not following me...! Whew!
Can you really tell where the
Blue Sea folks' ship is headed?
--...Bazooka!
My eyes!
--Yeah...
--What a mysterious power...
What are you-- Huh?!
Being able to hear people in
the forest from this far away...
Wait! The dials... they're backwards!
Is he a priest too?
But are you all right?
You've been shaking for a while now!
Wait! The dials--!
There are lots of places to hide here.
I just need to escape and meet up
with Luffy and the others!
It's just...
What do you think this place is?!
Don't destroy the ruins!
It's just, I've never felt this afraid before.
Straw Hat!
He seemed like a swordfighter,
Everyone's voices...
so if I stay hidden and get
further away, I can escape!
Everyone's voices are
disappearing more and more...
Why don't you worry about yourself
instead of some ruins, Missy?
He's run quite a long way.
Yes, I'm sorry. Let's just hurry, Conis-san.
How foolish, running from salvation...
Punch Mountain!
What you went around destroying
were great, priceless treasures.
That itself is an attachment
to life, and an earthly desire...
That bastard!
Yes, Father.
Relics so rare it's impossible
to measure their worth.
Oh, no!
However...!
History may repeat itself,
but people can't go back in time.
Hold on! Where are you going, weird knight?!
Sorry, but I must follow Eneru.
You don't understand that.
What?! You're just gonna
leave a lady all by herself?!
You simpleton...
I... I understand...
Again, I am sorry.
I am curious as to why Eneru has
sprung into action at this point.
I won't ever... do it again...
Could it be...?
--Please forgive...
--I will not.
There are no means to survive on
the sad path to attaining peace...
Could it be what?
How far does this cave go?
When Eneru appeared, he captured
650 of my Divine Squad members.
I can't find any exits,
no matter how much I walk...
In that case... I just need to kill you!
This is the Iron Ordeal,
with a survival rate of 0%!
What's wrong, Straw Hat?!
There is no time to give the details,
but my men's lives are in danger.
Man, I'm hungry...
I know you haven't kicked the bucket yet!
But I don't see anything edible at all...
My fingers! My fingers!
I wonder what Chopper and
the rest are up to right now...
No, this entire land may be in danger...
Cien Fleurs!
Yeah! Of course I haven't!
Are they actually heading for the city of gold?
Can you fly, Pierre?
Delphinium!
Wait!
What the...?! Stop!
I will leave behind the Impact gauntlet.
Make do with that.
Wait! Where are you--
You can't be serious...
Another voice disappeared!
Hey, I said wait! You ingrate!
--Aisa?
--I can't just sit here! I'm going to find Laki!
Stop!
And you call yourself God?!
Hold it!
It's too late for that now...
Come back! Reconsider!
Stop! Don't!
Can't breathe...
Urgh!
What the...?! What the...?!
I said stop!
What's your problem?!
Let go! Let go of me! Let go!
Clutch!
I'll cry if you don't!
His feet...
This is none of your business!
I see... a weak spot...
What happened?!
Maybe not, but I can't just
leave a kid like you to die!
I'm a warrior!
Walk Point!
Where did he go?
Yes, yes, okay. Kid warrior.
For now, I need to give these guys first aid...
Just awful...
Can I escape? I can't see straight...
You're both alive, right?!
Your glares don't scare me.
No matter. This is no time
to be wasting energy on him.
Hurry back, Chopper!
You can still move?
What?! What?! What?!
I need to save some strength...
My legs are unsteady... And the
Rumble Ball is about to wear off...
Umm, are you all right?
...and make it to Eneru!
Just fine!
Here! There's no use struggling! Get on!
This should be the center of the city,
Urgh! No! Let go! I'm gonna
save everyone! Let go!
One more Reject, and my body
probably will be blown to bits.
Nami-san! Heso!
but it doesn't match up with
the map on the monument at all.
Conis?!
Did everything get broken up in
the shock of coming into the sky?
Knock it off or I'll slug you!
I'm coming for you, Eneru!
--Heso!
--Mister!
And no crying!
Even two of our crew
have already been done in!
What are you doing here?
I can't leave you alone!
Shut that horn up already!
Let go!
I don't get it... Then why did you come here?
Now hurry and get on.
How do ya like that?!
--Wait... No! You can't get off!
--Let go!
Damn it! We absolutely
won't let you go any further!
If you go any further in,
you'll never leave alive!
What one expects and what
one hopes are different things.
We agreed to leave right away!
Shut up! I'm after Eneru's head!
What I was seeking was the Rio Poneglyph.
Yes. It's time to stop running...
--Let go!
--No! --Who's she?
Out of the way!
Oh, this is Aisa...
The only "stone that tells the
real history" among the Poneglyphs
Stay away, Blue Sea scum! I'll eliminate you!
You can beat him!
that are scattered throughout the world.
I'm a warrior of Shandora!
So? You gonna fight me?
Don't make me Impact you.
Not another one!
That's the Rio Poneglyph...
You little...! What do you think you're doing?!
How terrible! They're both charred black!
They need first aid, quick!
No way!
What do you mean by the "real history"?
Swamp Cloud Burger!
In any case, I'm sorry. Set sail
along the new path we came on!
I have no business with
Divine Soldier small fries!
I give up... I've searched for it
for 20 years and I'm out of clues...
Everyone protects me
because I always run away!
Whoa, that scared me! What's with this cave?!
We used a Milky Dial to create a new river.
This place was my last hope... and a failure...
If you follow it, you can go
straight to the White-White Sea.
First there's an earthquake,
then a flood of sea clouds...
That's some rare ammunition you have there.
That's why they don't rely on me!
Heavy matter that doesn't
normally exist in the sky...
Dying here like this would
be a fitting end for me...
I'm going to raise a pirate flag right here!
Hurry, before the enemy spots us...
I almost drowned there!
Then couldn't you have come more quietly?!
Stupid thing! Open up!
Living like this has exhausted me...
The Vearth mineral, iron?
Oh, yes. I also have something for you.
Why is it so huge?!
For me?
All I want is to learn the history...
Darn you! Where's the exit?!
It seems you've taken down
many of my men, Shandian.
Sore loser. Even the air is my realm!
Do you still not get it?!
A waver!
I repaired the one you
brought from the Blue Sea.
Gum-Gum Gatling!
But there're too many enemies...
to achieve my dream...
You're Genbou, one of the main forces, yes?
Come!
Here. It belongs to you.
Wow! Really?!
Divine Commander Yama!
--Yes!
--Sweet!
Get out of my way!
Still, this waver turned out
to be really something.
Oh! He removed my shoe just now!
Nami-san! That leads into the forest!
--Eh?
--Its power is beyond comparison. Sorry.
Nami-san!
What do we do? They went into the forest...
Damn you and your insolence, raccoon dog!
Damn it!
I'm a monster! I'm strong!
You're tough!
The weakest beasts howl the most!
Jet Punch!
Damn you...
I-I refuse...
...to die in a place like this!
I lost my composure and control of my Mantra!
What's that?!
Oh! You're still alive. You're tough, indeed.
He grazed me! That was close!
--Who's that?!
--S-Something's coming!
Arm Point!
Very well. As a symbol of respect
for your determined spirit...
I'm alive!
Cloven...
Shoo! Go that way!
...I will finish you off with my secret technique.
...Cross!
Oh, you're still at it?
That's strange...
It's the Lord of the Sky!
This is the city of gold?!
Was that... Aisa?!
The size and topography
are all completely different.
10-Axe Combo!
And what's most unnatural of all...
Damn you, Yama!
Sorry. I must've dozed off there...
What's wrong? You seem to
be in pain, Kamakiri-kun...
Axe Mountain!
The only entrance is at the top...
Now I'm a pirate, too!
As I promised, I haven't done anything...
We're... inside the forest...!
Could it be?!
I... can't... beat you...?
It looks like he fell right into
a swamp! Thank goodness!
So close. You did well to make it this far.
Hey! Let me down! Are you listening to me?!
Don't come back up! Please, just keep sinking!
Yes, that's right.
You stupid bird! I oughta chop you up!
Now do you understand?
I am lightning.
He's moving!
What?! Who are you?!
How can a struggling man defeat lightning?
Huh?
Don't give us, "What?!"
He's still alive...!
As a native of the sky, you've surely
seen distant lightning before.
We're the Deputy Divine Commanders!
H-How stupid of me! I can't believe
that raccoon dog overpowered me!
How dare you kill our brother Satori?!
T-The giant snake! Hey!
Fly higher! Or we'll get eaten!
How dare you?!
I can go below!
Since ancient times, man has replaced
all his fear of nature with God
How careless of me! I'm sinking
into a swamp! I must escape!
What?! I don't know any brother of yours!
to flee from the terror
he could not comprehend,
Hurry it up! Hey!
Don't come back up!
Don't play dumb! My name is Hotori!
Sink! Sink!
with the belief that all supernatural
phenomena are acts of God
It's still coming after us!
It seems irritable for some reason...!
Escape! Milky Dial!
My name is Kotori!
beyond human understanding...
It's so vast... These ruins
really do go much deeper!
You guys killed our brother!
He really sank!
The disasters from the heavens,
How careless of me!
I told you, I don't know
what you're talking about!
I thought it was strange how Blue Sea ruins
which all of mankind
accepted as being unbeatable...
had Island Clouds for ground...
Satori was one of Eneru's four priests.
Y-Yes! I beat him!
They are me.
The ruins above are nothing more
than the upper parts of the city,
Now do you understand what God is?
eaten up by Island Clouds...
He guarded Illusion Forest.
How careless of me!
There's still more below!
Why, you little...!
Then, the priest Luffy
and the others beat was...
Another of the priests' voices disappeared...
Yes! Their elder brother!
Oh? A Breath Dial, huh?
See! You do know!
This is bad! I have to hurry to the others!
Burn Blade!
You must pay!
Pierre!
Huh? What's going on?!
A breakdown at a time like this?!
Come on, work! Work, you!
God's Shrine is at the top of this Giant Jack!
I can barely even ride it, much less fix it...
I must take care of them
and hurry after Eneru.
And Eneru is there!
There is no telling what he
might do to my subordinates!
I'm going to bring an end to the
past 400 years of terrible history!
Light?!
Here he comes.
I must tell Wyper!
There's no point in fighting him!
Stand back, girl! Even with my
injuries, I will not lose to them!
He'd only die in vain!
Even if he risks his life,
a Reject will have no effect!
No! Sometimes, even I...
Wyper... Climb that vine any further
and you'll reach God's Shrine.
So now you choose to run?
...have to protect these guys!
I gotta retreat and think! As things
are now... As things are now...!
H-Help!
Who gave you permission to pass?
Very well!
First, ascertain their dials!
Ohm!
Right!
800 years ago, the city
of Shandora suddenly fell.
Please! Stay away from me!
We're going to avenge our brother!
Did you think you could
move faster than lightning?
There is no longer any point
in heading for God's Shrine.
It hardly seems that way.
It's still so majestic and grand!
Gan Fall!
Father! Hurry!
Your five minutes are up.
I know! Hold on tight, Conis-san! Here we go!
What are you doing here?!
Now it's my turn.
This is Shandora, the city of gold!
Still attached to the position of God?!
Right!
No, but I've yet to finish taking responsibility.
1 Million Volts... Vaari!
I've just come from God's Shrine up above.
It finally stopped...
--Now, Conis-san!
--Right!
Here! Grab my hand!
Run! Wyper!
A tragedy... It was utterly destroyed...
Could it be?!
That was close...
You're safe now. You're a Shandian child, right?
Naturally, Eneru was nowhere to be found.
Perhaps it means he no
longer has any need for it...
Don't be afraid. We're...
Let me ask you a question...
Where am I?
I'm not afraid!
By any chance... can the
untold history be uncovered?
It appears that their six years
of hard labor is nearing its end.
I'm a warrior of Shandora!
I'm not afraid of you Skypieans!
What was that?
Are you saying that the
Poneglyphs hold that record?
Hey! Guys! Is anyone here? It's me!
I thought I would come to bid you farewell.
No!
Her name is Suu! I think she likes you!
If you're here, say something!
What?! What?!
What's going on, all of a sudden?!
What happened?!
Just what is it you people seek, Ohm?!
Suu?
I guess no one's here...
They wrote with the ancient
Poneglyph symbols so easily!
Their voices... are disappearing...!
Eneru isn't in God's Shrine, you say?!
Where?
My name is Conis.
But only the ones who made the
Poneglyphs could use these symbols!
Hello, my name is Pagaya. I'm sorry.
Where did it go?!
G-Gedatsu-sama. Y-Your eyes
are rolled inside your head.
What's your name?
"Hold our true motive in your
hearts and speak not of it.
Whoops. It seems the electricity
traveled along the Milky Road.
I'm Aisa...
I know you just saved me, but I
want you to take me to Upper Yard.
Y-You cannot see ahead of you like that.
We are the ones who weave history...
Twenty voices disappeared
after that discharge. Fools...
How careless of me!
With the sounding of the grand belfry..."
Have a look at this photograph.
Eh?!
Even as we speak, everyone's
voices disappear more and more...
One of Straw Hat's friends?!
Here it is. That puny creature.
That's right! Noland's logbook did
mention a giant gold bell here...
That took its toll...! That bird's gonna pay!
He's with the Blue Sea people!
It's the truth! I can hear voices,
even from far away...
The 81-man Upper Yard survival game...
It's you!
What? It isn't a raccoon dog?
All kinds of voices...
All of the city's writings were burned...
Two hours have passed.
Raccoon dog? No, it is not a wild animal.
What is this place?
Actually, we're headed for Upper Yard, too.
56 have dropped out.
It is unquestionably a
creature from the Blue Sea!
--Eh?!
--We want to lead the Blue Sea people
in Upper Yard to the end of Skypiea.
The city's history was eradicated!
Ruins?
Thirteen of God's army remain.
Luffy! Where are you?!
Zoro! Are you asleep again?!
Five of the Straw Hats remain.
You mean the guys on the ship?
Looks like we got us some
ferocious ones here...
Eh? Yes...
I think they're trying to
escape from the forest...
They'll manage somehow, right?
Robin! Hurry over here!
Hey, hand over the gold!
Seven of the Shandians remain.
Oh, my. How sad...
Do you know where their ship is?!
...given that none can
escape from my Iron Ordeal...
Where is everyone?!
That makes for a total of twenty-five left...
Yeah.
I'm feeling insecure!
Father!
If you're going to get in my way,
I'll eliminate you all!
Yes. I'm sorry. Please lead us there.
Hmm. There are more left than I expected.
Quit following me!
Hey! Guys! It's me!
Tell me where Eneru and the Divine Squad are!
A-Alright.
No matter. I'll corner
them all slowly but surely.
Now it goes down?
A Poneglyph was carried into the city!
Who will get to accompany me in the end?
What's going on with this cave?!
I'm finally a pirate! I think I'll look
for the gold instead of the others!
There's no question about it!
This city fought against hostility!
Where?!
I'm going to surprise them all!
Shandora, the city of gold, fought and fell
This necklace is made of gold!
trying to protect that Poneglyph!
That seems suspicious to me...
Is the gold we're looking for inside this cave?!
Well, I'm sure you gentlemen
have all sorts of things to say,
Who knows? Maybe everyone
is already up there...
In which case, the grand belfry
located in the center of the four altars
Where did you go?!
but if you want to make yourselves heard...
...you'll need to survive here first!
I'd rather be inside a yakiniku shop right now...
might contain the "text of real history"...
Yikes! W-What is this?!
The Rio Poneglyph!
Geez!
Where am I?!
Racing full speed ahead as always
A to Z, we run through it
We all have worries and fall many times
But we just need to rise to the top someday
What could be beyond the sea
in which the morning sun rises?
Let's go little by little toward
the brilliantly shining sun
I never treat you "bad"
How many times did we fall?
It's all right, we're definitely
pointing at tomorrow now
Smile! Come back to you, friends
Come back to you, friends
Hey, you stupid bird! Where're you taking me?!
Damn! What's with this cave?! Where's the exit?!
Whew, I'm hungry!
Are you a priest?!
It seems that it's getting a
little busy in the Upper Ruins...
This area is already my territory!
All around us are Swamp Clouds!
Are there any yakiniku shops? I guess not.
What's with this cave?! Where's the exit?!
--What are you doing there?!
--Seriously! What, did you get lost?!
What is it you're after?! Where is Eneru?!
There is no escape!
Are you all right? You've been
shaking for a while now.
Yikes! The giant snake!
It seems irritable for some reason!
The situation in the sky is not
our concern! Hand over the gold!
Yeah! Everyone protects me
because I always run away!
--Same goes for you!
--What?!
Aah! Why is this snake coming after us?!
Man, I'm hungry!
I've never felt this afraid before.
You're all in my way! You can all... die together!
That's why they don't rely on me!
Will you people be able to live
through this survival game?
Huh? Looks like we got us
some ferocious ones here...
I'm going to raise a pirate flag
right here! I'm gonna beat him!
Everyone's voices are
disappearing more and more...
Seriously, where am I?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Mystical City! The Grand Ruins of Shandora!!"
"Climb Giant Jack!!
Deadly Combat in the Upper Ruins"
"Unbeatable Powers!
Eneru's True Form is Revealed"
"0% Survival Rate! Chopper vs. Ohm,
the Sword Wielding Priest"
"The Ordeal of the Swamp!
Chopper vs. Sky Punk Gedatsu!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!