Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King
of the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
The horizons everyone
dreamed of were separate at first
but now they can be seen
through a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny
is leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve
your dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
"Upper Yard" "Angel Island"
The survival battle in
God's Land, Upper Yard, continues.
God's Island, Upper Yard...
"Upper Yard" "Angel Island"
God's Land, Upper Yard...
In the ruins that spread around Giant Jack,
In the Upper Ruins,
Zoro clashed against Priest Ohm.
Priest Ohm, who serves God Eneru.
The nightmarish survival game
continued to rule over this land.
men clashed against one another.
Wyper, a Shandian warrior.
Three-Sword Style!
Eisen Whip!
Gan Fall, the Sky Knight.
One-hundred-eight Caliber Phoenix!
And Zoro.
My guess was that there'd be five survivors.
Their fierce battle for survival has started.
As this fierce battle for survival rages on,
Now, who will die?
Around the time that Nico Robin
finally found the city of gold, Shandora,
Laki, a female Shandian warrior,
falls at the hands of God Eneru.
Luffy and the others were inside
Chopper encountered
Priest Ohm in the Upper Ruins...
Ahhhh... That idiot...!
You die!
the stomach of the giant snake,
who was playing with Wyper.
Aisa!
...and sadly fell by his hand.
How insolent!
You're idiots who can't
even protect yourselves.
Laki!!
Meanwhile, Nami, Gan Fall and Aisa,
who were swallowed by the giant snake,
There are no means to survive on
the sad path to attaining peace.
After finding the ruins
of Shandora, the city of gold,
Quit worrying about others!
"Showdown in the Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!"
met someone they never
expected to see in its stomach.
Nico Robin encountered God Eneru.
At any rate, no one will survive!
This is the Iron Ordeal,
with a survival rate of 0%!
And Conis has come to know
God Eneru's horrifying secret.
No!!
"Bursting Slash! Zoro vs. Ohm!!"
Skypiea will be dropped into the Blue Sea!
There!
Where's the exit?!
Ah!
This nation will disappear!!
"The Ordeal of Iron!
White Barbed Death Match!!"
Hey, this house...
You remember that pretty lady who
often played the harp at the beach, right?
Meanwhile, at Giant Jack's Upper Ruins,
Yes, I know her very well.
four of the survivors were about
to engage in a fierce new fight.
That's our Ohm-sama!
Pagaya-san and his daughter,
Conis-san, live here.
The survivors in the Upper Ruins
are four Divine Soldiers.
Dammit! The one I have to beat first is...!
Father!!
Both of them are very nice people.
Since those two are probably still alive,
They treated me to lunch once.
Did it work?!
that makes four Shandians
and one Blue Sea person.
Well, that woman was actually a
bad person. And her father, too!
Seems like it wasn't enough!
Then I'll just keep trying!
One giant snake and Holy...
What?!
I heard it, too.
If I'm not mistaken, they helped
bad people from the Blue Sea.
In other words, ten people and two animals.
What is this place? Ruins?
It'll be five survivors soon,
just like God prophesied.
Looks like we got us
some ferocious ones here.
Can't be...!
"Collapsing Upper Ruins!
The Quintet for the Finale!!"
That's true! They're really bad
people who went against God.
Now, let's continue the battle, shall we?
Hey! Hand over the gold!
Damn! That extendable sword
this priest uses is a pain!
Oh, my. How sad...
I'll finish you off.
My father said so, too!
Y-Your father did? I see...
...given that none can
escape from my Iron Ordeal...
Ohm! You bastard!
How dare you harm Wyper?!
When that snake is the one I have to beat first!
Oh, come to think of it, your father is...
If you're going to get in my way,
I'll eliminate you all!
Oh? Even when this man is
but a speck in God's eyes,
Yes, my father is a member of the
Divine Squad, so he's been serving God.
I have to get Nami and the
weird knight out right away.
Tell me where Eneru and the Divine Squad are!
he is that important to you?
Well, they were swallowed whole,
so they probably didn't die outright.
Wyper is our leader!!
My mother always tells me
that he'll come home soon,
We've shared the Shandians' pride!
What's going on with this cave?!
but I've never even seen his face.
But it's just a matter of time before they do.
In order to take back our
homeland that was taken away!
Oh, but he works for God.
You have a wonderful father.
Eisen Whip!
Eneru's servant can't
understand the Shandians' bond!
Well, I'm sure you gentlemen
have all sorts of things to say,
Another one!
Really?!
Of course you do! I hope you'll
be able to see your father soon.
but if you want to make yourselves heard...
Well, even if I understood it,
I wouldn't feel sympathy or empathy.
...you'll need to survive here first!
Yeah!
In other words...
...it's all for naught!
"Climb Giant Jack!!
Deadly Combat in the Upper Ruins"
Die, Ohm!
That bastard... Where is he?!
Skypiea will be dropped into the Blue Sea!
Eisen Whip!
This nation will disappear!!
I can't let that man's feelings be wasted!
You can't escape my attacks...
That said, the time prophesied
by God is fast approaching.
I must... I must tell them at any cost!
Are you running away?!
...just as no one can ever
escape the reality of death.
It's the climax. Holy, it's time for that!
So you can't possibly survive.
Just accept your destiny.
Prophesied?
If you did not want anything,
you could have lived longer.
But I guess I'm just wasting my breath,
since you probably don't have enough
sense to realize you're about to die.
Father...
You might as well repent your
sinful life with all your heart.
You're telling me to die?
Realize your foolishness!
Ha! So I take it you're one of those
priests or whatever that serves God?
You're a small being who is very anxious
about the gold before your eyes,
Listen to yourselves.
Things like God or
prophecies don't interest me.
Dash, Holy!
and cannot see your inalterable fate.
Right now, my only business
here is taking the gold.
How sad...
Dangerous... That guy's dangerous!
I'll forgive that, too.
Huh?
Suu...
Your only salvation lies in the fact
Where is he? Where the heck is he?
That's just what you'd expect
from the game's survivors.
that no one can escape from my Iron Ordeal.
However, it seems you don't
realize who you're talking to.
Where will he attack from next?
There's no time to lose!
Eisen Whip!
I'll save you all.
Eneru is... Eneru is...
What's he doing now?!
...planning to eliminate
everyone living in the sky!!
Dammit! What's that dog
doing?! This is trouble!
Hmph! You sure like to talk high and mighty.
What's going on?!
Why does he know where I am?!
It seems that you still don't
understand the existence of God.
This surely is... the Iron Ordeal's true form!
Let's go, Holy. You can get as wild as you want.
It's as if he can see me from behind the wall!
The white barbed death match!
Just what is that horn-shaped
sunglass-wearing freak?!
He is our target, Pierre.
Skypiea will be dropped into the Blue Sea!
We have to stop Eneru's priest first!
An old fool who wishes
happiness for Skypiea...
Fence or no fence, I'm not running away.
Die, Blue Sea person!
This nation will disappear!!
A warrior who single-mindedly
desires his "homeland"...
I have no business with you!
It's no time... to cry...
And thieves from the Blue Sea,
who are after the gold...
You fool! It's not just so
you can't run away anymore!
You're surrounded by the white barbs!
There's no time... to lose...
There are many hardships in this world,
so I don't care what my lambs wish for...
But to think that giant snake
Another voice has disappeared.
ended up all the way up here...
So what?!
I have to do... what I can do!
...but this nation has a fundamental problem.
In other words...
The survivors in the Upper Ruins are now...
I have to... let people know!
...five people... and two animals.
Dammit!
If you have time to spout such nonsense,
tell me where the Divine Squad is!
This place doesn't break.
It just goes horizontal and vertical.
...once you touch it, you'll get hurt!
No...
Eisen Whip!
Just what is your goal?!
This cave is messed up!!
So where do I get out when
I'm done with you all?!
Prepare yourself, Ohm!
Take care of those two, Suu!
The return of His Majesty, Gan Fall.
It's four people and two animals.
You can think about that when you're done.
Because I have to go take care of something...
The return of His Majesty?
You can all...
That's right. After his visit,
God returns to his rightful place.
Hm?
...die together!!
Two-Sword Style...
I'll tell them at any cost!
I swear I'll give the message you
risked your life for to the islanders!
Eight more people and two animals left!
...Hawk...
Return?! Are you saying
that you're leaving Skypiea?
Eisen Back!
...Wave!
Wh-What?! An iron wall!
I'd better do something
about that giant snake first.
That's right. I've got a place to return to.
This sword is Iron Clouds!
Nami's in it... and...
It is a place regarded as God's home
by the people on the
sky island where I was born.
That's one pesky weapon you've got there!
You Blue Sea people don't know anything!
Sky Knight!!
What's he...?
You think clouds have a set shape?
People call that place "Endless Vearth."
...so's the guy who saved Chopper.
There's nothing here for you,
who just came to the sky!
You son of a...!
There, the ground extends
as far as the eye can see!
Eisen Fan!
It took longer than I thought.
I'm not about to figure out
every one of your problems!
Eisen Fork!
Does this mean that I still need more training?
That is precisely the dream world that I seek!
Eisen Fleuret!
In any case, it's gotten quiet.
The situation in the sky is not our concern!
Wyper...
This Endless Vearth is a land befitting me!!
When we were small, you told me...
That figures!
Wait!
This isn't good! I can't avoid it! Why is that?!
Fighting over Upper Yard...
such small Vearth... is a petty triviality.
I was going to eliminate you
from the start! No skin off my back!
He's reading my movements!
Huh?
So this dog listens to anyone?!
What's the matter?!
Die!!
Our ancestors originally lived in the Blue Sea...
You depend on your swords,
so keeping a distance does you no good.
Knock yourself unconscious!
Not quite!
...in the sacred city, Shandora.
Listen. The root of your
conflicts lies in a deeper place.
This guy's tougher than I thought.
The Great Warrior Calgara
protected our homeland.
Thirty-six Caliber Phoenix!
Now I have to take care of
that snake and the bazooka guy.
But 400 years ago...
Think about it carefully!
I'd better hurry up!
Eisen Whip!
There isn't time for a long fight. Die already!
It was born in the sky, though it's not a cloud.
...Shandora was shot up to
Skypiea by the Knock-Up Stream.
It lives in the sky, though it's not a bird.
It's gonna be repelled!
Die!!
They could never go back to the Blue Sea.
A nation rooted in the sky... This nation
itself is an utterly unnatural existence!
It must've been very tough for them.
You're an eyesore! Why don't you just die?!
But Skypieans took over the land,
calling it "sacred ground"!
Soil has a place to return to.
So do people and God.
D-Don't tell me you...
Dammit!
Tsk! To think that it isn't hurt
at all after taking so many hits...!
Our ancestors were driven
out of their homeland.
That's quite an interesting
technique, Blue Sea person!
We can't go back to our sacred city.
It's nothing you should be surprised about.
We aren't even allowed to touch
the ground of our homeland!
Sorry, but you'll have to die!
That's right... He's got poisonous fangs!
As God, I'm only adhering to...
yes, the province of nature.
But are you going to try that again?
For 400 long years, we, Shandians,
have suffered humiliation!
Even if you lose sight of me,
I can know exactly where you are...
That's right. I will drag down
every human from this sky!
This one's got fangs, too!
Even that didn't work?! Dammit!
Those are some hard scales!
That Upper Yard belongs to us!
...by using Mantra.
What's with this dog's moves?!
We will take back... our homeland...
Are you planning to wipe out this nation?
His name is Holy.
Man...! What the hell is going on?!
I'm warning you. I'm a stockbreeder in
the sky, in other words, a Sky Breeder!
...as well as our ancestors' pride!
What the hell are they doing
to the snake out there?!
That's just natural.
Hey! Someone help! Hey!
Once we defeat Eneru, we won't need
to revere a single bag of Vearth.
My animal training goes
beyond ordinary training.
Don't be conceited, Eneru!
The term "God" is just a title used
to refer to the leader of this nation!
I hammered bipedal walking
and then even boxing into him.
We're going back. To the 400-year-old
homeland of the Shandians!
Nami'd better still be alive!
Yes, up until now, anyway.
Savor his attacks thoroughly!
The real "God" does not
live in the human world!
Those who aren't prepared,
stay here. I won't blame you.
There's such a thing as going too far.
Wh-What did you just do?!
Sh-Shandian warriors aren't
intimidated by a mere dog!
C'mon, Wyper! We're always prepared!
I bestowed mercy.
Former God, Gan Fall...
A pitiful worm was in great pain, so I
saved him by releasing him from it.
Are you prepared to abandon
anyone who falls during the fight?
Gan Fall...
You were worried about the
Divine Squad, weren't you?
You were beaten by someone like Shura.
Haven't you learned a lesson?
Those who can step over comrades
and keep moving, come with me!
It was my duty as God.
You probably can't even wield
your spear any longer, can you?!
It seems that the young woman
is still behaving desperately,
Six years ago, you lost against my forces,
You old fool!!
Another one disappeared...
and I took your 650
subordinates under my charge.
but that's perfect entertainment for the party.
Yet I can't withdraw!
Today... Eneru's head will be mine!
Now there're three people
and two animals left...
Because I don't know what you
and the others are going to do!
They can all realize what despair is.
Just this morning, they finished the
work I asked them to do on this island.
Wyper!
Hmph! Don't be conceited!
This man... has Logia Power!
Even if you knew, someone
like you wouldn't be able
I told you, didn't I?
...although it'll soon be
two people and two animals.
Now, we are running out of time.
The only ones who are standing on this
island right now are the six of us here.
to understand God's noble thoughts!
Let's settle this, shall we?
Such a shame...
Y-You...
My ultimate plan will start soon, as well, so...
It's not that I wanted to harm them.
It seems that you're the axis
of the Blue Sea people group.
Ultimate... plan?
After them! After the Shandians!
When I told them my goal...
You and your comrades all fought well.
God is calling you!
...they challenged me with
angry looks on their faces!
However, I've already taken aim at your heart.
Come to me, lowly beings!!
What, what? What was that?!
I heard, "Meh." Goats?
They're Divine Soldiers!
If we get caught, we'll be killed!
They all have family on Angel Island!
Pray to God, swordsman from the Blue Sea!
What're Divine Soldiers?!
Yes, I know. I have to bury
their families soon, too.
Shango!!
They're Eneru's underlings!
Hurry up and get out of here!
Wyper!!
You fool! I'll never pray to God!
W-Wait! But where're we headed?!
How sad...
I'm glad I found you!
Are you...
What the...?!
The difference among people
is if they die sooner or later.
Laki!
Wyper! Listen to me!
Just do want you want.
What's that?!
...a devil?!
Why did you come here?!
I've had enough of your arrogant lecture!
That's Giant Jack!
Eneru's shrine is probably above there!
I came here to give you Kamakiri's message!
Although I can't see you,
Eneru's shrine?!
that extendable sword of yours
will tell me where you are!
What're you...?
No one can... defeat him...
Hmph! The moment you find out
will be the moment you die!
I invited your friends here... to Shandora!!
Get out of here, Wyper! Don't fight!
The past held 36 worldly desires.
--Wyper!
--What?!
I sense Wyper over there!
Five million... ten million... twenty million...!
The present holds 72 worldly desires.
This man's ability... What tremendous power!
He's alive!
The future will hold 108 worldly desires!
Weren't we...
We can see Giant Jack!
Eneru is in the forest!
Don't let them go to God's Shrine!
Three-Sword Style!
One-hundred-eight Caliber Phoenix!
Hey, Laki!
Weren't we the evil ones?
Eneru is lightning itself, which people
have feared as God since long ago.
Quit pestering us!!
The Shandian warriors...
They attack God's Island, Upper Yard,
The ground broke into pieces!
Don't come near here! Get out of here!
The iron clouds were repelled!
It's Eneru! He's the only one
who'd do something like this!
only because they want to get back
the homeland of their ancestors.
There's no way we can defeat him!
Hey, stop it!
This isn't good, I've gotta...
Are you thinking about that again, my Lord?
Wyper...?
Please look at the blessed
lives of people in Skypiea.
Chopper!
It all started when our ancestors
took away Upper Yard 400 years ago.
That damn snake! It keeps gettin' in my way!
You called me?
Isn't it our duty to carry on this battle
and protect that blessing for this nation?
Eneru...
What the hell...?! There's a hole below!
I'm sure we've tried to
negotiate as much as possible.
Those who cannot understand it do not
deserve your compassion any longer.
Stop it, Eneru! Don't!
She abandoned the battle!
Hey, Chopper?!
Let's start the finale!
400 years...
Hey! Why're you...?!
Hey!!
The time for us, or for them,
to accept defeat may have long passed.
Laki!!
I see... He was part of the
group from the Blue Sea.
I'll fly out of here.
Hey, be careful going over there.
Eww! Eww! Eww! Eww!
Laki! Don't fight him!
Yeah! This could go on forever!
Laki!
Luffy! Hold onto the waver!
Run!!
I'm gonna fire up the engine!
Hey, you! Hold onto me!
Enemy Attack! Enemy Attack!
What was that?!
A dead end!!
Barbed wire?!
Okay! I'm ready, Nami!
Here we go!
Gum-Gum... Balloon!!
So that's the ordeal...
I can finally get out!
Chopper! Hey, Chopper!
You fool! Don't think you can survive
while you're worrying about others!
Say something! Why did you come
to a place like this alone?! Hey!
What?! What are they doing?!
Pierre, go back! We have to save those two!
Such a shame...
Man... This mystery cave is a horrible cave!
Is this an attack by the Shandians?!
I-It's not the Shandians!
Like I said, this isn't a cave!
We're inside the snake's stomach!
What do you mean?!
They're "Iron Clouds."
A man who calls himself God Eneru...
They're light as clouds and hard as iron.
He's... invincible...!
Oh, Nami, you're okay...
God Eneru?
Who could he be to call himself
God in front of His Lordship?
Nami!!
They're blown into shape by a milky dial.
H-Hey! Aren't we falling?!
He's lightning... which people have
feared as God... since long ago...
Hey, Nami! Hang in there! Nami!
Each one is connected to
some part of the ground.
Ahh! We are dropping fast!!
Pierre, don't worry about us.
Go help those two inside!
When you step on it, it gets discharged.
I'm over here!
On this field, you never know when and
where they'll be activated to strike you.
Let me go! Are you gonna
squeeze me to death?!
Wh-What're we gonna do, weird knight?!
I got you, Wyper!
So you're okay...
That animal was partially defeated by me,
If we don't do anything,
we'll crash into the ground!
My name is Gan Fall. It's Gan Fall!
but he also became a victim
of the ordeal on his own.
Who cares about that right now?!
Wh-What're you doing, Aisa?!
You fool!
Th-This is...
He's our enemy! An enemy who
took away the Shandians' homeland!
Divine Squad, huh?
They weren't as strong as I expected.
No!!
I'll take his head!
So you are...
So do you want to get
revenge now or something?
Get out of here!
Well, you should at least acknowledge
that they were loyal to God.
No.
I don't really like fighting
for that sort of reason.
What's the point of taking the
head of the weird knight here?!
Eneru!
So you're God? No, former God, I guess.
Oh? Isn't that something?
Before Eneru showed up, he was
the leader of the Skypieans!
How dare you...?!
--But...
--Hm?
The Skypieans, who drove us
Shandians out of our homeland!
I'm getting a little fired up.
That was 400 long years ago, right?
It wasn't him who did it.
Ruins?
If your people would be satisfied by
taking my head, I'd gladly give it to you.
Why have this many pieces fallen from above?
But the way things are now, taking my
head alone wouldn't settle things,
Eneru!!
Oh? It didn't work on him?
--Swordsman!
--This is not my day!
as the hostility between the Shandians
and Skypieans does not change at all.
Eneru-sama, what are we going
to do with this old former God?
Then, I'll give you another shot!
Don't tell me you fell all the
way down here with these...
Just throw him in the sea or something.
Our ancestors took your homeland
away from you, Shandians.
I'm sorry. This is the
right place, right, Conis-san?
Dammit! I almost died!!
He probably couldn't even
be used for manual labor.
You're softer than I thought.
The seashore where they're
planning to meet up...
Yeah, that's what happens... to normal people.
I cannot find a way to
apologize for that action.
At any rate, this is quite a nice shrine.
Yes, Father. Nami-san told me so.
Wyper, Shandian warrior!
But what we need is the Divine Squad.
Oh, it's you.
Time passes by while I
continue to remain helpless.
Even if she's a woman, she's still a warrior.
But what should we do?
I'll have them work very
hard as my subordinates.
I treat all those that challenge me equally.
Where am I?
I didn't expect that we'd
have to look after the ship.
It's the city of gold that you were looking for.
I am powerless.
We have to protect it at any
cost until they come back!
They are my subordinates.
Well, try your best not to die.
I see. So this is the place.
If possible, I would like
to apologize one by one
"Knight"
It doesn't look much different
from the one that was up there.
Quiet! You are not "God" any longer!
Shall we sound the horns
to scare off the enemy?!
to all Shandians who died in seeking
their homeland in the past 400 years.
So did you find the treasure?
Yes, Father! It'll be reassuring!
No, there was no gold here.
This will do.
20 million volt...
I am sincerely sorry.
The weird knight has been trying very hard
so that everyone that lives in the sky
...Vaari!
Would you stand watch over there, Suu?
That's... God?!
can get along and live peacefully.
Weird knight!!
And yet, if you...
Old man!
We can't get along and live peacefully!
With bad guys!
God exists in this world.
They're not bad guys!
Nami-san, you said a promise...?
How mortifying...!
What's bad is when one race
refuses to coexist with another!
Luffy and the others went into
the forest for some little thing.
That God... is me!
Phew... This giant snake
went really crazy, didn't it?
Am I wrong?!
We're meeting up at the seashore in
the northwest, so I have to go there...
We're back where we were!
Do you think they're okay?
Things are terrible in the forest right now.
Are you stupid?
Who'd hold onto the waver's jet?!
A Devil Fruit's Power?!
It's probably the Rumble-Rumble Fruit.
If I'm not mistaken,
among the many kinds of powers,
Man, what a foolish woman,
I hope they're okay.
Sorry.
Don't worry.
Everyone else made it outside!
We've been left behind! It's all your fault!
insolently attacking God.
it's one of those said to be "invincible."
Our crew will be fine!
She received divine punishment.
The power of lightning!
--Don't worry!
--What're you gonna do?
Before I get out of here, I have
to take care of something.
Well, why don't we hurry up
and plop out from its butthole?
Aisa!!
Lightning... There's no way
that humans can defeat him!
You giant snake!
I don't want to do that!
Okay! I'll do my best to take care of you!
Please hang on, both of you!
I have business with your stomach!
Don't stand in my way!
Well, it's exactly the time that I prophesied.
--Oh, it's the horse!
--That's a bird!
Wh-Why did you stop me?! You idiot!
Holy! Shake hands!
Now...
Huh? Are you saying to get on your back?
He's apologizing, so there's no
need to take his life, is there?
...there are five! I'm glad you've survived!
Please everyone... be safe...
Eisen Whip!
I'm sorry that the sky island is like this.
Axe!
Ahh! The bird has become a horse!!
Now, I shall bring you along with me!
To the dream world that I'm setting off to!
Ahh! Your hands stretched!!
Head to God's Shrine!
To the Endless Vearth!
I shall bring you along with me!!
I ate a Gum-Gum Fruit
and became a rubber person,
Now's the time to get Eneru's head!
so of course I can stretch my arms!
The city of gold, Shandora...
Six people and two animals left!
What?!
Wh-What are you?!
The golden bell that must've been in the
center of the city isn't here any longer...
There, I will build an
indisputable "Nation of God"!
Don't let them go to God's Shrine!
A pirate! Now, let's go!
Climb up Giant Jack!
The belfry for that bell might've
had Poneglyphs engraved on it.
The only ones who can live there
are the chosen ones here.
Hold on tight, okay?
Okay...
Alright! We'll break out this time for sure!
What's that guy talking about?
If this city fell in order to protect
the Poneglyphs, as I suspect,
Those subordinates of mine,
who couldn't even handle
Wyper! Don't use Reject anymore!
Go! Horse!!
Full speed ahead towards the exit!!
Divine Soldiers! Come back!
Stop the Shandians!
a short survival game,
will only lower the nation's stature.
it should still be hidden
somewhere even now...
The belfry with the
Poneglyphs engraved on it...
And... What if we refuse?
Ow, ow...
If that's the case, where could it be?
Ow, ow, ow...
--Robin!
--Refuse?
Good. Looks like she wasn't seriously hurt.
Oh? This is... a rail for lorries.
Thanks, weird knight!
Don't challenge Eneru, Wyper!
Why? It was decided by God.
If you stay here, you'll fall into
a bottomless pit with this nation!
It was fortunate that we landed on clouds.
Where on earth...?
Something was taken out from here.
We left Luffy and Aisa behind.
I wonder if they're okay.
It's probably true that with
your power, you can do that.
We can't... We can't defeat Eneru! Never!
We're in the snake's stomach.
It's still new... I wonder what was taken out.
Trust Pierre. When push comes to shove,
he's a reliable bird, or horse...
We were swallowed!
But if you thoughtlessly destroy this nation,
Oh, that's right. It seems
to be quite a long stomach.
isn't the thing you want going to fall as well?
Isn't it amazing? Even after
being shot up to the sky,
Say, where on earth are we?
Hey, Aisa, are you all right?
this city, Shandora,
still majestically exists like this.
You mean the golden bell?!
It seems underground, location-wise...
That's right.
W-Wyper, I'm sorry!
Golden bell?
...but I have never seen
this place. Where on earth...?
The golden bell...
Huh?
Even if it's a legendary city,
if it's covered by clouds,
You needn't worry. I already have some idea.
What is this place?
Thanks.
it can't even show off its figure.
Inside the snake's stomach.
That's right.
In any case, to think that there
was a place like this in Upper Yard...
Pay more attention! You're so slow.
If I recall the actions you took,
there is only one possible place.
I'm the one who found it.
Everyone... climb up to the Upper Ruins...
Snake's...?!
Now, let's get out of here
before its stomach melts us.
Those stupid former Gods
didn't even notice this city.
...and kill each other.
I wonder if the waver still works.
Who're you?
In any case, why aren't you on the ship?
Is it possible... that this place is...
There will be five survivors.
God...
We were chased and had no choice but to run.
Well, more importantly,
isn't that girl Shandian?
I'm pretty sure that I'm thinking
of the same place that you are.
You're pretty good.
God's prophecy is absolute.
...the homeland of the Shandians?!
It seems like you're an
archaeologist from the Blue Sea.
Wha...?! God!
It took even us several
months to find these ruins.
You seem surprised.
I'll eliminate you!
Did you think you'd be able
to outwit me by saying that?
Hey! Stop it!
If you can read the letters on the ruins,
you can find this place that easily?
How foolish...
Stop it, Wyper! I am...
Robin!!
However, the gold you're
looking for isn't here any longer.
"I am" what?! You want to say
that you're not my enemy?!
I hate calculating women.
You're a few years late.
Light the fire of Shandora!
To us, you and Eneru are the same, Gan Fall!
Anyway, can't we break
through this stomach wall?
Gold?
In the name of the Great Warrior Calgara!
Come to think of it, I can't find any.
It must be you who took it out from here.
Are you nuts?! What're we gonna do
if irritating it makes it go wild?!
So you won't listen, huh?!
Light the fire of Shandora!!
Do you wanna die?! Try to use your head more!
Gold is a nice thing.
That glittering metal suits me well.
O-Oh, that was a joke.
We're going back!
No...
To our homeland!
Then, you took the golden bell
that used to be here, too?
Are you crazy?!
You're really weird, weird knight!
You son of a bitch!
To our homeland!!
Golden bell?
Geez...
So this is the place that we've been seeking!
He doesn't know?!
If there's someone who'd
seriously try to irritate this snake,
The proud city that our ancestors protected!
I'd like to meet 'em.
Shandora!!
That's interesting. What did you
learn by reading the letters?
Burn Bazooka doesn't work...
What kind of scales does it have?!
She's a woman!
This sound...
I can see that.
No... Unfortunately, if it wasn't
here when you first came here,
It's footsteps.
I... I can't take this cave anymore!!
it didn't come to the sky after all.
It looks like it's looking for something...
What could be in a place like this?
The huge golden bell that
Shandora took pride in,
...or maybe Luffy's doing
something inside again?
Who is it?!
and the large belfry for that bell...
I needed to see the belfry.
You've got good skills.
Are you... a nutjob?!
The giant snake is acting strange.
No, wait... Yes! It's here. It's here in the sky!
Ha! It is a dog, after all. As we
move around, I'll find an opportunity.
When this island was blown
into the sky 400 years ago...
It's crying!
Burn Bazooka!!
Nami! Weird old man!
What's the meaning of this, Lord of the Sky?
in other words, on the day that
God's Island, Upper Yard, was born,
You...
What are you so worked up for?
Luffy!
it's said that the loud chimes of a bell
rang throughout the entire nation...
Kari!
What're you doing?!
In a mystery cave like this?!
What an annoying snake!
How foolish...!
What are you doing in a place like this?!
I couldn't get out of this place.
El Thor!
I can't believe it!
To think that you were
swallowed by the snake too...
...although old people in this nation
call it the island's singing voice.
So the others are okay, right?!
Aisa!
C-Can't be! He erased the
bazooka's powerful fire!
Dammit! Nami!
Huh? I'm by myself.
She won't survive that!
I see! That bell was made of gold! Wonderful!
What?! Snake?!
What did you just...?
You still don't get it, do you?
That's right. That's why we're here!
Oh? Zoro! Robin, too!
Hmph! This is why Blue Sea
people get on my nerves.
The energy that you can
handle is nothing to me.
Oh, I see... That must've been terrible.
You were there?! When did you
get out of that snake's stomach?!
Soon the game will be over.
Eight more minutes to go.
This sword is also made of Iron Clouds.
So, you guys were eaten by a snake, huh?
Why are you here, Navigator?
The thunder reverberated...
Like I said...
While I'm at it, why don't I
look for... the golden bell?
In other words,
Well, I'm all right... but...
That means the air expanded
at the speed of sound!
...so were you! We're inside
the snake's stomach!
Iron Clouds are added to the
blade by a dial built in the haft,
It's that powerful!! The scale of
his energy is so different from ours!
...Luffy's in there.
Don't pull my nose!
H-He's really... lightning itself!
so it chases the enemy
to the ends of the earth!
Huh? Why in the hell is he...?!
The golden bell is in the sky?
Then... Poneglyphs, too?
That was my Usopp impression!
What was I supposed to do?! He was in there!
Oh, boy... We are about to set off
to the Endless Vearth together.
Geez...! Such a pain in the ass!
Why's he always like this?!
Were you able to understand that,
swordsman from the Blue Sea?
Who is this idiot?
I'd rather not say this,
but he's the captain of our ship.
How should I know?!
Looks like there's a maggot
at the edge of the island.
It's just like a whip. Yeah, I get it
You don't have to get so
blood-thirsty, you know.
that the White-White Sea has
a bunch of circus warriors!
Who said we're coming with you?
What?
Oh, you are the captain?
It's the end of the world.
With just one hit...
...when the Lord of the Sky wasn't hurt
at all after so many bazooka attacks.
Yeah, I guess that's how
people'd normally see it.
I don't care about your
so-called "dream world"!!
You must be really slow, not even
noticing that you were eaten.
Holy...
Dammit! This may have hurt Aisa inside!
Let's fight separately.
Ahhh! Then this place is inside
that giant snake's stomach?!
Zoro! Don't, Zoro! He's too strong!!
Please hang in there, Usopp-san, Sanji-san.
It seems that it's getting a
little busy in the Upper Ruins.
Until I teach your body a lesson,
you probably won't understand...
W-Was I eaten, too?!
They still haven't awoken yet?
That's what I've been telling you.
Your clothes have melted too, you know!
...the definition of "God."
But... But they'll definitely get well, Father.
Ball Clouds!
Whoa! You're right!
Hey, then let's look for its butthole right away!
Eneru!
They sure will. There's no way that
such kind people won't get better.
Butthole?
What was that for? That wasn't
very nice of you, Warrior Wyper.
Just where're you planning to escape from?!
I didn't expect that even the
Lord of the Sky would be here...
We were eaten, so why not just
go "plop, plop" out of its butt?
God has an overwhelming power
that could never be matched,
I kindly invited you to
your homeland, you know.
No!! I'd rather melt!
Conis-san...
We'll assist you, Ohm-sama!
no matter how hard you struggle!
My wish is that,
when the sky becomes peaceful,
Nami's scary.
And then you feel it...
Don't get so fired up. Wait a little.
A Blue Sea woman is brutal.
I'd like to once again show everyone
hospitality to my heart's content...
The despair!
You guys...!
The game isn't over yet.
...including you.
In any case, we were eaten because
this snake is in a bad mood.
Looks like...
Father...
Yeah... we're the only ones left.
Game, you said?!
Having all your hopes dashed
is the same as death itself.
We'll help you reach Eneru, Wyper!
That's right. It's a petty game.
Before it starts going wild again,
we'd better hurry up and...
You... and those behind you
as well, are the participants.
In a bad mood?
That's right. It seemed like
it was in a very bad mood.
What's the matter, Suu?!
Is it time for your meal?
It was going wild all this time.
Suu, what's wrong? Are you in pain?
Oh, yeah! I'll dig a hole to the outside!
Why is it in such a bad mood?
Zoro!
Don't tell me...!!
People fear death above all things!
C-Could it be that you're...?
Were you causing a ruckus in here all this time?
That giant snake...
I'm one of those who fought
with Gan Fall-sama six years ago.
Yeah, I thought I'd break the wall to get out.
Welcome, splendid survivors!
That's why people prostrate themselves
before God and beg for mercy.
Then, as I thought, you're a
member of the Divine Squad!
It's laughing!
Er... So this was your doing.
I'm glad you made it this far.
I'll praise you for that.
In a closed-off area, we were...
That just can't be helped.
Since I went a little wild, I got hungry.
Living beings are meant to
bow before that which they fear.
What on earth happened?
Hold it!
Do you have something to eat?
What a pity... That's how instinct is.
Conis-san, attend to him right away!
Quit pestering us!!
--Yes, Father!
--Wait!
What's with this guy? He's incredibly strong...!
Well, I'm just having a little fun.
Wh-What's the matter?
N-Nami?!
This is a survival game to see
how many people out of 81,
--Aisa!
--Young lady!
My wife and children are on Angel Island!
You... stupid idiot!!
Kill them!
Yes, everyone's worried about you all.
including me, are standing three
hours after you all entered this island.
Please let everyone know!
Eneru is planning to return everything!
What's the meaning of this?
What?
Skypiea will be dropped to the Blue Sea!
There're participants who entered
in the middle of the game,
This nation will disappear!!
Did you come to be killed?
but I'm allowing that as well.
What the...?!
Th-That can't be...
Are you familiar with a thing called
the "Sea Prism Stone," Eneru?!
My guess was that there'd be five survivors.
Aisa! What're you doing here?!
Nami! Why're you here?!
Sea Prism Stone?
There's no time to lose!
Tell them right away! Eneru is...
Five?!
If I'm not mistaken, it's a stone that
can take away Devil Fruit powers!
Ah! Zoro! Where's everyone?!
Zoro, Robin, weird knight,
bazooka man, and Eneru.
Wyper!
What're you plotting, Blue Sea person?!
...planning to eliminate
everyone living in the sky!!
That's exactly five people, right?
Aisa! Get away from that woman!
Phew. Good, he hasn't noticed I'm here.
I see... I feel weakened.
Ha!
In three minutes, it'll be three hours.
Groaning like a fool! That's just what I want!
Eliminate everyone from the sky?
Sea Prism Stone... It's said that it
gives off the same energy as the sea.
W-Wait a second, please!
If he does such a thing,
In other words, it won't do if
there're six people here right now.
That was close!
Demon! You're a demon, Wyper!!
It's a sea in solid form, so to speak.
there won't be a place
even for God Eneru himself.
Don't let its stomach acid melt you, Aisa!
Doh! He knew!
That's why it can weaken
the power of Devil Fruits!
Why did you two come to a place like this?!
He's got an ark! "Ark Maxim"!
God's prophecy cannot fail,
since he is absolute.
Why?!
Die!
Because a huge...
Ark... Maxim?
Y-You shouldn't... I know. It's Reject, right?
I'll tear open its stomach now!
...snake...
Now, who will die? Will you fight each other?
What're you...?!
Your body will pay a heavy price as well!
What?!
What are you dissatisfied about?
You want Vearth, too, don't you?
Ahhhh... That idiot...!
Or shall I take care of it myself?
Shut up! I'm happy to die...
You son of a...!
Aisa!!
We were forced to spend the last
six years building that flying ship!
...if I can take you with me!
D-Don't!
Reject!
What do you wanna do?
I'm not going to be the one.
Wyper!!
Hang in there somehow, Nami...
Me neither.
My wish is that,
when the sky becomes peaceful,
...and... er... weird knight!
I won't accept that, either.
I, too, firmly refuse.
You're idiots who can't
even protect yourselves.
I'd like to once again show everyone
hospitality to my heart's content...
Did you hear something?
...including you.
Quit worrying about others!
Hey, hold on a sec! I...!
No way...
At any rate, no one will survive!
Did he defeat him?
Until I beat this guy!
So you die!
Now... it's time for the finale at last!
Father!!
How insolent!
Racing full speed ahead as always
A to Z, we run through it
We all have worries and fall many times
But we just need to rise to the top someday
What could be beyond the sea
in which the morning sun rises?
Let's go little by little toward
the brilliantly shining sun
I never treat you "bad"
How many times did we fall?
It's all right, we're definitely
pointing at tomorrow now
Smile! Come back to you, friends
Come back to you, friends
Okay! Let's hurry up and
get out from the butthole!
Fence or no fence, I'm not running away.
Let's break out!
What's gonna happen to us?!
It's not that people fear God. Fear itself is God.
The time is approaching.
I'll put an end to the survival game.
Dangerous... That guy's dangerous!
Like I said, I don't want to, you idiot!
Once you touch it, you'll get hurt.
Only survivors are allowed to come with me.
--Let's plop out!
--What're you doing?!
In that case, I'm fear itself. Hence, I am God.
--Laki!
--Get out of here, Wyper! Don't fight!
Whoa! The ground broke into pieces!
How sad, swordsman from the Blue Sea.
Are you messed up in the head?!
Is this our homeland, the one we've
been fighting for for 400 years?!
Stop it, you son of a bitch! Laki!
No one can survive anymore.
I won't let you have your way, Eneru!
I will put an end to this nation
in the sky with God's power!
Pray to God with all your heart.
Now, let's set off, shall we?
To the Endless Vearth!
Although she's a woman, she's still
a warrior. I won't have mercy.
Fine, you creep! But I'll never pray to God!
Well, it seems there's an extra person.
Huh? I don't have a clue
what you're talking about!
You giant snake! I have
business with your stomach!
So you die!
And I'll bring you down!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Collapsing Upper Ruins!
The Quintet for the Finale!"
"Showdown in the Ancient Ruins!
Sky God Eneru's Goal!!"
"Ambition Toward the Endless Vearth--
The Ark Maxim!!"
"The Ordeal of Iron!
White Barbed Death Match!!"
"Bursting Slash! Zoro vs. Ohm!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!