Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King
of the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
The horizons everyone
dreamed of were separate at first
but now they can be seen
through a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny
is leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve
your dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
The commodore seems sad...
Eneru's attacks mercilessly
rained down on all of Skypiea.
Another warrior has perished...
Yeah. Just after he made such a
great friend all the way out here...
And then there was that earthquake... Damn it!
Everything is an eyesore!
Sanji and Usopp snuck aboard
the Ark Maxim to rescue Nami.
The people, the trees, the land!
Return to where you belong!
None of this makes any sense!
While God Eneru was busy dealing
with Sanji's last-ditch efforts...
Let everything rain into the Blue Sea!
You're the evil spirits!
We set sail first thing tomorrow morning...
I'm sure they've been aware
of us for a long while now!
--We're going to deal with you right now!
--T-This wasn't the agreement! Stop!
But the villagers are so
bloodthirsty we can't go near 'em,
--Stop!
--Look out!
They know?! What're we gonna do?! Hey!
not to mention, the bell
didn't ring again today...
There's no point in worrying about it.
Hurry!
We'll split up inside and
head straight for the deck!
...Usopp succeeded in rescuing Sanji.
Angel Island won't last much longer!
--Seto! Move aside!
--What's the meaning of this?!
Don't show your face around me!
Nami-san is there!
The Shandoran warriors
I know and look up to...
There are no safe havens left on this island!
Meanwhile, Luffy's group...
Do you want your wife to end up a widow?!
Meanwhile, Luffy had a gold ball
attached to his arm by Eneru
...have much more pride than this!
and was thrown from the Maxim
into the ruins of Shandora,
...headed up Giant Jack to
settle the score with God Eneru.
Meanwhile, Robin and Usopp's
group was still beneath Giant Jack.
Kid...
but he got back up to settle the score.
Robin! Eneru's after the gold bell, right?!
"Gyaaaaa!"
And it's at the top of this vine, right?!
"Free from the Spell!
The Great Warrior Sheds Tears!!"
Alright... Dammit!
I can't get this gold ball off!
He's far above now.
It's only a matter of time until
his ship reaches the top of the vine.
Don't call it that!
When this sun lowers in the
west and sinks once again...
"Eternal Friends! The Vowed Bell
Echoes Across the Mighty Seas!!"
What is it Eneru wants there?
They had but a mere
moment to enjoy their reunion,
for God Eneru, after repairing
the Maxim, took action again!
Usopp saved Nami in the nick of time,
A gold bell at the top.
...your men's lives will be offered to the gods!
A bell...
but unable to stand up to Eneru's power,
they found themselves
trapped in a corner, when...
What a heartrending way to leave...
I have no need for good
old God's Shrine either!
Mamaragan.
El...
Nor for the city of Shandora below it!
Umm...
--Sanji-kun!
--Go.
Damn it!
...Thor!
Doctor...
Everyone! Hurry to the ship!
I'll get Luffy and bring him back!
Mousse-chan?!
Do you have a minute?
The earth certainly swallowed you skillfully!
There is but one thing left
in this land that I want!
I was just about to ask... for a light...
Truly an act of god! The fact that
you're alive is what's hardest to believe!
An exquisite view!
Botanist, my ass!
Don't assume things are gonna
turn out how you want, Eneru!
The golden grand belfry!
"Capriccio for Despair-- Looming
Destruction of the Sky Islands!!"
And Luffy, in an attempt to
catch Eneru, rushed up Giant Jack.
Dammit! He isn't holding back!
We gotta get outta here!
Noland!
Nami! Be all right!
Everything's done for!
I'm going to pay... you say?
If these are the victims
of your "advancements,"
And I won't let you have
the golden bell, Eneru!
The entire ground?!
then we should never have accepted you!
Is that where the detestable
Shandoran warriors' hidden village is?
What the...?!
Kindred Trees?
They're originally from the Blue Sea;
surely they'd enjoy going home!
Yes.
"Angel Island Obliterated!
The Horror of the Raigo's Advent!!"
It is said that all the spirits of our
ancestors who died on this island
The ship!
Prepare for the ceremony!
Take every last sacrifice to the altar!
are guided to them by the bell
so they can settle inside them.
Hey, wait a little longer!
Now, then! Strike the world below!
The commodore'll be back!
Just two more hours! No, one! Please!
All of our ancestors who lived on
the island since the age of Shandora
No, you didn't!
Why do we have to be burned at the stake?!
watch over us from those sacred, white trees.
Yeah... You'll pay for this...
The sun is setting. The ceremony
should be starting soon.
A gold bell?
Damn you!
Is that what you said?!
Our village!
--Wyper...
--Yes...
How unsightly! Is this the wreck
of a man who defied the gods?
What were you doing
inside the ship just now?!
That was close! We'd be ashes
now had we left any later!
W-What're you guys talking about?!
The Kindred Woods are so
truly important to us Shandians
You also spoke of the bell before
being hit by Eneru's electric attack.
What are you so afraid of?
Damn you! You've got some nerve!
that we've protected them as much
as we've protected our own lives!
What?!
So he's going after it?
You tremble before intangible fears
The gears have gone awry... I must fix it!
In the name of Great Warrior Calgara...
Where exactly is it?!
and give up people's lives
for false consolation!
And we chopped them all down...
Hey! Wait! This is no time for that!
You saw that thunderbolt!
False consolation?!
Your sacrifices are nothing
but pointless deaths!
...light the fire of Shandora!
The warriors were angry and
instantly took up their weapons...
We're gonna die if we don't get outta here!
--We must drive them off this island!
--Yeah!
Somewhere near the top of this giant vine...
We have lived this way for centuries now!
Wyper.
...but since you had saved so
many of the villagers' lives...
How?! How do you know that?!
Your distant ancestor,
Great Warrior Calgara,
All right! He's gone!
Hey! We promised we'd wait
for Nami back on our ship!
That doesn't mean it's right!
had another reason for being so
determined to take back our homeland.
Silence, outsider!
I see. So that attitude was
anger they couldn't act on...
She's gonna be back with Luffy any time now!
Another reason?
However great your gods may be,
Don't worry! Nami fell safely
into some Island Clouds!
He's right, Wyper!
Yes. It was Calgara's greatest regret of all.
Even if it was just for tree research...
people's lives are even more precious!
The ruins of Shandora in the layer below us...
Even if you didn't know...
This vine pierces right through
the very center of the city.
The villagers' anger won't go away now...
Listen. Great Warrior Calgara
had a very close friend...
S-So high up!
Take the sacrifices to the altar!
Burn them at the stake and
send them into the heavens!
So, I thought I would at least ask why...
Not the jungle, not the ruins...
Focus on falling into the Island Clouds!
Oh, geez! Look!
A close friend?
I dunno if it's ruins or what,
but it's been blasted to pieces!
Yes. He met Calgara 400
years ago. His name was...
...before you left...
--Commodore!
--We're gonna be set on fire!
We could be next, you know!
U-Usopp Hopping!
Hey! Someone help with this!
--Trees where ancestors' spirits dwell...
--Get it all on board now!
A map I found in the ruins
indicated that the grand belfry
...Montblanc Noland!
I had no idea. We've done something
that can never be taken back...
You can send an innocent girl to her death...
that held the golden bell was
located in the city's center.
The villagers are right to be angry.
...and have no qualms about it,
so I doubt you'd understand!
A-Are you completely ignoring me?
But, Commodore! We had no choice, given--
I-I jumped too far! I jumped too far!
"Led by a Bell's Sound! Tale of
the Great Warrior and the Explorer"
No excuses! I only did what satisfied me!
What you're doing is less than human!
In other words, the shock from
being thrust upward by the vine
might have thrown the bell
even further skyward.
No! I'm falling! I'm gonna crash!
I'm gonna crash and die!
I'm told that aside from
proclaiming the city's existence,
No qualms, you say?!
This tale took place 400 years ago,
and though it has never been written of,
The girl yesterday...
It's directly above here?!
that bell also served to guide
their ancestors' spirits to the island.
The singing voice of the island...
...was my daughter!
it has been kept in people's hearts
from one generation to the next.
And we cut down those trees!
You would tell your own
daughter to end her life?!
It is a true story of a
warrior known as a monster,
We have no reason to be forgiven!
Yikes! I forgot to unhook it!
It's you people who don't
understand how much power there is
and an adventurer known as a liar.
Commodore...
Hey!
in the words our priests hear from the gods!
Listen up, everyone!
Get on board, quick!
Eh?! Leave all the gold behind?!
Our village is commanded to obey!
The city of gold has a huge bell, right?
The Monster of Shandora is coming!
We can't beg for our children's lives!
Hurry! Cast off! Cast off!
Noland and his men are preparing to leave.
--B-But there are still crewmen--!
--Just get us out to sea!
Now, then. I'm above Giant Jack.
Usopp! Sanji-kun!
It's one size smaller... It must
be the Kashi God's child!
He's here!
That voice! Nami! Sounds like
you're all right! That's a relief!
I doubt anyone would come
searching for something
The gods' blood has come
to pass judgment on you!
in these skies above God's Shrine.
Are you okay, Sanji-kun?!
I'm so sorry you had to get all
charred like this just for us!
Judgment, my ass!
Even after 400 years...
Mousse! Where were you?!
Now, then. Where is the golden bell...?
Sixty years ago, my own land
lost hundreds of thousands of lives
I-I can't breathe! N-Nami!
Pull me outta here, quick!
What if...
You must be eliminated!
to the Kinetsu plague that
is ravaging your village now!
What if you knew a single, important
tree was tainted by poison...
Oh! Sorry!
Anyways, let's get out of here...
But, in recent years, there've been
absolutely no deaths to this disease!
And that its poison would
eventually spread into the forest,
W-Why won't you come out?!
Do you know why?!
affect people, and kill an island?!
I'm gonna die...
Because we discovered a cure for it!
What if you knew beforehand?!
Leave all your belongings and go!
What I'm holding in my right
hand is the bark of a Cona tree!
--What are you talking about?!
--What do you mean?
What is this place?!
If it was us...
The Conine I can extract from it is the cure!
What would we do with
that single, important tree?!
If I return with this, I can save the village!
Curse you, Blue Sea man!
R-Reporting, Commodore!
Him...
Our ship's stores have finally been exhausted,
I'm astonished he made it here
with that weight attached.
Dad! Go quickly and stop them!
meaning we're now... lost... at sea...
Do you know how many man-hours
have been spent around the world,
Don't be a fool! You know what they've done!
There you are!
The cook's fainted!
and how many victims there have been?!
If we part now, we'll regret it
for the rest of our lives!
Wait right there! Eneru!
Dammit! There's no food left!
You finally made such a dear friend,
This ship is not so easily brought down.
And you people are trampling
all over this great advancement!
The commodore fell into the ocean!
and we Shandians owe them so much!
Such a pest.
This is the Grand Line! Did he decide
to drown himself and leave us?!
But we're going to leave them
hurt for the rest of their lives!
I'm fully acquainted with
this ship's drive circuits.
That's why I say your "ceremonies"
are insults to those people!
Maybe he was so starved he chose death?
What are you talking about?!
Even without electric power,
the wind power from the 200 Jet Dials
Don't be stupid! He's a hero who's
returned twice from these waters!
It'll probably sound like an excuse,
but for the commodore's honor, I must say this.
Will I die in judgment, or in an accident?!
I gathered from my homeland of Birka...
Then what're these carefully
folded clothes and shoes for?!
Those woods of yours were already dead.
H-Hey! Someone go check...
Will your village die by curse, or by disease?!
Eh?!
Screw that! It's a sea of monsters down there!
...will keep the ship afloat for a while!
The true horror of the Kinetsu plague
is that it can also infect plant life.
He's not coming back up!
Are you that afraid of gods?!
No matter what you feeble beings try...
--Commodore!
--Pretty nimble guy, he was. Here.
Wyper! What are you planning to do?!
It was because he knew this
Don't tell me you're gonna climb the vine?!
Eh? What's this rope?
I do know when a man is
speaking earnest words...
that the commodore pleaded with
you without regard for his own life.
Pull it in.
From people to forest, forest to people...
Everyone! Get away from the vine!
Answer me.
What is this, Commodore?!
Several small islands have been
destroyed in exactly that way.
...this land will meet its end!
Something's falling!
Don't tell us you killed it underwater?!
What did I just kill?!
Cook it up for us.
You really do lose your
touch when you get lazy.
But there's nothing to worry about now.
Look! That huge vine!
--A snake.
--No!
We finished checking
the entire forest yesterday.
If it's the same one I saw in the ruins,
The tip of the vine?! What happened above?!
I just broke our
commandments and killed a god!
It's a huge storm, Commodore!
these are the Island Clouds up above them.
Hey, now! Don't tell me
Luffy and Nami fell with it?!
I'm sorry that we cut
down your beloved woods
I bet so, given this swaying.
But you call it a snake, and our
deadly curse a curable disease!
Ruins? Oh, the city of gold?! It exists?!
without knowing or explaining...
You bet so? Is that all?!
Wyper!
It'd probably still be unforgivable
even with an explanation,
No! You can't in your condition!
You're all beat up!
Yeah. But all the gold is in Eneru's hands now.
The yardarm's been busted!
--Where?!
--Main! Main!
but a botanist would never harm
a forest without good reason.
This third voyage has lasted over two years.
In any case, Zoro and the others
should be in the ruins below!
And even if you do climb up, there's
no way to reach Eneru in the sky!
"Ruins of Shandora"
"Current Location"
The commodore doesn't hate
gods and spirits and stuff...
Will you really save my beloved village?!
"Ruins of Shandora"
"Current Location"
It's almost miraculous it has lasted so long.
"Ruins of Shandora"
"Current Location"
I don't know the topography or anything...
It's...
It's directly above!
Can you save it?!
Hey. Did you just hear something?!
...but I do know it's dangerous to stay here!
It's just that he always
knows what's most important.
The bell that Great Warrior Calgara sought!
Eh? Do you mean the thunder?
I can!
Yeah. Get on!
No, something beautiful, like a bell...
Let's find everyone and get off this island!
Calgara?
That means... they did it for us?
Yes.
Yeah!
That's what our true goal is!
There are no safe places left here in Skypiea...
Priest! Try to keep your senses!
This land is cursed! At this rate,
the Shandians will be wiped out!
Eneru! I refuse to let you have it!
Dad!
H-How can we save the village, Priest?!
I'm sorry, Noland!
O-Offer... a girl!
Don't go yet!
Everyone have everything?
At the sacrificial altar!
All except one thing...
Quit mopin'! Just forget about it!
Luffy! Look out!
How do you intend to
climb up here in that state?
All right! It's time to go!
Everyone to your positions!
We're now heading back
to the Lvneel Kingdom!
D-Damn you!
How many victims does that make?
Noland!
Over a hundred...
It's so fast!
L-L-Luffy!
I've committed such a sin!
What's going on?! This has
never happened to us before!
Wait! Not that way! Left! Left!
Wait! Noland!
Stay there for a while. I'll show
you something interesting.
Eh?! I can't turn so suddenly!
Set sail!
Gum-Gum Hook!
If I can be of use, I will gladly give my life.
Why do you cry, Mom?
Why is the bell ringing?
I'm about to be welcomed by the sun god!
Don't destroy my hometown!
Giant Jack's over there!
Ring it!
Being chosen to be a sacrifice
is a wonderful thing!
I'm sorry, Noland-san!
I know, but--!
Huh?
Louder! So Noland and the others can hear it!
Quit destroying stuff!
Stop!
Oh, right! I gotta figure
something out while he's gone!
Thank you for raising me, Mom.
A-A snake!
Commodore! Look!
Is this...?
Hey, Calgara! Look at this!
Mousse!
It's spewing out thunderclouds nicely...
What a shock! I didn't know
that snake had a grandchild...
That's my only choice!
If this is a bad dream, let me wake up!
"That snake"?
Dammit! Go away!
Noland!
So the rat scurried off...
A snake, huh?
Calgara...
Go away!
They're so restless and shrewd...
Gum-Gum...
Those two make no sense...
But no matter. The festivities are soon at hand.
Great Warrior Calgara...
They were trying to kill each
other until just recently...
Seto...
I wanted to be like you someday...
...Yo-Yo!
Now, they're such good friends!
Huh?!
Calgara is never very friendly
with any of the villagers, either.
I wanted to be a brave warrior
and fight to protect this land!
Robin and the others are gone!
Zoro and Chopper...
Come back again!
And Wyper and God...
I've never seen him smile like that before...
What is he doing?!
Where the heck did they go?!
I don't wanna die because
of something like this!
Just follow me.
Noland...
I bet they've already gone up it.
I'll be waiting for you here!
We climb down here.
All right! I'm back on track!
Oh, yeah! Robin!
Climb down?
I'll keep on ringing the bell!
You're amazing, Commodore!
All right! Let's go!
Now's my chance to get on board!
There really was an island in
the direction you said to turn to!
So that your ship won't get
lost at sea when you return...
A-Aisa?
Yes, what a relief. We can
ride out the storm here.
Luffy! I finally caught up to you!
So that you won't lose sight
of this island during a storm...
Eh? Nami! What're you doing here?!
Still, did you guys really not hear it?
This ringing...
I came to get you!
I'll ring this bell and wait for you!
Nope. None of us heard any bells. Right?
Hey, Calgara! Where is this
beautiful ringing coming from?!
Sanji-kun and Usopp saved me,
so I was down below!
Yeah! You must've been
hearing things, Commodore!
Follow me and you'll see.
I don't know...
Really?! You were?! That's great!
Listen carefully...
But more importantly...
The way things stand, this land,
Skypiea, will be annihilated...
Wait!
Let's meet again someday
for sure! Friend of mine!
What a magnificent forest!
What's that?!
I hope we find good research materials!
The sky island will?!
O-Our village, too?!
The thunderclouds... are changing shape!
I can... come back again?
Everything...
He said that he'd return
everyone in the sky to the ground...
Commodore! Was that the sound you heard?!
--The sky!
--Help!
Of course I'll be back! I will!
Hey, now! Don't tease me!
--This is bad! Save us!
--The sky's pitch dark!
Luffy.
I'd never mistake the sounds of
this odd bird for something else!
Yeah?
Are the sky islands... going to disappear?!
--What's happening?!
--Mom!
Into the ocean! Quickly!
C-Commodore! Was this--
There's a giant ball floating in the sky!
Let's meet again someday for sure!
That thing's bad news...
That's a thundercloud
wrapped in a spherical shroud...
They're here!
Lost for words?
...and it's packed with intense currents
and internal electric discharges!
This is Shandora, a city of gold.
We are its survivors!
A city of gold...
Wow... What a beautiful tone...
There once was a man
named Montblanc Noland,
"North Blue-- Lvneel Kingdom"
It's like I'm dreaming!
Seems there are people here!
from a kingdom in the northern seas.
H-Hold on, Commodore! Wait!
Noland the Explorer always told
stories of incredible adventures.
It's directly above Angel Island!
Wyper and the others are right through here!
But the villagers could never
tell if they were true or not.
The thunderclouds turned spherical...
Someone's lying on the ground!
Damn it... Intruders!
T-This is a nightmare! This isn't
something you see in real life!
W-Whoa! It's gold everywhere!
It's a city of treasure!
--Hey! Kid!
--Commodore! This kid doesn't look right!
One day, Noland returned from a
journey and reported to the king.
What more is he planning to unleash?!
The ship is headed for the grand belfry!
It stands all the more
proudly and beautifully in ruin!
Hey, guys! Stop!
Wait, you!
What happened to the
navigator and the others?
If they're on board, could that mean they're...?
Let go!
This city is named Shandora! The term
"city of gold" fits it like none other!
It's fine.
Load your ship with all the treasure
you can, aside from the gold bell!
It's the Kinetsu plague.
He hasn't been treated at all.
"Five Years Later"
We made it through!
T-This island is bad news!
Seto! Show them where the treasure is!
Marie Jois has finally granted us
permission to enter the Grand Line.
Doctor! Do we have any Conine left?!
Inject this lad and all of us immediately!
--Right!
--Are you sure this is okay?
As such, I wish to send
you on another mission.
Down there! Luffy! Stop! Stop!
The villagers already agreed to it.
Yes, it would be my pleasure!
Robin!
--Hurry! Into the ocean!
--Wait!
We owe you for saving our tribe
from that terrible disease.
W-What're you doing?!
But, I've decided my soldiers will
join you on this journey, as will I.
Look after these guys!
This is bad. Even the crops
are being eaten away at...
This is nothing at all.
You're so generous, Great Warrior!
--Understood?
--Yes!
But haven't your people been
protecting the city all this time?
"One Year Before Noland's Arrival"
Commodore! All the houses
are filled with the sick!
Now you will learn that the heavens are mine!
--Calgara!
--Seto...
Yes. We've protected the city...
but not necessarily its treasure!
You're off to ring the bell, right? I'll help!
Stop! Stop!
With the Maxim and my power,
I can accomplish such acts of God!
Luffy...
Hey, Nola. You've sure settled into these ruins!
You... You grew hands!
To be more specific...
"Gyaaaaa!"
What's that gold on your arm?!
--Look at that!
--It's falling onto Angel Island!
Robin! The gold bell is at
the top of this vine, right?!
Say! When do you suppose
Noland-san and the others will come?
And Eneru's after it, right?!
...only this stone.
That's all you ever ask when you come here.
If the belfry does exist, it'd have to be there...
--It's too late!
--We're not going to make it!
It won't be so easy for him to come back.
What is this? Writing?
--Run! Hurry!
--I'm scared!
"Gyaaaaa!"
--But he's already...
--All right, then!
Take the girl to the altar!
He was born in the far northern seas.
He also has a family back home.
Writings of history.
It's known as a "Poneglyph."
Luffy!
But he did promise.
He left...
We can't read it, either.
As long as we keep ringing this
bell here, he'll show up sooner or later.
Say.
You mean your ancestors didn't write this?
Raigo.
Do you know where our
navigator is? She has orange hair...
God of the sun... God of the rain...
Eh? If you mean Nami, she's on that ship...
All we know for certain is
that this city of Shandora
What's this?! This looks bad!
God of the forest... God of the earth...
Huh? I only hear one
voice coming from the sky...
fought and fell trying to protect this stone.
Come, Seto! We have to protect the village!
In exchange for this girl's life,
please save our village!
We must continue to protect it
with that amount of resolve.
There they are!
As descendants, it is our
duty to protect the proof
that our ancestors fought and survived.
Robin!
Navigator! Long-nose! Cook!
We revere our ancestors as if they were gods.
Aisa! Thank goodness! Are you all right?!
No, this can't be!
Still, I had no idea it was this
giant, gold bell I had heard...
Did the White Berets manage to escape?
Nami!
The White Berets saved us...
It's the Kashi God!
Zoro! Chopper!
Why?!
The island we were born on and our
hometown are completely gone!
This bell's ringing has words to it.
Weird old man!
Why does the island suddenly end here?!
Yikes! A guerilla!
Mousse!
Words?
Dammit! Everyone's been taken out!
Oh, if only I'd been there!
So that the spirits of our ancestors
who were greeted by the heavens
Let her go! It's for the village!
The Kashi God has such a divine form!
Damn you! You lied to me!
can return to this land at
any time without getting lost,
Oh, yeah! Aisa! Where's Luffy?!
Wasn't he with you?!
Where is this gold of yours?!
Luffy just went up the vine
to rescue you from Eneru!
Please save my mother!
we continue to ring this bell,
as a way to say, "We are here!"
Please save my son and father!
Where did the village go?!
Even the Sea Clouds were obliterated!
What happened to this island?!
Eh?! Crap! We just missed each other?!
Calgara! If you're alive, let me hear it!
The sound of the gold bell!
What the--?! Something fell!
Its sound proclaims the
unquestionable glory Shandora once had,
He left just now. I tried to stop him, but...
What's that?!
Talk about bad timing! There's no
time left! We gotta escape now!
Answer me, fire of Shandora!
and makes its existence
known to the ends of the sea!
What a wonderful sight!
This is how the sky should be!
We will never run or hide!
Go ahead! I'll go after him on the waver!
Noland's public execution's about to start!
That's why we call this city's
grand bell the "fire of Shandora."
You guys just get to the Merry somehow!
Hey! This way, guys!
Eh?!
W-What was that explosion?!
Six years ago,
That explains why it has
such a majestic sound!
I saw a giant city of gold on
the Grand Line island of Jaya!
And the thunderbolts are still raining down?!
What on earth?! Who is that?!
--Do you think so?!
--Yes!
Dammit! That ship's fast!
Kashi God!
God-killer!
The city of gold does exist!
I don't get the feeling
I'll be leaving alive now!
Eneru!
This fire reached out to us
and helped us arrive here.
Then let's hear from one of your crewmen.
He eradicated Angel Island...
Is this man telling the truth?
Get on, quickly! The sky is
getting darker and darker!
The ceremony is over.
I heard this bell in a storm where
it shouldn't have been audible...
No. It's an absolute lie.
You must've been really frightened.
How can you be so ruthless, Eneru?!
You're safe now! There's no need to die!
Eh?! Noland-san is a liar?!
Then were all his stories fake?!
--Kashi God! Please forgive us!
--We're all going to be cursed!
That's messed up! He lied to the
whole kingdom and acted like a hero!
You like this bell's sound, too?
What's wrong? You need to escape at once...
Kill! Give more lives to the gods!
Before we incur their wrath!
Are you going to grow up to be like
that other giant snake someday?
Who's that witness?!
He's not part of our crew!
Chief... Aisa still hasn't--
Did you see Calgara and the others?!
What loud rumbling...
--Calgara! Kill him!
--Sounds like he did something bad!
I see. She hasn't returned...
Commodore! What happened?!
Aisa is a bright child. Let us have
faith she is with some warriors...
We have to wait. We have to
take them back to the Blue Sea!
They're really freaking out!
Seize them!
Probably not for a hundred more years!
--He doesn't know how to ignore!
--He killed a god? What's that mean?!
Dammit!
All right...
Men...
Luffy! Get on, so we can go back down!
Hey! Stay here as long as you like, Noland!
Tribal rituals ain't something
you mess around with!
Everyone's headed for our ship!
We gotta get going, too!
You're the first guests here in
the 400 years since Shandora fell!
For his heinous lies, Montblanc
Noland is hereby sentenced
Quell the gods' anger,
Great Warrior Calgara-sama!
Hurry! Hurry up!
I can't.
to death by beheading!
I am an explorer from
the North Blue, Montblanc--
I want to treat you with lavish hospitality!
Captain!
You can't? Why not?!
What're you talking about?!
We can't make it through this
without the ships in the dock!
Liar!
It doesn't matter who you are!
You must be eliminated!
Even if I don't have to save you now...
I'd love that! I do want to
collect plants from the forest,
--Liar!
--He's a liar!
They'd have to go around the long way!
...I still have unfinished business here!
Men! Use dials to create rivers
inside the island at once!
--The commodore'd never lie!
--Commodore!
Is this how you've eliminated all
the few, yet vital advancements?!
and I want to see this
plague all the way through.
Unfinished business? What could
you possibly have left to do here?!
Yes, sir!
Commodore! Commodore!
Liar! Liar! Liar! Liar!...
Are you trying to get back
at Eneru or something?!
You're in no place to criticize!
Atone to the gods where you stand!
Hold on, now. What's with the clothes?
There's a gold bell up above!
Look, look! An Eternal Pose!
Everyone! Please go to Cloud End
and escape to the Blue Sea!
Who is that man?! He's holding
his own against Calgara!
Gold? Your life is more important,
you know! Just look!
And a map, Commodore! A map!
We took these from intruders.
God Eneru plans to eliminate this land!
Even if lightning doesn't hurt you,
Is that a map of this island?!
If you stay here, you'll all die!
he has the power to destroy
everything in other ways!
Yeah. This skull shape is definitely this island.
There! Use that knife to take your life!
For the last six years,
what we've known most of all
If it's gold you want, then look!
You have some on your arm!
The name "Shandora"
means "the skull's right eye,"
What?!
is that Eneru has the
power to bring us despair!
Forget about some gold bell! You'll be killed!
A sacrifice meant to save the village,
crying because she wants to live...
which refers to this city's location.
Have you no shame?!
I won't die...
And that the time is imminent!
Will you quit it, already?! You--
Well, take care! Be sure she gets lots of rest!
You saw it yourself!
Don't be a fool!
What's the point of waiting
for a miracle to happen?!
Saw what?
Thank you, Doctor!
Stop!
Before you pray... Before you
turn a blind eye to reality...
Hey! Come look, everyone!
Noland's giving us some weird crops!
The city of gold... it existed!
...you have to do what you can!
The time where you could survive
if you lie low as a victim is over!
I have a greenhouse on our ship,
with all kinds of plant samples.
You have to take action!
It wasn't a lie.
I'll leave some seeds and sprouts
that are suited for your soil.
You can't protect your own life
by blaming someone later!
C-Commodore!
Old diamond-head's ancestor...
Is that any good?
God! It's a giant island of Vearth!
Sure is! It's also full of nutrients!
Come on now! Make the
decision to leave this land!
Yes. Did you hear that? The singing
voice of this beautiful Vearth...
If it exists, that's fine. If not, that's fine, too.
For centuries we've strictly
upheld the commandment
I'm not really out to prove
his innocence or anything.
It is truly the birth of holy land.
That is where I must live!
that all intruders on this
island must be punished!
How many islanders are left?!
What's more, you're a god-killer!
You, alone, won't be enough!
This is a duel with the man
who screwed up my life.
Still half of them!
No more baggage allowed!
Get all the islanders out to sea!
You and all your men will pay with your lives!
What happened?!
He wasn't lying.
Yes, sir!
"Lives" this, "sacrifices" that!
Will those make your gods happy?!
What is this?! I can't breathe well!
So I have to let the old guy
and the others below know...
--Is everyone all right?!
--Pull yourselves together!
These ceremonies are flat-out denials
--Tend to the wounded! Hurry!
...that the city of gold was in the sky!
of the triumphs of all the great men
before us! I won't stand for it!
Hold it! Leave the
two-billion-Extol-per-person departure fee!
Calgara! Intruders!
I hereby claim this Vearth as mine! I am God!
If I ring the bell...
they should be able to hear it!
This is an insult to all the
adventurers and researchers
Amazon-san! You need to escape, too!
--Eh?
--Hurry! To Cloud End!
who've ever set out to sea in the
hopes of bringing people happiness!
God, my ass!
Otherwise, they'll keep on searching
the ocean floor until they die!
--Eh?
--This land...
Stop them, warriors!
--Eh?
--It's about to be destroyed!
If your gods value people's lives,
We cannot let this land be taken away!
then wouldn't they have contempt
for these ceremonies, too?!
Eh?
Luffy...
We made a promise, Noland...
I can't let Eneru take it!
That we would meet again someday...
Give me time!
I'm sure the huge bell can
be heard from anywhere...
Calgara... Where are you?!
I'll banish this so-called curse of yours!
When you return to Jaya, what will
you think when you see we're gone?
...so that's why I'm going to ring the gold bell!
And if I can't, you can do whatever you like!
All right! Let's work hard again today!
The wind stopped...
Hold on a little longer! I'll let
you know that "we are here"!
What nonsense!
Work hard doing what?
Having a campfire party?!
You think you're a god or something?!
Hey! The City of Gold has a huge bell, right?
In return, if I do save this village from tragedy,
Are you alive?!
Yes, Noland's logbook did mention it had one.
I have so much to tell you...
swear to me you'll never
hold these ceremonies again!
Calgara...
--Why do you ask?
Why?! Why would the doctor
and the others do this?!
Is that all you have to say?!
I'm only concerned for your well-being...
Such nonsense! Now you die!
I thought up a good idea!
Let's meet again on the
same land someday, Noland!
Try it!
What? What is it?!
--Eh?!
--What are you saying?!
Chief! Noland and the others are coming!
If we rang that huge bell,
Light the fire of Shandora!
These people have until
tomorrow evening to live.
Listen! Do not speak of last night!
do you think old diamond-head
and the monkeys below would hear it?
Great Warrior Calgara continued to shout.
They said they are going
to set sail in a few days.
Perfect!
Just once would've been enough.
Do not do anything rash!
They'd hear it, right?
For he believed the fire of Shandora
would echo and let all know that,
It's "goodbye, world" come sunset tomorrow!
I guess we can't understand
each other after all!
When he says he's gonna
do something, he means it.
"We are here!"
No matter how good his
medicine is, he's still a god-killer!
Then, he's...
Have faith in the commodore!
But the bell never once rang.
Hey, girlie. I feel bad for you too;
you were born in this village...
He did say that. But given the situation...
Do they think they're great enough
to stomp all over our history?!
Everything was later told to our
village by sailors from the Blue Sea.
Yeah! With your looks,
you could marry an aristocrat!
Run! Run!
Endure it! Suppress your feelings,
and quietly wait for them to leave!
Knock it off, guys! Don't you have any tact?!
He's going to ring the bell, you say?!
Noland, to whom we owe so much,
had such pride for our city
Who is he?
Oh, you mean the commodore?
They're here!
Yeah. Even if Nami tries to
bring him back, he won't come.
that he refused to deny Shandora's
existence and died known as a liar.
He's Montblanc Noland,
a renowned explorer. And a botanist.
Hey, guys! Is Calgara around?
The time has come.
Because he's after the same thing Eneru is.
Now then. Let us...
But it was already too late,
He visits uncharted islands and finds
and researches new plants there.
for Great Warrior Calgara had died
honorably in battle here in the sky.
...begin the festivities.
He's pretty much a hero back home.
Why is everyone acting so coldly
all of a sudden? Where's Calgara?
Never being able to convey his message...
But he's too good-natured...
That is Great Warrior Calgara's greatest regret.
And his biggest flaw is that
he can't ignore stuff like this!
You guys are outsiders!
We do trust him, though!
Mamaragan!
Calgara doesn't want to see you anymore!
I did it!
Do you think it could still reach him?
Why didn't you let Calgara kill him there?!
Seto!
That bell! If we rang it now,
would its sound reach Noland?!
The answer will make itself known tomorrow.
Who gave you permission to board this ship?
When are you gonna leave, anyway?!
He says he can save our village.
There is no harm in waiting.
Eneru!
That's a good question...
Get away from the island!
Eh?!
We are close to Heaven...
Don't dawdle!
They suddenly seem to hate us now...
How can you be so carefree?!
You'll listen to him, but not
the priest's last words?!
The lightning is getting bigger and bigger!
Wyper! We'll die if we don't escape now!
Hey, hold on, you guys!
You can't just start acting like this!
The boats in the port have been destroyed!
Calgara! Say something!
Luffy!
To the western end of the beach!
Quickly! There are still boats there!
See! I told you it was a bad idea!
Stop.
Come on!
If I sense the village is in
even the slightest danger,
Wyper...
Damn him!
Run to the west!
Let's continue our work.
Eneru...
Quickly! Toss your belongings!
I'll take that man's head without
waiting for tomorrow's sun to set.
Well? Did you see the silly
little island vanish from the sky?!
What gives you the right
to take everything away?!
We still have some forest to inspect.
I do not have the power
to hear the gods' voices.
Girl. I assume you're not
going to try and sweet-talk me
Here you are, Calgara!
Noland was looking for you!
This is the sky! God's domain!
But I do know when a man is
speaking earnest words. That is all.
by asking me to take you
to Endless Vearth again...
Yeah. I don't want to see his face anymore.
Chief! You need to get on a boat!
Everything is an eyesore!
The people, the trees, the land!
Return to where you belong!
Hell, no!
Yes...
If I do, I think I might kill him!
Once I have what I want,
Great Warrior Calgara...
Let everything rain into the Blue Sea!
I will destroy all of Skypiea
with this next Raigo!
Please protect everyone...
Should you really be up?
No one can be allowed to escape now!
I'm all better...
Hurry!
The bell didn't ring today...
Angel Island won't last much longer!
Yeah. It's the first time this's happened
in the month we've been here.
Great Warrior Calgara...
There are lots of injured people!
What does "advancement" mean?
Including the several unmoving
voices directly below you!
Get them into boats, then give them first aid!
Commodore...
I'll be finished exploring
the forest in two days.
Run!
--Hurry, into the ocean!
--Hurry!
Directly below?!
Y-Yes, sir...
I'm going to eradicate this land
that is out of place in the sky
Tell the crew we set sail again in three days,
I get chills when I imagine that
girl's speech being any later!
and change everything
back to how it should be!
What huge lightning!
Here we are! A Cona tree!
Is she all right?!
so now's their last chance to
enjoy solid ground for a while.
We're gonna end up sky dust if we stay here!
I'd be surprised if there wasn't
one in such a big forest!
That is my duty as God!
Commodore... To be honest, I wanna
get off this awkward island...
Everyone! Hurry to the ship!
I'll get Luffy and bring him back!
Only after we've finished
our duties! Get some sleep.
A-A-All right! Got it!
Earthquake!
He's far above now.
--It's happening! It's really happening!
--It's the Kashi God's curse!
I won't let you...
It's only a matter of time until
his ship reaches the top of the vine.
Live here, Noland!
I know! Why don't you
make Mousse your wife?!
...have your way!
Hurry, Robin!
What is it Eneru wants there?
Let us out of here!
Don't be silly.
We gotta carry these guys
to the ship somehow!
I have a family back home, with kids
about her age. I have to go back.
A gold bell at the top.
Wyper!
A bell...
Calgara doesn't want to see you anymore!
Farewell, rubber man!
The scurrying angels are like a
line of ants that's been disturbed!
Look on wistfully and
wait until the end arrives!
When are you gonna leave, anyway?!
Swordsman!
This is bad... The forest floor has sunk...
Weird old man!
Return to where you belong, Skypiea!
Luffy!
Thank goodness! You're conscious!
It looks like the island is about to tear apart!
Hey! We have no time! Can you walk?!
Eneru! So you've started it...
What is that?!
A hole in the White-White Sea?!
Luffy!
I have no need for good
old God's Shrine either!
I know you're here, Calgara! Come out!
No one can stop me now.
Don't you think this is too one-sided?!
Looking good!
Let's hurry. There's nothing we can do here.
Seems the gods have given a
crushing blow to you directly!
Tell me why! I won't
understand unless you tell me!
Nor for the city of Shandora below it!
Damn it!
We're going to set sail very soon!
I don't want to part ways like this!
In that case, these gods...
aren't that great... at all...
Wyper...
Listen! We will send you
into the sky, without fail!
They don't even have the strength...
to kill a single person...
Not even Luffy can deal with
an enemy flying into the sky!
There is but one thing left
in this land that I want!
Make it in time! We gotta escape
before this land is destroyed!
You're stubborn.
Luffy...
The golden grand belfry!
Sorry, but could you get lost?
I don't feel like looking at you!
I...
Don't show your face around me!
Two voices, at this final stage?
Do you want your wife to end up a widow?!
I... must hurry to the village!
Geez! How can he run so fast?!
...will ring that bell!
An exquisite view!
Amusing. I think I'll see this through.
Nami! Be all right!
And I won't let you have
the golden bell, Eneru!
Calgara!
Don't assume things are gonna
turn out how you want, Eneru!
Just try and squirm out!
If you're feeling lonely, talk to me
You gaze at the heavens
as you wander about
Just like the moon,
you keep your gaze constant
And your deep reflection wanes
as you slowly disappear
Stay as you are, let those words guide you
Dream, you travelers who spend
countless nights drifting
Even if you may not be able to go back
you will surely start moving forward again
How unsightly! Is this the wreck
of a man who defied the gods?!
The bell has lost all its meaning!
Some 400 years ago,
there was a man known as a liar.
Did you see the power of the Raigo?!
Now, then! Time for that eyesore
of an island to disappear!
Next up are the cumuloregalis
clouds themselves!
I only did what satisfied me!
What's that?! The clouds are changing shape!
Isn't there anything we can do?!
Will your village die by curse, or by disease?!
No one believed him as he was
executed for his great lies and trickery.
If these were sacrifices
for your "advancements,"
It's important that we, the inheritors
of Calgara's wishes, ring that bell!
I won't let you have your way, Eneru!
we should never have accepted you!
There is no stopping this Raigo!
--Are you that afraid of your gods?!
--Don't talk like you understand!
Knock over this vine?! Am I our
last line of defense after all?!
But the truth was still passed on
in the clouds high above!
They're right to be angry.
We have no reason to be forgiven!
We have to escape, too!
However great your gods are,
people's lives are even more precious!
If I can just catch him...!
Luffy! Guarantee me I'll survive!
We're returning to the Lvneel Kingdom!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Led by a Bell's Sound! Tale of
the Great Warrior and the Explorer"
"Angel Island Obliterated!
The Horror of the Raigo's Advent!!"
"Free from the Spell!
The Great Warrior Sheds Tears!!"
"Knock Over Giant Jack!
Last Hope for Escape"
"Eternal Friends! The Vowed Bell
Echoes Across the Mighty Seas!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!