Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King
of the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
The horizons everyone
dreamed of were separate at first
but now they can be seen
through a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny
is leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve
your dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
Sanji and Usopp snuck aboard
the Ark Maxim to rescue Nami.
I'm sure they've been aware
of us for a long while now!
They know?! What're we gonna do?! Hey!
There's no point in worrying about it.
We'll split up inside and
head straight for the deck!
Nami-san is there!
Meanwhile, Luffy had a gold ball
attached to his arm by Eneru
and was thrown from the Maxim
into the ruins of Shandora,
but he got back up to settle the score.
Alright... Dammit!
I can't get this gold ball off!
Don't call it that!
Usopp saved Nami in the nick of time,
but unable to stand up to Eneru's power,
they found themselves
trapped in a corner, when...
El...
--Sanji-kun!
--Go.
...Thor!
I was just about to ask... for a light...
"Capriccio for Despair-- Looming
Destruction of the Sky Islands!!"
I'm going to pay... you say?
What the...?!
The ship!
No, you didn't!
Yeah... You'll pay for this...
Damn you!
What were you doing
inside the ship just now?!
Damn you! You've got some nerve!
The gears have gone awry... I must fix it!
All right! He's gone!
Don't worry! Nami fell safely
into some Island Clouds!
S-So high up!
Not the jungle, not the ruins...
Focus on falling into the Island Clouds!
U-Usopp Hopping!
I-I jumped too far! I jumped too far!
No! I'm falling! I'm gonna crash!
I'm gonna crash and die!
Yikes! I forgot to unhook it!
Usopp! Sanji-kun!
That voice! Nami! Sounds like
you're all right! That's a relief!
Are you okay, Sanji-kun?!
I'm so sorry you had to get all
charred like this just for us!
I-I can't breathe! N-Nami!
Pull me outta here, quick!
Oh! Sorry!
Anyways, let's get out of here...
W-Why won't you come out?!
I'm gonna die...
Curse you, Blue Sea man!
This ship is not so easily brought down.
I'm fully acquainted with
this ship's drive circuits.
Even without electric power,
the wind power from the 200 Jet Dials
I gathered from my homeland of Birka...
...will keep the ship afloat for a while!
No matter what you feeble beings try...
...this land will meet its end!
Look! That huge vine!
If it's the same one I saw in the ruins,
these are the Island Clouds up above them.
Ruins? Oh, the city of gold?! It exists?!
Yeah. But all the gold is in Eneru's hands now.
In any case, Zoro and the others
should be in the ruins below!
"Ruins of Shandora"
"Current Location"
I don't know the topography or anything...
...but I do know it's dangerous to stay here!
Yeah. Get on!
Let's find everyone and get off this island!
Yeah!
There are no safe places left here in Skypiea...
Luffy! Look out!
It's so fast!
L-L-Luffy!
Wait! Not that way! Left! Left!
Eh?! I can't turn so suddenly!
Gum-Gum Hook!
Don't destroy my hometown!
Giant Jack's over there!
I know, but--!
Quit destroying stuff!
Stop!
It's spewing out thunderclouds nicely...
So the rat scurried off...
They're so restless and shrewd...
But no matter. The festivities are soon at hand.
Huh?!
Robin and the others are gone!
Zoro and Chopper...
And Wyper and God...
Where the heck did they go?!
I bet they've already gone up it.
Oh, yeah! Robin!
All right! Let's go!
A-Aisa?
I don't know...
Listen carefully...
The way things stand, this land,
Skypiea, will be annihilated...
The sky island will?!
O-Our village, too?!
Everything...
He said that he'd return
everyone in the sky to the ground...
Luffy.
Yeah?
Are the sky islands... going to disappear?!
Wyper and the others are right through here!
The ship is headed for the grand belfry!
What happened to the
navigator and the others?
If they're on board, could that mean they're...?
We made it through!
Down there! Luffy! Stop! Stop!
Robin!
W-What're you doing?!
Look after these guys!
Stop! Stop!
Luffy...
You... You grew hands!
"Gyaaaaa!"
What's that gold on your arm?!
Robin! The gold bell is at
the top of this vine, right?!
And Eneru's after it, right?!
If the belfry does exist, it'd have to be there...
"Gyaaaaa!"
--But he's already...
--All right, then!
Luffy!
He left...
Say.
Do you know where our
navigator is? She has orange hair...
Eh? If you mean Nami, she's on that ship...
Huh? I only hear one
voice coming from the sky...
There they are!
Robin!
Navigator! Long-nose! Cook!
Aisa! Thank goodness! Are you all right?!
Nami!
Zoro! Chopper!
Weird old man!
Yikes! A guerilla!
Dammit! Everyone's been taken out!
Oh, if only I'd been there!
Oh, yeah! Aisa! Where's Luffy?!
Wasn't he with you?!
Luffy just went up the vine
to rescue you from Eneru!
Eh?! Crap! We just missed each other?!
He left just now. I tried to stop him, but...
Talk about bad timing! There's no
time left! We gotta escape now!
Go ahead! I'll go after him on the waver!
You guys just get to the Merry somehow!
Eh?!
Dammit! That ship's fast!
Eneru!
Get on, quickly! The sky is
getting darker and darker!
What's wrong? You need to escape at once...
Chief... Aisa still hasn't--
I see. She hasn't returned...
Aisa is a bright child. Let us have
faith she is with some warriors...
All right...
Hurry! Hurry up!
Captain!
We can't make it through this
without the ships in the dock!
They'd have to go around the long way!
Men! Use dials to create rivers
inside the island at once!
Yes, sir!
Everyone! Please go to Cloud End
and escape to the Blue Sea!
God Eneru plans to eliminate this land!
If you stay here, you'll all die!
For the last six years,
what we've known most of all
is that Eneru has the
power to bring us despair!
And that the time is imminent!
What's the point of waiting
for a miracle to happen?!
Before you pray... Before you
turn a blind eye to reality...
...you have to do what you can!
The time where you could survive
if you lie low as a victim is over!
You have to take action!
You can't protect your own life
by blaming someone later!
Come on now! Make the
decision to leave this land!
How many islanders are left?!
Still half of them!
No more baggage allowed!
Get all the islanders out to sea!
Yes, sir!
Hold it! Leave the
two-billion-Extol-per-person departure fee!
Amazon-san! You need to escape, too!
--Eh?
--Hurry! To Cloud End!
--This land...
--Eh?
--It's about to be destroyed!
Eh?
The wind stopped...
Run! Run!
The time has come.
Now then. Let us...
...begin the festivities.
Mamaragan!
Get away from the island!
Don't dawdle!
The lightning is getting bigger and bigger!
The boats in the port have been destroyed!
To the western end of the beach!
Quickly! There are still boats there!
Run to the west!
Quickly! Toss your belongings!
Chief! You need to get on a boat!
Yes...
Great Warrior Calgara...
Please protect everyone...
What huge lightning!
We're gonna end up sky dust if we stay here!
Everyone! Hurry to the ship!
I'll get Luffy and bring him back!
A-A-All right! Got it!
Hurry, Robin!
We gotta carry these guys
to the ship somehow!
Wyper!
Swordsman!
Weird old man!
Thank goodness! You're conscious!
Hey! We have no time! Can you walk?!
Eneru! So you've started it...
Let's hurry. There's nothing we can do here.
Wyper...
Not even Luffy can deal with
an enemy flying into the sky!
Make it in time! We gotta escape
before this land is destroyed!
An exquisite view!
Don't assume things are gonna
turn out how you want, Eneru!
If you're feeling lonely, talk to me
You gaze at the heavens
as you wander about
Just like the moon,
you keep your gaze constant
And your deep reflection wanes
as you slowly disappear
Stay as you are, let those words guide you
Dream, you travelers who spend
countless nights drifting
Even if you may not be able to go back
you will surely start moving forward again
Some 400 years ago,
there was a man known as a liar.
No one believed him as he was
executed for his great lies and trickery.
But the truth was still passed on
in the clouds high above!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Led by a Bell's Sound! Tale of
the Great Warrior and the Explorer"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!