Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Whew, that's heavy!
W-What is that?!
I found it in the storeroom!
Those're cannonballs!
We finally got a cannon,
so I thought I'd do some practice!
Then just leave it to me!
I believe it was when I was three
that I jumped on a cannonball
flying my way and traveled
halfway around the world!
--How do you work this thing?
--Listen!
Hey, Zoro! Do you
know how to work it?!
He's been fast asleep all this time.
He's no fun.
A little further to the south is a
reef that'd make a perfect target!
For reals?!
Let's go! Let's go!
--Let's go there!
--Hey! You're gonna fire
a cannon without me?!
People used to call me Cannon
Master Usopp, you know! Listen!
"The Three-Sword Style's Past!
Zoro and Kuina's Vow!"
Hey!
I'm here to challenge your dojo!
Someone strong, come out! Fight me!
Dojo-challenging is
certainly rare these days.
Hmph! Don't take me
lightly just 'cause I'm a kid!
I'm unrivaled in the next village over!
Very well. I accept.
If I win, I get your dojo!
--And if you lose?
--T-Then, uhh...
I'll become a student here!
That will be fine. Now, then...
Kuina!
Yes, Father?
What?! You're not gonna fight me?!
Kuina is a girl, but she's even
stronger than the adults in the dojo.
I say this, even as her parent...
Fine!
Then please come inside.
I can use any I want?
To your heart's content.
All right, then! Let's begin!
Alright! Bring it on!
Bow before the gods!
--What's he doing?
--He's ridiculous...
Bow to each other!
Begin!
D-Damn it!
You've studied Two-Sword
Style techniques before?
No! Today's the first time I've
ever held a bamboo sword!
Today's your first time?
Damn it! I'm strong!
And I'm gonna get even stronger!
I refuse... I refuse to lose to this girl!
Oww...
Why doesn't he dodge?!
Match over!
He's like a boar.
Come now, Kuina!
It's 10 years too early for an
amateur to use the Two-Sword Style!
What?!
What? We can fight
another match, if you want!
Damn it! A loss is a loss!
Yes. It's good to accept
defeat gracefully. Then, you'll...
Yeah! I'll become a student here!
Got a problem with that?!
None whatsoever.
I'm going to train lots and lots and lots
and then I will beat you!
Remember that!
That day'll never come.
Match over!
The winner is Kuina,
with 2000 wins and 0 losses!
D-Damn it...
You're still as weak as ever, Zoro!
You're so pathetic. Especially for a boy.
Hey! Zoro isn't weak!
He's the strongest one
out of all the guys!
He's even beat grownups!
But he's weaker than me.
Even with two swords,
a weakling's still a weakling.
You losers'd do good to stay quiet.
Your howling makes you pitiful.
You lost again, Zoro...
Even after you've grown so strong.
Sensei! Are you
giving her secret training
'cause she's your daughter?!
Don't cheat!
No, no. I do no such thing.
Zoro did indeed grow stronger.
But Kuina has grown stronger as well.
--Zoro?
I'm gonna wash my face.
Damn it!
Why can't I beat Kuina?! Why?! Why?!
I'm gonna be the strongest
man in the world! So why?!
Tonight... I'm gonna fight her again!
A mere year since he became a pupil...
Zoro's improvement is
nothing short of spectacular.
He trains incomparably
more than any of the others.
So I suppose it's only natural.
But... it seems he's still
no match for Kuina-san.
Female swordsmen are
faced with immense walls.
As she is now, I cannot
let her inherit the dojo.
--Father!
--Kuina-san!
It's not nice to eavesdrop, Kuina.
I will become the world's
greatest swordsman! You'll see!
Kuina. As a girl...
...you can never be
the world's strongest.
Zoro?!
What're you doing out here?
That's my line! What are
you doing here at this hour?!
I'm here to challenge you
to your 2001st fight!
I plan to make this
my last fight with you!
I'm going to end this!
Fight me with a real sword!
You have a real one, don't you?!
Against me?
Sure.
The Wado Ichimonji...
Two real swords are heavy, huh?
It seems you still lack strength!
S-Shut up!
My 2001st win.
Damn it...
This sucks...
I'm the one who should be
crying out of frustration.
Eh?
You see, when girls grow up,
they get weaker than men...
Even you'll catch up to me soon...
You're always saying you're going
to be the world's best swordsman.
My father told me that
a girl can never be that...
I know...
I know that! But... But it's frustrating!
You're lucky, Zoro. You're a boy.
I want to be the world's
greatest swordsman, too!
My breasts have even
started to grow out now...
If only... If only I had
been born a man...
Don't be whining like
that after you beat me!
That's not fair! You're my goal!
--Zoro...
--Boy this, girl that!
Are you gonna say that stuff
too when I beat you someday?!
You act like none of it is skill!
You're insulting all the hard
training I've been doing!
So don't say that stuff!
Promise me!
Someday, one of us will be
the world's greatest swordsman!
We'll compete to see who gets there!
You dummy. You're so weak...
--It's a promise!
Whoa...
She's gotten even stronger than before!
Gotta get stronger! So I can
hold lots of swords just fine!
If two's not enough,
then I'll use three!
What do you guys want?
Kuina...
Kuina's dead...
Apparently, she slipped and fell
down the storehouse steps...
Storehouse?
Seems she was looking for a sharpening
stone for her beloved sword.
What would she need that for?
I don't know...
She was just a child, too...
There's just no understanding people...
No one knows what's
just around the corner...
People are such fragile things, Zoro...
Kuina... She was a very
competitive girl...
She practiced in this dojo
since she was little,
and achieved strength
that exceeded even adults.
Because of this,
she became a bit self-conceited...
But then that's when
you appeared, Zoro.
I thank you.
You grew ever stronger, so she
started to practice even more,
so as not to lose to you.
So as not to lose to a boy...
And she had begun to break down
the walls of female swordsmanship...
...but I'm an ordinary parent, too.
When I look at you now,
I feel pained, too...
Sensei...
Let me have... that sword...
Kuina's sword?
I'm going to get stronger for her, too!
I'm going to get strong enough
that my name reaches to Heaven!
I'm going to be the world's
strongest swordsman!
I promised her...
I...
Yes. You can have it.
I leave Kuina's spirit
and dreams... with you.
Eight years since then...
You're finally going to set out, then?
Yes, Sensei.
To fulfill our promise.
Zoro!
Take care.
Huh? That was way off!
What are you guys doing?!
Cannon practice!
But they sure don't fly good!
I'm telling you, let me try!
Judging from the last flying distance...
This should do it.
Fire!
Awesome! You hit it on your first try!
I really hit it...
Whadya think?! I'm awesome when
it comes to aiming! Impressed?!
Yeah! Yeah!
It's settled! You're our sniper!
What?! I don't get to be captain?!
I'm the captain!
Well, whatever! I'll humor you for now!
But if you do anything too cowardly,
I'm taking over immediately!
Yeah, that's fine.
But anyways, I was thinking, there's
one other position we need to fill
before going into the Grand Line!
Yeah! We have a fancy kitchen, too!
If you pay me, I can do it!
An important necessity
for long trips, right?
Yeah! All pirate ships need one, huh?!
A musician!
Are you an idiot?!
What do you see voyages as?!
Just when it seemed you were
gonna say something smart...
But pirates sing, you know!
Come out, you damn pirates!
What the... What the... Who are you?!
Shut up! Who I am
doesn't amount to crap!
How many are there?
One... I think?
Then leave it to him.
"Sea" Then leave it to him.
"Sea"
We've taken the heads of many a pirate!
Are you nameless pirate
wannabes trying to kill my partner?!
That voice...
What do you mean, "partner"?!
I dunno what's going on,
but stop breaking our ship!
L-Lost by a hair...
What's going on?
Hey! Is that you, Johnny?!
Who's saying my name all familiar-like?!
B-Big Bro Zoro?!
It is you, Johnny!
What are you doing here, Big Bro?!
Where's Yosaku? Isn't he with you?
What now? What now?
You guys know each other?
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
I guess we need a cook, huh?
They say there's a "Sea Restaurant."
--A navy ship's firing its cannons!
--Alright! Leave it to me!
The restaurant's that way, you idiot!
I'll go apologize!
What's taking so long?!
Let's check it out and get some food!
--Huh?! A fight?!
--What's with him?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Famous Cook!
Sanji of the Sea Restaurant"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!