Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King
of the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
The horizons everyone
dreamed of were separate at first
but now they can be seen
through a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny
is leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve
your dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
--Where am I?
--Oh, you shouldn't move yet.
Chief! The golden belfry...
In order to prevent Luffy and
Nami from reaching the ark,
Luffy and Nami were stranded at God's Shrine.
We still have the duty to protect it to the end!
Raigo!
Eneru released Mamaragan. However...
How's it look?! Have we lost them?!
Don't rush, Wyper.
Eneru's ship is too far from the top
of this vine. What should we do?!
Looks like they've given
up. I can't see them.
Vearth, at least, is not refusing anyone.
It's useless, Eneru.
Really? Good!
How can we get there?
Anyway, that monstrous
cannon sure scared me!
Isn't there some way?
The land won't be beaten!
Right... Right now, at least,
no one wants to fight.
Luffy was approaching the ark.
In the meantime, Eneru had
finally found the golden bell.
Where the heck were they hiding that thing?!
He eradicated Angel Island...
Hand over... the golden bell!!
A cannon?!
Yeah, you know, that huge thing
that the warriors were carrying.
"God"
Disappear with the land!
So this is it...
Raigo!
It's party time!!
Oh, that...
"Oh, that"?! Hey, it's no laughing
matter! It was really scary!
Splendid!!
Old diamond-head's ancestor...
Gum-Gum...
So this is the grand belfry that was the
pride of the legendary city, Shandora!
He wasn't lying.
The long battle of 400 years had ended,
He's right! Don't laugh!
So I have to let the old guy
and the others below know...
...Fi... re... works!!
Ah! There they are! It's Nami and Conis!
and all the citizens of Skypiea continued
their joyous party day after day.
What?! Nami-san!! Conis-chan!!
Nami, who had devised a plan, sent
a message to Usopp and the others.
...that the city of gold was in the sky!
Gold Peony!!
Ow!
Clear up!!
I can't let Eneru take it!
Oh? There's something written on it.
I'm sure the huge bell can
be heard from anywhere...
"I Made It Here! The Yarn the Poneglyphs Spin"
--Are you all right?!
--Of course!!
Straw Hat! Ring the "fire of Shandora"!!
...so that's why I'm going to ring the gold bell!
"Cut down this huge vine
so it falls towards the west."
"Off to the Blue Sea!!
Finale Woven by Feelings"
Luffy finally reached the ark, and at
the end of the fierce fight with Eneru...
"Knock Over Giant Jack!
Last Hope For Escape"
However, Eneru's final attack was imminent.
Well then, I'll ring you as well!!
What? They rushed off of the island?
"God"
Yes. We couldn't even give them our gift.
Gum-Gum...
I've accomplished all my objectives.
...Gold Rifle!!
How disappointing...
All that's left now is...
Even Heaven's Gate... was blown
away in the blink of an eye.
I wonder if they even realize how
much we appreciate what they did.
...to destroy this land together with
the cumuloregalis clouds using Raigo,
To think that Angel Island is gone...
What're we supposed to do now?
and set off for the Endless Vearth.
Exactly. They have no idea how I feel.
In any case, we have to escape
to the Blue Sea via Cloud End!
It's not fair, Aisa... that you alone
got to say goodbye to them.
I... I... I can't drink any more...
We have no other choice!
But there're still many people
left in the White-White Sea!
Reach!!
Everyone's in an uproar that
we let our saviors run away.
Reject!!
What can we do?!
How can we bring those ships down to
the White Sea without the Milky Roads?!
There they are!
But Luffy and the others
told me not to tell anyone.
"The Battle Ends! Proud Fantasia Echoes Far"
Then, are we giving up on them?!
Break! Giant Jack!!
Did you say anything to them?
Yeah! I said, "Thank you."
Hey!
--What is it?
--Nami, wake everyone up!
Here goes! Get on, Luffy!
Run it at full power!
Why?
Hey Laki, did you know?
Luffy's body stretches!
Okay!
We're gonna steal the gold and run!
He'd be like, "Gum-Gum Pistol!!"
There's gold?!
Hey, Aisa, don't move!
Idiot! Not so loud!
It's insolent of you to try and come to me!
You need to be taught a lesson!
What do you mean "idiot"?!
You're louder than I am!
I didn't know there was a strong
warrior like him in the Blue Sea, too.
Can you hear it?!
Old diamond-head! Monkeys!!
Hey! I'm louder, you say?!
You're the louder one!
I wanna be like him, like "Gum-Gum...!"
Even this area will be like that before long.
Mamaragan!
What?! You're calling me loud
when you're really super loud?!
Aisa...
The White-White Sea is...
Let's just trim your hair
for today. Let your hair grow.
Your voice is the one that's
really super-mega-ultra loud!!
The city of gold... was right here!!
"Miracle on God's Land! The Love
Song That Reached the Angels"
There's no way that's true!!
I'm talking loud because you're loud!
What?
Skypiea is fading away...
I'm sure it'll look good on you.
You're a girl, so you should look cute.
--Shut up! I can't sleep!!
--You're the one who spoke loud first!
Cute?! Me?!
"God"
Upper Yard is... being pulverized.
--What?! You're the loud one!!
--It wasn't me! It was you!
I'm a delicate woman! I wouldn't yell
with my mouth wide open, would I?!
That's right... since there won't be
any need for you kids to carry arms...
What?! There's no way
I'd do something like that!
Luffy!! Nami!
That bonehead did it!!
--See? See?! Your mouth is wide open!
--Geez, wake up, sleepyhead!
But you did hit me here! Here! It's really true!!
How beautiful...
...and since you can now live freely,
like people in the sky should.
--That's because you ticked me off!
--Nami-san! Good morning!!
Looks like he doesn't want to come
in contact with you ever again, huh?
What a pretty sound! What is this?! What?!
--Oh? It's not morning yet!
--Yeah, yeah... Go ahead and
be feeble-minded like that.
"God"
--Like I said, you don't
have to shout, you know!!
--What do you mean, "feeble-minded"?!
Blue Sea people sure like to party, don't they?
You're ladylike today.
Not a chance!!
I believed that this moment
would come one day.
This is the fourth day in a row.
Their vitality isn't normal.
Now, don't move, Aisa!
The ruins are being exposed!!
--Ladylike Laki!
--Aisa!
So this was the ring that Noland heard.
He intends to pulverize the ground.
So, that's the plan.
Wyper's lying on the ground down there!
Okay, guys! It's not often that
we get to visit a sky island!
Great Warrior Calgara...
So this is it...
Zoro, too! That son of a bitch!
We were told that the Shandians'
role had been fulfilled.
Suu... I wonder if Vearth is singing...
Make it so that you'll have no regrets!
Splendid!!
And I'm sure your wish was delivered
to your best friend as well.
He's so cool!
So this is the grand belfry that was the
pride of the legendary city, Shandora!
We no longer have to make
future generations shed blood.
The ruins...
This is getting exciting!
So God really... exists?
Amazing! This is a perfect fit
for me, the one who is God!
The battle is over...
but we won't lose our pride!
What a miracle!
It's useless, Eneru.
I had half given up on the bell ringing
again after its 400-year silence.
The bell that proclaimed the start
of this land's 400-year-old conflict...
So please continue to watch over us.
You can't bring down...
Chief! We found the golden bell!!
Wyper!
We swear that we will not let the
fire of Shandora go out ever again!
What?!
But to think that they carried on with
this pointless battle for so many years...
Great Warrior Calgara... Can you hear...
Hey, are you serious?!
Yeah. It's stuck on the fallen Giant Jack.
...the history of the proud warriors
who lived in the land of Shandora.
...the echo of the fire of Shandora...?
We're pulling it out right now.
Those who can help, come to the
western seashore! Hurry! Hurry up!!
...only to see everything disappear...
Okay, guys! Gather everyone!!
What happened to this land?
Hurry to the western seashore!
I am the Sky Knight,
a freelance soldier-for-hire.
No matter where it is, this grand power
is strong, creates and nurtures.
--The belfry was found!
--Where?!
What is this tone? Could it be...?
This land won't need such a thing anymore.
--At the western seashore.
--Okay!
Is this the legendary...?
You just can't bring it down!
--Are you sure?!
--Yeah! Hurry!
Luffy, you can't catch up with him any longer!
What this land needs now
is someone to govern it.
No matter how many forests you burn...
They said they found
the bell that fell in the sea!
Yeah. Those who can move,
gather at the western seashore!
I'm saying that I'd like
you to be that person.
Eneru's ship is not moving from that place...
No matter how many ruins you destroy...
Are you hearing this... Montblanc Noland?
You're the best suited for it. This city
belonged to your people from the start.
The belfry was found!
It's at the western seashore!!
Sorry to have kept you waiting so long.
I hope...
The belfry was?
What's this all of a sudden?
That's not a good reason.
One more time!!
...this reaches your descendants!
Luffy... Eneru must've taken
the golden bell by now.
One, two...!
With this battle, I think
everyone must have realized...
Pull!!
...that no one can own Vearth.
The land won't be beaten!
"God" is our support.
No matter how hard you stretch
your arms, you can't reach up there.
The name of the land is Skypiea.
The name of the city is Shandora.
If he took it, then I'll take it back!!
You like this bell's sound, too?
The only person who can unify them is you,
Let me use this!
who continued to be anguished
by the battle in this land.
--Get out of there, Wyper!
--It's dangerous!
Wyper's gonna die! Let me go, stupid!
Dammit! We still need more people.
Sky Knight Gan Fall... I would like
you to take the seat of God again,
Hm? I can still hear driveling from below.
and support this land
whose scar is still deep.
It's the pride of our ancestors' city,
Shandora. We'll get it at any cost!
Eneru's ship is too far from the top
of this vine. What should we do?!
That's right!
We'd like you to, as well!
Give it everything you got!!
One more time!! One, two...!
Gan Fall-sama!
Old-timer! Th-This is...
--If it's you, we'll accept it, too!
--Yeah!
Yeah! There's no doubt about it.
--Gan Fall!
--God!
How can we get there?
There's only one bell in
this world that echoes this far!
Please come back!
This is romanticism.
Everyone...
No one can be allowed to escape now!
--From the sky...
--I'm getting worked up.
Honestly...
Just when I thought I could finally
really enjoy growing pumpkins...
About the monsters that appear
with the cumuloregalis clouds,
Including the several unmoving
voices directly below you!
there used to be a story like this.
When there is a human far up in the sky
and strong sunlight shines on him,
That's right!
They haven't escaped yet...
Everyone's still down there!
his figure is reflected in
the deep mist of the far sky.
Pull harder!!
Vearth is... That's right!
The shadow looks as if it's a huge monster.
So the true form of those monsters are
the shadows of the humans in the sky?!
Rubber band?! So you call this a rubber band?!
Then does that mean that we've already
confirmed that people live in the sky?
Yeah! My Usopp Rubber Band did 90%
of the work of taking Giant Jack down!
It's not sinking!
Upper Yard wasn't affected at all!
Yeah.
Everyone! We can see it now!
I thought the story was a meaningless
fantasy and I'd forgotten about it,
--Whoa!
--Whoa! Incredible!
Please look to the front! It's Cloud End!
Watch out! Something's falling again!
I'm the only one in the world that has them.
What great power!
but it seems that it was true.
--Whoa!
--Whoa! Amazing!
Ah! Let's see!
--What's that?
--Everyone, heads down!
I see... So we can go back down from there?
I can hear the loud ring of the golden bell.
But... put that aside for now.
I'd like to show you this iron sheet!
That's right. Vearth is so grand!
We got here sooner than I thought.
A leaf...
Now, ladies and gentlemen!
This is no ordinary iron sheet!
So we're going back down, huh?
The city of gold really exists in the sky!
Yeah, now that we're about to
go back, I admit I hate to leave.
Vearth wasn't something to fight over,
I tore it off from the Going Merry,
our ship that endured very hard travels
Oh? There's something written on it.
"Noland The Liar"
It's time to say goodbye
to this pure white sea.
Noland wasn't... My ancestor wasn't a liar!
but the blood of many people
was shed, and many lives were lost.
It's a message! From Luffy and Nami!
on the Grand Line, as well as Eneru's
attacks! It's the "King of Iron Sheets"!
The sky island was fun...
though it was scary.
What does it say?!
So once we go through that gate,
we'll be heading straight down
Why didn't we notice it for 400 years?!
How about it?! You guys want iron, right?
You rang it to tell me that from the sky...
to the Blue Sea via a Milky Road, huh?
Would you trade me dials for this?
"Cut down this huge vine
so it falls towards the west."
No! I want this rubber band!
I'll trade you for this rubber band!
I wonder if we can visit
the sky island again...
...right, kid? I appreciate it!
Hard to tell with this place.
What?!
Wyper!
--I want one, too! Is that okay?!
--Me, too!
Um, what'll happen... if we do that?
--Whoa... Are they serious?!
--Give me one, too!
--Me, too!
Wyper!!
Hey, where's west?
Get out! The vine is falling!
Come over here, now!!
Well then, everyone! I'm sorry!
We'll say goodbye here!
A-Are we really gonna do it?!
"Monkey"
Water, light, fire...
So... where's west?
Please take care, everyone!
It's the direction where Eneru's ship is.
Things whose shape is transient...
Go...
Thanks for seeing us off!
Conis-chan! Take care of yourself!
--Old-timer?!
--What's the matter?! Are you sick?!
Say hello to the others!
Things with no form...
See you!!
Go! Straw Hat!!
Those kids... I'm glad they were safe!
Thanks for everything!
I cut them!!
No, we should be thanking you!
"God"
Here I come!! Eneru!!
I was... so worried...
I'll never forget you all!
They're a bunch of...
Conis, old guy and little
white one! You all take care!!
Hand over... the golden bell!!
Yes!
Shells! I got shells! Oh, yeah!
Now, furl the sails immediately
and hold on tight to the ship!
Enough of this! I'm sick of you!
I've accomplished all my objectives.
--Lucky, lucky! I got so lucky!
--You're in a good mood, aren't you, Usopp?
I think this is big enough.
Alright! Do as the old guy said!
Sounds like it's gonna go pretty fast!
All that's left now is...
Did the negotiation go well?
Yeah, we're sliding from a
7,000-meter height! Hurry up!!
"God"
Disappear with the land!
Hear that? I got lots of dials!
...to destroy this land together with
the cumuloregalis clouds using Raigo,
Okay!
and set off for the Endless Vearth.
Raigo!
I press it and...
Look!! That's...
Just like that!
Wh-What?! What?!
Good for you.
God's ship...
Good for me! With this many dials,
I can do many different things!
Now that the time has come,
I almost hate to go.
He says, "Don't forget about me."
Oh... That's the South Bird
we brought to the sky with us.
The Usopp factory'll be running full steam!
It's God!!
Eneru!!
Hey, Zoro, if you make
your swords Flavor Swords
Damn him!
Now, Captain! We got
the log for the next island!
They're sinking...
and store the smell of
stuff like melons in them,
That is way bigger than the one from earlier!
you can enjoy your everyday training!
Nami, thanks!
God Eneru and his ship are...
--No thanks.
--Oh...
What?!
Yeah! Once we get off from here,
we'll start on a new adventure again!
...sinking...
We... won't be able to escape
from this land... any longer!
There's no way I'll let your help go to waste!
Oh, yeah! I can make
Nami's Clima Takt stronger!
Wait, Luffy!!
My slingshot will be incredible, too!
Guys! You ready?!
The bell's ring is the fire of Shandora,
The ship is that way!!
We're gonna go back to the Blue Sea!
a long-gone city that
took pride in its prosperity.
Yeah!!
Farewell, Skypiea.
So, where are Robin, Luffy and the others?
Luffy! There's an eddy of air
and lightning in there!!
Luffy and the others are still inside.
Robin went somewhere.
It's bigger than the last one! That bastard!
The island's singing voice that
proclaims the end of the battle...
Who knows what'll happen to you?!
Yeah. Now that he's got the golden bell,
What can you do before this
huge power, rubber man?!
he no longer has any business with this land.
The promised ring was
delivered after 400 years...
In any case... this snake's really conked out.
Everyone! Be careful while dropping!
He's easy to figure out.
I'm not gonna let him have his way!
He kept dancing day after day...
...though I don't know
what he was so happy about.
Nami, weren't you going to escape?
While dropping?
Anyhow, they'd better come out soon,
because if he wakes up,
he could give them a hard time again.
You expect me to leave now?
Huh? This good-tempered snake?
You want to ring it, right? That golden bell?
Although the journey of
the restless island was long,
Idiot! You just don't know
how troublesome he can be!
Yeah! I'm gonna ring it!
it's hard to forget the distant memory.
This good-tempered snake?
Honestly... you can't even control the waver.
Heso!
Like I said, you can be so
optimistic because you didn't see
Long ago, people entrusted their
words in the sound of the bell.
Even if I just leave you here,
you'll keep trying to jump anyway,
what a pain this snake can be.
This good-tempered snake?
so I'll give you a ride and shoot you up there.
Here we go! The sky island's
famous Octopus Balloon!
Hey, now listen here, Usopp!
But...
This good-tempered snake?
They placed proud words in
the song sent to the distant sea.
--It was a Tone Dial!
--Don't do stupid stuff like that!!
...you have to guarantee my life!
Yeah, it's stupid! It's really stupid!
Okay, got it! Thanks!
Gum-Gum...
Comrades...!
What the heck?! What does this snake eat?
We're just gonna get one chance, one moment!
It's an octopus!!
Are we there, yet, Luffy?
...Fi... re... works!!
You son of a...!
Look! There they are!!
I hope they got my message okay.
Wow! Amazing!
It rang...
This is the real thing!
Yeah.
It's pretty! It looks just like the ones
that we saw at the monkeys' house!
Ow-ow...
Wh-What?! What the...?!
I wonder... if the old guy
and the others heard it.
Gold Peony!!
Yeah, I'm sure.
See? See? See?! There's all this!
Hey, look! This is so cool!!
Isn't it awesome?!
What the hell is this?!
It's a balloon!
This is fun!
We're... right here!!
We've slowed down!
They're gonna jump to the ship
by crossing the falling vine?!
I... I thought that I was finally
gonna go to the netherworld.
How dare you use thunder to create
bad weather for the idyllic sky islands?!
What else could it mean?
That's crazy...
Then you go up there and stop them.
You lightning freak!!
As if he could be stopped!!
In any case, reckless or not, we've
got no choice but to let him do this!
Wh-What is this abnormal electric discharge?!
That's right...! He has gold, which
can transmit electricity, on his hand!
Wh-What the...?!
Tie the ropes to strong-looking trees!
Long-nose!
Ah, got 'im!
If we stay here, we'll be
pushed off to the ruins below.
Everyone, get away from the vine for now!
Well, all I have to do is drop it before
the electricity completely discharges!
Escape to solid ground!
Ring it! See off the saviors of
this land by ringing the bell!
Anyhow, I'm gonna do it! I need to cut
the vine down towards the ship, right?!
So this is gold...
Everything... be gone!
What?! But...!
Heso!
The only ones on this sky
island who can reach Eneru
--How beautiful...
--Incredible...
--I didn't expect it to be this...
--How magnificent.
Luffy! See you again!!
--before that thing is dropped...
--Hey, Zoro!
Captain McKinley! Please stop.
This is God's Land. It's pointless!
But one of the side columns has been broken.
Come visit us again!!
...are those two!!
Thank you!!
Yeah, but there isn't much we can do.
Go back to the Blue Sea safely!!
I don't care if there's no point!
Hey! Look at that.
There's nothing else humans can do
when the situation is life or death!
You just don't know when to give up.
So this is... the Poneglyph...
It's too late to struggle or escape now.
Aisa... Were you worried?
The stone that our ancestors
risked the city's life to protect...!
In order to survive,
we chose to abandon our land.
You still don't get it?
When you look up, you see the sky.
Here... your treasure!
When you entered the survival game,
your fate was already decided.
Now we've lost a place to
return to and our way forward.
Is this God's Land on the
clouds a dream or reality?
I don't care about that!
Just what is written on it, Chief?
All that we can do is pray.
10,000 meters far up in the sky...
Laki...
I-I-Is he okay?!
If you listen carefully, you can
hear the sound of the bell.
Something we're better off not knowing...
When we hear the "island's
singing voice," this battle will end.
We're counting on you! You're the
only one who can cut that thing down!
It rings today, and it
will ring again tomorrow.
We just...
The sound of the bell that echoes in the sky
"Hold our true motive in your
hearts and speak not of it.
glorifies and sings about
the wandering land...
--How's everyone else?
--They're fine! Don't speak right now...
Damn you, making all these holes!
We are the ones who weave history...
I wonder if no one will survive at this point...
Someone's there!
...with the sounding of the grand belfry..."
Am I still alive?
How do you know those words?
I wonder if, had I had the
courage to stand up to Eneru,
No! You have to get treated right away!
They were carved on the Shandoran ruins.
This is cool!
My treatment can wait.
I wouldn't have had to involve those people...
So you were the keepers,
entrusted with this for generations.
Yeah! This feels so good!
Before treating me, do something
about that guy, or he'll die.
Alright!! He cut it!!
Say, Suu...
I wonder if God exists?
Ahhh! Zoro!!
Could it be... You can read those characters?!
If he does, I wonder if he'd save us...
You're right! His body's falling apart,
right down to the bones. This is terrible!
Please... if you really exist...
You worms!
Poseidon, the "ancient weapon"
named after a God...
Hey, that's one of the guerrillas.
We don't owe him anything.
You're calling off the search?!
It's just natural, right?!
The city of gold was in the sky.
Its whereabouts...
...please protect them! God!!
Yeah. I don't really know why, but it
seemed like he was going all out, so...
--What?! What's that?!
--She said "ancient"!
You bastard!!
We won't find anything
at the bottom of the sea.
B-B-But he did it! He cut it!!
Ancient weapon?
Please... make a miracle happen!
Protect this land! God!!
Why is it talking about something like that?!
This is the end.
Huh? What the heck?
Are you feeling sorry for him?
Yeah...
Oh, no... Look!
There's no point in staying here.
Another weapon...
--Old-timer...
Who knows...?
It's not coming down...
even though it was cut...
...separate from Pluton
that I read about in Alabasta...
Um...
I really thank you all... for joining
me to pursue my dream for years.
Is he gonna be okay, Raccoon-Doggy?
I hear that one shot from Pluton
will completely destroy an island.
What a strong vine!
Is that thing really a plant?!
I'm a reindeer! Look, I have antlers!
Don't worry. He'll survive.
What're you saying...?
How pathetic... This is what you
outsiders get for butting in.
Clear up!!
To think that there are such dangerous
things in this world waiting to be found...!
Don't treat us like strangers...
Thank you!
Say, you guys!
Wyper! Don't be reckless!
Quiet!
Just as I thought, this was a disappointment.
What kind of romanticism
shall we go after next?!
Pierre, go and rest with those Blue Sea people.
It is important that we, the inheritors
of Calgara's wishes, ring that bell!
This isn't what I want to know.
"Noland the Liar"
What does this have to do
with that Straw Hat?!
Hey! Aren't those the same kind of
characters on that engraving next to it?!
We'll follow you to the ends
of the earth, old-timer!!
Leave him be, Robin! He can't stop us
when he's seriously injured like that.
Pierre, hurry up and go bring the families!
What?!
Our priority now is knocking over that vine!
"Gol D. Roger"...!
Luffy and Nami are waiting up there!
Gold! Gold! Gold! Gold! Gold!
So, in the end, both the golden
bell and Eneru's golden ship...
In any case, Zoro cut half of the stem.
What?!
We've finally become super rich!!
What shall we buy?!
The whole thing should be tilting by now.
I think they fell.
I made it here. I will guide this
text to the ends of the earth.
By hitting it with my
Dance of Exploding Stars...
How about buying a huge bronze statue?!
So now it's a city of gold in name only, huh?
You moron! What's the point of
exchanging gold with bronze?!
...it'll be leveled with a loud scream!
Clear up!!
Pirate Gol D. Roger.
Which means our journey
in poverty continues.
We should increase the number of
cannons! Let's buy ten of them! Ten!
King of the Pirates...! Could this mean
that he came to this sky island, too?!
As expected, I am the last line
of defense of this pirate group!
I'd want those dials rather than gold,
Nami-san! I want a lockable refrigerator!
since we won't be able to get them
once we get back to the Blue Sea.
Robin, take care of those who have fallen!
--Don't be stupid! What're we gonna
do when we get hungry?! I object!
--I... I... I want you to buy me some books!
In any case, I wonder if Nami-san's all right.
What on earth do these words mean?!
I wonder where Conis-chan is...
--I want to read medical
books from other countries!!
--That's just why we should buy it, you dumb ass!
No, more importantly,
why can he use these characters?
They look like a kashiwa-mochi cake.
Hey, hold on a second, you guys!
Move out!
We'll split the treasure once
we get back down, okay?
The mass of thunderclouds has disappeared!!
Is it okay to leave Wyper
with the Blue Sea people?
Please buy books for me!
So it says Roger?
Don't worry. It seems that
Aisa made friends with them.
What happened?
If we buy whatever you guys like, I have
a feeling that it won't do us any good.
You know him?!
He's a Blue Sea pirate who came
to this sky more than 20 years ago.
At any rate, we have to hurry.
It's pointless if our enemy wakes up.
Navigator...
Four hundred years ago, an explorer
told a lie that he saw a city of gold.
What?!
I wonder where this ship is heading.
Gather those who can move.
We'll banish the priests to the clouds.
Where? The next island...
So his name is engraved there?
Yes. I don't know how he reached this bell,
Yeah!
Although people laughed at him,
his descendants believed his words
Are you done with him?
--What?! What?!
--What's the matter?
Yeah. All he needs now is rest.
but this sure is indelible proof that he did.
What's the matter, Nami-san?
and are still searching for this
city of gold in the Blue Sea.
Yoo-hoo!!
Luffy!
Darn! We started riding an air current
at some point and now we're drifting!
Luffy!!
Come to think of it, there're two
kinds of Poneglyph stones.
Air current?!
Nami-san!! Conis-chan!!
Come to think of it, there is a wind...
Is that a problem?
Ones with information, and others
that indicate their whereabouts.
If we ring the golden bell, we can let
them know the city of gold is in the sky.
Of course it is! As it stands, we don't
know where on the sea we'll land!
Luffy!!
And this stone is one of
the ones with information.
What're we gonna do? In this state,
I can't set the sails and control the ship.
Straw Hat! Ring the "fire of Shandora"!!
That's what that straw hat boy is thinking.
Everyone! I'm glad you are okay!!
Exploding Star!
Well, don't worry. We'll just head back
to the next island once we reach the sea.
Go, Luffy!!
That's a wonderful reason,
isn't it? It has romanticism.
I was so worried, but I couldn't do anything.
Let us hear the singing voice of the island!
"I made it here. I will guide this
text to the ends of the earth."
Conis-chan, so you were
worried about me that much!
You just blurt things out
casually, as always...
Even in a situation like this...
I don't think so.
But...
Is that food, you guys? Where'd you get it?
...going so far as to lose
his chance to escape...
What is it, Sanji-kun?
Guide this text... Guide...
We found the priests' food storage
on our way back through the forest.
Well... I guess it was my imagination.
He's nuts!
Hm? What're you talking about?
There were more.
Exploding Star! Exploding Star Star!!
How dare you destroy Raigo?!
You monkey from the Blue Sea!
But how did you get down from that height?
Usopp Rubber Band! Rolling
Exploding Star! Exploding Star!!
No, nothing...
There's a problem! Hey!
We used my Gum-Gum Balloon.
It couldn't be...!
Could the Rio Poneglyph be...?!
Well then, I'll ring you as well!!
By the way, Conis, where's your old man?
Hm?
"God"
You insolent brat!!
Well... um... he protected me...
Oh, it was just a dream.
What's with you?!
What... is the name of
this explorer's descendant?
Chief... This Poneglyph
has already fulfilled its role!
--I'm gonna cut you into fillets,
you damn Moss Head!
--You scared me!
200 Million Volt...
Now, now, Zoro's tired, too,
after the battle in the sky, so...
Montblanc Cricket...
It has?!
...Amaru!!
That's right. I bet those Poneglyphs with
information scattered around the world
Then... is the name... of his ancestor
from 400 years ago Noland?
What the hell is that?!
Ring, you said?! You mean the golden bell?!
will, when put together, become one text
...and then Eneru...
that will fill the "Blank History"
for the first time.
The sun's completely set now.
The next time it rings,
it will be the end of the battle.
But it's a nice view.
What?
Don't tell me...
Yeah, you're right.
Wyper?
In other words, the text
completed by connecting them...
Are you trying to hang onto such a legend?!
What're you doing all of a sudden, Wyper?!
Hm? Is it morning?
Conis-chan...
I just said that the sun set!
That is the Rio Poneglyph,
which still does not exist.
Conis-san...
I am God!
It's taking quite a long time
to get to the Blue Sea.
Conis...
Is this a miracle...
I'm so worried about how
far the ship will drift.
Hey, we're talking about you!!
Gol D. Roger, King of the Pirates,
...Great Warrior Calgara?!
I'm sorry I'm still alive!
definitely delivered this text to its destination.
Then shall I sing a love song or
something to take your mind off it?
You are just a Paramythia!
Father!!
Shut up!
Come on, Nola! We'll ring the bell again today
There's no way that I can't
crush you with my Logia power!!
In the White Sea on the lower level?
It'd be quick and easy if we
drifted to Raftel, wouldn't it?
so that the sound reaches
to the end of the sky!
Yes. I found myself there
after being knocked off.
Usopp! That'd be cool!
Let's send the sound that you love to Noland!
So it's no longer...
Those who came down to the lower
level heading towards Cloud End
That's not possible.
--Then...
--Hm?
To get to Raftel, we still have to go more
than halfway around the Grand Line.
...does that mean that our duty
has been fulfilled as well?
are also coming back to the White-White Sea
via restored Milky Roads right now.
We...
Uh, well, yeah... I know that.
I said it doesn't work on me!!
However, since there's
no Angel Island anymore,
We... don't have to... fight any longer?
In any case, I'm so bored.
I'm sick of this "I'm God" crap!
they're heading towards Upper Yard.
When are we gonna reach the sea?
What god wouldn't save anything at all?!
Oh, just go to sleep.
If you're bored, come here,
too, Zoro! This is fun!
I see... Our ancestors' wish
has been fulfilled, then?
Oh? Luffy?
--Chief!
Where did his voice come from?
Are you all right?!
It sounded sorta far off.
Good... Good... So our duty has been fulfilled!
Luffy! Where are you?!
What the...?!
--Thank you very much.
--Thank you very much, God!
Ouch!!
I'm over here! Everyone, come up here, too!!
Yes.
I'm no longer known by that name.
Oh? You grabbed hold of it
to avoid being skewered, huh?
Which means I, too,
This is fun!!
have to guide the text on those
Poneglyphs that I read in the past...
You were all forced to work in a place
like this for six long years. I'm sorry.
Ugh! So he is up there!
What was that?
Luffy!!
But... to think that this vine wasn't
affected by that shock at all...
What are you going to do, rubber man?!
...to the end of the Grand Line... to Raftel...
Awesome! This is awesome!!
--Ow, ow, it's hot! Ouch!
--You have nowhere to escape!
--Dammit! This time'll be Triple Explo...
--Out of my way!
We lost Angel Island, the home
we were supposed to return to.
The pull of your arm will make the spear
dig deeper and deeper into you!
Hey! Don't be reckless!
Our lives depend on that balloon!!
Young lady, the feeling that straw hat kid
gives me is reminiscent of Roger.
The Shandians, too, lost their home,
Village Hidden in the Clouds.
Yet, if you get away, you'll fall!
Is the battle really over?
Don't worry! Don't worry!
Calgara...
Is it my imagination?
You've done well to climb up this high!
They say that the
descendants of your best friend
His name is Monkey D. Luffy.
My interest in him never fades.
However, this is the end
of you and this land, too!
are still waiting for...
the ring of the golden bell!
God's army is gone, but...
No, Luffy! Come back down!
D? I see. He's got the same letter in his name.
Chief, is the 400-year rift
something that can be filled so easily?
Hey Luffy, stop it!
I can create another Raigo!
What's the matter all of a sudden, Sanji-kun?
This octopus is shrinking!
If we don't do anything, we'll fall!
What patience those guys have!
Yes... and I'm sure it's a big issue
that has something to do with history.
This is our citizens' duty... I'm sorry!
--What?!
--Hey, Luffy!
--Boy, I stuffed myself!
--It's totally night now.
Reject!!
What's going on?
Shall we go back to the ship now?
--He said this octopus is shrinking!
--What?!
By the way, young lady...
You guys wanted gold, right?
Nami, what're you saying?!
Now that you mention it,
it looks smaller than before.
Huh?! If we go back to the ship,
You said it's more valuable
than Vearth in the Blue Sea.
we can have a long relaxed
sleep in a warm bed, right?!
What're we gonna do?!
We're still pretty high up!
Ugh! What the heck was that?!
Yes.
Wyper!!
I wonder if it'll last
until we reach the sea...
Hey Usopp, you heard what she said?
How about taking the broken belfry column,
Yeah, it's terrible. Not thinking
anything after seeing that,
How foolish... A Reject Dial...
though we can't give you the bell...
Hey Luffy! Something is strange,
so come back down!!
Luffy... are the sky islands...
going to disappear?!
That's a good idea!
you're unqualified to be
a pirate-- no, to be a human!
Naturally, we have to show our
appreciation to you guys somehow.
Break! Giant Jack!!
"That"? What're you talking about?!
--That's right!
--Don't hold back!
Are you sure?! They'll be happy to hear that!
What the heck are you talking about?!
Yeah!
So you chose to fall!
Alright, then! Let's bring
this to the Blue Sea people!
It's coming down!!
Wrap it with cloths! It's hard to carry!
I'm returning... to where God should be...
That was quite a scare, since
it stopped bouncing suddenly.
We'll give this to those who saved our land!
Luffy!!
Man, this thing's huge...
Here goes! Get on, Luffy!
Like I said, the octopus is shrinking!
Nami! Out of the way!
Things that obstruct my field
of vision cannot exist in the sky.
Run it at full power!
To be honest, I've never tried the
maximum power of this Jet Dial
Wh-What're you...?!
You all were in my way.
O-Oh? I didn't do anything,
but we came back to the ship!
Don't mess with me, earlobes!!
What's Robin doing? She's late!
Gum-Gum... Rocket!!
Ahhh! We're falling! We're falling!!
because it's too strong for me to control.
I won't let anyone have it. It's fit just for me.
Darn! I'm hungry!
This is bad! At this rate,
we'll be swallowed by the sea!
In any case, this place is
so empty. What's going on?
--Then use it!
--Okay!
It's a boundless land, just like a dream.
There's no guarantee
that we'll fall into the sea!
Gum-Gum...
Ugh! That's right! Dammit!
Where the heck did the
guerrillas and angels go?
Now, let's set off, Maxim...
What're you doing, Usopp?!
--Here we go, Luffy!!
--Yeah!!
What else?! Protecting the ship!
Are you trying again?!
Well, it's better they aren't here.
If they find us, they'll chase us around!
To God's world that
floats brightly in the night...
Until the bell rings!!
Since we're trying to steal this much
gold and run, they won't just let us go!
To the land without end, the Endless Vearth!!
This time, I'll skewer you!
What're you gonna do?!
Gold Rifle!!
Don't be reckless, Usopp!
It's coming down!
Look!
Well, Nami and Conis are preparing
to set sail, but we still have to hurry.
What on earth is going on?!
Usopp Aa-aa-aa!
We're counting on you two! Luffy! Nami!
Before that, Sanji, do you
have something to eat?
It's too fast!!
Not until we get to the ship.
If the sky island disappears now,
we won't be able to ring the golden bell!
But you've gotta have
something to munch on, right?
Where am I?
Okay, it worked!
--Give me some!
--What a pain!
Inside the ruins of Shandora.
You'll ring it, right?! You'll let
old-timer Cricket hear it, right?!
--We don't have to wait for that woman, do we?
--I can't give you what I
don't have! Just give up!
Alright!
I'm gonna go on ahead and get on board.
Gan Fall!
I'm gonna use all the Breath Dials I have...
Oh, you shouldn't move yet.
--Idiot! Don't!
--Idiot!
Jump to where Eneru is!
--Idiot Moss Head!
--Moss Head Idiot!
You... are a Skypiean!
There! Float!!
Go!! Everything depends on you two!!
If you go into the forest alone, you won't
make it three steps without getting lost!
Rest.
Chief! Were we captured by the Skypieans?
Go!!
When you return to Jaya, what will
you think when you see we're gone?
Hey, look! It's Robin!
--It's slowed down.
--Sweet!
Were we saved?
There's no distinction among
those injured in battle.
Robin-chan!!
Looks like it.
Yoo-hoo, Robin!! Hurry! Hurry up!
We've gotta run!! We stole some gold!
My, my... Why can't you quietly
wait for the completion of Raigo?
Did you see my wonderful work?!
The golden belfry... We still have
the duty to protect it to the end!
Hold on a little longer! I'll let you know...
Usopp, you're so cool!
Idiot! Don't say that!
Take a good look behind her!!
How impatient they are...
I wondered what was gonna
happen for a moment there!
...that "we are here"!
This is...
Yeah, seriously, I thought that was it.
They're all coming back here together!
...the sound of drums announcing a battle!
I have no choice, then.
There's fire on the ruins, too?!
There's tons of them!!
Why?!
Don't rush, Wyper. Wait a little
and see how things turn out.
Light the fire of Shandora!!
This is bad! This is bad! This is super bad!!
Something's coming!
Usopp!!
Don't slow down! I'll repel those things!
No matter what kind of heroic reason for
the fight there was in the distant past,
And what's that? A huge cannon?!
It's been 400 years since
the battle in the sky started.
Everyone, grab onto something and hold tight!
to us who live in the present time,
this sky is our home.
That's gotta be it!!
They all came back all at once!
Just once, we wanted to...
The land, at least, is not refusing anyone.
It's missing us! You're a bad shot!
Hurry to the ship! We can no longer stay here!!
That's right. The sacred ground will...
But at this very moment, there's actually...
It's insolent of you to try and come to me!
You need to be taught a lesson!
Check this out! We got a good catch!
The bag's stuffed! We're rich!
Right... Go ahead and
check it with your own eyes.
...sing again...
It's cold...!
Right now, no one wants to fight.
Hm? They all have bags on their back!
Nami-san! Robin-chan! Are you okay?
Mamaragan!
Don't tell me... Are they already leaving?!
Hey, stop, you guys!! Stop!!
That startled me! The octopus
suddenly shrunk all the way!
...someday, for sure.
--Hey! Stop! Stop, you guys!
--See?! They found us out!
Run!!
I wonder if the air leaked out.
What the heck happened?!
I'll strike a pose and say it!
That bastard! He's trying to
sink the vine from the base!
But we somehow made
it down... without dying.
You guys say, "Stop! Stop!" but...
It's party time!!
You! Thanks!
Do something, Nami!
Yeah! Tell them, Usopp!!
I can't do anything! We're already climbing up!
Six years ago, I saw a giant city of gold
on the Grand Line island of Jaya!
Still...
We risked our lives to come
all the way to this sky island!
If this vine loses its foundation, we'll no
longer be able to come up this high!
--That's right!
--And we've found the legendary city of gold!
--Robin-chan! Hurry up! We'll be caught!
--How the heck can we, proud pirates,
...we really went to an
incredible place, didn't we?
We won't be able to get close to Eneru!
Now that we've fallen, it's so far up.
just go back empty-handed?!
The city of gold does exist!
It's as if we were dreaming.
What?! Caught?! What's he talking about?
It's a dream land. I wonder if
we can go visit again some day.
All we want to do is thank them!
Upper Yard is being pummeled with attacks!
Hey Miss, aren't you guys
gonna take this gold?
You might be able to get closer if you die.
No one in history's ever disproved
the city of gold or the sky island.
Zoro, so you think you can go to heaven?
You jerk!
Looks like they don't need it!
Well, things're calm now at any rate.
I'll make coffee or something.
What?!
Luffy! Nami!
Oh, no!
That's what romanticism is!
I'd rather have dinner, Sanji!
I'm saying I'll get on it right away,
so have some coffee and wait!
Reach!!
--Run!!
--Hey! Wait!
Okay...
Old guy! Can you hear it?
They're all after us! It's scary!
By the way...
The city of gold is here!
Even if the lightning doesn't work on you,
How was that?! Wasn't I cool?!
"God"
For 400 years, the city of gold
has been here all this time...
Yeah! Well done!
it doesn't mean anything
unless you can reach here!
Robin-chan! Hurry!!
Fall down below and wait for the
completion of Raigo, rubber man!
Hey! Come back!!
...in the sky!!
Guys! Keep running all the
way to the end of the sky!!
Where the heck... are we?!
Yeah!!
If you're feeling lonely, talk to me
You gaze at the heavens
as you wander about
Just like the moon,
you keep your gaze constant
And your deep reflection wanes
as you slowly disappear
Stay as you are, let those words guide you
Dream, you travelers who spend
countless nights drifting
Even if you may not be able to go back
you will surely start moving forward again
Listen, Luffy, make sure you end it this time!
I can hear the bell. This is romanticism!
Hold our true motive in your
hearts and speak not of it.
Listen, everyone! We'll split the treasure
once we get back down, okay?!
Ugh! Where are we?!
What are these spotlights?!
Where did you learn those words?!
Disappear with the land!
I'll keep it safe, so don't worry.
--A stage?! Is it my one-man show?!
--Idiot!
I thought the story was a meaningless
fantasy and I'd forgotten about it.
So these are the words engraved on the belfry...
--Where?!
--It's a secret.
This is the siren for a state of
emergency! Could this place be...?!
No matter how much you destroy,
the land won't be beaten!
The ancient weapon Poseidon?
There's no way I'll tell you where
I hide my secret stash, right?!
But there is only one bell in
this world that echoes this much.
If that's the case, it looks like we've
fallen to a damn troublesome place!
Why was Gold Roger...?
Could the Rio Poneglyph be...?!
--Hey!
--Just kidding!
What God wouldn't save anything at all?!
The city of gold was in the sky!
Looks like we'd better
first get away from the ship.
That's a lie! Her eyes say she's telling the truth!
We're pirates, you know.
Now, let's snatch the gold and run!!
I'm gonna ring the bell no matter what!!
Noland wasn't... My ancestor wasn't a liar!!
What?! What about dinner?!
Alright, guys! We're going back to the Blue Sea!!
Let us hear the singing voice of the island.
On the next episode of One Piece!
Yeah!!
"A State of Emergency Is Issued!
A Notorious Pirate Ship Has Infiltrated!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Off to the Blue Sea!! Finale Woven by Feelings"
"I Made It Here! The Yarn the Poneglyphs Spin"
"The Battle Ends! Proud Fantasia Echoes Far"
"Miracle on God's Land! The Love
Song That Reached the Angels"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!