Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King
of the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
The horizons everyone
dreamed of were separate at first
but now they can be seen
through a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny
is leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve
your dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
The Straw Hat Pirates have fallen right
into the middle of the fortress Navarone.
See ya, fortress guy!
"Sanji the Cook! Proving His
Merit at the Navy Dining Hall!"
The Going Merry fell right into the
middle of a Naval base, Navarone.
H-Hey! It's me!
--Hey!!
--Imprison him!
Zoro was captured.
# The impregnable fortress, G8! #
You should thank Robin.
I see... She thought that it'd be
safer for me to be with you...
In addition, Luffy and the
others infiltrated the base,
Is it true that this ghost
ship fell from the sky?!
Luffy and the others dispersed
under the cover of darkness.
# Pirates can't come near it! #
I can't believe it...
and an impending crisis drew
nearer to them each minute.
It might've been better if I didn't check into it...
But Navarone is a grand fortress that
prides itself on its impregnable defense.
Nami successfully disguised
herself as a cleaning person.
"On Duty"
# With its 108 cannons jutting out, #
To think that there's only one escape route...
Falling from the sky is the only way
a pirate ship could make it this far.
Luffy and Sanji slipped into
the dining hall as cooks.
"The Navy's Dragnet Closes In!
The Second Member Captured!"
I-I heard that there was no one on board.
# it's a hedgehog that protects the peace! #
"Daring Luffy and Sanji!
Their Great Rescue Operation!"
However, one of the crew,
Zoro, has been captured.
# Our pride, G8! #
Among the Straw Hat Pirates
that we already captured,
But they found coffee and
cigarettes sitting out on the ship
Welcome to Navarone.
You know, though, I hear our fortress
isn't very popular lately within the Navy.
there was a man wearing a uniform
who pretended to be a Navy officer.
Navy Command Branch 8...
as if there had been people
right there up until that moment.
That's the official name of Navarone.
"Captured Zoro and
Chopper's Emergency Operations!"
Listen up! You can report it later!
And inside the room in the back...
People also call it the Navy's
strongest, an impregnable fortress.
Yeah, I hear there're
some people who call us
When you see suspicious individuals,
imprison them immediately!
dim-witted hedgehogs made
soft by peace behind our back...
A mountain of gold?!
Its headquarters should be
in that island in the center.
It's not surprising, since we've had hardly
any pirate attacks the past few years.
Moreover, it's the kind of gold buried
for hundreds of years in ancient ruins.
Yes, sir!
But that's about all we know.
We don't have to know things like that.
So six more, huh?
What'd you say?!
I've never heard such a creepy story.
You want to investigate a fortress now?
It wasn't me who said that.
It's a rumor! A rumor!
Aren't ancient ruins enough for you, Robin?
One of the Straw Hat Pirates, Roronoa Zoro...
A-A ghost ship?
Of course! We're in the enemy's midst.
Did you hear?! That long-nosed guy
was a crew member of the Straw Hats!
They must've been cursed by
the ancient ruins and disappeared.
Drake, shall we try questioning him?
Tsk! What's their problem?!
Peace is wonderful!
Even so, we don't have the luxury
of looking around forever!
Yeah. But why did he take
the trouble to come here?
But you told us to check
the dining hall, Commander.
What's wrong with peace?!
What I wanna know is whether
the Going Merry is okay or not.
To the 4th, 6th and 10th units
under Lt. Commander Drake!
# The impregnable fortress, G8! #
Yeah. In the bay, there're lots of
ships that are better than this one.
Hm? I did?
Where the heck did you go, Merry?!
--Assume second-degree
battle formation and stand by.
--I don't know if it's a ghost ship or what,
You said that everyone gets hungry,
so they're likely to appear in the dining hall.
It's probably reasonable to think
that it was seized by the Navy.
They could've taken one
of them and quickly escaped.
--Commanding officers are to
report to Control Room #1
--but they think they can pick a fight
Geez...! How can you say
such a thing so calmly?!
--in the central building immediately!
--with our fortress, Navarone?!
That's how stupid pirates are!
I'll go to the dining hall.
--I repeat! Commanding officers
of the 4th, 6th and 10th units
--Hurry it up!
Jessica told me that new cooks from
headquarters are coming as well, so...
--are to report to Control Room #1
in the central building immediately!
--Just who the hell are these guys?!
Even if we find the ship, how are
we going to get out of here?
You're right!
Are you saying that the Navy
will show us the way out?
Every day is a beautiful day.
Navarone? I see. I get it now.
How should we proceed
with questioning Zoro?
W-Well...
"Justice"
That's why we should thoroughly
investigate first. Right?
I'll leave it to you.
Of all places, we jumped right into
the middle of that grand fortress
Oh? Are you already done
for the day, Mechao-san?
that the Navy's so proud of.
Don't slave-drive an elderly man.
So what're we gonna do, Captain?
I wouldn't be a pirate if I
were scared of the Navy!!
He says he's "elderly"!
Man, they really tore up this ship!
As if!
I can't take this anymore. I'll leave
the thorough investigation to you.
It'll probably take at least a week to fix it.
I guess he could care less.
Our orders are to fix it in three days.
Man... What the hell's with these guys?
Oh, man...
Hurry up! This is an emergency order!
My leg!
Did this ship climb a mountain or something?
Robin! What the hell are you...?
Oh, it's you, Mechao-san.
--Found them?!
--No, sir!
You damn idiot! At least try to be careful!
That's a good way of putting it!
Some of the Straw Hats're
hiding around here for sure!
We'll moor the pirate ship to Dock 88
and investigate it thoroughly!
Yeah, it'd have to climb a mountain
or something to get this wrecked!
S-Sorry.
Leave no stone unturned!
Well, you know, it might've
fallen from the sky.
Yes, sir!
Geez... This is such a complicated fortress!
It probably got caught around the
sea gate when entering the port.
Well, I guess I'll take it easy for a while.
Reporting, sir! The Stan Marey
is demanding entry.
There's no way they can escape when
even that Roronoa Zoro was captured.
I wonder where Zoro and Usopp are...
Yeah, that area is very narrow,
so it's hard to pass through,
What?!
even for a navigator who's used to it.
Since we're in a state of emergency,
I advised them to wait a while, but...
--Z-Zoro was?!
--Are you all right, Long-nose?
Well, since they got caught,
they were probably sent to jail.
Open the cell.
D-Did you hear that?
Now, let's stop joking around
and get to work already!
We ran into a storm and have many injured!
Yes, sir, Lt. Commander Drake!
But he's extremely dangerous.
Okay! Then we'll go to the jail!
This means they now know that it's
the Straw Hat Pirates, not a ghost ship.
This is an emergency! Please allow
us to receive treatment at once!
Do you know where the jail is?
By order of Vice Admiral Jonathan,
I'll question Roronoa Zoro.
Okay, okay...
You don't know, Sanji?
Our enemy's in a frenzy. Why don't you
worry about yourself instead of the ship?
How would I know?!
I know it's a ship from headquarters,
Yes, sir! Please be careful.
Geez... Sailors these days don't
have enough love for their ships...
I don't care! Sorry, but that ship
is more important than my own life!
Hmmm...
but there's a big possibility that there're
pirates hiding within the fortress.
I think that belly button island
is suspicious after all.
We cannot permit them to enter!
I'm going! I've decided! So don't
get in my way anymore! Later!
Roronoa Zoro... You used
to be called a pirate hunter.
If we allow outside ships to come in now,
it'll cause unnecessary confusion and...
What makes you think that?
Dunno, I just do.
Open the gate.
I would never have imagined that you'd
be a member of the Straw Hat Pirates.
But in any case, that sounds about right.
He's impossible...
I'll permit their entry. Immediately
assign a medical team to them as well.
What, you came all the
way here to tell me that?
It's surrounded by the sea.
What's the matter, Mechao-san?!
On top of that, the only way to
escape is to cross that bridge.
Where did you come from?!
How many of you are there?!
Yes, sir!
It's a pain, but I guess we should go there.
What is your purpose
in invading this fortress?!
Alrighty!
Commander!
The uneasiness felt by those who are
injured in the middle of the Grand Line...
It was a good strategy to invade this
"hedgehog" fortress from the sky.
How did you do it?
Did you build a launch pad?!
Dammit! Going the way we
came is also gonna be a pain.
Oh, we came from heaven.
You understand that feeling, don't you?
Don't mock me!
Of course! However...!
I'm not mocking you or anything.
We really came from the sky.
I've come all the way in a
storm to such a remote base,
You know, this is the first time I've
gotten a little fired up in a long time.
I don't intend to go along with such a joke!
Yes, sir! This is District 4 in Block F. All clear!
and they send no one
to escort me?! How rude!
Well, they can't get out of the fortress.
Like I said, we came from heaven
by riding a floating octopus balloon.
"A State of Emergency Is Issued!
A Notorious Pirate Ship Has Infiltrated!"
Hm? Hey, you over there!
Keep searching!
Yes, sir!
I'm supposed to meet the
commander of this base.
Still, why did they come to Navarone?
Got it?
Inform them to send someone
to escort me immediately!
Monkey D. Luffy...
So you insist on that, no matter what?
They're in contact with each other
using Mini Transponder Snails.
"Justice"
Yes, sir! Before that, please tell me what
business brought you to our fortress.
We've got a problem!
Ships are coming in!
This isn't gonna be easy.
I-It appears that we've been invaded
by a huge object from the sky!
Don't make light of the Navy!
--Hey, Sanji.
--Hm?!
We are now on first-degree alert!
I don't have to explain it to a mere private!
This is kinda exciting, isn't it?
An invasion from the sky?!
F-From the sky, you said?!
Have the boarding inspection bridge ready!
I'm gonna make you tell
us the truth at any cost!
Get moving already, you damn monkey!
Excuse me, but may I have
your division and rank?
I'm saying I don't need to explain it to you!
Contact your headquarters immediately!
"Justice"
This is a big fortress...
Even if I did, I don't think it'd do any good.
An unidentified mysterious
object has invaded the base!
"On Duty"
Anyway, where am I? Should I go back?
What do you mean by that?!
Hurry up! Guard the sea gate!
Since Commander Jonathan is eating
right now, I think he's in the dining hall.
Next, you'll be in charge of
cleaning this exercise hall.
You guys go watch the coast!
What's up with the layout of this fortress?!
Sniper Unit! Move it!
Okay, Boss!
Then all you have to do is go to
the dining hall to talk to him, right?!
But I'm sleepy...
It's too huge to grasp the whole thing!
Um... don't you know the motto of Branch 8?
Ouch!
"On Duty"
Where am...?
Close the sea gate!!
Motto, you say?
We have to get out of here
as soon as possible...
Freeze!
One! Wash your hands before eating!
What is this...?
Two! Never leave food on your plate!
...but the more time goes by,
the harder it gets!
Three! Never mention work while eating!
Where did everyone go?
I have to clean this... by myself?!
Four! After eating, make sure to brush...
"Port Entry Records"
That's enough! So to the
commander at this base,
eating is more important than a
VIP sent by Navy Headquarters...
No way!
Give the floor a good polish!
You'll enjoy lunch after your hard work!
What is this?! It's too huge!
--Is that what you're saying?
--Yes, sir! That's correct!
Hm? Where's the Merry?
This disguise may have been a mistake!
Over there! 4 o'clock!
The Merry's gone!
This is strange. There're times when
no ships enter or leave. Why is that?
All right, I get it. I'll go to
your headquarters on my own.
Hold on a sec! Where's the Merry?!
4 o'clock! All lights on the target!!
I heard that one of the
Straw Hat Pirates was captured!
Before I go, I'll give you a piece of advice.
Where the heck is my gold?!
Gold, gold, gold, gold, gold, gold!
What?! That wasn't a ghost ship, then?!
Find another job while you can.
Yeah, in a sense, it's scarier than ghosts.
Don't be surprised when I tell you this.
After we went through
all that trouble to get it...
I'm being watched...
It's Roronoa Zoro, the pirate hunter!
Huh?
Ships... And they're battleships...
--Whoa!
--What?!
Hey, you! What do you think you're doing?!
There should be other
crewmembers hiding, too.
The hedgehog that has now become
useless in this area of sea...
P-Pirate ship...
You must be the 31st unit!
Go to the B Building in the 7th block!
If we could find even one
of them, we'd get noticed!
Who do you think I am?!
The odd commander who stays inside,
never setting even a foot outside of it...
The pirate flag has... a skull with a straw hat!
Y-Yeah!
You told us over and over on our way here.
To think that Zoro was caught...!
What am I gonna do?!
Some ships came in... which means
that this place isn't a lake!
You're Special Inspector
Major Shepherd, right?
The Navy doesn't need either of them at all now.
Th-The Straw Hat Pirates?!
I'll probably report them to
Headquarters at some point.
Wh-What?!
It's connected to the open sea!
If you know that, get me
out of here right now!
Hmph! That darn badger! He'll no
longer be a commander in a few weeks.
All right! I have to gather everyone
right away and find the Going Merry!
Ready!
According to what they just said,
everyone else seems to be okay.
I have business with Commander Jonathan!
Target the Straw Hat Pirates' ship!!
Darn! I wanna get out of here already!
But I don't know where they are,
Go ahead and enjoy the few
Navarone meals that you have left.
Major Shepherd?
If I somehow slip into that crowd and
pretend to be a person on the inside,
Did somebody say "Straw Hat"?!
and I don't know what to do...
--Oh, I see! This is the guy
Robin was pretending to be!
--Enough of your nonsense! There's no way
I can collect information as well!
What's that?!
Where is it?
--So they've mistaken him for one of us instead!
--a Navy major from Headquarters would
let his ID and his coat be stolen so easily!
If I continue to live like this,
I'll break down before I get caught!
Luffy and Zoro's faces are known
to the Navy, but luckily, mine isn't.
If that's the case...
Hold it!
--Stop it now. It's disgraceful!
--Hm?!
Guess it was just my imagination.
Oh, is this it?
Lt. Commander Drake!
A man should know when to
give up! Let's not struggle...
Help!!
The ship that has invaded our base
is the Straw Hat Pirates' ship!
Oh, crap!
Hold it!
Straw Hat, you say?!
Where's Commander Jonathan?!
What is up with this fortress?!
...my comrade, Condoriano...
So it wasn't me...
C-Condoriano?! What's that?!
Who the hell are you?!
It's like a maze.
Well... we can't find him.
But I have to come up with
a different disguise... Hm?
Do you know where the kitchen is?
Honestly, that man's...!
Hey, hey... Stop making bad jokes...
Kitche... Oh! Yes, I do! Kitchen, right?!
Navy Headquarters Inspection Division...
You expect us to believe you've
forgotten my face or your own name?!
This is it!
I'll be damned... To think that
someone invaded from the sky...
What a good person to bump into.
We just came in by ship.
Hey! Don't come near me! I'm not your buddy!
Th-This isn't good! It's a dead end!
What a pain! We're lost.
The raccoon dog went that way!
I don't know him! I don't know this man!
Sorry to hear that.
All right! The corner is raccoon dogged...
no, the raccoon dog is cornered!
Ow, ow... What happened to you?
--Whoa! Yum!
--The new cook is pretty good!
I used to get lost all the time, too,
when I first came here five years ago.
It's just like what those guys who
ate first thing in the morning said!
What should I do?! What should I do?!
Oh, no... Did the impact from the fall
cause you to lose your memory?!
You've been here for five years?!
Everyone! The next 100 soldiers're waiting.
Then, take us to the kitchen.
How sad... It's too sad!
Hurry up and finish eating!
Hey! Please! Would you let at least him out?!
Aye aye, sir!
We can't ask for help from the
cooks here. Help us out here.
He's not here.
Resistance is futile! We have
you completely surrounded!
Here you go.
So he really was a raccoon dog.
He disappeared!
Can I say no?
He's not the same Condoriano that I knew!
Hey, Jessica...
We came from Marie Jois.
There's no harm in doing us a favor.
This is your usual dish, right?
Hm?
"Full of Power!"
"Carbohydrates!"
"Navy Dining Hall"
That settles it.
He's in there.
Yeah. There isn't even a
point in interrogating him.
Any problem, Commander?
--There's no benefit, either!
--Okay, pretty lady?
Wh-What do you mean, "that settles it"?
Well, my men are carrying on about
the incredibly delicious food
No problem!
Wait! What're you going to do with me?!
Do you two know anything about this fortress?
prepared by the cooks from Marie Jois.
Don't you think it's been pretty noisy outside?
Wait! Don't you get that
I'm telling you to wait?!
It'll be a lot of work finding him in here!
Yeah, I wonder if there're
intruders or something...
No, we brothers are both cooks, so...
So I came here looking forward to it.
Condoriano!
You don't like it? When I, the executive
chief chef, cooked it for you myself?
We're cooks of some reputation in the Navy.
Ouch!
Who's Condoriano?
No chit-chatting!
Whoa! Big name cooks?!
--Ah!
--Shh!
You can't continue to eat the same kind
of food as the younger ones, right?
Look! We have to prepare
meals for 1,000 people!
We're going to be the
chiefs of the kitchen here.
Shut up already!
It's a healthy dish filled with
lots of love. Bon appetit!
Nice move, Zoro!
In Marie Jois, we've satisfied generals
who have a discerning palate.
In two hours, a bunch of boys
from the night shift will show up!
But it has lots of vegetables as well...
I don't like broccoli and carrots.
It went well! You should thank me, Robin!
Here we go!
We're far from the kind of cooks
who excrete insignificant meals
You look creepy, Usopp.
There's no time for fooling around!
What're these?!
Branch 8's Motto 2!
in the middle of nowhere.
Did he leave just his antlers?!
--But...
--The siren from earlier...
Ah, um... A-All right... Here!
We first have to show them
that we're in a different league.
Who knows? But with just antlers,
we can't even make a pot dish.
See? I'm eating it.
Don't worry, lads!
When did I ask about that?!
In any case, unless I lose them
Whoa! This is yummy! This one's yummy, too!
The day this fortress falls
is the day the world falls.
and disguise myself or something,
I can't even collect information!
Dammit! Did we lose him on our way here?!
Guys! Keep up the good work!
Besides, when Jessica-sama
blows up, she's a lot scarier than...
What's that newbie doing?!
He's been sampling food all this time!
Wow! Just what you'd expect
from the legendary cooks!
Don't worry about him. He only does tasting.
Now, all you have to do is turn here
and turn right on the first corner.
I'm saved...
Commander...
Jessica-sama...
No matter how I look at him,
he doesn't look like a cook
Then go straight and turn left twice,
and you'll see the kitchen!
...there still haven't been any reports
of the other Straw Hats being seen.
who was in charge of the
kitchen at Navy Headquarters.
What is it?
--Okay.
--This way, huh?
In contrast, look at you! You're very skilled!
Where is the package?
Commander! Where have you been?!
--See ya.
--So is this the first corner?
It's probably that way.
You're quite popular among the soldiers, too.
Ah! This is it!
Thanks. I'll write down
my recipes for you, then.
What should we do, Commander?!
What're they doing with deer antlers?
Prepare food for table 8! Please hurry up!
I heard that they'll be used
as ingredients for medicine.
I didn't catch anything today.
They're probably having a
hard time finding the jail.
Again?!
Aye aye... sir!!
But I had a large catch yesterday!
Okay, this will do!
For a beautiful lady, I'd go through
hell and high water! There!
I guess we'll lead the way.
Roronoa Zoro.
What?! What happened?!
I'm not talking about that!
Commander, if you're always absent...
They told me that the ship they're calling
a ghost ship is Straw Hat Luffy's ship.
Huh?
They said that they ran into a storm.
Many were injured. Hurry it up!
You go ahead of them and wait.
What's the big deal? Night fishing
isn't necessarily a waste, you know.
Wh-Whoa!
At Commander Jonathan's direction, we,
the unit directly under Lt. Commander Drake's,
Be sure not to act hastily.
Take them to the medical room quickly!
Oh! That looks yummy! Okay!
I'll take it to the table for you.
were given a secret mission to capture them.
Yes, sir!
Hold it! If you touch that food,
you won't be eating meals. Got that?!
When we face them, the one
considered to be the strongest is...
Commander, I have a report!
According to the watchmen,
"On Duty"
...Roronoa Zoro...
Let me see... Plunge the scalpel
vertically, and if it bleeds...
as well as the maintenance men inside
the dock who saw the ship close by...
Aye aye, sir!
He's a great swordsman who used to
be feared as a pirate hunter, right?
I wonder if he really gets it...
Well, why don't we ensure our
victory by making the first move?
In any case, the guy at table 8 sure is lucky.
I hear that he uses the Three-Sword Style.
A-According to them...
In any case, we'll capture them and
make them regret ever coming here.
What is it?
Blood, blood, blood...!
She may not look it, but she
cherishes her husband, so...
Spit it out already!
Who is he saying he'll make regret something?
Yes... well... um...
Oh? Jessica-san has a husband?
Ow...
Hm? I passed by here earlier.
If you have time for chit-chatting, get to work!
They say they saw ghosts.
What're you doing, Sanji?
And why are you walking around so openly?!
Shh!
Who the heck is this
"luckiest guy in Navarone"?!
Like I said, something
suddenly fell from the sky!
Dammit! I guess we have to
force our way through after all.
That hurt, you son of a...! Oh, it's you.
A hairy monster appeared.
It jumped and then disappeared.
It's the Commander of this place, Branch 8.
If you're wearing three swords
so openly, they'll know right away!
What?! The Commander, you say?!
Hands... Hands...
--Hey!
--I'll be caught, too, right?! Geez...
Hey, it's unguarded down there!
Crap! Luffy...!
What about hands?!
Honestly! Why did all the doctors
have to go on a business trip at once?
Hands grew out from my body, and the
next moment, everything went black!
Let's go, Luffy! We'll head down there!
Oh, God, please don't
send any surgery patients!
Okay!
In any case, you need to hide.
Hey, my swords...!
--Medical Room Chief!
--Yes...
That's right... they were a girl's soft hands.
--Here you go!
--Thanks. You can go now.
We brought the deer antlers,
the medicine ingredient.
It's gotta be...
It's about time to eat.
Aye, aye, sir!
Hello!
I'm hungry!
A ghost ship!!
Oh... Please leave them there.
Reporting, sir!
Phew, they're gone now.
--Don't be ridiculous!
--Yes, sir...
The one we captured earlier
Okay!
Without doubt, that is the Straw Hats' ship!
We don't have to hide, you know.
turned out to be a Straw Hat member
whose name is Condoriano.
When push comes to shove, we can just fight.
There's no way it's a ghost ship!
Where am I?
You big idiot! If you do that when we
don't know where everyone else is...!
Moreover, of all things,
to say that it fell from the sky?!
This tastes just like they
said it did. It's amazing!
--Condoriano?
--Yes, sir!
They'll all meet up, won't they?
He insists that he's Major Shepherd...
Now there's an idea... No, I mean,
the Merry is missing, too!
Well... the part about it coming
from the sky, at least, is true.
This dish lives up to my expectations!
...but we think that it's clearly a lie.
No need to shout like that.
Anyway, isn't this a nice view?
Yeah, you're right!
I look pretty good in this uniform,
if I do say so myself.
Okay, thanks.
I'll be fine if I look like this!
When we got here, it was night,
so we couldn't see well.
I told you that it isn't a waste, didn't I?
Ugh! I'm sorry!
Oh, this is good. Hey, Nami, if we watch
from here, the others may soon app...
What're you apologizing for?!
Go to the medical room already!
So there're two Shepherds, huh?
Right, Lt. Commander?
Don't be ridiculous!
Anyway, you stay put here!
What?! Hm? Huh?
There's an emergency!
All the nurses are being called in!
Seriously, you always get lost.
Well...
I knew it... I'm screwed no
matter what clothes I wear!
Hey, my swords! What're you doing?!
Dr. Kobato! It's an emergency!
Dammit!
I-Internal case? Pediatrics? Or...
In any case, try to keep in mind
that you have no sense of direction.
There're quite a few seriously
injured marines on the Stan Marey!
Let me have some, you cheapskate!
Once I've found the others,
I'll come and get you, so until then...
S-Surgery?!
You certainly live up to my expectations!
Hey, you! What're you doing over there?!
I-I'll leave them to you nurses,
since surgery isn't my field.
They found me! Oh, no...
What're you saying?! You're the
only doctor in this base right now!
"Group Leader"
Stop slacking off out here
and start cleaning already!
"On Duty"
Oops! Dammit! Looks like I was late!
But...! I'm a pediatrician and,
um, surgery is outside my field!
Hey, Zoro... Don't you
think this is kinda strange?
Aye aye, sir!
Welcome, Straw Hat Luffy.
Yeah. It gives me a bad feeling.
I see...
Man, I'm exhausted from
all this ghost ship business!
I'm Jonathan, the Commander
of Navarone, Branch G8.
A ghost ship, huh?
Oh... This seems to be a medical room.
Anyway, let's eat and
prepare for an emergency.
But I wonder if that doctor is gonna be okay...
It smells good.
--Ghost ship?
--Did you find anything to eat?
Looks like the dining hall is that way.
--Dining hall!
--Idiot! Wait!
What're you doing?!
--Don't be rash.
--I'm gonna eat!
Commander! I found
these in one of the rooms!
Food... Food...
One, two, three!
Hm? Oh?
You're... Mechao-san...
You're so stubborn!
Who's there?!
Ingots and a crown... Those are quite old.
Wh... What're you doing in a place like this?!
Freeze!
Straw Hat, I don't wanna
get violent in the dining hall.
Hm? That's strange.
This is crazy! Did they run
into a cyclone or something?!
What am I...? I just had
a little matter to attend to.
They must've stolen them
from some ancient ruins.
Was it our imagination?
But could you answer me one question?
We've been on edge since yesterday.
It must be because we're tired.
Pull them back already!
--Send them to the forensics lab!
--Yes, sir!
If I answer, can I eat half of that stuff?
Here, treat their injuries!
In any case, we should eat.
Hm? Not just half, you can eat it all.
Okay!
Well then, let's explore inside, shall we?
Really? Then I'll take it.
Sorry that I called you a cheapskate.
Darn! I don't have time for stuff like this!
Hmph! I see...
Idiot! They almost caught us! Hm?
Idiot! Hurry up and get out!
We have to quickly find the Going Merry
and leave this place right away!
So, what's your business?
No matter how hard I think,
I can't figure out your purpose.
It's not with you! I need to talk to
that long-nose held captive there.
This is good. We'll probably look
less suspicious in these uniforms.
Right. It is said that Captain Smoker
is the one who defeated Crocodile.
Chirps?
Wha...?! Wait! I can't let you
talk to a prisoner so freely!
That's the one. It's just an ordinary
South Bird. There's nothing to fear.
I-I'm sorry!
Stop daydreaming!
Something smells good.
It won't take long. Cut me some slack!
It's not as if you gained reputation
in Alabasta, or even money.
--South Bird?
--Yeah.
Doctor, what should we do?!
It's a funny bird valued highly by old-time
sailors because they always point south.
So is this the kitchen?
Right... right... Give him 50 mg of painkiller!
--Hey!
--Ah! You're the guy from...!
It looks interesting, but...
What would someone like that want from us?
What about preparing the operation room?
What did you come to this fortress base for?
Operation?! Operation...
Yeah, he needs an operation...
Don't tell me something
happened to the Going Merry!
Hey, I heard that some ships came in.
What for? Well, when we fell from
the sky, we happened to land here.
Don't worry. Your ship is okay... for now...
What?! Then those assholes
are finally coming?!
--Hm?
--The Grand Line really is an interesting place.
Hey, stop it!
Yeah, those brothers are coming here.
Are you all right?!
I've come to like this fortress
quite a bit as well, you know!
Good...
So they're surprisingly violent.
First impressions are important.
Show them no mercy!
Doctor!
You're the one who
repaired that ship, aren't you?
You have good food here.
I guess I'm just lucky.
Yeah!
--Doctor! There's no time to lose!
--Please get a grip!
Hm? Oh, sort of...
Please advise us on treating the patients!
Listen, Straw Hat. Even if you've
got the power of a Devil Fruit,
Meat! I smell meat!
The way you did it isn't acceptable.
--Doctor...
--I can't just stand back and watch!
Unless you use splices,
even if you nail the iron sheets,
Is the word "patience"
not in your vocabulary?!
it's impossible to escape Navarone
without some sort of miracle.
it'll break in no time when
strong winds blow, you know.
I'll advise you all!
My vocabulary consists of the terms
"all the meat you can eat" and "free refills"!
I'll leave when I want to.
Splices?
They're well maintained.
What? You don't even know what splices are?
Is that all?! Hey, hey, Luffy!
First, give this patient phenicol,
cardiotonic and tialcillin.
Food!!
Even after you hear that
Roronoa Zoro was captured?
Well, actually, I'm not a maintenance
man or anything like that.
"Full of Power!"
"Carbohydrates!"
"Navy Dining Hall"
Medical books and history books... huh?
--Zoro?
--That idiot...!
I guess these ghosts study a lot.
The one that did those repairs was...
Respond if you got that!
Yes, doctor!
Fortress guy, where's Zoro?
Ghosts again? How ridiculous...
Someone did them in just one night?
And if I tell you?
So you guys are the Murray Brothers?!
What else? I'm gonna
go rescue him right away!
Yeah. That was when we were
in a place called a sky island
Perform cross-matching
with each patient's blood type!
--Murray...?
--Aw, man...
that was 10,000 meters up in the sky, though.
You don't have to be so hasty.
We'll take you to the same place soon.
Those who require an operation,
give them preoperative treatment!
Hm? 10,000, you say?
Thanks for your hard work. Continue
the investigation of this ghost ship.
Yeah, yeah... You probably
don't believe it anyway, do you?
Give that patient a tetanus
toxoid and 5 mg of morphine!
Ghost ship, he says?
Yes, doctor!
Come to think of it, that ship
fell from the sky, didn't it?
Is the operation room ready?!
There's no point staying
here any longer! Let's go!
It's ready!
Ahh!
What? You believe me?!
Then bring the patients in,
starting with seriously injured ones!
--Got that?
--Y-Yes, sir!
Since I saw it with my own eyes,
I have to believe it.
Yes, doctor!
--Jessica-san...
--Little did I know you were Straw Hats!
It appears that that ship
stopped by Jaya quite recently.
Hiya!
Your skills are too good for a pirate.
Considering the angle at which it fell,
So you're those despicable
cooks from Marie Jois...
it probably fell from a
considerable height, so...
Give it up! Cooks in Navarone are
tougher than your average marine!
--The coffee was tasty, wasn't it?
--Yes...
You're right! We had a really
hard time on the sky island!
I heard that you said you were doing
us a favor by coming to this fortress
The color and smell of the
coffee left on the deck...
Hmph! I come from a place
with many such cooks!
in the boonies even
though you didn't want to!
There was God and there were
angels... It was really tough!
That was definitely Jaya Coffee.
Get a grip, doctor!
And that we're excreting insignificant meals!
But you've got the courage to drink
it without investigating it well.
Chopper!
God and angels?
That said, I can't attack Jessica-san...
Nami! What are you doing in a place like this?!
You've sure got nerves to say that!
You talk as if you died once.
What?! Are they confusing
us with someone else?
What're you doing here?!
Now what should we do?
Um... Well...
And that South Bird... That's a bird
that inhabits the jungles of Jaya.
Far from just once, there were
tons of times that I thought I'd die.
I don't know what you're
all complaining about!
Excuse me... I don't know
what's going on, since I fainted...
I'm hungry! Give me food!
There were, huh?
Did you know? A legend of gold
remains deeply entrenched there.
So you're the idiots...
You're... a doctor, right?
By the way, about what you told me earlier...
I don't know who you are, but you
saved us with your apt instructions.
...who used million-Berry foods to prepare
dinners for the big shots in Marie Jois?
Was it foggy the night that this someone
who repaired the ship appeared?
Commander, then that ship is...
I don't know about its crew's whereabouts,
but it's certain that it came from Jaya.
I'm starving!
--You're not saved yet!
--What?!
Yeah! Exactly! How did you know that?!
Give us food!
It's not some ghost ship.
Even if your appointment was
decided by the government,
There're a number of soldiers whose lives
are in danger without an operation!
Give us the new cook's famous
ridiculously tasty food!
Right! I've seen that ship twice.
It's the Straw Hats' ship!
Oh, do you, by any chance,
know who that was?!
this is the kitchen, the most
sacred place in Navarone.
--Bring it already!
--Wait! We're in the middle of something!
Yes...
--Now! Let's go!
--Straw Hat!
Start the operations on seriously
injured patients as soon as possible!
But you, yourself, called it a
ghost ship earlier, Commander.
See ya, fortress guy!
That could be, you know...
I won't let any cooks that I don't
accept set even one foot in here!
Uh-huh...
We have fresh recruits
and prisoners at this fortress.
Yes... Operations...
Our enemy is the Straw Hat Pirates!
If we tell everyone about
the Straw Hats' invasion
Exactly!
--Wh-What're you doing?!
--That's it, old man.
What's with you?!
Be ready to engage in battle at any time!
That's our Jessica-san!
I-I can't...
without knowing their true purpose,
We're quite busy with various things.
1,000 stalwarts are always
stationed in this fortress.
To uphold the honor of Navarone,
we must capture them without fail!
it'll only cause confusion
within the fortress, right?
Can't do what?
--Escort him out.
--Yes, sir!
I can't bear things like seeing
people in pain and bleeding at all.
Hey, hey!
Yeah!
Cooks here show their respect by
preparing dishes with all their might
Yipes! Those marines're too fired up!
So let's just keep calling
it a ghost ship for now.
W-Wait! Hey! Tell me who that was!!
When I'm really terrible even at giving shots,
With all due respect, Commander,
and providing energy to everyone's stomach.
It's really dangerous to keep playing
hide and seek in our enemy's midst!
we should organize a special
investigation unit right away
That's right. I forgot to tell
you something important!
to think of cutting a human body
or putting stitches on it...
In order to support soldiers on the front lines,
and search for them as soon as possible!
I'd better do something about
my appearance, at least.
Listen, long-nose! When you repair the ship,
every morning and every night,
we never lose our focus for even an instant.
I can't believe this! This is a naval base, right?!
Please assign it to my unit!
pay attention to the areas
that you usually don't.
Hm? Yeah... Hm... All right!
--Now, don't be so hasty.
--But...
Those areas are often the
ones most in need of repair!
How have you been giving treatments
until now if you're like this?!
Building up our defense is the priority now.
We're different from the cooks who
sit back and depend on expensive food!
Transformation complete!
Now I should be able to openly...
You go reinforce security at the coast
as well as around the sea gate.
My field is pediatrics. Since the other
doctors are all out on business trips,
--Hold it!
--Ahh!
If you treasure your ship, don't forget that!
Yes, sir!
You got that?!
You go reinforce security at the
ammunition bunker, detention facilities
Are you gonna let me eat those?!
I was asked to serve as a
deputy Medical Room Chief.
If you're a Navarone marine,
you should dress neatly.
Yeah! I got it, old man! Thanks!
and the major passageways. I'll also
grant you authority to manage personnel.
Deputy...?
Are you forgetting...
Deputy or not, you're the
Medical Room Chief right now, right?!
Understood!
Huh?
...that good cooking comes from the heart?
This is why I say new recruits are trouble.
--You look dissatisfied, Lt. Commander.
--No, sir...
Y-Yes, more or less...
Yes, sir! I'll be careful, sir!
The night is still long.
They probably can't move around much.
Um, by the way, I'd like
to ask you something, sir.
More or less?!
Chopper! Let's get out of here already!
Well, that goes for us, too.
Do you know how to get to the dock
where the Straw Hats' ship is?
But...
Wait until morning, then take your unit
We can get out! This place isn't
a lake! It's connected to the sea!
It'll be six blocks down from over there.
In other words, you're saying that you
wanna teach me what cooking is about.
and thoroughly investigate
places where people gather.
Thank you very much... sir!
Places where people gather, you say?
We can get out with the Going Merry!
I'm not trying to say something
as dramatic as that.
Hey! But the dock is...
That was all I needed to know, sir!
That's right!
--I can't go yet.
--What?!
M-Merry! You're okay! Thank God!
It's hard to find green insects since
they live in green grassy places.
I just want you to show us the pride
that you talk so much about.
You're a doctor, a person that
saves people's lives, aren't you?!
Someone just came out!
Yeah. But that place really is fishy.
If the Straw Hats were to wear our uniforms...
It doesn't matter who you are in here at all.
A carvel-built caravel that uses a lateen
sail with a stern rudder in the center...
Yes... but even for a doctor,
there're things they can and can't do...
All right! Then shall we go?!
It's not that I don't trust my men's abilities,
But if you don't have credible skills,
you'll cause the others trouble.
Hold on! This is a little strange.
The model's a bit old,
but it's really a good ship.
The person who taught me
medicine told me this story.
but it's very possible that they'll
take some of our uniforms.
We arrived here after we
took the deserted route.
Huh?! Who are you?!
Let me make this clear. Unless you satisfy me,
If you don't know me,
then you must be a newbie.
It's as if they're telling us where
Zoro and Usopp are... Which means...
Y-Yeah, sort of...
Pirates are like stray dogs...
They're always hungry.
This ship must've had
quite a few wild journeys.
I won't let you call yourselves
cooks in Navarone!
There was a man who was told by
his doctor that he was going to die.
Though it's covered with patches,
the repairs were done appropriately.
I get it! The fortress guy is a nice guy!
I see... That sounds interesting, Mademoiselle.
He wandered in despair,
searching for a place to die.
Why don't you start by checking
the dining hall once morning comes?
It's a happy ship filled with lots of love.
It's a trap. A trap!
But as he was passing over a mountain,
Yes, sir!
You can tell that much?!
What is it?! What's that commotion?!
It doesn't matter if it's a
Navy ship or a pirate ship.
he saw vivid cherry blossoms
blooming all over the mountain.
They're probably trying to save
time and send us straight into jail.
Where did everyone go?
Apparently the cooks are
starting a fight over cooking.
Hey, let me see!
I can tell for the most part at the first glance.
Is he the cook who came from headquarters?
Who cares?
That's quite a compliment! Thanks!
Either way, we can't rescue Zoro
and Usopp unless we go inside, right?
What is this place?!
He went to see a doctor again.
And the doctor said to him...
You can go ahead and use whatever
foods you like. The rule is simple.
Idiot! I'm not praising you!
Idiot! Why would we want to get
trapped by our enemy so easil--?! Hm?
Well, don't get so upset! I like you!
Each will cook for 100 people.
The soldiers who eat it will decide the result.
You sure are perky for a newbie.
"You're completely healthy."
You haven't changed, putting pirate ships
in the same league as navy ships...
You're the only doctor to the patients here!
It's true that it'd be better than wasting
time wandering around aimlessly.
Crap!
I don't really know what's going on,
but it sure seems exciting!
Hm?
You're the only one who can save them!
I'm also worried about
Nami-san and Robin-chan.
Lt. Commander Drake, you need to wait
at least a week to have the ship repaired.
Good thing we've got a waver.
Start any time.
You mustn't give up! There's no illness
in this world that can't be healed!
Sanji, are you thinking it over?
It seems that marines these days
You mustn't say that
there're things you can't do!
No, I'm not!
are under the mistaken impression
that damaging ships is their job.
I can't lose this fight even if it kills me!
--You did, didn't you?!
--I said I didn't!
There're no patients that
we doctors can't heal!
--Thanks to that, docks are kept very busy.
--Quietly...
I'm gonna fill their plates
with nothing but juicy parts.
--Don't worry. I didn't come here to
bother our veteran maintenance soldier.
--Quietly...
Doctors can make miracles happen!
At least, we have to believe that!
Security is tight.
--I came for the other guy. Hey, you!
--Quietly...
We'd better get out of here right away!
There's nothing in here!
--Y-Yes, sir!
--Which unit are you with?!
Never mind that, get moving already!
Say...
Ugh! Wh-Wh-Which unit...?
You can't even tell me which unit you're with?!
Alrighty!
Is he gonna admit defeat
without even cooking?
Um, let me see... I think it's Unit 18, sir.
...will I be able to see
the cherry blossoms, too?
Hey, Zoro! Usopp! Where're you guys?!
Unit 18 is a sniper unit, isn't it?
--Finished!
--100 servings!
How's that?!
Don't you know that this dock is off-limits
except for the maintenance soldiers?
Or rather... can I show the cherry
blossoms to people who're suffering?
Oh? Did you hear Luffy's voice just now?
Don't tell me! This is...?!
Wow! You guys already finished?!
--Those look delicious!
--Don't touch!
Um... I'd forgotten that, sir! I'm going
back to the sniper unit right away, sir!
Hey!!
Of course! We cook 1,000
servings for each meal!
Yeah, of course! I'll help you!
It's really Luffy! Hey, Luffy! We're right here!
H-Hey! We don't have time for that!
There's no need for that!
We're fast like sharks dashing in the sea!
Well, well... We've fallen
to a troublesome place.
--No need?!
--Take him!
Sure you wanna do that?
Those guys can hear too, you know.
This is the essence of Navarone!
We don't, but people's lives have
priority over anything! I'm a doctor!
Yes, sir!
What did I do?!
Luffy, don't come!
No, I changed my mind! Come get us!
I wonder if Nami-san and Robin-chan
were able to escape okay.
It was reported to me that a
suspicious new recruit was seen.
How wasteful they are...
Hey, what should I say?
By the way, Unit 18 isn't a
sniper unit, it's a supply unit.
What's he going to do?
Beats me. Tell them to come
if they want to or something.
Are you serious?! You'll get left behind,
you know! Is that what you want?!
--What's the matter?!
--Well, I saw some sort of light in the tree.
Come if you want to!
H-He's...!
Ah, my bad! That's right! It's a supply unit!
I heard a voice!
Can't be...!
Doctor, preparations for
the operations are ready!
It's this way!
He's using the parts we didn't use!
Stop it, you idiots!
Where do you think you are?!
Umph!
Okay! I'll be right over!
Oh, no... They came...
You were probably seeing things.
Crush the tuna's bones and head
Chop... Dr. Chopper!
To us, the maintenance soldiers,
this is a sanctuary!
Be careful, Luffy!
They're here!
and mash its guts!
If you shed even one drop of blood,
you won't get away with it!
Hold on! I'll get you... out...
What the...?!
I can't even smoke in peace!
Knead it with vegetable wastes...
Oh, I see! This is the Sea Prism Stone's doing!
All right.
...and deep-fry them.
We've been waiting for you!
Pull back your swords.
Take him to headquarters.
Surrender obediently, Straw Hat!
Stew the fat from the meat until it melts...
Yes, sir!
Ha! You are making light of us, aren't you?!
Chopper!
It's okay to leave me behind.
Hmm, so this is the man...
You think that's enough to stop us?!
Cover them with a special sauce
made with stock from the shells.
If I leave here now,
I'll be scolded by Doctorine!
Commander, he insists that he's a marine,
Is this still not enough?
Beef, pork, chicken, beef, fish, pork...
The bitterness of the tuna's guts
stimulates people's appetites,
but the circumstantial evidence clearly
indicates that he's one of the Straw Hats.
and the strong tastes blow spirits
into their exhausted bodies.
Geez, you know we can't
just leave without you!
It's all the same to me, idiots.
Meat! Meat! Meat!!
Now, what should I do?
Which means that we need
marinated food that isn't too heavy.
"Operating Room"
--You!
--Yes, sir!
For starters...!
What's your name?
The skins of burdock roots and potatoes
have more nutrients than the insides.
No matter how I look at it, I haven't
eaten since we left the sky island!
What's your name?
What's he doing?!
--It's a secret.
--Which unit are you with?
They're the ideal nutrient source.
Ha! It's painful to watch!
It's a secret.
Why did you take the trouble to go
to the dock where the pirate ship is?
Use broccoli cores to make
soft, sweet-scented dressing.
Those bars can't be broken unless
you use a cannon or something.
It's a secret.
Well, that didn't help.
Dammit! These bars sure are tough!
--Secret, huh?
--Yes...
La...
If Chopper were here, he would've
caught the smell of food for me!
Let's imprison him right away
and put the screws to him!
Cannon...? Oh, yeah!
...cuisine a la carte!
Now, hold on, Lt. Commander.
Sanji! Hey, hey, hey...
Come to think of it, I hear that a special
inspector from Navy Headquarters
We had a doctor like that here?
Found them!
Take what's inside my pocket!
was on board the Stan Marey
that arrived this morning.
Your pocket?!
I have an Impact Dial in there.
Use it to break these bars!
Damn... We can't even get
close to the Merry like that.
We'll start the emergency operations.
--Yes?
--A special inspector?
This is a battlefield, right?
It's always best if the food tastes good,
There's a piece of iron in his chest.
We need to remove it.
C-Commander...!
Impact Dial... Hey, it causes
pain to the user, you know!
Oreja Fleurs!
It's natural that an inspector would hide
his name and division to investigate.
The patient is already sleeping
soundly from the anesthesia.
but wouldn't it be the worst
if you ran out of food?
This is no time to worry about that!
Now, take it already!
After all that, we couldn't find
even a single crewmember.
--Scalpel!
--Yes, doctor!
Th-That's ridiculous!
An idiot like him wouldn't be...
It doesn't matter if it's
10,000 Berries or a million Berries.
Even worse, the maintenance guys
said they saw monsters, right?
What're they talking about now?
You shouldn't waste even one piece of food.
I'm surprised that you figured it out.
Dr. Kobato! You'll be fine!
Yeah, and the Commander clearly
admitted that this is a ghost ship.
That's what you'd expect from
the Commander. You're right.
Give up gracefully!
No matter what food it is, giving love
to the whole thing is a cook's etiquette...
You're the one who can show
cherry blossoms to this patient!
I'm a special inspector from
Navy Headquarters, Captain Usopp!
Well, wait a sec, gorilla man.
How mean... asking us to
watch a creepy ship like this.
...just like loving everything about a lady.
I'll show you something remarkable,
so keep your mouth shut.
Yes!
A seashell?
That was borrowed straight
from a certain old geezer.
Is there any illegal activity in Branch 8?!
It won't be my fault if you
get hurt standing there.
I see. Apparently, the Navy thinks
that the Merry is a ghost ship.
Are military laws and regulations
being properly followed?!
It's near an artery, so be careful.
Oh, yeah, that's right...
Are the marines full of enthusiasm?!
Here we go!
--I've never tasted anything like this!
--It gives me energy!
So, I disguised myself as a mere
private to get the inside scoop.
Yes.
A ghost ship?! How rude! I'm gonna sue!!
"This well-tempered snake"?
--Y-Yummy!
--Dammit!
That's the story!
Nami, suction!
Just because we didn't wanna
lose to the famous cook,
We apologize, Captain!
Yes, doctor!
But it's better for us, as well as for
the Merry, if they think that way.
Don't be ridiculous!
we did what we shouldn't do!
We used only the juicy parts!
A special inspector has higher
authority than a branch commander!
Food in Navarone is different from the
luxurious food prepared for big shots!
We can buy time.
There's no way an idiot like you could be one!!
That total moron!
It's the food for soldiers
who live life day-by-day!
Idiot? Idiot?!
Now that I know that...
What's that? Are you trying to
tell us that's your secret weapon?!
The iron piece has been removed.
That was Jessica-san's belief, and yet...
--I did it!
--This is no time to celebrate!
I get it! They must've stolen
cursed gold from some ruins!
What're you saying, Drake whoever,
when you're a mere Lt. Commander?!
--To think that we, the cooks at Navarone,
were picky about the food...
--Eighty-six! Eighty-seven! Eighty-eight!
There're many other patients!
--What?!
--I can have you court-martialed for
insulting a senior officer, you know...
Shut up! Or I'll gut you!
--Yes!
--Let's give it our best!
Cut it out! I touched that gold...
Yipes, he's scary! A backlash!
Yes!
Ah! Um, Sanji-kun, sorry!
It's actually in the other pocket.
Eighty-nine! Ninety! Ninety-one! Ninety-two!
What?! A doctor you've never
seen is performing an operation?
But...!
Gh-Ghost!!
Do you wanna experience
the Navy prison? Huh?
Here. It's this side. This side... This...
Yes, sir!
Straw Hat Luffy and Pirate Hunter Zoro...
Ninety-three! Ninety-four! Ninety-five!
It might be one of the Straw Hats.
I'm sorry, Captain. I was thinking
about sending someone to greet you,
We can probably assume that
the woman with countless hands
--Ninety-six! Ninety-seven!
--Incredible...!
Chopper...
--Has there ever been anyone
who ate our food this brilliantly?!
--Ninety-eight!
and the hairy monster
are also part of the group.
but I got delayed. Please forgive me.
Pardon me!
Well, so long as you understand...!
Ninety-nine!
In any case, there're seven of them.
We're in the middle of
an operation. Please leave!
One hundred!
Among them are...
Commander! Special inspector Major Shepherd
It's an emergency! Dr. Kobato,
I wanna ask you something.
Flavor... It stinks!
A skilled cook...
from Navy Headquarters has arrived!
Th-This is...!
--Got it.
--The real one showed up?!
Dr. Kobato! His blood pressure is dropping!
A knowledgeable ship's doctor...
There may be a historian as well...
I-It stinks!
See, I was right!!
What's wrong?!
--You son of a bitch! Acting so impertinent!
--Ahh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Who the hell stored a fart in my Flavor Dial?
--Are you okay?!
--Hang in there!
Give him 6 units of red blood cell
suspension and 1 unit of platelets!
--What's the matter?! What happened
to the spunk you had earlier?! Huh?!
--I'm sorry.
I heard a suspicious noise!
Y... Y... ummy!!
This way! Hurry!
--What was that about the Navy prison?! Huh?!
--I'm sorry.
Yes, doctor!
I... I'm... sorry...
--What?! Are you apologizing?! I can't hear it!
--I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's all right. Continue the blood
transfusion! Also have dopamine ready!
I don't know what's going on! How do
these convoluted hallways work?!
--Do you think such a ridiculous
special inspector exists?!
--I'm really sorry. I'm sorr...
I'm stuffed! I'm so satisfied!
I guess I didn't have to ask.
Hm?
Nice to meet you, Commander Jonathan.
Let's go.
--Dr. Kobato!
--We're in the middle of an
emergency operation! Please be quiet!
--You'd better be prepared! Huh?
You stopped apologizing?! Huh?!
--R-Robin!
Yeah! I have no regrets.
Watch out! It's gonna explode! Get down!
--What is it?! Huh?! Where's
the spunk you had earlier?!
--Oh, I get it! She's disguising herself, too!
You're operating?! You fainted when
you saw blood flowing out of my arm!
Thanks for the food!
--What was that about the Navy
prison?! Huh?! Say that again!
--All right, then...!
I didn't wanna fight a pretty woman like you.
I'm trapped! What am I gonna do?!
What am I gonna do?!
Hey, Major! I didn't know
you were in Navarone as well!
See you again, Mademoiselle.
A doctor we've never seen
before should be in there.
What am I gonna do?!
What the heck should I do?!
You're interrupting!
H-Hey! It's me! Captain Usopp,
also from the Inspection Division!
Hold it!
Hm? You still have something for me to eat?!
All you'll find in here are doctors and nurses
giving their all to save precious lives!
Did you forget me since you've
been traveling so much?!
Are you leaving me humiliated like this?!
Major Shepherd, do you know the Captain?
No, I don't know him.
--Ahhhhhh!!
--See?!
I like your way of eating and your spirit!
An explosion in the jail!
H-Hey! It's me! It's me! Hey!
--It's downstairs!
--Okay, got it!
It's an emergency! Hurry up!
Let's go.
Starting today, you two are a part of our team!
--Hey!!
--Imprison him!
Now I'll start investigating Navarone, okay?
--Monitor them.
--Yes, sir.
I'm saved!
Please be my guest!
We welcome you, Major Shepherd.
That's what I wanted to hear! Jessica-san!
Thank you very much.
Hey, are you okay?!
Now... where should I head?
Escape... successful?
That darn Robin! Does she have a
grudge against me or something?!
It's not that easy to find them.
Looks like it.
That's a betrayal!
Of course it isn't, Commander.
You agree, don't you, Zoro?!
--Ouch!!
--Help...
They may be pirates,
Dammit! If Robin had only
gone along with what I said,
but they wouldn't be in a place like this
where they can be found so easily.
I would've taken Merry back by now!
Suture completed!
This place is in plain sight from anywhere.
Geez! What a pain in the ass!
Doctor, that was the last patient.
You should thank Robin.
Yeah, there're probably some
who act smart and hide.
Why should I?! Why should I?!
But among that kind of pirates,
there's usually one or two who have guts.
You've got me with you.
Now, there's no point staying here any longer.
Good work, Dr. Kobato!
O-Oh... I see... She thought that
it'd be safer for me to be with you...
Just as I thought...
It's surrounded by land in all directions.
Let's get out of here already!
--Is that right?
--Hm?
Ch-Chopper!
Robin was concerned about me...
Thank you!
You're a great doctor, Dr. Kobato.
Let's go, Luffy!
Alrighty! Guys, get out of here!!
Not at all... but you are a
great doctor, Mr. Raccoon Dog.
But...
Looks like I'll be able to catch a fish today.
Does that mean we fell on a
huge lake with no way out?!
Ahh! Hey, hey! Wait a sec!
...is this place... safe...?
Huh?
You dummy! I'm not a
raccoon dog! I'm a reindeer!
That darn stupid navigator!
Don't let Zoro go first! It won't
be my fault if we get lost!
Why the heck did she put them
in such a hard-to-reach place?!
It might've been better if I
didn't check into it, because...
Usopp, you jerk!
Shouldn't she be rather surprised
to see Chopper like that?
Darn...! Okay!
...that way I would've still
had hope for the escape.
Is everyone okay?!
To think that there's only one escape route...
Y-Yes, somehow...
At any rate, obtaining the information
we need to escape is our top priority.
Okay, then! Those who
can move, come with me!
Zoro!!
Honestly, what am I doing in a place like this?!
We'll go after the Straw Hats!
Let's be resolved... Long-nose.
Where are you, Zoro?! Zoro!!
Those fools! Our men should
be in place outside by now!
We don't even know if Nami-san
and Robin-chan are okay.
I don't want to.
Shut up! Be quiet!
We'll attack them from both sides and
send them to the netherworld this time!
Oh?!
Ahh! But out of regard for Jessica-san,
I can't just abandon this task.
Hey, this way!
In addition to Zoro, we've also captured
a crew member with a long nose!
Yeah, exactly.
Straw Hat and the other members are
definitely close by as well! Find them!
Hey, what're you doing?!
Well, I was watching this thing
and admiring how incredible it is.
Oh?
Yes, sir!
See?! We're lost!
Either help me out or come up
with a way to get us out of here.
--Where are we?!
--How can you get lost?! That's impossible!
Hey, what should we do now, Captain?
Just do something!
But I wonder why we're not
getting out of this place?
Shut up!
Straw Hat and a very skilled cook...
Commander! I'm sorry!
I failed to catch Straw Hat!
It's come to this because you were dawdling!
A swordsman and a man with a long nose...
--Say, Sanji...
--What?!
What about the other members?
Are Roronoa and the others with him?!
A doctor and nurse we've never seen before...
Octopuses can be eaten raw, right?
So what?!
Yes. Uh, well...
How is it? Is your stuff ready?
It was just my imagination.
Witnesses told me that they didn't
see Condoriano with the others.
And one more...
If you take your time, the next
100 soldiers are gonna show up.
...who calls herself Major Shepherd...
Oh, Jessica-san! I've just finished it!
I see... Lt. Commander,
the bridge is guarded, right?
That idiot! He's got no sense of tension!
Oh, yeah?! It's finally break time? I'm tired!
That makes seven people...
Now it makes sense.
Damn! I thought I became
a jellyfish for a moment!
Y-Yes, sir!
Good! Well, don't be so discouraged.
What I don't know is their purpose.
What on earth did they come here for?
You didn't do anything!
Then I'd like you to chop up 300 more onions.
We'll still have many
opportunities to catch them.
What?! Is she a devil?
We've already captured
the ship and two of them.
Welcome to my Navarone.
Okay! I'm your servant, Jessica-san!
The rest of the Straw Hats are within my hands.
So, what will you do now, Monkey D. Luffy?
I get it! It's your fault it's come to this, Sanji!
We've caught the first one.
Well, at any rate, my fortress
is no laughing matter.
I'll just sit back and see what you can do...
Looks like those kids made their move.
--What's going on?
--Beats me.
Hurry up and get moving towards the future!
Let's move ahead, pursuing our dreams
All the answers are right here, pouring out
Rush forth, rush forth,
on the road opened before us
Let's keep moving forward! We can do it!
We won't give in, we won't give in,
even if the obstacle is big
It's nothing to be scared of,
we can overcome it
Of all places, this is a Navy fortress?!
--Ugh! You stupid grass-head!
--What'd you say?!
A trap?!
Dammit! That bastard! That hurt!
Luffy, we're right here!!
Which means something fun might happen!
Luffy, don't come!! No, I
changed my mind! Come get us!
You're not supposed to get
caught right after I warned you!
Anyway, are the others okay?
I'm starving!
Well, worrying about annoying crap is annoying.
We can't do anything until
we know the entire picture!
Hey, Zoro! What should I say?!
Forget it! You stay there
and cool off for a while!
Oh, hey, Usopp! Is our ship all right?!
How should I know?! Tell them to
come if they want or something.
I'm starving!
We'll see what kind of trap it is.
Where's everyone else?! You all
think about the situation you're in!
Let me see your cook's spirit!
Robin, why're you dressed like that?
--Well, that's...
--Hang in there! I'll rescue you right a... waay...
So you think you can escape
from Navarone? And from me?
Captain and the idiot cook...
Never mind about them.
Are you talking to me?!
I said I'm starving!
Looks like the situation is starting to change.
Chopper! This is no time for you to give
treatments in the medical room, right?!
What the..?! Oh, I see! This is
the Sea Prism Stone's doing!
Welcome to the fortress of Navarone!
We won't get caught! We're pirates!
--On the next episode of One Piece!
--Don't read my line!
Are you talking to me?
Dammit! This is a trap!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Captured Zoro and
Chopper's Emergency Operations!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Enter the Hot-Blooded Special Forces!
Battle on the Bridge!"
"The Navy's Dragnet Closes In!
The Second Member Captured!"
"Sanji the Cook! Proving His
Merit at the Navy Dining Hall!"
"Daring Luffy and Sanji!
Their Great Rescue Operation!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
I'm gonna be a great swordsman!!
Hey!