Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
What great weather!
If we keep going this way,
we should see the
navy base island soon!
Wow, Coby! You're amazing!
We're actually gonna
reach our destination?
But of course!
These are the bare
minimum skills all sailors need!
This is no time
to be laughing, Luffy-san.
He's being held prisoner there.
The famous pirate hunter...
Roronoa Zoro!
The man who's chopped up
bounties like a bloodthirsty beast...
People say he's a
demon in human form!
"Enter the Great Swordsman!
Pirate Hunter Roronoa Zoro"
We made it! The navy base city!
Seriously, Luffy-san!
You're crazy to want him to join you!
I still haven't decided yet.
I just wanna see if he's a good guy...
He's been caught
because he's a bad guy!
Mm! Yum!
Do you know if Zoro's at the base?
It would seem the name "Zoro" is taboo here...
Well, let's check out the base anyway.
You're gonna be a marine, right?
Y-Yes... But I'm not really ready yet...
Rumor has it...
...a guy named
Captain Morgan is at this base, and...
What a funny town!
It's strange...
I understand Zoro, but why are
they afraid of a navy captain's name?
I suddenly feel uneasy about this...
You sure they didn't jump just for fun?
Nobody would do that!
Alright! This's the place!
I'm finally here!
I guess this is where
we part ways, Luffy-san.
It was only for a short time, but...
Upsy-daisy!
Luffy-san! What in the world are you doing?!
Now where's this demon?!
He wouldn't be out here.
I'm sure he's in
a prison cell or something...
There he is!
Alright!
See! There he is!
Yeah, right!
He wouldn't be out--
A black hood and a haramaki...
That's Roronoa Zoro!
He can get away easy
if we untie those ropes!
D-Don't be stupid!
There's no telling what'll
happen if we let him loose!
I bet he'd try to kill you too, Luffy-san!
Don't worry! I'm strong!
I can't believe this guy!
Hey, you guys.
You're an eyesore.
Get lost!
Luffy-san! There's no way you
could survive with him on your crew!
Oh no! Stop her, Luffy-san!
She'll be killed!
What?
You must be hungry!
I made you some rice balls!
Do you wanna get killed, pipsqueak? Scram!
You haven't eaten anything this whole time.
Here! This is my first time,
but I worked really hard to make them!
I ain't hungry!
You're an eyesore!
Get the hell outta here!
But...
I don't want 'em!
Don't make me kick your ass!
It's not nice to be a bully!
You seem surprisingly well, Roronoa Zoro...
Now there's another weird guy!
Thank goodness!
He must be with the navy!
Now that girl will be safe!
Oh? Those are some
tasty-looking rice balls.
Stop!
Too damn sweet!
Those're full of sugar!
You're supposed to use salt for rice balls!
But I thought they
might taste better sweet...
--Take this! And this!
--Stop! Stop!
H-How horrible!
And I worked so hard to make those...
Did you not read this notice?
"Those who help
criminals will be executed!
Navy Captain Morgan"
Looks like even little brats
know how scary my dad is!
Dad?
Then that's Captain Morgan's son?!
You. Throw this kid out.
Sir?!
I said throw her over the wall!
Or can you not follow my orders?!
Don't make me tell my dad!
Y-Yes, sir! Right away!
No!
I-I'm sorry, little girl.
Curl yourself into a ball.
T-Thanks...
Are you all right, Luffy-san?!
Are you all right?!
I can't believe how
horrible that guy is!
Do you hurt anywhere?
Damn you...
You sure are stubborn about staying alive...
Yeah! I will live the full month!
Well, good luck with that.
Ten days left, you know!
Assuming you can live that long!
How can he be so cruel, Luffy-san?!
He's gone?!
I hear you're a bad guy.
Are you still here?
Being stuck out here for all to see...
Are you really strong at all?!
Mind your own business!
If it were me, I'd probably
starve to death in three days!
I got more spirit than you.
I will live through this...
I swear it!
What a strange person!
Wait!
Could you pick that up for me?
You're gonna eat this?
It's mostly a mud ball now.
Just shut up and give it here!
Told you so.
It was good.
Thanks for the food.
Really?!
Yeah! He ate every last bite!
I'm so happy!
Is Zoro really as evil
as the rumors say?
No!
After all, he let himself
get crucified in our place...
Huh? What do you mean?
It's all that Helmeppo's fault.
He's Captain Morgan's son...
Outta the way!
Make way for my adorable pet-sama!
Get in the way, and you get executed!
No! Stop that!
Hey, you!
You gonna complain about
what my pet-sama's doin'?!
Rika! Stop that!
We'll get in trouble
if we go against him!
--Oh, crap!
--He's in trouble now!
Who the hell are you?!
Don't tell me you're...
...pirate hunter Zoro?
And if I am?
Why is a pirate hunter defying the navy?!
Just shut up and let me eat in peace!
Why, you...
You're annoying me.
Both you and your pet-sama!
You do realize that if my
dad finds out about this,
they're gonna get
executed for sure!
Whadya say? Let's make a deal!
You get strung up in place
of this mother and daughter!
For, yeah, one month...
If you can survive for one month,
I'll let you live, too.
Whadya say?
One month.
It's been three weeks since then.
Helmeppo punches and
kicks him while he's tied up!
I... I...
I see...
I'm hungry!
Let us all eat for free!
Hey! Bring me some booze!
Quit dawdling! Hurry it up!
Oh, yes.
I've been bored lately,
so I've decided
to execute Zoro tomorrow.
Look forward to it!
W-What the hell're you doing?!
Luffy-san! Please stop!
This guy is scum!
Y-You hit me!
I'm Captain Morgan's son, you know!
So what?!
I'm gonna tell my dad
and he's gonna execute you!
Fight me yourself!
Luffy-san! Calm down!
Are you trying to get
on the navy's bad side?!
I've made up my mind, Coby!
I'm... going to have Zoro join my crew!
I am...
great!
Yes! You're exactly right,
Captain Morgan, sir!
But hasn't tribute to me
been a bit lacking lately?
W-Well, the citizens'
wallets do have their limits...
The issue is the level of respect for me.
Wouldn't you agree?
Dad!
There's someone I want you to slaughter!
You're still as weak as ever, Zoro!
I promised her...
I can't afford to die
in a place like this!
You again?
You sure have lots of free time.
I'll untie you, so join my crew!
Say what?!
I'm looking for people
to join my pirate crew.
Forget it!
Me, stooping to a criminal's level?!
Screw that!
What's wrong with being a pirate?!
Pirates are despicable!
As if I'd wanna be one!
Oh, come on!
You're already known
as an evil bounty hunter!
People can say whatever they want,
but I ain't done anything I regret.
I will live through this
and accomplish what I want!
Yeah?
But I've decided you're gonna join me!
Quit deciding on your own!
I hear you use swords.
Yeah. But that stupid son took my stuff...
--I'll go get it back for you!
--What?!
So if you want your sword, join my crew!
You're really getting on my nerves!
Is he planning to bust
into the base by himself?!
You idiot! The base is
in the other direction!
Gum-Gum Rocket!
W-Who the hell is that guy?!
Alright! Stop there!
Stand it up in one shot!
Dad! Why aren't you
going to get revenge?!
The guy hit me!
Not even you've ever hit me in the face!
Do you know why I've never hit you before?
Eh? Because you think I'm--
Yes. Because you're...
...a stupid son who
isn't even worth hitting!
Don't get the wrong idea!
Your dad is the one who's great! Me!
Which reminds me, I hear a rat
snuck into the crucifixion yard.
I-I-If you mean that pipsqueak,
I made sure she was dealt with--
You killed her, I hope?!
N-No! I mean, she was just a little kid...
You, there!
Go into town and exterminate her!
Y-You can't be serious!
She's just a little girl!
I can't in good conscience...
Anyone who disobeys my
orders is a traitor, even little brats.
B-But... I can't do it!
Lieutenant!
Y-You didn't have to go that far!
It was with my strength that
I rose to my rank of captain!
Listen! In this world,
titles mean everything!
That means that I, the captain and
highest ranking officer at this base,
am the most superior person here!
So everything I do is right!
Isn't that right, you guys?!
Yes, sir!
You're absolutely correct!
The kid's death can wait for now.
Observe! This is the symbol of my authority,
which took many years to finally complete!
Now, stand it up!
Display my greatness
at the top of this base!
That's weird.
There's no one here...
I gotta find that stupid son
and get Zoro's sword back.
Pull! Pull!
You, there!
You bumped it, didn't you?!
I heard something up there...
I-I'm sorry, sir! I was careless!
I told you to think
of this statue as me!
The slightest scratch or speck
of dirt is treachery against me!
I'll just check it out!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Now you pay!
I jumped too far!
--What is that?!
--It flew up from below!
I stopped!
Sorry...
Seize him!
I'm going to kill him!
Yes, sir! Right away!
Dad! That's him!
He's the guy who hit me!
Oh! It's you!
I've been looking for you!
Come with me!
There's something I want you to give back!
--Let me go!
--Helmeppo-sama!
After him! Don't let him escape!
Captain! There's someone
in the crucifixion yard!
What?!
It's one traitor after the other...
After him! After him!
Hurry!
Someone just had to interrupt...
Where is Zoro's sword?!
I'll tell you! I'll tell you!
Just stop dragging me!
Alright! Talk!
In my room...
We just passed it...
What? Why didn't you say so?
Now we gotta go back.
--Freeze!
--Let Helmeppo-sama go!
No.
Go ahead and shoot, if you dare!
No! Don't!
Please escape, Zoro-san!
You'll be killed for doing that, you know!
I can't stand to watch
the navy like this anymore.
I want to be
an honorable marine!
Stop! I can't escape!
I only got ten days until--
You're going to be
executed tomorrow!
What?!
Helmeppo never once
intended to honor your agreement!
So Luffy-san got angry and punched him!
He did?
The navy is after Luffy-san now.
I won't ask you to be a pirate.
But please, help Luffy-san!
Luffy-san is the only
one who can save you.
And I think you're also the only
one who can save Luffy-san now.
End of the line!
For the crime of treachery against me,
I'll now execute you two where you stand!
This the room?!
Bingo!
But there are three here!
Hey! Which sword is Zoro's?
Oh, he passed out.
Coby!
This is some interesting
stuff you guys've pulled!
Were you two and that straw hat
kid plannin' a coup or something?!
I've always fought alone.
Unlike arrogant bastards like
you who use soldiers as cronies!
Roronoa Zoro...
Don't you dare underestimate me!
You may be strong,
but before my authority,
you're as good as scum!
Aim!
I...
...can't afford to die here!
You're still as weak as ever, Zoro!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Fire!
--What are you--?!
--Luffy-san!
Straw Hat?!
That doesn't work!
I told you I was strong!
W-Who the hell are you?!
I'm Monkey D. Luffy!
The man who's gonna
be King of the Pirates!
"To be continued"
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
I'm gonna be the world's greatest swordsman!
Great! Why not be a great swordsman pirate?!
Don't talk like it's so easy!
The soldiers have started to go berserk!
Probably 'cause we're
enemies of the navy now!
Here! I'll untie your ropes!
I gotta hurry! There has to be a
map to the Grand Line in this base!
Huh? The ropes are tighter now.
Hey!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Morgan vs. Luffy!
Who's the Mysterious Pretty Girl?"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!