Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King
of the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
The horizons everyone
dreamed of were separate at first
but now they can be seen
through a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny
is leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve
your dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
Whadya think, old fortress guy?!
I rescued my crew!
I'm sure it was right around here...
"The Gold and Waver Recovery Operations!"
Run! Run! Run!!
Found it!
If things are going as planned,
Luffy and the others
# We are the Navarone Marines! #
should be headed back to
the dock with our gold in hand.
All right, then! Here we go, guys! Ready?!
W-Wait up!
I'm sorry, I really did forget about this!
# We'll show you our fiery spirit! #
Where's the Going Merry?!
Gum-Gum Balloon!
--Yeah!
--Wait, wait! Wait, you guys!
I didn't realize it before, but this
Waver works in the Blue Sea, too!
What's wrong, Usopp?
All right! Now we just gotta hurry back!
Geez, you guys! Are you just gonna
go without thinking this over?!
"Enter the Hot-Blooded Special Forces!
Battle on the Bridge!"
Sanji-kun! Hold on tight!
Onto you?!
I'm so glad I'm alive!
This doesn't bode well at all.
--Nami?
--We've been had...
S-Someone...
God! Buddha! I thank you so much!
Seven people running around
will stand out way too much!
The special capture operation
at Dock 88 is ready!
Hey! There's still one here!
Our treasure is gone!
Yeah, yeah, whatever. Just get on already!
Damn, I can't believe the Straw Hats
left one of their crew behind!
That's true, come to think of it.
We can now capture the Straw Hats!
Don't mind if I do, then!
And even though it is disguised,
I'm worried about Merry!
"The Pirate Ship Disappears!
Fortress Battle, Round #2"
N-No! I'm Major Shepherd,
an inspector from the Navy!
You moron! I can't move like this!
Don't let your guard down.
Yeah, given this level of quality.
What do we do, Nami? Do we go there?
Your expressions of love are dynamic!
--Give me a hand!
--Inspector?
They'll notice, even though it's so perfect?!
Yeah! Let's rely on Dr. Kobato to lead the way!
I have to contact HQ...
I collapse and literally fall in love...
There's such a thing as worrying too much.
...and let them know
Navarone let pirates escape...
No one's gonna take this junky--
All right! Here we go!
Don't call it junk! Besides,
that isn't the issue here!
Okay!
You're a pathetic liar, Condoriano!
Honestly! I'm the only one
who considers the unexpected!
You may think you can fool us,
but you're wrong!
"Breaking Through the Siege!
The Going Merry Is Recovered"
What?!
Take him away!
"The One Fell Swoop Plan!
Jonathan's Surefire Secret Tactic"
There's no doubt it's gonna get
sunk the next time it's spotted!
Condoriano?!
They're getting away! After them!
W-What is this?!
But Lt. Commander!
--Give it up, already!
--Let go! I am not Condoriano! I'm Shepherd!
Plus... Nami!
These are shallow waters, and we
have to go through the shore reef,
Huh? Me?!
Major Shepherd, an inspector from the Navy!!
Looks like we've been had...
What happened to the Waver?!
so all this smoke is dangerous!
Is this really the right way, Usopp?!
I'm aware of that! And I don't care!
Oh, no! I left it hidden in some grass!
I have to hand it to them...
Don't worry! This is definitely it! Keep moving!
But...!
I wanna catch a fish that big!
What if they make it onto the ocean outside?!
See what I mean!
W-What is it?!
Y-Yeah! Merry's dock was
just around the corner there!
How can you be so carefree after
we nearly died trying to open it?!
--My bad!
--Forgetful Nami-san is lovely, too!
We'll wind up the laughingstock
and shame of the entire navy!
Marines!
T-This way, too?!
Our commander said you would appear here,
Well, stupidity aside...
But this seems too easy. I don't like it...
This is bad! Very bad!
There's no way out of this!
since you had stolen the map.
All right, men. I'll now explain
the plan. So listen good!
We-- the Navarone Fortress-- will?!
All right! Let's steal our ship back!
Cunning man.
There is nowhere to run now!
Things are finally getting interesting!
That's right! Those damn navy
bigwigs'll start arguing again
Dammit! As strong as Luffy and Zoro are...
Tadah!
The old fortress guy said there's
absolutely no escape from this place!
about destroying some useless
hedgehog of a fortress
Okay, gentlemen!
Do we wait for Sanji and the others
to break through from outside?!
I'll now explain the plan!
First, the gold recovery team!
No.
Our actions should already be known by now.
that can't even capture a
single bug that snuck inside!
I can believe that. There are at least
1,000 marines stationed here...
This will consist of Luffy, Zoro,
Robin, and me, Captain Usopp-sama!
It's only a matter of time
until reinforcements arrive.
You! As a marine of the Navarone
Fortress, can you tolerate that?!
And just how is that interesting?
--Now this is somethin'...
--So we were being ambushed!
There's no use in staying here.
Yeah! If the gold's not here,
then let's just go look somewhere else!
And the Waver recovery team will
consist of Nami and one other!
There's absolutely no escape!
Sniper Team #7, to the front!
No, sir!
--Again, how is that interesting?!
--Just forget it, Usopp.
Take aim!
Don't talk like it's so easy!
Attention, all warships!
Full speed ahead! Pass through the Sea Gate!
The only way out is to beat these guys
Once he says something, he doesn't stop...
Sanji!
Just like that?!
Gum-Gum...
and bust down those sturdy doors!
Unit 37 has arrived!
Nice plan, Usopp!
Unit 44 has arrived!
Fire!
So?
Exactly! We gotta do what we gotta do!
...Balloon!
Capture the Straw Hat crew!
--Let's work hard, okay?!
--Yeah, yeah.
In the name of Navarone, we will defeat you!
It's the outside ocean! We can
get out if we go straight ahead!
Gum-Gum...
--Dumbass eyebrows.
--What was that?!
--No, we can't leave!
--Eh?
Usopp's in trouble!
He's helpless to do anything!
What are you doing?!
...Gatling!
Hey, Usopp! Are you leaving me
alone with the ship again?!
Cannon Team #12, to the front!
Take the ship back! Turn it around! Hurry!
Don't worry!
--Bazookas?!
--Fire!
Merry's completely disguised,
so you can almost rest easy!
Don't let them escape! After them!
We're going back into the fortress!
The navy stole all our gold!
Almost?!
Plus, who's gonna tend to our
injuries if something happens?!
End of the line, Straw Hats!
Say what?!
Duds?
--Huh?
--Condoriano?
A-Are you insane, Nami?!
We almost died trying to get this far!
Stop, Straw Hat!
You came to the storage vault,
exactly as I expected!
Super Doctor!
Those are the Straw Hats!
Who the hell are you?! Who gave
you permission to open the doors?!
Damn, what is this?! My eyes!
You dummy! Praising me
won't help you, you jerk!
I'm very sane!
I can't see! My eyes are all irritated!
Quiet, you!
--A dead-end?!
--No, we can run along the cliff...
I am a special inspector
from Navy HQ, Major Shepherd!
Even if we do make it out,
there's no point without the gold!
Listen. Here's where we are now.
Those were flash bombs!
So you've finally shown yourself, Straw Hat?
Sword Team, to the front!
The gold recovery team
will avoid all regular routes
When money is involved,
she can be strangely persuasive...
Charge!
With the commander's permission,
The commander of Navarone!
and take the shortest path along
the coast to the storage vault.
I am leading a special
mobile unit from headquarters.
Jonathan, was it?
I love that side of Nami-san, too!
You are not needed. Step back!
Nami. Do you remember
where you hid the Waver?
But we made that huge hole!
Why can't we just leave now?!
Old fortress guy! What're you doing there?
Bastards!
Yes. By the bay on the
eastern side of the island.
This is my room.
Huh? Haven't I seen you somewhere before?
--Aren't we pirates, Luffy?!
--Yeah.
At the base of the rim... Right around here.
F-Fire cannons!
Don't you think pirates leaving
gold behind is shameful?!
Huh? B-But firing at the central tower isn't--
Oh, yeah! You were the guy
in jail with Usopp and Zoro!
I'm fine!
Oh, that's some nice equipment there.
I don't care! Fire!
Almost the exact opposite side...
Who are you to talk all big?!
--You can borrow these!
--Thanks.
Oh, right!
L-Luffy! Luffy! Oh, yikes!
Hey! Condoriano! You managed to escape!
It'll take too long to go by land...
Good! Then it's decided!
Right rudder, full! Make a U-turn
and take us back into the fortress!
Tatsu-Maki!
Whadya think?! I rescued my crew!
You seem well!
I owe a great deal to you all.
Blinders don't work on me,
unlike a certain lovesick moron!
Yes! Right there!
--Right! Got it!
--Yes! As you wish, Nami-san!
I told you, I'll leave when I wanna leave!
Nami! You two rush across the bay in that boat!
All the insults you've put me through...
Gum-Gum...
--Right rudder, full!
--U-turn!
Indeed. So do you want to leave now?
And we'll all meet back here,
at the Going Merry!
It's payback time for that, with interest!
...Gatling!
Yeah! We're gonna leave now!
--Hold on, you guys!
--What're you doing?!
And...
Right!
Major Shepherd!
Think you can escape
from Navarone-- no, from me?
...Whip!
Don't be reckless!
What?! Things were just getting good!
Taking them down with that level
of military might is impossible.
We won't get caught! We're pirates!
Huh? You're still there? You can leave now...
You shouldn't underestimate them...
Shut up, shut up, shut up! Shut up!
What a cinch!
The head chef has ordered me to stand watch
Huh? Where's Sanji and Zoro?
Don't compare us HQ elites
with you pathetic Navarone men!
That's it, that's it! Keep it up!
You took care of 'em!
until you've eaten everything on your plate!
--Oh, sorry.
--You dumbass!
Run!
--Oww...
--All right, you dimwitted moron!
Even if you dine in your
private quarters, rules are rules!
We will eliminate the Straw Hats!
What was that you said earlier?!
You just sit there and watch! Is that clear?!
You must eat every last bite!
Sound the alarm bell! Louder!
What the heck are you guys fighting for?!
Yes, sir!
Can't see a thing in this smoke!
Be sure not to hit any fellow ships!
That lousy Jessica...
Fire!
Are you done?
Yes! I'm gonna crush you good,
so stay right there!
--You too, General!
--Eh?!
We've prepared plenty for you!
--Bring it here!
--Yes, sir!
They got away!
What the--? Crap! I can't get this off!
Please eat up!
"Justice"
Something happen?
Commander! Unit 21 is currently
in Block 7, ready to ambush them!
Quiet, Luffy!
What's that?
You don't like broccoli either, General?
This is Navy HQ's very latest
invention: a portable bazooka!
--Luffy!
--Stay right where you are!
No, for me, it's tomatoes and carrots...
Wind chimes?
Your wanted posters say "dead or alive,"
These are alarm bells for signaling
your location to other ships in fog!
This is our chance to drive them
there and take them all out at once!
The Sea Eagle Talon-- the Eagle Launcher!
but here at G8, we prefer alive.
Oh! Lieutenant Commander!
It packs as much punch
as a warship's main cannon!
But if you resist any further,
I can't guarantee that.
Oh, are you eating? I'll come back later, then.
Have the men withdraw from Block 7.
Oh, no! One's coming straight at us!
What?!
They've brought out another incredible thing!
No, no! This is an exception!
You came at just the right time!
How's that? Is that good enough, Nami-san?!
It's a dead-end there! It's the perfect chance...
You don't scare me! Bring it on!
H-Hey, Luffy! Can't you get that net off?!
I'll fulfill that request! Time to die!
--Sir?
--I was just about to call for you!
No! Left rudder, full!
The Straw Hats don't play by the book.
I can't! It won't come off at all!
--Eh?!
--We have to change course or we'll crash!
Never underestimate someone
with a 100 million-Berry bounty.
O-Oh...
Commander! I apologize for letting the
Straw Hats escape three separate times!
Plus I'm suddenly out of strength...
--Huh?
--Way to go, Condoriano!
A proper fight would result in
significant injuries to the soldiers.
Whatever you want, Nami-san!
Major! You have it backwards!
Oh, that doesn't matter right now!
Say, have you eaten yet?
--Sea Prism Stone?!
--What?!
That's right! That was a Prison Bomb,
There is no point in needless
casualties or destroying our own base.
--O-Oh.
--Hey, now!
--No...
--That's not good! Not good at all!
meant for use against those
with Devil Fruit powers!
Shut up! I'll get you this time!
Yes, sir!
You can't fight on an empty stomach!
They will, without fail, head for
the dock to retrieve their ship.
What do you think, Straw Hat?!
In fact, it's your duty as a
high-ranking officer to eat first!
We're gonna crash!
Let's have a counterattack waiting
for the seven pirates at Dock 88.
It's harder for lower-ranking
people to eat otherwise!
Right...
There's no need to act reserved! Eat right up!
I knew he'd come...
Stop, Straw Hats!
What're you doing?!
No! No! Don't do that!
It's dangerous here! Return to your station!
--Drake.
--Sir!
We almost wound up in pieces
without ever seeing the gold again...
Don't be such a stick in the mud!
Way to go, Condoriano!
Rush ahead to the dock and lead
the capture of the Straw Hats.
Tell her it was exceptionally delicious!
What the hell'd he come here to do?
Not good!
Understood.
How are things up ahead?
That's pretty disappointing
for a "special mobile unit."
Use of the weapon is granted.
Well, then. Shall we go?
Yes, sir!
Dammit! There's still this many left,
even after all the ones we beat?!
--Not again...
--There are lots more wind chimes than before!
All right! Gold! Gold!
But won't it take time for
Lt. Commander Drake to reach Dock 88?
Just give yourselves up.
Escape is absolutely impossible!
Wait! Wait, you guys! Hey!
I'll crush you fools and this
hedgehog in no time flat!
Yes, that's true.
There's one-- two-- no, even more
warships coming from the smoke!
D-Damn you, Straw Hats! I'll get you--
For them to proceed to Dock 88,
they will have to cross this bridge.
Look forward to it, you damn commander!
My bad, Condoriano!
All hands, take aim!
Don't let them escape! After them!
"Justice"
Got no choice!
What?!
We simply need to defend it.
--So, where's the gold now?
--Don't look at me!
I suppose I'll lure them to the
Straw Gate on the upper deck...
It's almost time...
Nami-san! What'll it be? Left or right rudder?
Attack!
Looks like we'll need to reorganize our units.
However strong they may be,
More left!
it will take some work to break
through if we fortify the Straw Gate.
So the plan is to hurry ahead
of them and block their path?
We gotta get out of this smoke!
Security's tighter than I thought...
That should buy us some time.
Yes. General, contact each unit immediately.
What the heck's going on?!
All alone with Nami-san
on a romantic night at sea...
I see.
Just do what she says!
She's the best navigator in the world!
Yes, sir!
Now, then. Which unit shall I have defend it?
--Isn't it the damn greatest, Nami-san?!
--Sanji-kun...
What is this?!
--Damn bravo, Nami-san!
--Sanji-kun!
Attention, all warships
on standby! Urgent orders!
I guess it would have to be them...
You're damn fantastic, Nami-san!
It's bon voyage, Nami--
Monitor the area around
the Sea Gate and the bay!
Huh? Was that--?
We're gonna crash for sure this time!
I'm on the verge of death...
Sanji-kun! Could you be damn quiet?!
--# We are the Navarone Marines! #
What about my unit?
Usopp!
This means the Navy is certain
we're still inside the base.
What terrible injuries! He's badly
wounded! The marines did this?!
Send your men to the Sea Gate
as soon as they've finished eating.
Please, God...!
Damn them!
But then why are they just
sitting there? I don't like this...
--# We'll show you our fiery spirit! #
No, no, no...
Understood!
Kobato?!
Let's rethink our plan somewhere safe.
U-Umm, Lt. Commander?
You!
Who are you?!
Is there any safe place here on Navarone?!
Of course!
Why, hello there, Condoriano-- Oh, pardon me.
Please leave Straw Bridge to us, Unit 55!
Yeah! The kitchen me and Sanji were at!
We made it...
That's where loads of marines gather to eat!
I mean, Special Inspector Major Shepherd!
We will crush the Straw Hats, without fail!
Keep going straight now!
We can't go someplace that dangerous!
Commander Jonathan. I hear you
let the Straw Hat pirates escape.
# We'll show you our fiery spirit! #
No, wait. The enemy might
think the same thing, too...
What's the big idea?!
We've been taken hostage! Please save us!
We have to get out of this dangerous
smoke as quickly as possible!
# We are the Navarone Marines! #
All right! It's decided! Let's go get some food!
Not at all. They are likely still
hiding inside this fortress.
They're gonna spot us, you know!
We were forced here against our will!
I leave it to you...
That's not what we're doing!
Yeah! We'll be sitting ducks
once we leave the smoke!
I'm a full-fledged pirate now! I've grown a lot!
Kobato-san?
Oh? And you can eat a leisurely
meal knowing that, huh?!
--This giant is one of the pirates!
--Eh?!
Umm... Excuse me...
I'll protect it, no matter
who comes! I'm a reliable man!
We'll get blasted and wind up
at the bottom of the ocean!
--W-Wait! When did I do that?!
--What is this?!
You must not have a care in the world!
--What is it?
--Did something happen?
--Who's that other girl?
--How should I know?!
We'll just have to play it by ear!
It's no wonder they secretly call
you a peace-addict hedgehog.
Chopper!
Pirates have escaped!
--Navigator...
--Eh?
Nami! Sanji!
Seriously! Huh?! What're you talking about?!
"Justice"
You're all right! I wasn't
lonely at all, you dummies!
Vile ones called the
"Straw Hats," with bounties!
I did some research in the reference room--
We can't act carelessly
with the hostages there!
--Oh, I'm sorry.
--No, think nothing of it.
this fortress actually used to house
many more people and warships.
Apparently, a few are still
holed up inside the base.
Damn that coward! This is why I hate pirates!
So, I assume you know what
they're sneaking around for?
Are Luffy and the rest not back yet?!
Now what?! Luffy and the others
have already sprung into action!
Nope! I've been keeping watch all alone!
That giant was the fake doctor, then?
That's strange.
For the most part.
Hey now, Robin! This is no time for old stories!
Something might've happened...
They're probably headed for the
dock where the Going Merry is...
I believe they'll come back to
retrieve some gold they forgot about.
He has to be! He's carrying his crewmate!
Eh? Then, the gold, too?
--Yeah.
--I'm gonna go look!
It was military downsizing.
They've really fallen into decline since.
Gold, huh?
That's right! I'm a rough and tough
member of the Straw Hats!
That means Luffy rescued Zoro!
My date with Nami-san, Part 2!
Still, we've certainly declined
from our former dauntless selves.
So it seems there are many
unused docks in this port.
All alone again?!
Even crying babies shut up around me!
What're you so happy about?!
--You stay here, too, Sanji-kun.
--Eh?
We don't know the fortress' layout yet,
or even have an escape plan!
Better do as I say, or these
hostages are dead meat!
I have a favor to ask you.
Major. If you have any
sage advice, might I ask for it?
Unused docks...
Why couldn't they have stayed still?!
I'm pretty sure the vault
was down here somewhere...
I see! That's some nice info, Robin!
All right! Have your men stand
down and let us through!
B-But now we have no choice
but to go to the dock too...
I could put you in charge of an
especially skilled unit if you'd like...
Guys! We're gonna hide the
Going Merry in an old dock!
In any case, we gotta get out of here
and meet up with the others...
Don't be absurd.
--Now I get it.
--Interesting.
That's...
Eh?! And where exactly is that?!
You know you're the most worthy
to command this "skilled unit."
Hurry up, or I'll snap these
girls' necks like twigs!
The Straw Hats fled into
the mountains! Comb the hills!
The problem is them...
Just follow my orders!
Hurry! No dawdling!
Kobato-san! We know that one of
the pirates is disguised as a doctor!
He'll do it, too! He's so crazy
not even we can stop him!
Incidentally, where are the men
who mistook me for a Straw Hat?
Are you all right, Major Shepherd?!
Damn it! I almost had them, too!
You're done operating! Let us look inside!
Are you upholders of justice
gonna let two helpless ladies die?
Why do you want to know that?
But finding an empty vault doesn't
mean they'll give up just yet.
Kobato-san!
"Justice"
So I can court martial them, naturally.
Chopper! That's cowardly! I misjudged you!
W-What?!
--Kobato-san! Open the door!
--T-This is bad! Very bad!
We still have a chance!
It was I who gave the orders to
capture all suspicious people on sight.
You shut up!
Empty?!
You two!
Well, I figured this might happen,
so the next step is already set.
Call the cannoneers at the waterway!
U-Uhh, Dr. Kobato...
Ask if the Straw Hat ship passed through!
All they did was follow those orders.
I always know what I'm doing!
Y-Yes, sir!
--Am I a suspicious person?
--Under those circumstances.
--He's gonna kill us!
--Please, do what he says!
I'm sorry I didn't say anything!
It's true! We're... pirates...
Attention, cannoneers! This is Drake's flagship!
The vault was a trap! Then where is the gold?!
We seem to have a conflict of views.
Have you seen the Straw Hats' ship?!
I've just remembered something I need to do.
I'll return here once I'm done.
What?!
Apparently, no other ships have
passed through the Sea Gate yet!
Please run! There are pirates
loose inside the base!
Commander. Will you be all right?!
What?!
How terrifying! What's more,
they're pretending to be doctors!
He's a proud HQ inspector who
insists that G8 is wholly unnecessary.
Where did you disappear to, pirates?!
Don't tell me you managed
to sneak past the cannoneers
You two could be in danger!
He would never take
command of this branch base.
and vanish beyond the horizon
in that short period of time?!
U-Uhh, well...
I think it was around here...
No! No, no!
That wasn't what I meant!
Hey, now. Come on already...
How many times do I have to say it?!
We have 1,000 mouths to feed!
Now, then.
The truth is, those pirates... They're us.
Prepare to dispatch the most
powerful squad in all of G8!
I guess it wasn't.
We have to be efficient to
make it in time! You're too slow!
Weren't you just there?
--Not more of your jokes...
--I am serious.
--Oww...
--You didn't need to hit us...
The dining hall is at the far end.
This is the medical ward.
We're pirates!
I'm very sorry!
What's that? You got a problem?
We lost sight of the pirate ship
once it entered the outer waters!
Sounds like there's someone here!
I'll tell you right now-- save your big talk
And I know this is shameless,
but you seem like a nice person,
It's almost as if they
magically turned invisible!
until after you've proven yourself to me.
Dad! Please do as I ask!
Just as I thought.
Now come here and help prepare!
so we have a favor to ask!
Could you tell us where the docks are?
We're in a really big hurry!
I don't care if you are my daughter;
I refuse to drink that nasty stuff!
--Sir?!
--No, good work. Come on back for now.
Those damn fools...
Doesn't Jessica-san seem a bit wound up?
But it's medicine!
Hey!
I guess the fact that that cook
was a pirate hit her hard...
Those voices...
We can talk leisurely about
our forthcoming plan.
The Stan Marey entered port
this morning-- where's its captain?!
It's the doctor who acted as a hostage...
Not to mention that the real new
guys are losers who're all talk...
Pirates!!
...and the old man!
Sir! He's been in the infirmary this entire time!
They won't try to escape.
The infirmary?! What's he doing there?!
The gold wasn't on your ship?!
That's enough talking there!
Not with their dreams still in this fortress...
Nor in the vault.
Yes! We're sorry!
Apparently, many of his crew were injured,
Here, Billy! Try out my special sauce!
Still, I can't believe
you're father and daughter!
--That scream!
--Kobato-san!
so he's probably there out of concern for them.
Anyway, old man, are you sick or something?
Pretty good, huh?!
Kobato-san! What happened?!
Call him here! Right now!
Nah, just one swig of this
and I'll sleep it off like a baby!
Yes, sir!
--Or not...
--No, it's good...
Kobato-san!
He said they're after gold...
--Something happened inside!
--Alright! Knock it down!
This is a much better medicine for me!
But it's our usual flavor, isn't it?
Yes! Exactly!
And there's only one place
in this fortress that could be!
No! There is no drinking or
smoking in the medical ward!
--Kobato-san!
--Are you all right?!
Ever since I tasted his cooking,
I've felt like we're lacking something.
Just you watch, you worthless commander!
--Kobato-san!
--W-What the--?
--Just one drink!
--No!
Unhand me!
You're so stubborn...
I'll catch that Straw Hat myself
and crush this entire fortress!
Do you wanna be court-martialed
for insulting a superior officer?!
Are you alright?! Hey, say something!
Old man! You need to listen to
your daughter-- no, your doctor!
It's not bad or anything. It's just...
Hear that? He's gonna court-martial us!
He had flair, I'm sad to say...
What's this? Are you trying to lecture me now?
Go ahead! Be our guest!
Damn it! What did he do differently?!
I save your hides, and you
come waltzing right back...
I hope everyone is all right...
What?! They escaped through the ducts?!
You two! Let that man go!
Jessica-sama.
I'm so lonely!
Do you want your gold that badly, Long-nose?!
--What?
--Could this be of use somehow?
I'm so sorry, Major!
So they escaped through there?
Of course we do, old repair guy! We're pirates!
I told you so!
The stars! The moon!
Seems he left some recipe
notes before he left...
Y-Yes! Hurry and catch them!
And I'm all alone with Nami-san
in a boat beneath them!
I am Major Shepherd, special
inspector for Navy Command!
Yeah! These pirates worked
really hard to get their stuff!
--That pirate did?!
--Recipes for his cooking?!
What a wonderful situation!
I feel like I'm dreaming!
Oh, come to think of it, he...
You keep out of this, Kobato!
I'll write down my recipes for you, then.
I'd say the Straw Hats are right around here...
You're awake, Dr. Kobato--
We're saving up money!
The warships in the bay are moving!
Sorry! I understand why you want to shout,
Saving?
We decided that after we
exchange the gold for money,
What about it?
What are they doing? I have
a bad feeling about this!
I'd like to use them a little more.
but could you stay quiet for a bit?
Eh? Oh, I was hoping--
since he did leave it and all--
we're gonna do major repairs on Merry!
Sanji-kun! Go faster!
I guess I'll wait for them
to come out on their own.
Nami! Let's get out of here, quick!
--Yes! As you wish!
--Oh, but row quietly!
Like we can really believe a bunch of pirates!
that we could maybe use it...
Don't be stupid!
I don't care if you don't believe me!
C-Come to think of it, who are you?
Can you really proudly call
yourselves cooks of Navarone
Those Straw Hat pirates
have us working like crazy...
You got it!
This was our decision!
It's got nothing to do with you!
if you accept help from a pirate?!
Eh? Me?
All clear on the left and right...
Time for some good, energizing grub,
then it's back to searching.
What?!
Oh, it's me.
Who do you think our marines
are fighting as we speak?!
I believe you!
There's no telling where
there could be soldiers,
After all... they said that ship was their home.
Don't you have any sense of pride?!
I, umm, ate a Devil Fruit, so I can transform.
so we gotta move around unnoticed!
It'll be a miracle if we don't get noticed!
What is this?! This isn't
like this morning's food!
--Umm...
--Sorry to interrupt, but...
Yeah! I'd never had anything like it before!
She is such a ditz.
Home, indeed...
What the hell is this?!
Oh, yeah. Dr. Kobato. I know
how hard it is to understand,
Hey! Don't be skimpin'! Give us
some grub like this morning's!
Long-nose! We'll be fine for a while.
Can't you even peel potatoes right?!
This is it! It's a bit of a long way around,
Why couldn't you say so sooner?!
but there's no time to
explain the details right now.
Give us good food! Give us good food!
--Our men always did it...
--And it was always like this...
but this path is unguarded, and it'll
take you safely to the mountains.
It's all right. Nothing else
can surprise me now.
Jessica-san! The soldiers are
complaining about their meals!
What are you sleeping for?!
Listen! This is a battlefield!
Even a single potato is a vital resource!
This "path" is almost all cliff!
Get your act together, will ya?!
Well, we gotta go. There's no
telling when the marines'll be back.
Give us good food! Give us good food!
All right, then! Let's go
gold-hunting! Thanks, old guy!
He has no sense of tension at all...
Even shreds of potato skins are--
Please, let us use those recipes!
Oh, wait! Mr. Deer!
--Sure thing!
--Get going.
Where has your pride as
cooks of Navarone gone?!
Commander.
Even if you are a pirate and a magical deer,
Placing units all along the bay will
leave the base itself undermanned.
Thanks for your help again, old man! See ya!
U-Uhh...
you taught me what it means to be a doctor!
You two need to start all over
with dishwashing for a while!
Jessica-san!
--Wait!
--What is it?
It's true that he was a pirate,
but he was still an excellent cook
It can't be helped.
Our commander's hobby is fishing, you see...
Y-Yes, ma'am!
I'd, uhh, like to thank you somehow...
Against this adversary,
cautiousness amounts to nothing.
So that explains why he showed
off that huge fish painting!
I don't need thanks...
who made food for the famished
soldiers who came here to eat!
But having them prance around as if
they own the place is a bit much.
And I'm not a deer. I'm a reindeer!
Your gold is probably the
perfect bait to reel you in with.
Yeah! All these men want to be
revitalized by eating his food!
Oh, I'm sorry.
What do you say we mobilize the new recruits?
In which case, it should be
dangling somewhere you can see it.
Oh, right! You're looking for the docks!
No. It's too dangerous for them.
Please make a decision! Please!
Someplace we can see it? Bait?
L-Lt. Commander...
I could lead the way, if you'd like!
I thought you might say that,
so I kept it quiet until now,
Please, Jessica-san!
I'll pull my men back.
You'll take us there?!
--Hurry up!
--Yeah!
Please!
but many have actually
already volunteered to do it.
All hands, lower your weapons and withdraw!
B-But won't you get in
trouble for helping pirates?
--Now get going!
--Right! See ya!
Stand down! All sniper
squads, lower your guns!
They are already members of our forces,
Hey! Wait for me!
If they do steal back the gold
and manage to escape,
and have the same feelings of
fondness for this fortress as we do!
Yes. But if things turn bad, I can just
pretend I've been taken hostage!
--Lt. Commander...
--We have no choice.
Is that so?
all of Navarone will be in big trouble.
We will make our own cooking
In that case, order them
to observe and report only--
Wow, that worked well.
that's every bit as delicious
and replenishing as his!
I must be crazy...
--Good thinking!
--So if I can be of help...
I hope so...
But for today, we'll abandon our
cheap pride and borrow his recipes!
Huh?
no getting involved.
There was no time to think up
a plan after all, was there?
Yes, sir! I'm sure they'll be delighted!
Dammit! Are we left to
look around aimlessly for it?!
It's true that he wasn't a pirate
in the kitchen-- he was a cook.
By the by. I have one other
request for you, General...
I owe you one, Zoro...
Looks like they can't see us here.
Yes?
H-Hey! Was that Kobato-san's voice just now?!
What is it, Zoro?!
What's most important of all
is satisfying the people eating!
No, don't let your guard down.
The old fortress guy is tough.
Thought I heard something...
Y-You think so too?!
Jessica-san!
Mechao-san! What's going on?!
You're the one who
shouldn't let his guard down!
A bug? Must be my imagination.
What're you standing around for?!
Those men are waiting!
--Kobato's being held hostage.
--Eh?! Isn't that bad?!
Dock 88 is on the other side of that!
No, it isn't your imagination.
Right!
That's where the Going Merry's being kept!
Nah, don't worry about it.
Something's coming!
I can see whether my
daughter's crying for real or not!
But it looks like we'll run into lots of trouble...
What do we do now, Nami?!
A Waver?!
But my main worry...
What?! That's insane!
It's Nami!
It's not too late yet.
How about up there?
...is them!
We should go back to the
gate and get onto the ocean.
The Stan Marey is crippled and
still being repaired as we speak!
I see. So you ran into Dr. Kobato...
Yeah! These guys mean business!
As you can see, we've opened
the way! Now release them!
It seems crossable!
That doesn't mean every ship in
your fleet is out of commission.
We pretty much have no clues
about where the gold is!
It's a shame about the gold,
but our lives are more important!
But it's strange. There's no one there.
Yes! It worked!
That's true, but there are soldiers
who still can't even walk
It's almost like they're inviting us up...
What do you think, Luffy?
I'm sleepy...
Hey! Chopper!
If we sit around and dawdle,
dawn's gonna come,
No! I'm not letting them
go until we can escape!
A trap, huh?
We need the gold! But I'm hungry! Sanji! Food!
after the storm we ran into on our way here!
A trap?!
which'll make it even harder to move around.
It's the same either way! Plus,
I've decided that we're leaving!
Damn you!
I'll look for some food
and make you somethin'.
Say, are there any other storage vaults?
Captain. Are you arguing with me,
I've contacted Squadron #17,
as you ordered, sir.
If there are, they could be
traps to lure us in again...
And worrying about
annoying crap is annoying.
The storeroom is empty.
Good. Have them standby for my signal.
a special inspector dispatched from HQ?
There's gotta be something left somewhere.
Doesn't matter what traps come our way.
Come to think of it, the old man
said something earlier about "bait"...
I give in to your demands! Get onto your ship!
N-No, it's not like that... But...
He's a good sport. But is he telling the truth?
Hey, Luffy! Ahh, Sanji! Not you too, Zoro!
Do you really think it's okay to
escape without getting the gold?!
Then gather all your men!
Eh? What do you mean by "something"?
I'm not really sure, but he said...
Hey, hold on, you!
No, I don't wanna go!
Half will stay with me;
Yes! Yes!
the rest will board the Pinepeak
and wait for my orders!
If you get caught in a trap,
I'm not gonna come save you!
That's it! Usopp!
Well, that's a pity.
Pirate treasure is always divided up!
Without my help, you're gonna die!
Is that what you want?!
What's it?
I'm gonna show this useless fortress'
fools the power of Navy HQ!
Bait to reel us in... In other words,
the gold is somewhere in sight!
And given all that gold, we'd each
have gotten so much money!
But save me if I get in trouble, okay?!
In sight?!
Where's my reply?!
Could "sight" be referring to a
place we could imagine it being?
Hey! Zoro! You keepin' up?!
--Divided up?!
--Naturally.
I've been waiting for this!
I'm gonna buy me a bronze statue!
Just shut up, will ya?!
Oh, good thinking!
What do you mean?
In short, who's the one dangling
the bait to catch us in the first place?
Yeah! Can we buy books?!
I want the latest medical books!
Robin! Are we almost there yet?
Just a little more.
Nami. Chopper. Love cook.
I want to study all sorts of medical
techniques I don't know about!
--Huh?!
--Run to the ship on my signal.
Navarone's commander?
New pots and frying pans,
plus silverware and giant mousetraps...
Luffy, stretch your arms and get
everyone on board. Can you do that?
Yes! Navarone's commander is the fisherman.
--Is it really there?!
--There's only a door!
Where is your ship?
And if the bait is near the fisherman,
there's only one place it could be.
No problem...
That leaves a crapload left over!
Yes, assuming the map is correct.
Then the vault is behind there?!
I could drink all I want!
--I see...
--Lt. Commander...
There are actually many docks here...
Yes. Breaking in through there
should be the shortest route!
--Right?!
--Yeah! Yeah!
It doesn't matter. If anything
happens, I'll take responsibility.
You don't mean--!
Judging from where our ship landed,
Yep, that's right!
First, my stash will be 80%!
Then it's decided!
We've got no choice but to go!
it's probably in a dock on
the western side of the base.
If we let them escape now,
all of G8 will be shamed!
What are you doing?!
Hold on a second!
You said you know where the
commander's room is, right?
Just kidding.
The western side? Then I
suppose it could be Dock 88...
All right! Let's do this thing! Usopp Aa-aa-aa!
Obviously! You can't just
openly have a secret stash!
Lead us there!
O-Okay...
What makes you think that, Kobato-san?
By "stash," I mean money
saved up to repair the ship!
Okay! Luffy and I will go!
Yes, well, because of budget cuts and all that,
Robin and the rest, get to the coast!
Chopper's group should come to get you!
our number of docks has been reduced.
The ship? You mean Merry?
All right!
Will you be all right?
But there's still equipment in that one,
The Waver can only hold two people.
That's right. The Going Merry is
what brought us where we are now.
All right!
and actually, that's where my father is!
--Let's go, Usopp!
--Eh?!
It's right by where that warship is stopped.
Come to think of it,
Well, we're gonna get spotted
anyway, so it doesn't matter!
Whoops. Silly me.
it has given us a ride on the seas
ever since my East Blue village...
What the--?! Don't scare us like that!
What do we do, Nami? Are they headed there?
"Aaahhhhhh!"
I'm gonna run it at full throttle! You ready?!
There's no way for us to know right now.
N-No!
It's a slightly older model,
but I personally designed it!
Yeah! Anytime you are!
Now that they've already caused
trouble, we can't just sit around idly!
You fool! He's on your side!
W-We're gonna crash!
Here we go!
Crap! Nami-san!
A carvel-make caravel, with lateen
sails and a central stern rudder...
Get to the ship somehow! Let's do it, Captain!
Let's rely on Dr. Kobato to lead the way!
They've appeared!
I have no choice! All hands! Attack at once!
Where is it?!
I knew that dunderhead would do this!
The Going Merry!
Let's see...
There's no one here...
We have no choice!
Usopp. Don't get left behind.
That's perfect, then! Let's get going!
--Get on already.
--Eh?!
We're friends now, aren't we?
Hurry and find it, Luffy!
Say, wanna do that again?!
--Hey!
--Wait, Luffy! You moron!
Up! Up!
Screw that! I'm never doing that again!
I...
He never learns...
Up where, exactly?!
I get to be captain, right?!
Don't let them escape!
Don't be dumb! I'm the captain!
That's it!
All right! No marines!
Got it!
We've made so many memories with this ship...
Pardon the intrusion!
What a surprise this is!
So high up! Yikes!
--Nami-san. Watch your step.
--Thanks.
What is that vehicle?
I'm thinking of leaving this island!
Go, long-nose!
We can't afford to cause an uproar.
Hey, guys! We're gettin' on!
Is he the commander?!
Looks like our only choice
is to go along the coast now.
Yeah, he's the old fortress guy!
I'm... going now.
There's no time for us to
be dealing with marines!
I never imagined you would
make an entrance through there!
Oh! There they are!
Are they alive?
--And now for you and me!
--What?!
Sanji-kun! Let's hurry!
Cool, huh?!
Okay!
This is actually a vehicle from the sky!
Only Nami can ride it, though!
See! W-What did I tell ya?!
We're almost there, men! Push forward!
--Quit getting excited!
--Yes! I'm sorry!
I see it!
I've not met this girl before. Welcome.
It's right down there!
Were you not pirates, I'd greet you
warmly for your boisterous visit.
The vault is at the end here!
It's a real shame. You're perceptive and bold.
All right! I'm coming for you, gold!
So that's the score. Looks like
this'll be a good little workout...
But daring can also sometimes
be called recklessness.
Damn them! Don't let them escape!
All squadrons, open fire!
We made it here so easily.
Something's not right...
I'm leaving, no matter what!
--B-But there's still a hostage!
--Warning shots are fine!
There will be no soldiers coming
to eat this time, Straw Hat Luffy.
I'll be back someday!
We, the Hot-Blooded Unit of Navarone,
will guard this bridge to the death!
We did it, Merry!
But first! If there's no bait,
we have nothing to bite onto!
And it was with us when we
crossed Reverse Mountain
We will never let the likes
of you pirates cross it!
Why can't you ever rescue us normally?!
and burst onto the Grand Line...
Where's the gold?!
That takes its toll on regular people!
It's hidden in this room, isn't it?
Couldn't you at least show it to us?
This can't be real!
Don't be so damn boastful.
The ocean really is flowing up it!
All right, everyone! Get up!
Just sit there and wait while I have a smoke.
Yes. It's right there.
We made it!
Right in front of me?!
Don't underestimate us!
# We are the Navarone Marines! #
Oh, here it is! The gold!
Nami! We finally found it!
Is that the pirate ship?!
What's the deal? Why won't
they order us to attack?!
We're going into the clouds!
It's not fake bait, I hope?
# We'll show you our fiery spirit! #
It's indeed the genuine article.
Check for yourself.
I hear they have a hostage.
Some nurse they captured.
All right!
--Okay, then!
--Luffy!
That's neat! Is this how it goes?
It's true!
Pirates sure are nasty!
P-Pirates!
Charge!
This is our gold, no doubt about it!
Oh, is that her?
Y-You're not going any further!
I see it! This is the greatest sea
in the world! The Grand Line!
Whoa, the hostage is giving orders!
All right! Let's go now! Sorry for
the intrusion, old fortress guy!
Knock it off. We're not
plannin' to do anything crazy,
This is one hell of a fiasco!
Are the ships ready yet?!
The One Piece is up ahead, somewhere!
Whoops, I think not.
You can't just take the bait and run.
like destroy the fortress or slaughter you.
Gatling!
I'm having them hurry!
Quiet! As disrupters of peace,
you have to be punished!
Go!
--Dad!
--Oh, Kobato.
Zoro!
--Outta the way!
--Okay!
We just told you, we're not gonna do anything!
You've had quite the unusual day!
Try not to be too rough with the lady, now.
And then the sky islands...
Like I can really believe some pirates!
Thanks...
You released the ship, didn't you?
We are proud to protect these waters,
together with our commander!
Straw Hat comes first.
Alright! Zoro! Fight bravely!
You've caused a real mess.
You'll be punished for this, you know!
I'll beat the whole lot of you up!
Prepare yourself, Straw Hat!
Who's this ship's navigator?!
In other words, you're trying
to say you'll risk your life?
You are, Nami-san!
That's neat! Gum-Gum...
What father can sit idly by when
his daughter is about to get hurt?!
A-Another weird net... I'm out of strength...
All right, men! Do what Nami-san says!
Obviously!
Right!
Now!
Sea Prism Stone!
Kobato-san had been rescued!
The plan was underway!
Straw Hat is captured!
We're flying!
Excellent work. Now, then...
Then go eat a lot and train some damn more!
What about the other one?!
You completely ignored her!
Awesome! The ship is flying!
Not good! What do I do?!
There's gotta be something!
Nami-san! You're wonderful!
Wait, if these guys have guns,
I do have a chance!
Officers have to learn not
to view people too lightly!
We studied your moves, Straw Hat!
And I like you!
Rain Tempo! Sprinkler!
You could learn a thing or two
from Commander Jonathan!
W-What?! What?!
And I even risked my life to protect it!
Cool Ball!
Don't be interruptin' my smoke break!
Lt. Commander! About that hostage!
That's cold!
Heat Ball!
What is this?! Awesome!
All sections believe that she's
part of the Straw Hat crew!
It's warm...
Stop it! Stop it!
--I did it!
--W-What the--?!
Bastards...
That's quite heavy security.
What?!
Your fates end here!
A cloud?!
Yeah, this is definitely the
perfect place to hide gold!
Please don't harm the ship!
Today's forecast calls for
clear skies and 0% chance of rain!
Damn crappy marine!
Hey, guys! What're you doing?!
Fight for real, will ya?!
But cumulonimbus clouds may
suddenly develop in some places!
Dammit!
I bet there's lots of other good
stuff in there besides our gold!
Stop right there, Inspector.
Please watch out for lightning!
So, what do we do?
Where are you going?
Gum-Gum Pistol!
What is this, Miss?
I don't believe I'm required
to report my actions.
Thunderbolt Tempo!
And then someone fixed the ship for us...
We are.
I see. Then please tell the commander this.
I have you now!
Sorry, Zoro.
--Hey!
--Sorry...
H-Huh?!
"I had a lot of fun."
Brute strength won't open it!
Screw you!
Luffy!
I chopped with all my strength!
With this vault, you turn these dials,
and when the numbers match,
I really saw it!
An Impact Dial!
Luffy!
I guess there's no point
in disguising myself now.
When you think about it,
this ship's been through a lot!
the gears above turn, the bolts
come undone, and the door opens!
Pull yourself together!
Thanks, Nami...
Hurry! Grab our gold!
Why're we going along the edge of this cliff?!
We'd have cannons on both sides
if we went through the middle!
Got that, lady and gentlemen?!
This way, we only have
to worry about one side!
I'm not one to let prey escape
after hooking it once before...
There's... no end to 'em!
That's far enough!
--Where am I?!
--Oh, he's awake!
It's done so much for us,
but now it's all beat up.
--Huh? When did I get on Merry?
--After a bunch of this and that.
Listen up, you lousy pirates!
I'll catch all of you in one fell swoop.
Good idea! The Going Merry's Great Repair!
We're the "N" at the beginning of "Navarone"!
I see! Nami as a hostage! Nice!
I'm all for it!
We'll risk our spirit to make sure
you pirates never cross this bridge!
Well, Luffy?! See the ship?!
--Isn't it, though?!
--You are good at tricking people.
Okay, then. Since we don't
know how much it'll cost,
It's too dark to see anything!
we'll hold off on dividing up
the treasure when we get it back.
Shut the hell up, you stone-head!
But why'd the ship start moving on its own?
They took most of the food,
but not the stuff in the fridge.
Oh, I bet it was the old maintenance guy.
So they were waiting for us.
Look out, Nami! A navy ship!
It would seem so.
--Why's that?
--I just get that feeling.
Dig in.
You're trapped like rats!
Give yourselves up quietly!
Say, it does look kind of like a warship...
Oww!
Yeah. Usopp's cheap repairs
are just about at their limit.
Do so now and--
Nami-san dressed as a nurse is really nice!
There they are! Over here, Luffy!
What proud, great pirates would ever give up
I'll have you know that I'm a sniper!
We managed to get out, but what
do we do without maps or charts?
when there's treasure right in front of 'em?!
Nami!
But yeah, Mechao-san said the
same thing-- that it needs real repairs.
Ugh. There's no end to this!
This is why I wanted to look around
the place first, you morons!
Nami-san! Are you all right?!
They're all yours now!
Yeah. We should go to a real shipbuilding dock
Hey!
Robin-chan!
You just let Straw Hats who
were in your own room get away.
and have real shipwrights fix it for us.
So cool!
Damn you pirates!
How dare you?! Fire!
So Major Shepherd was a fake?
They even stole the gold. Even you
must admit this is a grave failure.
There are people better than
you at fixing ships, Usopp?
I'm sorry, sir. She got away.
Those are neat things you have!
Sometimes you gotta take extra good care,
They will not escape my
clutches, Major Shepherd.
You're not at fault.
or you'll wind up paying for it later!
Gum-Gum...
All right, it's decided!
I just have a bad habit of
being weak around pretty women.
Usopp! Take care of the vault!
Let's get a shipwright in our crew!
You still won't admit defeat,
after all that's happened?
Consider it taken care of!
Huh?
...Bazooka!
Our journey is far from over!
Anyway, that makes six. We're
currently searching for the last one!
No, I apologize. What do you say, Commander?
Yes!
We need those skills anyway...
Why don't you sit there quietly
and observe my leadership skills?
Oh, there's no need for
that now. I just found her.
Yes, yes!
I thought you had already had enough?
--Sir?
--I contacted the medical room.
And Merry is our home! Our life!
Well, Long-nose? Can you handle it?
What happened earlier was
simply a minor complication!
They said they aren't missing any nurses.
Let's find a shipwright who can keep it safe!
I had already sent out my
special pirate subjugation squad,
Now! Grab his arms while
they're slowed down!
A map of this fortress!
This is really Nami's specialty,
I thought we might need it to escape.
separate from my main unit.
but a lock of this level
is a piece of cake for me!
There he goes again...
Oh. Then I think I will sit back
and watch you in action.
You know the score!
Yeah, on rare occasion,
he gets straight to the point.
You're the only one who's on my side, Sis!
All right!
You're the captain of the Pinepeak?!
First one!
That's the best way! Let's do it!
A-Am I?
I'm not letting go this time!
They will appear near the Sea Gate!
You're so stubborn!
Just as planned, wait for them
to get drawn to it, then sink 'em!
--Okay, then that's the plan!
--I hope we find someone good!
They're shooting at us!
Gum-Gum...
W-What?!
I thought we were okay
cause we had a hostage!
And we need a musician, too!
It's instant death if those hit you.
--Got that?!
--Understood, sir!
No, just forget about that.
They were bound to
realize the truth eventually!
They come off?!
Captain! We're about to
reach the ambush point!
It's nice to be all excited, but have
you forgotten what comes first?
Uh oh.
One slip-up, and my head
could get smashed in!
Warships are coming after us!
...Battle-Axe!
All right! Do not let the pirate ship slip by!
There is no hostage! Everyone on
board is a Straw Hat member!
--What's that?
--We have to get our gold back!
The minute it's spotted,
commence a full-scale attack!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
I repeat, all cannons,
commence firing consecutively!
Oh, right.
That takes care of all the preparations.
Question is, where's it hidden?
That's this fortress' gateway: the "Sea Gate."
Now!
Now to watch things from a high
vantage point. Place a pole in--
In a vault, most likely.
Usopp, prepare the bow cannon!
Luffy! Don't stretch your arms
out too much! They'll cut 'em!
We know that! The problem is,
we don't know where it is!
Could you please not touch that?!
Chopper! Don't get my orders wrong!
Right!
Got it!
May I ask you something?
If that's the only exit, our only
choice is to break through by force.
You don't hafta yell at me!
Wouldn't it be here?
I-If it's about how to catch pirates,
I can teach you anytime you want.
Yes! The second one!
It's only a guess, but if I were
to hide gold in this fortress,
But I don't like that there are more
shallows than this chart shows.
Wasn't this special squadron
of yours on the Pinepeak?
this multi-lock storage vault
seems like the only place to do it.
That's unsuitable for a port, so why is it here?
Lt. Commander. All ships are
now at their designated locations.
--Eh?!
--You're so smart, Robin-chan!
Something doesn't seem right...
There seems to be one more ship...
Yeah, that does seem the most likely!
It's all-clear on your end?
That's fine, then. Keep watch.
Good! Tell them to wait as-is
until orders are given!
Say what?! T-That can't be!
All right, guys! Let's go there
and get our gold back!
That's no Navarone warship.
Yes, sir!
Reporting, sir. The pirate ship
appears to have reached the Sea Gate.
But are we just gonna leave the
Going Merry here? It'll get spotted!
No, it doesn't even look like it is a warship.
Fifty more minutes...
Geez. You never think
about the consequences!
That makes it checkmate...
W-What is that?!
I'm sorry...
But it's a real shame. You weren't
careful enough, Straw Hat-kun.
"Hide a tree in a forest! Hide a ship in ships!"
Well, let's go. Which way is it?
Captain!
I surrender!
A warship-- no, a warship-like ship--
is approaching from behind!
Oh. That way.
Say what?! We don't have
a single cannonball?!
Commander!
A Navarone ship?
And what do you mean, "like"?!
Part of the Straw Gate has been demolished,
Nice, Robin!
Nope! We don't even have
a box to hold explosives!
and the Straw Hats have fallen into the bay.
What, that's it?
I-I'm not really sure how to answer...
You shouldn't try to get too serious that often.
I'm surrounded...
That does seem only natural,
given that the navy confiscated the ship.
Moreover, Unit 55 appears to have
no casualties or missing persons.
It's going to smash into us!
These are the remains of a dock
where ships were built and repaired.
Stop! Stop!
Whoa, now! That's clearly
far too much destruction!
What're we gonna do?! We can't
bust through that gate like this!
Full speed ahead, Merry!
Treinta Fleurs!
When we came in just now, I saw
plenty of abandoned materials.
Those guys...
Just means we gotta fight our way through.
But they did buy us 22 minutes.
All we gotta do is gain control of
the device that raises and lowers it.
They just keep on coming!
There's no end to 'em!
W-What the--?!
Aha! I have a great idea!
Don't talk like it's easy!
Thanks for the piloting! Couldn't
have made it this far without you!
Usopp! Is it open yet?!
You showed us your fiery spirit, Unit 55.
Don't worry! I have a nice idea!
Whisper, whisper, whisper!
All right?! Help me out, guys!
Thanks a bunch! We owe ya one!
Commander! The special capture
operation at Dock 88 is ready!
Target the enemy pirate ship!
Yeah!
It's open!
Fire!
Don't let them escape! After them!
Gum-Gum Balloon!
This is no time for that!
We can now capture the Straw Hats!
What?!
Excellent. They've passed through Straw Gate,
Yes!
I-Impossible! To think they'd
use the Pinepeak, of all things!
Damn you!
so they're definitely headed for Dock 88.
Whadya think?!
Whoa!
Damn you, you Straw Hats!
Stay calm, and don't let your guard down!
At least now we don't have to
worry about it being stolen again!
Don't be so aggravated.
They're as good as caught in a net now.
All hands, retreat!
You're sure it's this way, Usopp?!
Don't worry! This is it! Just keep moving!
Net?
At 9:00 pm, the waters of
Navarone bare their fangs,
Gluing paper all over the
Going Merry was a great idea.
Here they come!
and the final-- and inescapable-- trap begins!
Commence the capture operation!
But I dunno how long it'll fool people,
--Yes!
--I see! I hadn't thought of that!
given how crappily it's been done...
Nice, Luffy!
Wha--?!
Yep! This is definitely a navy
warship, no doubt about it!
Now let's get--
Wow! This vault is so neat!
Okay! Now we can escape!
--Yeah!
--You serious?!
We have no cannonballs or explosives?
What?!
All right, then! Now to get our gold back!
There's an urgent patient
at the dock! Let us through!
Plus we got the gold!
We did it! We did it!
Everyone! We commence
tonight at midnight! Got that?!
Okay! Let's rush straight to the Sea Gate!
There's no gold at all!
Nami?!
Yeah!
--Nami-san nurse!
--W-What is this?!
But why don't we go now?
Hey, what's wrong?!
I won't let you escape from Navarone so easily.
'Cause the mood'll be
better at night, obviously!
--Nami?
--We've been had...
L-Luffy!
Oh! Mood! I see!
Yo...
No, I don't think that's quite why.
The treasure is gone!
Hurry up and get moving towards the future!
Let's move ahead, pursuing our dreams
All the answers are right here, pouring out
Rush forth, rush forth,
on the road opened before us
Let's keep moving forward! We can do it!
We won't give in, we won't give in,
even if the obstacle is big
It's nothing to be scared of,
we can overcome it
Attention, Straw Hat Luffy and his crew!
Where'd you disappear to, you damn pirates?!
Now we don't have to worry
about Merry, but hold on, you guys!
It's payback time for all your
countless insults toward me!
Flare bombs can't shut my eyes!
Don't tell me you managed
to sneak past the cannoneers
You've fought most valiantly against
the Navy's great G8 Fortress!
Are you just gonna go like this?!
--Impressive, moss-head!
--Thanks, fancy-eyebrows!
--Oh!
--My special unit from HQ will
take care of you Straw Hats!
and vanish beyond the
horizon in that short period?!
Geez! Seven people running
around will stand out too much!
--Bring it on, moss-head!
--You crappy cook!
They won't try to escape.
--Oh!
--This is the latest portable
bazooka, the Eagle Launcher!
You've done admirably, but this is the end!
Here! I'll give you my super secret plan!
This is no time to be arguing!
There's no point without the gold!
--Just give it up, Straw Hats!
--We still have a chance!
You will never reach your ship!
Pirates leaving treasure behind
is shameful! Right rudder, full!
Oh! So cool!
--On the next One Piece!
--I do this part!
--Now you die!
--Yeah!
On the next episode of One Piece!
I'm out of strength again...
--Hey, you!
--On the next episode of One Piece!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Gold and Waver Recovery Operations!"
"The Pirate Ship Disappears!
Fortress Battle, Round #2"
"Farewell, Navy Fortress!
The Last Battle for Escape"
"The One Fell Swoop Plan!
Jonathan's Surefire Secret Tactic"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Breaking Through the Siege!
The Going Merry Is Recovered"
I'm gonna be a brave warrior of the sea!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
You too?!