Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
And whoever gets it can be King
of the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
with the sun always in our hearts
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
The horizons everyone
dreamed of were separate at first
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
but now they can be seen
through a single telescope
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Now's the time to set
sail-- let's raise anchor
A bitter compass of destiny
is leading your heart astray
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
but what you cherish most will be right there
Toss aside your bonds and your past
And if you get into a jam
We can surely smile despite that
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
Tears shed trying to achieve
your dreams aren't for naught
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
Precious in my life
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
"Farewell, Navy Fortress!
The Last Battle for Escape"
One Piece
Not good! Not good!
Not good! Not good! Not good!
All right! All right!
The first round of the Davy
Back Fight is the Donut Race.
"Round 1! One Lap of the Donut Race"
My subjugation squad!
There's nothing at all!
The Straw Hat team managed to
overcome various acts of sabotage...
They got you good, Inspector Shepherd.
That ain't a giraffe...
...but Zoro and Chopper's boat
was knocked out of the race.
I-I've driven them this far!
I leave the rest to you!
It's got a long neck,
but it's a horse. A long-horse...
Sheesh!
Only the Cutie Wagon,
Barrel Tiger, and It's a Raft remain!
You've gotten us into a real mess, Luffy!
Gum-Gum Whip!
If they escape now, it will be
entirely your responsibility!
The battle is between these three boats now!
All we gotta do is win!
Entirely mine? Very well.
"Great Adventure at Long Ring Long Land!"
Hey! You forgot somethin'!
Write down your rosters and
give them to our party organizer!
But you'd best report to headquarters
"'Silver Fox' Foxy! The
Merciless Interference"
What's going on?!
about a certain someone else
who kept getting in the way.
Actually...
Members can participate only twice.
...I cut a bamboo tree and a spirit appeared!
Once you've chosen
your roster, it's set in stone!
The Straw Hat pirates...
The events of the contest are...
They're exactly as
Admiral Akainu described them.
The race is really heating up!
A race, a ball game, and a team competition.
The Long Coral Reef blocks
the course directly ahead!
What are they planning?!
What's this? The race is open to all members,
As strange as it sounds, it's thanks
to them that we can now prove
We are the Foxy Pirates!
In the lead is Porche-chan's Cutie Wagon!
Don't be hasty! All we want... is a showdown!
the ball game is open to three,
the importance of Navarone Fortress
to the faultfinders at HQ.
The Straw Hats' Barrel Tiger
and It's a Raft desperately pursue!
How's our bearing look, Nami-san?
and the team competition is open to five...
All right! I'm gonna do all three!
They entered our impregnable fortress,
Wow! They're like Chopper's antlers!
Perfect!
That's our Nami-san for ya!
broke through many traps and pursuits,
The rules say that isn't allowed.
"A Davy Back with the Foxy Pirates!"
What is this long, protruding coral?
and are now attempting to escape again.
What kind of coral sticks out like that?
Hey, what if we lose?
But, however great they may be as pirates...
I bet they'll want Captain Usopp...
Come to my house! I'm in your debt!
Let me offer you some hospitality!
Look! It's causing strange-acting currents!
The holes are just about patched up.
No, I bet it'll be me. Because I'm cute...
General? Oh, good.
Stand by until I give orders.
Boy, am I glad I had the foresight
--All right! Food!
--Yeah!
We can't just plunge in recklessly...
to take a bunch of scrap
lumber back at that dock!
I'll now announce the rosters
submitted by both teams!
Yuck! I can't believe the
race has lasted this long...
It's good to see my house again!
Yes, sir! Remain on standby!
You're great, Usopp!
It's custom in this village to treat
visitors to milk from our farm animals.
Yes, sir!
We should be okay for a little while now.
Monda! We're counting on you!
First is the Straw Hat team!
Commander! Are you just going
to sit there idly and watch?!
But let's not forget there's someone
on land just hoping to interfere:
Participating in Round #1's Donut Race is...
the entire Straw Hat crew!
Village? Where's the village?
Now, now. Just watch patiently.
The time for checkmate is nearing.
our boss, "Silver Fox" Foxy!
And your farm animals...
It went out!
--But...!
--As I said, they're as good as captured.
Actually, my "Can't Be in a Race"
disease is kicking in...
Out of fuel?
Just what does he have in store?!
What do you mean "where"?
Hey, Usopp! We're about
to make a splashdown!
I don't wanna do it either,
you know! Just accept it!
The 9:00 pm net has
already sprung into action.
Hurry, Chopper! Bring all those boards up!
The village is gone! And the farm animals!
Participating in Round #2's Groggy Ring is...
--Get 'em, Boss!
--Yahoo! Just a matter o' time now!
What do you mean? What is this
"9:00 pm" stuff you keep mentioning?
R-Right!
Get real. Villages don't just
disappear in ten years, you know.
...Roronoa Zoro, Sanji,
and Tony Tony Chopper!
Oh, what's this?! Both Straw Hat
boats have slowed a bit!
You'll just have to wait and see!
You can do it, octopus balloon!
You idiot! Just hit the deck!
Oh, actually...
--Don't go slowin' me down!
--That's my line!
--C'mon, Nami! Paddle!
--Not yet!
Well, I can explain it later.
For now, let me treat you.
I'm... gonna try my very... hardest!
But they're getting ahead!
All right! Full speed ahead!
I said not yet!
Hurry! Hurry!
I believe I had some milk stored away...
Participating in Round #3's
Run Around Roller is...
--Same goes for you, Sanji-kun!
--Your wish is my command!
...Monkey D. Luffy,
Nico Robin, Nami, and Usopp!
Our navigator doesn't seem
interested in going forward, though.
Stored away? You realize you were
on those stilts for ten years, right?
The Cutie Wagon uses this
chance to continue forward
Nami-san! What's wrong?
and plunge into the Long Coral Reef!
Only four people? We're one short.
Is there something behind us?!
Let's go, Monda!
J-Just in the nick of time!
That doesn't matter! Let's do it!
Hopefully this cheese is to your liking...
Wait! Oh, my! What's happening?!
Look! Navarone warships!
Don't look away! That's obviously
your ten-year-old milk!
A captain, a swordsman,
a navigator, a sniper,
Monda!
a cook, a doctor, and an archaeologist, huh?
I see. That's a shame.
Oh... They came back.
Oh, my! The Cutie Wagon
has been sent backwards!
Well, then. Who shall I take first?
There, you should be all better now.
Please make yourselves at home then.
Whew! They don't seem to be chasing us!
What in the world happened?!
Huh? This cheese is edible, old guy?
That's twice you've helped us out now!
I guess it'd have to be that one!
No! Why?!
Don't even try!
See? I knew something
was up with these currents.
I really want that member!
They dropped their anchors?!
Thanks!
It's okay! It's only ten-year-old cheese!
All right! It's finally time
for the merciless Davy Back!
Okay! Let's increase speed!
They must've given up.
Take care!
Unlike you folks, I live a
laid-back life on this island.
The winner gets a feast,
while the loser gets fleeced!
I hope you make some
good friends in the Blue Sea!
R-Right!
--I wonder.
--They gave in to our brilliant skills!
Follow us, Sanji-kun!
Go give all those Grand Line
octopuses a throttling!
It's made my stomach different from yours.
Aye-aye, Sir!
I, Itomimizu, the Foxy
Pirates' party organizer,
Honestly, now. Whippersnappers
these days are so frail...
So long, seafood ingredient!
Try again, Monda!
will be your commentator
for this competition!
This way!
Thanks for everything!
Even when they could at least fire at us?
First up is Round #1, the Donut Race!
Be careful on your way!
What's this?! Both Straw Hat
boats have sped up!
Call... a doctor...
Don't tell me there's some other reason?!
I told you so, you idiot!
That's what's bugging me-- I don't know!
All three boats are entering the
Long Coral Reef at the same time!
How shall we team up?
Doctor! Doctor!
Okay, then...!
Bugged Nami-san is lovely, too!
Considering that some of us
have Devil Fruit powers,
Set the sails, men! Let's go to the next island!
Th-That's me!
Hmm? The Barrel Tiger and
It's a Raft are staying inside!
It's food poisoning.
maybe we should split into two
teams of three and four people...
Whoa, hold on, Luffy!
Obviously!
Commander! It's finally begun!
Boats for the Donut Race can only be made
--Let us rest a little!
--Don't forget where we are!
You're funny, old guy!
Whoa! What the...?!
Good. Do as I instructed.
from two oars and three empty barrels!
You're nomads?
Anyone could sail these seas
if it was okay to be so carefree!
Yes. We're carefree nomads,
always on the move.
Use of any other materials
means instant disqualification!
Was that Drake?! Then order him
to pursue them this instant!
What are you getting at?
Ahh! There it is at last!
This is a chance for
shipwrights to show their stuff!
Devilish interference from you-know-who!
So that's how your village
disappeared after only ten years...
The waves have been looking a little strange.
Why are they lowering their
anchors and sitting there?!
Those without empty barrels, come get some!
Hop to it, everyone! Turn to port!
A smoke screen...!
The reason they've dropped their
anchors... is because it's 9:00 pm.
We'll give 'em to you for free!
We're generous like that!
Right, Nami-san!
This is the island of
Long Ring Long Land. Welcome.
What's that damn idiot doing?!
I'm not sure we can use three barrels
to build a boat for four of us.
I can't see in front of us!
-- "9:00 pm"  again?!
--If they don't drop their anchors,
Thanks.
Oh, my!
It's technically a single ring-shaped island,
It's too dangerous for the Straw Hat
the fangs of Navarone's
waters will eat them up.
Okay, three teams it is.
They'll consist of...
boats to continue forward one bit!
but because of the sea, it's usually
divided into ten separate islands.
The fangs of Navarone's waters?
Oh, here it comes!
Operation White Out is a great success!
Full speed ahead!
Hey, you! Don't go busting 'em up like that!
But on one day a year,
the tide gets especially low,
--This isn't good!
--There's stuff in the wave, too!
--What's that sound?!
--It sounds like a flowing river!
Let's see you find your way
through this coral maze blind!
Just watch! I'm gonna make an awesome boat!
and for those few hours, the island
regains its true, singular form.
Huh? Those are Sea Monkeys!
There's a river on this island?
Success?
I must not have noticed it this afternoon.
We use this fact to migrate from one
island to the next every three years.
Can you see now?
All right! While everyone's
busy with their boats,
How in the...?!
I'll explain how the race works!
They got through! With no
trouble at all! How did they do it?!
What's all the ruckus here?!
Nami-san! What's happening?!
The course will be one lap
around Long Ring Long Land!
Just as I thought!
Run!
So you got left behind
after the village moved?
Quit pushing! W-We gotta stay away from 'em!
It might sound easy, but it's anything but!
The Straw Hat boats slip through
the forest of coral with ease!
They're having a falling out?!
T-The rudder isn't working!
I like you, old guy! You're a big dummy!
A team is immediately out of
the race should their boat sink!
The tide! A huge outward tide
happens at this time at this fortress!
Meanwhile, the Cutie Wagon...
If they stay on each island for three years,
--Oh, no!
--...has been sent back again!
In addition, all weapons are allowed,
then it'd take 'em thirty years
to come all the way back here.
No!
even guns, cannons, explosives,
cutlasses or anything else!
What's going on?!
The boat's moving on its own!
Eaten by the waters' fangs?
Taking away the time you
were stuck on those stilts,
Whoever complains about unfairness
will be shamed as a pirate!
--This is a maze of sea currents.
--Of sea currents?
However skilled a navigator
those Straw Hats may have,
you won't see them again
for about twenty more years...
--Bellamy!
--Sarquiss!
Yep. The whirlpool up ahead is
Managed to finish it...
Please! Make him stop!
the fact that they're on a ship
means they can't escape from this net.
Pretty much.
causing strange currents in this reef,
If I only I had a hooorse.
Please! Stop! Why are you doing this...?!
full of smaller whirlpools.
Time is nearly up! Is everyone ready?
No one escapes from my clutches.
So we don't need to see ahead!
I could catch up to the others in five years
--What's happening?!
--Sarquiss is in pain!
Oh! The final odds are in!
The currents will carry us through,
as long as we take the right entrance!
by crossing to a new
island once every year...
Why? Why, you ask?
So that's what the deal was...
I'll list them in order of popularity,
starting with the most popular!
"Hooorse"?
Awesome! That's the power of our navigator!
What are you acting satisfied for?!
Yes. The most beautiful
animals on these islands.
Sarquiss... Bellamy...
When we first tried to escape,
Hurray!
The top spot obviously goes to our idol,
I was puzzled as to why they'd use
a bay so full of shore reefs as a port.
They gallop through the
grassy plains so gracefully...
Way to go, Nami-san!
the member of the powerful
Team Foxy: Porche-chan!
It's because you've tarnished
this symbol of mine, of course.
Ooh! Just leave it to me!
Curses!
They're absolutely necessary
to migrate from island to island.
--So?
--It was the other way around.
With her is the swordfish fishman
Capote and the star shark Monda!
Shallows are bad for ports,
so they normally use the Sea Gate
"Does the sky island exist or not?"
But their joy is short-lived!
Beyond the coral forest is the Long Ring!
They're strong and can carry large loads.
They're riding in the Cutie Wagon!
to regulate the water level inside.
"Is the city of gold real or not?"
I can't migrate on foot, either--
But they can use the low tide in an emergency
This'll be a cinch! You can do it!
Huh?! It's just one "Long" after another!
the tide would come back in before
I even got across to the next island.
to make this great fortress
of Mother Nature inescapable!
I don't give a care about any of that.
Hold on! You're using a fish!
Usopp! Quit freaking out and fire it!
Can't you just take a ship?
There's no rule against fish, you know!
You're to twist people around by
taking advantage of differing opinions.
--Fire what?!
--An Impact!
We don't know how to sail.
So that's why ships could only
come and go at specific times.
Second most popular is...
--I-I told you, we don't have it! Nope!
--Oh? Then what's this?
That's what I told you...
Besides, even if we charged a Log Pose here,
Oh! This is unexpected!
...wasn't it, Bellamy?
You're so smart, Nami-san!
Your logic is spot-on!
it wouldn't point to the
next island in the ring.
The Straw Hat team of Navigator Nami,
That's... Don Quixote Doflamingo!
Sniper Usopp, and Archeologist Robin!
When did you...?!
All ten islands are actually
one big island, after all.
So, what do we do?
Hurry! Before the whirlpool sucks us in!
All right! Let's head for the Sea Gate!
They'll be riding the Barrel Tiger!
He's one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
I'll just wait here twenty years.
We can't!
He used to have a bounty over 300 million!
What's with the smile...?
That orange-haired chick is hot!
Full speed ahead!
You've used it before!
You sure? It'll be lonely...
What's a guy like him doing here?!
You know using it can bust your shoulders...!
I want that dark-haired girl on our crew!
Pay attention!
I don't need useless punks
like you serving under me...
--That's okay! I don't mind!
--'Cause it's my shoulder!
Oh, wait!
--Don't need that other guy!
--Yeah. Never mind him.
Is a "hooorse" a "horse"?
I see! Looks like the rowdy Foxy Pirates
--Good luck!
--Hey, now!
--Luffy!
--W-What the--?!
Crap! My body's moving on its own!
Hurry! There's no time!
Oh, right! A horse! We saw one!
have a soft spot for cutey-pies!
We've run onto a reef!
Stop! Please, don't...!
No wonder you seemed so calm!
What lechers!
No!
--Are you sure this won't sink?!
--I already told you...
You had this in mind from the start...
The hull!
I'm not a shipwright!
Oh! Shelly! You waited for me?!
But it still beats those.
Well, it's been a nice life...
Bellamy!
It's been ripped open!
Treinta Fleurs!
Oh, Shelly! You're so adorable!
This sure brings back memories!
This ain't a boat! It's just some scrap wood!
Someone come help!
G-Give me...
That's okay!
You've grown so long since I last saw you!
--O-Oh, no!
--It's damn huge!
--Okay, Long-nose!
--"Okay," my butt...
--So you do that the whole time?
--Yep! I just keep running really hard!
Give me one more chance...!
Can't we plug it up?!
Fine!
That's a good girl!
A plug! Something to plug it up! A plug!
You must've been so lonely,
all by yourself all those years!
It's a miracle they even float...
I-- we-- will follow you loyally!
Oh! The Barrel Tiger and
It's a Raft have sped up together!
--Huh?
--The water stopped...
Looks like it's up to us if we
don't wanna lose this race...
Thank you! Thank you!
--Bellamy!
--No more, Bellamy!
More than just that! They're flying!
I'm drowning! I'm drowning!
Third most popular is the Harem Nocturne,
I'll never leave you again!
They're leaping right over Long Cape!
Yes, I lost, but I never went
against your principles!
a boat of the beautiful,
by the beautiful, for the beautiful!
Will they land back in the water?!
--The ship's completely run aground!
--Does that mean--?
I swear on your symbol!
She wants you to ride on her!
No, wait!
This is just my way of doing things!
In fourth place is the Crab Crane,
a regular in the top ranks!
We can't move forward or escape.
We couldn't just run 'im off;
Looks like the enemy was counting on this.
Huh? Huh?
In fifth and sixth place are
the Swordfish King #1 and #2!
he would've reached you someday!
Huh, huh, huh? Huh?!
I'm drowning! I'm drowning! I'm gonna drown!
Seventh most popular is the
party-loving Pleasure Boat!
How very touching,
obedient subordinate of mine.
It's one thing after the other with these guys!
It snapped off...
In eighth place is the Duke Special!
What now? Ditch the ship again and run?
That's what I like about you, Bellamy.
Ah, so that horse was waiting
for him the entire time...
Wait! What about our boat?!
The It's a Raft crashes
into pieces on Long Cape!
And go through the same stuff again?!
Yeah! Mine too!
It's not the same! The ship's gonna
sink when the tide comes back!
A "New Era" is just around
the corner. Do as you wish.
She's great!
It can't continue the race!
Let's see here...
She must really like him a lot!
What a shame! The It's a Raft
is now out of the race!
--The gold, too?!
--I refuse to let that happen!
Doctor Chopper and Swordsman
Zoro's Basically Barrels is...
Save me! I'm hungry!
But... I don't need you anymore.
Sorry, Nami-san! Don't worry
about us! Just keep going!
...third from last!
Man, that horse sure is
fast! I wanna ride too!
Right!
Doflamingo!
Not too surprising.
But the Barrel Tiger takes
a miraculously big lead!
This is the Impact Dial!
She really is graceful!
And the It's a Raft...
Can we use this?!
Shelly. Let's cross the sea
together on the next low tide day!
Does this spell defeat for
the indomitable Cutie Wagon?!
...wins the booby prize!
Given how much the tide has
gone out, we won't have to worry
He took out the notorious Bellamy--
a rookie worth 55 million--
What's that mean?
about the ship sinking
until the next high tide.
We underestimated them a bit!
All those days with rain...
Means we're second to last.
like he was a baby!
All those days with snow...
Hang on tight, Porche-chan!
But we can't move, either.
You mean there's an even worse boat?!
Thank you for waiting through it all!
We're counting on you!
Okay! Let's have some food!
It's finally beginning!
Incidentally, the very last place
goes to the giant boat...
You'd better get ready!
How can you be so carefree?! Look at that!
Combine!
Two Fish Engine!
A world where only true pirates
can survive is drawing near!
...the Mothership Coaster!
Those of you who are powerless--
run for your lives!
No! They haven't lost yet!
Their fishman muscle and shark fin
combo doubles their engine speed!
Soon, the tide of the times will wash over all
Shelly... Do you really insist
on waiting for Tonjit-san?
and a new era of champions will be upon us!
They zip through the coral and
turbulent waves to close the gap!
I don't think oars are long
enough for that thing...
We're going to take all
your friends with us...
Wait! Littonto!
How does it even move?
Attention, Straw Hat Luffy and his crewmates!
Are you sure?
The race is half over!
You guys are sharp!
We won't be back here for 27 years,
Meanwhile, the Barrel Tiger
paddles desperately!
Yup, oars are too short for this boat!
It's filled with seawater, too!
Get up, Usopp!
and we have no idea where Tonjit-san even is.
--Where am I?
--Just start paddling!
Those guys are dumb!
"Full of Power!"
"Carbohydrates!"
"Navy Dining Hall"
You'll be all by yourself!
Your arm is twisted in an odd direction.
How many barrels did they use, anyway?
Seems the Straw Hat pirates
got caught in the 9:00 pm net!
Take my advice, come with us!
This thing is just three giant barrels,
all stuck together!
What's that?
I'm gonna stay too! I'm gonna
wait for Grandpa with Shelly!
Not even they can escape from
the fangs of Navarone's waters!
--It's a course marker.
--It says to go right.
It ain't breaking any rules!
Okay! Right we go!
No, you're not! You can't
stay here all alone!
Things've sure calmed down...
What's gonna happen to him?!
Okay! All the boats are at the starting line!
Like we'd fall for that!
Can't lower our guard yet, though.
Well... Pirates have always been
subjected to capital punishment...
Emergency report! Emergency report!
I can too!
Oh, my! Our boss's Ploy #18,
"Operation Lie to Them," has failed!
Grandpa's here! I know it!
I'm gonna wait for him too!
I'll be providing commentary during the race
Ship spotted at 12 o'clock!
from atop Chirp-Chirp, a rare
South Blue Super Sparrow!
--Huh? Are they bad guys?!
--This is the worst possible time!
Live well, Shelly!
Truly formidable! Does this girl
not believe anything?!
Actually, there's no flag or sails!
I don't know what kind of ship it is!
Shelly!
You can't, not in your
condition! You're sick, Dad!
Shut up, you!
She's foul-mouthed, too!
Porche-chan!
Seriously, nothing at all?!
What are they on the sea for, then?!
Quiet! That stupid sickness is long gone!
The race continues!
Barrel Tiger is still in the lead!
I hope you sink, nose dude!
Me?!
He better not have ruined that wonderful ship!
We have to win now!
Heck if I know!
The crew seems unusually small, too...
Sinking opponents is fair game.
What are these columns of water?!
If he has, I'll kick his ass!
Oh, my. Listen to that crazy talk.
Plus...!
Mr. Raccoon Dog...
Let 'em talk, Porche-chan.
We'll sink 'em in three minutes!
They also clear the long waves
that reach high into the sky!
They're looking really timid!
Almost like they're lifeless!
Right, Monda?!
Natural phenomenon?!
You've fought most valiantly
against the Navy's great G8 Fortress!
Granny...
I'm getting excited!
Boss, err, Granny...
Do we even have a chance?
Yeah... I think I'm done for...
Listen up, Usopp! Anything happens
to the ladies and I'll filet you!
Sea Monkeys! Run!
I'm impressed, enemy as you are.
--Again?!
--They followed us?!
Our boss unleashes a third nasty trick!
You've done admirably, but this
is checkmate, Straw Hat Pirates!
--Crap! There's no wind!
--Hurry! Furl the sails!
We will win!
Oh! You on the boat! Please save me!
Row! Row!
Listen! Don't you even dare
think about trying to escape!
Fool! No one's ever beat us
in an orthodox-rules game!
Whoa there, Shelly!
Unbelievable! She completely
ignores a helpless, sick grandmother!
You know I'm afraid of heights!
What the...?! Is that ship gonna be all right?!
Is she heartless, or does she
only care about herself?!
Think this race will last
five minutes, Hamburg?
I can anticipate everything
you might think up!
The wave's gonna swallow 'em!
Whatever the case,
Navigator Nami has a heart of ice!
Hey! You guys!
Nope.
Will you shut up already?!
I'd never fall for that crap!
Yes! Atta boy!
A giant wave and monkeys are coming! Turn!
Now take these Eternal Poses
so that you don't get lost!
As commander of Navarone Fortress,
She's foul-mouthed, too!
I will greet the Straw Hat
Pirates with utmost respect!
--Oh!
--Whoa! A ship!
A pirate ship!
Lost?
Give yourselves up quietly!
Look! It's the goal!
Men! Get up! An enemy ship!
Let's swipe their treasure!
Try not to leave the island and go too far!
Luffy!
The finish is close at hand!
Wait! A giant wave's coming!
We gotta escape first!
Leave the island? Why would we do that?
Not so fast!
Straw Hat!
--We can't let that ship get away!
--Ready the cannons!
You and Roronoa Zoro both
have bounties on your heads,
The Cutie Wagon has caught up!
We're taking the shortest route,
along the inside track!
Who made you boss?! You do it!
Who will be the winner of
Round #1's Donut Race?!
so I will have to hand
you over to headquarters.
Turn! Someone turn!
--I don't think it'll be that simple...
--Why not?
But I will guarantee the safety
of the rest of your crew.
What an unorganized ship...
Just look!
Forget 'em. They're not on our side.
They wanna steal our treasure.
Besides that gigantic one in the back,
But if you even think of escaping... I'll get mad!
Horse!
all their other boats are on the
outside track, facing outward!
Old guy!
--Which way do we turn?!
--How should I know?!
--Someone, give orders! Navigator!
--Don't got one!
Too lenient!
Suspicious, don't you think?!
I'm the commander here. You're the
inspector. Be quiet and inspect.
Okay! On your marks!
--Captain!
--Don't got one!
Ready!
Who just fired that?!
Shelly!
Why won't it be so simple?!
A-At this rate, I'll wind up having done
nothing but get in the way of a badger!
--You okay?!
--We heard a gunshot!
Grrr!
Who will be the winner?!
Just trust me! Men! Leave the
shore as soon as we start!
I came to crush this fortress, but now
my own relevance is in question!
--It's no use! It's gonna swallow us!
--Damn! You're all incompetent!
I told you...
If you'll excuse me, please!
--You're one to talk!
--We can't handle a single wave?!
What'd he say?
Cut it out! You're annoying!
--Why?!
--Grin...
What's this net?!
She even sees through "Operation Fake Goal"!
--Just a sec!
--Old guy!
Donut!
Formidable! Truly formidable!
--I've got a bad feeling about this!
--Tell us why!
I have a question for her now!
What does it mean to "believe"?
The horse is mine now!
--Push it! Push it! Push it!
Yeah! Yeah! That horse is our boss's!
I don't care!
Oh, it's too late! Her heart's
already closed! She's a heathen!
Who are you guys?!
We're gonna teach ya what
this boat exists for!
The real goal is near, though.
--No more Impacts!
--Yeah, I know!
We still have a chance!
An Impact Dial!
Meanwhile, Porche-chan's team has
tragically stopped at the fake goal!
When we escaped from the fortress,
I gathered a ton of impacts!
What are these?
Oh, no! We're too late!
--What happened to the race?
--Hey! Where is everyone?!
We might be able to make the
ship float in the air using this!
What are these?
These are traps?
Who are you guys?!
The purity of your heart is dazzling!
N-Nami! Don't...!
--Oh!
--Ah!
We just need to use it to go
somewhere where there's ocean!
But you've been duped!
Pay attention, Porche-chan!
Man, it's one thing after another...!
Who am I, you ask?
So many idiots!
But one shot won't be enough.
They're so rude!
I'll be too embarrassed to live
if we lose to these guys!
With that huge hole,
the ship'll sink right away!
It's finally calmed down.
Those waves were actually
the Sea Monkeys' doing.
If we could just make the
octopus balloon fly again...
They'll take our crew too! That's even worse!
And there they are! The Mothership
Coaster's infamous Barrel Mines!
Don't pretend you don't know this face!
Yeah, good thinking!
The humidity and temperature
are pretty stable now,
Oh, no! This goal is a fake!
Couldn't we re-inflate it
with Flame and Breath Dials?
I don't know your face! I'm gonna beat it up!
so we must already be in
the next island's climate zone!
What?! Who would be so evil?!
Yes! Yes, that's great!
Eep!
Hey, Robin. See anything?
Th-They don't know me...
The Barrel Tiger is finally
approaching Long Bamboo Cape!
See you later!
Oh, no! Boss! Don't get depressed!
An island's been visible for a while.
Don't sink right away, though!
Give us some fun!
--The octopus isn't here...
--The octopus...
He's lying! I bet he's just saying that!
Why couldn't you say so sooner?!
The goal is just beyond it!
This is the homestretch!
--The octopus.
--Damn octopus...
--The octopus...
--The octopus?!
You're such a wet blanket!
He can't possibly know him.
--I have it.
--He says he has it.
Listen! Whenever you see an island, say this!
He's right! There's the goal!
--He has it?
--He has it.
Stop laughing, Hamburg!
Go ahead!
Wait!
--He damn has it.
--So he has it.
--Go away!
--Stupid things! I'm gonna send you flying!
Men! I see an island! Yahoo!
My name is Foxy! I take whatever I want!
But they're catching up to us!
He has it?
Yep. I have it.
We're no match for their speed!
Gum-Gum...!
Eh?!
That's it, Usopp! Can you
knock that bamboo down?!
--Stop, Luffy.
--Yeah! They'll explode like crazy!
Now you say it!
Let this be a lesson, you fools!
--The fog is rather thick.
--You're ignoring me again?!
The bamboo?!
All right!
But we have to do something...
Why are you so worked up
about a single horse?!
See?
Fog? We gotta be careful.
We just gotta get rid of 'em
without touching 'em.
Hunting is nothing more than entertainment!
--Like that?!
--Do more!
What do you have that thing for?!
--Chopper! Keep forward watch!
--Right!
Hand me that oar, Luffy!
Full speed, Capote! Monda!
Why, you...!
It saved our lives on
our way back from the sky.
Gum-Gum...!
We have to sink them!
Hey! Do you know how much we've
been waiting to see an island?!
Wh-What are you doing, Zoro?!
Stop, Straw Hat Luffy!
Maybe so, but didn't it feel gross?!
Just watch...
I'm sorry. I'll be more mindful.
How do you know my name?!
Take this! And this! And this!
Really? In that case, okay.
Gross how?
Of course we know who you are!
We've done our homework!
Hey, is anyone else curious
about that ship from earlier?
Let's have the octopus work
for us again. Okay, Long-nose?
Monkey D. Luffy, with a
100 million-Berry bounty.
They said they had no captain or navigator,
Roronoa Zoro, with a 60 million-Berry bounty.
Wow! Bingo!
Y-Yeah.
and they didn't even have flags,
sails, motivation, or organization...
But hold on. I can't find my Flame Dial--
A total bounty of 160 million
with only seven people...
Oh, no! Capote!
What kind of pirates
would go around like that?!
Th-They're coming back!
They'll pay for this!
It was neat, so I was playing
with it in the kitchen!
That's really something.
Probably got into a battle and lost.
Cutie Baton!
We Foxy Pirates challenge you
Straw Hats to a "Davy Back Fight"!
Oww! You moron!
And their captain died
and they got plundered...
Now, then! That just leaves us
with who'll fire this Impact Dial...
What's that? Flower magic?
No, that can't be it!
I got a good look at their ship!
Flower Shurikens!
Stop talking crazy! Just bring it on!
If you wanna fight, let's fight!
There weren't any signs of a battle at all!
Ah, they're throwing stars... Yikes!
Yet the ship was completely bare of
all the essentials that pirates need!
What's with those looks?!
Nami-san! Robin-chan! Hold on
to your boat! Ride the wave!
Wait, Luffy... A Davy Back fight is...
Whose Impact Dial is that?
Oh, no! We've sprung a leak!
Usopp's.
So they weren't pirates, then.
Don't worry about it.
It's okay! We can make it!
The goal's right there!
Ah! That explains the ship
we encountered near here!
Huh?!
Right, Long-nose?
It's only natural that the suggester does it.
We can't ride that!
Let's make a run for it!
Round #1 of the Davy Back Fight,
the Donut Race,
You're so wonderful, Usopp!
But they sure seemed like pirates to me...
--Which way do we turn?!
--How should I know?!
I really respect you!
--Oh, come on. We'll help you out.
--Y-You can't be serious...
--Someone, give orders! Navigator!
--Don't got one!
I somehow get a bad feeling about this...
is about to reach a conclusion!
Then it's decided!
You always do.
--Captain!
--Don't got one!
No!
Okay! I wonder if there's a town!
I hope they have a shipyard!
Hold on, Luffy! That game...!
Luffy! Don't go jumping off right away!
Stay strong, Monda! We
can't let them beat us!
General! Prepare to open fire!
Don't do it! We'll lose crew members!
Yes, sir!
What's the deal, Usopp?!
We'll lose if we don't do something!
Stay in line with them!
Yahoo! This is neat!
Prepare to fire!
I'm telling you, don't agree to his game!
I hope we'll get a good shipwright to join us!
Right, Boss!
Crap! We're breaking apart...
Which one is winning?!
Preparations complete!
I'm scared!
We're near the shore! Get the anchor ready!
Fool! I heard you say it, Straw Hat Luffy!
That's cold water...
C'mon, guys... Listen to me...
--Made it in time!
--All right! Nami's team is winning!
You clearly agreed to my challenge just now!
Chopper! Usopp's got the
"Can't Go On the Island" disease!
Wh-What the...?!
Didn't he, Porche-chan?!
Good work, dear.
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
Yes, Boss! I heard him, too!
Work is important, but you need
to eat at the proper times, too!
There's no cure for that.
Do you honestly think you can back out now?
You speedy ladies are lovely!
All right! All right!
But broccoli and carrots
and green peppers aren't--
Man, you guys almost won...
Oh! The Straw Hat teams are
speeding to the front of the pack!
Well, you can't.
Huh? We are winning!
No, I haven't finished work yet!
Or, what? You're not man
enough to keep your word?
Incredible!
For now! But look!
The Straw Hats are sealed off so completely--
Are you kidding me?!
What the...?
--Our boss is there!
--So?! What can he do now?!
No way! They're going to catch up to us!
I am too!
There's nothing at all!
surely they can't do anything now.
--Don't get talked into it!
--But... the horse!
Let's go, Monda! Give it
everything you've got!
Now you just need to capture them alive.
Our boss is just like you.
What is this place?! So cool!
Yes... But they could still
defy all our expectations.
He has Devil Fruit powers.
Shelly... Oww!
Give us backup, you guys!
It's all grass as far as I can see!
Don't push yourself! You hit your back hard!
How can they possibly escape,
trapped between land and sea?!
Right!
Slow-Slow Beam!
Man, what a dull place.
Where did they appear from?
Do you suppose anyone lives here?
Eh?!
--You two! Step aside!
--Old guy!
They still have the sky.
--Yahoo!
--Hey!
Finally calmed down...
Me too!
Shelly faithfully waited ten
years for me! How dare you...?!
Oh, man. The shock busted
the raft a little...
All set here!
And the winner is the Cutie Wagon!
Roger that!
Wait, old guy! They're pirates!
Whew, that was fun! I hope
there's another wave! Don't you?
Our idol, Porche-chan, has won the
Things are ready up here!
Take care of things down there!
Sheesh. They barge right into
uncharted territory like it's nothing...
first round of the Davy Back Fight!
No! I don't wanna!
This's gonna hurt like crazy!
Are you stupid?! We will sink next time!
A Davy Back Fight?
With a view like this,
it's clear there's no danger.
All right! Way to go!
"Unruly"
That's right! The fight begins the
moment two captains are in agreement!
I just hope the girls are
okay... There they are!
Oh! Thanks, everyone!
--Three!
--Two!
--You're the greatest, Porche-chan!
--It's only natural I won!
One!
As we speak, our captain
is challenging your captain,
--Welcome!
Now let's swipe us a crew member!
Monkey D. Luffy, to battle!
What is it, Chopper--?
Damn you, Straw Hats!
You've embarrassed me to no end!
No one's a match for the Foxy Pirates!
Wow!
Challenging? What kind of
sleepy nonsense is that?
What the...?!
Now, now. Don't be so cross.
I will crush you all myself!
If you want a fight, just start one!
Please, make yourselves comfortable...
Hey, you've never heard of a Davy Back Fight?
A human?
Wha...?
Some inari sushi and
kitsune udon! No charge!
Impact!
No human's this fluffy and shaggy!
It's not a fight. It's a pirate game.
For real?! Thanks! Yum!
It's a bear!
All right! Time for you to
hand over a crew member!
Yes. A game that supposedly arose
long ago on "Pirate Island,"
We'd love to have a cook like you join us!
Whoa! So long! A long bear!
Are you guys hurt?! Are you okay?!
which is said to be a pirate
paradise somewhere in the sea.
So high up!
Your twirly eyebrow's so cute!
Yes, we're all right.
What happened?
Oh! Maybe I should be Davy Backed right now!
In it, pirates plunder each other
for top-notch crew members.
They are flying!
Beats us...
Hey! This is an apple! It's so long!
That's what we'd like to know!
Did we end up losing?
Gentleman in the fur coat--
you must be exhausted!
--Don't eat it!
--Yum!
--Pirates plunder each other?!
--Yes.
You were about to win, but then you
This isn't a fur coat!
All the other trees are crazy tall too!
Now, now! I have just the thing for you!
I'm amazed you've survived this
long without even knowing that!
Those guys...
suddenly got slow and they passed you!
How does a candy apple sound?
A Davy Back Fight is about
swiping crew members!
What's that?! Is it sweet?!
What?!
There's no need to be mystified!
After each match, the winner can take
Hey! Some more drinks over here!
It was caused by Slowmo Photons!
any crew member they want
from the opposing team!
Hey, look! Is that a house?!
Hey! What did you do to Nami's team?!
Have all you want!
How do I put this...?
Thanks, guys!
Whoever's chosen must immediately
swear loyalty to their new captain!
Yeah, it looks like it.
Slowmo Photons...?
We're falling! We're falling! We're falling!
And the Pleasure Boat and Harem
Nocturne unleash their secret move:
They're a type of particle
unlike anything currently known.
Robin! You're up!
Let's check it out!
In the name of Davy Jones,
the pirate of the deep!
the Party Distraction!
Cien Fleurs!
Whatever this light touches--
Two Straw Hat boats have been KOed!
So if you lose... you lose a crew member?!
whether it's alive, a liquid, or even a gas--
Yum! Seconds, please!
physically loses a fixed amount of speed
It's your relative!
That's right!
That's a deer! I'm a reindeer!
--Wow, this is sweet! You jerk!
--Whoa, you're really chowin' down!
In addition, if the enemy ship
has no one of interest,
while retaining all other energy.
--We're still falling!
--Luffy! The Flame Dial!
Your beard's so cool!
they can instead be stripped of their
Jolly Roger-- the life of their ship!
I don't get it! Are you stupid or something?!
All right!
Hey, you guys! Get back to the race!
--He snapped at me...
--Oh, no! Boss!
Inflate, you!
But that sounds too ridiculous...
Should you really be concerned
about others right now?
So crewmates and pride are on the line.
...to be real?
You need to focus on yourselves first!
Winning will make you stronger,
while losing will mean a serious loss.
You surely know that such childish
Usopp-sama! You got another order up!
Capote! Give 'em a taste
of your Fishman Karate!
What a vicious game.
claims have no merit in these waters!
D-Don't be stupid! I'm not a tofu seller!
Shake!
Right!
Wait, does that mean
that ship we ran across earlier
Everything they touch slows down!
Sea Surface Splitter!
--Watch this, Chopper!
--Oh!
I'll make you some damn
tres bien tofu sometime! Okay?!
That's the power of Slowmo Photons!
without an organized crew,
sails, or even a captain was...?
Oh, now that makes sense!
You can't be serious!
The boat's come apart!
Wow! You're awesome, Usopp!
After eating the Slow-Slow Fruit,
I became a "slow person"
Oh? Did you run into the
Fang-Frog Pirates' ship?!
Fly!
Please, please, please fly!
Sit!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
capable of producing these
particles from my body!
They fell prey to our game earlier!
I said fly, so fly!
Luffy!
Observe its power!
Beg!
The girls are in trouble! Let's go!
You can do it, Mr. Octopus!
Say hello to our new crewmates!
--Chopper! Let's go!
--Huh?
--Whoa! What now?!
--Water's getting in!
Yikes! He slowed a flying cannonball!
--Nami-san! Robin-chan! I'll save you!
--Forget those floozies!
Yeah! Long live the Foxy Pirates!
So long!
Urgh! All right! Usopp-sama's
going for another one!
Slow-Slow Beam!
--Yeah!
--Come back, Twirly Eyebrow Man!
I was the former captain of that ship!
I-I can't even see its head!
The effect lasts approximately 30 seconds.
Support my shoulders and arms again...
--Former ship doctor!
--Former navigator!
It'll regain its original speed afterward,
as if nothing had happened.
--Well said!
--That's how you do it!
Our balance...!
Former shipwright!
We tried five three-coin
games, but lost 'em all!
Take this!
Special Attack: Flame Star!
This pain is the Going Merry's pain!
Fourteen men and our flag,
taken just like that!
That won't work!
Can't believe your eyes? This is--!
Ocho Fleurs!
--Three!
--Two!
Where'd they run off to?
With so many people jumping ship like this,
--One!
--Fly!
They were rolling around just a minute ago...
Boss!
--Fly!
--What the...?!
--Capote!
it was more like a merger than anything!
We should disembark too.
There could be food here.
Fly!!
Crap! So that's what happened to us?!
Yeah!
Flip!
Idiots. How can you be so happy,
ditching your crew like that?
So this is the reason they're
strangely confident about the game.
Oh, no!
Hey! Robin-chan! We're getting off the ship!
Yes! Now's our chance!
Impact!
What a joke of a power...
Usopp, swim and pull the boat!
Seriously. The ship's in
a watery grave by now.
Right!
Do you get it now?! You lost!
Man, talk about long...
Don't be crazy!
Capote! Monda! Pull yourselves together!
Watery grave...?
--A giant octopus?!
--You gotta be kidding me!
Victory in Round #1's Donut Race...
Paddle! Paddle!
Hmph! So what?!
Why is everything here so loong?
All right! Currently in the lead
is the adorable Cutie Wagon!
goes to us!
There's no talking reason with you!
It worked!
A hot-air balloon, huh?
Hmph, so you refuse to listen to me?
Oh, my! You were so close, too!
But we'd never agree to such a
ridiculous game in a million years!
I feel like just looking at them's
gonna make me looong too...
That concludes Round #1!
In second is the Barrel Tiger, followed by--
Shoot it down when it's within firing range!
Fool! A regular crew member
can't make that decision!
Just what kind of island is this?
Now for the long-awaited spoils of war!
Oh? When did they get back into it?
This game only begins when
two captains reach an agreement!
It's time to call one member
of the opposing crew!
But do not shoot the ship itself!
They must be caught alive!
Hi! We're coming in!
Followed by the Crab Crane!
Well, let's get to it, Hamburg.
Just like that?!
Like it or not, you're all in this game
if your captain nods his head!
H-Hold on, Luffy! I bet this is
where the boss of the island lives!
Really? It's finally time, Boss?
Those are some tall orders...
He's gonna be some horrifyingly long
snake-man monster! I just know it!
Fire a warning shot!
If they don't stop, aim the
second shot for the balloon!
The first person I want is...
No one's here.
Nami-san! Robin-chan! I'm coming to save you!
They're right, Nami-san.
Understood!
Hey! Luffy! Usopp! I found a giraffe!
you!
This is an unwritten rule
in the pirate world.
The ship doctor! Tony Tony Chopper!
What?!
I have a great idea!
Run, and we'll be completely humiliated.
Me?!
I refuse to let you escape, Straw Hat!
Bring him here at once!
Sanji! Get me that!
Oh, no! Chopper!
So what if we're humiliated?!
That ain't a giraffe...
What a rare creature!
You're way softer than I imagined!
Not yet... The first one's just a warning shot!
--This thing's fast!
--Yeah, huh?!
It's got a long neck,
but it's a horse. A long-horse...
I'd rather die than live in shame.
Hang on, Nami-san! Robin-chan!
You're a horse?
Oh, Boss! Let me touch him too!
What he said.
What a pretty horse!
It's all over!
Are you two crazy?!
Nauseatingly cute!
He's ours now!
She's a girl! She says her name is Shelly!
We're gettin' nowhere like this.
Wouldn't it be faster just to paddle?
Forget about it. This is how men are.
This saddle must mean
someone's here after all...
Chopper!
Urgh! I gotta stop Luffy, then!
Y-Yeah... But we used the oars for this.
So that creep was after Chopper?
Don't bother. It's no use.
What's up, Luffy?
The captains will signal
the start of the fight
Well, I guess he is the
rarest of rare animals...
Usopp.
by firing shots at the same time!
--See those two bamboo trees?
--Yeah.
He's into cute things?
Just sit here and--!
Or furs, perhaps?
Whoa! I can't see their tops! Talk about long!
You've done it again, Major Shepherd...
Huh?! What?!
This is no time to chat!
This is serious!
They just took our friend!
Please, no...!
Take a closer look...
Guys...
He agreed to it...
Okay...
Fine by me.
All right, Dr. Chopper.
You're a member of my crew now.
They're running away!
Not even a "hello," huh?
This should be interesting.
Wha...?! This must be another long animal!
Sorry. This is just our style.
He's agreed to the game!
You need to pledge loyalty to me!
Now put on this mask...
That so? In that case...
The bamboo tree's attacking Luffy!
H-Hey! You all right?!
Bull Needles!
I can't let you beat me, bamboo!
Guys...!
Careful, Luffy!
I'm sorry we lost, Chopper...!
Gum-Gum Whip!
You idiot! You idiot! You idiot!
Damn!
Zoro!
Why did you agree to it?!
This is a true rarity!
He's gone...
You have no idea how horrific this game is!
Damn! We're taking you down with us!
A talking reindeer! Amazing!
All right! You beat it!
Then we just won't lose!
Mr. Raccoon Dog and the others are flying!
Chopper! Run!
Yeah! I cut it!
Our challenge is now officially accepted!
Let's be buddies!
Just like I told ya! They fell from the sky!
Where's your owner?
Yeah! I'm gonna kick your butt!
Yo! Comrade!
The Basically Barrels and
Swordfish King #1 and #2 have sunk!
You don't know? That sounds lonely...
Awesome! It really is a hedgehog!
That'll be the day!
Unfortunately, they're out of the race!
What an impressive-looking fortress!
Guys!
I will too, Split-Head!
Chopper!
I only set sail so I could be with you guys!
This is goodbye, old man!
Thanks, Zoro...
--Split-Head...?
--Boss!
Adieu, Jessica-san!
How dare you?! Our boss is a sensitive man!
They're out of the race...?!
No! I-I don't want this!
It could be bad guys! Stay there and hide!
Are we gonna be okay?!
Won't we get shot down at this speed?!
Looks like it's up to us...
He has a heart of glass.
Doesn't suit him, though.
Luffy! I only set sail
because you invited me to!
This fortress is for protecting the peace at sea.
What's going on?!
Oh, yeah! Usopp! Use a dial!
They don't have cannons that aim into the sky.
Actually...
O-Oh, right!
I don't wanna go with these guys...!
Hey! I told you not to laugh!
All right! I'll use this Breath Dial to...!
...I cut a bamboo tree and a spirit appeared!
Dear...
No! I'm the Straw Hat Pirates'
ship doctor, Tony Tony Chopper!
Look, Luffy!
They finally got away.
Thinking about the horse and the
old guy makes me mad too, but...!
Paddling would be faster than this!
Oh, General! Are you all right?
Did we use up all the wind
escaping from Navarone Fortress?!
Use that anger to thrash 'em!
Yes, Commander! The battery has
been ruined, but no one is injured!
He got back up way too fast!
I don't want this!
--Don't you have a Jet Dial?!
--Those are impossible to get!
Leave it to me!
Glad to hear it! Good work!
Quit your griping, Chopper!
What about an Impact Dial?
Our ship's... been blocked from leaving?
Commander! Let's go after them!
Order a search-and-destroy!
I'm going to teach you a thing or two!
You're being a poor sport!
I-I left it on the Merry...
What are they planning?!
Zoro...
They escaped into the sky. Give it up.
You're the one who decided to set sail!
Wh-What?! You don't believe me?!
Why would I lie about that?!
That's the ship I saw earlier...
But--!
No one else is to blame if
you end up dying somewhere!
Frankfurters! Get your frankfurters!
Who are you guys?!
Lt. Commander Drake. You did well!
Thank you for your hard work!
Only you are!
One of our crew members is on the line here!
Rum and cheese! Crackers and salted meat!
If it's a fight you want, get down here!
We agreed to this game.
I didn't say anything.
Commander...
I've got yakisoba noodles too!
We are the Foxy Pirates!
Yeah! That's the issue!
Usopp, you, and everyone else did their best!
It's time for the opening ceremony!
Oh! Major Shepherd!
Don't be hasty! All we want... is a showdown!
If we end up losing,
they'll definitely take me first!
No one in the pirate world would
sympathize with your tears!
--Please quiet down! Please quiet down!
--Shut up! You be quiet!
Commander!
Are you going to blame this on me?!
This was all your fault!
--C'mon! Let's hear the odds!
--All participants, get ready!
I can't let that happen! I'm too cute!
A real man...
A spirit?
I'm going to contact headquarters
Yeah. He appeared after I cut the bamboo tree.
...would roll up his sleeves and
watch the rest of the contest quietly!
and make sure your heads
roll and roll and roll and roll!
This is looking fun!
You wish. Now just paddle.
Hey. Say something, you.
These are all Split-Head's crew members?
How can you say that?!
Don't you know how he feels?!
Wow! There's so many!
Even if you are Admiral Akainu's lapdogs,
What?! This is no time for reading, Robin!
Of course I remember you.
Hi. Five jumbo yakisobas, please.
"Cotton Candy" "Yakisoba Noodles"
my report will bring this
outdated hedgehog down!
It's been a long time. How are you guys?
I'm paddling too.
Stop that, old guy!
Your hands are, but you
don't seem like you're--
All right! Do anything you like with me!
Okay, men! Simmer down!
One of you knows him?
I'm going to make it so none
of your men remain in the navy!
Yeah, Robin...
--Nope.
--Me neither...
You'll end up like me if
you don't work hard...
Chopper...
--Porche-chan!
--Sexy!
Ah, no wonder I didn't recognize you.
All right!
--Whoa!
--That swordsman is awesome!
It's time for the pledge to follow
these three rules about losing!
I am working hard.
I don't kiss!
You dumbass!
You're surprisingly savvy about the world...
Whoa, what a flake! Who are you, old guy?!
All right! Teach 'em a lesson, Zoro!
"Justice"
First, the only way to take back crewmates,
Jolly Rogers, or anything else
Get Chopper back!
Shall we head straight for the goal,
or shall we sink them instead?
--Let's take him next, Boss!
--This reindeer's got guts!
My name is Tonjit. You have my thanks.
Are you sure about this?
You let the Straw Hats escape...
is through another Davy Back Fight!
Let's get the second round started.
I enjoy the occasional leisurely
trip across the goal line,
I assume you're the ones
who knocked me off my stilts?
So moving! I'm moved to tears!
Yes. I didn't invite them here,
plus we achieved our primary goal.
Second, anyone taken by the winner
but I wanna make that chick pay!
Yeah. There's still two rounds left.
Stilts?
Winning isn't enough for me now!
must swear loyalty to that
ship's captain immediately!
We're gonna take back our precious
emergency food... and then some.
Oh! They are!
All right! The race has entered its climax!
Third, if your Jolly Roger is taken,
you can't ever display it again!
Eh?
But they were so long,
we couldn't see the top at all!
Sanji! We're counting on you!
The Cutie Wagon remains in the lead,
The exchange is finished
Nami-san! I bought some cotton candy!
as the Davy Back Fight suddenly
explodes with excitement!
followed by the Barrel Tiger
and the Crab Crane in third!
Indeed. I was at the very top!
Don't you get the feeling that
everyone here has started to unify?
How can you guys be so calm about this?
Huh? Wait, Chopper's in the second round.
Oh, so you're not a spirit that came
out because I cut a bamboo tree,
Huh? Where'd the Crab Crane go?
--But they took him.
--You're right.
Are you still moping about that?
Oh! There it is!
you're an old guy who fell
'cause his stilts broke?
That's the real thrill of this game!
Damn!
Should you break these rules,
you'll be considered dishonorable pirates
Th-Those guys' kicks were insane!
We told you!
I have noticed it, actually.
You can't change your roster!
No replacements allowed!
Why were you on such long stilts anyway?
and sent to Davy Jones' Locker!
Unbelievable! The Crab Crane is out
of the race! When did that happen?
That's good enough. They gave
a good jolt to this fortress.
I've always been fond of stilts,
In other words, only the other
two Straw Hat contestants
Do you swear to uphold them?
so I tried to make the world's longest
stilts using this island's bamboo!
--I swear!
can participate in Round #2's Groggy Ring!
What's that?!
Team Foxy already has the advantage!
I'm aware that headquarters
thinks we're unnecessary.
What?!
That we're "too big,"
that we're "peace addicts"...
What a lovely rendezvous!
I managed to get on them, but then
I was too scared to come back down!
You can drop out too, if you want.
See ya!
Okay, Straw Hat! I'll let you choose!
But that's fine with me!
No, but you can, loser.
H-How are they going so fast?!
What's most important is that
we soldiers and you support staff
You're crazy, old guy!
One coin? Two coins? Or three coins?
I find it hard to believe
they'll work as a team...
Out of strength...
I was up there... for ten years!
Choose whichever you want!
You're really crazy!
They stopped!
--Say what?!
--Stop that!
work hard to protect
the peace, don't you think?
Oh, Boss! You're so gracious!
You were on stilts for ten whole years?!
Gum-Gum... Screw...
I'll now explain the rules of Groggy Ring!
That's right. The bamboo continued
to grow the entire time, too,
I'm out... of...
What are they for?
It's the number of games.
There's a field, and two goals!
There are still pirates out
there like the Straw Hats.
It appears he was in the water too long.
Our boss is letting you choose
if it should be a one-match game
Knock the balls into them and you win!
making it even harder
for me to come back down...
Hey! We better get paddling
or this'll all go to waste!
However, the balls are no ordinary balls!
Headquarters will probably be
reminded of the need for this fortress.
I don't know what you did, but we won't lose!
or all the way up to a three-match game.
So scary...
They're people!
Both teams, select someone to be a ball!
Oh, no! We just passed them, too!
That's your only comment after ten years?!
I won't let you all get
thrown out into the street.
The game'll be more fun with more stuff.
There are many trees on this island
just as tall as the stilts, though.
--So I'll go with...
--Luffy!
Which of you's gonna be the ball?!
You'll never get close to us again--!
Have you fallen for me again?
What?!
I was able to survive on fruit I could find.
--How is this?
--Wonderful, Robin!
Here's your ball mark!
You dummy...
Who made you boss?!
You be the ball, Moss Head!
He talks about it so casually.
Especially being up there for so long...
Cheater!
But do you think he'll give a
good report to headquarters?
Got it!
Oh, there it is! Their entrance song!
Let go!
Three coins!
Speaking of long...
I got carried away and slugged him...
They already caught on. Too bad.
Why is everything on this
island so long, old guy?
It doesn't matter! Besides,
I was going to hit him, too!
It's the undefeated elites of Groggy Ring!
Capote!
You idiot! Why'd you add them?!
And include an enemy in the count?!
It might seem that way to an outsider,
but there is a reason.
Yes! Defeat is impossible for them!
How dare they?!
So many morons!
Luffy! Can you try it...
As you can see, a giant,
grassy plain covers this island.
...again?
Well, then, Straw Hat. How far will you go?
I hereby announce this three-coin,
orthodox-rules game...
I don't think he'll be much help for a while.
Crush 'em!
In short, everything here is long
due to a longing for excitement.
There are people at headquarters
who express interest in you.
The famous Groggy Monsters
have just taken the field!
Let's just keep moving!
We can't let 'em get a bigger lead!
Whoa. He went and said it.
...to Davy Jones!
Your road ahead won't be an easy one.
Over there, for example...
Yeah! Let's go!
Flying feels so nice!
I guess I'll sink them after all.
At the lead is "Full Dash" Hamburg!
--...is a plaaatypus.
--You just said it longer!
How far are we gonna fly?
He's followed by "Tackle Machine" Pickles!
Oh!
How should I know? Ask the octopus.
Who's Davy Jones?
That's a Daaachshund.
Ahh!
It's nice to enjoy a leisurely trip
through the sky sometimes.
An old pirate cursed by the devil
Up ahead are the biggest obstacles
of the course: the Long Coral Reef
Last but not least is Big Pan the wotan:
a half-fishman half-giant!
Oh? Are you that same dog?
who's said to live in the depths
of the sea to this very day.
But no more navy bases!
You're still passing by?!
He lives at the bottom of the sea?!
and the Long Ring Whirlpool
of Long Cape beyond it!
As long as I'm with Nami-san and Robin-chan,
Be careful-- there are ferocious animals too.
This is literally a monstrous march!
That's what the legend says.
everywhere is heaven!
See? That's a snow leooopard.
Don't let it bite you!
All the ships and treasures
that sink into the sea
--Moron.
--Huh?!
How will they overcome these?! And...
Now, then!
--I said, "Moron."
--Huh?!
are said to go to his ship's bosun--
his "locker," in other words.
Well, then! Guess I'll get to fixing the hull!
Leopard?!
Oh! Is that...?!
Why is it only long sideways?!
What?
The bottom of the sea is scary...
There's someone on the island!
But I sure am hungry!
What is that?!
Sweet!
Sanji! Food!
Pirates call this a "Davy Back"
What is that giant fishman?!
It's "Full Dash" Hamburg!
I'm hungry!
Atop him, making an appearance at last,
is the Master of Obstruction!
because you steal whatever
you want from the enemy,
They're putting the ball mark on him!
The great scoundrel who
hates fairness: our boss!
Let's see you win this!
just as Davy takes everything
that comes sinking his way.
"Silver Fox" Foxy!
Are you ready, Straw
Hat?! Let the game begin!
There he is...
Hurry up and get moving towards the future!
Seem like a good match?
Him!
I just got an evil idea!
That's the captain.
All right! Let's do this!
Yep.
Let's move ahead, pursuing our dreams
All the answers are right here, pouring out
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Rush forth, rush forth,
on the road opened before us
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Let's keep moving forward! We can do it!
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
We won't give in, we won't give in,
even if the obstacle is big
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
We pray to this endless
sky that we look up at
It's nothing to be scared of,
we can overcome it
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
That fortress was so fun!
But where are we gonna land
this time? I feel so uneasy...
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
An island's been visible for a while.
Why couldn't you say so sooner?!
--Man, how dull!
--Are you referring to me?
No, I'm sorry.
It's the island that's dull.
What's with this island? What is this?!
--What are you doing?!
--Huh? Look who's talking!
So many idiots! I'll be too embarrassed
to live if we lose to these guys!
All right! The Davy Back Fight has begun!
On the next episode of One Piece!
My name is Foxy! I take whatever I want!
"Great Adventure at Long Ring Long Land!"
I'll chop you up if they score a goal!
I've never lost using
orthodox rules, you know!
They'll take our crew, too!
That's even worse!
Not another weirdo!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
Shut up! Don't try anything funny!
I challenge you, Straw Hat!
You get thrown around too easy!
We're gonna lose if we don't do
something! Time for my trump card!
A chef, a doctor, an archaeologist...
Who should I take?!
I don't need you to give me backup!
--Stop talking crazy, Split-Head!
--"Split-Head"?!
Oh, man! Who's winning?!
No, I want that one!
Let's get this first round started!
It's only 'cause I can't count on you!
Bring it on! I'll fight you all you want!
I've actually eaten a--!
They're funny! They're fighting
even during the match!
--I don't understand you, Split-Head!
--He said it again...
--On the next episode of One Piece!
--Let me finish!
No, Luffy! Don't agree to his game!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"'Silver Fox' Foxy! The
Merciless Interference"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Round 1! One Lap of the Donut Race"
"A Davy Back with the Foxy Pirates!"
"Round 2! Shoot It into the Groggy Ring"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!