It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set
sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"Round 1! One Lap of the Donut Race"
Sheesh!
You've gotten us into a real mess, Luffy!
All we gotta do is win!
Hey! You forgot somethin'!
Write down your rosters and
give them to our party organizer!
Members can participate only twice.
Once you've chosen
your roster, it's set in stone!
The events of the contest are...
A race, a ball game, and a team competition.
What's this? The race is open to all members,
the ball game is open to three,
and the team competition is open to five...
All right! I'm gonna do all three!
The rules say that isn't allowed.
Hey, what if we lose?
I bet they'll want Captain Usopp...
No, I bet it'll be me. Because I'm cute...
I'll now announce the rosters
submitted by both teams!
First is the Straw Hat team!
Participating in Round #1's Donut Race is...
the entire Straw Hat crew!
Actually, my "Can't Be in a Race"
disease is kicking in...
I don't wanna do it either,
you know! Just accept it!
Participating in Round #2's Groggy Ring is...
...Roronoa Zoro, Sanji,
and Tony Tony Chopper!
--Don't go slowin' me down!
--That's my line!
I'm... gonna try my very... hardest!
Participating in Round #3's
Run Around Roller is...
...Monkey D. Luffy,
Nico Robin, Nami, and Usopp!
Only four people? We're one short.
That doesn't matter! Let's do it!
A captain, a swordsman,
a navigator, a sniper,
a cook, a doctor, and an archaeologist, huh?
Well, then. Who shall I take first?
I guess it'd have to be that one!
I really want that member!
All right! It's finally time
for the merciless Davy Back!
The winner gets a feast,
while the loser gets fleeced!
I, Itomimizu, the Foxy
Pirates' party organizer,
will be your commentator
for this competition!
First up is Round #1, the Donut Race!
How shall we team up?
Considering that some of us
have Devil Fruit powers,
maybe we should split into two
teams of three and four people...
Boats for the Donut Race can only be made
from two oars and three empty barrels!
Use of any other materials
means instant disqualification!
This is a chance for
shipwrights to show their stuff!
Those without empty barrels, come get some!
We'll give 'em to you for free!
We're generous like that!
I'm not sure we can use three barrels
to build a boat for four of us.
Okay, three teams it is.
They'll consist of...
Hey, you! Don't go busting 'em up like that!
Just watch! I'm gonna make an awesome boat!
All right! While everyone's
busy with their boats,
I'll explain how the race works!
The course will be one lap
around Long Ring Long Land!
It might sound easy, but it's anything but!
A team is immediately out of
the race should their boat sink!
In addition, all weapons are allowed,
even guns, cannons, explosives,
cutlasses or anything else!
Whoever complains about unfairness
will be shamed as a pirate!
Managed to finish it...
Time is nearly up! Is everyone ready?
Oh! The final odds are in!
I'll list them in order of popularity,
starting with the most popular!
The top spot obviously goes to our idol,
the member of the powerful
Team Foxy: Porche-chan!
Ooh! Just leave it to me!
With her is the swordfish fishman
Capote and the star shark Monda!
They're riding in the Cutie Wagon!
This'll be a cinch! You can do it!
Hold on! You're using a fish!
There's no rule against fish, you know!
Second most popular is...
Oh! This is unexpected!
The Straw Hat team of Navigator Nami,
Sniper Usopp, and Archeologist Robin!
They'll be riding the Barrel Tiger!
That orange-haired chick is hot!
I want that dark-haired girl on our crew!
--Don't need that other guy!
--Yeah. Never mind him.
I see! Looks like the rowdy Foxy Pirates
have a soft spot for cutey-pies!
What lechers!
--Are you sure this won't sink?!
--I already told you...
I'm not a shipwright!
But it still beats those.
This ain't a boat! It's just some scrap wood!
That's okay!
--So you do that the whole time?
--Yep! I just keep running really hard!
It's a miracle they even float...
Looks like it's up to us if we
don't wanna lose this race...
Third most popular is the Harem Nocturne,
a boat of the beautiful,
by the beautiful, for the beautiful!
In fourth place is the Crab Crane,
a regular in the top ranks!
In fifth and sixth place are
the Swordfish King #1 and #2!
Seventh most popular is the
party-loving Pleasure Boat!
In eighth place is the Duke Special!
Wait! What about our boat?!
Yeah! Mine too!
Let's see here...
Doctor Chopper and Swordsman
Zoro's Basically Barrels is...
...third from last!
Not too surprising.
And the It's a Raft...
...wins the booby prize!
What's that mean?
Means we're second to last.
You mean there's an even worse boat?!
Incidentally, the very last place
goes to the giant boat...
...the Mothership Coaster!
I don't think oars are long
enough for that thing...
How does it even move?
You guys are sharp!
Yup, oars are too short for this boat!
It's filled with seawater, too!
Those guys are dumb!
How many barrels did they use, anyway?
This thing is just three giant barrels,
all stuck together!
It ain't breaking any rules!
Okay! All the boats are at the starting line!
I'll be providing commentary during the race
from atop Chirp-Chirp, a rare
South Blue Super Sparrow!
Porche-chan!
I hope you sink, nose dude!
Me?!
We have to win now!
Sinking opponents is fair game.
Oh, my. Listen to that crazy talk.
Let 'em talk, Porche-chan.
We'll sink 'em in three minutes!
Right, Monda?!
I'm getting excited!
Do we even have a chance?
Listen up, Usopp! Anything happens
to the ladies and I'll filet you!
We will win!
Fool! No one's ever beat us
in an orthodox-rules game!
Think this race will last
five minutes, Hamburg?
Nope.
Now take these Eternal Poses
so that you don't get lost!
Lost?
Try not to leave the island and go too far!
Leave the island? Why would we do that?
We're taking the shortest route,
along the inside track!
--I don't think it'll be that simple...
--Why not?
Just look!
Besides that gigantic one in the back,
all their other boats are on the
outside track, facing outward!
Suspicious, don't you think?!
Okay! On your marks!
Ready!
Why won't it be so simple?!
Just trust me! Men! Leave the
shore as soon as we start!
What'd he say?
--Why?!
--Grin...
Donut!
--I've got a bad feeling about this!
--Tell us why!
--Push it! Push it! Push it!
We're gonna teach ya what
this boat exists for!
What are these?
Oh, no! We're too late!
These are traps?
N-Nami! Don't...!
And there they are! The Mothership
Coaster's infamous Barrel Mines!
See you later!
Don't sink right away, though!
Give us some fun!
--Go away!
--Stupid things! I'm gonna send you flying!
Gum-Gum...!
--Stop, Luffy.
--Yeah! They'll explode like crazy!
But we have to do something...
We just gotta get rid of 'em
without touching 'em.
Hand me that oar, Luffy!
Wh-What are you doing, Zoro?!
Just watch...
Th-They're coming back!
Nami-san! Robin-chan! Hold on
to your boat! Ride the wave!
Huh?!
We can't ride that!
Yahoo! This is neat!
Crap! We're breaking apart...
I'm scared!
That's cold water...
Wh-What the...?!
Oh! The Straw Hat teams are
speeding to the front of the pack!
Incredible!
Are you kidding me?!
No way! They're going to catch up to us!
Let's go, Monda! Give it
everything you've got!
Give us backup, you guys!
Right!
Finally calmed down...
Oh, man. The shock busted
the raft a little...
Whew, that was fun! I hope
there's another wave! Don't you?
Are you stupid?! We will sink next time!
I just hope the girls are
okay... There they are!
--Welcome!
Wow!
What the...?!
Now, now. Don't be so cross.
Please, make yourselves comfortable...
Some inari sushi and
kitsune udon! No charge!
For real?! Thanks! Yum!
We'd love to have a cook like you join us!
Your twirly eyebrow's so cute!
Oh! Maybe I should be Davy Backed right now!
Gentleman in the fur coat--
you must be exhausted!
This isn't a fur coat!
Now, now! I have just the thing for you!
How does a candy apple sound?
What's that?! Is it sweet?!
Hey! Some more drinks over here!
Have all you want!
Thanks, guys!
And the Pleasure Boat and Harem
Nocturne unleash their secret move:
the Party Distraction!
Two Straw Hat boats have been KOed!
Yum! Seconds, please!
--Wow, this is sweet! You jerk!
--Whoa, you're really chowin' down!
Your beard's so cool!
Hey, you guys! Get back to the race!
Should you really be concerned
about others right now?
You need to focus on yourselves first!
Capote! Give 'em a taste
of your Fishman Karate!
Right!
Sea Surface Splitter!
The boat's come apart!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
Luffy!
The girls are in trouble! Let's go!
--Chopper! Let's go!
--Huh?
--Nami-san! Robin-chan! I'll save you!
--Forget those floozies!
--Yeah!
--Come back, Twirly Eyebrow Man!
Our balance...!
Take this!
Special Attack: Flame Star!
That won't work!
Ocho Fleurs!
--What the...?!
--Capote!
Flip!
Oh, no!
Yes! Now's our chance!
Usopp, swim and pull the boat!
Don't be crazy!
Capote! Monda! Pull yourselves together!
Paddle! Paddle!
All right! Currently in the lead
is the adorable Cutie Wagon!
In second is the Barrel Tiger, followed by--
Oh? When did they get back into it?
Followed by the Crab Crane!
Well, let's get to it, Hamburg.
Really? It's finally time, Boss?
Nami-san! Robin-chan! I'm coming to save you!
I have a great idea!
Sanji! Get me that!
--This thing's fast!
--Yeah, huh?!
Hang on, Nami-san! Robin-chan!
We're gettin' nowhere like this.
Wouldn't it be faster just to paddle?
Y-Yeah... But we used the oars for this.
Huh?! What?!
Not even a "hello," huh?
Sorry. This is just our style.
That so? In that case...
Bull Needles!
Zoro!
Damn! We're taking you down with us!
Chopper! Run!
The Basically Barrels and
Swordfish King #1 and #2 have sunk!
Unfortunately, they're out of the race!
Chopper!
Thanks, Zoro...
They're out of the race...?!
Looks like it's up to us...
Oh, yeah! Usopp! Use a dial!
O-Oh, right!
All right! I'll use this Breath Dial to...!
Paddling would be faster than this!
Did we use up all the wind
escaping from Navarone Fortress?!
--Don't you have a Jet Dial?!
--Those are impossible to get!
What about an Impact Dial?
I-I left it on the Merry...
Wh-What?! You don't believe me?!
Why would I lie about that?!
One of our crew members is on the line here!
I didn't say anything.
Yeah! That's the issue!
If we end up losing,
they'll definitely take me first!
I can't let that happen! I'm too cute!
You wish. Now just paddle.
What?! This is no time for reading, Robin!
I'm paddling too.
Your hands are, but you
don't seem like you're--
Yeah, Robin...
You'll end up like me if
you don't work hard...
I am working hard.
You're surprisingly savvy about the world...
Shall we head straight for the goal,
or shall we sink them instead?
I enjoy the occasional leisurely
trip across the goal line,
but I wanna make that chick pay!
Winning isn't enough for me now!
All right! The race has entered its climax!
The Cutie Wagon remains in the lead,
followed by the Barrel Tiger
and the Crab Crane in third!
Huh? Where'd the Crab Crane go?
Oh! There it is!
Damn!
Th-Those guys' kicks were insane!
Unbelievable! The Crab Crane is out
of the race! When did that happen?
What's that?!
What a lovely rendezvous!
See ya!
H-How are they going so fast?!
Out of strength...
They stopped!
Gum-Gum... Screw...
I'm out... of...
It appears he was in the water too long.
Hey! We better get paddling
or this'll all go to waste!
I don't know what you did, but we won't lose!
Oh, no! We just passed them, too!
You'll never get close to us again--!
What?!
--How is this?
--Wonderful, Robin!
Cheater!
Let go!
They already caught on. Too bad.
Capote!
How dare they?!
Luffy! Can you try it...
...again?
I don't think he'll be much help for a while.
Let's just keep moving!
We can't let 'em get a bigger lead!
Yeah! Let's go!
I guess I'll sink them after all.
Oh!
Ahh!
Up ahead are the biggest obstacles
of the course: the Long Coral Reef
and the Long Ring Whirlpool
of Long Cape beyond it!
How will they overcome these?! And...
Oh! Is that...?!
What?
There's someone on the island!
It's "Full Dash" Hamburg!
Atop him, making an appearance at last,
is the Master of Obstruction!
The great scoundrel who
hates fairness: our boss!
"Silver Fox" Foxy!
Him!
I just got an evil idea!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless
sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
So many idiots! I'll be too embarrassed
to live if we lose to these guys!
They'll take our crew, too!
That's even worse!
We're gonna lose if we don't do
something! Time for my trump card!
Oh, man! Who's winning?!
I've actually eaten a--!
--On the next episode of One Piece!
--Let me finish!
"'Silver Fox' Foxy! The
Merciless Interference"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!