Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Gum-Gum...
What's with this restaurant?
It's as if... as if...
this were a pirate ship!
Only to defeat this man...
Here, Ghin. Let him eat it.
We've got trouble!
Pirate Krieg's underling...
What do you mean by that?
Sanji-san...
Three Swords Style Technique!
Thank you!
Please reduce it to a week.
Better not regret it when I kill you!
Don't mess with me!
This is a restaurant, right?
"Hawk-Eye Mihawk! The Great
Swordsman Zoro Falls on the Sea"
Three Thousand Worlds!
Sir, do you have money for that?
You could've eaten it if you
took that bug out, couldn't you?
--Would a bullet do?
--So you don't have money, right?
It took three full days to
cook it, skimming the scum...
This is a good restaurant.
Zoro!!
I'm a customer! I'm paying you!
--Ugh...
--What'd you just say?!
Nami ran off with the Going Merry?!
Eat it.
I'll take this ship.
Can money... satisfy your hunger?
What do you mean by that?!
So... that's what you want...
"The Deadly Foot Technique Bursts Forth!
Sanji vs. the Invincible Pearl"
I found a good cook!
It happened just a moment ago!
What'd you say?!
This is a good opportunity.
Meat Ball of Doom!!
I'm asking, "Can it...
satisfy your hunger?!"
Damn geezer!
Leave this place with them!
You're no longer needed
at this restaurant!
What's the matter, Big Sis Nami?
Huh?
"Unwelcome Customer!
Sanji's Food and Ghin's Debt"
You were looking at wanted posters.
Oh... Nothing...
"The Strongest Pirate Fleet!
Commodore Don Krieg"
You're damn annoying!!
You're impressive as usual.
So you've set your eyes
on a big bounty pirate.
All right!
I can't... hold it anymore...
Serving customers! That is "love"!
And "love" means "restaurant"!
They want to fight, too!
Hey, you damn geezer!
I'm the Sous Chef here.
But Arlong is the one pirate
that you shouldn't go after.
Don't defy me!
Umph!
I'm getting fired up!
The customer is king!!
What do you mean you
no longer need me?!
I hear he's super terrifyingly strong...
When I tell you to prepare food,
Pops! You promised, okay?
He kept himself quiet
and out of sight for a while.
You often get into
trouble with customers.
Motto! Motto! Service motto!
Service is about pleasant greetings!
Once I drive them away,
I'll quit doing chores. Okay?
all you have to do is
obediently follow orders!
You flare your nostrils
the second you see a girl.
Don't defy me!
But he started going
wild again recently.
Couldn't ask for more.
You can't even cook a decent meal,
If you do chores for a year,
this place will get messed up.
Welcome, ya damn crook.
Well, it's hard to give up on that
20-million berry bounty, though...
so you're dead weight
to this restaurant.
Please never come back.
There's probably enough
for 100 meals in this.
That's what I said.
This guy's so strong that
there's a shred of possibility
I'm terribly sorry.
All right!
Bring it to your ship right away.
Say that again...
Ten thousand berries coming in!
You said you were going to be
King of the Pirates. Are you serious?
--Owner Zeff!
that even we may be killed by a hair...
You look pathetic!
Also, the other cooks
steer clear of you...
Z... Zeff?
Huh?
Yeah, of course! I'll definitely
be King of the Pirates!
All right! I took a healthy dump, and
I'm in excellent shape again today!
Big Sis Nami?
So go be a pirate or whatever,
Uhm, I'm sorry, but could you
turn around? I want to change...
I've come across tons of roughnecks.
and just leave this restaurant already!
Oh? Welcome, ya damn crook.
"Protect Baratie!
The Great Pirate, Red Foot Zeff!"
But you're the first one in a long
time who said that so clearly.
What?! W-Well...
Motto! Motto! Service motto!
The customer is...
Say what?
Change? Here? Now?!
I heard that you were
an incredibly strong pirate.
May I?
If I keep quiet, you just shoot your
mouth off, huh? You damn geezer!
Ahh! Our customer!
Please go ahead!
You again, Sanji! What're you
doing to our customer?!
Were you going to be
King of the Pirates?
The rest I could overlook,
I forgot about the past.
but I'm not just gonna
let you trash my cooking!
Of all people, he's a Navy Lieutenant!
True to her looks, she's so bold!
I'm the owner of a restaurant
now and that's enough for me.
No matter what you say,
I'll stay here as a cook!
It wouldn't hurt if we take
a quick peek, would it?
What're you doing?!
What're you thinking?!
What is it, you damn cook?!
And that's final!
Oh, yeah...
Don't call my name as
if I were your friend!
If we revive even those on the ship,
Just what's the meaning of you
grabbing the owner by the collar?
Guys! As long as we take that ship,
our restaurant will be
completely taken over!
A damn cook has no right
to call me "damn cook"!
You idiot!
the Grand Line is
nothing to be scared of!
If they have the will to fight, that is...
Restaurants can't exist
without customers!
Damn you...
We can get closer and make a surprise
attack on enemy ships more effectively
Hurting our precious customer...
What do you think you're doing?!
Right, defeated warrior
of the Grand Line?
Wh-What're you doing?!
What's the big deal with customers?
Quit screwing around...
than pretending to be a Navy ship
or raising the white flag of surrender.
He treated the food carelessly.
On top of that, he insulted cooks.
No matter how hard
you try to kick me out,
What am I doing? Of course, business!
I'm a thief that only targets
pirates. I'll take this ship.
C... Can't be...
I'll continue to work here as a cook...
We can make a definite sneak attack.
Don Krieg is a defeated warrior...
...until you die!
It's true that no one would think...
I never said that I became a member.
I just joined forces with them. That's all.
Then even the ruler of
the East Blue couldn't...
I won't die! I'll live 100 more years!
So I taught him a lesson.
that pirates are on board
such a silly-looking ship.
Even the pirate fleet with
50 ships couldn't sail across...
I only spent a short time with Luffy
and the others, but I had lots of fun.
That geezer is never short of words...
B-But, Don... Even if we enter
the Grand Line again using that ship,
What's with this restaurant...
All right, you have permission!
Now you can become a pirate.
Grand Line?
No restaurant should treat
its customers like this...
No way!
--Tell them...
--What?!
if we come across someone
like Hawk-Eye Mihawk again...
Y... You must be Red Foot Zeff!
Now... Sorry about that.
...that if we're linked
by fate, we'll meet again.
I'll shut it down... I'll shut down
this restaurant! I'll shut it down!!
I'd like to make up for it by serving
you fruit macedonia, my princess.
Big Sis Nami!
So you are alive...
Wow, thank you! You're so kind.
Are you still afraid of
someone like that? Huh?!
I'll contact the government
immediately and...
An incomparable pirate who was
a cook and yet also a captain...
--Any time...
--And no apology to us?!
Then I'd better finish you off here...
N-No...
I'm gonna sue you,
you stupid love cook!
You think an ordinary human
can slice up a large sailing ship?!
So what if I'm alive?
H-Hey! We'll be in trouble!
I'm serving you tea, aren't I?
Thank me for that, long-nose.
It has nothing to do with you.
Stop it, Sous Chef!
We were more or less
asked to watch the ship!
--A stuck up asshole like you
--What're you doing?!
If you keep going at him,
--A stuck up asshole like you
That's probably the
power of a devil fruit.
As you can see, I live as a cook now.
Huh? You wanna fight?
I won't go easy on you.
--What're you doing?!
If you keep going at him,
--who's too big for his britches
--we'll be in a big trouble!
Stop it, Sanji!! Stop it!
--who's too big for his britches
--we'll be in a big trouble!
Stop it, Sanji!! Stop it!
--just pisses me off!!
Although those with devil fruit powers
are considered by society to be legends,
--You're going too far, Sanji!
--just pisses me off!!
Beat him up, Zoro!
Do it yourself.
the Grand Line is crawling with them.
Stop! Please don't fight because of me.
If you put it that way, it sounds nice...
So you think you're a big shot?! Huh?!
--Yes, I'll stop.
--Who said it was because of you?!
...though rather than living as a cook,
Mihawk must've used some strange
power when he sliced up the ship.
--By the way, you know...
--Yes?
it looks like you can live only as a cook.
The food you have here is delicious...
Even that straw hat brat is a mere
pirate once he enters the Grand Line.
...but it seems a little
expensive for me...
--What happened?
--Oh, boy...
Red Foot Zeff was a master of kicks
who never used his hands in battle.
Of course, it'll be free.
--What now?
--What happened?
Thank you!
So that's how she took the ship...
Boy... that startled me...
--Yours are not free.
--Wha...
I hear that his strong
legs crushed bedrock
We're sorry!
O-Owner! What the heck are you doing?!
You're too predictable.
Dammit! She's making
this crisis worse for us!
Oh, dammit!! The ceiling
of my restaurant...
and even left footprints on steel.
What are you sitting around for?!
Kaya gave that ship to us!
But Red Foot Zeff
traveled there for a year.
It's your fault, you brat!!
Wait! I can still see it!
It's the Going Merry!
When customers sit down,
bring them moist hand-towels!
And Red Foot referred to your shoes,
which were covered in the blood
Yes, sir.
You broke it yourself!
that spattered as you
kicked your enemies down...
Where's your ship?
What're you doing, Owner?!
We still have it here...
You can do that later!
Please stop, Sanji!!
I can't but think that he had ways
of confronting those monsters.
Zoro! Usopp! Leave right away!
Take that ship and follow Nami!
But you no longer have
that precious leg of yours...
Hey, Sanji!
Forget about it.
Just give that ship to her.
Well... with this and that going on,
And those methods must
be written in his logbook.
Are you going on a rampage in
the restaurant again, you idiot?!
No need of going after that woman.
I've heard the rumor...
four days have passed...
Shut up, you damn geezer!
I won't accept anyone
but her as our navigator!
How unlucky for you to
have an accident at sea...
What'd you say?! Who do
you think you're talking to?!
If we're lucky, so is
information on the One Piece.
When can we leave here?
Are you trying to put my
restaurant out of business?!
To you, losing one of your legs
must mean you are unable to fight.
Who knows?
I see... That's our Don Krieg!
Is he really going to work here
as a chore boy for a year?
So long as we have
that ship and the logbook,
You brat!!
we'll find a way to the One Piece again!
What's the problem? The food
is free and it's comfortable here.
You, too! Get out of here already!
What about fighting?
All right, all right...
What a high-maintenance captain...
Got that, guys?! Let's go!
We'll take over the restaurant!
For you it is.
I can cook without a leg
as long as I have these hands.
Hey Usopp, let's go!
--Yeah!
Uh? Okay...
Hey, Luffy!
What're you trying to say?
Just come right out and say it!
Hmm?
This ship belongs to us... to the cooks!
What's with this restaurant?
Even the owner is like a gangster...
What's going on?!
Let's leave here soon!
We can't let them have it...
no matter what happens!
--Big Bro Zoro, the ship is ready!
Wait a little longer.
I'll try talking to Owner again.
Red Foot Zeff.
It's as if... as if...
this were a pirate ship!
Luffy, what about you?
N-Now... what do we do
to operate this again?
You're the man who once entered
the Grand Line and came back unhurt...
I can't go since I haven't settled
anything at this restaurant.
Hurry up!
I'm begging you!
You listen! The customer is king!
Be careful.
The situation here isn't normal.
Just those who eat your
damn crappy dishes.
There should be a
logbook with the full year of
Yeah, I know.
As it stands, the restaurant
will be a battlefield...
your journey chronicled in it...
Patty, Sanji! If you wanna
fight, do it in the kitchen!
Wh-What? What the hell just happened?
Give that to me!
The ship's been split into two!
Are these idiots really cooks?
Whoa! You've been to
the Grand Line, too, pops?
Look at that!
L-Lieutenant! Lieutenant Fullbody!
Yeah...
It's him!
My logbook, huh?
Indeed, I have it with me.
W-We've got trouble!
I wish there was a restaurant
in the middle of the sea...
Geez... what a wild restaurant...
Don Krieg! It's him!
But I can't give it to you.
Hey, what's the matter?
Pirate Krieg's underling escaped!
It's the man who destroyed our fleet!
I was thinking that if I
could leave this place alive,
The logbook is the pride of all
the crewmen that I traveled with.
What?!
After seven of us finally captured him
to get a lead on the Krieg Pirates...
I'd build a restaurant as
my final purpose in life...
Th... That man!
It's too important to give it to you.
A restaurant as my
final purpose in life...
Can't be! When we captured him three
days ago, he was close to starving!
Then, I'll just take it from you by force.
Go to the operating room
and open up the fins.
And we haven't fed him at all since!
It's true that I fell from the Grand Line.
What? Open up the fins?
K-Krieg Pirates...
So that man is...
Even if that's the case, I'm still
Don Krieg, the strongest man.
That's gonna give
a foothold to the enemy!
They're the ones who're said to be
the strongest pirates in the East Blue...
That son of a bitch!
An hourglass...
on each side of the skull...
That's fine. We can't make the inside
of this restaurant a battlefield.
It's merely a dark sea route.
To sail across it, I had enough power...
...to show the threat to enemies...
He followed us here... to kill us!!
I'm very...
That flag is... that flag is...
...and forces... as well as ambition!
If it becomes a battlefield,
that damn geezer will complain.
We're done for!
There's no mistake... it belongs
to the ruler of the East Blue...
Zoro?
Did you say something, you damn brat?
The only thing that was regrettable
was that I lacked information.
Who's that?
Don Krieg!!
Yeah, I said you like
to complain! Now, go.
The man I've been looking for.
I just didn't know things...
O... Okay...
Hawk-Eye Mihawk!
We have a new customer.
I'll take your logbook.
Hawk-Eye Mihawk...
Here they come! They're finally coming!
He'd better not be someone who'll
go on a rampage in my place.
And I'll form a large pirate fleet
again and seize the One Piece.
Here I come! Gum-Gum...
A pirate, huh?
...Rocket!
And then, I'll stand on top
in this Great Pirate Era!
Ugh! He's flying over here!
The world's strongest man...
Why... why are the Krieg Pirates here?!
And Gum-Gum...
That's the man who sank Krieg's
50 ships on his own in the Grand Line?
You see it, Patty?! They actually came!
...Giant Scythe!
You're gonna get rid of them, right?!
I-Isn't it a mistake?!
Then, the one who destroyed
Krieg's ship just now is also...
This is the Don of a pirate fleet with a
5,000-pirate force we're talking about!
Anything's fine. Bring me food.
Oof!
Hold on a second!
But he looks just like
an ordinary human.
Why would he come all the way here
to get revenge just for one of his men?!
I'm the one who's gonna
be King of the Pirates!
This is a restaurant, right?
It's no mistake! He's really here!
Hey, that chore boy is pretty good!
It doesn't look like he
has any special weapons.
Chore boy!
Welcome, ya damn crook.
--J-Just what the heck...
--...is he...
Hey, back off, chore boy!
You're no match for him!
Hey, this is not good!
Shouldn't we just get out of here?!
His weapon is on his back...
The Grand Line is crawling
with guys like this?
I'll say it only one more time,
so listen good. Bring me food.
That... can't be!
What a huge galleon!
I can't back off on this.
Did he really slice up that large
sailing ship using that sword?
That cook is gonna get killed...
--Sanji!
--Hmm?
Did you say something, kid?
Um, sir, I'm terribly sorry,
but do you have money for that?
Watch carefully how he fights.
He's the master swordsman Hawk-Eye...
I can let it pass...
Don't take your eyes off him until
the moment this fight comes to an end.
...the man who stands above all
other swordsmen in the world...
What a huge ship!
You don't have to. I just stated a fact.
I wonder if Ghin came back
to repay you for your kindness.
Hmm?
--Would a bullet do?
--So you don't have money, right?
I don't think so...
This isn't a game.
To think that you attack the
restaurant after they gave you food...
But it seems strange...
Of course not.
I'll conquer the Grand Line.
What?!
I never thought I'd be
able to see him this soon...
Patty, that dumb ass!
He broke the chair...
I'll beat up an ungrateful jerk like you!
What power!
It's no joke, you brat!
It's finally... time to fulfill my promise...
It's true that we didn't
have information,
If you can't pay for the food,
you're not a customer.
So you actually want to fight on
the water when there's little foothold?
but a fleet with 5,000 men was
wiped out in just seven days!
Y-You son of a bitch...
--H-Hey...
--Wh-What the...
That's a devilish sea!
Those with devil fruit powers are
helpless in the sea. I know that much.
Good job, Cook!
What grudge do you
have to come after us?!
There's no way someone
like you can sail across it!
Beat that pirate up, Patty-san!
S-Seven days?!
Just killing time.
--Anchor boy!
--Instead, I can stretch.
Oh... Your stomach is grumbling, pirate.
Krieg's pirate ships were
wiped out in just seven days?!
Wha?! Don't mock us!
What on earth happened?
That was a fart, you stupid
racoon dog. Just bring me food.
Their ship sure is beat up...
Unfortunately, I don't find
those kinds of jokes funny.
Sanji! The fins are gonna open up now!
It doesn't seem like they
were attacked by cannons...
If you're not a customer,
beat it already!!
But then, it's hard to think
that damage is manmade.
If you're not going to let it drop,
then how about I just crush you here...
--Hmm?
--What's going on?
Did they come across
a tornado or something?
Wh-What?!
I'm sure I aimed straight for him!
Go ahead if you can...
He averted them.
Here he comes...
He gently changed
the course of the bullets
Fine by me.
using the point of his sword.
As you wish, I'll send
you to the netherworld.
That can't be true...
Hey! Who are you?!
I-I've had enough already!
Three swords... Could it be...
I don't want anything
to do with this restaurant!
From the sea...
I've never seen a sword
moved so gently...
...a foothold has appeared!
I-I'll never come back here!
There is no strength in
swordplay based only on force.
Did you use that sword to
slice up this ship as well?
Now, dumb customers,
please continue your meal!
Gonna fight, Luffy? Need a hand?
That's right.
I see... You're the strongest...
I-If you don't need help,
though, th-that's fine too...
Whoa! Check that out!!
I came out to sea to meet you.
Zoro! Usopp! You stopped by?
Please never come back. Hmph!
Don't worry. Just watch from there.
What's your goal?
We'll fight to the utmost,
you damn pirates!
Y-Yeah? T-Too bad,
To become the strongest!
Hmph... How foolish...
Dammit! If I were in a normal
state, I wouldn't have been...
but if you say so, what can we do...
I see. You set up that battlefield so that
the restaurant itself won't be damaged.
B-But if push comes
to shove, we'll help you.
S-S-So, g-g-good luck!
...mocked by someone like that...
That works out for us too,
since that ship's gonna be ours.
You've got spare time,
right? Let's fight!
What'd you do that for, Zoro?!
Hey, are you hungry by any chance?
Th-This guy is Zoro! Roronoa Zoro
of the Three Swords Style!
I want this ship all the more.
Shut up! Just keep quiet!
Shut up! I'm not hungry!
We won't let you have this restaurant!
S-Sorry... Can I have
some water and food?
What?!
Are they your crewmembers?
Oh, a pirate hunter, huh?
That's right! Don't make light of us!
That's quite a small group you got!
He is?!
We're fighting cooks!
What're you saying?!
I've got two more!
We have money... tons of money...
Hey, this isn't good, Luffy!
Hey! You counted me, didn't you?!
The Going Merry will
be out of sight soon!
I don't even remember
the last time I ate.
Eat it.
Hey, Luffy!
Take sail! The Baratie's sea
battle weapon, Mackerel Head 1!
Fight? Hmph! How pitiful, weak one...
Shut up! Beat it!
Please... give me some water and food...
I'll deal with you later.
Even when I'm down and out,
I won't take charity from others.
If you don't wanna die,
get out of here now!
I'll go feed my underlings.
Take this food away now!
If you are a competent
enough swordsman,
What the hell is that?
Those who don't want to die can
abandon the restaurant and escape.
you should be able to see
the disparity in our abilities
Stop whining and eat it already!
Wh-What's that?!
That's so cool! I want it!
He shows neither dignity nor force.
To me, anyone who's
hungry is a customer.
even before we cross swords.
--Paddle faster!
--I'm paddling as fast as I can!
Is he really that Don Krieg,
Commodore of the grand pirate fleet?
Is it your courage or ignorance that
causes you to turn your sword on me?
All I'm after are the
logbook and this ship.
Sorry, but I'm not a customer.
Fire!!
So he's hungry...
It's my ambition!
But if you still wish
to be uselessly killed...
I'm gonna sink!
How large and cruel the ocean is...
C-Captain!
And it's also because of a
promise I made to a dear friend!
...it's a bother, but I'll
bury you into the sea.
--All right! Good job!
--Patty! Carne! Get them!
How scary it is to lose food
and water on the ocean...
Don Krieg!
Hawk-Eye Mihawk,
the world's strongest swordsman,
Know that.
P-Please! Help our captain!
and the pirate hunter Zoro...
How hard it is...
They're pretty good!
What kind of fight will it be?
He's really about to starve!
I can understand how a hungry
person feels more than anyone.
There can't possibly be anyone
who can defeat Big Bro!
Don't look away! We're aiming at him!
He hasn't eaten anything for days!
He'll die if he doesn't eat!
Yeah!
Big Bro is the strongest already!
Krieg! Be prepared!!
You can die for your pride if you want,
but if you eat and survive, don't you
think there's a future for you?
Watch how powerful the Sea Restaurant
Baratie's sea battle weapon is!
Hey, what's the meaning of that?
It's gotten quiet.
This is good! It's a riot to see
Big Bro Zoro went in there.
It should be all right.
I'm no beast that goes all
out when hunting a rabbit.
the famous arch rogue
Don Krieg like this...
Hmm... Are they really okay, though?
Even if you're a swordsman who's
earned a bit of a name for himself,
We have money this time.
We're customers!
If you put it that way...
this sea, the East Blue, is the
weakest among the four seas.
Say, Big Sis Nami, should we go in, too?
Don't be ridiculous!
Hey, contact the Navy right away.
What? Did we bump into something?
Sorry...
Hmm? We can't move!
What?
He's at his weakest right now.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity!
Unfortunately, I don't carry any
smaller sharp instrument than this one.
Sorry... Thank you... I thought I'd die.
I'm Don Krieg!
--Big Sis?!
--Ahhh! Ugh!
There's no need to feed him anything.
Keep him under arrest.
That's enough making fun of me!
I'm the man who will
rule the world's oceans!
I thought I was done...
I told you that's gonna be me!
He's right! We don't know what
he'll do once his energy's back.
Better not regret it when I kill you!
Frog in the well...
Know how big the world is.
I don't have time for your games!
He's done bad things.
Delicious... Delicious...
He deserved to starve because
of everything he's done!
Oni... Giri!
I've never eaten food so delicious.
B-Big Sis Nami?
Once he's back to normal, I bet he'll
attack this restaurant straight away.
Hmm? Ahh, what is it?
Is something wrong?
Wh-What?!
What Herculean strength he has!
There's no need to give
him even a glass of water.
It's damn delicious, isn't it?
I won't do anything...
I found a good cook!
Zoro?!
Wha... Big Bro's Oni Giri was stopped!
It's coming this way!
Hey you, it's a good thing
that he gave you food!
I won't do anything...
The restaurant will be destroyed!
Once I eat, I promise I'll leave quietly.
Even a big technique that never
fails to blow any enemy away was...
You almost died!
What's going on?!
Hey you, cook! Join my group!
So please... help... me...
I'm sorry, Sanji-san.
I... I can't move them! What did he do?!
I never imagined this would happen...
Huh?
Don Krieg, please stop!
Be the cook on my pirate ship!
That's not something you
should apologize for, underling.
No one has ever seen
through this technique,
Please stop begging!
It's not something you should do!
--Huh?!
and he stopped it using a toy like that?!
This... can't be happening!
Each cook at this restaurant acted
as they felt was right. That's all.
Please don't do
something so disgraceful!
I promise... Please...
I'll take leftovers or anything...
Our abilities are this far apart?!
--Sanji!
--W-With his foot?!
That can't be right!
There's no way that it's this far...
Owner! Why are you acting as
if you're taking Sanji's side?!
Anything...
The world's strongest can't be this far!
That's right! He's responsible
for this whole thing!
Are you a pirate?
Yep!
Don...
Why the hell did you shoot
a cannonball into this restaurant?
He's going to put your precious
restaurant out of business!
Shut up, you idiots!
That was an accident!
A self-defense, stray shot.
This can't be happening,
right, Big Bro?! Get serious!
Have you felt what it's like to
be on the brink of starvation?!
Ha! Are you trying
to gain our sympathy?
Big Bro!
A what now?
Hey, out of my way, Patty.
We can't be this far apart!
In any event, don't do anything
stupid to this restaurant.
Losing food and water
on this grand ocean...
The owner of this place used to be
a cook in a famous pirate group.
Oh, boy...
Wh-What strong legs!
Do you know how scary it is?!
Do you know how hard it is?!
I see... So pops was a pirate...
S... Sanji-san!
He kicked back that weird boat!
What?! What do you mean, Owner?
That foot technique is...
To that damn geezer, this
restaurant is like his treasure...
There goes! Sanji's kick!
Here, Ghin. Let him eat it.
The difference between Sanji and you all
He's pretty good!
On top of that, those cooks, who
came here out of admiration for him,
is whether you know it or not.
Sanji-san...
You son of a bitch, Sanji!
are all hot-headed just like pirates.
Are you trying to crush your allies?
Hmm? What does he mean?
--Yeah...
--Don't "yeah" us, you crazy stew!
What's he saying that Sanji knows?
Well, they're actually perfect for
this place since pirates come and go.
Thank you!
You almost lost powerful assets,
you stupid spaghetti!
What ferocity your swordplay has...
Yeah, this restaurant is really wild.
If you have time to grumble,
leave the restaurant from
the back door already!
Do you really think you have
time to crack jokes, cooks?
Yeah. This is how it is here every day.
There're even customers
who come to see
He's taking Zoro's Three Swords Style
attacks with such a small knife...
I'll stay and fight.
Hey, Sanji! Take that food away now!
fights between cooks
and pirates these days.
Let's get them!
I couldn't bear it if I was just
beaten and didn't fight back.
Because of that, the waiters
all got scared and ran away.
Do you realize what kind of man he is?!
He's a monster even beyond
the monstrous Zoro!
I'll stay, too! This is the
restaurant where I work!
He's the man who's called
the East Blue Ruler,
Ah, I see... That's why pops
told me to work here for a year...
We don't have anywhere
else to go anyway!
the foul player Krieg!
I didn't pursue
swordsmanship all this time
It started in a prison.
He pretended to be a marine soldier
Hey, join our group.
to be dealt with by a toy like this!
I refuse. There's a reason that
I have to work in this restaurant.
and took over a Navy ship by
killing a senior officer on the ship.
Even with a weapon, a cook's a cook.
Zoro...
What do you think you're doing?!
You saw how powerful Don is, right?!
We're expert fighters who're in
a whole other league from you.
That's how he declared himself a pirate.
No! I refuse!
Wh-What do you mean?!
Now, be good little cooks and go
find a land restaurant to cook for.
Hey, Ghin!
He sometimes raised the Navy
flag and entered into harbors
I refuse your refusal!
Let me tell you something.
Feeding someone who's
hungry is my morality.
in order to attack the
towns and passenger ships.
Hey, you guys! Why are you letting
those guys beat you up so easily?!
You're a good cook,
so let's be pirates together.
He also raised a white flag
and then attacked enemy ships...
You're lucky, Zoro. You're a boy.
Do you still call
yourselves fighting cooks?!
But...
He did anything to continue winning.
That's how he got to where he is now!
Hey, listen to what I say.
Well, they're strong!
I want to be the world's
greatest swordsman, too!
So what's that reason?
They're totally different from
those we've fought before!
I don't need to tell you.
If only... If only I had been born a man!
...those we'll be dealing with
are plunderers with full bellies.
Huh? You just told me
to listen to what you say!
Huh... so he plays dirty.
Don't lump us in with
those average pirates.
His real strength is
overwhelming as well.
I'm telling you
to accept what I say!
I won't let you complain even
when I beat up your fellow pirates.
We're the Krieg Pirates,
the rulers of the East Blue.
Don't be whining like
that after you beat me!
Leaving after eating?
That's not possible with him!
I'm gonna cut you into three
pieces, you damn straw hat!
That's not fair! You're my goal!
Just decree to them... that the ship
already belongs to the Krieg Pirates!
If someone's going to
take over this restaurant,
Letting such a wicked fiend die
without help is for society's sake!
What'd you say?!
I'm gonna beat you up
even if it's you, I'll kill
them without hesitation!
Zoro...
if you make fun of the
straw hat, you jerkwad!
Promise me!
Don't be mistaken.
Got that?
Sorry to interrupt...
Someday, one of us will be
the world's greatest swordsman!
We won't let you take even
one step into the restaurant.
--What?!
Ha! Letting him live and now
killing him? You're hopeless, Sanji...
I'm Ghin of the Krieg Pirates.
He's exactly right!
Promise me!
You're a pirate, too, right?
Do you have any goals?
Shut up, you damn cook!
--It's a promise!
You see? He's kinda cool, isn't he?
I've been a cook for
more than ten years.
I'm aiming for the One Piece.
I'm going to enter the Grand Line.
Who cares about him?!
I visited 300 restaurants.
To become the world's strongest!
We'd better get out of here now!
I got fired for causing a scuffle
all the time and I lived a rough life.
Calm down! Even if it's Krieg,
he's a wreck with injuries.
This is the place we finally came to
Given that you're looking for a cook,
it seems you have only a few members.
after going to restaurant
after restaurant...
Ghin! You said you didn't know
anything about the Grand Line.
Anybody there?!
Yep. He's the fifth member.
I... I'm going to get
stronger for her, too!
Is this the restaurant
run by Red Foot Zeff?!
Even though you've been there?
Why are you counting me?!
Since you seem like
a nice guy, I'll warn you.
This "Damn Cooks Wanted"
better be true!
I'll be the world's greatest swordsman
so that my name will reach heaven!
The Grand Line is the one
place you should avoid.
It's still true that I don't know.
You're still young.
You don't need to rush.
Yeah, it's true.
What happened on the seventh day
after we entered the Grand Line...
I promised her... I...
The Grand Line is only a small
portion of the entire ocean.
Be they arch rogues or jail breakers,
I don't know if it
was a dream or reality...
If you wanna be a pirate,
there's an endless ocean out there.
What?!
if they badly want to eat and
find their way to this restaurant,
I still haven't been able
to come to terms with it...
I see... You know something
about the Grand Line?
S... Sanji!
Only to defeat this man...
we'll feed them until they're stuffed.
Can you handle that?!
I still just can't believe...
No... I don't know anything...
I don't understand anything about it...
...that the 50-ship fleet...
Y-Yes, sir!
That's exactly why I fear it...
Th... This isn't what
we agreed, Don Krieg!
...was wiped out by only one man...
You're an underling of that Krieg,
and yet you talk so wimpy...
I brought you here under the condition
that you wouldn't touch this restaurant!
What do you bear on your shoulders?
We can't serve such a nasty
soup to the customers!
Hmm? Who's Krieg?
What do you desire once you've
obtained power, weak one?
And that man saved our lives...
What did you hit me for?!
--What?!
That's a sign for determination!
You called Big Bro a
weak one? You cross bastard!
Shut up!
I'll teach you a lesson! He is...
Scuffles... cooking...
We're allowed to do whatever we like.
Yeah, that was delicious.
Stop it! Yosaku! Johnny!
Don't intervene!
The hors d'oeuvre for
table three is ready!
There's no other
restaurant as good as this.
Take it yourself.
We don't have any waiters.
Be patient!
I feel alive again.
So they say. Got that, Krieg?
Is it really okay, though, Patty?
Committing ourselves to cooking
every day is a fierce battle.
Luffy...
Is what okay?
I hear the guy you beat up
earlier in the restaurant
I can't lose...
Compared to that, the pirates
we're facing today are nothing!
is one of the Krieg Pirates.
He's exactly right!
Oh yeah, I heard.
--Fight!
--Yeah!
It happened suddenly...
--Protect Owner!!
--Protect the restaurant!!
"Don Krieg" is the strongest
and most evil pirate
H-Hey... Wh-What the hell
is going on in there?
As soon as this man appeared,
he sank the ships one after another.
in this part of the ocean.
That's right.
We'll see when we go in there.
Hmm?
What?! A-Are you serious?!
Tiger...
Oh? Are you scared?
That sounds great!
The world's greatest swordsman?
After all, he's the don of
a pirate fleet that controls
If we hadn't been lucky enough
to have that storm then,
Wha... Don't be silly!
The King of the Pirates would need
no less than that on his crew!
Hmph!
Th-That's...
our main ship would've been
completely destroyed as well...
the captains of 50 pirate ships.
This is strange...
...Trap!
There's almost no sign
of anyone on that ship...
He's no less than a monster...
Hmm...
Just what're you guys doing?
So, what's the big deal?
I don't know how many
ships we have left...
I heard that his extraordinary force
consists of more than 5,000 pirates.
What's with that guy?
It was just so dreadful that I
don't want to accept it as reality...
Unassailable! Hence invincible!
For example, if that guy from earlier
I don't want to remember...
When someone says,
"Pearl-san, the Invincible Shield
told Don Krieg what
happened to him here,
...that man's...
of the Krieg Pirates," they mean me!
Are you just going to
let me pierce your heart?
...sharp, hawk-like eyes whose glare
alone gives one the chill of death.
Pearl-san!
this restaurant would
probably be crushed
This is a good restaurant.
I'll take this ship.
Why aren't you withdrawing?
Patty! Carne! Are you all right?!
I don't know...
like a large parade of
elephants stomping on ants.
They're not all right, because they
took my killer punch, "Pearl Surprise."
I don't know why, but...
Wha...
Oh, yeah?
...if I withdrew even a step,
What did he just say?!
So... that's what you want...
Then you're saying that
I should've just treated him?
I feel like those various
important things such as pledges
Ow, ow, ow...
and promises in the
past will be shattered,
Whoa! This is a nice knife. I'll take it.
That...
That's rude to the other customers.
...must be Hawk-Eye...
and I won't be able to come
back to where I am now...
Hmm? Hey, let go. Give it to me!
Let it go, you damn loser!
What?
That you felt his eyes were like
a hawk's isn't proof in and of itself,
Yes, that's what defeat is about.
It will ruin the reputation
of the famous fighting cooks
My ship became a wreck,
so I wanted a new one.
Then, all the more reason
I can't withdraw...
at the Sea Restaurant Baratie!
but what this man did is
enough proof that it's him...
Even if you'll die?
How many pirates do you
think we've beaten off?
I'd rather die.
You'll get off this ship after you
take care of what I tell you to do.
What a strong heart!
So he chooses death over defeat!
If you're that scared, just quit!
Hawk-Eye!
Wh-What?!
Huh? You know him, Zoro?
He's really got some good kicks!
Don Krieg... This isn't
what you promised.
What'd you say?!
Oh yeah, all the waiters
I didn't come to like him for nothing!
Yeah... He's the man I'm looking for.
quit because of those words of yours!
Kid! State your name.
A kitchen knife is a cook's soul.
Patty! It's your fault
that we're this busy!
There're about 100 of my
underlings still alive on my ship.
I went out to sea to meet him.
Don't you amateurs
carelessly put hands on it!
Ha! Those wimps were
useless from the start!
I see...
They're weak with
hunger and severe injuries.
Roronoa Zoro.
Sanji...
Isn't it possible that that man had
some deep grudge towards you guys?
Hold this tight and stay down there.
First, prepare 100 meals
and water for them.
I'll remember it.
Go for it!
I haven't seen anyone like you
in a while, strong one. Thus...
Carne, take him out!
We never did anything to him!
I'll take care of them.
Patty, beat him!
Like you guys disturbed
his nap or something...
We won't be beaten by a mere cook!
Hey, you idiots! Get to work already!
There're some who've
already starved to death.
...as a swordsman's courtesy,
Don't be ridiculous!
I'll sink you using the world's
strongest black sword.
I'll be damned if he crushed
our fleet for such a reason!
Yes, Owner!
W-Water...
I appreciate it.
So long, then...
Don't get so worked up.
It's just an example.
But I'm still going to the Grand Line.
Bring them over immediately!
H-He took it out!
A mere cook, you said? I'm gonna
cut you in three, you bastards!
That's the sword that sliced up the ship!
Yeah. Do whatever you like.
I'm just giving an example of what
kind of place the Grand Line is.
Are you telling us to revive pirates
So this'll be the last hit...
I'm a stranger to you. I don't
have the right to try to stop you.
Ha! How impudent you are
to beat them using only kicks.
that are gonna attack this ship?!
Will it be the world's strongest?
What the heck kind of place is that?
We refuse!
I just wanted to warn you.
Or death?
Is that your policy?
Refuse? Don't get the wrong idea.
It probably means that
anything can happen.
And Sanji-san, thank you so much!
To cooks, hands are most important.
I can't have them hurt in battle.
I'm not placing an order.
I'm giving you orders.
Hey Luffy! Let's not
go to a place like that!
Big Bro! That's enough! Please stop!
I owe my life to you. The food you
gave me was the most delicious.
Three Swords Style Secret Technique!
Luffy!
I'll take you down with this leg as well.
It doesn't matter who
you are... don't defy me!!
Take me down? That's impossible.
Is it okay if I come back for it?
Fall!
Three Thousand Worlds!
I'm an invincible man that won
all 61 of my battles unharmed.
Any time!
Hey, Luffy?
Hey, you, chore boy!
Ahhh! It sounds so exciting!!
Ugh! Pops!
I've never shed blood in
a battle, not even a drop.
That's how it should be!
There you are!
You need to get the concept of
"danger" into your thick skull!
--Sanji-san...
--Hmm?
But my goal is now completely
narrowed down to the Grand Line.
I lost...
Go, Ghin.
Winning unharmed is
the very proof of my power.
Sanji-san, I'm sorry...
I didn't mean for this to happen...
I never imagined I'd ever lose...
Ahh, sorry.
What?!
You're gonna get yelled at,
because you fed me free, right?
That man... I can see
that man if I go there...
I'm a shield man and a gentleman.
I'm refined, aren't I?
You son of a bitch!
Look what you've done!!
So this is the power
of the world's strongest...
Well...
Was that supposed to be a gag?
It wasn't funny at all.
Are you guys stupid or what?
Hey, straw hat brat!
Guys like you die before anyone else.
What are you...
If you're not paying
attention, you'll get hurt!
Scars on the back are
a swordsman's shame...
Yeah, but you didn't
have to call us "stupid."
Admirable!
...there's no proof, so there's no
reason for me to be yelled at.
When I decided to become
the strongest swordsman,
Even battleship cannons
don't work on me.
Zoro!!
I decided to devote my life to it.
Since it was my decision, the only
one who can call me stupid is me.
I come out of any attack unharmed!
Hey Sanji! Where're you going?!
Don't live so hastily, young man.
Boy, that startled me.
Good thing I didn't fall in the sea.
Don't ever get caught again, Ghin!
To the kitchen.
I have to prepare 100 more meals.
Ahh! Me too, me too!
Me, too! That's just natural
as a man of the sea!
Thank you, Sanji-san!
Zoro!!
I'll never forget your kindness!
In your case, that's a lie.
--Big Bro!!
--Sanji-san!
--Sanji?!
What?
--What?!
Ahh... This isn't good.
What nonsense...
Sanji! Chore boy! Get to work already!
Why?
Blood! Oh, no!
Right. That's how it should be.
Pearl-san, don't worry.
When I decided to become
the strongest swordsman,
--It's just a nosebleed!
--It's not a wound from fighting!
Hey!
I decided to devote my life to it.
Hey, table three is ready!
Do you idiots understand
the current situation?!
--Please calm down, Pearl-san!
--What's going on?
Th-Th-Th-These guys are dangerous!
The ship moored in front
of the restaurant
He's crazy! His opponent
is the real world's strongest!
I'm Luffy!
is the huge Galleon that
belongs to Don Krieg,
Are you Krieg's spy, Sanji?!
What's with him? He's acting strange.
I'll be the chore boy from now.
Nice to meet you all!
Commodore of the "pirate fleet"!
How it'd turn out was clear. He should
give up his ambition rather than die!
We can't let you go in the kitchen!
What about his nosebleed?
If you wanna escape from reality,
We're fed up with your crazy behavior!
It should be easy...
to give up your ambition, right?!
do it after surviving
this life-or-death crisis!
Stop it, Pearl! It's just a nosebleed!
Don't lose your cool!
Go ahead...
So this is the power of the Grand Line...
the power of the world!
If you want to stop me, go ahead!
What the heck is he about to do?
To think the pirate hunter Zoro
is as helpless as a new-born baby!
Danger! Danger! Danger!!
Isn't the dessert for
table six ready yet?!
I know...
--We're saved!!
He's an incorrigible rogue...
I know that much...
Damn you, damn you... Damn you!!
Hey, who's responsible for that order?!
Great! We're still alive!
Isn't that you?!
It seems like a dream!
--Big Bro!!
I'm too busy right now!
We're free from that nightmare!
Oh, no! It's started!
But that doesn't matter to me.
That doesn't matter!
That's because you keep spacing out!
When Pearl-san gets upset,
he catches fire!
We came back alive from
the pirate graveyard!
What'd you say?! Wanna fight?!
What was that?
Wh-What's that?
What happens after we feed them...
It's too much of a bother to think about it.
Fire Pearls... Special Treat!!
If you have nothing to do, wash
dishes or something, chore boy!
So that brat... has the
power of a devil fruit!
That's right...
which means that we can now
head to the Grand Line again.
I'm a cook. No more. No less.
Where's Sanji?
You bastard...
If there's someone who's hungry,
I'll feed him. That's all.
He's hitting on a customer
in the dining room.
Ouch!
Pearl-san! Please stop!
Again?!
Are you that young
swordsman's comrade?
I'm already annoyed by him just
being the Sous Chef to begin with!
Huh? What's with those faces?
You also impressed me for
watching it to the very end!
It's all right for a cook to be
that way, don't you think?
A-Are we going to that place again?
Burn! With this flame
and the flame shield,
It can't be helped since he's
worked here the longest.
you have no idea how invincible I am!
Don't worry. I didn't kill that man.
Do you know why he keeps staying here
That idiot! Is he going to burn down
the ship that we're gonna take over?
when he doesn't get along with Owner?
No more objections, right?
What?
Patty!
Big Bro! Big Bro! Say something!
Hey, someone keep him restrained!
--Ow, ow, ow, ow...
--Dammit!
He's aiming to be the next Head Chef.
Zoro?!
Sanji, you sometimes feed customers
I drive away at the back door, don't you?
You can tell if you watch him.
Zoro!!
Crap! There's no escape from a sea
of flames in the middle of the sea!
Now, hurry up and get
him up on the ship!
--Huh?
This isn't good!
The restaurant will catch fire!
This is medicine! Throw it over him!
I'm not gonna say who's right,
but this time, it's your mistake.
Hey, chore boy!
It's still too early for you to die.
My name is Dracule Mihawk!
This restaurant will burn?
How many dishes have
you broken so far?!
First, abandon this wrecked ship
that could sink at any moment
--Burn! Burn!
--You son of a bitch!
I'm not going to let you do
what you want any longer.
You idiot! You'll get burned, Sanji!
Oh, sorry. I forgot to count.
Learn about yourself!
Learn about the world!
I'll protect this restaurant.
and take over the restaurant.
That's not what I meant!
Apologize for breaking them!
And become strong!
I'm not just gonna let you...
burn this restaurant down!
Fortunately, we have
only one enemy to fight.
Our enemy's just some punk cooks.
No matter how many years it takes,
Even if it's Don Krieg,
what can he do against us?
Forget about washing
dishes. Clean that area!
I will hold this seat of
the strongest and wait for you.
Even if you take your opponent lightly,
that's still more than enough...
Okay, leave it to me!
Surpass this sword!
H-He's so reckless!
This is a sea restaurant where
pirates come and go every day.
Try to surpass me! Roronoa Zoro!
Don't take food!
Does he want to turn
into a human torch?!
That's a main dish!!
We're fully prepared to
serve any kind of customer!
When even fierce animals would
stay away from Fire Pearls...
Big Bro! Big Bro, say something!
Oh, don't worry about it!
That's...
Big Bro!
Ouch!!
Are you full now, Krieg-san?
You fool! I'd be unfit to be
a cook if I was afraid of flames!
Attack!
To think that he got Hawk-Eye
Mihawk to say this much...
After the main course, how about...
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
D-Dammit! What a refined guy he is!
Would you get out
of the kitchen already?!
...a piece of iron dessert?!
Kid, what is your goal?
You go take orders, okay?
Here they come!
We can hear their war cry!
King of the Pirates!
Here I come!
We'll protect the ship to
the end! It's our restaurant!
Go ask what customers want
to eat! You can do it, can't you?!
Meat Ball of Doom!!
It'll be even harder than surpassing me!
Yes...
Ahh! That hit him good!
How would I know when
I haven't done it yet?!
Chores're sure tiring. It must've
been a lot of work for Koby, too.
He broke through
Invincible Pearl-san's wall!
He's alive!
Out of our way, cooks!
Hey, chore boy!
He's just unconscious.
Ugh! You guys...
--Big Bro!
--Big Bro! Say something!
I hear you have to work for a year here!
What's with this cook? He's really crazy.
Zoro?
Is it okay if we redraw
our flag for the ship?
Y-Y-You son of a bitch!
Fire! I need more fire!
Big Bro!
Ahhh... You're eating
yummy food without me?!
L... Luffy...
Don!
I need to feed more Fire Pearls!
Can you hear me?
How could you?!
Yeah!
That's our business, right, guys?
Ahh! The restaurant will catch fire!
I might've broken the doors.
Owner's gonna yell at me again.
Did I worry you?
If the fire gets into the kitchen,
the restaurant will be blown away!
Take this!
You need no less than the world's
greatest swordsman, right?
Well, you did it to
protect the restaurant.
Y-Yeah...
Owner! Please get out of there! Owner!!
What the...?!
It's a small price to pay.
Well, it's true that
the food here is good.
What happened?!
What're you gonna do
about those in Krieg's ship?
Don Krieg!
The main ship was... cut!
I feel bad for you, but...
Big Bro! Please don't talk any more!
Who knows?
Maybe we'll spread butter
on the ship and stir-fry it...
Big Bro!
--Whoa!!
Cut?! It was cut, you said?!
I... I will not be defeated ever again!
...drink it yourself!
This huge Galleon was?!
M-My Fire Pearls...
That can't be true!!
--I can't believe you did that!
It'll taste good, right? You lame cook!
Something like that is child's play!
Until the day I defeat him
and become a master swordsman...
The gust from his kick
put out the flame!
My stomach hurts! That was nasty!
What the hell?! That's
definitely a divine technique!
I'll never... be defeated!
Got any problems with that...
So Red Foot Zeff is still strong?!
How dare you serve
such a nasty dessert?!
This is the lousiest restaurant!
Raise the anchor! Or we'll be
swallowed along with the ship!
Pops is really cool! I'm impressed!
How noisy... Could they be his buddies?
...King of the Pirates?!
Yes, sir!
You're damn annoying!!
This is bad! Nami, Yosaku and Johnny
are still on our ship out there!
Nope!
You're a good team.
I want to see you guys again.
Now that it's come to this,
I'll sink you all with the fins
Dammit! It might be too late!
Do it yourself.
before the restaurant catches fire!
From all over his body...
Oh, dear ocean!
Hey, Hawk-Eye!
Bullets...
I thank you for today's encounter!
Didn't you come to take my life...
What?!
Sanji! Watch out!!
Oh, love, I can't bear this hardship.
Go ahead and laugh at me.
...the life of the East
Blue's ruler, Don Krieg?
Oh, no! He's surrounded by fire!
Big Bro! Big Bro!
I was going to, but I had enough fun.
I'm now prepared to be a lowly
pirate or devil if I'm with you!
Yosaku! Johnny!
--Ow, ow, ow...
--Chore boy!
So I'm going home to get some rest.
Are you all right?
Where's the ship?! It's gone!
What happened to Nami?!
Don't defy me!
Gum-Gum... Bazooka!
You may have had enough,
but I'm tired of getting beaten.
That... I'm sorry, Big Bro. She's gone.
However, how tragic it is! There's
too great an obstacle between us!
I'm the strongest!
--Ow, ow, ow...
--He hit that iron ball back!
D-Don?
Steel arms more
powerful than anyone's...
Why are you trying to keep him here?
See ya! Tell them...
That obstacle is me, right, Sanji?
A wootz steel-made body
that is harder than anyone's...
Big Sis Nami...
...that if we're linked
by fate, we'll meet again.
Die before you leave!!
And a diamond fist that
can destroy anything!
Damn geezer!
This is a good opportunity. Why don't
you become a pirate with them?
She took all the treasure and ran off!
As I expected...
he never learns a lesson...
I have all sorts of built-in
weapons throughout my body...
--Wh-What'd you say?!
The 50-ship large fleet
and 5,000-pirate force!
You're no longer needed
at this restaurant!
Pearl-san is really down this time!
I've won all battles in the past!
Damn! He escaped...
--Pearl-san is...
I am the man fit to be called Don!
What the heck?
That guy sure is dumb.
Geez... They're all...
Out of my way, kid!
That man is...
In the end, I can only count on myself...
Usopp!
When I tell you to prepare food,
Luffy!
I see...
Go! I'll leave Nami to you!
all you have to do is
obediently follow orders!
That cook saved your life,
Got it! Zoro and I will
bring Nami back for sure!
Don't defy me!
The battle ends here.
and you were able to come back here...
Make sure you get that cook to join us!
Is that what you're saying, Ghin?
Th-That son of a bitch!
He followed us!
When all five of us
are reunited, let's go to...
Y-Yes... B-But...
There's probably enough
for 100 meals in this.
That's right! Shoot Red Foot Zeff!
...the Grand Line!
Bring it to your ship right away.
I never imagined the main
ship was in this condition...
Yeah! Let's do that!
--Owner Zeff!
Guys! We ran into some interference,
but the real fight starts now!
All we need to do is kill him.
Then the restaurant will be ours!
What's with that, pops?
I could've gotten hurt!
Don Krieg!
What?
We'll take that ship!
I'll take you there...
to the Sea Restaurant Baratie...
Yeah!!
Z... Zeff?
Pops, can I stop doing
chores if I drive them away?
Is it possible... that's...
...Hawk-Eye!
Suit yourself.
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Krieg and his pirates are coming!
There's no way I'm gonna
let them take this restaurant!
The customer is king.
Who's that?
Is it really okay to give
Krieg food like this?
The man I've been looking for. I never
thought I'd be able to see him this soon.
Honestly, what an
ungrateful bunch they are,
That's right! Smile no
matter who the customer!
Taking a hostage! That's dirty!
I'm gonna kick that bastard's ass!
Yeah. Do something about that, pops!
when they were given food!
Hey, a big fish is here!
Okay, leave it to me!
--Are you gonna fight him?
--Yeah. I went out to sea to meet him.
Come to think of it,
Butt out, chore boy!
Keep your hands out of this!
--That's...
--Krieg Pirates!
Hey! What're you doing, Luffy?!
there's another ungrateful one
who took treasure and ran off...
That's a large pirate group
with a 5,000-pirate force!
Don't go picking a fight
with Krieg, you idiot!
Hey Zoro, what's wrong?
Then, is it okay to use my legs?
You shouldn't worry
about it! Get some rest!
5,000? I wonder if we
have enough chairs...
Am I this far from
the world's strongest?
I'm gonna cut you in three,
you damn Straw Hat!
That sounds fun.
Gonna fight, Luffy? Need a hand?
Hey, a weird guy came out...
So this is the world's strongest...
Idiot! They came to attack this
place! Close the restaurant!
He's fully armed with shields!
Ow, ow, ow! Fire! Fire!
I can't let the damn geezer's
purpose in life get taken away!
--Zoro!!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Protect Baratie!
The Great Pirate, Red Foot Zeff!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Hawk-Eye Mihawk! The Great
Swordsman Zoro Falls on the Sea"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Deadly Foot Technique Bursts Forth!
Sanji vs. the Invincible Pearl"
"The Strongest Pirate Fleet!
Commodore Don Krieg"
"Zeff and Sanji's Dream;
The Illusory All Blue"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!