It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set
sail-- let's raise anchor
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
Zoro and Sanji have teamed up
in Round #2's Groggy Ring
Luffy accepted the Foxy Pirates' dare
and agreed to Davy Back rules.
Incredible!
Armée de l'Air Power Shoot!
The Straw Hat Dangers
come from behind to win
in order to win Chopper back.
the final round of the Davy Back Fight!
Hamburg catches Sanji! Incredible!
He's within range of the ring!
Go!
However, his team lost the first-round
Donut Race, due to Foxy's trickery.
I lost... And so did my Slow-Slow Beam...
I ain't gonna...
What speed!
All right! We did it!
...let 'em score!
--He's well on his way to
catching up with Porche-chan!
--Flower Shurikens!
The first person I want is... you!
Goal!
Thank goodness! What a relief!
I can't let that damn swordsman snub me...
Goal! Goal!
...by saving my hide!
The ship doctor! Tony Tony Chopper!
--It all worked out in the end.
--Yep.
I'm a wall...
Team Straw Hat is victorious!
All right! Do anything you like with me!
Now it's time to take someone!
Now I'm mad, Leader!
Oh! But he clears the wall with a skillful toss!
Who do you choose, Straw Hat Luffy?!
The team must now win the
second-round Groggy Ring
Hamburger Hammer!
Is it only a matter of time
until he catches Porche-chan?!
Chopper! Come back!
Shelly!
Punk...
to get Chopper back, but...
...Attack!
--Seem like a good match?
--Yep.
Oh, no! Choppy!
He's already back?!
Wh-What's this?!
Thank you! I'm so happy!
Captain Monkey D. Luffy has
chosen Shelly, Tonjit's former horse!
Take this!
Sling Tackle!
"Round 2! Shoot It into the Groggy Ring"
--Oh...
--Oh?!
Don't cry! You know we'd never lose!
Size Attack: S!
That's it.
What in the world is he thinking?!
Now do it just like I explained!
The grueling Davy Back Fight
has come to an end!
That's it! Stand up, Luffy!
M!
Our mighty Groggy Ring
combatants have taken the field!
L!
Both teams ultimately reach a
draw as the Straw Hat Pirates
Old stilts guy. I took Shelly
back from those guys.
Opposing them...
take back their ship doctor, Chopper!
...is the violent cook who kicked
the interference squads'
The opponents literally are "groggy"!
You guys...
--The competition is now ov--
--Hold it! Hold it! Hold it!
"A Seriously Heated Race!
Into the Final Round!"
Now you can always be together.
butt in Round #1: Sanji!
All that remains now is to stuff
the ball man into his ring coffin
I truly appreciate this. Thank you.
That's "first-rate cook."
There are no "draws" in the pirate world!
and this will be two wins in a row!
And the pirate hunter with a bounty
of 60 million: Roronoa Zoro!
Well, that explains that.
Guess it couldn't be helped this time!
It's either plunder or be plundered!
C'mon! You can do it! Just a little more!
Right, Straw Hat?! Well?!
This is what they called us
out here for? What a laugh!
Hey, cook...
Man, this is great!
That's a good girl!
Lend me a hand for ten seconds...
Wh-What's he tryin' to say?!
Right, Big Pan?
Chopper!
What do you say to another
three-coin game right now?
Got a problem with that?
Sounds like... a reasonable length of time...
Huh?
Nope!
He can't hear ya.
"A Barrage of Red Cards in Groggy Ring!"
What's with these guys?
Is he an idiot?
Chopper...
We'll start with a coin toss.
Seriously! Who'd agree to
more of these lame games?!
Leave it to me! It'll be just fine!
This is so moving! Seriously!
Yeah, sure. Uh-huh.
Tails.
All right! I'm up!
Ack! You can't be serious!
--What do you choose?
--Heads, obviously!
I wonder what the next game will be.
This is Round #2 of the
Davy Back Fight, Groggy Ring!
Hang on, Usopp!
Let's get started!
The outcome of the match is now clear as day!
Tails.
You're on!
Luffy!
We will win Chopper back!
No one is a match for our monsters!
--What the heck are you thinking?!
--You stupid rubber monkey dimwit!
Field or ball?
And then...
"Round 3!
The Round-and-Round Roller Race!"
Although Team Straw Hat was defeated,
...like this?!
Ball.
--You idiot! Moron!
--How can you be so stupid?!
Our Groggy Monsters have chosen the ball!
I can't help but applaud them
for putting up such a gallant--!
This is the last time... I won't do it again...
The Straw Hat ball man will
enter the other team's mid-circle!
It's so fast! Awesome!
Hey! Look!
--Which side do you want?
--Doesn't matter.
Wha...?!
We have to fight them again?!
During the game, there are two
"ball men" with a ball on their heads!
They're up! Team Straw Hat is standing again!
I won't let you win!
Don't worry, Shelly. I'm sure it'll be all right.
Nothing we can do now.
He's already agreed to it.
Knock your opponent's ball man into
your opponent's ring and you win!
He must have something in mind.
Roronoa the swordsman and Sanji
the cook are terrifyingly tough!
Let's have faith in them.
Amazing!
Just get on with it!
"Delectable oden"
I wouldn't be so sure...
It's hard to believe Straw Hat Luffy
couldn't even stand up moments ago!
Two daikon sticks and two
mochi tofu pouches, please.
They really know how to make a game exciting!
Get in position, ball man!
Or maybe he's planning
to snag us a shipwright?
You got it!
Hey, now.
He's keeping pace with Chiqicheetah,
--Bring Support Pillar #6!
--Hurry it up!
"Screaming-Hot Bombardment!
Pirate Dodgeball!"
I don't care how pushy you are,
They're back up! Now get those jerks!
who's powered up with his
Double Speed Full Dash!
I still ain't gonna be the damn ball.
Hey, where'd you put my wood plane?!
But do these two have
enough strength left to fight?!
I refuse to wear this stupid thing!
Quit your whining!
It's time for the second three-coin game!
This next game sounds fun.
Crap! I never taught him how to turn corners!
The events are a team-wide ball game,
a six-on-six all-star retro game,
"Foxy Life!"
Fun? How can you say that, Robin?
--Oh! Looks good on you!
--I won't fall for that, moron!
Hey, you guys...
Put yourself in Chopper's shoes. Poor guy...
Zoro! Sanji! It's up to you guys!
and a one-on-one fight!
One Monster Burger, please!
That's a good point. I apologize.
Like last time, each person
can only participate twice!
Win Chopper back! We can't lose now!
Lineup changes won't be allowed!
It's no big deal...
I'm really sorry! We're counting you!
Straw Hat Luffy has left the course once again!
They're gonna take me for sure this time...
--Wh-What?!
--What could that mean?
Whoa, a wotan... I've never seen one before!
...compared to these carefree dimwits!
He's out of Round #3 as well!
No, it'll definitely be me...
Huh? Do they sell burgers here?
I guess they're not as large
as pureblooded giants.
It's my fate to wind up as their idol...
Oh, ladies!
Darn it...!
Obviously not!
--You're both so lovely!
--Oh! Are you ready?
My word!
--Not interested.
--Huh?
--Why not?
Cheer them on all you
want; it's still no use!
Our boss has just ordered a Monster Burger!
What are you eating, Luffy?
I knew it! He's hopeless...!
--You're weak.
--And scary.
A Long Kiwi!
Okay, it's time for Round #1: Hit and Dead Ball!
Everyone on our team is a Groggy Ring expert!
That old hooorse guy gave
it to me! It's pretty good!
There goes the Speed King, Chiqicheetah!
He's four laps in the lead now!
As always, I'll explain the rules!
What do you want, Split-Head?
Two balls are used!
--You can't have it.
--I don't want it!
He said it again...
Players throw these balls at
opposing team members on the court!
Mellorine!
Oh, Boss!
It's time for Round #3,
the "Run Roller Round" roller skating race!
Get hit and you're disqualified! Outta the game!
Long-nose! Grab on! Hurry!
Now quit doing that, Straw Hat!
Right! Whoa...!
It's a head-to-head race on an outdoor track!
Whichever side runs out of
on-court members first loses!
I doubt I'll need to
interfere with this game,
What's this?! Archaeologist
Nico Robin uses a Long Whip!
Once again, the rules are simple!
You're free to choose which members
should be on or off the court!
First, each team's scorer will start
skating at the sound of the first whistle,
so I thought I'd watch too.
Hold on! They're clearly using weapons now!
Will this help him rally back?!
But keep in mind that although
off-court members can throw the balls,
Got a problem with that?
Interference is allowed with this game too?!
Grind 'em up like a burger patty...
and team defenders will follow suit after
the second whistle 20 seconds later.
Oh, that woman!
Imbecile! It's allowed for every game!
And slice 'em good like fresh pickles...
they're not allowed to enter the court!
It's just, some people will stoop
to anything to help their team win,
Porche-chan! Just leave it to me, ya know?!
Who are the guests?!
Defenders can hinder the opposing
team or root for their own!
I see. So it's basically a variation of dodgeball.
Green lettuce... and yellow cheese!
Anything goes!
while others might insist on a
fair-and-square contest, you know?
Be sure to carefully read the rule book
for other miscellaneous details!
After five minutes are up, the team
whose scorer is in the lead wins!
Crush it all between big pans and you get...
So it depends on the situation.
--Rule book?
--It's rather thick...
...a Monster Burger!
But if you can't even
handle a little interference,
Naturally, being even a single step
ahead means victory in that round!
There it is! Their utterly
horrific triple weapon attack!
Yes! Hit and Dead Ball is the greatest
how can you hope to survive
as a seafaring pirate?
and most time-honored Davy Back Fight game!
There it is! Chiqicheetah's
Triple Speed Rocket Dash!
It's a question of character.
Incidentally, yours truly will
be doing the play-by-play
That's how you justify it?
from a special seat by the starting line!
Many rules have been added
over time, little by little,
There's no escape! Foul play
like this clearly calls for red cards!
What's with that team of yours, anyway?!
to make it a more clear-cut game!
All right! It's time for
both teams to come on out!
Team Straw Hat is in a tough bind!
Hey! He went off the course just now, dammit!
There's no point in having strict rules
if you're not gonna follow 'em!
If you can even call it a team!
Talk all you want! Once the match starts,
you'll see what they can--!
Okay, guys. We have to
get Chopper back this time.
He was only in the air! Only in the air!
It's obvious you're just gonna
keep ruling in their favor again!
Violent coach Sanji's desperate
complaint is shot down!
You went too early just now!
Oh, but wouldn't you know!
Non, non, non! Read the very first page!
Let's do it!
Yeah!
The ref just happens to have
his back turned as he stretches!
Did not! I win!
"Referee Regulations."
Oh! The Straw Hat Dangers
come out with a war cry!
I have to do something before it's too late!
"He who makes a judgment contrary
to these rules shall be beheaded."
At everything.
Mucha Caramente!
What are you doing?!
Oh, no!
Don't be a smartass!
I wouldn't move if I were you!
--Stop, Luffy!
--But...!
Beheaded?! Yikes!
We're talking about rock-paper-scissors here!
They want us to butt in!
The more you struggle,
the tighter it gets, ya know!
There you have it!
No, you lost!
Just decide on a ball man already!
Incidentally, this game will be
officiated by a team of five referees
And lying in wait are the
indomitable Foxy Devils!
We need to grin and bear it, Luffy!
They haven't even agreed on that yet...
Everything's set! The Groggy
Monsters commence their attack!
headed by Rokuroshi,
a fifty-year veteran referee!
Sanji-kun! That ball looks nice on you!
First is the team's playmaker, Porche-chan!
It's no use! I'm soft-bodied!
That doesn't hurt me one bit, ya know!
Whatever happens now, don't blame me!
Looks like it might actually
be a fair game for once.
I'll do it! I'm the ball
man! I'm the worthiest!
Next is the speedy Chiqicheetah
Team Foxy has a veritable crowd
of players! A truly grand spectacle!
and Masshikaku, the defense's linchpin!
Naturally, they go after Sanji, the ball man!
It does suit you. You look like a prince.
Then there's the fishmen Jube and Girarin!
Will he be ground up, sliced,
and crushed into a hamburger patty?!
Well done, Jube!
Oh, and last but not least!
Of Moronica.
That's one down, ya know!
Our own Foxy is the head coach,
with Hamburg as manager!
But the diminutive Team Straw Hat
pales in comparison...
Damn! They got Robin-chan!
I can't make much with
third-rate ingredients like you guys,
A truly powerful lineup, indeed!
Hey, idiot coach!
As usual, they have a measly seven members!
We're gonna lose unless we do
something about that Chiqicheetah guy!
Just start the game!
Drop the "measly" part!
but I'll cook each and every one of you!
Okay, let's get it started!
Don't need you to tell me that!
We'll begin with the double jump!
Hold on! Weapons are against
the rules! Lose the swords!
You're mincemeat now!
"Chiqi... cheetah"...
Troisième...
Cheetah?
Each team, bring two players forward!
Huh? Really?
--He's fast!
--...Haché!
Could it be?!
Yes, this is a ball game!
Old guy!
H-Huh?!
Oh, my! Chiqicheetah is clashing
even before the starting whistle?!
Old guy with the horse! You here?!
It wouldn't be much of a game
if weapons were allowed!
I wanna do this, Zoro!
Oh, you mean me?
Be my guest! Go jump your heart out!
I'm fine either way, to be honest!
That Long Kiwi you gave Luffy!
Where'd you get it?!
What's with this guy?! He's creepin' me out...
Yeah!
Hey, you gonna be okay?
A master swordsman without swords is...
--What are you talking about?!
--Shut it!
He's indeed a quick runner,
but he's also sensitive to smells!
Bouquetiere...
Oh! Ship's doctor Chopper has changed form!
Is what?
Hurry! Tell me where!
...Shoot!
There! They grow on those trees!
He appears to have mysterious abilities!
...nothing but a worthless wimp.
You ate something pungent, didn't you?!
He could be formidable indeed!
Hey, Shrub Head! Run and get us a kiwi branch!
Ha! You didn't eat that old guy's
rotten hunk of milk, did ya?
Oh, my! What is that? That's not cute at all...
Is that how you ask for stuff?!
Oh, no!
All right! Let the game begin!
It might be the only way to stop him!
Stop crushing!
Oh, is that why?
Knock it off, you guys!
You did eat it?!
Stop him?!
All right! It's now or never!
Yeah! So get goin'!
Leader!
M-Man, you're rude!
The Straw Hats' ball man, Sanji,
has entered the opponent's circle!
Shoo! Shoo!
--Wh-What the...?!
--What's he doing?!
--Hey, cook. Hope you get trampled.
--Shut up!
--You can ride Shelly!
--Thanks!
Oww!
Looks like nothing happened...
Stomp 'im, Big Pan!
How dare you...?!
All right, that's it! Now clobber 'em!
Allow me to continue explaining the rules!
The crowd is all fired up!
Okay! Here goes, Chopper!
Big Pan! Let's run-and-gun 'em!
Each team has a coach and a manager!
Dunno if it'll work or not,
but it's better than nothing!
Aim for Split-Head!
Don't forget this is a team battle.
Neither is allowed to directly
participate in the game!
Right!
Huh?
Why, you...!
I'll cut you up!
Be aware that a person
can only be a scorer once!
After four minutes,
Chiqicheetah has a huge 13-lap lead!
He can't hear ya!
Our boss is in trouble!
U-Uhh...
No-Sword Style...
Oh, but there are only four
Straw Hats who can serve as scorers!
C'mon, man...
...Tatsu...
Four and a half minutes have passed!
His lead has increased to 15 laps!
Pay attention!
H-He's already out of the game?!
...Maki!
They're one man short!
All right! We showed their boss who's boss!
Things are looking bleak
for the Straw Hat Dangers!
What will come of this?!
All right! I'll let one of you
participate twice, since I'm a nice guy!
Doesn't count! Doesn't count!
What?! That was a clear hit!
What's taking that loser so long?!
M-My word! Big Pan has fallen
victim to Pickles' spinning blades!
It's not that funny, is it?
Article 23! Hits to the face don't count!
Pride permitting, of course!
The Groggy Monsters are as jolly as always!
What?!
Oh, no! Dammit...!
I can't stand his tone!
Let's get this delightful show on the road!
Darn it!
You're so generous, Boss!
Is that it?!
You okay, Boss?
Your kindness seriously moves me to tears!
Four minutes and fifty seconds have passed!
There's no time limit,
and the first team to score wins!
You shouldn't laugh, Hamburg-san...
Ten more seconds and the Foxy Devils
will clinch a shut-out victory!
You're a real man!
Bad Manner...
So we win if we knock Jumbo's
head into the other ring...
Oh, you guys!
You're too much!
Now's our chance!
He's actually taking that
lame flattery seriously!
Not gonna make it...!
...Kick Course!
Hit 'em like crazy and win!
Man, Split-Head sure is dumb.
Okay! I'll hit them like crazy and win for us!
It's like watching a lame play.
And we lose if the cook's head
gets knocked into our ring...
Here they come! Run for it, ya know!
Oh, Boss! Come back!
Five seconds to go!
But maybe we should take him
up on his offer! You know?
Wh-What's happening?!
I-Incredible!
Can Team Straw Hat win back
the reindeer they lost in Round 1?!
I-Is that...?!
The gigantic Big Pan was falling over,
but is now upright again!
Well, as much as I hate to
admit it, it is our only option...
Crush 'em!
Th-There's no need to get that fired up...!
A tremendous kick has kept
Big Pan on his feet and in a daze!
Or will Team Foxy swipe
another crew member?!
It's for Chopper's sake. This is
no time to get hung up on pride.
They're about to clash in Groggy Ring!
What will Pickles do now?!
The whistle is about to sound!
Team Foxy is in a pinch!
Thanks!
A match is a match, though! We won't lose!
Oh! Now Zoro the swordsman charges in!
O-Oh, my! What on earth
happened to Chiqicheetah?!
You're too soft-hearted.
Naturally, he's going after
Big Pan, the ball man!
Wanna know why I would make
an offer that benefits you?
Eighteen members of Team Foxy
are out for going out of bounds!
Let the game begin!
You're not getting past me!
It's because...
...we're the best--!
What will ball man Sanji
do in enemy territory?!
Chiqicheetah left the course
just before the round ended!
Yes!
All right! Let's win Chopper back!
Amazing! They each knocked
nine people clear off the court!
Will he retreat or attack?!
What a conclusion!
Yeah!
Let's do it!
The Straw Hat Dangers come from
behind to win the third round!
Boss!
Ugh! The same number as you?!
There goes "Tackle Machine" Pickles!
Both captains have agreed
to the rule amendment!
I've had enough of you and the ref!
Way to go, Sanji! Way to go, Zoro!
Oh, no! Chiqicheetah!
All right. I'll take care of this myself.
The crowd-- no, the referee-- takes a direct hit!
Straw Hat Dangers, please
select a scorer for each round!
Sling Tackle!
So sorry.
What?!
Sanji the cook is truly fearsome!
I don't care about you!
Wow! Nine people each!
With five rounds, the odd-numbered
rounds of 1, 3, and 5 are key.
H-Hooray!
I'm only after you!
All we gotta do to win is beat you down!
Okay! I'm next!
That was on purpose...!
--What happened?!
--What's the deal?!
It's a ball man battle!
Especially the very first round...
Gum-Gum Slingshot!
Collier...!
Put me in two rounds! Okay?! Okay?!
How dare he... hurt the ref...?!
Okay! Just shut up! I'm trying to think!
Kiwifruits have catnip-like properties.
Red card!
Just like with catnip, the smell of the
plant itself mesmerizes some cats.
Huh?
Wh-What the...?! His skin's all slimy!
Okay, so I'll stick Luffy in
Round #1 and Round #5...
My cards and whistle... They're gone...
Sanji the cook slips and slides
on Big Pan's outstretched arm!
Ten members of Team Foxy
are out for going out of bounds!
All right!
You're a naughty girl.
Cheetahs are cats too,
so I figured it was worth a shot.
It's only natural, though...
But I can't ask too much
out of Nami-san and Usopp...
Couldn't help it. It's an old habit of mine.
All right! A new record!
...for Big Pan is a slippery-skinned
wotan of loach origin!
So that's why he was sniffing Luffy earlier!
Robin-chan.
Wow, another big group is out of the game!
I hate to ask, but could
you switch to Round #3?
What the heck are you doing?!
I'm guessing so.
But Team Foxy finally has one of the balls!
Sure. Any round is fine with me.
Excellent thinking, Cook!
Run-and-gun!
Now it's my turn!
Thanks-- Oh, wait.
You idiot!
Oh! It was nothing!
Oh! What's this?!
Get 'em, Chopper!
Knock eleven out for a new record!
Could the other team have the same idea?
Who are you calling an idiot?!
Is Team Straw Hat arguing again,
in front of the lone Big Pan?!
In which case...
Okay! You got it!
Come on! Hurry up!
Punk Pass!
Okay! All set!
Whew, just barely made it...
Luffy has Rounds #1 and #5. Nami-san has #2.
The Straw Hat Dangers have
scored a point of their own!
Armée de l'Air Power Shoot!
Usopp has #3, and Robin-chan has Round #4!
But the Foxy Devils still have the advantage!
There it is! Big Pan's super-long pass!
Hold on! Why do you get to decide that?!
There's no time to bask in the
afterglow of victory, though!
Huh? 'Cause I'm the coach
and you're the manager, duh.
Sanji!
It's time for Round #4 to begin!
I-Incredible!
Oh! Our very own Hamburg
has fended off the attack!
Their leader, Hamburg,
makes for the landing point!
Big Pan...
--What?!
--No way!
The scorers will be Nico Robin the archaeologist
Screw that! Why do I have
to take orders from you?!
...the gigantic wotan...
Team Foxy now has both balls!
It's finally time to fight back!
With Roronoa Zoro racing by his side!
versus Jube the fishman!
...is airborne!
Isn't it obvious?!
I'll chop you up if they score a goal!
A great match-up, indeed!
You can't be coach with all that
moss seeping into your brain!
Go!
Well done, Hamburg!
They're headed for the goal ring!
Shut up! Quit your whining!
Listen up, Luffy! When you reach a curve...
Your eyebrow's funnier than you are.
Looks like coiled poop.
--Give the balls to Big Pan!
--Right!
No!
I got it! I'm fine now!
Sweeping Tackle!
Eep!
Poop?!
What do you mean "fine"?
You screwed up just a second ago...
There's one more very important
thing to keep in mind!
Pickles enters enemy territory!
Get 'em, Big Pan! Send 'em all flying!
Meanwhile, can Hamburg
catch Sanji in the air?!
Don't you remember, Zoro? You told
me to watch everyone else earlier...
Knock it off! I can't hear him!
Yes! And then...!
Be aware that going in reverse
or leaving the course
Gorilla Throw!
Whoever he hits is a dead man! A goner!
will result in immediate disqualification!
He's definitely going to shoot that beam again.
Goal!
I got it! I got it!
Waiting for him now is Pickles!
Yeah. That Idiot-Idiot Beam is bad news.
Starting before the whistle
means disqualification, too!
Get back here! I'll teach you to...!
--Idiot-Idiot Beam...?!
--B-Boss!
Roronoa moves to intercept, but...!
All right, everything appears
to be set! The first round pits...
Usopp! Hear me out!
Spinning Tackle!
What is it?
Oh! It's a clash between two big shots!
Straw Hat Luffy versus Porche-chan!
You're a wicked one, all right!
What?!
Ball man Sanji is sent flying skyward, too!
This looks to be a heated
battle from the very start!
Oh, no!
I-Incredible!
Good idea, huh?!
Now let's get underway!
Wh-What is this?!
Sanji!
Oh! Does the heartless Nami
have a secret plan?!
Bringing up the rear is Big Pan!
Talk about exciting!
He's airborne!
Long-nose and 22 Team Foxy members
are out for going out of bounds!
--I love these races!
--Me too!
Her dishonest face is on par
with that of our own boss!
He rushes for the falling Hamburg!
Go!
Punk Receive!
Porche-chan! Beat that rubber dude senseless!
Who're you calling dishonest?!
No!
Hamburg catches Sanji above
enemy territory! Incredible!
You.
Check it out!
Usopp! Are you all right?!
I-I'm somehow still alive...
Wha...?! Wh-What in the world?!
They're within range of the ring!
I got the ball now...
You can't be serious...!
Big Pan took out Usopp,
the long-nosed sniper, with his power throw,
Stupid Eyebrows!
Here it comes! The Hamburger Dunk!
It goes in! Goal! Goal! Goal!
Th-This is hard...
but wound up knocking out a slew
of his own teammates in the process!
Nice, Zoro! Sanji-kun!
Team Foxy is down to two players!
It's time for Round #4!
A-Am I seeing things?!
Wh-What are you--?!
All right! Zoro! Sanji! You're awesome!
Have their superior numbers
backfired on them?!
Zoro! Sanji! Do something!
I don't see it! I don't see anything at all!
You bums actually did it!
Is it about to end already?!
This doesn't bode well!
Got ya good earlier, huh?
Don't need to tell me...!
What will they do now?!
Ready! Go!
Y-You did it!
Aww! But I don't wanna give Choppy back!
Oh, my! He can't skate at all!
I ain't gonna... let 'em score!
Zoro! Sanji! Way to go!
And according to the roster, Straw Hat
Luffy plans to skate in two rounds!
Oh, no, you don't!
I'm no Chiqicheetah, but I'm
pretty fast too, ya know!
Whoa! They're awesome!
Is this game already over?!
Bravo! Bravo!
I'm totally moved to tears!
Are you serious?! This'll be a cinch!
Twenty seconds are up! Defense, go!
You ain't gonna score!
You guys really are the best!
I'm still in tip-top shape!
Upsy-daisy...
I-Is Luffy gonna be okay?!
You dimwits! Who the heck
praises their enemy?!
I can't let that damn swordsman snub me...
--What now, Boss?
--Whadya mean, "What now?"
Now what do we do?
...by saving...
I can't believe this! No one
defeats the Groggy Monsters...!
Wait... Does this mean the third round's
gonna be extra important now?!
I can't use my Slow-Slow Beam as long
as that archeologist chick is there...
...my hide!
So there's only one thing to do...
Oh, hi, Ref. Wakey-wakey.
You mean... you-know-what?
Hurry and blow the whistle! Go on!
Yes. You-know-what.
--Yes!
--Way to go, Luffy!
No goal!
O-Oh, right.
His behavior toward me was a flagrant foul!
Bring it on anytime! I'll give you
another taste of my Mucha Caramente!
He's outta the game!
Oh, my! Now Hamburg is out of the game too!
No, you won't!
And there's the final whistle!
Nice, Robin!
The top of the head doesn't count!
The Groggy Ring match is over!
No goal!
No, Page 103, Article 54 states
that the top of the head does count.
It looks like ball man Sanji isn't going
to pass through the goal so easily!
Oh! Is he finally in fighting form?!
Both teams are finally at the starting line,
but will this even be much of a race?!
She's correct.
Straw Hat Luffy sends Jube flying!
Don't do anything shameful!
Do you want to be beheaded?!
It's time to begin!
You did it!
Mind your own damn business!
Go, Robin! I'll take care of this guy!
I can't believe you asked to be in two rounds!
Hurray! We won!
Sorry...
Wow! Robin has a sharp mind!
You get thrown around too easy, idiot!
Right!
Way to go! Zoro! Sanji!
It's not my fault! I didn't think it was this hard!
Has she memorized the entire thick
rule book in such a short time?!
A duo as powerful as the
Groggy Monsters has appeared!
Thanks for your hard work!
You're amazing, Robin!
We have an epic game on our hands!
It's over! It's all over!
I haven't read all of it yet, though.
We have no choice, though.
We'll have to pick up the slack.
This has never happened before!
This is unprecedented!
All right! Just one left!
Okay, it's time! Scorers, get in position!
In Round #2 of the Davy Back Fight,
Finish 'em off, Sanji-kun!
These behemoths were sent
flying through the air!
Hey! Not you again!
Team Straw Hat has
unbelievably snatched victory away
Yes, Nami-san!
The crowd is stunned!
Team Straw Hat is formidable!
You'll have hell to pay if you
try any funny stuff again!
Sanji-kun!
from the previously
undefeated Groggy Monsters!
Huh?! My baton is gone!
Yes?!
I don't need you to give me backup!
There's no need for "funny stuff";
it's already clear we're going to win!
Please don't hit him...!
So sorry!
Give us the ball, okay?
Oh! How could you?!
It's only 'cause I can't count on you!
It's time for the third game:
the Run Roller Round!
--Of course!
--Ack!
--They're amazing!
--They actually threw Pickles!
Of course we won!
Zoro and Sanji would never lose!
Thanks!
Now please get out of the game!
Okay, Twirly Eyebrow Man?
Will Straw Hat Luffy emerge
from Round #1 victorious?!
They sent Hamburg-san flying!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
Or will it be our own Porche-chan?!
I'd stay down if I were you!
Did you see that?! Did you fall for me?!
My pleasure! Please hit me wherever you like!
Okay...!
On your marks! Get set!
You were wonderful!
You jerks! Don't scare me like that!
Incredible! The Straw Hat Dangers are on a roll!
What are you doing, Sanji-kun?!
--Who asked for your help?!
--You get tossed around too much!
That hurts.
There she goes! Porche-chan
starts off with a spectacular dash!
They've taken a one-lap lead!
You did great! You did just what I said!
Oh, no! What are you doing, Hamburg?!
You didn't do a thing.
We'll just see about that!
Meanwhile, Straw Hat Luffy is...
Hamburg! Prepare for a full dash!
Oh! Love Hunter Sanji has been
blissfully and passionately knocked out!
Lose and you'll regret it!
...flat on his face!
Are you an idiot, Pervert Cook?!
He's collapsed before even
crossing the starting line!
Right!
Now that Team Straw Hat has
won Round #2's Groggy Ring game,
Get ready, Usopp!
I do things my way, Twirly Eyebrows!
He's the second Straw Hat out of the game!
You're nothing--
That was an impressive fall...
Yeah! I dub it "Operation
Laugh and Fall"! Ready?!
Just shut up and do what I say!
they're allowed to swipe either a
member of the Foxy Pirates' crew
Bye-bye!
Stupid things!
You're a real idiot for someone so green!
Whoa, now! Removing your skates
will mean instant disqualification!
Okay!
You mellorine moron!
or the Foxy Pirates' symbol!
Oh, but Team Straw Hat is acting strangely!
He never changes...
Still, their boss is the only one left.
Darn it!
Who does the Straw Hat captain want?!
Although the game is still going
with both ball men in bounds,
You never know for sure, until the very end.
Oh! I can just grab those--!
the two teammates are
arguing instead of playing!
Precisely.
Lousy Split-Head! Shootin' your
Idiot-Idiot Beam again, huh?!
They're funny!
Ooh! This is too easy!
Huh? What is that?
Zoro! Sanji! You idiots!
Huh?
Twenty seconds have passed!
It's time to let the defenders loose!
What are you doing?! Now's your chance!
Split-Head?! Idiot-Idiot Beam?!
There it is! The top-secret
item of Hit and Dead Ball!
Isn't it obvious?
The other ball man's all alone!
He's not like that! He's an
intelligent, handsome man!
Masshikaku!
Gang up on him and knock him into the ring!
Huh?! Is it me...?
Say hello to the Mr. Accu-Cannon!
Huh?
Don't listen to her, you stupid fox!
Hey! He's about to get pinned! Help him!
They wanted me from the very start...!
No, I'm serious! I'm head over heels for you!
Are you crazy?!
Big Pan goes in for a surprise attack!
Oh, man... I'm not ready to go yet...
No one would like you, Crappy Split-Head!
Hey! You're just gonna allow that, Ref?!
It's clearly against the rules!
Crap, it must be me! Our eyes just met...!
He added "Crappy" to "Split-Head"...!
Whoa...!
Wha...?
Too Bad Dance!
So handsome!
That's the Mr. Accu-Cannon?
--Split-Head!
--Handsome!
I bet it'll be me...
What's with that "I already knew
about it" reaction of yours?!
--Split-Head!
--I'm in love!
What are you running for?! He's the ball man!
All lies!
Gum-Gum Balloon!
Could be me!
I didn't know what it was referring to,
but I came across it in the rule book.
Split-Head! Split-Head--!
That's it! Now, Usopp!
If he chooses me, I'll say goodbye
to these guys with a smile...
Yeah, we know! But hang on,
he has blades under his shoes!
Huh?
What are you doing, Nami?!
You need to compliment him!
H-Hey!
Yes! Rule 322: the only weapon
allowed is the Mr. Accu-Cannon!
They like me, I just know it...
Listen! We're gonna keep
knocking you forward!
I can't go on... It's making me sick...
Don't you dare exhale, Luffy!
Is that really a rule?
Hey, Ref!
Switch places with me...
Talk about low!
What happened to "no weapons allowed"?!
It's so cool! I like it!
Why, you... How dare you?!
Come on, Luffy... Hurry...
Cien Fleurs! Delphinium!
This is stupid!
Hey! Bringing that thing out now
still ain't gonna help you!
I can't think of any nice things to say...
--Okay! I choose--!
--Hold on!
--All right! Let's just keep repeating stuff!
--Right!
I wouldn't be so sure.
Whoa! Can you be any more blatant?!
What is it, Nami?
--You're manly! You're manly!...
--Split-Head! Split-Head!...
Porche! Are you ready?!
Their boss will probably take
part in the next round, right?
Robin!
If he misses a play, it's out of his hands!
Sure am, Boss!
--It's her again!
--Awesome!
He can't fire his Slow-Slow Beam!
Yeah...
Here goes!
What speed!
Has our boss been KOed by
this ingenious verbal assault?!
With that Slow-Slow Beam of his,
Quit screwing around, Ref!
Flower Hypnosis!
we won't stand a chance in any game,
no matter what the rules are!
He's well on his way to
catching up with Porche-chan!
Time is nearly up!
Crap!
It's hypnosis! Don't look!
But if we take him now,
we'll have the upper hand in Round 3!
Oh, no!
Flower Shurikens!
Always pulling these tricks on us...
Hold on, Sanji-kun!
You saw the whole thing!
Why are you sweatin' like a waterfall?!
Now, Boss!
All right!
If we take Chopper back now
but lose in this next round,
You're all mine!
Oh, no!
I-I didn't s-see a th-thing...
Amazing! I've never witnessed
a race like this before!
--Manly! Manly! Manly!...
--Split-Head! Split-Head!...
they could just steal him again!
Having your eyes open or closed...
Liar!
But the Foxy Devils have some serious defense!
--Split-Head!
--Manly!
Hey, hold on! He's the ref, you know!
In which case, taking their boss now
--Split-Head!
and playing the next game in tip-top condition
Incredible! Just incredible!
Yellow card to Sanji of Team Straw Hat!
I'm a wall...
...makes no difference to a swordsman.
is the best way to get
Chopper back and keep him.
The Straw Hat Dangers win
Round #4 by a landslide!
Say what?!
W-Wait! Wait! Wait!
U-U-Unbelievable! Is he going to
call for the Foxy Pirates' captain?!
Incredible! What power!
And there's the yellow warning card!
Oh! But he clears the wall with a skillful toss!
Swordsman Zoro sliced the ball in two
with his bare hands and with his eyes closed!
Is it only a matter of time
until he catches Porche-chan?!
One more and Sanji the cook
will get a red ejection card!
Th-That's the Peanut Strategy!
Oh, no...
Zoro of Team Straw Hat is out!
There'll now be a five-minute break
before the final round begins!
You guys are the lowest!
Nice, Robin-chan!
What for?!
I'll eject you!
Nope!
You lousy Peanutters!
Rule 645!
I can't believe he's scummy
enough to attack the referee!
Fight us fair and square!
No slicing the balls!
I can't believe I fell for that childish trick!
Killer Sword Festival!
There's no rule against it,
Team Foxy gets a new ball.
Shut up! I oughta knock you off!
Or that this would drag out to the final round!
but suddenly calling out an opponent's
leader after the second round
What?!
He's a gangster!
We can't lose the next one!
Too bad!
is an obvious attempt at avoiding
a fair-and-square, head-on match!
We'll use you-know-what to win for sure!
We gotta do something about his weapons...
The plan?!
Oh, what a shame!
Swordsman Zoro is out of the game!
Hold on! You're allowing that now?!
What a turn of events!
All right! Let's win this thing!
I can't believe my ears! This is the
devilish idea of an inhuman woman!
The final round is about to begin!
Straw Hat Luffy has gone outside the course!
Zoro...
--I just happen to be looking away...
--No way!
--He cut him!
Both teams, to the starting line!
...got knocked out of the game...
Her name is Nami, the heathen navigator!
--Look out there, Ref!
You okay, Luffy?!
Oh! The Foxy Devils' scorer,
Girarin, is all alone!
That idiot's using an axe now! An axe!
Crappy swordsman...
How dare you insult Nami-san?!
I oughta filet you!
You got knocked out first, lousy cook.
No! Stop! You can't afford to get ejected!
All the others are off the track!
Rest easy! My Killer Swords don't cut!
Things are really getting good now!
It's two against one!
Could they be planning to
unleash that huge technique?!
In the long history of Davy Back Fights,
Are you kidding me?! I can't let
'em get away with this insanity!
They're all show!
no one has ever tried to
pull this wretched trick!
I-I don't feel so good...
Huge technique?
Don't you see?! They want you to get mad!
What kind of bragging is that?
Just gonna be another Idiot Beam, obviously.
Let me ask you all! Is a win against
a leaderless team a true victory?!
--Just let it go!
--I won't!
Oh, my. How did you know?
Pull yourself together!
This is for Chopper's sake!
Now to pick up where I left off!
This is bad...
All right! Then I'll beat him up!
Yes. This tactic is all about getting
the Slow-Slow Beam to hit its mark.
Luffy's in the fifth round, so me,
Usopp, and Robin all have to win...
Yeah! Give us your best shot!
No!
Don't go complicating things!
After swearing to Davy Jones
to hold a fair match,
Chopper might not be
the only one at risk now...!
Bring it on!
Sanji-kun! Just beat 'em!
is it okay to turn it into a lie?!
Ultra-fast Level 5!
But knowing that still won't help ya!
"Pose of Love"
You got it!
No!
The winner of the first round is Porche-chan!
Let's see you dodge this!
--Peanuts! Peanuts! Peanuts!...
--I hate them...
As if! Weren't you paying attention last time?!
You don't make any sense...
All right! Back to the game!
Even if it doesn't go against the rules,
One point to the Foxy Devils!
We have Operation Laugh and Fall!
it seems it would go against pirate aesthetics.
Darn it!
Don't worry, Luffy! Just skate like crazy!
Peanuts! Peanuts! Peanuts! Peanuts!...
Just get down from there!
Yeah! Leave it to me!
All right! Let's move right along!
You didn't have to start with that again!
What's with them?! They're making me mad!
Okay, it's time!
The second round match-up
pits the heartless Navigator Nami
This is gettin' us nowhere!
Ready! Go!
I'm with Nami on this!
But we can change our game plan
now that we know they've got weapons!
Their reaction's only natural.
You're in the wrong, Nami.
against the King of Defense,
the Human Wall: Masshikaku!
Oh! Choppy!
It's time to take him out!
What a beautiful self-sacrifice
by ship's doctor Chopper!
Will you shut up already?! Quit actin' cocky!
What?! Already?!
Stay out of my way! I can handle him myself!
I just have to give it everything I've got!
--Manly! Manly! Manly!...
--Split-Head! Split-Head!...
Our apologies!
--But this means...!
--The face doesn't count, right?
Still, like it or not, Monkey D. Luffy,
captain of the winning team,
Work together! You're a team, you know!
Round #2!
On your marks! Get set!
And there they go!
All three are about to collide!
F-Face?
gets to decide how this game will unfold!
I-it's extremely difficult to tell
where his face begins and ends!
Slow-Slow Beam!
There it is! A barrage of Slow-Slow Beams!
Can't attack where his skin
is exposed! He's too slippery!
He's free to choose anyone
he wants from Team Foxy!
And they're off!
Talk about brave!
Oh, but what a shock!
Why isn't Operation Laugh and Fall working?!
Hey, Ref! You're a man of the sea too,
ain't ya?! That was his face!
He'll choose me, I just know it...
Masshikaku is slow!
That leaves his hands,
feet, mask, and trunks...
I bet an adventure with them would be fun...
Like, really slow!
Yeah! That furry fella has some serious guts!
The heartless Nami quickly increases her lead!
Huh? Did you say somethin'?!
Loach Scooping Slide!
It's obvious I'm the only choice here...
You ain't men if you can't see that!
Crap!
It hit his face! It hit his face! It hit his face!...
What's with this guy? Is he even trying to win?
Earplugs!
No, don't look at me! Please! Don't!
Loach Racing Circus!
The Straw Hat Dangers have been bested!
That's our boss for you!
What the...?
What is this?! What's going on?!
Is he gonna choose me? These guys are cool!
There it is! The Racing Circus acrobatics!
C-Crap!
It hit his face! It hit his face! It hit his face!...
Is this some sort of tactic?!
Forget about him, Nami! Just keep movin'!
Is it me? Is he gonna pick me?!
Both opponents slide across his wide back!
We "ain't men"...?
Ha! Won't work this time!
I can handle a little skating!
Right!
Wha...?! It's gonna be me, huh?!
There's the second whistle!
I can't just ignore that!
Is it me, or do the Idiot Beams
bounce off that guy?!
Now they can't escape!
Let's do it, Robin!
The call is clear as day!
It hit his face! He's safe!
Straw Hat... You're...
Oh! You noticed?
--So dizzy...!
--Come on, you guys!
Slow-Slow Beams don't work on Girarin!
All right!
Wh-What are they doing?!
Meanwhile, the other two players
have gotten back into the game!
However...!
Oh, really? Why not?
However...?
Just try and get through, if you dare.
--Oh! They're back in it!
--Slaughter 'em!
Oh, I'm afraid that's a secret!
Although it hit you in the face,
you're unfortunately still out of bounds!
You're going to choose me, aren't you?!
Not even water can get past us!
Oh? Their attire is a little different now!
Little late to be playin' roadblocks!
We're the ones in the lead...
Oh, a secret? That's what I thought!
Yes, yes... It's obvious you are!
Oh, my! He's regrettably out of bounds!
Hamburg, their leader, is wearing
iron knuckles and iron elbow guards!
Wh-What's with you guys?! Move!
That's why you're already off the course, huh?
Farewell, Foxy Pirates.
Farewell, wonderful crew!
Just after his gutsy face
catch was given the okay!
Wait! Don't push yourself, Luffy!
Meanwhile, Pickles has donned
spiked shoulder protectors!
That's right. All your guys are gonna
turn into slowpokes, but not us!
When he picks me, I'll say goodbye
to them with a smile on my face...
We're gonna win if things stay as they are!
What a pity! Ship's doctor
Chopper is out of the game!
These clearly violate the "no weapons" rule!
Oh, having such a marvelous personality
and beautiful looks is a sin!
And they can't hide behind us!
Oh, but the referee just happens
to have his back turned right now
Even so, he's still a true man of the sea!
Yes, maybe!
Choppy!
So that's their deal! This is bad! Really bad!
as he does some stretches!
That's definitely something
the Straw Hat Pirates lack!
You okay, Chopper?
Twenty seconds are up! Defenders, go!
Flower Hypnosis!
Yeah... But I'm out of the game now...
Oh, there's no doubt they like me!
Now I'm mad, Leader!
Say, Navigator.
Your proposal does give us
an overwhelming advantage,
Time for you all to slow down!
Here goes!
Just leave the rest to me!
Loach Coaster!
But never mind that. Thanks, Chopper.
but that also makes their boss part of our crew.
No!
Nami-san!
Direct hit!
Hearing that doesn't make
me happy at all, you jerk!
Everything's spinning...!
No, thanks.
Let's do it, Leader!
Navigator Nami and Sniper Usopp
have fallen prey to the Slow-Slow Beam!
Yeah!
Spinning Tackle!
Not bad, Choppy! Now I
wanna have you even more!
Our boss has sunk into the ground
from the weight of his feelings!
The recovered players counterattack!
But their target isn't the ball man--
it's the swordsman Roronoa!
I can't believe they all
rejected our boss like that!
I won't let you take him!
What...?
They're sniping him with the iron knuckles!
Luffy! Look out behind you!
It's now one against one!
Both teams have their backs to the wall!
Oh, Boss! It's okay! We need you!
We were asleep?!
Hamburger Hammer!
So it would seem...
They finally got Straw Hat Luffy!
It's the final showdown!
We do, Boss!
Luffy! Get up! Hey!
Is victory a near-certainty now?!
G-Guys...
Zoro!
Let's teach these guys a lesson!
Take my advice and lose like a good little boy!
The attack isn't over yet! Big Pan
instantly takes an attack stance!
But things still look the same... right?
That just leaves you!
Yeah! I can't wait for the next round!
I can't risk it! We'll be
done for if that beam hits me!
We love you, Boss!
I absolutely won't lose!
Yes...
Hamburg prepares to use
his iron elbow guards!
Boss!
Nami! Hurry!
What nonsense!
Guys...
Hurry up!
Take a good look around you
before you spew such drivel!
Yes! You are my only true comrades!
--No way!
--It can't be...
--You need to get moving!
--Five!
This is truly dangerous! A horrifying combo!
Here it comes! The Omni-Directional Shift!
--Huh? Why?
--Four! Three!
Thank you!
Cut the crap, will ya?
Two!
Boss!
Say your prayers!
One!
He's almost like...
Now that Team Straw Hat's
harassment of our boss has ended,
...an arrow!
Yikes! What the heck?!
Oh! What's this?!
Hey! What's the deal, old ref!
What's with all those balls?!
it's time to pick someone!
Team Foxy wins two rounds in a row!
Punk Attack!
Who will he choose?!
Nico Robin was keeping the
Straw Hat Dangers in the game!
Victory is already within reach!
There's no rule whatsoever
against using fake balls.
That can't be...!
And now... she's given up?
They did a full lap while we were asleep...?
I knew it. You really are on Foxy's side.
She's exited the course of her own
accord with only one minute left!
All right, then. I wanna take back...
Damn! They'll always have the upper
hand unless we get a ref of our own!
Yep! Sucks to be you!
Don't worry, Luffy! Only you
and their boss have a real ball!
The Slow-Slow Beam lasts for 30 seconds...
...Shelly!
I can't believe we beat 'em with Masshikaku!
Zoro!
If Luffy can dodge the next attack,
he'll still have a chance...!
It connects! Direct hit!
Don't let him fool you!
Is this for real...?!
Ack! That's right!
Note that deaths in Groggy Ring are
to be expected and are of no concern.
Failure isn't an option!
What's with this guy? Is his brain split too?!
Team Foxy scores twice in a row!
Luffy's team is in a real pinch!
Wh-What's this?!
I have to wait for my chance!
So... dizzy...
Captain Monkey D. Luffy has
chosen Shelly, Tonjit's former horse!
My brain... split too...
The third round is now a crucial one!
Team Foxy isn't ready to stop its attack yet!
What's going on, Robin-chan?
It pits long-nosed Usopp against
Chiqicheetah the speedster!
Oh! Then I'll just send that
entire Mr. Neato Thing sky-high!
I can avoid those beams by staying here, right?
Human...
What in the world is he thinking?!
Cannon!
Ugh... I feel sick...
Do you know what you just said,
you dumb captain?!
M-My chronic sickness--
Robin-chan...?
The spiked shoulder protector draws near!
Here goes!
Don't give us any crap about
a "Can't Race Anyone" disease!
Forty seconds remain!
Girarin has an easy, three-lap lead!
Sanji! Get out of the way!
Of course.
Huh?
Eep...
Seriously! What are you thinking?!
Try this on for size!
Urgh! You always pull this nonsense!
Sling Tackle!
Umm, could you not pull my face?
Ouch...!
They're setting up Sanji the ball man now!
Are you kidding me? Chiqicheetah is a cheetah!
Time for another dose, just to be safe!
Looks like you're staying with us, Choppy!
Huh?
Size Attack: S!
--I don't stand a chance...
--Oww.
Oh! Right over here!
Hamburg sends him flying back!
They're not preparing to score at all!
No. Relax more and use your hips.
You stretched your arm too far!
Wha...?!
If you weren't going to take their boss,
All right, everyone! Shuffle!
M!
then you should've chosen Chopper!
You've skated before?
It's been fun, Straw Hat Luffy...
But...!
--No, but just watch how the others do it!
--Can't expect much help...
...but this is the end!
Shuffle! Shuffle! Shuffle! Shuffle!...
L!
--Stand with your legs spread out more!
--What I need is a strategy...
Thirty seconds left!
The Groggy Monsters unleash
a spectacular team attack!
Victory is guaranteed if he can hit
Straw Hat Luffy with another beam!
Old stilts guy. I took Shelly
back from those guys.
Like this? Oww...
--No!
--Like this?
You guys...
--Oww!
--No!
Now you can always be together.
Oh, no! Now we can't tell
which is real and which are fake!
Like this?
--Ouch!
--No! Listen to me, dammit!
Say, what happened to you two in the back?
You're really hurt. Are you okay?
On your marks!
--Get set!
--Nothing comes to mind...!
End of the line!
Some idiot with crazy eyebrows
slowed me down, that's all.
All right, whatever! I'll just go
as fast as I possibly can!
Huh?!
They're certainly full of life...
Once again, which one is the real deal?!
You'll need to figure it out
before it hits you, though!
Crap!
Shut up! It doesn't matter
as long as I catch all the balls!
Oh! I'm in the lead?!
Skate, Luffy! There's no time!
I appreciate it. Thank you...
Don't get snarky with me!
It's nothin'. Don't worry about it!
So fast!
All right!
You're one sore loser, you know that?!
No one's a match for Chiqicheetah's speed!
All right, men! Throw like crazy!
That's a good girl!
He doesn't need any support, ya know!
Twenty seconds left!
Damn! It's hopeless after all?!
Well, that explains that.
Guess it couldn't be helped this time!
No way! A full lap already?!
Mucha Cara...
Let me treat you all! How about
some cheese at my place?
Maybe you two should sit back and relax too?
No, no more of that!
You're...
It's not over until it's over!
...finished!
Twenty seconds are up! Defense, go!
Luffy! Look out!
I truly appreciate this.
Just terrible...
Grilled or deep-fried... Which do you prefer?
--Let's go, Robin!
--Yes!
Luffy! Let it hit your face!
Zoro!
Thank you.
My! How admirable!
D-Damn!
You're a heartless monster!
Sanji!
D-Damn...!
I'm glad for you, old guy!
He's already back?!
Are you sure about this, though?
Your friend is still...
Take this!
Looks like Team Straw Hat
isn't getting up from this!
Yes!
Yeah, Luffy! You need to
consider Chopper's feelings too!
Piece o' cake!
Ten seconds left!
Straw Hat Luffy is moving at incredible speed!
The opponents literally are "groggy"!
All right!
This could turn into a mad dash for the finish!
--Oh...
--Oh?!
All that remains now is to stuff
the ball man into his ring coffin
Luffy...
Chopper...
and this will be two wins in a row!
Sorry, Chopper!
Straw Hat Luffy is out!
We will win the next game and get you back!
The undefeated Groggy Monsters
are supremely powerful!
That's it.
What for?! Getting hit
in the face doesn't count!
Now do it just like I explained!
Oh! Our boss slowed himself down!
So just hang on a little more!
We win again!
Oh! Is he gonna make it?!
You're a man, right?!
Rule 999! No swallowing the balls!
Just a little more! You can do it!
Got a problem with that?
Five seconds left!
It's right there in the rule book!
That's it! Stand up, Luffy!
Swords that can't cut...
Nope!
...won't work on me!
He's right. It's on the very last page.
Hey, cook...
Chopper...
Leave it to me! It'll be just fine!
A l-lousy rule like that...?
Lend me a hand for ten seconds...
--Oh!
--I'm so moved!
Yeah, sure. Uh-huh.
Totally!
The Straw Hat Dangers
come from behind to win!
I wonder what the next game will be.
Luffy!
Team Foxy emerges victorious in
Round #1's game of Hit and Dead Ball!
Sounds like... a reasonable length of time...
All right! I'm up! Hang on, Usopp!
Let's get started!
We will win Chopper back!
Yes!
Hang on, Chopper!
Stupid!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
We pray to this endless
sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Round #3 is the Roller Skate Race!
A five-round match on a track!
Straw Hat Luffy has finally found his footing!
Round #2 is that game from my childhood!
--Thank you, Luffy!
--You know we'd never lose!
Hold on! They're clearly using weapons now!
All right! I'm not gonna lose now!
This is a pirate game! All weapons
and obstacles are allowed!
--Hey, Prince Moron!
--Come on, you wimpy swordsman!
As a pirate, I refuse this outcome!
I challenge you to extra rounds!
But standing is all you can do!
They'll take me if we lose! Because I'm cute!
Can't this idiot who's inferior to me
in every way do something?!
--Go get 'em, Zoro and Sanji!
--You're a member too!
You gotta be kidding-- Oww!
--Ugh, I can't stand them!
--Forget it. This is the way men are.
But that cheetah and the others are back!
--Are you an idiot?!
--Id--?!
Don't be sneakin' insults in!
You're absolutely no
match for us! For you see...!
Who'd agree to more of these lame games?!
Wait! I know just how to turn the tables on 'em!
Me and Nami are too weak and scary anyway!
--Okay, guys! Let's get Chopper back!
--Yeah!
All right! You're on!
They're funny!
Zoro-kun? That's a scary look! Stay away!
Come on! This is for Chopper!
Pull yourselves together!
Look forward to seeing me in action!
What a surprise.
Ignored again...?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Screaming-Hot Bombardment!
Pirate Dodgeball!"
"A Seriously Heated Race!
Into the Final Round!"
"A Barrage of Red Cards in Groggy Ring!"
"Showdown on the Cliff!
Red Light, Green Light!"
"Round 3! The Round-and-Round Roller Race!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
Huh? Zoro's lost again?!