It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
That's it!
Team Foxy wins yet again in the
second round of this second fight!
I never thought of that!
Luffy and friends have agreed...
Now you've lost two crewmates.
In the right corner, hailing from East Blue!
...to another Davy Back Fight
with the Foxy Pirates.
One game remains, and you can only
take back one crew member at most.
The leader of a miniscule pirate band
with a 100 million-Berry bounty...
Despite putting up a good fight,
Luffy soon found himself all alone.
So, even if you do beat me in this next game,
The final round of the
Davy Back Fight is underway.
..."Straw Hat" Monkey D. Luffy!
The epic battle between the two captains...
you've already lost one crewmate for good!
...has finally reached a climax!
"The Captains Square Off!
The Final Combat Round!"
Wow! The afroed Luffy is all
fired up in the right corner!
Luffy...!
Straw Hat Luffy is out!
I've finally found some...
I won't... let you have...
a single member of my crew...
Wha...?!
Lookin' sharp, Luffy!
Some people with such nice memories...
Now then, Boss!
Choose your bounty, if you please!
Team Foxy emerges victorious in
Round #1's game of Hit and Dead Ball!
...even if it costs me my life!
Are you kidding me?
There's the starting bell!
--Let's do it!
--Yeah!
"Epic, Heated Combat!
The Fateful Final Conclusion"
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
"Showdown on the Cliff!
Red Light, Green Light!"
You're the second one I choose!
Oh, Choppy! I won't leave you ever again!
Our Foxy Pirates have claimed victory
in Round #1 of this second fight!
Only my fist is slow!
With great drive, Straw Hat Luffy
gets back on his feet yet again!
Robin!
Nine-Tails Rush!
It's time to claim our booty...
--Even after countless knockdowns...
--Luffy...!
Don't cry, Doctor.
...and take one member of Team Straw Hat!
...he just gets right back up!
Who will our boss choose?!
--The one I want...
--...is obvious to us all! Right, Boss?
Just what are you?!
Hey, things are looking pretty bad!
What are we gonna do, Luffy?!
Oh...! I wouldn't ride that one if I were you...
Don't worry! We'll just do
another Davy Back Fight!
Luffy!
You!
He's unsteady on his feet!
The archaeologist, Nico Robin!
Oh, or that one.
Another one?
Luffy!
And he's out of breath!
Forget it.
Me?
This guy is incredible!
Oh, my! Our captain has chosen
Nico Robin, the archaeologist!
Say, shall I tell you why we Foxy Pirates
are known as the mightiest of all?
And yet...
Told you so!
...he still stands tall with a glimmer in his eye!
Oh, Captain! You naughty man!
Oh, no! Why didn't you choose Choppy, Boss?!
--Heh. Says they're the mightiest.
--After losing to us twice.
All for his friends!
She's dangerous as an enemy.
Yes! Now this is a Davy Back Fight!
Don't be like that...
Taking her first will give us
the advantage from here on out.
I'm so teary-eyed I... I can't see straight!
We had five three-coin games
with the Fang-Frog Pirates
today before we ran into you.
--Still...!
--We can get Doctor Chopper
for sure in the next round!
Luffy!
Luffy...
Luffy!!
Many of us are hurt. We're exhausted,
both mentally and physically...
Oh, no...!
--I'm moved to tears!
--Afro dude!
Now I get it! You're so smart, Boss!
"Full-Blast Slow-Slow Onslaught
vs. Invulnerable Luffy"
--Robin!
--Robin-chan!
We're ready to call it quits.
Luffy! Luffy! Luffy!...
Bye.
So we won't agree to any more fights,
however much you want one!
A Luffy chant comes up from the crowd!
I can feel the deep sorrow
hidden behind her smile!
Has there ever been any other foe
who's given our boss so much trouble?!
Knowing when enough is enough--
when it's time to quit--
E-Explosions suddenly rock our ship...
The pain of having to part with me...!
is why we're the mightiest!
Damn! How dare they take
Robin-chan against her will,
What do you idiots think you're doing,
cheering the enemy on?!
...which just happens to be the battlefield...
even if it is in the rules?!
Caused by Foxy Face Bombs that
also happened to be loaded...!
Robin!
Wh-Why aren't you saying anything?
--Boss...!
--Boss!
Making their ship the battlefield
is such a dirty trick!
How do I look?
Boss! Boss! Boss! Boss!...
--Suits you perfectly!
--You look great, black-haired lady!
What a joke.
--Hey! Luffy! What's going on?!
--Simmer down!
Acting like you're the
underdogs here... Are you an idiot?!
I wanted you to join us from the very start!
Oh, good morning.
Just you watch. I'll end this now!
Ugh! She's so popular!
Using this to his advantage, our boss succeeded
Is that what you call the "mightiest crew"?
What a bunch of Peanut crap.
in blowing up Straw Hat Luffy
with a cannon attack!
R-Robin's really gettin' along with 'em...
Slow-Slow Beam Sword!
How can you be so laid-back?!
No way! Is Luffy...?!
I never trusted her to begin with...
You'll have to do better than that!
We can't choose between Chopper and Robin!
Is something the matter?
Don't be crazy! Robin is counting on us!
Is it all over for him?! He's nowhere to be seen!
Are we just gonna let 'em keep 'em?!
Damn! He hasn't got
enough strength left to run?!
Who are you?
I think.
Don't be stupid! I'm gonna get both back!
Whew, that was close!
Good point as always, Nami-san.
I can't stand to watch Luffy like this!
What?
And how do you plan to do that?!
Indeed, it was a--!
I'm gonna win her right back in the next round.
"Was It Lost? Stolen? Who Are You?"
Okay! It's time to finish this!
What a pain. Maybe I
should just chop 'em all up...
What?!
Okay! Let's do the next round already!
Slow-Slow Beam!
Quit it! You're annoying!
Uhh, this is a game, you know. A game...
You can't play in the next round, Luffy.
You're in the third round.
Our boss makes the first move!
He starts by slowing down a cannonball!
Straw Hat Luffy is... alive!
Learn the rules already, will ya?
Foxy Fighter!
Hey, "Boss"! I have an offer...
Oh. I guess I'm on cheering duty then.
--Y-You serious?!
--He's mind-boggling!
But there's only five of us for Round #2...
A Megaton Punch with
the speed of a cannonball!
Huh?
He somehow evaded the
close-range cannon barrage!
I can still eat lots more...
It'll knock you out for good!
What do you say we bet
five people on the next game?
There it is! Our boss's cannonball stunt flying!
What speed! I-Is this the true power
of a man worth 100 million?!
Pathetic Straw Hat team!
You've lost more than another member!
--Hey, now! You can't just decide--!
--No, let's leave this to her.
He's going for the finishing blow
aboard the Foxy Fighter!
You've lost a major part of your offense!
--Of course it is!
--Just finish 'im already!
How do you like them grapes, err, apples?!
Come again?
Luffy! He used a beam
on you just before the ball!
Gimme seconds!
Now let's start the next round!
This game is all about taking
crew members you want, right?
Dodge as soon as you can move!
Well, we want those two!
There's no point to this if
we can't get 'em both back.
Huh?!
Round #2 will be a game held on
Long Reef: Dash Touch Domination!
Oh! I can move!
So, if we win the next game,
you'll give them back to us.
The beam wears off on Straw Hat
just a moment sooner!
Or "D.T.D." for short!
And if you win, all five of us
will join your crew too.
It's no use!
Oh! But it looks like our boss's
next attack is already underway!
It's a six-on-six group competition,
There's no escape!
but without Nico Robin, Team Straw Hat
will only have five players!
What do you say? It's a pretty
good deal if you ask me...
The rules are simple!
Luffy! Look out!
This girl has some serious guts
to try and bargain with me...
Basically, it's like the
"Red Light, Green Light" game!
From out of the resulting smoke screen
comes our boss's disturbing laughter!
Move even a muscle after the
"stop light" stops calling and you're out!
Those two clearly have enormous power...
Here's a present for you!
Wh-Where am I?
And who are these people?!
But where exactly is he?!
He got him! All of his attacks nail Straw Hat!
Whichever team touches
the "stop light" first wins!
This one and his strange
implements could be useful...
What does "Silver Fox" Foxy
have up his sleeve this time?!
--Hey.
--Yes?!
And most valuable of all is this
guy worth 100 million Berries!
You know anything about this?
But this is no kid's game!
--Oh!
--There he is!
Luffy!
Keep in mind, this is a pirate
version of "Red Light, Green Light"!
--Huh?
--I'm Sanji.
Boss! Boss! Boss!...
I'm a cook at the Sea Restaurant Baratie.
All right! Two is way too cheap, though!
All weapons are okay to use!
I remember going to sleep in
my room yesterday like always,
What's with him?!
He didn't have to go that far!
D.T.D. is a truly perilous game!
Okay, I hope you're ready!
I'll bet 500 people!
but then I woke up in this strange
place with you complete strangers.
First is Team Straw Hat...
with the same ol' lineup.
You got blown up?!
If you win, I'll give you 500 people,
including those two!
I did not! Don't be stupid!
Leave us alone!
H-H-He's...
Do you know why?!
Team Foxy is led by our idol
Porche-chan and Hamburg the oddball!
Wha...? Why 500?
Liar!
N-N-No...
He's back up!
Don't assume for one minute
you'll leave this battlefield alive!
Oh, my! Our boss has made
the "Hellish 500-Man Wager!"
Huh? What?
I'm going to win Choppy
with my own two hands!
How...?!
You mean you guys didn't save me?
--Slow-Slow Beam--!
--Gum Hook!
Will Straw Hat accept?!
We don't need 500 people!
Are you stupid or something?!
Then there's the ever-swift Chiqicheetah,
the swordfish fishman Capote,
Save?
No more beams for you!
I'm gonna smash your arms!
I'm Luffy.
You idiot!
I left Fusha Village and went sailing,
We're so close to making a deal!
Don't back out now!
as well as "Tackle Machine" Pickles
and Big Pan the wotan,
He disappeared into the smoke again!
but then I ran into this gigantic whirlpool...
who have both vowed revenge
for their Groggy Ring defeat!
The Merry can't carry 500 people!
I remember getting into a
barrel and getting all dizzy...
Huh?! There you are!
Getting Chopper and Robin-chan
back is all that matters!
Those losers will pay for humiliating us!
...and then I suddenly wound up here.
Five or 500, it makes no difference!
Oh.
--A board?!
--Slow-Slow Beam!
I figured you guys had saved me.
Do you accept?
I... win.
These are the six members
of the truly mighty Team Foxy!
Yeah! Of course!
Wh-What's going on here?
Incidentally, should the losing
team not have 500 people,
What?! You're barely
even able to stand upright!
I remember having a silly conversation
with Kaya-chan yesterday,
What's the old stilts guy doing up there?
the remainder will be made up
by the team's descendants.
then playing with Pepper and
the gang before hitting the hay...
I forgot an important detail!
But if that's how you want it...
In other words, your children,
grandchildren, and great-grandchildren
Tonjit the nomad here
will act as the "stop light"!
But I don't remember a thing after that!
...I'll pound you until you stay down!
Now, then! Which one is me?
Where will the beam come from?!
will be forced to swear loyalty to
the Foxy Pirates until the total is met!
The great fool, err, man of bravery
who stood atop stilts for ten whole years,
Megaton Nine-Tails...!
And these guys are the same?!
Gum-Gum...
So, do you know anything?
reaching high into the heavens!
Darn it! How should I know?!
They all look like stupid-heads!
...Rush!
Tonjit is the only logical choice
to be our "stop light"!
Huh?
Do you have any idea why we're here?
...Gatling!
Children...?
I'm seriously sick of heights, though...
Stupid-heads...
I don't know what's going on,
much less who these guys are...
Daddy!
Hold on!
If he's the "stop light," doesn't that
give us a big advantage in D.T.D.?!
Yes! What is it?
There!
Such intensity!
I'll just have to bluff for now...!
They've suddenly added a
strange condition to the mix...
The combatants now exchange an
even more ferocious flurry of punches!
Don't abbreviate it too!
We don't have much of a choice.
All right. I'll tell you.
But Usopp's right! Luck's on our side!
Slaughter 'im, Luffy!
You just have to win! Understand, Luffy?!
It's no surprise you've forgotten
everything up until yesterday.
Beat him!
And you call yourself a
warm-hearted individual?!
You sure about this, Boss?!
Their barrages don't stop!
They just keep going!
Yeah! Leave it to me!
You're in for it now! Look up!
After all, you were attacked
by a legendary giant whale.
It's nothin'! We pirates have to
battle the deep blue sea all the time!
Huh?
It's nice that you're raring to go and all,
but I should warn you now
A legendary giant whale?
Don't sweat the small stuff!
That's right. I defeated it and saved
you guys after it swallowed you.
that it's impossible to beat me
in the final combat round.
--Talk about generous!
--Wow! What a great guy!
I suggest you all ready yourselves!
Crap! A trap door!
That's what you get for being distracted!
Generous, my butt!
What?! I'd never lose to you in a fight!
Wow! Really?! Thanks!
You're the one who told me to look up!
Right off the bat, we're given
a clearly unfair course!
Slow-Slow Beam!
Just who are you?
You might wanna pay more attention!
How many times must I repeat myself?
I'm glad you asked!
Huh?
A fight and a game are two different things...
I'm Usopp, leader of a great pirate crew
that rules the seas of the East Blue!
Wh-What the...?! Whoa! The floor's moving!
Oh...?!
--What the...?
--He stopped moving...
I guess that Idiot-Idiot Beam is his only talent...
It's dragging me away!
I have the people's undying praise!
--Lame Fox!
--Split-Head...
Idiot-Idiot Beam...
"Captain Usopp" is what they call me!
--There's Luffy!
--Why'd he come out of there?!
Foxy!
Lame Fox...
--Split-Head...!
--Boss!
Oh, no! He'll lose if he falls into the water!
At last, it's time for the final combat round!
--Pull yourself together!
--You really take things to heart, Boss.
Wow! Captain Usopp!
I ain't gonna fall in...!
First order of business:
establishing the battlefield!
The two competitors spin the cannon!
First, as the D.T.D. rules state,
both teams must start by calling out...
--You know him?
--No, not at all!
S-Straw Hat has been knocked down!
Better watch what you say.
So close!
And then...
...wherever it stops will be where--!
First step!
No! Strike that!
The Usopp Pirates have 8,000 members--
Nah, it'd be no fun if it ended so soon!
Straw Hat is the one who's moving!
Hold on! That was clearly not normal!
Oh! Team Foxy suddenly takes a big lead!
Hang in there, Straw Hat!
What?! 8,000?!
Just what has transpired?!
Curse... you...
Bastards...!
Incidentally, you're both my
subordinates as of yesterday!
Geez! What's with this ship?!
The battlefield has been set!
This'll be a cinch if we
follow the plan! Let's do it!
How?!
For real?!
By sheer coincidence, it's on
the deck of our own Sexy Foxy!
Where'd you go, fox?!
Boss?!
Yeah!
You're lying.
I'm sure it goes without saying,
--Eep! You could tell?!
--See, you even admit it.
Coincidence, my butt! You idiot!
What's this?!
but there's more to this than rushing
ahead to touch the "stop light"!
A Foxy pin eerily taunts Straw Hat
Luffy after his narrow escape!
A mirror! A mirror fragment
has fallen from Straw Hat's hand!
I'll now explain the rules of combat!
I admitted it! You dirty schemer!
This terrain makes it easy to lose
your balance during a sudden stop,
It was stuck... in my afro...
Everything within 50 meters
of where the cannonball landed
In there!
You're a funny guy!
so we can also expect the
enemy to use that against us!
is part of the battlefield!
The inside of the ship is our boss's
playground! Will Luffy be lured in?!
It's from the mirror in your room!
Hey, you! Don't make fun of me!
In other words, it's a 100-meter-wide circle!
Split-Head! Get in the way
and I won't sit by quietly!
You little...!
I'm a proud man!
No, Luffy! It's totally a trap!
I have so much pride that people
call me "Usopp the Proud"!
Weapons are allowed, as well as
anything else within the circle!
Gum-Gum...
He obviously has a bunch of booby traps set!
Split...
Ha! Like I need to interfere!
This is going to be a piece of cake!
Only the two competitors
are allowed inside the circle!
That jerk! I'm gonna beat his brains out!
Are you ready, Stop Light?!
Knock your opponent out of
the circle and you win! That's it!
Straw Hat Luffy rushes right in!
--Mm-hmm.
--All right, then!
...Flail!
The battle has moved inside, but I
can't enter to give the play-by-play!
Note that the air and water inside
the circle still counts as in-bounds!
Huh? What's wrong?
Oh, it's just... I feel like I've done this before...
You can do it!
This is the true essence of this round:
a solitary battle between two combatants!
F! O! X! Y!
After Team Foxy's victory in the first round,
Me too...
Foxy!
Get up! Get up, Luffy!
Remember your painful training!
The Flower Cheerleaders
are currently on the stage
it's now time to begin Round #2's
Dash Touch Domination!
What a pain.
Ready! Go!
performing cheers for our boss,
Let's just leave it at that for now.
Quit playin' around and sit down. I can't see.
while an opening fight is
being held aboard the Foxy!
What we need is food. People
can't think on empty stomachs.
"Green..."
Oh, a gun deck!
Man, it's big! I bet Usopp would love this!
Additionally, the Association of Stalls
Food?!
Dash, Hamburg!
is selling limited-edition
Davy Back Fight merchandise,
Yeah, didn't you say you're a cook?
Now where is he?!
Chiqicheetah is already ahead of the pack!
A first-class cook.
so be sure to check them out!
There he is!
We don't need any of this! Just get started!
If this is a ship, there's gotta be something.
He's followed by "Full Dash" Hamburg!
Oh, no...!
--...please!
--Okay! Limited-edition Foxy pins!
"Foxy Pins"
--Eight seconds to go.
--Huh?
Meanwhile, Roronoa and Sanji
are leading the Straw Hat pack!
A cook...
Huh?!
Don't buy their junk!
Could this be what I think it is...?!
Hey, hold on a sec!
--Move, dammit!
--No, you back off!
All right! He's coming after me...!
--Excuse me. Where's the participant...?
--There! Just take him already!
Just who are you, anyway?!
Now he'll bust through
the door at breakneck speed!
This is no time to argue while running!
Seven.
Me? I'm the man who's
gonna be King of the Pirates!
What?
Knock it off, Sanji-kun! Zoro!
What are you so mad about?
Little does he know...
Sheesh! Why isn't anyone taking this seriously?!
Six.
Yeah, Sanji-kun! Zoro!
Boss!
...that this room is filled with spikes!
Huh?
They're awesome!
It really ticks me off how their boss
is dictating the pace of everything!
"...light..."
Whoa. This ship's been through a lot.
Now rush in and get--
Man, that's long! How can you hold
your breath so long, old stilts guy?!
I dunno, it's probably just 'cause
they've gained so many crew members...
Oh! An island!
Five!
What are you guys doing?!
Start counting too! Four!
I wonder where we are!
They clearly have more than enough now!
He's an ideal "stop light"!
I have bad news, guys. Our navigator is...
"Red..."
All that matters is that Luffy wins, Nami-san!
--What?
--Dunno! But it seems fun!
Oh? Who the heck are they?
--You lovey-dovey loser!
--Say what, fish flake head?!
I'll go buy us some drinks! Go on ahead!
Are they also your subordinates, Captain Usopp?
Three!
Oh. There he is.
Hm?! Y-Yeah, of course!
Whoa, what's with that room?
These are the two Straw Hats to look out for!
You guys lost your memories, too?
Two!
Hey, you two! Come on over here!
Who fires cannons inside other
people's ships?! Seriously!
Let's knock 'em outta the game
right away, just as planned!
Oh, I finally understand how a foolish
moth feels as it flies into a lamp...
One!
Here! For you!
Oh. It's coming back.
Go, Big Pan!
--How much is it?
--It's on the house!
People can't help but leap into
the brilliant radiance of others!
Oh, thank you.
Punk Attack!
You have some nerve!
Are you trying to kill me?!
Hi, pretty ladies! Your names, please?
Oh, yeah! Even if Luffy loses,
they'll all be part of this team too!
They're in trouble!
He's about to call "red light"!
Dammit!
If you're free, what do you
say to dinner tonight?!
This isn't the time for that!
I'll show you!
We won't have to go our separate ways!
Three!
"...l..."
Oh! He's running away!
Two!
But if that happens, Captain
won't be our captain anymore.
One!
"Infirmary"
Get back here!
Zero!
Man, this guy's funny!
Does this brat have any common sense?!
He suddenly has a different personality...
We'll all be serving under a new boss...
Uhh, who are these guys?! And where am I?!
"...ight...!"
That's it! Foxy Face Transformation!
Stop!
Not to mention...
--The King of the Pirates...
--...will be me!
Hurray!
Stop right there, fox!
Luffy!
You guys better work hard for me!
--A person?
--Dear me!
Yeah...
Whatever's the matter? Do you feel sick?
Boss!
Isn't that... backwards?
Say, Luffy's going to win, right?
Where are you sick? The head?
Are you sick in the head?
Our boss is sent soaring!
H-Huh?! Did anyone just come in here?
I-If we move now, we'll be out...!
--What the heck is that?
--It's a deer.
All seven of us are gonna get
to continue our journey, right?!
Boss!
No, I didn't see anyone. But never mind that...
Shut up, human! I'm a reindeer!
What's wrong with you? Your face?
It talked!
Let's pray it turns out that way.
Hurray! Hurray! Hurray!
Out!
Hey! Let's catch it!
That's weird... I'm sure I saw him--
Wow! Pickles and Big Pan of Team
Foxy are already out of the game!
Hey, stop! It's creepy!
Hold on! That woman looked like him!
Hey, girl! Help me out!
What the hell?! Why does popcorn
and a cola cost so much?!
All right, Zoro! Sanji!
No way! S-Stay away from me!
No big deal! All we need is
one person to touch him to win!
And he lands...
If you don't like it, don't buy it.
Could it be?!
Hey, you! You're that guy's sister, aren't you?!
--Lower it 80%!
--Get outta my face!
Oh, boy... Where do I even begin to explain?
...outside the battlefield!
Counter Fox Blow!
The final combat round of the Davy Back Fight
Chiqicheetah, Porche, and Hamburg
have a huge lead over the Straw Hats!
What is all this?!
has ended after a heated, epic
battle between the two captains!
Fool!
This is the dressing room.
It's a gloved fight, so choose anything you like.
Our boss's legendary record of 920
wins and 0 losses has been snapped!
What is this thing?!
Ooh! We're in a "totally going to win" mood!
Awesome!
Unbelievably, victory goes...
Wow, this is more like a costume
room than a dressing room...
That's weird! He really was in this room!
They're too fast!
Zoro and Sanji are our only hope, but...
Look at all this stuff! And I can
use anything I want, Usopp!
Is he even trying to fight?!
Damn Moss Head!
Stupid Love Cook!
I won't... let you have...
a single member of my crew...
Oh! The kitchen!
Just so you know, I have the important task
Fish, fish! Cut it up, sour it up! Carpaccio!
of getting Robin-chan back.
I've had enough of you!
...even if it costs me my life!
Hey, how about this? Does it look good?
All right. Listen, everyone.
--"Gree..."
--I don't give a damn about you!
...to Straw Hat Luffy!
Grill up a sole, fa-mi-re-do!
We're currently located in...
No... This is it...
--"...eee..."
--Hold on, you protected species head!
Oh? Can I help you?
Have you seen a fox with its head split
in two who looks like a real moron?!
The boundaries are in place!
Despite losing two players,
Luffy! You did it!
This ends the opening entertainment!
Thank you for your patience!
Team Foxy is closest to
reaching the "stop light"!
What did you just say...?
That's going too far...!
Now for today's main event...
At this rate, Team Straw Hat
has no chance at all!
Luffy!
I said we're in the Grand Line.
It's you!
Our boss... lost...
Combat! The bell will ring shortly!
I was the lady in the infirmary, too!
Have you forgotten that too?
Foxy Pirates versus...
Go! Go!
That thing, too?!
Seriously?!
Hey! Don't just sit there!
The boss needs our help!
Yes, that's it! Just like that!
Slow-Slow Beam!
Hey! What are you so happy for?!
Oh... no...
They say the Grand Line is
teeming with monsters and stuff!
Hurry to the spectator stands, everyone!
All right! I'll go!
...the Straw Hats!
Nine-Tails Rush!
--I'm going! Move!
--I'm going too!
You should be freaked out!
What's happening?
This orthodox-rules, three-coin game
Davy Back Fight is now over!
The sky is turning dark...
Still, it doesn't seem so
different from the regular sea.
Don't think I lured you
in here without a reason.
Nami-san! Where are you?! Say something!
Is this really the Grand Line?
Go check out what's waiting
for you when you get sent flying!
Navigator?
"...een..."
Who, me?!
Do you recognize what's on your arm?
Watch where you're walkin', crappy cook.
Crap! It's your fault we're so
far behind, you damn Moss Head!
Boss!
It ain't a living creature.
That'd be against the rules, after all.
What is this?!
It's a Log Pose.
Boss!
This time we're being treated to
a captain-versus-captain battle!
Compasses don't work here,
How did this happen?!
so islands' magnetic fields
are used for navigation instead.
The path is gone!
I know you have no sense of direction,
but this takes the cake!
That's what that tool is for.
--Beat 'im up, Boss!
--We're counting on you!
It's essential for crossing the Grand Line.
How can you even get lost in
a place with such a clear view?!
First, in the left figurehead corner...!
Geez, could you have been any more reckless?!
Take this! And this!
Tell me, Miss. I need to return
to my restaurant in the East Blue.
A man who takes on all challengers
It might be easier to catch up
here than on a curved track...
Quit poking him so much!
He's seriously hurt, you jerk!
and boasts a legendary, undefeated
record of 920 wins and 0 losses!
Guess it's do or die!
How can I go about that?
--And this!
--Afro power, my butt.
I wouldn't recommend it.
Boss!
He had us worried the entire time...
We've been traveling a long time;
heading back alone would be suicide.
While a Slow-Slow Beam
is in effect, any impacts given
Our boss, Silver Fox Foxy!
Afros really are powerful, Nami-san!
Oh! Sanji is taking a chance now!
are stored up and then go off all at once.
Oh! He's conscious!
Yikes...!
We've continually followed
the Log Pose's directions.
All right...
H-Huh?!
Listen up, Luffy. You ain't your old self no more.
Go on, now! Your life's final stop lies ahead!
Sanji's big gamble pays off!
He's now right behind the lead group!
The game! How'd the game end?!
And that's led us to this coral-surrounded isle.
I thought I won... Was it just a dream?!
That hairstyle arouses a man's true wildness.
This is all too much at once for me to believe!
30 seconds are up.
Oh, that's no fair! Hurry, Hamburg!
Don't worry. You won.
Why would I be cheerfully
traveling with people like this?!
Some ask if the champion makes the afro,
or if the afro makes the champion...
Wh-What do you want...?
That's a relief...
That's why.
Not even modern science can explain it.
Never hurts to reduce the number of opponents!
I was never worried in the least!
Time for all three of you to kick the bucket!
Luffy... With an afro on, your punches
will have some serious firepower.
Oh, man! That's a pirate flag!
Crap!
Liar.
N-Nami! Usopp!
Now that I think about it, I got no reason
to be a pirate for any other ship.
What?! It's a pirate ship?!
--Where's Straw Hat?!
--Did he wimp out on us?!
We've got no choice...
Th-That's right! It's the great
Captain Usopp's pirate ship!
Huh? Where is he?
--Everyone run for it!
--Roger!
I'm... right here!
Hmph! There's no getting away from me!
For real?!
Let's do it, Pops.
--Boss!
--You should really stay still!
Actually, Captain Usopp...
Oh, yeah!
Hey, Straw Hat!
Get back here!
Is it me, or is that skull wearing a straw hat?
How dare you tarnish my
legendary undefeated streak?!
Man, old stilts guy's "Green"
is really long this time...
And in the right corner, hailing from East Blue!
Oh!
Boss!
The leader of a miniscule pirate band
with a 100 million-Berry bounty...
That just means... this hat is mine!
Feh-feh-feh-feh-feh!
Oh?!
Put 'er there, brother!
What are you doing?! Give it back!
--Boss!
And another feh!
H-He's asleep...!
..."Straw Hat" Monkey D. Luffy!
All right, Boss!
--Get up!
--Hey, you! Wake up!
Don't touch my straw hat! I'll kick
your butt if you do that again!
What's with that outfit?!
--Don't be sleepin'!
--"...light, red light!"
I am Pilot Foxy! And...
What? I thought you lost your memory?!
Spiteful Shoulder Throw!
...let me introduce you
to the Gorilla Puncher 13!
I remember this! It's my treasure!
Wow! The afroed Luffy is all
fired up in the right corner!
Boss!
A gorilla-like punching machine
Are you that stupid?
Treasure...?
C-Crap!
that's had every single flaw ironed
out through constant improvement!
Lookin' sharp, Luffy!
Have you forgotten the rules?
Out!
It's a precious treasure a friend
gave me when I was little!
Choose your 500 people already!
Are you kidding me?
Is the gorilla face really necessary?!
Yes! The final exchange awaits!
Luffy looks so cool!
Even though the "stop light" was napping,
Capote was caught off guard!
I swore on this hat I'd become
a pirate and gather a crew!
He certainly does.
He's out of the game!
Both fighters have stepped onto the battlefield!
Chopper and Robin!
What kind of nerves does this guy have,
napping in a place like that?!
Excellent point!
Pirates this, pirates that! What a stupid era!
Can Straw Hat successfully
knock our boss out of the circle
I mean, shut up! Who asked you?!
But at least now I know that
everything you've said is nonsense!
That's old stilts guy for you!
Thank you! I'm so happy!
and protect his crew and pride?!
Go, Gorilla Puncher 13!
All right!
They're in firing range now!
Or will our boss's legendary undefeated
streak strip him of everything he has?!
You can have this back.
I hate pirates! What I like
are money and tangerines!
He starts off with two obvious choices!
It was gonna be such an easy win, too!
Now I'm a little worried...
This final and fateful combat
round of the Davy Back Fight
Now who'll be next?! Hurry and decide!
There's no way that I'd
be traveling with pirates!
How is it moving on its own?
is about to begin!
The four players in the lead are now
within 100 meters of the "stop light"!
But first, a word from our sponsors.
It's a secret...!
Give us your pirate flag!
You're sure sweatin' a lot...
Hey, now. Might wanna watch your tone, girl...
What?!
Shut up!
You can't be serious! You'd strip
us of our pride just like that?!
Will it be a mad dash to the end?!
You think you can dodge these
measly punches, don'tcha?
It'll be one of these four
who touches the "stop light"!
I don't need your sail.
You need it to go places, after all.
Tangerines? Like those?
Huh?
Slow-Slow Beam!
--Wow! He's so merciful!
--But our symbol's on there!
Come on, Sanji!
What? Where are you aiming--?
No one's paying any attention to us...
Yeah, they're completely ignoring us...
Take a look behind you!
How do you expect us to use the sail?!
Those tangerine trees...!
Huh? Who's that?! A mirror?!
I do feel a little useless.
We don't need your pity! Just take what's yours!
Yes! Mirrors reflect Slowmo Photons!
Hey, Straw Hat! Nice fashion!
Got ya!
All right.
What was that?!
Since your mark is all we need,
I'll draw a new one over it for you.
At least there's comfort in knowing
we're not the only useless ones...
Whoa...! It just grew an arm!
Your butt is as good as kicked!
Mystery tangerines?!
Keep your arms tucked in and
show 'im your golden right punch!
Just who are you?!
That way you can keep your sail.
T-The path ends again...
More important is that tangerine...
Yeah!
Whoa! His brotherly soul is burning red-hot!
Ouch! Ouch!
Straw Hat... You're such a...!
Brr! I hope this'll end soon so
I can go eat something warm...
This is one of Bellemere-san's tangerines!
I know that much for sure!
"Fox"
There!
Oh, that hurt? Too hot for you?
Letting Usopp be his corner man was a mistake.
What are her tangerines doing on this ship?!
This sucks...!
I forgot to mention that this
thing's punches are flaming hot!
--Wow, they're really grateful!
--No, we ain't!
I wish he'd take this seriously...
Unfortunately, I don't know
much about that myself.
Outta the way!
Better watch out! Not even Sea Kings
can withstand a beating from this!
Get him, Hamburg!
Hey! Not too shabby!
This time... I will make mincemeat out of ya!
What a wild style!
H-Hold on just a minute!
Mirror Racket!
Why don't you check the
ship's logbook in your room?
You still have 497 more people to pick!
Quite admirable, even if you are my opponent!
Huh?
You wanna fight, you damn gorilla?!
As I recall, there's a picture
of your Bellemere-san in it.
We don't need any more.
I wouldn't act so confident
if I were you, Champion!
I'll get you this time!
Rules are rules! You have to
choose 497 people, like it or not!
Hamburg intercepts Sanji!
He's liable to bite your head off!
Better watch out!
Aww. Do I have to?
All right, corner man! You're in the way! Scram!
Meanwhile, Chiqicheetah heads for
the "stop light" at breakneck speed!
Of course you do, idiot!
Whoa! My job as corner man is over already?!
Luffy! A captain's orders are absolute... Right?
Sanji has fallen right into Porche-chan's trap!
Corner man, out!
Get goin' already!
We're just getting started!
Yes. In which case...
What?!
You're absolutely right!
Oh! Good thinking!
There's no need for me to remain
here either! I'll leave as well!
Huh? Huh?!
It's my handwriting...
Slowpoke Ball Demon Coach! A two-sided
attack with bouncing beams and punches!
Victory is ours!
What? What?!
Oh! Okay!
Dammit!
Chiqicheetah rushes straight
for the "stop light" from behind!
What? The stands are...!
I'll choose, then!
Oh, cool! I didn't know they did that!
You!
"Ggg..."
Bellemere-san...
--Me?
--Yeah. Everyone from you...
Oh! So that's why the beams
didn't work on that fishman!
Grachoo!
Now then, Straw Hat Luffy.
Let's have some fun!
Man, this is irritating!
If I can just get close to him...!
This entire ship is our battlefield!
Rampage to your heart's desire!
--...to you.
--Me?
How many people is that?
Keep running! You'll end up squished
between the gorilla and the mirror!
Well, we have 500 in our crew,
Bellemere-san!
We have plenty of skilled shipwrights, you see!
so excluding our boss, Hamburg-san,
and Porche-chan, that makes...
Out!
Look at how many I got!
Oh, my! It was just a sneeze!
Oh, 497 exactly! It's 497 people...
That's it!
Some of them are still green!
Tonjit hasn't started calling out
"red light, green light" yet!
You know better, Nami!
You have to pay attention!
...Captain Luffy!
By sheer luck, this bout is taking
place aboard the Sexy Foxy!
Okay! It's decided!
What? But they were nice and sweet!
I never thought of that!
Has his speed backfired on him?!
Chiqicheetah is out for jumping the gun!
What kind of deadly struggle
is about to unfold?!
You ate some?! They're
merchandise, you know!
The Straw Hats are victorious!
This concludes the Davy Back Fights!
It's all right. We can eat these ones ourselves.
The two pirates are now all alone
inside the spacious battlefield!
What?!
Blast! Don't sneeze, Stop Light!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Okay! You're a big meanie, Nojiko!
It's the birth of the New Straw Hat Pirates!
--Boss!
--Keep your undefeated streak going!
We were so close to winning, too!
What?!
Win, Luffy! You hafta win!
But the Merry can't hold this many people...
All right, get to work, you two!
Got him!
His beam! Watch out for his beam!
Even your snot is long, old stilts guy!
We'll just have to follow along
in the Sexy Foxy for a while.
Excitement fills the stands!
Slow-Slow Beam! Beam! Beam!
I guess so!
Sure lucked out there...
It's plunder or be plundered!
D-Don't be stupid!
He was sneezing...
I have to go back...
500 people are on the line in this final
combat round of the Davy Back Fight!
Fool!
Something might've happened
to Cocoyashi Village...
The Sexy Foxy is my ship!
This is no time to be laughing, Hamburg!
It's one match only, with no time limit!
Your ship?
We have to win and take Choppy!
Gorilla Punch Golden Hits!
--Luffy!
--Boss!
I'd love to see the three of you run
this huge ship all by yourselves!
Both teams are closing in on the "stop light"!
Silver Fox Foxy versus Straw Hat Luffy!
So... what exactly is it?
Never gonna happen!
At this distance, the next play
should decide the game!
It's a head-to-head battle between
these two pirate powerhouses!
Neato reindeer!
Never gonna happen...
Will the "stop light" be touched by
the duo of Porche-chan and Hamburg?!
The fate of everything hangs in the balance!
Fine, then! Jerks!
Here comes...
Reindeer!
Or will it be Sanji?! Which will it be?!
--So long, Former Boss!
--Don't catch a cold!
You idiot! Stay away!
...the starting bell!
Reindeer...
This is the moment of truth!
--Brush your teeth!
--Take a bath!
--Let's do it!
--Yeah!
"Green..."
--Gum-Gum... Pistol!
--Slow-Slow Beam!
Hey! Straw Hat!
It's great when thinly sliced,
slowly simmered with vegetables,
It appears he's indeed
calling out his line this time!
Round #3 of this second Davy Back Fight--
the combat round-- is underway!
I'll get you for this!
and made into a stew...
What's happening now is
anyone's guess, but there's no doubt
What?! We can eat it?!
Do they ever stop being comedians?
Only my fist is slow!
a truly epic battle is
taking place inside the ship!
Reindeer steak with berry sauce is also superb.
All right, men!
Take this! And this!
Steak, it is!
You're not so tough! You're all show!
Here's your first job as members
of the New Straw Hat Pirates!
Boss! Boss! Boss!...
See you later!
Why, you...!
Despite not being able to see him,
the crowd cheers for our boss!
What?!
Listen well!
I ain't no food!
Come back!
H-Hamburg! What are you doing?!
He ain't gonna lose!
--You can count on us!
--Rubber Boss!
Of course not! He's Luffy! And he has a 'fro!
--"...light..."
--Here comes Robin-chan's savior!
Slow-Slow...
You're all off the crew!
Being Luffy is more than enough.
Oh, no!
Just kidding!
That damn fox...
Don't eat him. He's the ship's doctor.
Oh! Sanji!
Wha...?!
What's so special about an afro?
Does it power you up or something?!
--You're kicking us out?
--Yep.
--What?!
--What's Porche-chan doing?!
Slow-Slow Beam!
Doctor?
--Stay still, Porche-chan!
--Do something!
A captain's orders are absolute, remember?
Yes. He's a brilliant doctor
beyond even human compare.
Luffy!
This is taking longer than usual...
"...rrr..."
You can go back to your old crews,
or even to Split-Head if you want!
Isn't that right?
Now Robin-chan's ours again.
Well, the guy is made of rubber.
He's floating! He's slow even when falling?
Sh-Shut up!
He's made of rubber and has a 'fro!
She's totally gonna fall in love with me!
You're free to go now!
Seriously, what's that
have to do with anything?!
Being praised by humans doesn't
make me happy at all, you jerk!
Sanji! Hurry up! Touch him!
That's all!
I told him to watch out for that!
Former Boss! Wait up!
Luffy will win us back...!
--"...eeee..."
--Good work, old man.
Oh, you sure seem happy to me!
We belong with the Foxy Pirates after all!
Talk about lame!
He's a reindeer who ate the Human Human
Fruit and gained human abilities.
The game's over now.
Now beat 'im, Boss!
Yes. He does have that afro and all.
How cunning.
Not you too, Robin...!
Aww... Crap...
Incidentally, I ate the Flower Flower Fruit
and gained Devil Fruit powers.
"...dddd..."
Oh, my! There's activity on the deck!
Oh, my! Sanji is turning back
before touching the "stop light"!
Looks like it's all over.
And Luffy has eaten a Devil Fruit as well, right?
Who has the upper hand?!
Or could the fight be over now?!
What's the matter, Straw Hat?
Ready to throw in the towel already?!
Yeah! I ate the Gum Gum Fruit!
What is he doing?!
Say...
Even if you are my enemy,
I can't turn my back on a lady!
Don't worry. They won.
I see two figures!
I'm made of rubber!
Th-Three people with Devil Fruit powers...?!
...what...?
There, there. I won't ride on stilts ever again.
Nine-Tails Rush!
This ain't normal...
Incredible! Sanji, the nefarious cook,
has saved Porche-chan!
We can follow the village together now,
however many years it takes.
Are you guys pirates?! Real pirates?!
Oh! Our boss unleashes a
fierce attack right off the bat!
"...light!"
That's right. You are too, you know.
Our boss is the one still standing!
Straw Hat is helpless to do anything!
Hamburg is fighting to remain still!
You folks...!
All right! As of today, you're a
member of the Usopp Pirates too!
Boss!
But Sanji is as good as out,
despite having saved Porche-chan!
What?! How come?!
Huh? He isn't even budging...
I went and kicked their butts!
You're taking him seriously?
No, that's not true!
The effects are slow too, that's all!
In any case, along with one other person,
Meanwhile, Straw Hat is charred black!
No, wait! There's Sanji!
And he has Porche-chan!
He seems to have taken some
seriously heavy punches!
we've been crossing these seas
as a seven-member pirate crew.
You're really hurt...
Luffy!
Not only that, Sanji is completely still,
despite his current situation!
One other person?
This is nothing new.
Why don't you come down, Swordsman?
That's impossible...
How could some simple punches
burn him?! What did he do?!
He's not moving in the slightest! He's safe!
Thank you...
That was just a little "hello."
Impossible...!
The punches themselves
didn't hurt you too much.
How can he stand completely still
in the middle of the ocean?!
Luffy!
You guys're making quite a
racket so early in the morning.
Look!
Ah, so that's why you accepted their challenge.
That much is obvious to me, rubber man!
Oh! He's treading water!
You're interrupting my morning nap.
Darn... it...
Wh-Who are you?! State your name!
Not like you wouldn't have otherwise, though.
All while carrying Porche-chan and
keeping his upper body motionless!
Man, you're rude!
Well, your thirty seconds are about up!
You're supposed to give your name
first when asking someone's name.
Just like a swan!
Straw Hat Luffy is up!
He's kicking furiously beneath the
surface while looking elegant above!
--Oh...
--I'm Luffy! Nice to meet you!
Just when it seemed he was down
for the count, he got back up!
--It's hitting him all at once!
--Oh, no! He's going overboard!
I'm Roronoa Zoro.
As long as the "stop light"
can't see him moving, he's safe!
Wh-What is this?!
Luffy!
As in "Pirate Hunter"?
Sanji is incredibly determined to win!
I've never once gone by that name.
I just wound up with it.
Yikes!
Who are you?!
Looks like you barely
pulled through, Straw Hat...
I will save Robin-chan, no matter what!
No, who are you?!
You're still a bounty hunter, though.
Crap! The Slow-Slow Beam is
more dangerous than I thought!
Th-The thing can talk!
I only did it when I needed money to survive.
Sanji still has a chance to touch the "stop light"!
I'm not a thing! I'm a mooole!
Beams sure are nice...
It ain't my goal.
It's the brotherly soul! Afro power!
"Mooole"? Like a mole?
But I take it you're only here 'cause
you were targeting a pirate ship?
Kick his butt, Boss!
--He's one heck of an opponent!
--Impressive, Cook!
Guess I shouldn't stretch more than I need to...
I'm the champion! Yo!
Sanji! You're too much...!
Where'd that jerk go?!
Beats me. I got no idea why I'm here.
Oh, my! I could really fall for you, Mr. Cook!
Not another weirdo...
Take this!
Champion of what?!
Damn! I won't get hit by that anymore!
Are you guys notorious pirates?
I'm glad you asked!
I'm the world champion of hole-digging!
Oh! Both Porche-chan and Sanji
have dived underwater!
You're out to get us after all!
Come out, Split-Head!
F-Fine, bring it on! I have 8,000
people under my command!
I'm challenging my own record as we speak!
Please don't take your anger out on the ears!
This is the Slow-Slow Beam Sword!
You're both out!
I've restrained your arms and legs!
But feel free to move anything else!
Oh? Then I bet you're worth a lot.
What kind of challenge has you
wrecking the old stilts guy's house?!
H-Hey! Keep swimming!
You're gonna make me drown!
I needed some food money anyway.
I'll be more than happy to take you on!
A-Another Slow-Slow?!
Not that you can, though.
Oh, what have I done...! Robin-chan...!
"Old stilts guy"...?
Megaton Nine-Tails Rush!
N-No! That's not what I meant! C-C-Calm down!
Welcome to my ship!
"Green..."
Rush! Rush!
Here we go again!
Why, you...!
Take a look. This is a "mooole."
Say something, will you?!
He got me!
The only ones left now are
Hamburg of Team Foxy, and...!
Rush!
He doesn't have a bounty.
Not even a single Berry.
Littonto. I'm about to go for
the stilt-standing world record.
Calm down, will you?
Rush! Rush!
Nothing at all?!
--We're almost to the "stop light"!
--There's no one to stop us!
I'm trying to show you some hospitality here...
Huh?!
Rush!
Competing with the world is a long, hard road.
Those cannonballs have been Slow-Slow-ed...
I can't believe we're gonna touch him!
Rush! Rush!
I'll be gone a few days. The mooole
will keep you company, though, right?
If you can ride one, then I can too!
"...light..."
Rush!
Let's all touch him together!
Can you manage while I'm gone?
Oh...! I wouldn't ride that one if I were you...
I have to get out of here somehow.
30 seconds.
Yeah!
Sure. But make sure you
come back as a champion!
Oh! The trio of forgotten Straw Hat
slowpokes is poised to touch him!
Oh, or that one.
But of course I will!
An upset's in the making!
Who would've thunk it?!
Gold!
He's down for sure this time-- No, wait!
This is enough to buy Cocoyashi Village
back and have money left over!
I promise!
Told you so!
Could it be? Are you...?!
Luffy!
It's me!
Just when I finally get on the real path...
--Grandpa!
--Littonto!
Straw Hat Luffy is up!
Ugh! Kicking is that crappy
cook's specialty, but...
What is this? What's going on in the fight?!
I missed you! I missed you so much!
Get outta the way!
You went and grew so much
since I last saw you...!
Whoa! Who is this guy?!
"...red..."
It's gotta be the 'fro! Is it the afro's wildness?!
Hey! Robin!
Yes!
Can you see anything from up there?
Victory is certain for Team Straw Hat!
I'm sorry for worrying you...
Nothing but smoke!
Stubborn little...!
All right! We win!
He's your grandson?
Take this! Slow-Slow Beam!
I missed my grandpa so much,
and that devotion led me to hole-digging!
Now how do I haul it out...?
Megaton Nine-Tails Rush!
Darn it...
And before I knew it, becoming
the greatest digger in the world
Man, he's wrecking his own ship...
"...light!"
had become my greatest goal in life...
Dammit, that's not fair!
That beam's against the rules!
What is that?
I'm just getting started!
So you became the champion?
Usopp!
Slow-Slow Foxy Face Bombs!
Yep! "Shoot for the other side of the world!"
Whoa! This looks like the end...!
Hamburg has touched the "stop light"!
I like that! You sound
just like the old stilts guy!
Team Foxy is the winner of Round #2's
Dash Touch Domination game!
What's that?!
Freaky!
--Oh, you're too kind!
--That's not praise!
Huh? Pin badges? They're
bigger than the one I bought!
Say, couldn't you follow your
holes to reach your village?
Of course we are! We're bombs!
That's two supreme victories in a row!
You are?! Yikes!
Oh...
Dealing the punches ain't so easy, either!
Huh? A bomb just talked!
Huh? It's over already?
Isn't this great, old guy?!
I'm... the real deal!
You ended it!
He's beating him to death out there!
Yes. I don't know how to begin thanking you...
In the worst possible way!
Amazing! It can run on the water too!
It's all your fault, Zoro!
Sorry, Straw Hat...
Don't worry about it!
Oh?! Again...?!
You too, Miss! I achieved my true goal,
all thanks to your insight!
...but I upgraded my gloves!
Huh? She left!
And the Face Bombs'
30 seconds are just about up!
A-Again...?!
That thing's so neat!
I'm up next, right?
Miss...
I'm gonna take back my crew! I'm their captain!
I'll never forget what you've done for us!
I've got no idea what's going on,
Luffy...!
Oh, yeah! Luffy! The body! The body!
but it seems like there's
no point in me staying here.
Haven't you forgotten an
important fact, Straw Hat?
Oh, Usopp!
Thank you!
You've lost twice now, which has cost
you Nico Robin and one other member!
Hey, what's happening with the fight?
Take care on your way home!
I won't...
Dunno. Beats me.
You too! I pray for your safe journey!
Are you serious?!
Huh? He left too. What's the deal?
But you can only win back
one crew member per game!
...let you have...
In short, if by some incredibly
rare chance you win the next round...
...a single member of my crew...
All right! Time for us to leave!
...even if it costs me my life!
Nami! Is the Log ready?
Get to the point, Split-Head.
Yep! We're good to go!
What the heck's going on around here...?
Let's get movin', then.
Split...
In other words, there's only one round left,
Yeah.
Luffy... Oh, no...!
Let's hurry and snag us a shipwright!
so even if you win it, you can
only take one person back.
I haven't the slightest, either.
Yeah!
Luffy...
Straw... Straw Hat Luffy
is on his feet once again!
This is a real conundrum...
Huh?
All right, men!
Struggle as you might, Straw Hat,
you can't change the fact
Let's go find a shipwright!
that you've already lost one
of your crewmates for good!
Yeah!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
He's unsteady and out of breath,
yet he stands with a glimmer in his eye!
Get up! Get up, Joe-- err, come on, Luffy!
This is crazy! I'd never team up with pirates!
Hey! Split-Head! Quit your blabbing
and start the next match already!
--Umm... What am I doing again?
--Who are these guys?
--Do a No-Guard stance, then a double-cross!
--Who are you pretending to be?!
--Do you even understand the situation?!
--Luffy!
Why am I with a bunch of pirates?!
But this is my handwriting in the logbook...
Now this is a Davy Back Fight!
I'm so teary-eyed I can't see straight!
Now! Remember the eye of the tig--!
Who what where am I?
He's surprisingly cold-hearted.
Oh, and the treasure's mine too!
Not you too, Robin!
--Don't tell me all your memories are...!
--Oh, my head! My head!
His brotherly soul is burning
red-hot for you guys! Ain't it so?!
--Luffy!
--Luffy! Luffy!
Wait! Whoa! What kind of scene is this?!
--Pops... I'm gonna be pure white ash...
--Don't burn up! Fight!
--Are you okay, Long-nose?
--Oh, it's so itchy...!
Don't cheer on the enemy!
Ahh! Hey! Was it you?!
Give our memories back!
Oh, yeah!
Shut up, all of ya!
I'm having fun! Come on, Straw Hat!
Boss! Boss!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Captains Square Off!
The Final Combat Round!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Full-Blast Slow-Slow Onslaught
vs. Invulnerable Luffy"
"Was It Lost? Stolen? Who Are You?"
"Epic, Heated Combat!
The Fateful Final Conclusion"
"A Mysterious Boy with a Horn
and Robin's Deduction!"
King of the Pirates! Oh, yeah!
--I'm gonna be King of--
--Nope, I am!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
You're never gonna be King of the Pirates!!
Huh?!