It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"Now, Let's Get Back Our Memories!
The Pirate Crew Lands on the Island"
--Who are you?
--What?
Zoro...!
That straw hat guy?
Oh? Who the heck are they?
I'm surprised that Roronoa Zoro
couldn't perceive his strength.
Are they also your subordinates, Captain Usopp?
Where is Luffy?
Did Luffy get cut down by Zoro?
Vice Admiral! He's not around!
Hm?! Y-Yeah, of course!
"Golden Pavilion"
I couldn't perceive it?
"Justice"
"He's not around!" doesn't cut it!
You guys lost your memories, too?
Hey, now you want to fight Luffy, don't you?
Where the hell did he go?!
There's no mistaking that this is my handwriting.
Hi, pretty ladies! Your names, please?
Don't tell me... It can't be...
Since his bicycle is gone,
he probably went to... sea.
Sky islands... Navy base G8...
What the heck is that?
It's a deer.
And this gold...
Contact the Five Elder Stars immediately!
Shut up, human! I'm a reindeer!
Where's our captain?
Yes, sir!
If this is all true, everything makes sense.
It talked!
I see...
Did you find something out, Robin?
Oops. Sorry about that.
If I could go back to Cocoyashi Village,
I should be able to figure everything out!
Pirates this, pirates that! What a stupid era!
I figured out the culprit who
took your memories away...
But there aren't any decent ships.
How can I go back...?
You damn swordsman...!
I hate pirates! What I like
are money and tangerines!
No... I mean, the real culprit.
If you're gonna harm the ladies,
I'll be your opponent.
And, of all the places, I'm in the Grand Line?
There's no way that I'd
be traveling with pirates!
That damn brat isn't the culprit?
That man again? He probably
just went to do some sightseeing.
According to this sea chart,
Now, let's head to the Sea God's Palace.
you can't exit the Grand Line midway
through to get to the East Blue.
Seriously... Doesn't he realize his position?
You guys're making quite a
racket so early in the morning.
The Sea God's Palace?
You're interrupting my morning nap.
What the heck is that?
We can't just have him wandering about.
I have to get out of here somehow.
Wh-What'd you say?!
He said, "I still haven't
played my trump card yet"!
I'm calling it that for now...
You're the captain, you say?!
One of the Navy Headquarters'
ultimate powerhouses, Admiral Aokiji...
"Zoro Bares His Fangs!
A Savage Animal Stands in the Way!"
At any rate, that was close.
If I hadn't remembered things, I would've
remained Usopp's underling forever.
I've got no idea what's going on,
but it seems like there's
no point in me staying here.
Shut up! I'm never gonna believe it!
"The Last Counterattack by the Memory
Thief Who Revealed His True Colors!"
At any rate, there's not a single
good egg in this guy's family...
"A Mysterious Boy with a Horn
and Robin's Deduction!"
No matter what anyone says,
I am the great pirate, Captain Usopp,
So that damn brat's home turf is ahead of here?
--Yeah.
--Hey, so, who's the real culprit?
who leads 8,000 underlings
in the Usopp Pirates!
"Proud Man! Silver Fox Foxy"
Isn't it about time you told us?
That's the spirit! That's our Usopp!
Navigator...
But you're the sniper of
the Straw Hat Pirates, Usopp!
I'm pretty sure you'll know when
we get to the Sea God's Palace.
Oooh! All right! I'm... me!
Shoot... Now he's above me.
Hey, Captain! Stop fooling around!
Help me out here!
Now I can rest easy for a while.
I'm glad that unpleasant pirate
hunter is off the ship, but...
This guy is a monster just like me,
and yet he's a captain?
Ahhh! I'm me!
Whoa! What a huge wave! It's scary!
Don't tell me... they're gonna take
me deep in the jungle, lock me up,
I have a feeling that Navigator
might set foot on the island.
Chopper!
Ahh! Don't come this way!
Knowing her, she probably won't do too much
and then they're gonna take the gold away...!
He sure looks like he's having fun.
Are you still acting like that?
Oh, no...!
until she can make a level-headed decision.
Tell me about it. I bet he'll be laughing
even if the ship gets capsized.
I wonder if he really is here...
I hope so.
Let's play like we always do!
Excuse me, but aren't you one of the guests?
I'm the ship's doctor, and yet I was
really doing something like this?
This place seems kinda peaceful.
Wouldn't this thing snap before that happens?
That's right! I'm a guest!
Hey, I'm starving. I wanna eat!
Sure, this is your signature party piece.
Really?! If that happens,
what's gonna happen to us?!
D-Don't let your guard down.
This is that damn brat's home turf.
You look tasty!
Why am I dressed like this?
You did it whenever we had a party.
What?!
Don't worry.
A one! A two!
Geez... You have no sense of tension, do you?
--A one, two, three!
--That rubber monkey said
that he regained his memories,
Even if the mast gets broken,
it doesn't mean the ship will sink.
He might have crazy monsters
as his subordinates.
Hm?
What're you doing, manager?!
Please come to the front desk right away!
but he acts just like he did before.
But, well, I guess we can think about
what to do after we finish eating, huh?
Besides, we have an excellent,
cute navigator on this ship.
It means that our captain doesn't change,
no matter what happens.
M-Monsters?
So I was right... I'm the inn manager, aren't I?
To start with, monsters
normally hide themselves,
By the way, Miss, I didn't get your name yet.
Hey, let's sing the usual song!
Even if I'm part of a pirate crew, if I'm
nobody, they might just slave drive me.
and then suddenly go "boo!" and attack you.
M-Mom! Where have you been?!
I'm Nico Robin.
Oh, no! It looks like the mast is about to break!
First, could you tell us about
the memories that we lost?
On top of that, being around monsters like them,
You see...
Really? What's gonna happen to us?
no matter how many lives
you have, it won't be enough.
I'm sorry. Are you okay? How have you been?
I don't know how many times monsters
lay in ambush waiting for me
Now it's clear.
Sure.
when I was traveling around the ocean.
Don't worry!
It's not that everyone lost their memories.
Their memories were taken away.
All right! Our memories...
Our memories are back!
Even if the mast gets broken,
it doesn't mean the ship will sink!
B... Behind you!
And the culprit, after all, is...
Hm? What's the matter? Did you
see a monster or something?
Ah...
No way that I'd stay in a place
like that for even a second!
Who's that damn brat?
Ahoy! Guys! Long time no see, huh?
That stuff won't work on...
Yeah, what does he want with our memories?
Pirates cold-bloodedly steal
things that people cherish!
Boss! That's Straw Hat!
Good question.
Ahoy!
Ah! Shoot!
I have to come up with a way to
return to Cocoyashi Village quickly.
How dare you, Straw Hat?! Don't look this way!
--Get if off!
--Nooo! Hey, keep away from me!
What?
I have to bring back Nami
and Zoro. Let's go, everyone!
--Hey, please! Please! Please!
--S-Stop it! Stop it!
E-Everyone! There's trouble!
We haven't fallen so low as to need your help!
--Hm?
Huh?
What?!
Oh, it's you, Drim.
See ya!
What're they doing?
Let's wait until morning.
Don't scare us like that.
Hm? Why, Robin?
Hey! If you want to help us,
we're okay with that, you know!
Drim... Drim...!
We've never been to this place.
On top of that, it's the dead of night.
I hate snakes! I hate snakes!
Mom! Mom!
I'm glad... that you came, lady.
Boss... look behind you...
So you're okay.
It won't be that easy to find them.
Hmm... I guess you're right.
I welcome you.
Wouldn't it be better to
sleep a little until dawn?
This is nothing! Slow-Slow Beam!
That boy seems to have learned a lesson.
Looks like everyone's memories are back.
I don't think we have to worry
about him showing up again tonight.
Good, good.
But how did something like that happen?
It's awfully quiet here.
Beam!
Okay! We'll leave tomorrow morning then.
I wonder if something happened...
Everyone! There's trouble!
This is it for us!
I finally stopped.
--Hold on.
--Hm?
The one who took our
memories away is in the forest!
I wonder if I'll find something
if I go up a bit higher...
I'm all for bringing back that lady, Nami-san,
That damn giant snake! It got scared
of me, Captain Usopp, and ran away!
but I don't see why we're
going after that Zoro guy.
--What?!
Hey, isn't this bad?
Me neither! If you wanna go,
you two can go by yourselves!
A small boat like that won't stand a chance.
--Hey!
--Hm?
Guys! Stay back!
We got separated from everyone!
What're we gonna do, you jerk?!
I-I...
Hold on to this!
What're you guys saying?!
What? Oh, shoot!
We're saying, why do we have to include Zoro?
Hm?
He's a pirate hunter, you know!
What're we gonna do if
monsters attack us now?!
Idiot! No! I meant the rope!
Newspaper...
Why do we have to go to the
trouble of chasing after him?
Hm? Oh, don't worry about it.
Luffy!
What's it saying?
Why else? It's because he's one of us!
I just told you a little joke to scare you.
Wh-What?!
"T-Take them out, Roronoa Zoro!"
Even if you say he's one of us... Right...?
H-Hey, wait!
So he said.
S-See? He's being controlled by that thing!
He doesn't feel that way even a bit.
You know that, too, don't you?
Oh, so it was just a joke.
Hey! You made fun of me?! You jer...
This is mine!
The fact that he left in a hurry is proof of that.
Shut up! This newspaper is
the only thing I can depend on!
I'm not gonna let you have it!
M-Monster!
You bastard! Stop screwing with me!
So it wasn't a joke?!
Usopp is the sniper. Sanji is the cook.
Why would I give you something to go on?!
Shut up! It's mine!
If you're gonna eat, eat him!
Chopper is the ship doctor.
Robin is the archaeologist.
I got it first!
--He'd make a good raccoon dog soup!
--Stop it! No!
--Who cares?!
--Hey, who are you?!
Nami is the navigator.
And Zoro is the swordsman.
Hey, someone, do something...
If I knew, I wouldn't be having this problem!
We, the Straw Hat Pirates, can't leave
anyone out, not even one person!
Huh...? Oh, it's you. You scared us.
What's with these people?
Well, I feel ashamed.
Geez... You damn swordsman,
you're always bringing in trouble...!
We just have to get the
swordsman's memories back.
First, I lost 500 subordinates.
And now, to think I even lost my ship...
Oh, man... Another scary guy came back.
If so, then I just have to beat up that brat,
just like I did earlier, right?
This is finally the end of Silver Fox Foxy...
What the heck is going on?
Right, Chopper?
--Hey...
--Hm?
Ahh, Sanji! Be careful!
At any rate, he seems kinda different
from when he was on the ship.
It might've been better if I'd let fate
take its course and sank into the sea.
Well, looks like we'll have a busy day tomorrow.
Hm?
Let's get some sleep while we can!
What's the matter, lady?
Boss...
"Now this will buy me some time"?
The key to solving all the
mysteries is on that island...
I see... So you're looking for a boat?
What do you think about that?
Collier!
Well, if you agree to mend
your ways and be faithful to me,
Well, I may not be in a position
to say this, but that's a lie.
--Yeah.
--The boats docked at this harbor
are the only boats on this island.
Huh?
then I'll accept you as one of the great
Captain Usopp's subordinates... Hm?
Therefore, I'd like you to take pity
on me and let me stay on this ship!
What? Is that right?
I underestimated Monkey D. Luffy.
They all seem to be in disrepair, as if
they haven't been used in a long time.
Hey... H-Hey! Don't ignore me!
Okay. Since you don't have
your own ship, it can't be helped.
Wait! Do you know where everyone is?
It seems that everyone is too busy
with other things to care about them.
If I make an enemy out of him,
I could be in big trouble.
Here's some soup. It'll warm you up.
Hm?
Don't interfere...
But I'll definitely make my wish come true.
If you don't believe me, go ahead
and go around the island.
Whoa! This looks good! I'll have it with Choppy.
...you idiot cook!
Hey! Don't leave me here alone!
In order to do so, I have to make friends, too.
It's a small island. It won't take long.
Sanji! I wanna have some, too!
There isn't any left. Wait until tomorrow.
Well, take it easy and stay a while.
I'm sure you'll enjoy it here.
Oh? There he is!
And you can't go wrong
with a skilled swordsman.
I can't stay too long.
What's wrong? Don't hold back.
Zoro!
--Oh, I see.
--I'm sorry.
What's this?! There's nothing in the soup!
Hey! Wait up!
No, don't worry about it.
Don't act so full of yourself!
--Hm?
--Hey!
I've gotten kinda sleepy. I'm going home now.
--Ahh! Sanji!
--How about I put you in the soup?!
Oh, Zoro!
Hey! Calm down! Calm down, Sanji!
That damn swordsman again?
You too! Apologize to Sanji! Okay?! Okay?!
Ah... hey!
That's right. It's different from yesterday.
Well then, see you later!
Huh?!
This is Zoro, a pirate hunter.
So you're okay!
Oh, no! What's this?! This is amazing!
If I carelessly get closer,
I may make another blunder.
Luffy! What'd you do that for?!
Lots of gold... I didn't know they were rich.
Hm? He's...
Zoro, did you just... say "Luffy"?
Okay. I won't do it now.
There'll be another chance, anyway.
So you decided to come along with us?
Oh, shoot. The soup will get cold.
These guys are real pirates!
Tsk.
Yeah, when that time comes,
I'll have you do your job but good.
So your memories are back?!
Choppy! You're here, right?
So clouds are really fluffy?
--Watch out!
--Captain!
Daaachshund... Horsey-Bird...
Darn it! Why can't I remember them?!
Of course.
What is it?
Your face is scary! If your memories are back,
then approach us with
a smiling, kind face like this!
Choppy!
Davy Back Fight, the large Navy fortress...
Oh...
It's said that the All Blue has
foodstuffs from around the world.
It was just a candleholder...
Sky islands and the sand country, Alabasta...
Argh! Shut up!
What happened?!
I used to dream of going to that legendary sea.
We really had such a grand journey?
Ow!
Hm? Who am I?!
Yes, we did.
--Huh?!
--Hey! Don't make it more
complicated than it already is!
I-I can't believe it...
I didn't ask for your help!
The captain of this ship has a
100-million-Berry bounty on his head?
I can't think of any reason
for you to be kind to me!
Hey, what'd you do that for all of a sudden?
Ah, Zoro! How dare you do that earlier?!
Hey, don't you have some
more neat adventure stories?
Why...? Why did you?!
Geez, do what you want, you guys...
Because you had the same dream as me.
I joined your crew after you left Alabasta.
Hm? Where's Boss?
Good! Now we're all back to normal.
Hm...?
Ahhh!
So, unfortunately, I don't know
what happened before that.
Restaurant?
Robin-chan really is wonderful, to figure out
that that sea horse horn is the real culprit.
Choppy!
Yeah. I was thinking that I'd build a
restaurant as my final purpose in life...
Darn! That sucks!
As if I'm gonna sit around fishing. I'm a guest.
Stop, both of you!
What?! So that was it?!
Although I have a hard time buying her story,
Hey, better not meddle.
You were the first one to
get your memories back.
All right, then, I'll help
you do that. So don't die!
Besides, we have food right here, too!
That damn swordsman is giving off a totally
different air from when he was on the ship.
it is true that the seasonings and equipment
Why didn't you notice it?
How rude! I'm better than Zoro!
Ha! It's impossible for a
weak little brat like you!
are where I would like them to be.
Don't tell me...
He's an idiot.
So where did that thing go?
Robin-san, could you tell us about the
most crucial thing-- about yesterday?
I'll become strong, too!
Ah...
Did it get away?
No...
Sure. Well then, let's include
the ship's doctor, too.
There's no way that I'd leave that
damn annoying geezer, my benefactor.
Hm?
...it's so obvious where it is.
That's...
Boss! I see the Sexy Foxy!
Why...? What happened to me?
Like I said, it's backwards.
How dangerous... Stop it!
What?!
--Ahoy! Ahoy!
--Good! You guys're gonna get off our ship, huh?
Sh-Shut up, you bastard!
You're hungry, aren't you?
Come and eat with us.
--Ahoy!
--Are they leaving the ship?!
Pepper, Carrot, Onion... I wonder what
the Usopp Pirates are doing now...
Ahh! Don't be ridiculous!
I can't eat with humans!
--Ahoy! Ahoy!
--Hurray! Hurray!
It's coming down!
May I ask your opinion, too?
Yipes!
Alright! Let's go, Usopp Pirates!
To protect this village's peace!
Please, our exceptional ship's doctor?
Where's that straw hat guy?
Dummy! Praising me wouldn't
make me feel happy! You jerk!
So what adventure are
you going to tell me today?
Sodium...
You're right. It turned pale.
Hydrogen phosphate.
He sure looks happy.
You sure are acting reckless!
Hmm, let's see...
It should've hurried up and escaped.
Does it think it's hiding wel--
We were traveling this area of sea.
What are those guys doing?
The story of when I fought the giant
goldfish at the South Pole when I was five!
They've already gone to their ship.
You bastard! How dare you manipulate me?!
Guess I'm just wasting my breath
asking you to stop, huh?
Nami, are you really sure
we're on the right track?
Goldfish?
Yeah! What first shocked me
was the immense size of its poop!
I'm gonna catch and fillet you!
Don't worry. The Log Pose
is pointing this direction.
Hey, what's going on with him?
Guys... You all couldn't forget about Boss
even after we got separated, huh?
Usopp! Can't you see anything yet?
Oh, his feelings are hurt in his own way.
It was so big that I landed on it,
thinking it was solid ground!
It's probably a kind of hypnosis.
I bet it's because of that kid!
"Now, catch me if you can!"
Err, hold on, okay?
I see, I see...
Let's see... Ah! I see an island!
"You really piss me off! Hold it!"
Hmph! What a hassle. Let's all
work together and stop him.
You can all come back to the Foxy Pirates.
I had a dream that I wanted to
become a pirate like my old man.
"Hahaha! You can't catch me!"
"Then how about this?!"
There are coral reefs scattered all over.
But to think that I became a pirate
when I had to leave them to do so...
Leave us alone.
"I'm right here!"
It's dangerous to keep heading ashore like this.
What's the matter, you guys?
"What?! No way! Now, I'm getting serious!"
You guys, just hurry up and go.
I'll take care of him.
Let's drop anchor off the coast
tonight and land tomorrow morning.
Let's have fun together again!
"There, I've caught you!"
What?
Why am I with humans?
That's not possible, Foxy-san.
Are you saying you don't
wanna listen to your navigator?
Sanji-kun, Luffy won't be having dinner.
"I'm not gonna let you go!"
The only ones I trusted were
Dr. Hiriluk and Doctorine.
--What?!
--Okay, Nami-san!
What'd you say?! Who the hell are you?!
I'm sorry.
Okay. Let's go.
Even among the reindeers, I had
no friends. I was always alone.
This ship is now under the control
of the Fang-Frog Pirates!
After that, everyone went to bed except
for me, as I was doing some research,
You're next, Usopp!
--What?
--But he's fighting pirate hunter Roronoa Zoro.
and the swordsman, who was standing watch.
Those guys are now my underlings!
I will never shoot you!
"I'm going to play my... trump card"?!
In other words, he isn't someone
who can be stopped so easily... huh?
I know it's not much, but that's about it.
My name is Dr. Hiriluk!
Fang-Frog? Who's that?
The rest is what you remember... probably...
I'm a doctor!
That's right. What we have
to do first is capture the boy.
In other words, there's no disease
in this world that can't be cured.
What?!
Ah... If I remember right, they're the ones
Given the way the pirate hunter talked earlier,
who lost in the Davy Back Fight
and had stuff taken away.
No matter what anyone says about me,
I'll save this country as a doctor!
it seems he fell asleep
partway through the night.
And this time, Foxy got
his ship taken over by them?
It would seem so.
Would you like another cup?
What a stupid guy that Split-Head is.
That's why I raised this skull
towards all the diseases!
Yes, thank you.
Well, it is a motley crew of pirates
won by playing games, after all.
C-Can't be...!
In any case, I wonder why only you
didn't lose your memory, Robin-san...
Skull...
That's right! This is a symbol of
the belief that nothing is impossible!
Bellemere-san... is that you?
Gum-Gum...
I think I'll pass on the send-off.
If the swordsman was really asleep,
the only difference between you guys and me
Hey, let's go. We've got no business here.
By raising this, I'll fight just like pirates do!
is that you were sleeping and I wasn't.
Hold it!
...Pistol!
I've got some business with you.
Although I was asleep, I remember!
I'm certain that we're the Usopp Pirates!
Doctor...!
My friends? On top of that, six of them?
My underlings still won't
take off those strange masks.
In other words, sleep determined
whether we lost our memory or not?
Kaya...!
I can't believe that I'm the
ship's doctor for a pirate ship!
It's quite annoying, but it seems they're
still devoted to their former captain.
Are you better now?
I just stated the facts, that's all.
I can't draw any conclusions.
Is that how he goes about stopping his friend?
But what if it's true...
If you get hit with a punch
like that, you could get killed!
I've never heard of such a case.
It's probably because they
don't like their new captain.
Now, it's your turn.
Because the swordsman is his friend...
They won't.
Please tell me the very last thing you remember.
My dream won't be lost. It must
be the same for you guys, too.
Because he realizes his strength...
Whoa! Boss is kinda cool.
...he knows he can't stop him
unless he fights with all his might.
I thought I went to pick
medicinal herbs with Doctorine,
For a split-head.
Like it or not, small fries
follow the strong after all.
I see...
returned to the castle and went to bed.
And then, when I woke up, I was here.
I've been traveling with monstrous guys, huh?
Whoa!
As for me... Hey, you're ignoring me?
If they see you get beaten up,
they'll probably come to their senses.
Now, let's hurry.
I fainted after being
swallowed by a big whirlpool.
Whoooa!
And the next thing I knew, I was here.
How have you been?!
Fight me, Silver Fox Foxy!
I'll leave things here to you, Zoro.
I thought I went to bed in my room after work,
How conceited... You think you can defeat me?!
These are...
but when I woke up, I was here.
So you don't remember
anything after those points, huh?
...afterimages of their memories...
Three-Sword Style! Whoa!
Looks like he'll accept.
That's right! I heard the sound
of a horn from somewhere and...
Hey, Split-Head is on fire!
Come check it out already!
A horn... Yeah, a horn! I heard it, too.
Nami, Zoro, just wait. I'm coming for you now!
His head...
Gum-Gum...
...is on fire?
Come to think of it...
Boss...
...Gatling!
A child suddenly appeared before my eyes!
What's the matter, Porche, Hamburg?
Show some happiness.
Everyone! Wake up!
You wanna fight, you jerks?!
I'll kick all your asses at once!
We've been up for a while now.
The cook and the ship's doctor
said that they're coming along.
He's gonna give this ship
and my subordinates back to me.
Don't tell me... It's not that
we lost our memories...
Hm?
We can't just abandon that lady.
...but in fact, that the kid
stole our memories from us?
We Foxy Pirates challenge you
Fang-Frog Pirates to a Davy Back Fight!
Also, Robin-san needs a bodyguard, too, so...
I don't know if that's the case,
If someone gets injured, you'll be in
trouble without me, a doctor, right?
but it's certain that he
holds the key to this matter.
I'll teach you who the real captain is!
So I'm taking on the job of guarding the ship!
Isn't it possible that we'll lose more
memories each time we fall asleep?
--Come along with us too, Usopp!
--Like I said...
--Ahhhh!
Oni... Giri!
Well, actually, I've got "My Heart Will
Stop Once on the Island" disease.
What's going on?!
Don't scare me like that!
Hey, wait. It happened in my dream, right?
Shoot...!
--Ow, ow, ow...
--Just come with us.
A supernatural thing like that
can't actually happen, right?
I know that Usopp, a brave warrior
of the sea, has his moments.
Then how do you explain the fact
that we all had the same dream?
Dammit! I can't move!
Supernatural or not, it's the fact.
I don't mean to scare you,
but in the worst-case scenario,
Well, I guess.
All right! We'll all go!
You said you'd beat me up, huh?
it's possible that you will no longer
be able to tell who you are.
Shoot! I just got too elated...
What is it saying?
If it's duels you want, why don't
we start with us captains?!
"Thanks to you guys, I even lost all the
memories I collected from the villagers.
So, how are we gonna get to the island?
Whoa! That scared me!
How about using a raft?
I assume you have no objection?
But if I can obtain all your rich memories,
Hey, why do you care if we
remember things or not?
Oh, that's a good idea.
We're counting on you, Usopp!
Boss is quite confident, isn't he?
Why me?! I'm Captain Usopp!
I can become one!"
Sure, it sucks that I lost all those fun memories,
He's got that stuff, so...
Become what?
Is he gonna use that?
I don't know.
Well, what else would he do?
Yeah, yeah...
but we can just start over and go on
new adventures together, right?
At the very least, I'm a sniper!
Here I come! Slow-Slow Beam!
Either way, there's no way I could
do stuff like a shipwright would do.
D-Don't be ridiculous! We may
end up losing all our memories!
To make a raft, all you have to do
is to put logs together, right?
I-If that happens, our past
and dreams will all be--
Whaaa...
...aaat?!
They won't.
That's easy!
Are those knots done right?
My dream won't be lost. It must
be the same for you guys, too.
Guys! Take him down!
"I'm not going to miss this opportunity!"
Well, that's pretty much it.
Hey, hey... Knots like that will untie
right away and the logs will drift apart.
Wh-What a positive thinker he is...
That beam of yours is no
threat at all once I reflect it!
Oh, that's right!
If we're gonna make one,
I want a cool-looking one.
Our captain is the same...
whether or not he has his memories.
Right here are a cook, a ship's doctor,
a sniper, and me, a navigator.
How about this?!
I already know your trick.
He's kinda amazing.
Boss!
No! This one is cooler!
There's no problem sailing out
on the ship with these members.
Hey! What're you doing?!
Ahh! My food is gone!
According to my tastes, it should be this!
Stop right there!
Say, everyone!
Drop your weapon!
Hey!
You guys call yourselves pirates when
you can't even make a decent raft?!
Hm?
Don't touch other people's food!
Are you really gonna listen
to that woman and follow her?
Sorry...
I don't know if he's crazy or what...
Whoa...
--Hm?
--Pirates are all devious and sneaky.
What amazing workmanship!
...but I feel like I'm an idiot for
thinking about things seriously!
Damn... it...!
Usopp has his moments!
You're being deceived by that
pirate named Luffy and this woman!
I admit, I have no idea myself why I built it...
It's about time for you to notice that!
All right! We're off!
Where's the town?
If you come with me, I'll take
you wherever you wish to go!
Guys, did you see how stupid
your former boss looked?
Thanks for letting me stay.
How much do I owe you?
Don't you wanna go back to
your hometown? Don't you?!
Hm? Who are you?
You don't have to be loyal
to a guy like that! Got that?!
What? I'm your inn guest
who stayed here last night.
Hey, you! Wasn't it supposed
to be a duel?! That's dirty!
Do you know her?
No, I don't know her.
I have a place that I wanna go
back to... That I have to go back to.
Is it possible that she's a thief?
Wh-What?!
You're an outsider, so shut up!
This is kinda exciting!
Hold on a sec! I'm your guest!
To start with, I never said that
I'd accept the Davy Back Fight.
There's no telling where they're taking me.
Wha...
I met all three of you yesterday, right?
"Inn" "Inn"
What're you making?
A-A new medicine for regaining
memories! Don't interfere.
Rather than being with monsters
like them, maybe I should go with her.
That bastard...!
You guys really don't remember me? Manager?
What the heck is that?!
Don't. It's their fight.
--Did you find something?
--Ahhh! Don't touch that without asking!
And...
Manager? Me?
--No. It seems like an ordinary island.
--Ugh! What the heck is this? It's bitter!
It has nothing to do with you.
...who am I?!
All right! Done!
He's the manager, right?
Who are you guys?
Sure, I, too, have a place like that.
Oh, is he?
He's right.
Right?! Right?! Right?!
This is, indeed, my great invention.
Who am I?
Then what's there to think about?
Let's go back together.
What the heck is that?
Just shut up and watch, Straw Hat...
Thanks for asking! Now...
I'm lucky that I got a free stay out of it,
but what on earth is going on?
Watch the proud Silver Fox Foxy fight!
I can't blame you for not trusting us,
since you don't remember things.
Hey, the one who's drowning over there!
...we don't have to worry
even if we lose our memories!
--Huh?
--Do you know?
Could this be...
How would I know?!
But just take my word for it and come with me.
I name them, "My name board"!
Ah! What the hell is that?!
Who are you?
See? Did you hear that?! She's deceiving us!
"All right! I was able to
become a Millennial Dragon"?
You guys lost your memories, too?
That's a good idea.
A question mark? That's rude!
The fox guy is gone.
I was like that...
--You...!
--Amazing! You can understand what it's saying?!
I'm not a raccoon dog or emergency food!
Where did he go?!
Everyone has a dream... that they
want to achieve on this sea.
...yesterday...!
That way! I saw him go that way! It's true!
"Stupid Lovelyn"?!
How do you like my idea? Cool, huh?
--Err...
--Hey... This raccoon dog talks!
Oh, that way, huh?!
About yesterday?
Don't be silly!
Yeah. I think they came to this village.
You think we'd fall for that?!
Ahhh! Am I a raccoon dog?!
There's no way we could live just
by chasing our dreams as we please!
Don't make stupid stuff!
A moss-head swordsman and a woman
on a strange vehicle. Did you see them?
My memories... huh...?
A talking raccoon dog and a Millennial Dragon...
Give me a break!
I wonder if they're having a party or something.
Yeah... But...
Yesterday... what did I do?
Maybe I'll go check it out.
People are such fragile things, Zoro...
And a damn bastard who almost drowned...
You too?! Seriously, what the heck
is with the people on this island?!
...what could be more
important than your dream?
Oh, so, you'd rather have that girl
chasing you than stay with me, Doctor?
What the heck...?
Just watching that dragon...
somehow gets me pissed off! Why?!
Ah...
To think no one even
remembers about yesterday!
"Let's chase our dreams.
There's nothing funner than that."
Zoro...
What carefree people!
What happened? How? Why?
Okay, it's your turn, Robin.
Is it an issue of being carefree?
You're lucky, Zoro. You're a boy.
I'm sure our captain would say that.
We can't complain about them.
Strange... Why am I here?
--What?
--We, too, can't...
I want to be the world's
greatest swordsman, too!
The cause might be the same.
Amazing!
You see, when girls grow up,
they get weaker than men...
One roasted fox, coming up!
A dragon, huh? I wanna ride it!
What're we gonna do? It'll be kinda
tough finding them in this situation.
I...
Are you an idiot? There's no
way you can ride it from...
Boss...
It's frustrating!
I'll go with Nami.
Okay, then. Let's go back to the ship.
You don't know until you try... Ahh!
Boss!
If only... If only I had been born a man...!
Hey, let's go back to our hometowns.
Staying on this creepy island won't
do us any good. Right? Let's go back.
Don't be whining like that after you beat me!
I'll go with Luffy.
That's not fair! You're my goal!
Get back here! I'm your boss!
What the heck is he?!
Why?!
He accepted me as his friend...
Nami!
--Zoro...
--Boy this, girl that!
Oh, shoot!
Are you gonna say that stuff
too when I beat you someday?!
What's going on?! My arms and legs stretch!
Wait up.
You act like none of it is skill!
...just like Dr. Hiriluk and Doctorine did!
You're insulting all the hard
training I've been doing!
This is fun!
Hey...
Besides... before I go to the
place I need to go back to...
He really jumped on it...
So don't say that stuff! Promise me!
Aren't weapons something
you use against your enemy?
Wait... What's with his body?!
Before I achieve my dream...
Someday, one of us will be
the world's greatest swordsman!
This is terrible...
He's a monster.
Before anything, I have to catch
that damn brat and kick his ass.
Why did you run away, Nami?
Why do you hurt your own subordinate?!
We'll compete to see who gets there!
I'll never give this to you!
Even if you kill me, I won't give this to you!
Hm?
It's dangerous! Hey, keep still!
If you rely only on power, you're nothing
but the head of a group of thugs.
Don't say that! There's no way
we'd hurt a pretty lady like you!
You dummy. You're so weak...
I-I can't believe you guys...
It's a promise!
So, we're gonna go.
We won't even lay a finger on you!
You don't have the caliber
to be the captain of a ship.
Sensei...
Though I want to, to be honest...
Now, shall we go?
Let me have... that sword...
What kind of disease does he have?
Do something about it, doctor.
Just give up on this ship
and my subordinates as well.
Somehow that thing looks like it's in pain.
Kuina's sword?
I'm going to get stronger for her, too!
It's definitely a serious condition,
but I'm also sure that there's no cure for it.
"Let go of me! Hey! The memories
are going to leak out"?!
I'm going to get strong enough
that my name reaches to Heaven!
Then, let's make a deal.
Dammit! We can't just go back without
getting our memories back, can we?!
I won't give you anything-- not a single thing.
Memories?
A deal?
I'll give you 10% of this treasure.
I'm going to be the world's
strongest swordsman!
So take me to Cocoyashi Village using that ship!
What? Ahh... Hey!
Shut up!
I promised her...
I... I...
--No.
--Then, how about 20%?
Geez... Now that it's come to this,
even if it's just me, I'll...
--No.
--Then, 30%!
Boss!
Yes. You can have it.
--No.
--Pretending that there's no tomorrow, 50%!
Ah...
Hey, Split-Head!
No.
Gold...!
Hang in there!
Just how much do you want to rip me off for?!
I leave Kuina's spirit and dreams... with you.
You love treasure.
Hey!
Again and again...
There's no way you're thinking
of sharing any of it with us.
Oh... It's you, Straw Hat...
How can you tell what I'm thinking?!
After that, I trained hard every day
and set out to sea to search for that man.
How dare you steal our memories?!
I guess that was pretty pathetic, huh?
You bastard!
Aiming to become a master swordsman...
Because we're friends, of course!
I got on a boat and went to sleep.
I remember up to that point.
Me, friends with you guys?! Give me a break!
Say... would you do me a favor?
What is it saying?! Chopper!
After that... I can't remember
what happened after that at all.
There's no way we're friends!
The negotiations broke down. See ya!
Chopper? M-Me?
What's weird, in the first place, is these swords.
This...
Who else could it be?! Right?!
When on earth did I obtain these two swords?
Would you take this...?
Please move.
I won't. Nami, you come along with us, too.
And yet, they suit me quite well.
What's going on?!
Yep!
That match was the best stage of my entire life.
"I was finally able to become a
Millennial Dragon! Don't interfere!"
No way! Why would I go with you guys?!
Who's there?!
Oh, yeah?!
Please move!
I won't.
Navigator.
People's memories aren't yours to take!
You've been feeling something's odd too,
since you came to this island.
Hey... that's...
If you wanna become a Millennial Dragon,
You're super groovy right now!
become one by making your own big memory!
Am I wrong?
The most current date on the logbook
is the day before the newspaper.
Three-Sword Style... Secret Technique!
"Shut up! Take this! This is it!"
What's the matter, lady?
So it's consistent... but...
Gum-Gum...
I'm your opponent!
A child with a strange horn...
Now, bring it on, Fang-Frog Pirates!
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
I kicked his ass. And then,
smoke came out from the horn.
Afro!
Hey, hey, this has nothing to do with you.
I can't believe it... Is what
that woman said all true?
When I thought it went into my body...
--It does!
--I don't wanna fight a guy with a
100-million-Berry bounty on his head.
If it is...
The captain's memories came back.
...Bazooka!
If you wanna fly that bad...
No way. Wasn't it a dream or something?
I'm a member of a pirate group...
What good will it do me to fight you?
I'll send you flying!
Three Thousand Worlds!
Me...?!
There's... There's no way that's the case!
It's true. I saw it clearly with my own eyes.
What're you saying?
But this tattoo... What on earth happened to it?
That damn brat... I feel like I saw
him the night before last, too.
If you defeat the Straw Hats,
you'll get the 160-million-Berry bounty.
Why did he come twice?
I don't know what's going on!
Maybe because he couldn't steal
all your memories in one shot.
And, that's not all.
Strange things sometimes
happen in the Grand Line.
I don't know...
They have a mountain of gold on their ship.
Even with just what I know,
you guys have experienced an
incredible number of adventures.
You seem to be in excellent spirits,
pathetic humans!
Sailors suddenly losing their memories
one day during their voyages...
I bet that's worth quite a bit.
He couldn't eat them all in one shot, so he
returned yesterday on an empty stomach?
As of this moment,
this island is under my control!
Yep, yep.
You've heard things like that, haven't you?
Are you shocked?! Just take it, you thieves!
I think that's what happened.
On this memorable day, you will
all buy your lives from me!
That phenomenon is
happening on this island, then?
Oh? I wonder if memories taste good.
Geez... When did they...?
Those who can't pay... die!
On the stone monument
we found on our way here,
Then that kid is...
Why is he talking proudly about it?
See you later!
I don't want to.
I'd better check later to
make sure nothing is missing.
a story was written about a monster
who lives off of people's memories.
Why do we have to leave?
All right, then! Let's kick that kid's ass again
A-A mountain of gold...
I... want to live in this village...
It seems like it has this island as its base.
Seriously...?
--Hey...
--Hm?
and get everyone's memories back!
Prepare to fire! The target is Straw Hat!
This story is practically a legend,
You're gonna catch a cold.
Is it because we're poor that I can't
be Bellemere-san's kid anymore?!
If we do that, Zoro will
probably come back, too.
Yeah!
but thinking that way makes the most sense.
I'm doubtful whether it'd go that smoothly,
but we have to get even with that damn brat.
Hold it!
Since memories are created every day,
Fire!
That 100,000's for my two daughters.
I don't got enough for me.
Why don't we forget about Zoro?!
it must be eating the islanders'
memories little by little.
I kicked its ass!
Even if we regain our
memories by some chance,
I see. So it's like a broiler, huh?
it's kinda unsettling to be on
the same ship as a pirate hunter.
Bellemere! What are you--?!
I'm sorry, Gen-san. I just can't
say I don't have a family...
Hmm... Although I have a
hard time buying that story,
At any rate...
Zoro is the swordsman. Nami is the navigator.
--Let's go join him!
--Yeah!
...if I remember right,
don't Millennial Dragons hatch from eggs?
Both of them are our friends that we need.
it's also true that we're
missing some of our memories.
What're you gonna do?
Even if it costs me my life...
Even if you say so, I'm in a bind!
Hey!
Yeah, maybe we're not related by blood...
Stop right there!
Yeah. You can't become one
just by eating memories.
To think that I'm one of you...
What?!
I'm the one who'll be in
a bigger bind without you.
...but we're a family.
Is that right?
Just hand over the gold nice and...
I want to be their parent,
even if it's only in name.
Yeah, you probably don't know it,
Without a navigator,
the ship can't go anywhere!
I guess this won't be settled unless
we take them all out, huh? Good grief...
but we saw it with our own eyes
before we entered the Grand Line.
They're... my kids.
Seriously, pirates are really persistent.
Robin, can you tell where that kid is?
Really?
Well, forget that. People must be
making a racket in the village by now!
Bellemere-san!
I'm gonna manipulate you guys
just like that swordsman
Well... there's a place that I want to check out.
Ha! We've got 500 crew members!
and have you guys crush each other.
After all, we're their benefactors who
got all the villagers' memories back!
Take him down!
Okay then! Let's go!
I'm sorry! I was never able to
do anything mother-like for you!
H-Hey! My gold is...!
We weren't listening!
I won't let a lady carry stuff!
Hey!
No doubt they're gonna treat us like heroes!
Too bad they weren't listening, huh?
That's not true!
If I can be with you, Nami-san,
this is no trouble at all!
First all-you-can-drink party
we've had in a while, huh?
We don't need anything! Just don't die!
Oh, no!
Nami...
Hey, look at that!
There's something you wanna forget?
Ahh... I have a bad feeling about this.
Hm?
Make your dream... come true!
Shut up.
Ah! Hold it!
Seems like we can expect
them to reward us good!
--Wh-What's going on?!
--What are these hands?! Ugh!
Hands are growing out of my head!
Live...!
No matter what they say, they all follow Luffy.
I want a bronze statue.
What's going on?!
So, how is it, Fang-Frog?
My brother is strong, isn't he?
Looks like you should be the first.
I'm gonna be so popular
with girls, huh? Not bad.
I wonder if it's true that I now have friends...
Die with your pathetic love.
Nojiko! Nami!
It's not my style to kick a brat, but...
After all, he's so strong--
What about you, Robin? If you're able
to get something, what would you like?
What're you doing?! Hurry up, Chopper!
No, it's not the boy!
that you can't find anyone besides me--
who can defeat him.
Okay!
Books, as expected?
Yeah. If possible, maybe books
on this island's history.
You guys, go easy on them--
you don't wanna kill them.
I love you!
I knew it! I want a medical book--
one that's this thick!
They're just ordinary humans.
Take this!
I'm joining the Arlong Pirates...
We can see the seashore now.
Sword... Catch...!
...to be a surveyor and draw sea charts!
Nami...
I made an agreement with Arlong
to buy Cocoyashi Village from him.
Hey, ladies and gentlemen!
Thanks for coming to greet us!
What're you doing, you damn cook?!
To buy the village?
For 100 million Berries. If I buy
the village, we can be free.
You bastard! You pushed Nami-san
down earlier, didn't you?!
Huh?
But, 100 million Berries?
--What?!
--Why?!
I did it to save her! Got a problem with that?!
I'm not sure you can earn that
much working your entire life!
Wh-What on earth was I...
What're you gonna do if she gets
seriously injured, you idiot?!
I will earn it! No matter what it takes!
U-Um... H-Hey...
If you wanna eat, help yourself.
It's true that I am hungry,
I-It's them!
To start with, you don't know how to treat ladi...
If I ask for help from anyone,
more people will get hurt.
Everyone! Attack!
Was it you who stole our memories?
Sword...
but I don't eat this kind of stuff.
Ahhh! What's going on?!
I see.
Like I said, what's your problem, you bastard?!
Usopp! Aren't we supposed to be heroes?!
Why aren't you asking who I am?
It'll hurt, you know...
Shut up! We weren't done yet, were we?!
Yeah...
Beats me! I wanna ask that question myself!
Oh, yeah... People on this island
don't even remember their own names.
Cook... That boy was just
being manipulated, that's all.
Staying with the people who
killed Bellemere-san'll hurt.
What's the deal? Wanna fight?!
Nami-san! Where's the waver?
This way!
You thought it was no use asking, huh?
If you survive, lots of fun things will happen!
Hold it! Stop right there, pirates!
The real culprit is...
Out of the way!
You set out on a journey to become
the world's strongest, right, mister?
You damn memory thieves!
I'll be fine. I'll put on a big smile,
even when I see his face!
You damn girl! Pay your bill!
Oh... a human firework.
Looks like they're in full swing.
Then, to you, Monkey D. Luffy is
the perfect opponent, you know.
Hm?
What's with them?! They think we did it!
I've decided not to cry anymore.
My chronic abdominal spasms...
I've decided to fight on my own!
Looks like it.
Well, we're pirates. It can't be helped, huh?
Hey, hold it.
I'm Luffy! Nice to meet you!
H-Hey, are you oka--?
That straw hat guy?
Give us back what belongs to us,
or I can't let you go through here.
I'm surprised that Roronoa Zoro
couldn't perceive his strength.
You got tricked, young fellow.
Now that it's come to this,
we're to the point of desperation!
Bellemere-san...
I couldn't perceive it?
Hey! Hold it! Stop it!
Can't wait...
That's right. In the East Blue,
Oh, no. This is bad. I'm a doctor.
Let me take a look.
"I went to so much trouble
to get such tasty memories.
What pirate would stop just
because they're told to stop?!
I'll steal all the rest... All the rest...
he destroyed the vicious fishman
pirate group, Arlong Pirates.
I hate doctors!
I'm not gonna give them back, you idiot!"
Here in the Grand Line,
he brought down Crocodile,
What?!
one of the Seven Great Pirates, all by himself.
That was Ketchup Star.
Our ship's doctor can
understand animal languages.
Ow, ow, ow... My back...
Seven Great Pirates?
Don't talk nonsense, you idiot!
Oh, shoot.
Hey, pull yourse--
That's not all.
Did I wake you up?
On the sky islands, he even
beat up the god named Eneru.
Ouch!
--No...
--You can go back to sleep.
I'm glad we made it back.
If I notice something unusual, I'll wake you up.
He's saying, "How rude!
I'm not an idiot! I'm a sea horse!"
Oh, yeah... He went on a
rampage in a Navy base, too!
It's okay. Sorry, Robin-san.
Gum-Gum...
A big bronze statue... It was so close...
Against Luffy, even the
Navy throws up its hands.
Shall I make some coffee to help us stay awake?
Ouch!
That's not the point!
...Whip!
Thanks. That would be great.
...to being built... A big, dark statue...
I've never seen a pirate like that before!
At any rate, he's sleeping like a log,
Don't talk nonsense!
after saying that he was gonna
stay awake no matter what.
I don't have time to listen to lies like that.
Ahh! You...!
At any rate...
Gum-Gum...
Ah! You...!
To think that losing memories
would turn into such a big fuss...
Hey, now you want to fight Luffy, don't you?
...Pistol!
So you two weren't asleep yet?
Hurry up and spit out our memories!
Yeah, I totally agree.
So it was you who stole everyone's memories?
There was even some guy who
schemed to make us his pirate crew.
I'm surprised that you've noticed.
You jerk! What on earth...
Well... Sanji-kun... I just got
carried away... I just got carried away.
But it's too late.
Oh? I...
It's not...
On the other hand,
Wake up! Everyone, wake up now!
there was a damn simpleton
whose body and soul got taken over.
That was splendid, Straw Hat.
...over yet!
Oh? I see you have some mysterious technique.
You're as marvelous as ever.
--Huh?
--Hm?
What'd you say?!
Ugh! He's here!
To start with, if you were
actually standing guard,
Hm? What's this place?
Hm?
--Ahhh!
--What? Breakfast?
I was just pulled in by your passion.
--Sanji-kun!
--My memories are back!
this racket wouldn't have happened,
you idiot moss-head!
That wasn't nice, lady.
To think that you woke them up...
We all got our memories back!
Let me tell you just one thing.
Shut up! I was sleepy!
Cook, how about you?
Of course, I got them back, too!
Robin-chan! Nami-san!
I guess it can't be helped now.
I didn't wanna do this.
If you wanna sleep that much,
sleep for the rest of your life!
Oh, stop it. We're friends.
You don't have to thank me.
Is that weird brat here? This is kinda creepy.
Argh! Shut up! That's enough!
Even after I got my memories back,
you two are beautiful!
I-I wonder if I caught a cold or something.
Or would you like to lose your memories again?
I've been feeling a chill for a while.
But...
Oh, Nami-san! Please don't say things like that!
I wish we had a doctor at a time like this.
...we don't know if that moss-head
guy got his memories back...
Hm? Ahhhh!
What're you doing there?!
That's me!
Slow-Slow Beam!
--What?
--I'm not gonna let you take that place!
If Zoro didn't get his
memories back, what on earth...
I bet these people are trying to take me
to a deserted place and steal the gold!
Huh?!
I've decided that that place is my special seat!
My memories...
Don't you dare...
...sit there without asking!
That's our Boss!
Zoro...!
I won't let that happen!
If I hadn't gotten my memories back...
Where is Luffy?
Nami-san has been giving me
passionate eyes all this time!
Remember this good, Straw Hat!
Did Luffy get cut down by Zoro?
...what would I have...
I am Silver Fox Foxy, a man
who obtains whatever he wants.
What's wrong... Robin?
There's no doubt! She fell in love with me!
What?
--Wink!
--Wh-What?!
Don't tell me... It can't be...
I'm sorry.
I'm okay.
Is that a sign that he's gonna steal
the gold?! What a creepy guy!
Okay.
I'm a little sleepy, that's all.
Your luck ran out when you
got on this ship, you fool.
Whoa?! Wh-What's this? What's this?
It's just natural. Robin-chan hasn't
slept much because of this racket.
I see...
Ah, a butterfly!
Just clearing up the humiliation of
the Davy Back Fight wouldn't satisfy me.
Where's our captain?
Did you find something out, Robin?
Argh! What the heck is this?!
--Oh, that's right!
--All right then!
I'll take the 160 million Berries
along with the gold.
It's scary!
I'll make a special healthy dinner with
a mixture of herbal medicines tonight!
I figured out the culprit who
took your memories away...
Ah, food! I forgot about it!
No... I mean, the real culprit.
You... idiot...!
You damn swordsman...!
Sanji! Food!
That damn brat isn't the culprit?
Wh-What was that?
If you're gonna harm the ladies,
I'll be your opponent.
All right!
I'm gonna make it now, so just wait quietly!
Now, let's head to the Sea God's Palace.
Hey, isn't he in trouble?
This time for sure, I'll show you
--Say, Luffy.
--Hm?
He's not moving.
that we, the Foxy Pirates,
are the strongest pirates!
Why didn't you come back
with Zoro at that time?
The Sea God's Palace?
Is he still alive?
What the heck is that?
Doctor! Doctor!
Oh... Well, I got stuck
under a rock Zoro cut down.
Oh, right, that's me.
I'm calling it that for now...
--A rock?!
--Yeah. That was one huge, hard rock.
My memories are back!
He said, "I still haven't
played my trump card yet"!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Ahh, this really was a bad idea!
Now, things have been settled.
To the next island, full speed ahead!
All right! My memories are back!
You are all my friends!
Zoro! You put the afro on, too!
That's right! Fire up your brotherly soul!
I feel it's pointless to go with you guys!
What the heck is that thing saying?
Cook, swordsman, navigator,
doctor, scholar, and... liar.
Geez, you're full of hot air!
She's right. Hey, let's go back. Let's go back!
"If I can obtain all your rich
memories, I can become one!"
Stop it!
The moss-head man looks cool!
I think with this incident, you've all
learned how important memories are.
--Hey...
--Well then, we'll go bring back Nami and Zoro!
No. We're going to bring Zoro back.
--Black moss-head.
--I'm gonna cut you down, you jerks!
That damn swordsman is coming this way.
Become what?!
I totally agree about Nami-san,
but we don't need that man.
What are you trying to summarize for?
Oh, you're right. Hey!
I don't know.
Wait. Something is odd.
Hm? I feel like I just saw something
I don't wanna remember.
His wildness awakened!
--Right, we don't.
--I guess we don't. No! We do!
Geez... Like I said, what's with this afro stuff?
Oh, that Split-Head is...
Really? Zoro is always like this.
He's saying that he's gonna play
his trump card! Everyone, watch out!
We can't do without even one person!
--You put it on, too, Nami!
--No!!
On the next episode of One Piece!
Boss?!
"Now, Let's Get Back Our Memories!
The Pirate Crew Lands on the Island"
"Zoro Bares His Fangs!
A Savage Animal Stands in the Way!"
"The Guy Who's the Closest to Invincible?
And the Most Dangerous Man!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Last Counterattack by the Memory
Thief Who Revealed His True Colors!"
"Proud Man! Silver Fox Foxy"
I'm gonna cut you jerks down!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
Him again?