It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
That straw hat guy?
I'm surprised that Roronoa Zoro
couldn't perceive his strength.
I couldn't perceive it?
Hey, now you want to fight Luffy, don't you?
I see...
Did you find something out, Robin?
I figured out the culprit who
took your memories away...
No... I mean, the real culprit.
That damn brat isn't the culprit?
Now, let's head to the Sea God's Palace.
The Sea God's Palace?
What the heck is that?
I'm calling it that for now...
"Zoro Bares His Fangs!
A Savage Animal Stands in the Way!"
So that damn brat's home turf is ahead of here?
--Yeah.
--Hey, so, who's the real culprit?
Isn't it about time you told us?
I'm pretty sure you'll know when
we get to the Sea God's Palace.
Don't tell me... they're gonna take
me deep in the jungle, lock me up,
and then they're gonna take the gold away...!
Oh, no...!
I wonder if he really is here...
This place seems kinda peaceful.
D-Don't let your guard down.
This is that damn brat's home turf.
He might have crazy monsters
as his subordinates.
M-Monsters?
To start with, monsters
normally hide themselves,
and then suddenly go "boo!" and attack you.
You see...
I don't know how many times monsters
lay in ambush waiting for me
when I was traveling around the ocean.
B... Behind you!
Hm? What's the matter? Did you
see a monster or something?
That stuff won't work on...
--Get if off!
--Nooo! Hey, keep away from me!
--Hey, please! Please! Please!
--S-Stop it! Stop it!
--Hm?
What're they doing?
I hate snakes! I hate snakes!
I finally stopped.
That damn giant snake! It got scared
of me, Captain Usopp, and ran away!
--Hey!
--Hm?
We got separated from everyone!
What're we gonna do, you jerk?!
What? Oh, shoot!
What're we gonna do if
monsters attack us now?!
Hm? Oh, don't worry about it.
I just told you a little joke to scare you.
Oh, so it was just a joke.
Hey! You made fun of me?! You jer...
M-Monster!
So it wasn't a joke?!
If you're gonna eat, eat him!
--He'd make a good raccoon dog soup!
--Stop it! No!
Huh...? Oh, it's you. You scared us.
Oh, man... Another scary guy came back.
At any rate, he seems kinda different
from when he was on the ship.
Well, if you agree to mend
your ways and be faithful to me,
then I'll accept you as one of the great
Captain Usopp's subordinates... Hm?
Hey... H-Hey! Don't ignore me!
Wait! Do you know where everyone is?
Hm?
Hey! Don't leave me here alone!
Hey! Wait up!
--Hm?
--Hey!
Oh, Zoro!
That damn swordsman again?
Hm? He's...
So you decided to come along with us?
--Watch out!
--Captain!
What is it?
What happened?!
Hey, what'd you do that for all of a sudden?
Hm...?
Stop, both of you!
Hey, better not meddle.
That damn swordsman is giving off a totally
different air from when he was on the ship.
Don't tell me...
How dangerous... Stop it!
It's coming down!
Yipes!
Where's that straw hat guy?
You sure are acting reckless!
Guess I'm just wasting my breath
asking you to stop, huh?
Hey, what's going on with him?
It's probably a kind of hypnosis.
I bet it's because of that kid!
Hmph! What a hassle. Let's all
work together and stop him.
Leave us alone.
You guys, just hurry up and go.
I'll take care of him.
What?
Okay. Let's go.
--What?
--But he's fighting pirate hunter Roronoa Zoro.
In other words, he isn't someone
who can be stopped so easily... huh?
That's right. What we have
to do first is capture the boy.
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Is that how he goes about stopping his friend?
If you get hit with a punch
like that, you could get killed!
Because the swordsman is his friend...
Because he realizes his strength...
...he knows he can't stop him
unless he fights with all his might.
I see...
I've been traveling with monstrous guys, huh?
Now, let's hurry.
I'll leave things here to you, Zoro.
Three-Sword Style! Whoa!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Oni... Giri!
Oh, that's right!
Right here are a cook, a ship's doctor,
a sniper, and me, a navigator.
There's no problem sailing out
on the ship with these members.
Say, everyone!
Hm?
Are you really gonna listen
to that woman and follow her?
--Hm?
--Pirates are all devious and sneaky.
You're being deceived by that
pirate named Luffy and this woman!
It's about time for you to notice that!
If you come with me, I'll take
you wherever you wish to go!
Don't you wanna go back to
your hometown? Don't you?!
I have a place that I wanna go
back to... That I have to go back to.
There's no telling where they're taking me.
Rather than being with monsters
like them, maybe I should go with her.
Sure, I, too, have a place like that.
Right?! Right?! Right?!
Then what's there to think about?
Let's go back together.
I can't blame you for not trusting us,
since you don't remember things.
But just take my word for it and come with me.
See? Did you hear that?! She's deceiving us!
Everyone has a dream... that they
want to achieve on this sea.
Don't be silly!
There's no way we could live just
by chasing our dreams as we please!
Give me a break!
Yeah... But...
...what could be more
important than your dream?
Ah...
"Let's chase our dreams.
There's nothing funner than that."
I'm sure our captain would say that.
I...
I'll go with Nami.
Hey, let's go back to our hometowns.
I'll go with Luffy.
Why?!
He accepted me as his friend...
...just like Dr. Hiriluk and Doctorine did!
Besides... before I go to the
place I need to go back to...
Before I achieve my dream...
Before anything, I have to catch
that damn brat and kick his ass.
I-I can't believe you guys...
So, we're gonna go.
Now, shall we go?
Dammit! We can't just go back without
getting our memories back, can we?!
What? Ahh... Hey!
Geez... Now that it's come to this,
even if it's just me, I'll...
Ah...
Gold...!
Three-Sword Style... Secret Technique!
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
Three Thousand Worlds!
Strange things sometimes
happen in the Grand Line.
Sailors suddenly losing their memories
one day during their voyages...
You've heard things like that, haven't you?
That phenomenon is
happening on this island, then?
On the stone monument
we found on our way here,
a story was written about a monster
who lives off of people's memories.
It seems like it has this island as its base.
This story is practically a legend,
but thinking that way makes the most sense.
Since memories are created every day,
it must be eating the islanders'
memories little by little.
I see. So it's like a broiler, huh?
Hmm... Although I have a
hard time buying that story,
it's also true that we're
missing some of our memories.
Hey!
Stop right there!
What?!
Seriously, pirates are really persistent.
I'm gonna manipulate you guys
just like that swordsman
and have you guys crush each other.
Oh, no!
--Wh-What's going on?!
--What are these hands?! Ugh!
Hands are growing out of my head!
What's going on?!
Looks like you should be the first.
It's not my style to kick a brat, but...
No, it's not the boy!
Wh-What on earth was I...
Was it you who stole our memories?
Cook... That boy was just
being manipulated, that's all.
The real culprit is...
Hm?
Hey, hold it.
Give us back what belongs to us,
or I can't let you go through here.
"I went to so much trouble
to get such tasty memories.
I'm not gonna give them back, you idiot!"
What?!
Our ship's doctor can
understand animal languages.
Don't talk nonsense, you idiot!
He's saying, "How rude!
I'm not an idiot! I'm a sea horse!"
That's not the point!
Ahh! You...!
Ah! You...!
Hurry up and spit out our memories!
Oh? I...
It's not...
...over yet!
Hm?
--Sanji-kun!
--My memories are back!
We all got our memories back!
Cook, how about you?
Of course, I got them back, too!
Robin-chan! Nami-san!
Even after I got my memories back,
you two are beautiful!
But...
...we don't know if that moss-head
guy got his memories back...
If Zoro didn't get his
memories back, what on earth...
Zoro...!
Where is Luffy?
Did Luffy get cut down by Zoro?
Don't tell me... It can't be...
Where's our captain?
You damn swordsman...!
If you're gonna harm the ladies,
I'll be your opponent.
He said, "I still haven't
played my trump card yet"!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
What the heck is that thing saying?
"If I can obtain all your rich
memories, I can become one!"
Become what?!
I don't know.
He's saying that he's gonna play
his trump card! Everyone, watch out!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Last Counterattack by the Memory
Thief Who Revealed His True Colors!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!