It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
Let me tell you just one thing.
Chopper, were you able
to find any medicinal herbs?
Ice Age...
Yep. I've collected most of them,
So where do you guys wanna go?
A-A frog is doing the front crawl!
but there may be even rarer ones on this island.
Slow-Slow Beam!
What?!
It went to your side, so take a look at it!
Huh?!
More importantly, something's
been bugging me for a while.
Since we've got our own ship,
we won't take the train.
--Is that true?
--Hey, Luffy...
Remember this good, Straw Hat!
I'm impressed that you survived as a child.
I wonder what this weird groove
is that runs down this path...
We'll just follow the log.
Are you taking what that
stupid Admiral said seriously?
I see. Then it must be Water Seven.
You betrayed people and ran away.
You gained people's favor and used them.
I am Silver Fox Foxy, a man
who obtains whatever he wants.
To start with, there's no way a frog
would do the front cra... Hey, it is!
Water Seven?
Come to think of it, yeah, I wonder what it is.
Above all, it's a city that made
a name for itself with its shipyard.
You've survived in the underworld
by being quick to switch sides.
It looks as if a bicycle passed by.
A-A frog is doing the front crawl!
I'll take the 160 million Berries
along with the gold.
We'll follow it, guys!
Their technology is No. 1 in the world!
Yeah!
We're suddenly out in a large open space.
So this is the group that you
chose as your next hideout, huh?
All right! I've decided!
We're gonna go there and get a
shipwright to join our crew for sure!
This time for sure, I'll show you
Why is there a lighthouse in a place
like that? I wonder if someone's there...
The organizations Nico Robin had
something to do with up until today
that we, the Foxy Pirates,
are the strongest pirates!
all got annihilated...
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!...
Ahh... Hmm?
What the hell is this?!
...except for her.
"The Guy Who's the Closest to Invincible?
And the Most Dangerous Man!"
"Fox"
It flew!
A raccoon dog?
All right! The frog stopped. Corner it at once!
This area should be okay, don't you think?
I'm a reindeer! See? I've got antlers!
Are you okay, Chopper?!
Holy crap! The Going Merry
has gotten this rickety?
Who the heck is this?!
Luffy, what happened?!
We ran ashore on something!
What's with you guys?
Take this with you.
What's this sound?
A map?
What's with you?!
Boss!
This'll be helpful! Thanks!
Wh-Who's that huge guy?
Porche!
That's perfect. Once we get the money,
we can go to the shipyard right away.
Who's that guy?!
Hamburg!
You've come across some good friends.
But you're still you, Nico Robin!
Yeah. We can finally have
the Going Merry repaired!
Those five all fell.
Boss, what're we gonna do now?
No...! I'm no longer...
All right! Go! Yagara!
Robin...
"Navy Headquarters Admiral Aokiji!
The Ferocity of an Ultimate Powerhouse"
What else?! We're gonna
clear up the humiliation
Robin!
Thanks for your business! Be careful!
of the Davy Back Fight by
defeating the Straw Hats.
I'm...
Ow, ow, ow...
Robin-chan!
Dash to the shipyard!
Go back! Go back! Turn 180 degrees!
Porche! Hamburg!
We're gonna go with Operation D!
"The Dashing Sea Train and
the City of Water, Water Seven"
Yahoo!
"Duel between Rubber and Ice! Luffy vs. Aokiji"
"Adventure in the City on the Water!
Head to the Mammoth Shipbuilding Plant"
It sounds fun over there.
I wonder if they're still partying...
Why don't you go, too, Doctor?
I can watch our ship by myself.
What the hell is that?!
Just turn around! Now!
I-I'm in charge of watching the ship, too!
I'm also studying. I don't wanna go at all.
To think that he got Robin this shaken up...
This is great!
Who is he?
Hey! I'm counting on you!
Dammit! How dare you trick me?!
Come out, Split-Head!
It's amazing that such a convenient
creature exists in this world.
It doesn't rock much. It's comfortable!
Hey, cool down a bit, Luffy.
He's a marine.
You bastard!
To the right! Right!
Navy Headquarters Admiral... Aokiji.
That afro is getting you all worked up...
--The ball is headed your way!
--Here we go!
Don't yell... She'll still live
if you defrost her carefully.
Yeah, no doubt about it.
The afro boosts your spirits.
Admiral?!
A... Admiral? He's that high up?
Ah! Stop the ball!
What the hell is this?!
Like I said, what's with the afro?!
But her body has become fragile, so be careful.
After we went through
the trouble of saving them...
Wh-Wh-What the hell is this lump of iron?!
If her body is broken, she'll die.
To think that he returned
our kindness with malice...
There're only three officers in the Navy
who hold the position of Admiral.
For example...
--Pass the ball! Pass the ball!
--This is neato!
Yeah! And he's trying to take
our gold, too?! That's unforgivable!
A ship?
What?!
No! Something shaped like
this can't travel on the sea!
if you smash it like this...
At any rate, that guy is too optimistic.
Akainu...
Aokiji...
If we get serious and go on a rampage,
Robin!
This area seems to be a residential area.
Kizaru...
Hey, frog! Run! What're you doing?!
No!
a ship like this will be shattered
into pieces in an instant...
The only one above them
This town really is built around canals.
If the five of us do it...
is Fleet Admiral Sengoku, who reigns
as the top official in the Navy.
Stop it!!
That man is one of the three men
Hey, mister!
If the four of you do it...
called the World Government's
ultimate powerhouses.
Hey, pops!
Ahhh! It got run over!
Where are you going? Sightseeing?
Anyway, for now, we have to
figure out how to get out of here.
Wh-Why is someone like that here?!
To the shipyard! We're gonna
have our ship repaired!
Hm?
Considering how that Boss is,
I bet he's up to something sneaky!
Why don't you go deal with big-time pirates
with several-hundred-million-Berry bounties?!
Then go to the backstreet
shopping district first!
That was close...
It seems like we can get out from here.
G... Go someplace else!
Checkmate.
Hm?
Thanks!
What?!
Oh, my, my...
S-Sure...
What the hell is this room?
Backstreet shopping district...
Wh-What?
Choppy!
Here's another sexy lady with super
big bazongas! Are you free tonight?
--Good job!
--Amazing, Usopp!
We'll turn right ahead of here.
Where is Choppy?
What the hell...?
Oh, my beautiful mademoiselle!
How about dinner with me tonight?
Where're you hiding?!
What's the big idea, you tall, lanky jerk?!
Usopp! Chopper!
Pay attention, you jerk!
Run to the ship! Treat Robin and save her!
Geez... If you don't come out,
you... will... be... punished!
Huh?
Hold on a sec, you guys, geez...
The ship was puffing out smoke!
G-Got it!
Ow! Ow, ow, ow!
Did you hear what I said?
Hurry up...! But gently, okay?
Is something wrong, Doctor?
Don't worry about him. The guys
around here say that like it's a greeting.
--It's cold!
--You idiot! Think of how cold Robin is!
I said I just took a stroll, didn't I?
Don't get so worked up.
Nothing.
You jerk! I hate this kind of joke the mos--
O-Okay.
Don't bother...
To start with, you guys are...
whatchamacallit... you know...
Wait, Sanji!
It'd be better for the world
not to save that woman.
Luffy...
Hey! Hurry up and go to work already!
"Wh-Whatchamacallit"?
Pirates...?
Grandma! Grandma! Pirates are here!
"You know..."?
Err...
I know, I know. Stop nagging.
Hey, you!
What?! Is that true, Chimney?!
I forgot. Oh, well.
Not to split hairs, but a pirate group
is a collection of people like that.
Yes?
Where's Split-Head?
You don't make much sense!
At any rate, people in this
town are generous to outsiders--
Okay then, bring the Transponder Snail to me!
Huh?!
What the heck's with this guy?!
or should I say they're overly friendly?
Okay!
Hey, Robin, aren't you
mistaking him for someone else?
You got that right, lady.
Hey! You with the long nose!
This is a problem.
Someone came out of the building.
Oh, I don't know.
There's no way someone
like him is a Navy Admiral!
--Huh?
--Nothing. I was just saying hey, that's all.
Get out of my way, would you?
--Oh, you don't know?
--His cluelessness knows no bounds.
Hey, hey... Don't judge
others by their appearance.
They're gonna call for help.
Nami-san!
--Oh, no! Where did Boss go?!
--Why can't he see it?
Want a fist in your face, pops?!
--We can't...
--...just let you...
Here it is, Grandma!
--Well, if he's not around, he's not around.
I guess I'll go look somewhere else.
--Even for Luffy, this really takes the cake.
Wait, you two!
Err... Hello?
My motto as a marine is "total slovenly justice."
Let's see... What was it? I forget.
Looks like he's not here.
Luffy!
Hm?
That totally matches your appearance!
So she's drunk?!
Hm? What happened?
Don't interfere. I wanna fight him in a duel.
In any case, well...
Ah, a hill is coming up. We're gonna
go against the flow. Is that okay?
Luffy, take a close look at the face.
Oh, excuse me for a sec...
Can we go up?
What about the face?
Standing made me tired. Umph.
Oh? Paille, huh? It goes good with alcohol.
Then why were you sleeping standing up?
Let's you and me...
Are you... Split-Head's little sister?!
...settle this fight!
Whoa! This is good!
Wait! Wrong way! Go right! Right!
Anyway, to make a long story short,
That's fine...
I'm Chimney. This is our cat, Gonbe...
I have no intention of capturing
you guys, so don't worry.
So it doesn't matter even if the
water is running downhill, huh?
Argh! Enough with the disguises!
...but since I don't have a ship to
take you back in, I'll kill you, okay?
...and Grandma Kokoro.
Not bad, you guys!
Ahh! You're Split-Head! I got fooled again.
You guys aren't train robbers, are you?
I came to check the whereabouts
of Nico Robin, who disappeared
after the Alabasta incident, that's all.
I'm Luffy. I'm the man
who'll be King of the Pirates.
The canals even go above the rooftops!
She... can't breathe, can she?
I don't even feel like making a comment.
Just as I thought, she's been with you guys.
But we're going the wrong way!
We have to go to the shopping district first!
--Really?!
--Yeah.
Take this, Straw Hat! Slow-Slow Beam!
I think she's probably in a
state of suspended animation.
This guy sure is apathetic, isn't he?
What a funny guy.
Th-Then won't she die if we don't hurry up?
His audacity shows he's a leader,
in a manner of speaking.
Say, Chimney, that thing is a steamship, right?
Oh, don't be so hasty.
But if we warm her rapidly, her body will break.
I'm going to at least report
this to Headquarters, though,
This is a rare opportunity.
Let's stroll through the canals.
But with a shape like that,
it can't go on a voyage.
We need to restore her body
temperature from the inside.
Don't you guys get it?! No one
can escape the Slow-Slow Beam!
as with another wanted person, the total
bounty for you guys has now changed.
--Hm?
You've never seen something
like that, have you?
I-Is this really gonna work?
H-Hey! L-Look! Look ahead!
Even if you look all over the world,
this is the only place you can find it.
Seriously, that beam's a real pain.
I don't know... but this is the only way...
It's a sea train called the "Puffing Tom."
Yeah, seriously.
100 million... plus 60 million...
plus 79 million equals...
Oh, that's right! We're at the top of the hill!
You can't just say you don't know!
Robin's life depends on you!!
Puffing Tom?
Which means...
Slow-Slow Beam!
It turns paddlewheels using a steam
engine and runs on the sea railway.
But I've never seen a human whose
entire body got frozen like this!
--Nami!
--What?!
I don't know exactly, but I'm
sure it's not too shabby.
Hey, you bastard!
Why don't you calculate it?
Sure, Aokiji said she was still alive,
Idiot! Don't come this way!
Railway?
That's right. It runs a little
below the surface of the sea.
Gum-Gum...
Sanji-kun! Zoro!
but to me, it's surprising that she's still alive!
Oh, shoot! It hit them!
The train travels the same route every day,
This is fun!
Don't whine! If you can't do anything,
then no one can save her!
Hold on a sec! Hold on, Luffy!
Stop it! Stop it!
Hmph! You dodged it well,
Straw Hat! You play dirty!
This is fun but scary!
Nooo!
taking passengers from one island to another.
Let me go! What're you guys doing?!
Hold it, you jerk!
You're the doctor on this ship!
It carries ships and the mail as well.
What's the point in us picking a fight?!
Does he know what "dirty" means?
I know that! Just shut your mouth for a while!
She's right. There really is a railway.
He's one of the strongest marines!
Hey, Nami! Let's go!
So what?! Then are you saying we're
gonna hand over Robin without a fight?!
Then we ran ashore on that, huh?
Okay!
That's right! There's both
a signal and a partition.
Both of you, be patient for 30 seconds!
You jerk!
What?! Hold on a sec!
Well, you guys... I'm saying I'm
not gonna do anything, aren't I?
It's dangerous to come inside like that!
N-Nami-san!
But the signal should face the other way.
Otherwise, how do we see it?!
Sorry!
I'm gonna beat him up!
Stop it, Luffy!
Even if it's dangerous, that guy
wouldn't understand, right?
Hold on!
--What?!
--There's something on the door!
It wasn't nice to send him flying.
We were after him, you know.
Arrrrgh! We went flying!
Let's see... From here on,
women aren't allowed. It's a man's path.
We're falling. We're falling.
S-So you're a marine...
I wish you had told us sooner.
Chopper!
We're falling. We're falling. We're falling...
What? "That guy"? Are you
talking about Yokozuna?
We're falling!
--Hm?
--Who are these people?
What does this mean?
Yep, that front crawl frog.
Beats me. In any case,
let's be careful moving forward.
Ah... What?! Why?! Just the three of you?!
Yokozuna wouldn't die from that.
Hey, get hold of yourselves.
Then this isn't an uninhabited island?
He's the source of all our
headaches at this shift station.
We'll explain it later!
Well, they're probably the passengers
who drifted here from a wrecked ship.
We're gonna go back right away!
He loves strength contests and
always tries to defeat the sea train.
Do something about our frozen arm and leg!
Is something wrong, Doctor?
Nothing.
Ahh, okay. Let's see...
He'll show up again.
Don't get full of yourself!
Strength contests? Oh...
That's why he didn't run, huh?
About a month ago,
We have to melt those frozen
areas with water immediately.
there was a report that a passenger
liner went missing in this area.
That was close.
He's sure got guts.
But we're using the shower
room for Robin right now.
Yeah, you got that right.
Hm?
Give me a break! We're having problems!
Is she okay?!
Miss! Our stuff is cheap!
The rail guard was broken many times, too!
It's too early to tell.
How about taking a look at our products?
It looks like an ordinary passage.
What?
Every time he shows up, it causes
the passengers a lot of trouble!
Yeah.
How are they, Chopper?
There're some injured people,
but their wounds aren't serious.
So will this do?
I see...
We've got lots of superb
items that are hard to find!
They'll be fine once I apply the medicine I have.
Wh-What the hell is this?!
Okay, then! I'm not gonna eat him!
I'm not gonna eat a fighter!
We're now starting our 50%-off sale!
More importantly, it seems that
they haven't been eating well.
Once you melt the ice at low temperature,
What's the deal with these guys?
You shouldn't have thought about
eating a frog in the first place!
come up to the ship while
rubbing the affected parts!
Oh, I see. Underneath this
passage must be a jail,
They're weakened.
Sanji-kun and Usopp went to get some food.
So where do you guys wanna go?
Nami! Help us treat Robin!
and they probably got locked up there
for making blunders or something.
Okay!
If you're gonna take the sea train from here...
Wow! Things have gotten lively!
Hey! We're back!
I-I can go through a place
like this with no problem!
Oh? We ended up in the shopping district!
Hey...
The town of the Spring Queen, St. Poplar...
The gourmet town, Pucci...
Why are you guys here?
Where's Luffy?! What about Aokiji?!
A-A woman!
Could it be that you took a shortcut?
--All right!
--It's been so long!
You must've been really hungry.
The Carnival town, San Faldo...
They're all fun places.
You don't have to wolf down the food.
Luffy said he wanted a duel.
I'm sorry. You guys are actually smart, huh?
There's plenty more where that came from.
A duel?! And you guys left
Luffy there by himself?!
I can't do it! I can't stand being treated like this!
That's right! There's plenty more!
If you work for the Government,
there's a separate, special train.
I've never been to such an
energetic shopping district!
Hey, why are you eating?!
Leave it to me, Nami.
Usopp...
Those were the captain's orders.
At any rate, even if this is an uninhabited island,
Hey, look at that! That's a huge bull!
Since they've been locked up in
this dimly lit place all this time,
Hey! Even if it was the captain's order,
you can't just do that!
The gourmet town, Pucci?
if you are so inclined,
you can find food, you know.
Whoa! Hey, it's coming this way!
they must be vulnerable to light.
This is the problem with amateurs.
Oh, I see...
Aren't you guys a little
too cold-hearted?! Luffy is...
That's the place the guys we met on the
uninhabited island were talking about.
So if we use this flash ball,
they won't be able to see for a while.
I'm surprised that you survived
after a shipwreck in the Grand Line.
Shut up!
Oh... Come to think of it...
It's a duel. Can't you understand?!
We're the only ones who made it to this island.
We'll use that chance to
make a break for it, huh?
Stop it! This is no time for that!
That's right. Close your eyes, Nami!
This guy is scary!
Then, we'll pick the gourmet town.
What happened?
It's like he's about to eat us!
On our way back from a gourmet
tour to the gourmet town, Pucci...
We're... in a crisis right now.
Obviously not!
Considering its size, I wonder if this is a King.
Since we've got our own ship,
we won't take the train.
Hm? What the heck is that?
Whether this decision is his
passing whim or whatever,
We'll just follow the log.
All right! Now, Nami!
Oh...? Where is it pointing?
Okay!
Masks...
...our ship collided with a huge frog
that was doing the front crawl
if anything should happen,
be prepared to respond to that!
East of here.
Wow, they're pretty. They're gorgeous.
I see. Then it must be Water Seven.
and shattered into pieces.
I wonder if there's a party or something.
--N-Nami!
--All right! I got her!
The train you saw earlier came
from that island's Blue Station.
Doing the front crawl?! A frog was?!
Usopp!
What? What's going on?
--Ahh! Hey! H-Help!
--Let me touch her, too!
Frogs normally do the breaststroke, though.
Got it! You're saying I should go on
ahead and not worry about you, right?!
It's called the "City of Water." It's a nice place.
Here! These are freshly made
water-water octopus dumplings!
Interesting! I wanna see it, too!
As I thought, you're an odd one.
--Ahhh! Hey! Hey!
--Ah, the smooth leg of a woman!
Water Seven?
--Are you out of your mind?
--It's true!
Above all, it's a city that made
a name for itself with its shipyard.
--Nooo!
--It's been a while...
--How soft...
Two water-water croquettes?
That's Yokozuna.
Both look yummy! Yagara, go over there.
--Huh?
--Yokozuna?
Their technology is No. 1 in the world!
Is something wrong, Doctor?
Then, after a great struggle,
we were able to make it to this island,
The ships they build are the World
Government's favorites! Isn't that amazing?!
No, nothing.
Hey, where're you going?!
Hey, Luffy! Where're you going?!
I see... Then there's gotta be
some amazing shipwrights, right?!
That was close!
yet we lived on the verge
of starvation for a month.
Ask the Yagara!
Hm?
We rejoiced when we saw someone was coming,
Wh-What is this place?
Not just "some"! It's a hangout
for the world's best shipwrights!
but when we looked carefully,
he was riding a bicycle on the sea.
Hey, Nami!
Welcome! What would you like?
Usopp!
Hey, now... Under no
circumstances can one ride a...
Hm...? Luffy!
Yeah!
What took you so long?
All right! I've decided!
Oh, so you were hungry.
What're you doing in a place like this?!
Oh... that was me.
Gum-Gum...
We're gonna go there and get a
shipwright to join our crew for sure!
Water-water meat is the Yagara's
favorite food, although it's human food.
--Huh?
--And then, the next one
that came was a pirate ship.
...Storm!
Oh, is that right? Then hold on a sec.
What am I doing? I'm eating
rice crackers and having some tea.
Us, huh?
Water-water? Then give me ten of them.
I can tell that much!
Oof.
Then you guys are... whatchamacallit...
I'm impressed you've gotten this far.
I'll give you credit for that!
They're so good that the cooks from the gourmet
town would secretly come to purchase them.
--What's that about?
--Beats me.
...you know... um... well...
However...
Well, then... Here's a simple map
of the island and a reference letter.
It captivates your body and soul, doesn't it?
Well, however, having Straw Hat stranded here
Say it clearly! Clearly!
Ice Time...
Oh, shoot! I totally forgot!
and you reaching here
are all according to my plan!
Give this to a guy named Iceberg
and ask him to fix your ship good.
Hey, you! Don't mess with us!
They... are... so... soft...!
--L-Luffy! Hold on! Hold on!
--Calm down!
Why me?!
That's because you're a navigator as
well as an excellent strategy advisor!
Water Seven is a big place. Don't get lost.
Well, like I said...
--Yummy!
--What?! Is it that good?
Hey, Luffy! Give me one!
--Whoa!
--Kokoro-san! You have a big heart!
What a nice person you are!
Like I said several times already, I took a stroll.
If we eliminate you and Straw Hat,
No! Buy it yourself!
the Straw Hat Pirates are practically wiped out.
Oh, it was a stroll? Then don't go
passing a place like this! Leave!
Hm?
Hey, Nami! Pull the boat over to that shop!
Oh, I see.
You don't make sense.
We're gonna go back to Water Seven soon, too.
More masks... Now that I look closer,
they seem to be everywhere in town.
Luffy kinda has the upper hand here.
Well then, shall we start now?
Yeah. If I see you guys again, I'll treat
you to a drink at my favorite bar.
Well, then... Okay.
I'm going back, but before that...
Nami!
Those people with masks...
That's the spirit, huh, brother?
You guys, get ready to depart right away.
Okay. I hope we'll see you guys again!
Let's you and me...
Hey, Nami!
Oh, wow! We can finally beat up Straw Hat?
...settle this fight!
Fortunately, there's an inhabited
island not so far from here.
It'll take about a week for the log to
be stored in Water Seven. Take it easy.
Hey! Some pirates started
causing a ruckus at Dock #1!
You should go there to get
the treatment you need.
What are they?
What?! Is that true?!
Darn... I was tricked.
Yeah! Thanks!
We'd better get there right away!
I don't know what that is,
but this one is Gorilla Pants.
Hey, you guys! You don't have to
listen to this guy! He's a marine!
All right, guys! Get ready to set sail!
Since I accepted the duel,
this fight ends when I win.
N-No, it's not "pants"!
It's the Gorilla Puncher 13!
I don't understand what you're saying.
--Yeah!
--Well then, we'll get going!
Well, actually...
Here I come, Straw Hat! Gorilla Punch!
Thanks for all your help, Kokoro-san! Chimney!
Now I see...
If I mess with the others now,
I'd be the senseless one here...
Go hide, Nami.
I thought about it carefully.
Is there a problem?
--Okay!
--Gum-Gum...
You haven't forgotten, have you, Straw Hat...?
I thought about it really carefully.
...right, Captain?
That when your punch touches these...
Oh... That's right. It's fine,
it's fine. That's right. It's fine.
Be careful!
...Pistol!
Well, it's true that you guys repaired our ship,
Or...
...it'll burn...
Normally, marines are your friends
and we are the bad guys, huh?
...did you seriously intend to defeat me?
but no matter how I looked at it,
I thought the fee was too high.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Watch out for the Government people!
So you have?!
Luffy!
Yahoo! Let's go! To the city of meat! Yahoo!
It's no time for laughing!
You should pay attention!
You're interrupting our work.
He said he'd help those guys.
So... I decided not to pay--
not even a single Berry.
Let me say this.
You are the prey of Mr. Donkey Kicker 18.
But does he have a ship?
Were you even listening?
In the future, Nico Robin will grow...
Besides ours, I didn't see
any other ships anywhere.
That woman will definitely grow
to be too much for you to handle.
Hey, Nami!
There's no ship. They don't
have a Log Pose, either.
Thanks for the perfect repairs!
Water! Water!
How are they supposed to
go to that nearby island?
Oh, I see... I get it!
On top of that, it was free!
Oh, they'll be fine.
You guys will no longer be able to
shoulder the burden of the brutal fate
Nothing you say sounds convincing, you know.
Oh, wow.
She's trying to get Boss to forgive them
by humoring Boss with magic tricks.
that Nico Robin was born into.
It's true that...
Hm?
...that man can make it happen.
Hmm... What a nice wind!
Well... Kalifa, what's going on over there?
We may be able to get to the city
of water sooner than expected.
Are you ready, Luffy?!
That's what it means...
I hope so.
Yes, Iceberg-san.
They're the customers for Dock #1.
Luffy, leave the shipwright search to me.
I'll find an incredibly pretty woman.
Now that the work has been completed,
they're saying they won't pay.
The weather forecast is thunderstorm!
...to let her on your ship...
Thunderstorm Tempo!
That's sexual harassment.
Are you an idiot?! It's a
shipwright we're talking about!
All right, done!
...Monkey D. Luffy!
It's gotta be a big guy like
a mountain! Five meters tall!
Well... That is sexual harassment.
We loaded up food and water.
With this much, you'll be fine for a while.
But if he's too big, we don't know
if he could live okay on this ship.
It's nice to work once in a while.
You fool! You thought you could break
the Gorilla Puncher 13 with lightning?!
Breaking you right here, right now
and killing you would be very easy,
Yeah, it feels good! You're quite a sensible guy!
All that matters is that he's skilled, right?
More importantly, the question
is if we could find someone
He hit it off with him after all.
but we owe you one.
So what're you gonna do?
crazy enough to want to be on a pirate ship.
Are you gonna swim while
pulling these guys and this stuff?
You really don't get it, do you?!
I'm looking forward to it.
We're gonna have another new friend!
There's no way you can break something
with rain if it can even withstand lightning!
No way.
Now I want you to cancel our debt
to you for suppressing Crocodile.
Sir, it'd be wise not to tease craftsmen like that.
We were lucky to stop at the station first,
since they drew a map for us.
We'll see about that.
Step back a bit.
You still don't get it?
If we go to the place on the map
and visit the Iceberg guy...
Also...
Your punches don't work with this guy.
Err... Well, I guess I don't have
to talk about that idiot Smoker.
"Around here" "Water Seven"
I see...
Gorilla Punch Golden Hits!
Ha! Too simple to figure out!
See you around!
Whoa! This is like Luffy's drawing.
Fire can be put out with water!
"Shipwright
5 meters"
So, we're gonna all look for a guy like this.
B-Boss!
Boss!
If there was a guy like that, I'd run.
Oh, no! What's he doing?!
Oh, pardon me.
--There he is!
--Luffy!
Yeah, me, too. If I had a boat,
I'd escape to the sea.
You son of a bitch!
Watch carefully where you're going!
He didn't get broken into pieces!
But this guy seems to be related to octopuses.
Good, good...
He might follow me to the sea.
We'll carry him!
What the hell are you guys running on about?!
Oh, pardon me.
Wh-What the heck?!
Let's hurry to the ship!
Well then, guys, come here!
Don't talk at the same time!
Y-You bastards! Are you picking a fight?!
Who do you think we are?!
A sea animal! I bet that's the
guardian of this area of the sea!
I'll give you some allowance for
the week we're gonna stay there.
Seriously?! Yaay! I'm first!
Whoa! That's generous!
Hey! Stand in line!
Allowance! Allowance! Allowance!
What?! Hey, you! Run!
According to this island's log,
their next destination is... Hm?
Watch out! Gum-Gum...
Hey, have you test fired the cannon?
Water Seven... The city of water, huh?
Ice Age...
Oh, not yet, sir.
Oh, my, my... They're really
getting closer to our Headquarters.
Dammit! Who the hell are you guys?!
What's the matter, Usopp?
Oh? Oh?
This tinplate patchwork brings back
memories of battles and adventure.
We'll remember this!
Gum-Gum...
...Spinning Top!
I'm filled with deep emotions when I
think that she will be repaired soon.
Devil Fruit...!
--I do understand that, but...
--Hm...?
...especially since we entered the Grand Line, our journey has taken quite a toll on the Merry.
Boss! Please don't come this way!
Oops, sorry about that.
The deck squeaks and the leakage at
the bottom of the ship is bad as well.
The pirate way of doing things doesn't
work on craftsmen's turf, now, does it?
Holy smoke!
Th-The sea... froze!
Oh, no!
If we don't do anything, both we
and the ship will be in danger.
This is the power of a
Navy Headquarters' Admiral.
Yeah, but we've got tons of money now.
We can have her repaired perfectly.
We can power her up, too!
What happened?
All right! Let's get more cannons!
Then, let's get a bronze statue on board, too!
Hey, isn't that the one?
That's Boss!
Hm?
Boss won!
Both of them...
Guys...!
The island! We can see the island!
Their hearts...
I lost.
Now... We're finally going to
go to the shipbuilding island
...started beating!
Okay, guys! Paddle!
All right!
by using a water gate elevator.
We've got enough wind.
Don't make us waste our energy!
Luffy!
--Robin-chan!
--No! You can't go in yet!
A water gate elevator?
You'll make a racket, right?
See? You took so long
that we missed all the action.
That tower-like thing is the one.
Hey, Dr. Chopper. I'll make something for them.
It was because you got lost!
Y-You calling me "doctor" wouldn't
make me feel happy, you jerk!
Hey, Straw Hat!
This will probably last at least a week.
How wonderful...
I lost in a fight between pirates,
so I won't whine.
Please come in!
Ah, when they wake up, some drinks
that can warm them up would be good.
Amazing...!
Do what you want with us!
The elevator will go to the shipbuilding island,
I'll carry them to the lounge later.
Yeah... Then... why don't you
let them be your crew again?
Take your time and head in that direction.
Aye-aye, sir!
shipbuilding plant, and downtown Water Seven!
Nami, are we gonna sail out?
What the hell is this?!
You'll get to an inhabited island in four days.
No, we aren't, with our captain like that.
What? After they tainted the pride of pirates?!
We've already got the log,
but let's stay here for today.
Please hurry inside the gate!
It's a little cold, so dress warmly while walking.
You don't want to?
Hm?
Straw Hat... You're such a...
One minute until the gate gets closed!
What a huge fountain!
Is this... a dream?
What's the matter, Usopp?
Are you feeling drained?
Okay, then! For Straw Hat's sake,
you go scot-free!
Amazing! This is indeed an industrial city!
What'll happen inside?
I wonder if strong guys like him
are coming after us from now on...
The sea has become ground!
B-Boss...
It's no surprise that this
place would have a sea train.
Wow... This is a lot of water!
We can now cross the sea!
We can get off of this island!
Now, go talk to them.
All I did was get flustered.
Where is that water springing out from?
Whoa! The water gate is now closed!
Thanks, Straw Hat.
Mr. Marine! Thank you!
How interesting... It looks like
the water comes from the fountain,
We're going up!
We're going up! We're going up!
Get some sleep, you idiot. You're exhausted.
This is a miracle! A miracle without doubt!
Will you guys work for me again?
goes through the canals and falls into the sea.
I see. That happens. Then, this happens.
Boss!
Hey, do you wanna race on those water slides?
Boss!!
And then, they do this and that.
So that's why it's a water gate elevator.
Race?
Whoa! Water Seven is interesting!
At least, his charisma is something else.
Boss!
Well then, we'll get going now.
So they use water for all sorts of things!
No! There's no way I'm doing that!
--It pisses me off for some reason.
--Boss!
Yeah. I'm happy for you guys.
Dream on, you idiot. You can't even swim.
What do you think you're doing, Sanji-kun?
Be careful.
I guess there're different kinds of pirates, huh?
Oh, yeah...
Just kidding. I was just kidding.
More importantly,
what do those numbers mean?
We can't thank you enough.
Huh...?
Hey!
Take care, Straw Hat!
Not only did you treat our injured,
--Don't know.
--Are they walls? Or...
Who're you calling Moss Head?
but you also shared your
food and water with us.
You take care, too!
I bet those are the entrances
for the five-meter shipwrights.
"Shipwright
5 meters"
Don't worry about it.
Hey, Zoro.
Oh, yeah!
They say that even a chance meeting is
due to karma from a previous life, so...
In order for Luffy and Robin to get
some rest, the Going Merry anchored
--Huh?
--Where's Robin-chan? She isn't on the ship.
There's a bunch of them?!
--Ah, yeah!
--Stop it already!
Take good care of the children
so that they don't catch a cold.
The one up front must be the station.
off the uninhabited island for four days.
Hm?
Right, she isn't. She went
out with Chopper earlier.
After that, we sailed out.
It says Blue Station.
You came around, Usopp?
In this state, the food will
probably stay fresh for a while.
This is the third morning since
we started our voyage again.
Chopper... Why am I...? Ahhh!
I wonder where the harbor is.
--Bye-bye!
--Thank you very much.
--What?!
--She said she was going shopping.
Its a fine day today, partly spring...
It must be in the town.
--Thank you!
--We'll never forget your kindness,
Straw Hat Pirates!
Nami, you jerk! How dare you
desert me and go like that?!
--Hey, you guys!
--Hm?
What the hell?! Then are you
the only one on the ship?
...with occasional bouts of summer.
You got it wrong, Usopp. The truth is...
It's not good for you pirates
to be openly sailing in the front!
See ya! Take care!
What a boring environment!
Go around to the backstreets over there!
You got that right.
Be careful on your trip!
Oh, I see... So that's what happened.
What a beautiful day!
Okay! Thanks!
Nami-san!
All right, then. I'll go grocery shopping, too.
Good, good.
To think that he outwitted my plan...
Whoa, it's cold. It's cold.
He's our enemy, but I admit, he's brilliant.
So make sure you watch the ship good.
This is completely like winter.
I made potato paille. Mademoiselle, if you like...
Whoa, this is amazing! A city on the water?!
I can ice skate!
Boss, what are we going to do now?
Whoa! That's amazing, Chopper!
Wow! This place is cool! What a beautiful city!
Geez, he's already asleep.
Just as you'd expect from
someone born on a winter island!
Well, fine. I'll leave the ship to you.
Are we going to find another opponent
to challenge to a Davy Back Fight?
Hmm, this is good!
I'm so happy!
How about this?
What do you think?
Whoa! That's amazing!
Boss is cooking up a scheme again.
Shut up, you jerk. You're disturbing my sleep!
Why don't you try?
Yeah, yeah, sorry about that, cactus head.
But the city is flooded.
The houses are submerged in the sea.
Listen, guys. Unless we defeat them,
Boy, it's cold, it's cold!
I'm gonna freeze!
What'd you say, you dartboard jerk?!
"Fox"
we'll have to keep flying this
ugly pirate symbol forever.
Hm?
Dar... What'd you just say, you bastard?!
That's not it. The city was designed
with the base being submerged.
Hmm...
If that's the case, there's only
one place we're headed, right?
Dartboard eyebrows.
--Huh?
--Look at the foundation
underneath the buildings.
What?
Yeah!
How should I put it... You're just
like your gramps, Monkey D. Luffy...
I won't let you get away, Straw Hat.
You're right! The pillars are built higher!
Luffy! Yeah! Luffy! All right!
I see... That's why it's called
the city of water, huh?
Wh-What?
Luffy! Yeah! Luffy!
You're free-spirited, or should
I say you're hard to figure out?
Guys! I see an island!
Hey, hurry up and dock the ship!
Hmm...
We're here!
Looks like it's an uninhabited island.
Hm?
G-Gramps...
At last!
Hey, hey, you guys!
Pirate ships shouldn't come in here!
Ready the anchor! We'll land on the island!
Luffy!
Gramps...?! Luffy's?!
So this is the world's No. 1 shipyard!
Downtown Water Seven!
Well then, go find some foodstuffs.
What'd you come here for?! To plunder?!
No! We wanna get our ship repaired!
Yeah!
Hey, what's the matter, Luffy?
You're drenched in sweat.
Listen. No rats or frogs, okay?
Would people normally ask
if we're here to plunder?
I'm impersonating my frozen self.
Well... N-N-Nothing. Um... well...
How self-centered you are. Once it's
in your stomach, it's all the same.
Then, there's a cape ahead of here,
so anchor your ship there for now!
Your gramps really helped me out a while back.
As expected, I see more ground around here.
Okay!
Thanks!
The reason I came here was to
have a look at Nico Robin and you.
Hey, Sanji!
Geez... I can't believe he's doing that
after he got frozen and almost died.
Again?
We got fish, shellfish, fruits...
We got a good catch!
It can't be helped, right? We're pirates, after all.
Things are huge all over!
Thanks!
On second thought...
maybe you should die now, huh?
--Did I do a good job?
--You did! You looked exactly like that, Luffy!
Cheers!
This area should be okay, don't you think?
I've never seen a huge town like this!
In any case, what a dull place this is.
Clean that up good, okay, Luffy?!
Yummy!
Seeing that fountain up close
makes it look especially big!
Hey, Luffy! Don't stuff your mouth like that!
The government is still taking you guys lightly,
Hm? What're you eating, Nami?
All right, then! Furl the sail!
You snacked a lot earlier. I can't
believe you're still eating so much!
but if I delve into your history, I can
tell that your group has a backbone.
It's paille, a potato dish.
This still isn't enough!
Potato, huh? I'm hungry, too. Hey, Sanji!
Although your group is small,
since it's gathering shrewd members,
With this amount of food,
we're gonna run out quickly.
Just how much sleep do
you need to be satisfied?!
Hm?
What're you doing?!
Robin, you should eat now or it'll all be gone.
What's with that crowd?
it'll probably become a problem later on.
Nothing! I just pulled the rope!
How much sleep I get is my business!
I'll take you on if you wanna fight!
Aren't they watching the shipyard?
I'm almost done, so...
The circumstances that initially
led to your search orders...
Okay, stop right there!
Let's go see it! Go, Yagara!
No! If you're always reading,
you'll become a worm!
All the actions you took up until now...
Hey, Sanji-kun, our captain says
that he wants to eat paille.
Holy crap! The Going Merry
has gotten this rickety?
They call it a bookworm, right?!
Okay, Nami-san!
The speed of your group's progress...
Sanji! Potatoes! Potatoes!
I've been dealing with outlaws for a long time,
By the way, why aren't the people
on this island scared of pirates?
Even when you're recuperating,
you're the same old Luffy, aren't you?
Hey, look over there!
It's Lucci-san! He's so handsome!
There you are, Straw Hat!
but it worries me to think how you'll turn out.
Probably because pirates are just
another customer to their shipyard.
Guys, are you ready?
Th-That's too sudden!
Isn't Paulie here?
Stop talking and fix it already!
Yes, Boss.
You said earlier that you just
came to check things out!
Lulu's here! How refined he is!
He's truly a man's man.
We're ready.
The reason I especially regard
you guys as dangerous is...
Maybe because they have
bodyguards strong enough
They said this is called paille. Yummy!
to deal with pirates who cause a ruckus?
What's paille?
...you, Nico Robin.
Who's manlier than Tilestone?
They probably do...
considering the size of the city.
It's the tail meat of a huge monster Paille.
Boss, they're all looking this way.
So you're after Robin after all!
I'm gonna beat the crap out of you!
Really?! Hey, what're we gonna do? This is bad.
Don't be flustered. Any way you
look at it, this is an ordinary crab.
--Hey, pops.
--Hm?
I killed it. It was at least 100 meters high.
Did something happen?
Her bounty amount isn't just
an indication of her strength.
Why would it be bad? We're customers.
Yeah. It seems that some pirates
caused a ruckus at this here Dock #1.
100 meters?! That's amazing, Usopp!
It's so obvious, it's unnatural.
Y-You think so?
Okay, then! See you later!
Hmm, a piece of cake. I did it before breakfast.
Don't tell me it's them again.
It also indicates the level of danger
she poses to the government.
Wait, Luffy! Usopp!
But, well, it ended when the
craftsmen knocked them down.
What? You got up early and killed it?
They never learn, do they?
I wish they'd stop.
You guys, come with me.
Chopper, say my name.
That's why you got a 79-million-Berry
bounty on your head at the age of eight.
Okay. We're gonna destroy their ship!
There's no end to those fools.
Hm?
What? That's, of course, C-Captain...
Shipwrights beat pirates up?
To where?
What the heck?!
First, we'll take the reference
letter from Kokoro-san
That's right! My name is... Captain... Usopp!
Oh, you must be a voyager.
I'm impressed that you survived as a child.
This looks yummy!
and go find the man named Iceberg.
That crowd is... well, in short, busybodies.
Hey, don't tell me...
You betrayed people and ran away.
You gained people's favor and used them.
We'll ask him to help us
arrange the ship's repair.
Yeah, he thinks it's a real one.
Those shipwrights at the Galley-La
Company are admired by all the residents.
We also have to find a place
where we can cash in our gold.
Argh! Let it go, Straw Hat!
You've survived in the underworld
by being quick to switch sides.
I see... All right, then! Anyway,
let's go! To the city of water!
Oh? It's trying to run away!
Robin!
They're strong...
So this is the group that you
chose as your next hideout, huh?
Yoo-hoo! Robin-chan!
Dammit. Take this!
...and skilled.
They're the pride of Water Seven.
You're forgetting the gold.
Robin!
Hey, you jerk! How insulting you are!
How are you feeling? Do you feel a chill?
Now's our chance! Crab-Crab Punch!
Ah...
I'm feeling a lot better.
Thank you, my excellent doctor!
Zoro! Make sure you fix it good!
What grudge do you hold against Robin-chan?!
This is finally the end of Straw Hat.
Stop it, Sanji!
I don't have any grudge against her.
Be careful, Nami-san!
Oh... Being called an excellent doctor
wouldn't make me feel happy, you jerk.
Wow, I'm looking forward to meeting them!
If we are somehow connected...
Ahh... I somehow missed
the chance to go with them.
You're just a crab! How dare
you make me get serious?!
Ahh...!
...it's that I let her get
away once, that's about it.
--He sure does look happy.
--Yeah.
Hey, Luffy!
Let's go out together later.
Hm?
Take this!
Take it easy, Robin.
Really?! I wonder if they have a bookstore.
It was a long time ago.
Let's hurry up and go to
the money-changing shop.
You might feel uneasy when you
see Luffy being as good as new
We can come back here later.
I'm sure they do.
You guys will eventually realize it, too.
after having the same experience as you,
In the not-so-distant future, you'll regret
that you took in a troublesome woman.
Okay!
but you can take your time and rest, you know.
Why don't we go to the
money-changing shop first?
Oh? Did you guys get eaten
by this crab? How pathetic...
--Yay!
--That wasn't a compliment!
Why? Let's go to the shipyard.
As proof, the organizations Nico Robin
had something to do with up until today
Robin-chan! Shall I make
something that can warm you up?
But we can't walk around the island
with this much gold. I get nervous.
Oh, just get a clue already!
Now, let's leave those guys alone
and continue with our BBQ!
Do you have an appetite?
all got annihilated... except for her.
Then... May I have some coffee?
Even after changing it to money,
the value is the same.
All that activity made me hungrier.
It says that we're in the
backstreet shopping district.
It's true, but it being this big will
attract people's attention, right?
Okay! It's my pleasure!
Hey, that one isn't done yet.
They call a place this lively the backstreet?
Well, I like this way the best.
I wonder why... Nico Robin?
What if we run into bad thieves?
We're the thieves!
Stop it, you jerk! Her past doesn't matter!
So they have places that
we can walk around, huh?
He's got a point. If we change it
to bills, we can all carry them.
Oh, no! Boss, I'm hungry.
He's right! If you're worried about others' pasts,
The water is clear and the town is beautiful.
you can't be friends with ruffians like
a pirate hunter or a former thief girl!
Hm? Your remark had a sting to it.
Yeah.
You idiot! You're hungry?!
It sounds like me carrying it is a problem!
And you call yourself one
of the proud Foxy Pira--
Scary!
"Ruffians" was unnecessary!
What's more important is
the present, rather than the past!
Yeah. You might drop it somewhere or lose it.
Hm?
Wow!
What the hell is that?
Yeah, he would. It's Luffy we're talking about.
What a beautiful lady!
Robin is our precious friend now!
Don't badmouth our friend!
Thanks for waiting, Mademoiselle!
Such beauty hasn't been
seen for the last 100 years!
What?! You guys! Don't you trust me?!
This is today's special lunch.
--Nope!
--Ah... Ahh... Ahh... That really hurt!
Err...
Oh, wow! It looks good!
I see... You really did a
good job befriending this lot.
This place is full of Sanjis...
Please go ahead.
Anyway, this paille thing is so good
that we can't stop eating, isn't it?
I may not be able to recover from thi-- Hm?
Just get to the point already! If you
want to capture me, go ahead and do it!
Oh, wow! This is scrumptious!
Please come to our ship, Mr. Cook!
Is this the only entrance to the city?
Yeah, it's yummy!
Whoa! What's that?!
Hey, if we sell this thing, don't you
think we can make some money?
Treinta Fleurs!
That's a mask shop.
Hey, Luffy!
A rental bull shop?
Robin! Stop it!
Oh, no! If you ask me that,
Porche-chan, I'll have to consider it!
A-A frog is doing the front crawl!
What's that?
Oh, my, my... Maybe I talked too much.
What do they rent out?
I've noticed people are walking
around in town wearing those masks.
What?!
What's "bull"?
It went to your side, so take a look at it!
You should definitely go. I'm begging you, too.
How disappointing!
Beats me. Bulldogs?
--Is that true?
--A frog... Could it be that frog?
I had too high an opinion of you,
thinking you were a little smarter than that.
Oh, so they're wearing them, huh?
I thought those were weird faces.
"Fox"
Can't be, right?
Clutch!
Hello. This is the communications room.
Excuse me! Please let us rent bulls!
Hey, Luffy, are you taking what
that stupid Admiral said seriously?
Ahhh! He shattered into pieces and died!
Hi, it's me. Boss is knocked out,
so please come and get us.
Ask what they are first!
It sounds like they're holding a
costume carnival every day right now
To start with, there's no way a frog
would do the front cra... Hey, it is!
Welcome! You wanna rent bulls, right?
How many are you?
on San Faldo, an island you
take the sea train to get to.
A-A frog is doing the front crawl!
Three!
--We'll follow it, guys!
--Yeah!
Don't worry. He's alive. Well then, see ya.
What kind of bulls would you like?
What? How come you know that?
There're three ranks.
"Yagara," "Rabuka," and "King."
N-No... We're screwed...
Furl the sail! Stand by the oars!
Turn the ship to 2 o'clock!
People walking by are talking about it.
Well, for the three of you,
two Yagaras would probably do.
Mr. Cook! Goodbye! Your food
was very delicious! I was so moved!
--Yeah!
--Hurry up!
I'm surprised that you can hear them.
H-Hey! Guys! Run! Let's get out of here!
Okay! Please roast them nice and tasty!
I don't know why, but I feel
like we have to go after it!
It's a habit...
Weird! That conversation is weird!
You take care, Porche-chan!
Since my childhood, I've lived by trying to judge
people's feelings and listening in on them.
Oh? You followed logs to get here?
Sorry to keep you waiting, mademoiselles.
Are you really sure you don't have to go?
--Yep.
--That's quite an achievement, you guys.
Don't be ridiculous. If I'm gone,
What the...
That wasn't nice.
Then you had no idea what bulls were, did you?
What?! What happened?!
You're amazing, Robin.
who's gonna be in charge of
Nami-san and Robin-chan's meals?
--Right.
--Well, to make a long
story short, those are bulls.
Right, Nami-san?
Seems like the ship changed course.
They're Yagara bulls.
They're everywhere in town.
Sanji-kun! Zoro! Let's go find
foodstuffs for emergency stocks!
Hey, you guys! Why'd you change
the course without asking me?!
In this area, there's a fish called
Yagara that swims with its head out.
--Doctor...
--Hm?
Hey, Nami, you've got to hear this!
Okay, Nami-san!
Over there! There's a bookstore.
This is the city of water.
There're more canals than walkways.
We found a huge frog
with scars all over its body!
Really?!
Can we stop by here?!
So bulls are a means of transportation
necessary to the residents here.
What the heck?
Ice Saber!
Of course! Let's go inside.
We're definitely gonna roast it whole and eat it!
I wasn't going to kill you, but...
Hey, Chopper. Were you able
to find any medicinal herbs?
It's the same when you go
sightseeing on this island.
All right!
You're gonna eat it?!
That fish is pulling a boat?
Yep. I've collected most of them,
but there may be even rarer ones on this island.
Rather than pulling, they're letting
people ride on their back.
Hey, you're right...
Hm? Is that a lighthouse?
Well, it's like horseback riding
or riding in a carriage on land...
More importantly, something's
been bugging me for a while.
Why is there a lighthouse in a place
like that? I wonder if someone's there...
Oof.
I wonder what this weird groove
is that runs down this path...
You see the fish pen there?
Well, try and ride on it. It's comfortable.
CP9...
Wh-What's the matter? Do you see an island?
Come to think of it, yeah, I wonder what it is.
Slice Shoot!
No, there's a lighthouse. A Log Pose
wouldn't point to that sort of place.
It looks as if a bicycle passed by.
It'll be 2,000 Berries for two
two-passenger Yagara bulls.
All right!
Hey, hey. This is an uninhabited island, right?
Hmph! How dare you butt in, you damn cook?
What about the frog? Tell us
the direction the frog went!
Wow, they're cute!
This can't be a trace of a bicycle
when there's no one here.
It's a fish that looks like a horse.
The same to you, you natural monument!
Not a chance!
The frog is headed to the lighthouse.
That's true.
Gum-Gum...
You jerk! What'd you do that for?!
Hey, we're almost through the jungle!
--What?
--To cook frogs, first remove
the slime using white wine,
Oh? He must like you. Let's get him for you.
and then dredge them in
flour and fry them crisp.
...Pistol!
Robin! I'm gonna go on ahead and go in, okay?
We're suddenly out in a large open space.
Hey, Sanji-kun!
If our captain says we're going,
what choice do we have but to go?
Ahh!
It's cold!
What's with Chopper?
Robin...!
He's headed to that rock.
Is there something there?
Can he carry heavy stuff okay?
All right! Full speed ahead!
Their power is incredible!
You can even use them for moving.
Yeah!
Ahh!
What's with the solidarity?!
He froze them!
Those three... all at once...
That darn Chopper!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!...
That bag, huh? What's inside?
He must be trying to have that
huge mushroom all to himself!
Gold.
Hold it!
You're funny. Whatever it is, it'll be fine.
--See?
--Whoa! Give me some!
What's the matter, Chopper?!
No way!
It flew!
Looks like something happened. Let's go!
What an awfully honest old guy...
Don't let it get away! We'll move
ahead of it and block its course!
Ow, ow, ow... Hm?
You too! Don't show it to others so lightly!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Whoa! What the heck is this?!
Why? It wouldn't hurt, would it?
If I'm in my human form... it may be okay.
My, my... What a surprise...
O-Oh, no! They have to be treated right away!
Well, then... it'll be a million
Berries for two Yagara bulls.
Oh?
Ahh... Hmm?
If they get frostbite, their limbs
will become gangrenous!
Wow, what a cool mask!
What're you dressed up as?
Hey, the price went up, pops.
A raccoon dog?
What're you doing, Usopp?!
We have to go help those three now!
Sorry. It'll be five million Berries.
I'm a reindeer! See? I've got antlers!
Y-Yeah... A human reindeer.
It went up even more!
Are you okay, Chopper?!
I-I really would like to,
but my body can't move.
You noticed?
Who the heck is this?!
Did I get frozen, too?
Geez... We can't be too careful.
We ran ashore on something!
If you're having fun, that's what's important.
No! You're just too scared to move!
What happened?!
Here, 2,000 Berries.
Thanks.
What's going on, Luffy?!
Ahh... Nami-san, Robin-chan, are you guys okay?
--Luffy!
--Sanji! Zoro!
By the way, are there any
money-changing shops around here?
Oh?
What's with you guys?
Yeah, there are, but with that amount of gold,
What's with you?!
Robin! Run!
Yeah, somehow...
Wh-Who's that huge guy?
I'm okay.
the shops around here probably
wouldn't have enough money.
You've come across some good friends.
Who's that guy?!
Robin?
Good... Hm?
But you're still you, Nico Robin!
You should go to the downtown
area of the shipbuilding island.
Hello?!
What? What's this sound?
The downtown area of the
shipbuilding island? Where is it?
No...! I'm no longer...
Robin?!
What? What's going on?
It's over there. Take this with you.
Robin!
Robin! Watch out! Run!
A map?
What's wrong, Robin-chan?!
This'll be helpful! Thanks!
Robin!
Pops, is the shipyard there, too?
Wh... Why are you frozen?
I'm...
Yeah. The world's No. 1 shipyard!
Robin-chan!
Robin...
That's perfect. Once we get the money,
we can go to the shipyard right away.
Oh-ho-ho?
Now, now. Don't be so bloodthirsty, guys.
Is this...? Don't tell me...
Yeah. We can finally have
the Going Merry repaired!
Robin!
It's not like I'm here on orders.
And we'll find a shipwright, too!
I'm getting excited!
Since it's a nice day, I took a stroll here.
Orders?! From what organization?!
--Well, then...
--Shall we...?
He's a marine. And he's one of the people
All right! Go! Yagara!
known as the World Government's
ultimate powerhouses.
Thanks for your business! Be careful!
Why... in a place like this...?!
This guy is?!
Yes... An Admiral at
Navy Headquarters... Aokiji.
Dash to the shipyard!
I thought we were attacking you in your sleep...
Yahoo!
Ow, ow, ow...
Oh, my, my, you've turned
into a good-looking woman...
Who are you bastards?!
Go back! Go back! Turn 180 degrees!
...Nico Robin...
Identify yourselves!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Ahh! Robin got...!
Incredible! Usopp flew in the sky!
What's wrong?
What the hell is that?!
Whoa! This is fun!
There're only three officers in the Navy
who hold the position of Admiral.
A ship?! No, it's not!
Yeah! Hm? Hey, I'm right here.
...frozen!
It's amazing that such a
convenient creature exists!
Hey, it's coming this way!
Don't yell! Her death will benefit the world.
It doesn't rock much. It's comfortable!
--Amazing!
--It's not!
Come to think of it, that Usopp
has a square-ish nose.
He's one of the World Government's
ultimate powerhouses.
Whoa! The canals even go above the rooftops!
We'd better get out of here now!
--What'd you say?!
--You bastard!
--When it comes to guys,
nothing beats a round nose!
--Well, welcome, Straw Hat.
Hey, that frog is headed towards it!
--Wait, you guys!
--Luffy!
--Is he trying to collide with it?!
--Ahh! Wait! My meat!
I've never seen such a huge town before!
Huh? Well, yeah, that's about it.
Don't interfere in this fight!
I'll fight him in a duel!
I'm Iceberg, the boss of this city.
Yeah. This is a town built around canals!
Are you a big shot, pops?
Then please repair our ship!
I finally found you, Nico Robin.
That's not meat!
Water Seven is getting me fired up!
That's fine by me, but...
err... whatchamacallit...?
What're you doing to Robin?!
--Sure.
--Whoa, that sounded frivolous!
Is it okay to be that frivolous?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Dashing Sea Train and
the City of Water, Water Seven"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Adventure in the City on the Water!
Head to the Mammoth Shipbuilding Plant"
"Navy Headquarters Admiral Aokiji!
The Ferocity of an Ultimate Powerhouse"
"The Franky Family and Iceberg-san"
"Duel between Rubber and Ice! Luffy vs. Aokiji"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!