It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
They... are... so... soft...!
Shall we go follow Franky?
What's the matter, Usopp?
So how much does it look like it'll cost?
Where?
The money... The money is gone!
Drat. Looks like they really
don't know where the money is.
We can pay as much as you like!
We've got tons of money!
Yummy!
Hm?
Whaaat?!
Ahh! Over there!
--What?! Is it that good?
--I don't understand what you're saying.
Who's trying to defy the Franky Family?!
Well, actually...
Even if we strangle this Franky guy,
if he already spent the money...
Her scars from battle are too deep.
Thanks for the money!
Do you mean it'll take
quite a long time to fix her?
I decided not to pay--not even a single Berry.
What do we do now? Even if we wait for
him here, he won't be back for a while.
Hold it!
No...
Give me the money back!
Frankly speaking, your ship...
"Give me the money back"? Then are
you one of the Straw Hat's underlings?
Thanks for the perfect repairs!
We did it!
Hold it!
Staying here talking won't get us anywhere.
Sir, it'd be wise not to tease craftsmen like that.
The Franky Family...
Let's go back to the ship for now.
We left Nami-san alone there, too, so...
...can no longer be fixed, even with our skills.
Those bags... They're ours...!
That's right, Bro! Since he's with
Straw Hat Luffy, I expected him to be
Oh, no...
Money! Money!
We have the thing with
Robin-chan to deal with...
Oh, pardon me.
"Galley-La Company! A Grand Sight, Dock #1!"
But we've been traveling
just fine up until today!
a really strong pirate, but then...
...and the issues with the ship, too.
Let's suppose that we did
what we could anyway.
Yeah.
Hey, Luffy!
He's so weak!
That's none of your business!
The probability of her
reaching the next island is...
Hold it, Paulie!
About the ship...
The pirate way of doing things doesn't
work on craftsmen's turf, now, does it?
I've made a decision.
Oops!
Today, I'm not
gonna let you get away!
Hm?
...zero.
I'm saying, wait a bit longer!
I'll admit you've got guts to come
to get the money back all by yourself,
Let's say goodbye... to the Going Merry here.
That tower-like thing is the one.
but I can't let you have it back.
Who's that?
That's Paulie.
He's being chased by debt collectors again.
--Give us our 200 million Berries back!
--Sorry, mister! Thanks for giving us the money!
Give it back to me!
"Big Fight under the Moon!
The Pirate Flag Flutters with Sorrow!"
Merry... Can you really not...
We have to... have our ship repaired...
Things are huge all over!
--Hey!
--Goodbye!
...sail anymore?
They're strong...
Did you give them the money?!
"Pirate Abduction Incident and a Pirate
Ship That Can Only Await Her End"
Why would I do that?! They stole it!
...and skilled.
Ah!
They're the pride of Water Seven.
That money is crucial to us!
What?!
Pay back the money!
Hey! Usopp woke up!
Like I said, I don't have money today.
Really?! Good!
With that money, we can finally...
That's not gonna cut it!
Scary!
Crap...
Now we can relax a little.
They're really persistent!
We can finally repair the Merry's scars!
I'm sorry, Sanji. I was so
focused on books that...
Hm? This is perfect! I see Yagara bulls!
Whoa! What's that?!
Hey! Usopp!
I can't let you jerks have it!
That's a mask shop.
It's nothing you should apologize about.
Rope... Action!
I just assumed that the one
who was with Robin-chan
was you in your human form.
Robin-chan isn't back yet...
--Ahhh!
--He's one of the shipwrights at Galley-La!
"Rescuing Our Friend!
Raid on the Franky House"
CP9...
Then, who on earth was that masked man?
Seriously, don't worry us so much!
Sorry, but I'd like to borrow
one of your Yagaras for a bit!
In addition, it's strange that
they suddenly disappeared.
Round Turn!
She's right. To think that you marched
in by yourself... That was so reckless.
Yeah... Robin's scent disappeared there, too.
Robin?
What are you so worked up about?
You were lucky that you didn't die.
I hope nothing bad happens...
My stomach's in a knot...
Looks like you love your ship quite a bit.
Think a little before you act.
What?
Look who's talking!
Well, no matter what happens to your ship,
Do you want me to take a look at you?
I'm not sick!
Just because I'm so good-for-nothing...
This reminds me of what Aokiji said.
this money is already ours.
I'm sorry...
Really... I'm ashamed! Guys!
I thought we were attacking you in your sleep...
Did he say something worrisome?
Unfortunately for you, no matter what we
steal from pirates, we won't be accused
He said stuff about Robin-chan's past, right?
"The Franky Family and Iceberg-san"
And he said to us that we'd
someday regret taking her on.
of committing a crime.
Dammit! He got away again!
That money was so crucial to
us and yet, I let it... I let it...
This is dirty money that you stole
from somewhere anyway, right?
Well then, everyone, take care!
Now that you mention it...
But does that have something to
do with Robin's disappearance?!
Hey, hold on a sec! Calm down!
Let's run together again!
Well, let us have it.
I-I get it, so let me go!
Who are you bastards?
I don't know.
But... the huge amount of money we got,
after all that we went through...
Dammit!
Identify yourselves!
In any case, we're getting nowhere like this.
Let's go back to the Merry for now.
Seriously... you came at just the right time!
If you like, try begging the Navy for help.
Usopp, you should still be in bed.
You guys are the ones who'll be captured.
If there's no problem, she'll be back soon.
Hey, listen to Chopper.
Yeah.
Too bad for Straw Hat Luffy...
What a relief! He's one of
your shipwrights, right?
Take us for a spin, will ya?
...that he has a useless underling
who can't even watch over money.
Then, as I was afraid...
That's right.
"Identify yourselves"?
...the money won't come back?
Hey! Thanks!
Well, we won't know for sure
until this Franky guy comes back.
Pirate hunter Zoro...
That money belongs to us!
What? Money?
Oh, this...
I see... I'm sorry.
We're bounty hunters...
Guys, have some fun with him later.
Well, even if we don't get it back,
we still have the 100 million Berries.
Hello...! Hm? Hey!
...the Franky Family! Even a crying child
stops crying when they hear our name!
So that's okay. Don't worry about it.
I'm gonna take this money
and go shopping at once.
Come back here!
Your head's worth 60 million!
We'll gratefully take it.
That son of a bitch!
I'm gonna catch him--! Huh?
It's not okay about the money!
And we'll wait in ambush inside your ship...
This is gonna be great!
--Nami...
--Ah... Sorry.
Hold it! Special Attack! Exploding Star!
...and catch the entire crew in one swoop.
I'll go.
You can't fix the Merry?! Why not?!
No, that's okay.
What? A... A pigeon?
But Luffy... What about the ship?
What about the Merry?
Aren't you guys amazing shipwrights?!
We'll make a killing! How lucky!
Can we somehow have her repaired
with that remaining 100 million?
I'm the first!
If you're worried about money, look!
We've got tons!
Remember this, long-nosed boy.
My name is Franky...
This must be a guy's room.
It has nothing to do with money.
We're lucky that we can have her
repaired in such a first-class shipyard.
"Lucky"?
At first glance, it looks tidy, but...
If you want to leave this town alive,
you shouldn't cross me.
No matter how much you pay, that ship
can't be restored to how she used to be.
In order for her to be able to travel in
the seas ahead, I'd like her to be stronger.
The floorboards have to be replaced, too.
You mean, "unlucky," right?
I'm rather impressed that you guys
made it this far in the state she's in.
I want her to be repaired perfectly.
Say, does it look like those guys will
repair her if we pay 100 million Berries?
Wh... What're you doing?! Let go of me!
Don't flinch!
Does it, Luffy?
What do you mean?!
What's going on with the Merry?!
Two-Sword Style...
Er... well...
Hey, what're you doing?
Do you know what a keel is, shameless girl?
Usopp, about the ship...
Such a pathetic weapon wouldn't work on us.
...Rhino Cycle!
Hm?
I decided to get a new ship.
Don't worry. I'll put it back once
I check beneath the floorboards.
Shamele...
The one at the bottom of the ship?
What?
See ya, Long-nose.
That's right. It's the most
important wood beam on a ship.
I'm sorry that I made the
decision without consulting you.
Thanks for the 200 million Berries.
--Oh, my...
--Hm?
It crosses from stem to stern
and supports the ship.
But I've already made my decision.
Hold it! Give it back to me!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow! Hey, hey, let me go!
The Going Merry took good care of us,
but our journey with her ends here.
When you build a ship,
you start off by placing the keel.
Give it back to me!
How senseless...
Give it back to me!!
What the hell are you doing?!
Then, the stem wood, stern wood, frame wood...
D-Dammit!
I won't run! I'm saying I got it, aren't I?!
...frame brackets and deck beams...
Let go of my ear!
We accurately place all those
pieces of wood around the keel.
Here I was lucky enough to
find a lot of money and now...!
That's how a ship is built.
You'll regret this, Lucci!
Don't pay back your debts with
someone else's money, you fool!
The keel is the very foundation
of a ship's framework.
This is the place.
Give it... back to me...
It's the essence of the ship.
I found this money!
And...
It's not something you can just replace
if it takes on a lot of damage...
You're still saying that?! Coo coo!
I took a look at the catalogue
that Ice pops gave us.
G-Give it back to me...!
It just happened to be on
the Yagara that I borrowed!
Replacing the keel is the same
as building a ship from scratch.
So, what do you want?
While checking the ships in it, I noticed
that there're quite a few kinds.
Give it... back to me...!
They're back.
We want cash for our stuff.
So no one can fix her anymore.
If we get a used one, 100 million will
allow us to buy a bigger ship than Merry.
Well, I'm happy for you, Usopp!
Your ship is just a collection of wood
that can only await her end.
How much is this gonna be?
You talk like it was someone else's problem!
It's our 200 million Berries!
Wait.
Hey! Don't say it like that!
Wait... Wait a sec. You're taking
the joke too far. That's ridiculous.
Owner! This is serious!
That's right! Why the hell weren't
you the first one to go get it back?!
Not my problem. That's the truth.
G-Gold... Th-This much!
Right?
What?! Take them to the VIP
room im... im... immediately!
But that pigeon said he'd go.
Give it back to me!
See? Chopper took it seriously.
Then... Then build a ship from scratch for us!
Well... I'm sorry.
Seriously, what'll we do with our captain?
Please let us take care of our idiot coworker,
Give it back to me!
Build the Going Merry!
as if you guys were to capture him,
it would create bitter feelings.
Coo coo! That's not possible, either.
Say something to him, Nami.
Wow! This is comfy!
Why not?
Yeah! Hey, this is really bouncy!
Well, please excuse him. Consider it good that
the money wasn't stolen by the Franky Family.
We can build a similar ship,
Well... does that mean that we don't
have enough money for the repair?
but strictly speaking,
no one can build the same ship.
Does this one also have water in it?
Hmm... That's true, but...
In this world, there are no two
ships that are exactly the same.
Yeah, that's true, that's true.
Because I got that 200 million stolen by them,
I just have to hold out until Robin comes back.
What does that mean?!
w-we're now short on money, right?
Say... who were those
weird-looking guys earlier?
Are there any trees in the world
that grow exactly the same way?
Hey, that's what's going on, right, Luffy?
Hm? Hey, don't tell me you're
gonna say they're fake.
I'll only become a burden to
them if I march in with them.
The cost of a first-class shipyard
would also be first-class, so...
The Franky Family is a group
of ship demolition workers.
Sailing ships are mostly made of wood,
F-Far from it! I've been
an appraiser for 25 years.
No! That's not it!
It'll be scary, too.
Demolition workers? They didn't look
like such decent craftsmen, though.
so the size and curves of the ship are
all affected by the shape of the trees.
Then why?! Spit it out! Are you
trying to be considerate to me?!
At any rate, I'll protect this ship and
the 100 million Berries all the way.
This is roughly estimated at...
Right. They're also bounty hunters on the side.
I'm not! It has nothing to do
with that money being stolen!
That's why an exact duplicate
of the ship can't be built,
I'm counting on you... guys!
O-One hundred million Berries?!
even when using the same blueprint.
Then why are you saying stupid stuff
like that we're gonna get a new ship?!
Every time they find pirates coming
through this city, they cause quarrels.
For example, even if we build such a ship,
I-Idiot! You're too loud! Everyone can hear you!
Stop. Stop!
Hey, stop it, both of you!
without a doubt, the ones who would
feel that it's a totally different ship...
What good will fighting do?
Calm down and talk!
They're a public nuisance.
Y-Y-You're gonna give us that much money?!
If they crush the pirates who come to our town,
L-Like... Like I said, Luffy, you're too loud!
If I remember right, this should be
the place Nami-san was talking about.
they can take their ship, too, right?
...would be you guys! Coo coo!
How can I calm down when he
starts saying stupid stuff?!
They demolish the ship
and sell the useable lumber.
Oh, no...
This is indeed worth that much.
Hey! This is an important matter.
Don't get so worked up.
Then we really can no longer
travel on the Going Merry?
This is wonderful gold, taking its
historical value and purity into account.
Look. This is the backstreet shopping district.
That's how their business works.
She's right, Usopp. You need
to rest, or you won't get better.
How bad-natured...! Are they trying to
completely wipe the pirate groups out?
You go up this canal... and here!
Usopp is right here.
With that much money,
we can fix the Merry good!
That's right.
Who cares about my body?!
You either do nothing and wait until she sinks...
Yeah! We'll even get some change.
How can I be quiet when our captain
casually says we'll get a new ship?!
Well, if you become their victims,
not even your bones will remain.
Okay.
...or you take her apart quickly.
Then, we'll spend the rest of the
money to buy a bronze statue!
So, Nami-san, where can we find these
demolition workers, the Franky Family?
But they didn't look that strong.
It's not casual! I made the
decision after agonizing over it!
Don't. Don't buy it.
Whoa...
If you accept that amount, please sign
and put your thumbprint here.
They're just underlings.
A caravel!
What and how did you agonize over
to make this kind of decision?!
What a good ship!
Usopp!
Whatever you do, don't underestimate the
family's boss, Franky, who's behind them.
He isn't here?
How dare you talk about it
while waving this stupid thing?!
Are you sure? Didn't you just
screw up the directions?
I'll go prepare the money immediately.
Alright! All done! Now the
Going Merry pirate ship is all set!
I'm not you! Keep your mouth shut!
Okay! I'll put however
many thumbprints you want!
What'd you do that for?!
Usopp!
It's an eyesore.
Dammit! We were a little too late!
--What'd you say?!
--Ah, look at that!
If that's not enough, I'll put mine, too!
Hey, Luffy, if it wasn't because we
got our money stolen, then why?!
Hey! Are you okay?!
Well... your ship stands on her last legs.
Luffy, why don't you say it?! Hey!
Why are you keeping quiet?!
Yeah... That was close.
This is a good opportunity.
Hey! Where are the Straw Hats?!
Look! It's blood!
If you're not being considerate
to me, then don't hold back!
Just give up and buy a new ship here.
That idiot! He just walked off
without waiting for us!
Th-They're probably still at Dock #1.
Say it! I won't accept it unless
I hear good reason! Hey!
You've got money, right?
I heard that your ship is a caravel.
What? What's the matter, Nami?
Don't tell me he...
The Merry can no longer...
There're three things I
want to say, Mr. Appraiser.
To start with, your future journeys will
be tough on such an old-style ship.
Usopp...
We brought him over, Iceberg-san.
First... I forgot to tell you, but this guy's
got a 100 million bounty on his head.
Hm?
No... I don't intend to get a new ship.
"Ahhh..."
You're doing it again! You're hurting my ear!
Luffy...
Thanks, Lucci.
Our...
We're sorry that that idiot caused you trouble.
Our ship is the Going Merry!
Second...
What... did you just say?
If she's repaired, she can still sail!
Ahh! He spoke again!
...I don't accept the appraisal
you've just given us.
Coo coo!
It'll be fine! Today, too,
she sailed here comfortably!
Third... if you lie to us again,
we'll go after your head.
Ow!
Don't make me repeat myself.
Help me!
Now, apologize to them, Paulie!
Luffy?!
The Merry can no longer be repaired.
And yet, we're suddenly told
that she can't sail anymore...?
That pigeon is doing all the talking!
That is all.
How can we believe that?!
No matter what we do, she won't be fixed.
I... I'm sorry!
You guys're saying that because
you don't know how strong she is!
It's as if he's speaking for that man with a hat.
What're you doing?!
Where'd you come falling from?
In any case, I'm glad we got the money back.
Otherwise, I wouldn't say something like that.
Th-Three hundred million Berries?!
Isn't this a dream?
Hey, you're the owner of the money?
This ship?! Are you talking about this
ship that we're on board right now?!
Will you be satisfied if you keep
sailing on her until she sinks?
Shipyard...
Our adventure on the sky islands
has finally borne fruit!
I picked it up for you.
I was jumping around imitating this
one shipwright to look for Usopp.
Oh, thanks!
Good grief...
That's right. This ship will sink soon.
If you wanna thank me, then give me 10%.
I'm super rich!
Are you okay?
And you call yourself a ship's captain?!
That should be "we"!
Yeah.
P-Please come again!
Oh, that's right. We've got a problem, guys!
Sorry, mister.
What're you talking about, Luffy?
Usopp got abducted along with the money.
I-I-It became 300 million! I-I'm scared!
This guy racked up a gambling debt,
It's the truth. They told us at the shipyard.
Our discussion is over for now.
Yeah, we know.
Think about it carefully. If you decide
to buy a ship, come again. I'll help you.
so he's greedy and has no manners.
Come on. We're on our way to their hideout.
I'm carrying 100 million?
They said that she can't
even reach the next island.
Well, Nami can really make scary threats, huh?
So, why the heck are you talking?!
Usopp got beaten up and had
the money stolen from him.
If you give us your 300 million, we can
even build a state-of-the-art ship for you.
You bastard! You're really
running your mouth, Lucci!
Oh, really... She can't, huh?
I estimated it to be that much from
the start. But then he said 100 million.
What?!
So you were persuaded by
strangers you just met today
Kalifa!
I won't take it anymore!
It's possible that he felt responsible
You two were restless,
so he didn't take us seriously.
Yes. Please give it a thought.
Rope Action!
and gave up just like that?
and went to pick a fight with
the Franky Family all by himself.
What'd you say?
Coo coo!
This is a catalogue that contains
both new and used models.
Hey, Luffy. If you flail it like that...
Just because first-class
shipwrights told you that this is it...
Please use it as a price reference.
Bowline Knot!
Well, anyway, I'm glad it went well.
Iceberg-san!
...you gave up just like that?!
There's someone at the gate
who wants to see you.
Huh?
Well, then... I'm leaving now.
Punishment...
We've traveled together all this time!
Hm?
Ahhhh! The river!
I don't see any appointment, though.
We made it through all sorts
of waves and battles together!
100 million Berries are gonna sink into the river!
Ahh...
Looks like that World Government
Official is here again.
Wait! Oh, no! He's serious!
She's our dear friend!
Are you gonna abandon her in a place like this?!
Shall I turn him away?
Phew! That was close!
Well... yeah... Tell him I'm out.
...Pole-and-Line Fishing!
Seriously, what a stubborn man he is.
Anyway, you've got quite
a case of bed head, Lulu.
--I'm gonna knock you out!
--I'm gonna break your teeth, you son of a bitch!
Even though we don't know
whether he has it or not,
Is that how little this ship means to you, Luffy?!
Oops. Pardon me.
I-I'm... I'm sorry.
they send me out this far each time.
Well then, I'll ask him to leave.
I wish people would put themselves in my shoes.
Y-Yeah, would you?
You shouldn't shout like that, Usopp.
Hold it, Iceberg-kun.
Did you hear that?
--Sorry, but step aside.
--What?
Yeah. They said 300 million Berries.
So you're around.
They must be members of the Straw Hats.
I'm not done talking with him.
...Pole-and-Line Fishing!
It's Kalifa.
That's a bigger amount than their total bounty.
Usopp...
Hey, you guys, hide! It's a government official!
Well... come in.
We're changing the plan.
What? O-Okay.
Then can you make an accurate assessment?!
You must be worn out, Iceberg-san.
I-Is he okay?
Hey, go let the guys who
went to their ship know.
Would you like something to drink?
We don't have a shipwright on this ship.
That's why we asked them to check her!
Well... it's nothing new.
Yeah...
Well... Hi, Corgy. I'm not around today.
I'll have some tea today.
Whoa! L-L-Look at that!
Fine! We don't have to
ask those guys to fix her!
I've prepared it.
Yes, you are!
S-Say, Nami, maybe we really
should take it back to the ship.
He's parried that impact with just one arm!
Well... Just as I'd expect from you, Kalifa.
Seriously, I've come all
the way here by sea train.
I'll repair her, as I always have!
That'd be a waste of time.
The shipyard is right over this hill.
Thank you very much.
Please don't refuse me.
That's how we've continued
to travel in the first place.
Hm?
His fingers are sinking into the ground.
Hey, I'm a bit shocked you guys
won't let me near the money.
Okay, let's start now. Hey, help me, guys!
Mr. Corgy is always angry
when he leaves, isn't he?
Wh-What the heck kind of fingers does he have?
Hey, wait, Usopp.
Once we see a shipwright,
What on earth does he come to talk about?
Oh, yeah, we don't have enough lumber.
I'll go buy some at the shipyard.
What's with the shipwrights working here?
we'll probably need to go back to the Merry
right away so that he can assess the repair fee...
I somehow detect the scent of pirates.
Yeah...
He wants something I have,
so he suggests all sorts of deals.
Now, we're getting busy.
Well, that's okay. In any case,
I want to talk to you.
Hey! You, with the goggles!
I see.
You're not a shipwright, are you, Usopp?!
Hm?
That's true.
I hate you! Go home!
Hey, Luffy!
It must be something very precious, huh?
I don't really know what to do, since I've
never carried so much cash around.
Hey, think about it carefully.
Are you a child?
I'm a fully grown man.
Yeah, you're right. So what?!
Well, I always tell him that I don't know
what he's talking about and refuse.
The one who mocked or
provoked you was that pigeon!
Well, that's only natural.
But I don't trust irresponsible
shipwrights who easily give up on a ship
I can't understand why a
person would flail it around.
Well, please don't be so obstinate.
just because it belongs to someone else
They really are a pain in the ass.
Ah! Hey, look over there! They're selling
water buns! Let's buy 100 of them!
I brought a good deal for you today.
Give me a chance to explain.
by taking advantage of
their position as craftsmen!
--Shut up.
-Then, let's buy 1,000 of them!
That's fine! The one who hit me was Lucci!
Usopp...
--Shut up.
--Then...
Shut up!
This must be a lesson that we should
protect our own ship by ourselves.
Now, let's go somewhere inconspicuous.
Okay...
The pigeon can't hit you himself,
so he had that guy hit you!
I'll never... give up on this ship!
They keep coming back. How persistent...
Hey, pigeon!
What business do they have with Iceberg-san?
Are you guys stupid or what?!
If you wanna fight, fight yourself!
It has nothing to do with us. It must be
something to do with power. Coo coo.
You probably got fooled by the shipwrights'
convincing argument, didn't you?!
Say something!
Shall I go beat them up?
The Luffy I know would've believed
in the strength of the Merry first
Don't. They're from the World Government.
Is he breathing, Chopper?
rather than buying those guys' sales talk!
Coo coo!
Although he's completely
unconscious, he's still alive.
Oh? You wanna fight? Bring it on, you bastard!
Hm...? What? What's the matter?
Such a clear-cut answer that sounds
Stop it, Paulie.
He'll be okay. I can save him.
like one made by an old man
who understands everything...
Coo coo. Well, sorry for the fuss.
This is something I noticed when I
carried these bags and hid earlier...
How can you make a decision like that,
suddenly acting all captain-like?!
We're back at the entrance to the shipyard.
I misjudged you, Luffy!
I'm Rob L... No, I mean, Hattori the pigeon.
Just wait a bit... Usopp.
They are light, after all.
Wait a sec, Usopp! Luffy, too, first--
And this is Rob Lucci. He works here.
Nice to meet you. Coo coo!
What...? Why?
Stay out of this, Nami!
This is something I decided!
Good! Looks like the
crowd from earlier is gone.
Oh, don't joke like that. Why would they
be light with all that money in them?
Oh? He almost introduced
himself as if he were human!
I won't change my opinion.
No matter what you say now,
Anyway, let's find... well...
What's his name again?
we're gonna get a new ship!
We'll say goodbye to the Merry here!
A-ha! Yeah, I got it!
That's ventriloquism, isn't it?!
Don't be ridiculous! I won't allow that!
Iceberg-san.
Whoa! Seriously?! Then it
was you who was complaining!
Right, that's it! Ice pops!
Listen, Luffy! It's not like everyone
can live looking ahead like you do!
What are those voices?!
I wonder who he is.
You're really, really good! I didn't notice!
The granny at the station told us to ask him.
Stop it. It's no big deal. Coo coo.
I can't just leave our wounded friend
here and move on to the seas ahead!
You idiots! What's the big fuss?!
Yeah...
Hey, woman! If you sit like that...!
Don't be ridiculous! Even if she's a friend,
ships and humans are different!
More importantly, I wonder if
it's okay to go inside there?
He's a weirdo who can't talk to people properly.
We're gonna go blow that stupid house away!
They're the same! Merry has
the strength to live left in her!
Don't tell me... There's...
I'm coming in!
Not again!
Wait a sec! What's with that woman?!
--Considering how you are, aren't you
excited thinking about the new ship
--Hey, that's enough, you guys!
--Hold it!
--Hm?
...no way...
Wh-What?
Wait.
--while pretending to be concerned about Merry?!
--You can't have a conversation
if you're worked up like that!
You're shameless!
You're an outsider, aren't you?
Our 200 million Berries...!
Enough, already!
Huh?
Let's talk outside for now.
Luffy!
You're showing your legs too much!
It's gone! It's really gone!
Don't think that you're the only
one who feels pain over this!
On closer inspection, they're not our bags!
Everyone feels the same way!
Only authorized people can go inside the plant.
If so, there's no way you'd
decide to get a new ship!
This is a workplace for men!
Look how you're dressed!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What're we gonna do?!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh...
Fine! If you dislike what I decide
that much, then get off this--
Hey, what are you guys shouting so loud for?
Now, Paulie, calm down.
Our money is... gone.
Heave-ho.
It's... totally... gone.
Sanji...!
Do you have some business at this dock?
--What?!
--Paulie! Did you...
You, too, Kalifa!
Oh, it's you, Usopp.
It's not me!
You haven't learned your lesson and are
wearing such outrageous clothes again!
Hey! Go get more food!
--Are you telling the truth?!
--Why would I lie?!
Hey! I'm right here, Luffy!
--Is that really true?!
--How noisy... More importantly, Kaku.
How many times do I have to tell you?!
Wear pants! Long pants!
We've got money!
You idiot... What were you about to say?!
Yeah. He's square-ish!
The alcohol today sure tastes good!
Which means, he's square Usopp!
Weren't you with the Franky Family earlier?
--What the heck...?
--Long pants...?
Cool down! Be careful about
what you say! Got that, Luffy?!
No, I'm not a triangle or a square.
Hm? What're you talking about?
He's a weirdo, too!
Oh, yeah! Um... We'd like to see Iceberg-san.
I've drawn graffiti on the walls of
people's houses for all these years.
I haven't seen the Franky Family today.
Well, that's it. Let's open the
door and go inside already.
That's strange. I'm sure I saw your long nose.
Hm? Iceberg-san? Are you a customer?
Oh, I see.
Hold on a sec, you guys!
This is a reference letter from
Granny Kokoro at Shift Station, huh?
Thanks! So you took my goggles back from him?
That's Usopp!
He was with the Franky Family?!
Sorry. I just...
Hm? Are you an old guy?
He was with them, or rather,
he was carried away by them.
That's okay, Luffy. That's how
you really feel, isn't it?
At any rate, what a huge door!
And this requires manual operation?
I'm 23.
23... You talk like an old man.
Okay, then!
That's an abduction!
What'd you say?!
Luffy! We'll go look for him right away!
I'll tell you a story about when I bravely
fought Sea Kings in the Calm Belt.
Can those two weirdos open it by themselves?
Okay!
People often tell me that.
Hey! Hold on a sec!
Where're you gonna look, Luffy?!
Go ahead and cut off useless friends
one after another and move on.
So... do you know this Iceberg person?
Big ones! They were...
Whoa! It's moving!
Know him? Well, Iceberg-san
is the mayor of Water Seven.
If you're gonna abandon the Merry...
Well... each dock has only
five shipwright foremen.
Just wait, Usopp! Money!
They may not look like it, but their
skills made them foremen at Dock #1.
...why don't you do that to me, too?!
A-And what's more...
I have 8,000 men under me!
Whoa... So he's that high up?
Geez...
Hey, where's the Franky Family's hideout?
Not only is he the mayor,
Kaku, who we talked about earlier,
is one of them, too.
he's the president of our company,
Galley-La Company,
This is a world where craftsmen's
skills are all that matters.
It's more like a workshop rather than a hideout,
and he also manages the sea train.
Even if their personalities are weird,
don't worry about it.
but it's at the seashore quite a ways
northwest from the rocky cape
So he's the most powerful guy in town?!
That large amount of money... They stole it all.
Well, in Water Seven, there's no
one who doesn't know him.
Yeah, they're weird.
Ah, the door's started opening.
where your ship is anchored.
Nami...
Don't let the money leave your hands.
I don't think we have thieves inside, but...
Where do we have to go to see him?
It's called Franky House.
I can't face everyone.
Hmm, I wonder where he is right now.
Go ahead and cut off useless friends
one after another and move on.
He can be hard to find,
since he's a very busy person.
Well, it was also my fault earlier,
and it caused you trouble, too.
Make sure you beat up every one of them, guys!
If you're gonna abandon the Merry...
Oh... Can't you get in touch
with him or something?
--Hey, Luffy!
--Huh?
Make sure you guard me good!
...why don't you do that to me, too?!
That's probably possible, but...
Are you in a hurry?
Okay, got it. Leave it to me!
Hey, Usopp. Don't say stupid stuff like that.
--I'm worried.
--Leave it to me!
It's not that we're in a hurry, but...
No, I'm serious.
This Dock #1 comprises the main
force of the Galley-La Company,
So that's what you wanna do?
See? You lose.
I've been thinking about this for a while.
In short, you want to talk about
having your ship repaired, right?
Luffy!
Now, go buy some food!
and it undertakes the most difficult work.
To be honest,
Make sure you buy all the food at
the store, okay?! We've got money!
Luffy!
Here, come inside.
Where did you anchor your ship?
I've been thinking that I can't keep
up with your monstrous strength.
Wow!
Rocky cape.
Seriously, when there's no way he
could find Usopp all by himself...!
Well then, I'll go run and check
the condition of your ship.
Like today... I can't even watch over money.
Whoooa!
I have no time to look for Luffy.
Dammit. Just you wait and see.
I'll beat you later.
It'll save some time when you see Iceberg-san.
I'd better go leave this
money at the ship for now.
I'll just keep causing you guys trouble.
You can talk about the repair fee, too.
If I march in saying, "Give me our 200
million back" with 100 million on me,
"Go run"...? On a Yagara bull?
Whoooa! Huge!
I'd be asking them to steal it too.
Anyway, Yagara-chan, head towards
the bull shop using the shortest route!
Huh?
You don't need weak friends, right?
If I do that, you'll grow tired of waiting.
Well, just wait for ten minutes.
A shipyard has a tremendous
impact when seen up close!
Luffy... you're the man
who'll be king of the pirates.
--Yeah!
--True!
Ten minutes?
Oh? They're building a
huge galleon! Whose is that?
But I don't have to go that high up.
That's right. Ten minutes.
I'm gonna take Zoro and the others
with me and teach them a lesson!
It's full of craftsmen.
Thinking back, when I was about to sail out,
you guys asked me to join you.
Franky Family! Stealing from pirates?!
You're the lowest!
Now, this way.
What?! What happened?!
Whoa!
--He's fast!
--Whoooa!
Oh, it's Iceberg-san!
What're you talkin' about? Get on already.
Someone's there!
Hey! Boss is here!
Oof!
Who the hell are you jerks?!
Ahhh! He jumped!
We're friends now, aren't we?
This is the first floor,
the backstreet shopping district.
Good morning, Iceberg-san!
Good morning!
Boss! Could you take a look at
how the outer panels turned out?
Take care and have a good day!
What... but wait! Over there is...
That's all that's tying us together.
Sure! I'll come by later!
...a precipice!
--Ahhhh!
--He fell!
That's...
Good day, Iceberg-san!
We don't have to travel together
when we have a difference of opinion!
I'm counting on you, Yagara-chan!
Well... Hello, are things going well?
Yes, sir! They're going pretty well!
What the heck?!
Hey, where're you going, Usopp?!
Whoa! Ice pops is quite popular.
Hey, watch out, lady!
Where I'm going is my own business.
Sorry!
Amazing!
That's...
Of course he is. In this city,
skills are all that matters.
It has nothing to do with you guys anymore.
I hope... Usopp got away okay.
Is he okay?
...Straw Hat Luffy!
He runs freely in town.
On this island, shipbuilding was
well-developed from the start,
I'm...
--What?
--Huh?
and seven shipbuilding companies
were competing with each other.
People call him the "Mountain Wind."
...leaving the gang.
He's a shipwright foreman of
Galley-La Company's Dock #1...
Meanwhile, he attracted craftsmen
with his genius shipbuilding skills.
Then he put those seven companies together
So you came to get the
money back, huh, you fools?
His name is Kaku.
This is terrible.
Who the heck is he?
to form a company five years ago.
And that's this Galley-La Company.
See all the guys here? What do
you think the four of you can do?
Hey! Does anyone know who this guy is?!
Well, well... I see...
His passion and skills in
shipbuilding have never changed,
A crowd of people...
Yagara-chan! Stop! Stop!
and the craftsmen won't forget
their respect towards him.
The city of water... This is amazing!
But, well... you're here.
You've got a bounty on your head.
And, because the craftsmen
are proud of their skills,
Usopp...
Clear springs and rivers...
Clean streets and lively crowds...
So why don't you leave
that head of yours with us?
Oh, no...
they never give in to pirates or authority.
Usopp!
He's the captain of that weak long-nosed guy.
Hey! What're you doing, Luffy?!
And many pretty women.
This is that kind of place.
Usopp! Wake up!
I wanna go out on a date with Nami-san
or Robin-chan in a town like this!
Is it okay to let him go like this?!
Hey...! Are you okay?!
Hm?
He can't be that strong.
Hey! Go after him!
Hey, pops. I heard that
you're a topnotch shipwright.
Hey!
Stop him now!
Hey! Usopp! Usopp!
Being between two pretty women is good, too.
Do you wanna be a pirate with me?
Hey, are you guys pirates by any chance?
What the hell are you saying,
you son of a bitch?!
Come on, shorty.
H-How insolent!
We've come this far together.
Is it okay to part like this?
Shut up! Don't stare at us!
Now, now... He's always like that.
This side is Nami-san
and this side is Robin-chan.
Gum-Gum...
Sorry about that.
Well... you guys don't even
have a single shipwright?
Hey, mister. Stop making that weird face.
Usopp! Was it the Franky Family
who did this to you? Was it them?!
Usopp is our precious friend.
Hm?
So which water-water napa
cabbage are you gonna buy?
That's right. We came to this island
in order to have our ship repaired
Hm? Oh, yes, I'll buy both. Oh, and...
Stop him!
What're you doing?
Yeah... Because I'm weak...
and to find a new crew member.
Hey, Luffy... You are the captain, right?!
He's punching? At that huge steel armor
that even a battleship cannon can't shatter?
I want to get some food that's in season
from this town. What's available?
It's true that we have tons of shipwrights,
but I wonder if anyone would
want to go on board a pirate ship.
That large amount of money...
Water-water apples and water-water pears!
They stole it all.
What a joke!
If you find someone who wants to
go with you, you can headhunt him.
Interested in fish that are in season?
My hubby runs a fish shop.
Nami...
Why aren't you saying anything?
Really?! You're generous!
Can't I ask you to join us, pops?
Yeah...?
If you're just fooling around,
I'll go ahead and crush you!
Where is it?
I can't face everyone.
Get back on the land, turn right
six times and turn left twelve times.
Well... I can't. I'm the mayor.
Usopp!
Who cares?!
Wait! It shouldn't be like this!
Huh?
Hey! Turn around!
We were finally about to have Merry repaired...
By the way, is the woman named
Nico Robin really on board your ship?
Let's see... Hm? What the heck...?
Hey! Come back!
Don't go! Usopp!
In any case, it sure is
inconvenient when we have to walk.
Yeah, she is. She's really smart.
I feel so ashamed.
Come back!
Another dead end? Shucks.
...Cannon!
What? Is something matter with Robin?
Luffy...
Dammit...!
Did I get lost? This is bad...
No...
Hey, pops, is it okay to go
closer and see that ship?
Usopp, I get it.
I'm just like a certain damn swordsman.
Sure, that's fine.
Don't worry about the money.
We'll all go and get it back for sure.
Hm?
Thanks!
He's hurt quite badly.
I probably shouldn't move him.
H-He punched a hole in that huge armor!
Oh! Robin-chan!
Usopp, stay here just for a while.
Hey!
Hello! It's me! Yoo-hoo!
In any case, it's really amazing!
I'll hurry back to the ship and bring back help.
W-Wait a sec, you guys! Let's have a talk first!
Robin-chan!
Keep that steady! Don't rush! Go slowly!
I'll bring Chopper, too, so that he can treat you!
Hm?
Let's have a...
Luffy! I can't go along with you anymore.
If we could install a cannon like that,
the Merry would also be... Hm?
Let's... Let's...
Don't worry about the stolen money.
She disappeared?
Let's fire cannonballs!
I heard that their hideout is ahead of here.
When there're no doors or streets?
Yahoo!
Whoa! A demi-culverin!
Sorry to cause you trouble until the end.
So we'll crush them and
that'll be the end of them!
Did she fly or something?
How cool! It's so long...! And shining!
Three-Sword Style...
Hm?
Hey! This isn't a show!
It's true that the ship
belongs to you, the captain.
...Raven...
I wanna fire something like that, one time!
Usopp?
Listen, Usopp. Just stay put here, okay?
What's with this town?
Am I the one who's off here?
This is a good chance.
So fight me...
It looks like it's made of copper.
That must be expensive!
I'll be back right away!
...Hunt!
Monkey D. Luffy!
I wonder if they'd let me try firing it.
Oh, wait. We've now got 300 million Berries.
Go faster, Yagara-chan!
We should be able to buy
one or more cannons like that!
Fight a duel with me!
Ahhh! A runaway bull!
Th-The cannonballs are made of iron, you know!
Hey!
Oh... That ship must be the one.
We were finally about to have Merry repaired...
What? What? Er, hey... what're you saying?!
Hm?
Pardon me.
Wasn't there someone there?
No matter how much you pay, that ship
can't be restored to how she used to be.
Even a cannon, too!
At 10 o'clock tonight, I'll come back here.
Where did Robin go?
Bad news! These guys are seriously bad news!
Whether we decide to buy a new ship
Oh, it's just Usopp.
Then we'll fight a duel over the Merry!
G-Get out of here!
Get out through the back door!
It's this way.
or have someone else manage
to fix and improve the Merry,
I see. It's damaged.
I'll defeat you and take the Merry.
unless we spend all the 300 million
on the ship to upgrade her,
That's...
...the end of the bond
between you guys and me.
Hm? This smell is...
our future journey will certainly be hard.
The mast needs to be replaced, too.
You started the fight. Don't act pathetic.
I knew it!
We definitely need that money.
Usopp...
Hmm... At any rate, who the heck was that
masked man who was with Robin-chan?
We have to get it back without fail!
Party Table...
Hold on a sec! Who the hell are you?!
What's with you?! Stop this nonsense!
...Kick Course!
Is that true?!
Oh, I'm sorry. I woke you up.
Was that Chopper after all?
At least that's what that shipwright said.
Why do you have to fight
a duel with your friend?!
Sanji!
Boy... was I shocked!
Hm?
If you give it a little time,
you two will cool down, right?!
He jumped from there!
This ship...
Chopper?
...can no longer be fixed?
Even if we pay lots of money?!
Well... Don't make light of my craftsmen.
Usopp, too. He just got flared up
because things were moving quickly.
Then... What's gonna happen to Merry?!
W-We can't use the back door!
Now that we've come this far, we can't go back.
Beats me.
In the end, it depends on how
Luffy and the others decide
Windows! Get out through the windows!
That's not true!
--Come to think of it, who's this guy?
--Beats me.
You can apologize to him and talk it over again!
after hearing the outcome of the assessment.
Rumble...
Hm? Kaku...
In order to build a faster, stronger ship quickly,
...Horn Point!
Those three at the shipyard will
probably make some decision.
--Where have you been?
--An assessment.
Ah! You're the guy from earlier!
So you checked our ship?
an ordinary physical ability isn't good enough.
But it's too extreme.
Yeah, I did.
By the way, Kalifa...
Like I said... it's no longer possible.
Look at the ship!
Yes, I've already checked.
So you were here, Iceberg-san.
She's the same old Merry.
Straw Hat Luffy,
pirate hunter Zoro, Nico Robin...
We and Merry traveled together
all the way here from the East Blue!
Why not?
Roseo Colonnade!
I know the situation. How was it?
Usopp isn't stupid enough to risk
his life under the influence of anger.
Well...
That's exactly why, right?
Their group has those three members
with bounties on their heads.
Luffy! Come down now!
Human beings can become
stronger after each hardship,
Besides, if talking it over
would change his opinion,
Their total bounty is 239 million Berries.
W-W-Wait a sec, you guys!
It was formed in the East Blue.
but ships are different.
this wouldn't have happened.
Okay! I'll be right down!
The money, right?!
You want the money back, right?!
They're the Straw Hats, and they
currently have seven crewmembers.
Their pain only accumulates.
If you get it, leave me alone.
The 200 million Berries that
worthless guy had, right?
Th-They know about us big time.
Luffy...
I see. I'm glad you came.
Unfortunately, that money is no longer here.
I'm saying, the Franky Family
came here this afternoon, right?!
It's hard to swallow.
I'm Iceberg, the boss of this city.
Besides, what's Usopp
gonna say when he hears it?
Our boss, Franky, took that
money and went shopping.
And this is a mouse I found earlier.
Huh? So what?
I love the Merry!
His name is... let's see...
Why didn't you beat them
all up beyond recovery then?!
Since he's buying something
on the black market,
We all do. But her scars are so deep
that there's nothing we can do, he said.
What?! Is that true?!
...Tyrannosaurus.
we don't know where he went.
If you're lying, you'll pay for it!
I have to prepare his food and cage.
If you had, Usopp wouldn't have
been attacked and felt guilty!
In short, no matter how much
you go on a rampage here,
I've already taken care of them, Iceberg-san.
I never lie on the job.
that 200 million Berries won't come ba--
The Merry... Robin-chan...
I'm worried about both.
Well, that's my Kalifa.
Then, instead of going shopping,
you should've stayed and fought them!
I'm a goner!
Thank you.
Ahh! Zambai!
More importantly, you're dining with
an executive from a glassware factory
What a restless afternoon...
I went to get necessary food as your cook!
That's enough out of you.
It has nothing to do with money.
at the hotel in Chiza in ten minutes.
Guys!
Stop fighting at a time like this!
After that, you'll give a
talk at the Liguria Square.
There's been enough fighting.
Oh? Nami's back!
When that's done,
a conference with Mr. Bimine,
Yeah... It's too late.
Hm? Looks like she's alone.
Don't fight over what's done.
the mayor of the gourmet town Pucci.
Hm? Where's Usopp?
You'll also be interviewed by
a newspaper company there.
What happened to Luffy and Usopp?
Nami-san...! But this idiot is...
Nami-san! Did something happen?!
After that, please go back to the main
office and go through some documents.
He was wandering about over
there up until just a moment ago.
We'll beat you up so bad that
not even your bones will remain.
Chopper... Didn't you... go follow Usopp?
Not even our bones?!
I don't want to!
Hey, you guys! Don't these bags belong to you?
You idiot! Don't get frightened!
Yow! Yow, yow! 200 million?!
Well then, I'll cancel them all.
"Not even your bones will remain"
Hey! Is that okay?!
is what we, the Franky Family,
demolition workers and bounty hunters, say!
I wanted to continue treating his wounds,
but he turned me away.
Yes, 200 million!
I'm someone powerful enough
to do things like that.
Ahh! They're the bags Usopp was carrying!
What do you think, Bro?!
Show them the Franky House's specialty!
You're completely unfit to be a mayor.
Yeah, they're ours.
Incredible! You guys are amazing!
Thanks!
He got a place to stay in town.
What a selfish guy you are!
Geez... Where did Usopp go...
leaving our precious money alone?!
We've always wanted that. With this
much money, we can finally get it!
But isn't this guy the one
that granny was talking about?
He said...
He said, "You and I are no longer friends,
so go back to the ship!"
Yeah, he's "that guy."
--Money?
--Yeah. Those bags hold 200 million Berries.
Anything Shot Cannon!
How insolent!
We did it, didn't we, Bro?
Three years of persevering...
We've always said, "If only we could get it..."
200 million Berries?
--It was such a long time.
--Yeah...
No way. See ya!
There's no way...
All that fun time up until this
morning seems like a dream.
Each time we got a chunk of money,
we'd pin our hopes on Yagara races...
What'd you do that for?!
Here they come! Attack them!
Holy crap!
...and lose all the money!
D-Don't flinch! Keep firing
until we run out of cannonballs!
So how much does it look like it'll cost?
Each time we captured a criminal
with a bounty, we'd party it up...
If something is happening
to Robin on top of this...
We can pay as much as you like!
We've got tons of money!
There are only four of them!
...and lose all the money!
Where're your manners?! Referring to one
of the world's leading shipbuilding engineers
We couldn't quite save up the
200-million-Berry business expense!
I feel like... the gang is falling apart.
as "this guy" and "that guy"...!
If possible, I'd like her to be stronger,
have more cannons, and be faster!
What's going on?
But we finally have it now!
Kalifa, the secretary, has exploded
for the first time in a while!
Oh, yeah. Good job, you guys!
I wanna be kicked by her, too.
Can you also add pretty
decorations on the outer panels?
Pardon me. I lost my head there for a moment.
Well then, this isn't much,
but here is five million Berries.
Can you renovate inside as well?
However, Iceberg-san is admired
by the citizens. Please be polite.
The Straw Hats, huh?
Also, I want a bronze statue!
This is to show my appreciation.
Eat and drink as you please!
Hm?
Try not to get Kalifa angry.
When she gets angry...
I want it to be as huge as possible!
What're those noises? Fireworks?
Well... I somehow feel restless tonight.
It's from the northeast! They're coming
from the direction of the Franky House!
"Ouch"
Well, hold on a sec...
...she is indiscriminate.
"Ouch"
Them again? What's the fuss about this time?
You've been having some
tremendous journeys, haven't you?
That's our Bro!
You kicked him big time!
It's party time!
It's 10 o'clock, the promised time.
You're the one who's impolite!
Yea... Ugh! Shh! He'll hear us!
Usopp is coming.
Um, but in any case, you're Iceberg-san, right?
Oh, yeah! We flew in the sky, and fell as well.
We climbed a mountain and got skewered.
Oh, boy, they're getting too carried away.
Please look at this. It's a reference letter.
Wh-What the hell?!
We've gone through quite a bit!
From Granny Kokoro...
They really don't show any
restraint when they party, do they?
So we'd like to have her fixed good!
Hm?
"Take a look at their ship.
Kokoro"
"Take a look at their ship," huh?
Dammit!
You guys, don't leave the ship.
Who's trying to defy the Franky Family?!
Ahhh!
It's okay once in a while, right?
It's a wonderful day today.
I'm not lying, you know.
What?! You won't?! Please!
Please repair our ship!
Got that?!
I believe it.
Hm?
We have money!
Her scars from battle are too deep.
The Merry is beat up after
our voyages! Please, pops!
Huh?! You're that weak guy from earlier!
--There he is!
--Usopp!
Do you mean it'll take
quite a long time to fix her?
--Okay.
--How frivolous! So it's okay?!
What? You could still stand?
No...
--Yep.
--Then why did you rip it up?
Frankly speaking, your ship...
Her lipstick mark was unpleasant.
Give me the money back!
Granny Kokoro and I have
been drinking pals for ages.
...can no longer be fixed, even with our skills.
"Give me the money back"? Then are
you one of the Straw Hat's underlings?
Well... that being said, Kaku has
already gone to make an assessment.
Shall we go follow Franky?
Where?
The matter is already in progress. Don't worry.
Drat. Looks like they really
don't know where the money is.
That's right, Bro! Since he's with
Straw Hat Luffy, I expected him to be
It's a boring day today anyway.
a really strong pirate, but then...
Shall I show you around the factory?
Even if we strangle this Franky guy,
if he already spent the money...
Whoa! Seriously?
Well then, this way, please.
He's so weak!
Is that the attitude a man who
canceled his appointments should have?
Is her keel damaged or something?
That's none of your business!
All right! We're gonna go
to the shipbuilding plant!
What do we do now? Even if we wait for
him here, he won't be back for a while.
Yeah, it's taken a lot of damage.
Oops!
Oh, that's right. The money...
Oh, no...
Money... What?
But we've been traveling
just fine up until today!
Hey! I finished giving him first aid!
What's he doing?!
What? What? What?
I'd like to take him on a stretcher,
so help me here!
I'll admit you've got guts to come
to get the money back all by yourself,
Whaaat?!
Let's suppose that we did
what we could anyway.
Hm? What's the matter, Usopp?
Staying here talking won't get us anywhere.
but I can't let you have it back.
The probability of her
reaching the next island is...
Let's go back to the ship for now.
We left Nami-san alone there, too, so...
Th-Th-The money... The money is gone!
Give it back to me!
Whaaat?!
We have the thing with
Robin-chan to deal with...
...zero.
--Look for it thoroughly!
--I can't find it!
We have to... have our ship repaired...
...and the issues with the ship, too.
--Hm? Huh?
--It's gone! I can't find it anywhere!
Yeah.
Hey, Luffy!
Ahh!
Ahh! Over there!
About the ship...
That money is crucial to us!
Hm?
Merry... Can you really not...
So you didn't get cold feet, huh?
I've made a decision.
H... Hey, you bastards! Who the
hell are you?! Who are you?!
With that money...
You'd better be sure you're not going
to regret this, no matter what happens.
...sail anymore?
This is the duel you wanted.
Why are you taking our money?!
Of course. You'd better fight seriously.
...we can finally repair the Merry's scars!
Hey! Hold it!
Let's say goodbye... to the Going Merry here.
I'll turn the tables on you.
I can't let you jerks have it!
Thanks for the money!
I've already figured out how to defeat you.
Give us our money back!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Hey, hey, you're taking the joke too far.
Give me back...
Hey, Usopp! Did you give them the money?!
Hey, Merry... Can you really not sail anymore?
Stop it. It's ridiculous for friends to fight a duel!
I'm not joking.
Usopp!
Why would I do that?! They stole it!
Just give up. The damage is too serious.
Once what we protect becomes
different, we're no longer friends.
Give me that money back!
We'll say goodbye to the Merry here.
At any rate, your ship...
Bull! Don't be ridiculous!
--Oh, no...
--All your ship can do is wait for her end.
Chopper?!
Oh, how was she?
It's over between us!
Hey, Usopp...
...must've had some tremendous journeys.
He's hurt very badly, but he'll be okay.
I can somehow manage to save him!
Don't say that. Luffy, you restrain yourself, too!
This ship can't be fixed anymore!
She'll sink soon.
--That can't be true...
--I can't believe that! We have this much money!
Yep, she has. Please fix her good!
Precisely because we're all friends,
be prepared and watch quietly!
Frankly speaking, your ship...
--Luffy!
--No matter what you say,
I'm never gonna give up on Merry!
The 200 million Berries are gone!
Okay. Just wait a bit, Usopp.
Hey, Usopp is gone, too!
I won't give up the bronze statue!
We're gonna go blow that stupid house away!
Come on, Usopp!
What? Don't tell me...
--...can no longer be fixed.
--What?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Pirate Abduction Incident and a Pirate
Ship That Can Only Await Her End"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Big Fight under the Moon!
The Pirate Flag Flutters with Sorrow!"
"Galley-La Company! A Grand Sight, Dock #1!"
"Luffy vs. Usopp! Collision of Two Men's Pride"
"Rescuing Our Friend!
Raid on the Franky House"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!