It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
So how much does it look like it'll cost?
We can pay as much as you like!
We've got tons of money!
Her scars from battle are too deep.
Do you mean it'll take
quite a long time to fix her?
No...
Frankly speaking, your ship...
...can no longer be fixed, even with our skills.
Oh, no...
But we've been traveling
just fine up until today!
Let's suppose that we did
what we could anyway.
The probability of her
reaching the next island is...
...zero.
Merry... Can you really not...
...sail anymore?
"Pirate Abduction Incident and a Pirate
Ship That Can Only Await Her End"
Crap...
I'm sorry, Sanji. I was so
focused on books that...
It's nothing you should apologize about.
I just assumed that the one
who was with Robin-chan
was you in your human form.
Then, who on earth was that masked man?
In addition, it's strange that
they suddenly disappeared.
Yeah... Robin's scent disappeared there, too.
I hope nothing bad happens...
My stomach's in a knot...
What?
Do you want me to take a look at you?
I'm not sick!
This reminds me of what Aokiji said.
Did he say something worrisome?
He said stuff about Robin-chan's past, right?
And he said to us that we'd
someday regret taking her on.
Now that you mention it...
But does that have something to
do with Robin's disappearance?!
I don't know.
In any case, we're getting nowhere like this.
Let's go back to the Merry for now.
If there's no problem, she'll be back soon.
Yeah.
Take us for a spin, will ya?
You can't fix the Merry?! Why not?!
Aren't you guys amazing shipwrights?!
If you're worried about money, look!
We've got tons!
It has nothing to do with money.
No matter how much you pay, that ship
can't be restored to how she used to be.
I'm rather impressed that you guys
made it this far in the state she's in.
What do you mean?!
What's going on with the Merry?!
Do you know what a keel is, shameless girl?
Shamele...
The one at the bottom of the ship?
That's right. It's the most
important wood beam on a ship.
It crosses from stem to stern
and supports the ship.
When you build a ship,
you start off by placing the keel.
Then, the stem wood, stern wood, frame wood...
...frame brackets and deck beams...
We accurately place all those
pieces of wood around the keel.
That's how a ship is built.
The keel is the very foundation
of a ship's framework.
It's the essence of the ship.
It's not something you can just replace
if it takes on a lot of damage...
Replacing the keel is the same
as building a ship from scratch.
So no one can fix her anymore.
Your ship is just a collection of wood
that can only await her end.
Hey! Don't say it like that!
Not my problem. That's the truth.
Then... Then build a ship from scratch for us!
Build the Going Merry!
Coo coo! That's not possible, either.
Why not?
We can build a similar ship,
but strictly speaking,
no one can build the same ship.
In this world, there are no two
ships that are exactly the same.
What does that mean?!
Are there any trees in the world
that grow exactly the same way?
Sailing ships are mostly made of wood,
so the size and curves of the ship are
all affected by the shape of the trees.
That's why an exact duplicate
of the ship can't be built,
even when using the same blueprint.
For example, even if we build such a ship,
without a doubt, the ones who would
feel that it's a totally different ship...
...would be you guys! Coo coo!
Oh, no...
Then we really can no longer
travel on the Going Merry?
That's right.
You either do nothing and wait until she sinks...
...or you take her apart quickly.
Whoa...
A caravel!
What a good ship!
Alright! All done! Now the
Going Merry pirate ship is all set!
Well... your ship stands on her last legs.
This is a good opportunity.
Just give up and buy a new ship here.
You've got money, right?
I heard that your ship is a caravel.
To start with, your future journeys will
be tough on such an old-style ship.
No... I don't intend to get a new ship.
Luffy...
Our...
Our ship is the Going Merry!
If she's repaired, she can still sail!
It'll be fine! Today, too,
she sailed here comfortably!
And yet, we're suddenly told
that she can't sail anymore...?
How can we believe that?!
You guys're saying that because
you don't know how strong she is!
Will you be satisfied if you keep
sailing on her until she sinks?
Good grief...
And you call yourself a ship's captain?!
Our discussion is over for now.
Think about it carefully. If you decide
to buy a ship, come again. I'll help you.
If you give us your 300 million, we can
even build a state-of-the-art ship for you.
Kalifa!
Yes. Please give it a thought.
This is a catalogue that contains
both new and used models.
Please use it as a price reference.
Iceberg-san!
There's someone at the gate
who wants to see you.
Hm?
I don't see any appointment, though.
Looks like that World Government
Official is here again.
Shall I turn him away?
Well... yeah... Tell him I'm out.
Anyway, you've got quite
a case of bed head, Lulu.
Oops. Pardon me.
Well then, I'll ask him to leave.
Y-Yeah, would you?
Hold it, Iceberg-kun.
So you're around.
Hey, you guys, hide! It's a government official!
What? O-Okay.
Well... Hi, Corgy. I'm not around today.
Yes, you are!
Seriously, I've come all
the way here by sea train.
Please don't refuse me.
Hm?
I somehow detect the scent of pirates.
Well, that's okay. In any case,
I want to talk to you.
I hate you! Go home!
Are you a child?
I'm a fully grown man.
Well, please don't be so obstinate.
I brought a good deal for you today.
Give me a chance to explain.
Now, let's go somewhere inconspicuous.
They keep coming back. How persistent...
What business do they have with Iceberg-san?
It has nothing to do with us. It must be
something to do with power. Coo coo.
Shall I go beat them up?
Don't. They're from the World Government.
Hm...? What? What's the matter?
This is something I noticed when I
carried these bags and hid earlier...
They are light, after all.
What...? Why?
Oh, don't joke like that. Why would they
be light with all that money in them?
What are those voices?!
You idiots! What's the big fuss?!
Hey, woman! If you sit like that...!
Don't tell me... There's...
...no way...
Our 200 million Berries...!
It's gone! It's really gone!
On closer inspection, they're not our bags!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What're we gonna do?!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh...
Hey, what are you guys shouting so loud for?
Our money is... gone.
It's... totally... gone.
--What?!
--Paulie! Did you...
It's not me!
--Are you telling the truth?!
--Why would I lie?!
--Is that really true?!
--How noisy... More importantly, Kaku.
Weren't you with the Franky Family earlier?
Hm? What're you talking about?
I haven't seen the Franky Family today.
That's strange. I'm sure I saw your long nose.
Hold on a sec, you guys!
That's Usopp!
He was with the Franky Family?!
He was with them, or rather,
he was carried away by them.
That's an abduction!
Luffy! We'll go look for him right away!
Okay!
Hey! Hold on a sec!
Where're you gonna look, Luffy?!
Just wait, Usopp! Money!
Geez...
Hey, where's the Franky Family's hideout?
It's more like a workshop rather than a hideout,
but it's at the seashore quite a ways
northwest from the rocky cape
where your ship is anchored.
It's called Franky House.
Luffy!
Seriously, when there's no way he
could find Usopp all by himself...!
I have no time to look for Luffy.
I'd better go leave this
money at the ship for now.
If I march in saying, "Give me our 200
million back" with 100 million on me,
I'd be asking them to steal it too.
Anyway, Yagara-chan, head towards
the bull shop using the shortest route!
I'm gonna take Zoro and the others
with me and teach them a lesson!
Franky Family! Stealing from pirates?!
You're the lowest!
This is the first floor,
the backstreet shopping district.
Take care and have a good day!
I'm counting on you, Yagara-chan!
What the heck?!
Hey, watch out, lady!
Sorry!
I hope... Usopp got away okay.
This is terrible.
Who the heck is he?
Hey! Does anyone know who this guy is?!
A crowd of people...
Yagara-chan! Stop! Stop!
Usopp!
Usopp! Wake up!
Hey...! Are you okay?!
Hey!
Hey! Usopp! Usopp!
Hey, are you guys pirates by any chance?
Shut up! Don't stare at us!
Usopp! Was it the Franky Family
who did this to you? Was it them?!
Yeah... Because I'm weak...
That large amount of money...
They stole it all.
Nami...
Yeah...?
I can't face everyone.
We were finally about to have Merry repaired...
I feel so ashamed.
Dammit...!
Usopp, I get it.
Don't worry about the money.
We'll all go and get it back for sure.
He's hurt quite badly.
I probably shouldn't move him.
Usopp, stay here just for a while.
I'll hurry back to the ship and bring back help.
I'll bring Chopper, too, so that he can treat you!
Don't worry about the stolen money.
I heard that their hideout is ahead of here.
So we'll crush them and
that'll be the end of them!
Hey! This isn't a show!
Listen, Usopp. Just stay put here, okay?
I'll be back right away!
Go faster, Yagara-chan!
Ahhh! A runaway bull!
Hey!
We were finally about to have Merry repaired...
No matter how much you pay, that ship
can't be restored to how she used to be.
Whether we decide to buy a new ship
or have someone else manage
to fix and improve the Merry,
unless we spend all the 300 million
on the ship to upgrade her,
our future journey will certainly be hard.
We definitely need that money.
We have to get it back without fail!
Is that true?!
At least that's what that shipwright said.
This ship...
...can no longer be fixed?
Even if we pay lots of money?!
Then... What's gonna happen to Merry?!
Beats me.
In the end, it depends on how
Luffy and the others decide
after hearing the outcome of the assessment.
Those three at the shipyard will
probably make some decision.
But it's too extreme.
Look at the ship!
She's the same old Merry.
We and Merry traveled together
all the way here from the East Blue!
That's exactly why, right?
Human beings can become
stronger after each hardship,
but ships are different.
Their pain only accumulates.
It's hard to swallow.
Besides, what's Usopp
gonna say when he hears it?
I love the Merry!
We all do. But her scars are so deep
that there's nothing we can do, he said.
The Merry... Robin-chan...
I'm worried about both.
What a restless afternoon...
Guys!
Oh? Nami's back!
Hm? Looks like she's alone.
What happened to Luffy and Usopp?
Nami-san! Did something happen?!
Yow! Yow, yow! 200 million?!
Yes, 200 million!
What do you think, Bro?!
Incredible! You guys are amazing!
We've always wanted that. With this
much money, we can finally get it!
We did it, didn't we, Bro?
Three years of persevering...
We've always said, "If only we could get it..."
--It was such a long time.
--Yeah...
Each time we got a chunk of money,
we'd pin our hopes on Yagara races...
...and lose all the money!
Each time we captured a criminal
with a bounty, we'd party it up...
...and lose all the money!
We couldn't quite save up the
200-million-Berry business expense!
But we finally have it now!
Oh, yeah. Good job, you guys!
Well then, this isn't much,
but here is five million Berries.
This is to show my appreciation.
Eat and drink as you please!
That's our Bro!
It's party time!
Wh-What the hell?!
Hm?
Dammit!
Who's trying to defy the Franky Family?!
Huh?! You're that weak guy from earlier!
What? You could still stand?
Give me the money back!
"Give me the money back"? Then are
you one of the Straw Hat's underlings?
That's right, Bro! Since he's with
Straw Hat Luffy, I expected him to be
a really strong pirate, but then...
He's so weak!
That's none of your business!
Oops!
What's he doing?!
I'll admit you've got guts to come
to get the money back all by yourself,
but I can't let you have it back.
Give it back to me!
We have to... have our ship repaired...
That money is crucial to us!
With that money...
...we can finally repair the Merry's scars!
I can't let you jerks have it!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Give me back...
Usopp!
Give me that money back!
Chopper?!
He's hurt very badly, but he'll be okay.
I can somehow manage to save him!
Okay. Just wait a bit, Usopp.
We're gonna go blow that stupid house away!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Rescuing Our Friend!
Raid on the Franky House"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!