It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
Hm?
Who's trying to defy the Franky Family?!
Give me the money back!
"Give me the money back"? Then are
you one of the Straw Hat's underlings?
That's right, Bro! Since he's with
Straw Hat Luffy, I expected him to be
a really strong pirate, but then...
He's so weak!
That's none of your business!
Oops!
I'll admit you've got guts to come
to get the money back all by yourself,
but I can't let you have it back.
Give it back to me!
We have to... have our ship repaired...
That money is crucial to us!
With that money, we can finally...
We can finally repair the Merry's scars!
I can't let you jerks have it!
"Rescuing Our Friend!
Raid on the Franky House"
What are you so worked up about?
Looks like you love your ship quite a bit.
Well, no matter what happens to your ship,
this money is already ours.
Unfortunately for you, no matter what we
steal from pirates, we won't be accused
of committing a crime.
This is dirty money that you stole
from somewhere anyway, right?
Well, let us have it.
If you like, try begging the Navy for help.
You guys are the ones who'll be captured.
Too bad for Straw Hat Luffy...
...that he has a useless underling
who can't even watch over money.
Guys, have some fun with him later.
I'm gonna take this money
and go shopping at once.
This is gonna be great!
Hold it! Special Attack! Exploding Star!
Remember this, long-nosed boy.
My name is Franky...
If you want to leave this town alive,
you shouldn't cross me.
Wh... What're you doing?! Let go of me!
Such a pathetic weapon wouldn't work on us.
See ya, Long-nose.
Thanks for the 200 million Berries.
Hold it! Give it back to me!
Give it back to me!
Give it back to me!!
Give it... back to me...
G-Give it back to me...!
Give it... back to me...!
Give it back to me!
I just have to hold out until Robin comes back.
I'll only become a burden to
them if I march in with them.
It'll be scary, too.
At any rate, I'll protect this ship and
the 100 million Berries all the way.
I'm counting on you... guys!
Stop. Stop!
If I remember right, this should be
the place Nami-san was talking about.
Look. This is the backstreet shopping district.
You go up this canal... and here!
Usopp is right here.
Okay.
So, Nami-san, where can we find these
demolition workers, the Franky Family?
Usopp!
He isn't here?
Are you sure? Didn't you just
screw up the directions?
I'm not you! Keep your mouth shut!
Usopp!
--What'd you say?!
--Ah, look at that!
Look! It's blood!
That idiot! He just walked off
without waiting for us!
Don't tell me he...
Usopp...
Hm?
"Ahhh..."
Help me!
Luffy?!
What're you doing?!
Where'd you come falling from?
Shipyard...
I was jumping around imitating this
one shipwright to look for Usopp.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Oh, that's right. We've got a problem, guys!
Usopp got abducted along with the money.
Yeah, we know.
Come on. We're on our way to their hideout.
Usopp got beaten up and had
the money stolen from him.
What?!
It's possible that he felt responsible
and went to pick a fight with
the Franky Family all by himself.
Well, then... I'm leaving now.
Seriously, what a stubborn man he is.
Even though we don't know
whether he has it or not,
they send me out this far each time.
I wish people would put themselves in my shoes.
It's Kalifa.
Well... come in.
You must be worn out, Iceberg-san.
Would you like something to drink?
Yeah...
I'll have some tea today.
I've prepared it.
Well... Just as I'd expect from you, Kalifa.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Corgy is always angry
when he leaves, isn't he?
What on earth does he come to talk about?
Yeah...
He wants something I have,
so he suggests all sorts of deals.
It must be something very precious, huh?
Well, I always tell him that I don't know
what he's talking about and refuse.
They really are a pain in the ass.
Is he breathing, Chopper?
Although he's completely
unconscious, he's still alive.
He'll be okay. I can save him.
Just wait a bit... Usopp.
We're gonna go blow that stupid house away!
Hey! Go get more food!
We've got money!
The alcohol today sure tastes good!
I've drawn graffiti on the walls of
people's houses for all these years.
Thanks! So you took my goggles back from him?
Okay, then!
I'll tell you a story about when I bravely
fought Sea Kings in the Calm Belt.
Big ones! They were...
A-And what's more...
I have 8,000 men under me!
That large amount of money... They stole it all.
Nami...
I can't face everyone.
Make sure you beat up every one of them, guys!
So that's what you wanna do?
See? You lose.
Now, go buy some food!
Make sure you buy all the food at
the store, okay?! We've got money!
Dammit. Just you wait and see.
I'll beat you later.
Huh?
What?! What happened?!
Someone's there!
Who the hell are you jerks?!
That's...
...Straw Hat Luffy!
So you came to get the
money back, huh, you fools?
See all the guys here? What do
you think the four of you can do?
But, well... you're here.
You've got a bounty on your head.
So why don't you leave
that head of yours with us?
He's the captain of that weak long-nosed guy.
He can't be that strong.
Come on, shorty.
Gum-Gum...
Hm?
What're you doing?
He's punching? At that huge steel armor
that even a battleship cannon can't shatter?
What a joke!
If you're just fooling around,
I'll go ahead and crush you!
...Cannon!
H-He punched a hole in that huge armor!
Hey!
W-Wait a sec, you guys! Let's have a talk first!
Let's have a...
Let's... Let's...
Let's fire cannonballs!
Yahoo!
Three-Sword Style...
...Raven...
...Hunt!
Th-The cannonballs are made of iron, you know!
Even a cannon, too!
Bad news! These guys are seriously bad news!
G-Get out of here!
Get out through the back door!
You started the fight. Don't act pathetic.
Party Table...
...Kick Course!
W-We can't use the back door!
Windows! Get out through the windows!
Rumble...
...Horn Point!
Roseo Colonnade!
W-W-Wait a sec, you guys!
The money, right?!
You want the money back, right?!
The 200 million Berries that
worthless guy had, right?
Unfortunately, that money is no longer here.
Our boss, Franky, took that
money and went shopping.
Since he's buying something
on the black market,
we don't know where he went.
In short, no matter how much
you go on a rampage here,
that 200 million Berries won't come ba--
I'm a goner!
Ahh! Zambai!
That's enough out of you.
It has nothing to do with money.
Yeah... It's too late.
We'll beat you up so bad that
not even your bones will remain.
Not even our bones?!
You idiot! Don't get frightened!
"Not even your bones will remain"
is what we, the Franky Family,
demolition workers and bounty hunters, say!
Show them the Franky House's specialty!
Anything Shot Cannon!
Here they come! Attack them!
D-Don't flinch! Keep firing
until we run out of cannonballs!
There are only four of them!
Hm?
What're those noises? Fireworks?
It's from the northeast! They're coming
from the direction of the Franky House!
Them again? What's the fuss about this time?
Yea... Ugh! Shh! He'll hear us!
Oh, boy, they're getting too carried away.
They really don't show any
restraint when they party, do they?
It's okay once in a while, right?
It's a wonderful day today.
Shall we go follow Franky?
Where?
Drat. Looks like they really
don't know where the money is.
Even if we strangle this Franky guy,
if he already spent the money...
What do we do now? Even if we wait for
him here, he won't be back for a while.
Hey! I finished giving him first aid!
I'd like to take him on a stretcher,
so help me here!
Staying here talking won't get us anywhere.
Let's go back to the ship for now.
We left Nami-san alone there, too, so...
We have the thing with
Robin-chan to deal with...
...and the issues with the ship, too.
Yeah.
Hey, Luffy!
About the ship...
Hm?
I've made a decision.
Let's say goodbye... to the Going Merry here.
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Hey, hey, you're taking the joke too far.
I'm not joking.
We'll say goodbye to the Merry here.
Bull! Don't be ridiculous!
Hey, Usopp...
This ship can't be fixed anymore!
She'll sink soon.
--Luffy!
--No matter what you say,
I'm never gonna give up on Merry!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Big Fight under the Moon!
The Pirate Flag Flutters with Sorrow!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!