It's all right! Now let's move forward
Well... you wanted to see me...
right, pirate lad?
These guys are really strong...
with the sun always in our hearts
I came to hear the truth!
Dammit! What's with you guys?!
Tell me the reason at least!
As power passes through our clasped hands
Last night, I saw Nico Robin with my own eyes.
We're the ones who'd like to know why.
let's grab hold of our wishes
And... she is one of you.
The culprits who attacked
Iceberg-san last night were...
That's the truth.
Was it really Robin?!
...from your gang, weren't they?!
Don't say a word.
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Your words no longer mean anything.
I called you in here...
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
...because I have a favor to ask.
Let me see Nico Robin again now!
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Iceberg was attacked?
What're you talking about?
Extra! Extra!
The culprits for Mr. Iceberg's
attack were the Straw Hat pirates!
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
Wh-What did they mean?
We, Water-Water Newspaper, will buy
any information on their sightings!
D... Don't be ridiculous! Why...
Why would we do such a thing?!
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
So you'd play innocent to the end, huh?
And if you get into a jam
But we really didn't...
The culprits...
I'll say it again. Let me see Nico Robin.
I'll always be there to protect you
When Iceberg-san came around, he told
us that he remembered the two culprits.
It's all right! Now let's move forward
That's not possible.
with the sun always in our hearts
One was a big man with a mask on.
We don't know where she is.
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
The other was a tall woman.
and gaze at the light beyond
When we asked the government,
they said that she's one of you guys...
Gunfire!
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
It came from the bedroom!
Nico Robin, the woman
with a bounty on her head!
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
Robin?!
Iceberg-san!
under the same flag-- together, we're one
Did you come to this island in order
to kill Iceberg-san from the start?
One Piece
Y-You're okay...
Or did you decide to do so after
you guys met him yesterday?
Yeah...
I bet on a silly hope that I might
be able to get closer to the truth.
I don't know what you pirates think...
Capture... all the Straw Hats!
I'll never give up on this ship!
He was shot twice from the front,
and thrice from behind.
...but now that we've come to know you're
the culprits, we won't leave you at large.
Of course!
Are you guys stupid or what?!
You probably got fooled by the shipwrights'
convincing argument, didn't you?!
I don't know what happened in that
room last night, but it sure was brutal.
So he's one of the culprits?
Hey, Luffy...
We can't forgive him!
We definitely can't forgive him!
The Luffy I know would've believed
in the strength of the Merry first
Were you able to talk to
Iceberg-san by any chance?
Oh, no...!
An extra edition! Extra! Extra!
Hey, hey, so did Iceberg die?
Yeah. He said he really saw Robin.
rather than buying those guys' sales talk!
Who the hell did it?! I'm not
gonna let him get away with it!
Can't be...! Why would Robin
do something like that?
Heaven forbid that he'd
get killed by fools like them!
Such a clear-cut answer that sounds
like one made by an old man
who understands everything...
Precisely because he's still alive,
this guy could go after his life again.
How dare you, Straw Hat Luffy?!
How can you make a decision like that,
suddenly acting all captain-like?!
I refuse to believe it!
So you did this as retaliation for my
stealing your 200 million Berries?
Do what you want with the Merry.
I misjudged you, Luffy!
So we'll take care of him right here, right now.
Wait a sec, Usopp! Luffy, too, first--
I won't forgive him.
We'll get a new ship and
move on to the seas ahead!
Stay out of this, Nami!
This is something I decided!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
Come now, don't be shy, ask me my name!
Dead or alive...
I won't change my opinion.
No matter what you say now,
with the sun always in our hearts
They don't care if you're captured alive or not.
we're gonna get a new ship!
We'll say goodbye to the Merry here!
As power passes through our clasped hands
Do you know what it means
to be on the wanted list?
Listen, Luffy! It's not like everyone
can live looking ahead like you do!
Show yourself, Straw Hat!
You pirates can't complain,
no matter who does what to you.
let's grab hold of our wishes
Well then, bye, Usopp...
"Gum-Gum Human vs. Fire-breathing Cyborg"
It's been fun.
I can't just leave our wounded friend
here and move on to the seas ahead!
In other words, the world's
laws won't protect you guys.
Don't be ridiculous! Even if she's a friend,
ships and humans are different!
That's right.
They're the same! Merry has
the strength to live left in her!
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
We are outlaws.
--Considering how you are, aren't you
excited thinking about the new ship
--Hey, that's enough, you guys!
I know that. But...
Don't lose yourself.
...don't say things like that when
you know nothing about Robin!
--while pretending to be concerned about Merry?!
--You can't have a conversation
if you're worked up like that!
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
If you waver, who can we trust?
Enough, already!
Show yourself, Straw Hat!
Luffy!
Don't think that you're the only
one who feels pain over this!
You must be here, Straw Hat Luffy!
Everyone feels the same way!
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
If so, there's no way you'd
decide to get a new ship!
Let's vacate the ship.
It's all right! Now let's move forward
What the heck? That perv called my name.
Fine! If you dislike what I decide
that much, then get off this--
We can't come back... to this ship, so...
with the sun always in our hearts
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
Didn't people call him Franky just now?
As power passes through our clasped hands
So he is...
Sanji...!
let's grab hold of our wishes
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
He is the one who beat up Usopp!
This money is already ours.
but what you cherish most will be right there
You idiot... What were you about to say?!
And if you get into a jam
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Cool down! Be careful about what you say!
I'll always be there to protect you
"Severe Shock Hits the City
of Water! Iceberg Targeted!"
It's all right! Now let's move forward
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Give it... back to me...
with the sun always in our hearts
Sorry. I just...
Give it back to me!
Who was the first to find him?
Please let us question them!
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
That's okay, Luffy. That's how
you really feel, isn't it?
He is...
Who's the culprit?!
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
and gaze at the light beyond
Are they connected with the
annihilation of Franky House?!
Luffy?
What'd you say?!
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
Please give us a statement!
Please tell us the latest developments!
Go ahead and cut off useless friends
one after another and move on.
--Hey! Bikini guy!
--Hey, Luffy!
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
Hey, did you hear about the incident
at the shipbuilding island?
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
Is it true that he died?
So let's grab hold of our wishes
If you're gonna abandon the Merry...
It must be Franky who did it!
Huh?
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
This happened because they left him at large!
under the same flag-- together, we're one
...why don't you do that to me, too?!
Well, there's also a strong chance it was
done by pirates who visit the shipyard.
but what you cherish most will be right there
I'm Luffy!
You don't need weak friends, right?
One Piece
There's no information available?
And if you get into a jam
In fact, I heard that there was an
explosion at the cape late last night.
What's going on?
Luffy... you're the man
who'll be king of the pirates.
Everyone...
Is that related to this incident?
I'll always be there to protect you
I don't know, but there are many pirates
who got beaten up by the foremen, so...
But I don't have to go that high up.
It's all right! Now let's move forward
Kalifa...
"Eternal Farewell? Nico Robin,
the Woman Who Draws Darkness"
with the sun always in our hearts
Hey, where're you going, Usopp?!
Please enter the room... quietly.
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
Where I'm going is my own business.
What...? Then...
and gaze at the light beyond
I'm...
We're here! We're here!
Grandma Kokoro! Hurry! Hurry!
Iceberg-san has...
...leaving the gang.
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
...just regained consciousness.
Don't get carried away.
Usopp!
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
Good!
Wait! It shouldn't be like this!
So let's grab hold of our wishes
That's excellent news!
Water Seven... It's been a while...
Hey! Turn around!
So this is where you guys were...
under the same flag-- together, we're one
Iceberg-san!
Grandma! Hurry! Hurry!
We went to the trouble of getting a room
at this inn and yet no one's in there.
Okay, okay.
Well... sorry for making you worry.
Luffy! I can't go along with you anymore.
Wearing a mask is prohibited today
when you get on board the sea train.
One Piece
In any case, I'm glad you're alive!
I guess you all couldn't sleep, huh?
Please focus on resting up.
Sorry to cause you trouble until the end.
Please show me your ticket and your face.
We'll take care of the stuff at the shipyard.
This is my own face! My own face!
It's true that the ship
belongs to you, the captain.
By the way, about the culprits that
broke into my room last night...
Where's Luffy?
"The Straw Hat Pirates Are the Culprits?
The Protectors of the City of Water"
Hm?
Over there.
Hey, you...
Oh! Kokoro-san! Hello!
So fight me...
Er... they're still investigating.
What's all the fuss about?
Where'd you go, Sanji?
Monkey D. Luffy!
Well, I remember it.
Yes... We're after the
Straw Hats who're the culprits
Luffy...
Hm... I kept a lookout at
the rocky cape all night,
--What?
Fight a duel with me!
Let me see Ice pops!
in Iceberg-san's attempted assassination.
I'm sure he was mistaken!
There's no way it was Robin!
thinking that Robin-chan might come back.
Iceberg's assassination? Hm?
There were two. One was
a big man with a mask on.
Why would we let you get closer
when we don't know what you'd do?!
What's the matter? Ah...
The other was...
At 10 o'clock tonight, I'll come back here.
These people...
He's right! Tie up the culprits!
...a tall woman with long, black hair.
I wonder where she went...
without saying anything to us...
N... Nooo!!
They tried to kill our town's hero!
Then, we'll fight a duel over the Merry!
Send them to the gallows!
There's no mistake about it.
Those black eyes belong to...
I'm falling! I'm falling!
I'll defeat you and take the Merry.
H-Hey! What're you saying?!
It's been nothing but trouble
since we got to this island.
I'm falling!
That's...
You bitch!
...the end of the bond
between you guys and me.
We had our money stolen, and moreover,
Hey! You were with that Straw
Hat guy earlier, weren't you?
"He regained consciousness"
look what happened with Usopp...
You must be one of them, too!
He's badly wounded.
Iceberg-san...
Is that right?!
"Luffy vs. Usopp! Collision of Two Men's Pride"
Yeah, he's right! I saw her, too!
Iceberg-san regained consciousness!
I bet he's running a fever
by now and can't even move!
All right! We've landed!
We're not gonna let you get away!
Boy, I'm exhausted.
Don't fight!
Chopper...
--Is that true?!
--All right!
Stop talking about him.
--Good!
--All right!
Hey! Stop it!
Don't "We've landed" me! I thought I'd die!
I am Usopp, leader of the great
pirates who reign over this village!
Nami!
Let go of me! I said let go
of me! What did we do?!
What else could we have done?!
It was you who said that
we couldn't use the elevator
People praise me-- and then praise
me more-- as "Captain Usopp"!
So you are... Straw Hat Luffy?
Don't play innocent! You bastards are assassins!
I think I'm gonna wander around
town looking for her today.
because we didn't want them to find us!
Even so, you didn't have to jump off!
How dare you shoot Iceberg-san?!
We won't let you get away!
We're not that shipwright with a square nose!
I wonder if we can find her.
Hey! Stop it, you guys!
We're saying we didn't do anything!
I... I'm sorry.
You're neat!
Who knows?
You went on quite the rampage
while I was gone, didn't you?
Hey, you! Don't insult me!
Well, fine. At least it did get us down.
That's right!
It's not like I have specific
places in mind to check,
First off, Robin doesn't have a reason
to go after Iceberg-san, either!
If it was okay, then don't hit me!
but in any case, it's certain that
she's somewhere in this town.
When I got back, I couldn't believe my eyes.
Just keep insisting that.
I'm a very proud man!
But... this may be kinda bad.
Well, my house is totally unrecognizable.
Let's make this inn the place to
meet up if something happens.
Because of my great pride,
people call me "Proud Usopp"!
In any case, this is it for you two.
Bad? What's bad?
I'll go look for her, too.
How dare you also treat
my underlings so badly?
Learn that harming Iceberg-san
This island's geography and the weather.
Okay. Well, then...
You guys take care, too!
Let's meet again sometime!
means that you're turning us,
Galley-La Company, into an enemy...
Luffy!
With this much wind blowing,
if the atmospheric pressure drops,
I can't take it anymore.
Nami-san!
--How come?
--Huh? How come? Man, you're antisocial...
No one can stop me this week!
This is terrible! The whole
town is talking about it!
a typhoon might come through here tonight.
That you're turning this city,
Water Seven, into an enemy.
This town is called the City of Water.
No matter what you say,
until I tear you up like rags,
Luffy! Last night, Iceberg-san
from the shipyard was...
I'm gonna be a pirate too, so we'll
meet on the high seas eventually!
In other words, it can be a weak point
that could easily lead to flood damage.
Why are you saying
groundless things like that?!
What're you talkin' about? Get on already.
my anger won't subside!
So? What about it?
Let me talk to Ice pops!
Eh?
--Hey, you!
--Hm?
Iceberg-san was shot at his home?!
Well... It bothers me a little,
so I'll check into it later.
We're friends now, aren't we?
Just give up, pirate!
What'd you do with our money?!
The 200 million Berries?!
Hey! Don't be silly!
Anyway, let's go back to the inn.
The information will spread
throughout this town immediately.
Give it back to us!
--Was he killed?!
--Well, hey!
I... I get to be captain, right?!
Huh?! 200 million Berries?!
He isn't someone who
makes enemies of people!
There's no longer a place for you to escape!
Don't be dumb! I'm the captain!
Hold on a sec. Calm down, Paulie!
We'll bring down everyone in your gang!
I've already spent it! It's completely gone!
Listen to me.
Beat him up, Galley-La Company!
Look, Iceberg-san was found covered
in blood in his room this morning.
Don't get all uppity and try to protect
the money you stole from
somewhere! You're just pirates!
He's still in a coma, so he's
unconscious right now.
--It doesn't matter.
--Hm?
So you didn't get cold feet, huh?
In any case, come to the
main office immediately!
Not true! Money does matter!
You'd better be sure you're not going
to regret this, no matter what happens.
Oh, welcome.
At any rate, I won't be
happy until I beat you up!
Yow! How's it going, Blueno?!
This is the duel you wanted.
Is it going super?!
Of course. You'd better fight seriously.
Lulu! Where's Paulie?
Hmph.
I just called him. He'll be here soon.
It's me who won't be happy, you bastard!
I'll turn the tables on you.
I see.
I think we're doing good.
What's the matter, Straw Hat?!
I've already figured out how to defeat you.
Hey! Come down here already!
Newspaper reporters are already here
and it's quite an uproar outside...
What do you mean, "I think"?!
You sure are an indecisive guy!
You've only been defending.
Don't you wanna fight back?!
Whoa! This is it! Franky is
gonna start going on a rampage!
Like I said, I don't have any reason to fight you!
...even though we're the ones who
want to know what's going on.
Give me the usual! Fill them up!
Can't we stop them?
Usopp is wounded quite badly!
Evacuate! Everyone, evacuate!
Get out of here!
You got money?
If you can't bear to watch this, go inside.
Although they tore up the whole office,
Just refill them! Cola!
We now know that pistols don't work on you.
there's no trace of money
or valuables being stolen.
To think that you run a bar
with such a stingy notion
If it wasn't for robbery, who'd have
a reason to shoot Iceberg-san?
What's he doing?
that you take money from your customers...!
Dammit. Looks like they're
all serious about this.
We've got money.
We've got a million Berries
left over from shopping.
Yeah...
Don't lump me in with your past
enemies who didn't know your skills.
At any rate, we're in big trouble.
What?!
We've got that much money from yesterday?!
The whole town is in a panic.
Luffy... We've known each other for a long time.
How shameful! How uncool!
It was a direct hit!
If something happens to him,
the Galley-La Company--
To think that I didn't spend it all yesterday...!
I know about your powers very well.
No... He got away.
Now, give it to me!
as well as Water Seven-- will be finished.
Yow! You guys! You're lucky!
Don't be surprised when you hear this, Luffy.
That was close...
All your alcohol is on me!
I have 8,000 men under me!
Drink as much as you like!
If you don't wanna die, surrender now!
Whoa! That's our Franky! You're generous!
What?! 8,000?! That many?!
He shot fire out of his mouth!
You're the man! The face of the
Water Seven underworld! Thanks!
You go inside.
What is he?!
Doctor... How is he?
You don't have any subordinates.
I know that much!
You've never seen anyone who
shoots fire out of their mouth?
Usopp Spell!
Whoa! Awesome!
Hey, there's more on the floor over there!
You've got razors stuck between all your teeth!
Hey, he might have Devil Fruit powers.
Hey, Blueno! Where's my cola?!
Hmm...
Hurry up, already!
Then, what fruit?
It hurts just to imagine that!
Looks like you're doing well, Franky.
He was shot twice from the front,
and thrice from behind.
Go inside.
Hm?
You've got cactus spines inside your fingernails!
Shoot! I can't move!
Old hag Kokoro! That was you?!
I don't know what happened in that room
last night, but it sure was brutal.
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
I thought it was a statue of a monster!
What's with him? He jumped into the water!
--Luffy!
--All right! They got him!
According to the forensics,
Is he an idiot? If he ate a
Devil Fruit, he'll drown and die!
Hey, is it okay to get a
refill for my juice, Franky?!
there's no trace of locks being
picked anywhere in the building.
Usopp!
I bet he slipped and fell.
He must have fire-breathing powers!
This is a bar. It's not a place for kids!
See?! His body is already...
The incident occurred in a
room no one could've entered.
You're doing well, right?
Special Attack... Ketchup Star!
Huh?! Okay, then. Suit yourself.
The only thing found in the room
was a commonplace mask.
What? Are you sympathizing with
your enemy? What confidence...!
Yay! Just as you'd expect from our
pride and joy, Galley-La Company! Yay!
All right! Juice!
Well, I'm doing well, but I'm
feeling gloomy. I feel terrible.
Flash Dial!
That feels great!
I'm feeling terrible this week,
thanks to that damn pirate!
Ice pops was?
Right. A guy like that should be blown away!
They said that he's unconscious right now.
What the heck?! He can swim?!
Special Attack! Egg Star!
Here's the refilled cola! Thanks for waiting!
Yeah, took you long enough!
Nooo!
Everyone thinks the world of him. Why...
Star! Star! Star!
Fuel! Fuel!
I didn't eat any Devil Fruit!
Well, well, well...
Who's that, Nami-san?
But, you know, that Straw Hat shorty
is the Franky Family's detestable enemy.
Someone who helped us yesterday.
It stinks! They're rotten!
Here it comes! Here it comes! Oh, yeah!
Dammit! You jerk! Be serious!
He's the president of the shipbuilding
company and the mayor of Water Seven.
Gum-Gum...
I was the one who was fighting him first.
Is this silly? I'm very serious, Luffy!
I've heard about your power.
Sounds like he's quite a big shot.
--What?
--This is my way of fighting!
Yeah. You couldn't come up with a
bigger incident than this in this town.
Don't you come and snatch
my prey when I'm fighting!
Hey, if you open your mouth
that big, you'll have a burn!
Strong Right!
I'll go check.
Wait, Luffy! I'm coming, too!
Super!
Just how many times do I have
to repeat myself, you bastards?!
Special Attack! Tabasco Star!
I've revived! That jerk! Next time
I see him, I'll beat him up!
Well then, let's go look for Robin-chan.
Galley-Laaa!!
It's hooot!!
Watch out when you wriggle!
Just hold on a sec. We'll deal with
you after we capture him completely.
What the...?
By the way, old hag, why are you here?
What about you?
Beneath your feet, it's already Caltrop Hell!
Well...
Aqua Laguna is coming.
I'll wait a little while and
see how things turn out.
Like I said... why in the hell
are you capturing my prey?!
Oh? Is that right? No wonder the wind is strong.
Ouch!
Usopp is in control of the fight!
Are you done getting your house ready?
Well, never mind. Seems like you
guys don't get what I'm saying.
Extra edition! Extra! Extra!
Listen, Luffy!
Well, my house is gone.
I'll defeat you without fail and take the Merry...
Water Seven's hero-- our mayor,
Iceberg-san-- fell victim to an assassin!
I've got nothing that could sink,
so I have no worries.
Paulie! Watch out!
Galley-La! Run!
...no matter what it takes!
Franky is gonna launch a crazy attack!
"Mr. Iceberg Falls Victim to Assassin"
This is a news flash about the incident!
Luffy!
Hm?
Is Iceberg-san okay?
I was going to have a drink with Iceberg,
but I heard he got shot.
Usopp...
This is terrible. How could this happen to him?
Luffy! Luffy!
Special Attack! Pepper Star!
Connecter set...
Yeah, sounds like it.
Who did this?!
They say it was the pirates' doing.
Who's the culprit?!
Owwww!
Galley-La and the townspeople
are furious right now.
The paper doesn't have any clues.
He brought down a huge crane
earlier with the same attack!
Hey, paper guy! This doesn't have
the crucial piece of information!
Pirates' doing?
What...? What was that?
Brought down a crane?
What's the deal?!
Do you seriously think that's the case?
Oh...? You guys didn't know?
A cannon?
Such a vicious attack... It must be pirates!
Run! Galley-La!
I told you. I won't use attacks
that won't work on you.
You sound like you know something.
Go! Get them, Bro!
Don't say whatever comes to mind, old hag.
Well then, I'll tell you...
I'd sure like for us to catch them!
Iceberg has been getting nagged all this
time by the World Government, right?
Well, I'm not gonna shoot a cannonball.
There were pirates who went on a
rampage at Dock #1 yesterday, too.
I'm a modified human... A cyborg!
What I'll shoot out is an air bullet.
The Mikazuki gang?!
Huh? Then, what? Are you saying
that official, Corgy, did it?
Dammit. It stinks... My mouth is burning...
But its speed exceeds the speed of sound.
It may be shocking, but I think it
might be the government's doing.
That tubby isn't an assassin type!
Air?
Lulu, what're you saying?!
And it hurts!
No... Shadowy incidents are the work of CP9.
I won't give you even the
slightest chance to attack!
I'm talking about Corgy.
It's dangerous! Run!
Special Attack! Shuriken Shooting Stars!
Each time he comes to talk to Iceberg-san,
he gets turned down and goes back.
One of the Straw Hats, you say?
Do you know about it, Blueno?
Is that true?
Just heard some rumors.
Franky must be the culprit after all.
Geez... Common folk sure do like to believe
rumors of things like nonexistent organizations.
Yes. My own investigation
led to the same culprit.
What the hell?
I don't know what it was all about,
but he must've done it out of spite.
I just had Lucci confirm it
with the government. Then...
How foolish... It does exist.
Don't complain about the government.
Coo coo! Yeah... When I
contacted the government,
But they never show themselves, since their
unit works secretly in the shadows.
If someone hears, you'll pay for it.
Coup de Vent!
they said that she's one
of the Straw Hats. Coo coo!
Is the goal of this unforgivable
culprit to gain wealth or power?!
Who is this assassin who
disappeared without a trace?!
Where's that confidence coming from?
Do you know something?
"Mr. Iceberg Falls Victim to Assassin"
Then... they, the Straw Hats, are the culprits.
Who the hell did it?! I'm not
gonna let him get away with it!
I heard about it over there.
Hey, that's just a rumor, then!
Don't mess with--
What the hell?! Did they do it to get back
at us since we wouldn't fix their ship?!
Thank you for riding the train.
It always being a rumor is the scary part.
Hard to say.
We'll be arriving at Blue Station in
the City of Water, Water Seven, soon.
But no matter the reason,
the truth is that they did it.
They eliminate people without anyone noticing.
Smoke?
If you meddle with them, you're dead meat.
We can ask them the reason
after we tie them up.
I'm using a Breath Dial.
I don't know what you have to say,
but you'll pay for this, Straw Hat!
You didn't notice the smell
because of the eggs, did you?
Thanks. The job we had
to do yesterday went well.
The smell of the gas that's
filling the area around you...!
Well done, Nico Robin...
Ow... What the hell was that?!
It felt like high-pressure winds crashed into us!
Gas?
Don't tell me...!
That was a piece of cake.
Another crane is coming down!
Sorry! Take this!
Although naturally you're now
being pursued by the whole town.
Run! It'll reach this far!
Keep your eyes peeled for
Robin-chan, Chopper. Hm?
Flame Star!
Yeah.
But that's just temporary.
Hurry up!
Yeah...
It's coming down!
What's important is... tonight.
Say, Sanji...
Yeah! Get crushed!
--Hm?
--Um...
We'll infiltrate Iceberg's
residence one more time.
What an explosion!
A shipyard like this should be... crushed!
Ah, Paulie-san!
Aqua Laguna must be pretty crazy, huh?
If worst comes to worst, it's okay
to eliminate all the evidence.
Paulie-san! Please give us
a statement on the incident!
Yeah. They say that the town gets submerged.
What were you told before you came here?!
Among the disciples of this
Tom guy who originally had it,
Shut up. Get out of my way.
There might be someone who doesn't
know such a storm surge is coming, huh?
Luffy! Usopp!
Iceberg is the only one currently alive.
What explanation did your company give you?
Please give us a statement!
Well, probably...
No matter how much he plays innocent,
For example, his ship might
get damaged quite a bit, huh?
Are you deaf? I told you to get out of my way!
in the name of CP9, we'll take
it away tonight for sure.
Hasn't there been any trouble that could have
caused someone to target Mr. Iceberg's life?!
What is he?! A cyborg? Where did
he get that kind of technology?
Well, I mean...
Bear in mind that this is a mission for justice.
I am Usopp, leader of the great
pirates who reign over this village!
Anything that comes to your mind!
Any trouble with pirates?!
--Paulie-san! Tell us...
--I said get out of my way!
--Say, Sanji--
--Chopper...
And what was that weird cannon?!
People praise me-- and then praise
me more-- as "Captain Usopp"!
You dumbasses!
Come to think of it, you said you
forgot something at the Merry, right?
Ah... but...
I was able to escape thanks to that.
Luffy! I'm right here!
What?
Nami! Run!
You said that, didn't you?
Luffy!
Yeah.
Are you okay?
Then... we can't help it.
No way I'd get brought down
by something like that!
You're neat!
Okay! Hurry, Yagara!
Following the Aqua Laguna warning
issued for the entire island,
Anyway, I don't get it.
Hey, you! Don't insult me!
Are you okay, Yagara-chan?
How come?
Let's go see Ice pops somehow!
We're friends now, aren't we?
Just wait, whatever it is I left!
all the shipbuilding factory docks
on the shipbuilding island
What?! We're going?! It's not
possible in this commotion!
Well then, please get going.
will be opened as evacuation centers.
Ow, ow, ow...
Hey, look! Straw Hat is getting away!
I see an island!
Large crowds are expected,
so please evacuate ahead of time.
It's talking about Iceberg-san.
Whoa! Incredible! What kind of island is that?!
Oh, shoot!
Hm?
We're gonna be surrounded!
All right! Go!
In addition, since Dock #1 is
currently in a dangerous state...
--Nami!
--Hm?
So it's true that he was attacked.
Merry! Full speed ahead!
Okay, I'll put the iron board on.
Full speed ahead!
Hold on tight!
Yeah. Even if we go to the shipyard,
we may not be able to see him like this.
Hey, wait!
Don't let them get away!
You guys have everything you need?
Then, let's go to pops' house.
Yes, we do. Let's evacuate to the shipyard.
They said that his private residence
is inside the main office.
Hey! There's trouble!
Daddy, hurry up!
You're too loud, Tilestone!
Hurry up!
--They got away!
--Go after them!
Well, hold on a bit. I'd better
fill the gap good with hempen.
How rude! You all be quiet!
If the inside of our house gets flooded,
everything will be ruined.
Oh, Iceberg-san! I'm really
glad that you came around!
Hey, tie that side, too!
Hey, the wind is starting to get strong!
Get ready for waves soon!
You speak each and every word too loud!
That isn't good for him, right?!
Guys! If we're taking our time,
assassin pirates will show up too this time!
Yeah! You're right! I'm sorry!
That's scary!
Oh, that's right! There's trouble!
Listen, you guys!
Where did he disappear to?!
I'm pretty sure he came this way.
Don't come inside the room.
Speak from where you are.
He should still be around!
Okay, you guys go search over there.
At Dock #1, the pirate Straw Hat,
who came yesterday,
Yeah... Because I'm weak...
Got it!
That large amount of money... They stole it all.
started a fight with Franky
and they're wrecking the shipyard!
I don't see him.
What the hell is going on?
Yeah... Maybe he still can't move...
I can't face everyone.
Why am I being chased after? I don't get it!
Straw Hat...
But it wouldn't be good if
we go closer and he finds us.
Iceberg-san!
Yeah...
We were finally about to have Merry repaired...
That bastard...! How dare he just
show up at the Dock like that...?
I can't stand this.
Chopper, are you ready?
Luffy! Usopp!
So this is the reason they've
been chasing after me!
Yep.
Assassination culprits?
This bites. I can't even go
back to the inn like this.
Please get some rest, Iceberg-san.
Ah... Who is it over there?!
Hey! I heard that a storm surge
called Aqua Laguna is approaching!!
Nami...
I'll be here by your side, so...
What are you thinking about?
This way! I found a suspicious guy here!
Yep! This town will be
submerged by midnight tonight!!
Are you sure, landlord?
Yes. Those pirates have been
staying at this inn since last night.
This shore will be totally submerged, too!!
Nothing.
That's terrible!! We shouldn't
stay around here!!
They were there until just a bit ago.
I know... that an attack like
that wouldn't take you out.
That's right! We shouldn't stay around here!!
...Pistol!
They were here?!
Yes. Since they've still got a
lot of luggage in their room,
We'd better hurry up and
evacuate to high ground!!
That's right!! Let's hurry up and evacuate!!
they might come back.
--Evacuate!! Evacuate!!
I know, Luffy...
Watch out! It's coming down!
Okay, then! You guys, stay here.
...that you fight every battle
with all your strength.
The ship is breaking down!
The rest of you, let's go
search this area together!
Evacuate!! Evacuate!!
Stop it! This fight is crazy!
Listen, make sure you leave
no stone unturned to find them!
I know every detail of your skills!
Yeah!
Kiwi... Mozu...
Luffy! Beat up that bikini bastard!
Am I dreaming?
Special Attack...!
Gum-Gum... Gatling!
Bro!
No, Bro...
Fight!
...Bursting Cactus Star!
This is, without a doubt,
the place where Franky House was.
Hey, there's no one here!
But this is...
Is this really their ship?
...terrible...
Run!
There's no mistake about it! Look!
Ouch!
Anyway, I'm gonna... beat you up!
That's the Straw Hats' pirate flag.
Triple Exploding Stars!
What the hell is going on?!
I bet they've already abandoned it.
What were those voices just now...?
Go ahead if you can!
Your attacks don't work on me!
This ship is all beat up.
Make sure you evacuate!
Evacuate, Usopp!
How was it? Did you find them?
They were saying something
about a storm surge.
No, they aren't here!
There isn't much stuff left inside the ship.
This ship definitely is abandoned.
Come to think of it... the wind is awfully strong.
Who did this while I was gone?
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
Let's go look someplace else.
Weapons Left!
I see... It must be them.
Bro?
Gum-Gum... Whip!
Hm?
How dare you, Straw Hat Luffy?!
They got away. Don't you
have to go after them?
So you did this as retaliation for my
stealing your 200 million Berries?
Who were they?
No... I ran out fuel with the
Coupe de Vent I just shot.
Gum-Gum... Bazooka!
How dare you do this to
my precious underlings?!
Look at my ducktail.
Is something happening in town?
How cold-blooded...
What the heck?! What happened?!
Yeah... It looks like a
willow swaying in the wind.
I won't forgive you.
--Did you find them?
--No.
Ah! That's...!
I have a dial here.
Big Bro Franky!
Dammit! Where are they?!
Those damn bastards got in my way.
I got... your impact!
You're back!
Who was that?!
Bro!
Once I'm done refueling,
I'll eliminate him for sure.
Oh, you guys are okay? Good.
Impact!
Hey, Luffy.
How dare you pull all this crap?
What's your goal, Straw Hat?!
Just as you'd expect from a man with
a 100 million bounty on his head...
Hm? What is it, Nami?
We had a terrible time.
Those guys are really crazy.
Do you think everyone's okay?
He sure is a man of mettle.
Craftsmen are everywhere in town.
An Impact Dial!
We want you to get revenge for us at any cost,
I think Chopper and Sanji-kun are okay,
since their faces are still unknown, but...
so we've been spying on
the Straw Hats' movements.
Seriously...
At any rate, let's hurry!
Yeah.
Galley-La... What do you want?
Franky has really done it...
Where are they?
How'd you like that?! Dammit!
What a terrible day today is!
We saw them going into an inn.
The sea train is still in service...
At any rate, we can't let them get away.
It's the foremen from Dock #1!
From there, they headed to the
shipbuilding island a bit ago.
Looks like the afternoon train has already left,
I bet they went to the place
they went yesterday, Dock #1.
Aqua Laguna is coming tonight.
but there's another one that
departs at night in this bad weather?
Except for the two sea train
departures left today,
Okay... I got it.
11 PM, leaving for Enies Lobby...
The sea train is pretty impressive.
they have no means to leave this island...
Straw Hat Luffy... I'll crush you without fail!
...since they can no longer
use the ship they came on.
Hey! Any information on the pirates?!
All right! The foremen are finally here!
We'll gather information.
No. We've got nothing.
If we capture even one of those three
whose faces are known and squeeze him,
Have every Galley-La craftsman
spread around the island.
That was close! The shipyard
almost got destroyed!
the rest of the gang will be identified.
We're gonna settle this before sunset!
Hurry up! Before the waves get high!
Good! They're the shipwrights
we met yesterday!
I wonder if Robin got on the sea train.
Grandma! Grandma!
They're on our side, right?
I am Usopp, leader of the great
pirates who reign over this village!
The wind is blowing like crazy! Hey, Grandma!
Hey, hey, guys from Galley-La!
If she did, things can't get any worse.
You shouldn't butt into our fight!
When Water Seven is
already too big to handle...
Do you wanna get hurt?
Crazy wind! Crazy wind!
It's amazing you say that.
Grandma! Grandma! It's Water Seven!
I wonder if... I did something
to upset her at the bookstore.
--Crazy wind!
--Don't romp around.
After you messed up our factory this much,
To our new ship and crewmate!
You dummy... There's no way that's the case.
Cheers!
we don't even need a reason to come stop you!
Be careful not to get too
excited and fall into the sea.
Oh, hey, excuse me.
He's right, Franky! How are
you gonna settle this?!
Have you seen a pretty woman like her?
It's a southern wind... Karock, huh?
I guess that's more like it.
Oh, that... The pretty woman who's 20
years older than in that picture, right?
It's good! Let's draw it on the sail, too!
Hold on a sec, Tilestone.
We'll talk about it later.
If I had, I would've told either the paper
company or Galley-La immediately.
Alright! All done!
Now the Going Merry pirate ship is all set!
We have more important business right now.
But to think she's an assassin...
What a surprise, huh?
The waves are becoming quite rough, too.
That must be the Galley-La
Company's main office.
Gum-Gum...
Well, it's fine if you wanna look for
the culprits, but you should evacuate soon.
Right, Straw Hat Luffy?
As it stands, the sea train service
will have to be stopped tonight.
It's connected to Dock #1.
...Bullet!
You know what I'm talking about, right?
Or you'll be swallowed by Aqua Laguna.
Look.
I'm surprised that you
could show your face again.
Chimney! Gonbe! Get ready
to go back to the island!
People who look like reporters are all over.
Well then, see ya.
What? Why? We came here because
we heard the news about pops.
Okay!
Shipwright-looking people
are gathered there, too.
Geez... Our family wasn't enough,
so you messed with Galley-La, too?
Iceberg-san must be in that building.
Things are going wrong for all of us, too...
Usopp!
I wonder if Luffy and the others are okay.
Aqua Laguna is coming.
Are you guys all going through puberty,
hurting everyone you come across?
Luffy's fine. The one I'm
worried about is Nami-san.
Are you serious about going?
Like I said, we didn't do anything!
Of course.
At any rate, the town is becoming quite empty.
I'll go ask Ice pops in person why
he said Robin was one of the culprits.
If you play innocent, then we'll
just put the screws on you.
The wind is gradually getting stronger, too.
People have started evacuating.
Attention, please.
Rope Action Half Knot!
Let me warn you.
This is the Water Seven
Weather Forecasting Center.
Just remember that we're also being
chased after by the entire island!
Dammit...
An Aqua Laguna warning has just
been issued for the entire island.
I can't breathe... I can't breathe...
Make sure you get some idea
where his room is beforehand,
Hey, Robin-chan! Where'd you go?!
Air... Drive!
Its arrival time at Water Seven is
estimated to be after midnight tonight.
and seize an opportunity to carefully sneak in.
This scent... Could it be...?
Well then, I'm off.
Game over.
Oh, yeah... It's that time of the year.
You bastards! I said don't
interfere! Don't you get it?!
Huh?
I was preoccupied with Iceberg-san's incident.
Chopper, what's the matter?!
Hey! Aqua Laguna is coming!
I'm the one who holds the grudge against him!
Hey, Chopper?!
--Hey!
--They said they couldn't find them.
Let those who didn't hear
the warning yet know!
Hey! Wait!
No more working today!
It's close!
Coo coo!
What's going on?
Aqua Laguna?
Beat them up, Galley-La Company!
Hey! I said wait! What's the matter?!
Who's that?!
You fool...!
Oh, excuse me.
Ah... He is...!
The company's strongest five are fighting!
What was that broadcast about?
She's here.
There's no way that you
could defeat me, is there?!
What? What? Why are the
shipwrights fighting against us, too?!
What was it about? Of course it's...
Hey, Chopper! Chopper!
Oh, are you a traveler?
Itching, itching...
The window got broken!
Whoa! Oops!
Well, you came here at a bad time.
What happened?!
Hm?
Hey! Wait! I don't have the
slightest reason to fight you guys!
An attack!
Aqua Laguna is a storm surge.
Straw Hat Luffy has broken into the main office!
H-Hey, are you okay?!
A storm surge, huh?
Chopper! Are you okay?!
That's right. Make sure you
evacuate to high ground.
What?! In the middle of the day?!
Are you hurt?
To think that he attacks the
main office again out of the blue!
Geez, don't be reckless!
What on earth is going on...
This town will be submerged in the sea.
He's... got Devil Fruit powers?
Where is he?!
The town will be submerged...?
Starting to run so sudden... ly...
He went to the mezzanine
stairs to the third floor!
--Where are the foremen?!
--They're stationing craftsmen all
over the island, so they're all gone!
Don't worry. It's not going
to happen right away.
I knew she'd be here.
According to the forecast, it'll be
here around midnight tonight.
Well, this happens every year. Be careful!
He's wearing a red vest and a straw hat!
I can't stand this...
--Robin!
--Robin-chan!
Hey, you bastards, are you listening?!
Okay.
Protect Iceberg-san!
Wh-Where have you been?!
We looked all over for you!
It'll be submerged in the sea?
What?! This place will sink?!
It's Straw Hat!
Everyone's worried about you!
Now, let's go back to the inn together.
I said...
Sounds like it. At any rate,
let's hurry and find Robin-chan.
Where did he go?!
Well, a lot has happened while you've
been gone. I'll explain in detail.
...he's my prey!
Yep.
Do what you want with the Merry.
Where is he? Where is he?
But this distance is annoying.
By the way, where should we look?
Hold on! I'll be right over there!
Well... where would she be likely to go?
Hm?
We'll get a new ship and
move on to the seas ahead!
No, that's okay. Stay there.
Hmm... Let's see...
We don't have time to play with you, Franky!
Idiot! Don't shoot a pistol!
We're inside, remember?
What?
Ruins, maybe?
Hey! Let me sit there, too, Luffy!
What'd you say, you wild monkey?!
I won't... return to you guys.
It's not good for Iceberg-san!
There probably aren't any here.
No! This is my special seat!
Anywhere else?
The one who's interfering here is you, Franky!
Don't know...
Oh? What's that?!
We're parting ways here... in this town...
I'm sorry about the
commotion outside the room.
Then, what does she like?
What're you making, Usopp?
--That'd be ruins!
--You keep saying that!
Whoa! Hey, you guys!
No shoes in Usopp Factory!
Well... what's going on?
Wh-What're you saying, Robin-chan?
Then do you know what else she likes?!
That's our Tilestone!
He's super strong, as always!
I was told that Straw Hat Luffy
has broken into this building.
I'm asking because I don't know!
Oh, I get it. You're thinking about the
newspaper, right? Don't worry about it!
Hey, don't get in front of me!
Why not?!
None of us believe it,
Kalifa... I have a favor to ask.
and being falsely accused of a
crime often happens to pirates!
Someday, I will go to Elbaf!
Coo coo! Coo coo!
Yeah...
Could it be that we don't know
anything about Robin-chan?
--There he is!
--Dammit!
I'm sorry for pinning an
unreasonable crime on you guys.
To the village of warriors!
All right, Usopp! Let's go there for sure!
Whoa! So many of them!
But the article is telling the truth.
You jerk...! Stop it!
He's going to Building #2!
Go around from upstairs!
Please tell us something!
Let's get this party goin'! It's the
night festival before gold-hunting!
It really was me who infiltrated
the mayor's residence last night.
--Iceberg-san!
--What the hell happened?!
What's going on?!
What?
We can't enter, huh?
No...
Straw Hat!
I carry a darkness within me
that you guys don't know about.
We'll have to see Ice pops sooner or later.
This darkness will destroy you someday.
She is...
Say, excuse me. Do you know where
the entrance to the main office is?
Well then, bye, Usopp...
Kalifa-san, didn't a pirate come here?
These guys are really strong...
The organizations Nico Robin had
something to do with up until today
Oh, it's no use. You go in through Dock #1,
It's been fun.
No, he didn't. More importantly,
chase after him more quietly.
Dammit! What's with you guys?!
Tell me the reason at least!
all got annihilated... except for her.
but only concerned parties and
certain reporters are allowed inside.
Iceberg-san still needs to rest quietly.
Hey, don't go, Chopper!
It's not just you guys. Everyone is so
worried that they can't just sit and wait.
I'm sorry.
As a matter of fact, I'm pinning this
crime on you and planning to run away.
Straw Hat... We're the ones
who'd like to know why.
Looks like the Straw Hat
hasn't reached this far yet.
Why not?! He was already
wounded so badly to start with,
I see... Thanks.
Let's stand watch around here.
His target is definitely this room!
and now he got beat up worse!
The situation will get worse.
The culprits who broke in to our main office
last night and attacked Iceberg-san...
This isn't a quarrel or a game.
What do you mean?! Why are you--
What's all this fuss about?
Lots of people are here.
So what?! I'm a doctor!
Let me at least treat him!
Why I'm doing it... It's something
you don't need to know.
Well, the bigger the audience, the better.
...were from your gang, weren't they?!
Can't be... This can't be...
Robin-chan! I don't get what you're saying!
What happened to you?!
They butted into my fight.
He lost the duel. On top of that, he gets pitied.
Robin! Let's go back together!
Imagine just how miserable
that must make him feel!
Ahh! This rhythm is...
Although I only spent a short
time with you, after today...
Well... you wanted to see me...
right, pirate lad?
Don't tell me...! Oh, no...!
Imagine how much suffering careless
kindness can cause the loser!
Why at a time like this?!
Hey, you guys! Did you just call my name?!
...I'll never see you again.
That's right. Thanks for
calling me in. That saved me.
He fought a duel knowing full well
this was how it might turn out!
Thank you for being nice to a person like me.
We didn't! Go away!
I doubt you came all the way here by
yourself to kill me in this commotion.
Where?! Where is he?!
Goodbye.
Ahh! He's over there!
I came to hear the truth!
--He's here!
--Yow! Yow!
Last night, I saw Nico Robin with my own eyes.
That was... without a doubt, Nico Robin.
Yow! Yow!
Come now, don't be shy, ask me my name!
And... she is one of you.
Is that big guy next to her
also one of the Straw Hats?
This is really tough...
We don't wanna ask! Get lost!
That's the truth.
Why did they attack me in the first place?
You're the one who attacked
Iceberg-san, aren't you?!
That's what it means to be a captain, isn't it?
Was it really Robin?!
--What?! He did it?!
--It's gotta be him!
Don't lose yourself.
Don't say a word.
It's hard to think that they
did it as payback for yesterday.
Be gone from this island!
You should be sent to the gallows, you punk!
They must really be after one of my possessions.
If you waver, who can we trust?
Your words no longer mean anything.
Geez... what noisy flies...
Wait...
Then, are those pirates
connected to the government?
Hey... wait...
I'm the No. 1 super guy!
I called you in here...
Or are they after "that" on their own?
I can't...
...because I have a favor to ask.
The face of the Water Seven underworld!
...accept this.
Let me see Nico Robin again now!
Straw Hat...
That's right! People call me... wow...
Hey...
News flash! News flash!
Wait!
Let's vacate the ship.
From what Iceberg-san said,
the culprits have been identified!
Extra! Extra!
...Franky!
The culprits for Mr. Iceberg's
attack were the Straw Hat pirates!
Stop joking!
What?! Is that true?!
Wait! Robin-chan!
Let's let the entire town know
immediately and corner the culprits!
Robin-chan!
We, Water-Water Newspaper, will buy
any information on their sightings!
Wait! Robin-chan! Robin-chan!
Don't let them leave Water Seven!
We can't come back... to this ship, so...
Capture the culprits!
Show yourself, Straw Hat!
The culprits who attacked Mr. Iceberg are...
The culprits are on this island!
Find the Straw Hats and send
them all to the gallows!
...the Straw Hat Pirates!
Robin!
Yeah!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
It's gotta be a mistake that
Robin is the assassin, right?
Show yourself, Straw Hat Luffy!
Isn't it time to settle
whether Robin is friend or foe?
Luffy, there's trouble! The whole
town is talking about this!
You bastard! How dare you hurt Iceberg-san?!
So that guy is Franky?!
Like I said, we didn't do anything!
I wonder where she went.
Hey, you, bikini guy! I won't
be happy until I beat you up!
Craftsmen are everywhere on the island.
--What's the matter?
--They say that Iceberg-san was
shot at home and is unconscious.
Hold on a sec!
Hey! Don't ignore me!
She's suddenly changed because
of the masked man she was with!
We have to find her soon.
Now that it's come to this,
we just have to ask pops in person.
I can't take it anymore.
No one can stop me now!
They say that a crazy storm is approaching, too.
Ice pops is?! I'll go check.
--I won't let you go!
--Hold it! What about our fight?!
That's right! That man is
making her do bad things!
What're we gonna do?
--I'll go, too.
--Then, Chopper and I'll go look for Robin-chan.
Prepare yourself, Straw Hat!
Maybe Robin really betrayed--
Whoa! What the hell?!
He breathed fire! That's kinda cool!
That would be fortune.
Don't interfere, Franky! I guess I've got
no choice. I'll just beat you both up!
No! I don't believe it!
I kinda have a bad feeling.
If this guy is Robin's real friend,
then that would be misfortune.
Don't tell me he's got Devil Fruit powers?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Severe Shock Hits the City
of Water! Iceberg Targeted!"
"The Straw Hat Pirates Are the Culprits?
The Protectors of the City of Water"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Eternal Farewell? Nico Robin,
the Woman Who Draws Darkness"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Gum-Gum Human vs. Fire-breathing Cyborg"
"Capture Robin!
The Determination of the Straw Hats"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!