It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
Do what you want with the Merry.
We'll get a new ship and
move on to the seas ahead!
Well then, bye, Usopp...
It's been fun.
Don't lose yourself.
If you waver, who can we trust?
Let's vacate the ship.
We can't come back... to this ship, so...
"Severe Shock Hits the City
of Water! Iceberg Targeted!"
Who was the first to find him?
Please let us question them!
Who's the culprit?!
Are they connected with the
annihilation of Franky House?!
Please give us a statement!
Please tell us the latest developments!
Hey, did you hear about the incident
at the shipbuilding island?
Is it true that he died?
It must be Franky who did it!
This happened because they left him at large!
Well, there's also a strong chance it was
done by pirates who visit the shipyard.
In fact, I heard that there was an
explosion at the cape late last night.
Is that related to this incident?
I don't know, but there are many pirates
who got beaten up by the foremen, so...
So this is where you guys were...
We went to the trouble of getting a room
at this inn and yet no one's in there.
I guess you all couldn't sleep, huh?
Where's Luffy?
Over there.
Where'd you go, Sanji?
Hm... I kept a lookout at
the rocky cape all night,
thinking that Robin-chan might come back.
I wonder where she went...
without saying anything to us...
It's been nothing but trouble
since we got to this island.
We had our money stolen, and moreover,
look what happened with Usopp...
He's badly wounded.
I bet he's running a fever
by now and can't even move!
Chopper...
Stop talking about him.
I think I'm gonna wander around
town looking for her today.
I wonder if we can find her.
Who knows?
It's not like I have specific
places in mind to check,
but in any case, it's certain that
she's somewhere in this town.
Let's make this inn the place to
meet up if something happens.
I'll go look for her, too.
Okay. Well, then...
Luffy!
Nami-san!
This is terrible! The whole
town is talking about it!
Luffy! Last night, Iceberg-san
from the shipyard was...
Iceberg-san was shot at his home?!
Hey! Don't be silly!
--Was he killed?!
--Well, hey!
He isn't someone who
makes enemies of people!
Hold on a sec. Calm down, Paulie!
Listen to me.
Look, Iceberg-san was found covered
in blood in his room this morning.
He's still in a coma, so he's
unconscious right now.
In any case, come to the
main office immediately!
Lulu! Where's Paulie?
I just called him. He'll be here soon.
I see.
Newspaper reporters are already here
and it's quite an uproar outside...
...even though we're the ones who
want to know what's going on.
Although they tore up the whole office,
there's no trace of money
or valuables being stolen.
If it wasn't for robbery, who'd have
a reason to shoot Iceberg-san?
Yeah...
At any rate, we're in big trouble.
The whole town is in a panic.
If something happens to him,
the Galley-La Company--
as well as Water Seven-- will be finished.
Doctor... How is he?
Hmm...
He was shot twice from the front,
and thrice from behind.
I don't know what happened in that room
last night, but it sure was brutal.
According to the forensics,
there's no trace of locks being
picked anywhere in the building.
The incident occurred in a
room no one could've entered.
The only thing found in the room
was a commonplace mask.
Ice pops was?
They said that he's unconscious right now.
Everyone thinks the world of him. Why...
Who's that, Nami-san?
Someone who helped us yesterday.
He's the president of the shipbuilding
company and the mayor of Water Seven.
Sounds like he's quite a big shot.
Yeah. You couldn't come up with a
bigger incident than this in this town.
I'll go check.
Wait, Luffy! I'm coming, too!
Well then, let's go look for Robin-chan.
What about you?
Well...
I'll wait a little while and
see how things turn out.
Extra edition! Extra! Extra!
Water Seven's hero-- our mayor,
Iceberg-san-- fell victim to an assassin!
"Mr. Iceberg Falls Victim to Assassin"
This is a news flash about the incident!
Is Iceberg-san okay?
This is terrible. How could this happen to him?
Who did this?!
Who's the culprit?!
The paper doesn't have any clues.
Hey, paper guy! This doesn't have
the crucial piece of information!
What's the deal?!
Such a vicious attack... It must be pirates!
I'd sure like for us to catch them!
There were pirates who went on a
rampage at Dock #1 yesterday, too.
The Mikazuki gang?!
It may be shocking, but I think it
might be the government's doing.
Lulu, what're you saying?!
I'm talking about Corgy.
Each time he comes to talk to Iceberg-san,
he gets turned down and goes back.
Franky must be the culprit after all.
I don't know what it was all about,
but he must've done it out of spite.
Don't complain about the government.
If someone hears, you'll pay for it.
Is the goal of this unforgivable
culprit to gain wealth or power?!
Who is this assassin who
disappeared without a trace?!
"Mr. Iceberg Falls Victim to Assassin"
Who the hell did it?! I'm not
gonna let him get away with it!
Thank you for riding the train.
We'll be arriving at Blue Station in
the City of Water, Water Seven, soon.
Ah, Paulie-san!
Paulie-san! Please give us
a statement on the incident!
What were you told before you came here?!
Shut up. Get out of my way.
What explanation did your company give you?
Please give us a statement!
Are you deaf? I told you to get out of my way!
Hasn't there been any trouble that could have
caused someone to target Mr. Iceberg's life?!
Anything that comes to your mind!
Any trouble with pirates?!
--Paulie-san! Tell us...
--I said get out of my way!
You dumbasses!
Luffy! I'm right here!
Okay! Hurry, Yagara!
Are you okay, Yagara-chan?
Well then, please get going.
Ow, ow, ow...
It's talking about Iceberg-san.
Hm?
So it's true that he was attacked.
Yeah. Even if we go to the shipyard,
we may not be able to see him like this.
Then, let's go to pops' house.
They said that his private residence
is inside the main office.
Yeah... Because I'm weak...
That large amount of money... They stole it all.
I can't face everyone.
We were finally about to have Merry repaired...
Nami...
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
Kiwi... Mozu...
Am I dreaming?
No, Bro...
This is, without a doubt,
the place where Franky House was.
But this is...
...terrible...
What the hell is going on?!
Who did this while I was gone?
I see... It must be them.
How dare you, Straw Hat Luffy?!
So you did this as retaliation for my
stealing your 200 million Berries?
How dare you do this to
my precious underlings?!
How cold-blooded...
I won't forgive you.
Big Bro Franky!
You're back!
Bro!
Oh, you guys are okay? Good.
We had a terrible time.
Those guys are really crazy.
We want you to get revenge for us at any cost,
so we've been spying on
the Straw Hats' movements.
Where are they?
We saw them going into an inn.
From there, they headed to the
shipbuilding island a bit ago.
I bet they went to the place
they went yesterday, Dock #1.
Okay... I got it.
Straw Hat Luffy... I'll crush you without fail!
Grandma! Grandma!
The wind is blowing like crazy! Hey, Grandma!
Crazy wind! Crazy wind!
--Crazy wind!
--Don't romp around.
It's a southern wind... Karock, huh?
The waves are becoming quite rough, too.
As it stands, the sea train service
will have to be stopped tonight.
Chimney! Gonbe! Get ready
to go back to the island!
Okay!
Aqua Laguna is coming.
Attention, please.
This is the Water Seven
Weather Forecasting Center.
An Aqua Laguna warning has just
been issued for the entire island.
Its arrival time at Water Seven is
estimated to be after midnight tonight.
Oh, yeah... It's that time of the year.
I was preoccupied with Iceberg-san's incident.
Hey! Aqua Laguna is coming!
Let those who didn't hear
the warning yet know!
No more working today!
What's going on?
Aqua Laguna?
Oh, excuse me.
What was that broadcast about?
What was it about? Of course it's...
Oh, are you a traveler?
Well, you came here at a bad time.
Hm?
Aqua Laguna is a storm surge.
A storm surge, huh?
That's right. Make sure you
evacuate to high ground.
This town will be submerged in the sea.
The town will be submerged...?
Don't worry. It's not going
to happen right away.
According to the forecast, it'll be
here around midnight tonight.
Well, this happens every year. Be careful!
Okay.
It'll be submerged in the sea?
What?! This place will sink?!
Sounds like it. At any rate,
let's hurry and find Robin-chan.
Yep.
By the way, where should we look?
Well... where would she be likely to go?
Hmm... Let's see...
Ruins, maybe?
There probably aren't any here.
Anywhere else?
Don't know...
Then, what does she like?
--That'd be ruins!
--You keep saying that!
Then do you know what else she likes?!
I'm asking because I don't know!
Hey, don't get in front of me!
Why not?!
Could it be that we don't know
anything about Robin-chan?
Please tell us something!
--Iceberg-san!
--What the hell happened?!
What's going on?!
We can't enter, huh?
We'll have to see Ice pops sooner or later.
Say, excuse me. Do you know where
the entrance to the main office is?
Oh, it's no use. You go in through Dock #1,
but only concerned parties and
certain reporters are allowed inside.
It's not just you guys. Everyone is so
worried that they can't just sit and wait.
I see... Thanks.
What's all this fuss about?
Lots of people are here.
Well, the bigger the audience, the better.
Ahh! This rhythm is...
Don't tell me...! Oh, no...!
Why at a time like this?!
Hey, you guys! Did you just call my name?!
We didn't! Go away!
Where?! Where is he?!
Ahh! He's over there!
--He's here!
--Yow! Yow!
Yow! Yow!
Come now, don't be shy, ask me my name!
We don't wanna ask! Get lost!
You're the one who attacked
Iceberg-san, aren't you?!
--What?! He did it?!
--It's gotta be him!
Be gone from this island!
You should be sent to the gallows, you punk!
Geez... what noisy flies...
I'm the No. 1 super guy!
The face of the Water Seven underworld!
That's right! People call me... wow...
...Franky!
Show yourself, Straw Hat!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Show yourself, Straw Hat Luffy!
So that guy is Franky?!
Hey, you, bikini guy! I won't
be happy until I beat you up!
I can't take it anymore.
No one can stop me now!
Prepare yourself, Straw Hat!
Whoa! What the hell?!
He breathed fire! That's kinda cool!
Don't tell me he's got Devil Fruit powers?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Gum-Gum Human vs. Fire-breathing Cyborg"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!