It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
He was shot twice from the front,
and thrice from behind.
I don't know what happened in that
room last night, but it sure was brutal.
An extra edition! Extra! Extra!
Who the hell did it?! I'm not
gonna let him get away with it!
How dare you, Straw Hat Luffy?!
So you did this as retaliation for my
stealing your 200 million Berries?
I won't forgive him.
Come now, don't be shy, ask me my name!
Show yourself, Straw Hat!
"Gum-Gum Human vs. Fire-breathing Cyborg"
You must be here, Straw Hat Luffy!
What the heck? That perv called my name.
Didn't people call him Franky just now?
So he is...
He is the one who beat up Usopp!
This money is already ours.
Give it... back to me...
Give it back to me!
He is...
Luffy?
--Hey! Bikini guy!
--Hey, Luffy!
Huh?
I'm Luffy!
There's no information available?
What's going on?
Everyone...
Kalifa...
Please enter the room... quietly.
What...? Then...
Iceberg-san has...
...just regained consciousness.
Good!
That's excellent news!
Iceberg-san!
Well... sorry for making you worry.
In any case, I'm glad you're alive!
Please focus on resting up.
We'll take care of the stuff at the shipyard.
By the way, about the culprits that
broke into my room last night...
Er... they're still investigating.
Well, I remember it.
--What?
There were two. One was
a big man with a mask on.
The other was...
...a tall woman with long, black hair.
There's no mistake about it.
Those black eyes belong to...
"He regained consciousness"
Iceberg-san...
Iceberg-san regained consciousness!
--Is that true?!
--All right!
--Good!
So you are... Straw Hat Luffy?
You went on quite the rampage
while I was gone, didn't you?
When I got back, I couldn't believe my eyes.
Well, my house is totally unrecognizable.
How dare you also treat
my underlings so badly?
I can't take it anymore.
No one can stop me this week!
No matter what you say,
until I tear you up like rags,
my anger won't subside!
--Hey, you!
--Hm?
What'd you do with our money?!
The 200 million Berries?!
Give it back to us!
Huh?! 200 million Berries?!
I've already spent it! It's completely gone!
Don't get all uppity and try to protect
the money you stole from
somewhere! You're just pirates!
--It doesn't matter.
--Hm?
Not true! Money does matter!
At any rate, I won't be
happy until I beat you up!
Hmph.
It's me who won't be happy, you bastard!
Hey! Come down here already!
Whoa! This is it! Franky is
gonna start going on a rampage!
Evacuate! Everyone, evacuate!
Get out of here!
What's he doing?
He shot fire out of his mouth!
What is he?!
You've never seen anyone who
shoots fire out of their mouth?
Hey, he might have Devil Fruit powers.
Then, what fruit?
What's with him? He jumped into the water!
Is he an idiot? If he ate a
Devil Fruit, he'll drown and die!
I bet he slipped and fell.
He must have fire-breathing powers!
What the heck?! He can swim?!
Nooo!
I didn't eat any Devil Fruit!
Gum-Gum...
I've heard about your power.
Strong Right!
What the...?
Luffy!
Luffy! Luffy!
What...? What was that?
Oh...? You guys didn't know?
Well then, I'll tell you...
I'm a modified human... A cyborg!
One of the Straw Hats, you say?
Is that true?
Yes. My own investigation
led to the same culprit.
I just had Lucci confirm it
with the government. Then...
Coo coo! Yeah... When I
contacted the government,
they said that she's one
of the Straw Hats. Coo coo!
Then... they, the Straw Hats, are the culprits.
What the hell?! Did they do it to get back
at us since we wouldn't fix their ship?!
Hard to say.
But no matter the reason,
the truth is that they did it.
We can ask them the reason
after we tie them up.
I don't know what you have to say,
but you'll pay for this, Straw Hat!
Keep your eyes peeled for
Robin-chan, Chopper. Hm?
Yeah...
Say, Sanji...
--Hm?
--Um...
Aqua Laguna must be pretty crazy, huh?
Yeah. They say that the town gets submerged.
There might be someone who doesn't
know such a storm surge is coming, huh?
Well, probably...
For example, his ship might
get damaged quite a bit, huh?
Well, I mean...
--Say, Sanji--
--Chopper...
Come to think of it, you said you
forgot something at the Merry, right?
What?
You said that, didn't you?
Yeah.
Then... we can't help it.
Just wait, whatever it is I left!
Hey! There's trouble!
You're too loud, Tilestone!
How rude! You all be quiet!
Oh, Iceberg-san! I'm really
glad that you came around!
You speak each and every word too loud!
That isn't good for him, right?!
Yeah! You're right! I'm sorry!
Oh, that's right! There's trouble!
Listen, you guys!
Don't come inside the room.
Speak from where you are.
At Dock #1, the pirate Straw Hat,
who came yesterday,
started a fight with Franky
and they're wrecking the shipyard!
Straw Hat...
Iceberg-san!
That bastard...! How dare he just
show up at the Dock like that...?
Please get some rest, Iceberg-san.
I'll be here by your side, so...
...Pistol!
Watch out! It's coming down!
The ship is breaking down!
Stop it! This fight is crazy!
Luffy! Beat up that bikini bastard!
Bro!
Fight!
Anyway, I'm gonna... beat you up!
Go ahead if you can!
Your attacks don't work on me!
Weapons Left!
Gum-Gum... Whip!
What the heck?! What happened?!
Ah! That's...!
Who was that?!
How dare you pull all this crap?
What's your goal, Straw Hat?!
Galley-La... What do you want?
It's the foremen from Dock #1!
All right! The foremen are finally here!
That was close! The shipyard
almost got destroyed!
Good! They're the shipwrights
we met yesterday!
They're on our side, right?
Hey, hey, guys from Galley-La!
You shouldn't butt into our fight!
Do you wanna get hurt?
It's amazing you say that.
After you messed up our factory this much,
we don't even need a reason to come stop you!
He's right, Franky! How are
you gonna settle this?!
Hold on a sec, Tilestone.
We'll talk about it later.
We have more important business right now.
Right, Straw Hat Luffy?
You know what I'm talking about, right?
I'm surprised that you
could show your face again.
What? Why? We came here because
we heard the news about pops.
Geez... Our family wasn't enough,
so you messed with Galley-La, too?
Are you guys all going through puberty,
hurting everyone you come across?
Like I said, we didn't do anything!
If you play innocent, then we'll
just put the screws on you.
Rope Action Half Knot!
I can't breathe... I can't breathe...
Air... Drive!
You bastards! I said don't
interfere! Don't you get it?!
I'm the one who holds the grudge against him!
Coo coo!
Beat them up, Galley-La Company!
The company's strongest five are fighting!
What? What? Why are the
shipwrights fighting against us, too?!
Itching, itching...
Hey! Wait! I don't have the
slightest reason to fight you guys!
He's... got Devil Fruit powers?
Hey, you bastards, are you listening?!
I said...
...he's my prey!
Hm?
We don't have time to play with you, Franky!
What'd you say, you wild monkey?!
The one who's interfering here is you, Franky!
That's our Tilestone!
He's super strong, as always!
Coo coo! Coo coo!
You jerk...! Stop it!
These guys are really strong...
Dammit! What's with you guys?!
Tell me the reason at least!
Straw Hat... We're the ones
who'd like to know why.
The culprits who broke in to our main office
last night and attacked Iceberg-san...
...were from your gang, weren't they?!
Can't be... This can't be...
They butted into my fight.
That was... without a doubt, Nico Robin.
Is that big guy next to her
also one of the Straw Hats?
Why did they attack me in the first place?
It's hard to think that they
did it as payback for yesterday.
They must really be after one of my possessions.
Then, are those pirates
connected to the government?
Or are they after "that" on their own?
Straw Hat...
News flash! News flash!
From what Iceberg-san said,
the culprits have been identified!
What?! Is that true?!
Let's let the entire town know
immediately and corner the culprits!
Don't let them leave Water Seven!
Capture the culprits!
The culprits who attacked Mr. Iceberg are...
...the Straw Hat Pirates!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
You bastard! How dare you hurt Iceberg-san?!
Like I said, we didn't do anything!
Hey! Don't ignore me!
Now that it's come to this,
we just have to ask pops in person.
--I won't let you go!
--Hold it! What about our fight?!
Don't interfere, Franky! I guess I've got
no choice. I'll just beat you both up!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Straw Hat Pirates Are the Culprits?
The Protectors of the City of Water"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!