These are the fake blueprints
that you passed off on us earlier.
Protect Iceberg-san!
This scent... Could it be...?
Isn't it about time for us to settle this matter...
You're no match for our martial arts skills.
Yeah!
...as to whether that woman is... foe or friend?
When I look at it carefully,
there're signatures by the architects.
Hey, Chopper, what's the matter?!
You're acting like I'm a stranger.
Please leave it to me.
Now, hand it over already...
"Tom," "Iceberg," and "Cutty Flam."
By the way, why did you put up Nico
Robin's wanted poster in your room?
...or else it'll get dirty with your blood.
Hey, Chopper?!
Well... You have my gratitude.
At the end, there's a
company name: "Tom's Workers."
Are you curious?
Oops!
There're tons of people there.
Dammit...
I thought... I could defeat you.
I remember hearing this
name Cutty Flam before.
If we carelessly plunge in,
we'll be in big trouble.
A little.
Hey, Chopper! Are you okay?!
Tom's other disciple Cutty Flam is still alive...
It's better if you don't know.
Look who's talking!
Hey, are you okay?!
She is... a devil.
This is where we find out what we're made of.
Are you hurt?
Yeah...!
...and lives in this town...
Tonight, we'll infiltrate Iceberg's
residence one more time.
To tell you the truth...
What on earth is going on...
...Iceberg-san told me to run right away.
Among the disciples of this
Tom guy who originally had it,
Starting to run so sudden... ly...
An explosion!
He told me to drop it quickly and run...
...after changing his name to Franky!
Iceberg is the only one currently alive.
I knew she'd be here.
Things have gotten kinda crazy!
No matter how much he plays innocent,
Now, you go ahead! Ahead of us!
Cut down the door and make a dash!
...since...
--Robin!
--Robin-chan!
in the name of CP9, we'll take
it away tonight for sure.
Hm? Where's Luffy?
...it's a complete fake.
Whaaat?!
I won't... return to you guys.
--Go ahead!
--What the hell?! Don't order me around!
Give it to us...
What?
Bear in mind that this is a mission for justice.
...and... we'd like you to die.
We're parting ways here... in this town...
This is no longer something as
simple as an assassination, is it?
If something is to happen,
it'll be tonight. Are we going?
I got stuck! Dammit! I got stuck again!
I carry a darkness within me
that you guys don't know about.
We are.
Where's Robin?!
What's our goal?
We're a group that carries out justice.
We'll capture Robin.
--Why does this always happen?!
--Straw Hat...!
--Luffy!
This darkness will destroy you someday.
Tempest Kick.
We are Cipher Pol No. 9,
an undercover intelligence agency.
Otherwise, we won't know anything.
As a matter of fact, I'm pinning this
crime on you and planning to run away.
True. Thinking about it is a waste of time.
Robin! I've finally found you!
I see. So thanks to Luffy,
this is our chance to infiltrate, huh?
His kicks cut the wall!
If we wanna know the truth,
that's the only way.
The situation will get worse.
Hey, Luffy! Where the hell have you been?!
Robin-chan! I don't get what you're saying!
What happened to you?!
Are you guys ready?!
Robin! I'm glad that I could see you again!
Okay, I'll do my best, too!
Wh-What the hell are these?
Robin! Let's go back together!
Well then, let's go...
Hold on a sec... What's going on here?
We've got an emergency situation.
...to Galley-La Company!
What part of this is light?!
We don't have time for you.
Although I only spent a short
time with you, after today...
--I can't move!
--Hey, restrain that guy, too.
Well, well, well...
I'm stuck and can't move!
...I'll never see you again.
I have to hurry...
Thank you for being nice to a person like me.
I-Iceberg-san...
Just wait... Robin!
Everyone, be on your guard!
Yeah!
Wh-What the hell...
Goodbye.
If we allow those pirates to infiltrate
with so many of us on guard,
Go home!
it'll be an embarrassment
to Galley-La! Don't let them in!
...is going on?!
I've got nothing I could give you people!
Protect Iceberg-san!
Wait...
If you don't, that puts us in quite a bind.
Hey... wait...
Don't let the assassins get away with this!
What about the back door?
Back door? We're surrounding
the entire main office building!
I can't...
Paulie... Why... didn't you run?
What should I tell you first...
...accept this.
There's no blind spot!
Bring it on! We'll take care
of all the Straw Hat Pirates!
Wait!
...when you're about to die?
Yeah!
Dammit! Where'd they go?!
What's going on?
Stop joking!
You disappointed me.
One person, and one animal with
two people. That's all we've confirmed.
How is it, Chopper? Does it look
like something is happening?
This looks... as if...
Wait! Robin-chan!
Lucci!
For now, nothing.
...they're the culprits who tried to kill you!
It's your own fault.
Shall we go guard the bedroom?
Robin!
But...
You should've given it to the
Government when they asked nicely.
But our foremen are there.
...they're all carrying weapons,
and they look strong.
There's no such thing as too
many guards. Let's go back them up.
Kaku!
I wouldn't be surprised.
The shipwrights here beat even pirates.
If possible, I wanted to make this town
part of my memory without hurting you.
Why are you guys dressed like that?!
We should be careful and take
action when the time is right.
Kalifa...
Yeah, if we carelessly plunge in,
we'll be in big trouble.
Hey! Kalifa...! Blueno...! Kaku...! Lucci...!
I lost sight of her.
So you also inherited your
master's obstinacy, huh?
Yeah.
Blueno, from the bar...
Stop joking, you bastards!
--Chopper...
--Hm?
You guys... work for... the Government?
Look who's talking! He jumped in
without any plan this afternoon.
You go join Luffy and the others and tell
them everything that just happened...
That's right. Going undercover
was a pretty easy mission for us.
It's all right! Now let's move forward
Chopper, we don't know what'll happen.
Don't miss even the slightest movement.
...without leaving a single word out.
with the sun always in our hearts
In any case, your prudence
leaves me at a loss for words.
--What're you gonna do?
--We'll part ways here for a bit.
As power passes through our clasped hands
What the hell is going on?!
Yeah.
If you see any movement,
let us know immediately.
Well, don't worry. I won't do anything reckless.
Now, Iceberg-san...
let's grab hold of our wishes
Someone! Third floor!
Yep. Got it.
Where're the blueprints of
the ancient weapon Pluton?
It's gonna be a long night,
but don't let your guard down.
Come to the front of the
president's room and the bedroom!
The guards were annihilated!
Someone! Come upstairs!
If we miss our chance tonight,
Please tell us, before many people get hurt.
It's all right! Now let's move forward
we'll have to say goodbye
without knowing what happened.
What are you saying?!
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Think that we won't have a way
to go after Robin anymore.
--Tilestone-san!
--Kaku and Lucci should be there!
with the sun always in our hearts
But they're...
As power passes through our clasped hands
This is where we find out what we're made of.
What?!
Yeah... We'll definitely capture Robin.
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
let's grab hold of our wishes
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
It's all right! Now let's move forward
Kaku! Lucci!
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
with the sun always in our hearts
Good grief, there's no
end to this. No word yet?
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It's all right! Now let's move forward
As power passes through our clasped hands
You bastard!
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
let's grab hold of our wishes
with the sun always in our hearts
How dare you...?!
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
As power passes through our clasped hands
What a noisy man.
but what you cherish most will be right there
Iceberg-san had better be okay!
let's grab hold of our wishes
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
And if you get into a jam
Check it yourself.
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Iron Body.
I'll always be there to protect you
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It's all right! Now let's move forward
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
with the sun always in our hearts
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
but what you cherish most will be right there
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
and gaze at the light beyond
His giant hammer was...!
And if you get into a jam
N... No way...!
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
I'll always be there to protect you
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
You son of a...
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Let go, you bastard!
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
It's all right! Now let's move forward
Is that Herculean strength of yours your pride?
So let's grab hold of our wishes
I can't move my arm!
There's no way my power can be beat...
with the sun always in our hearts
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
under the same flag-- together, we're one
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
but what you cherish most will be right there
and gaze at the light beyond
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
And if you get into a jam
One Piece
but what you cherish most will be right there
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
I'll always be there to protect you
And if you get into a jam
It's all right! Now let's move forward
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
"Come Back, Robin! Showdown with CP9!"
So let's grab hold of our wishes
I'll always be there to protect you
with the sun always in our hearts
under the same flag-- together, we're one
It's all right! Now let's move forward
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
As power passes through our clasped hands
and gaze at the light beyond
with the sun always in our hearts
let's grab hold of our wishes
One Piece
Oh, yeah!
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
They're some of the shipwrights
who were with you! Right?!
and gaze at the light beyond
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
Come to think of it, I know
that square long-nosed guy.
"Capture Robin!
The Determination of the Straw Hats"
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
So let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Could this mean... that the
assassination was an inside job?!
under the same flag-- together, we're one
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
What? What do you mean?!
So let's grab hold of our wishes
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
One Piece
Paulie, to tell you the truth,
we're Government intelligence agents.
under the same flag-- together, we're one
--Hold it!
--Hold it right there!
Don't let them get away!
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
One Piece
Well, you'd forgive us if we apologized, right?
What's wrong with you?!
"Cannon Fire Is the Signal!
CP9 Goes into Action"
We were fellow shipwrights who worked
together building ships every day.
It was going to happen eventually!
With this many people, it'd be
strange if they didn't find us!
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
You can't get away from us anymore!
"Secret Bond! Iceberg and Franky"
If you can't believe me because this is too sudden,
shall I step on Iceberg's face or something?
This way!
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
This way!
Stop messing around! That's enough...
Kalifa...
And if you get into a jam
Yes, Iceberg-san.
After all, the bull-masked man's voice I
heard earlier is the same voice as yours!
H-Huh?
I'll always be there to protect you
Sorry, but could you step outside for a while?
Where'd they go?
Look in every nook and cranny!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
I'd better hurry up. The waves
and wind are getting rough.
What about the alleys?!
Okay.
Dammit, you bastard! You can talk just fine!
Also...
Couldn't they have climbed
up on some rooftop?!
with the sun always in our hearts
...please send Paulie in here.
Dammit! They shook us off?!
But they definitely ran in this direction!
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
Yes, sir.
Shall we check over there?!
How dare you mock us?!
and gaze at the light beyond
Then, we'll search inside the buildings!
Don't, Paulie!
All right, then! Let's split
into two groups and search!
Pipe Hitch Knives!
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
Yeah!
What's he doing?!
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
Is it okay now?
Not yet.
So let's grab hold of our wishes
--Paulie...
--Hm?
Finger Pistol!
G-Give it back to me!
Where did you lose them?!
Iceberg-san says he has something
important to discuss with you.
under the same flag-- together, we're one
We have to... have our ship repaired...
A bit longer.
With me?
Yes, just you.
One Piece
I'll be in the secretary's office,
so if anything happens, just call me.
You still haven't learned your lesson, Paulie?
That money is crucial to us!
Yeah...
With that money...
Taking the trouble to have a
talk alone at a time like this...
"CP9 Takes Off Their Masks!
Their Shocking True Faces"
...we can finally repair the Merry's scars!
What on earth could it be about?
Beats me.
I can't let you jerks have it!
A will?!
Ah...
Hey! Rope guy!
She said it was something important.
Get in there and talk to him already.
Come to think of it, he said
that 200 million Berries
Y-Yeah...
Why...?
was going to be used for
the repair of their ship.
Shall we stay a little ways away from the door?
Please...
You guys...
Come back some other time!
I'm evacuating now. Stop pestering me!
It appears that he doesn't know
Aqua Laguna is coming tonight.
Yeah.
His giant hammer was...!
Hmph! What a waste of effort.
Please... I've got money.
N... No way...!
I wonder what he needs to talk to Paulie about!
You son of a...
As much lumber, tar, and rope
as this amount will buy...
Let go, you bastard!
Okay! If I keep it airtight like this
It's Iceberg-san we're talking about.
It must be very important.
Stop this pointless resistance.
Is that Herculean strength of yours your pride?
and reinforce the ship with lumber,
it'll probably do fine.
Also, some nails, latches, and tinplates...
We've mastered techniques beyond
the limits of human abilities.
More importantly, our current
problem is those pirates.
I can't move my arm!
There's no way my power can be beat...
That's not necessary.
I'm closing the shop.
Yeah.
After years of training, these techniques,
According to Kalifa's investigation,
there're seven of them. Coo coo!
Ah... I'm sorry, but...
Wh... Who's there?
called the "Six Powers," allow human
bodies to be a match for weapons.
"Who's there"?
The captain, Straw Hat Luffy.
Pirate hunter Zoro and Nico Robin...
Once one masters them, he alone
is as strong as 100 people together.
Hey, hey... You've already
forgotten me... long-nosed lad?
Tsk... Okay, then.
In addition, the young woman who
came to Dock #1 this afternoon
But you can't buy that much
with this little money.
Th-That voice... That guy's...
and the round long-nosed guy.
Th-Then, to make up for the rest,
I'd like to exchange my tools.
Coo coo! Don't get carried away with gambling.
Wh-Wh-What'd you come
here for, you bastard?!
Yeah. There're two others besides those.
That's everyone. Coo coo!
Now, now, don't lose your cool like that.
You dummy! I was lucky today.
That's why I'm treating you guys!
Hey, hey, don't be ridiculous! Stop it!
Three of the foremen have been...!
Fighting in a place like this
won't get us anywhere.
I only sell. To think you're tryin' to barter...
What are you, a bumpkin?
Their purpose is the least of our problems.
Blueno! Bring us more alcohol!
When they make their entry here,
that will be the end of them.
This area will soon sink due to a storm surge.
Okay!
We'll bring them all down together. Coo coo!
I guess we'll make this ship that you
love so much our hostage, too, huh?
Get some reinforcements from downstairs!
Shave!
Yeah!
Wh-What're you talking about?
Geez... You win.
Kalifa! You're dressed like that again?!
Well... I have some business with Straw Hat...
Okay... understood.
--We found them!
--It's Roronoa Zoro!
They showed up at last!
This could be very risky.
...so I came here to kidnap you.
Stop it, Paulie. Just don't look at her. Right?
Don't let them get away!
I thought about it hard, but you're
the only one I can ask this.
I saw that woman this afternoon, too!
H-Hey! Are you okay carrying that
stuff when you're injured that badly?
After them!
Hey! Why isn't Luffy here?!
Will you do it for me?
How should I know?! I wanna ask that question!
Surely you have friends, right?! Hey!
You're acting like I'm a stranger.
Please leave it to me.
What do we do?!
Why are you guys...?
See, what did I tell you?
Now that it's come to this, it's like
we've been caught in the act anyway.
You have my gratitude.
Well then, I'll get on it immediately.
If we go on the offensive,
there's a way to get in.
Well, never mind.
Yeah.
What?! Hey, Zoro! What're you gonna do?!
Don't worry. I used the back of my swords.
Either way, you're gonna be killed.
Running around the building
won't get us anywhere.
Coo coo... Are you guys done talking?
Why'd you have to knock
down all the shipwrights?!
This is sad, but my friend...
We'll openly plunge in from
the front and look for Robin.
Wow, Zoro is strong!
Yeah.
Oh, well... Let's go already!
Lucci! You...!
Something came up. Sorry, but I
have to leave for a bit. Is it okay?
What?!
Stop it! You jerk!
Hey, hold on a sec, lad!
But they're shipwrights!
They're not our enemy, you know!
Zoro! This way!
Yeah!
No, I said, this way!
That's fine. The four of us
will be more than enough.
Don't worry. I'll use the back of my swords!
I'm okay. This is nothing.
How could you go in the wrong direction
when we're leading the way for you?!
--Hey!
--What is it? Are you gonna...
I see.
A miracle?!
Out of our way!
Oh, that way.
No...
Watch over Iceberg-san.
Nami! Zoro has disappeared!
Here. Take these. You're hungry, right?
This is a miracle!
Gum-Gum...
He got lost again?!
But you're inflicting fatal wounds on them!
--Iron Body.
--...Gatling!
Thank you.
Sure... Be careful going back.
Listen, Paulie.
Right underneath the desk
in the president's office...
If you lift up the carpet, you'll find...
Be careful going back!
...a safe buried there.
See?! My head came out...
since it's made of rubber.
What? It's not working at all!
This must be it.
Okay, good job! Get every body
part out by doing what you just did!
Yep! No problem!
I'll give you the combination, so listen carefully.
Well... I'm shocked.
First, turn it right to 6...
How annoying... Shave!
To be honest, I never thought
I'd see you here... Nico Robin.
These're good.
He disappeared!
These're really good.
What a considerate pops he was.
Have we met before?
No.
Click.
We met for the first time last night.
Finger Pistol!
Are you ready?
But I've wanted to see you all this time.
Yeah, we're ready.
Then I'll cause a disturbance.
The other four of you, please carry out
your own mission after the signal.
I even put your wanted poster up
in my room to ensure I never forgot.
All right! I'm out... since I'm a rubber man!
The waves are getting quite high.
Luffy!
Understood. In the name of CP9...
Good job! Okay! Take off my cuffs!
Shall I give you my autograph or something?
Okay!
Ready? Nico Robin?
That would be... nice!
Yes... anytime.
Just wait and see... damn bull and skull...!
Don't worry. It'll be okay.
So you wanted to kill me?
That's right.
If you had a flesh-and-blood body, you would've
gotten a hole in your neck and died instantly...
Before you destroy the world!
An explosion!
We were undercover for five years.
Why do you go searching for the Poneglyphs?!
...rubber man.
You're a ship... that flew in the sky!
What was that explosion?!
Please don't worry. We didn't
cut corners with our work.
Since ancient times,
the Government has declared
globally that it's a serious crime
Bring water, now!
Don't worry!
Take the injured someplace safe!
to seek and decipher the Poneglyphs.
I do understand how dispirited you are.
Hurry! Put out the fire!
I'm sure you know that much.
However, since we can't spend
any more time on this matter,
W-Was it cannon fire?
You too know of the
existence of the Poneglyphs.
No, it didn't fly in!
Just knowing about it wouldn't be a crime.
It was set up to explode!
we're going to try our best to achieve our goal.
Put out the fire! Hurry up and put out the fire!
What're you doing, Straw Hat?
What's the matter, all of a sudden?
But the only one in the whole world
who can decipher those texts...
Someone! Give me a hand!
You're planning to kill him, aren't you?!
If you're thinking of putting up an
unwise resistance, I suggest you don't.
...is you.
What a showy signal...
I thought you were all shipwright
friends who worked together!
That's exactly why the Government
put a bounty on your head,
Let's go!
You know the name "Cipher Pol," don't you?
It's the Government's
supreme intelligence agency,
Up until earlier, yes.
But that's no longer the case.
even though you were only eight years old.
It's because you're the only one in the world
The explosion happened in the
north corner of the first floor!
with eight bases around the world,
called CP1 through CP8 by people.
Then you guys really are traitors?!
who can restore the ancient weapon!
Is everyone okay?!
What's wrong, Franky?
At least half of you stay at your post!
We still haven't seen the enemy!
Fine, then!
When the Government orders it, they dig
up any kind of information in any place.
At any rate, I promised him
I see... So you even know about the weapon...
To prepare for an attack,
strengthen the defenses!
that we'd beat the crap out of those
who're trying to kill Ice pops together!
I know about them...
Don't let them come in the building!
...but only up to CP8.
Right...
All things considered...
However, we are CP9, the 9th Cipher Pol,
a supposedly non-existent unit.
...I never thought CP9 was an
organization that really existed.
Bro?
Why are you siding with Paulie?
Are you okay, Iceberg-san?!
Yeah... I was surprised.
If it does, it means that you've
already left the Straw Hat Pirates
I'm getting ticked off!
Because I have some business
with you people, too!
Maybe it's about time to
go on another rampage!
I saw someone!
Since we possess a certain privilege,
we can't reveal ourselves to the public.
and have been helping the Government.
He's wearing a costume! Catch him!
Hey, Robin! Why are you with jerks like them?!
It's bizarre for a woman who's been
pursued for 20 years to act like that,
Bro! Wait for us!
Here they come!
Privilege?
That's right...
Leave them to me!
Thanks for the drink, Blueno!
If you wanna leave us, tell us the reason!
but, well, that's not my concern.
This is in the name of justice to the end,
I'll nail them!
Hey! Wait!
He's right! They said they work
for the Government! So why?!
but when there're citizens who are
uncooperative toward the Government...
If the weapon gets restored through
deciphering the Poneglyphs,
Geez...
What happened to Franky
all of a sudden, Kokoro-san?
Coo... coo...
whether its owner is righteous or evil,
the result will be the same.
...we have permission to kill them.
This way! Catch him!
How selfish...! Justice cannot
be a reason for killing!
Beats me... How should
I know... how idiots think?
The weapon can never bring
forth "peace" to this world.
Don't let him get away!
You're not listening, are you?
He's just by himself! Corner him!
The World Government has
partially changed their thinking.
I did say goodbye to Cook and Doctor.
The world will go under for sure.
Come on! Assassin pirate!
Rather than remaining in fear
of the weapon's restoration,
You didn't tell them?
We mustn't call forth a relic of the past!
I did! But I can't accept it, either! Why, Robin?!
they decided to awaken it
to make it into a force of justice
that can end this Great Pirate Era.
To make my wish come true...
You're right. I do agree with you.
A wish that can never come true if I'm with you!
But it's none of your business.
Whatever I do to research history,
However, you don't want to help them.
I guess things have finally calmed down.
"Finally calmed down"?!
You're saying that you don't want to "save"
those people who keep being victimized
You had all those shipwrights chasing after you!
He climbed to a higher floor using a whip!
you, a stranger, have no
right to say anything to me.
That's why we ended up
getting dragged into it, too!
by pirates around the world.
I said it was unavoidable, didn't I?
Well... not quite...
Nonsense... If the weapon is restored,
the world will only fight over its power.
At any rate, Chopper, I'm surprised
you found out where we were.
You thought there'd be no one on the rooftop?
...since you and I are in
the same boat, in a sense.
In order to make it happen, I don't
care what sacrifices need to be made!
The damage only keeps growing!
Don't underestimate Galley-La's craftsmen.
--Your scent.
--Oh, yeah.
I...
It seems that you don't trust
the Government, Iceberg-san.
Hm? Come to think of it, where's Sanji?
How dare you mock us by
attempting an assassination?!
I have the blueprints of
the ancient weapon Pluton.
That's why... you set your friends up
as assassins without hesitation?
Well...
Prepare yourself, pirate!
The blueprints of the weapon?!
I just know the nature of humans, that's all, lad.
We're definitely not gonna
forgive you bastards!
Pluton is the name of a battleship
built on this island a long time ago.
What's that wish of yours?!
I don't need to tell you.
You'd better not try anything.
You're no match for me.
This is insane!
That woman is...!
The shipbuilding engineer who created
this overwhelmingly powerful weapon
Are you out of your mind, Nico Robin?!
There're two here!
Did Robin really say that?!
They're headed to the back door!
Do you realize what you're about to do?!
had the blueprints passed
down for generations.
Restrain yourself. Just how long are
you going to keep acting like my boss?
He felt that if by some chance
Pluton started running out of control,
You no longer have the right to say anything!
Yeah.
Don't let them get away!
We'll attack from both sides!
Don't let them inside the building!
there would need to be a force to counter it.
Follow them! Capture them immediately!
Keep your mouth shut!
In order to get them...
...the Government has finally
resorted to using force.
We all... were prepared for it, right?
Iceberg-san!
Kaku, check his pulse.
You have the blueprints of his residence
in your head, right, Nico Robin?
To think that you're helping
them without knowing that...
Even though it was for a
short time, we let Robin,
I won't let anyone get in my way!
who showed up as an enemy, come on board.
Yes.
Pardon me.
I'm too shocked to speak.
It'd be embarrassing if we ran
away because we got scared.
The man named Tom,
who entrusted the blueprints with me,
Ahh... The craftsmen are in a frenzy.
had been concerned about a girl
Yeah. It's gotten quite noisy.
Iceberg-san...
Isn't it about time for us to settle this matter...
who alone was able to escape from
the Ohara incident 20 years ago.
To tell you the truth, we came up
with a hypothesis a bit ago.
He said that although she was small,
...as to whether that woman is... foe or friend?
What do we do? Shall we go in soon?
she was dangerous, since she had the
same ideology as the Ohara devils.
Please don't worry. It's not that
we're going to torture you now.
I inherited the creator's will, so I have
the responsibility of stopping you!
Hm? Where's Luffy?
I won't let anyone get in my way!
Whaaat?!
All you have to do is listen to our
hypothesis without saying a word.
Think thoroughly before you
take action! You dumbass captain!
Now that the Government has come to
know of the existence of the blueprints,
Hey, Robin! What're you doing?!
essentially, it'd be better if I burned them.
Do you really mean it?!
I'm sure your blood will tell us the truth.
Robin! What happened to you?!
But I can't do that, because you're alive,
Are you just realizing that?
The situation will get worse.
and so there's still a possibility
that the weapon can be restored!
After today... I'll never see you again.
Are you really our enemy now?! Robin!
So you're sure that Robin said that, Chopper?
Sorry, but I need you guys to stop now.
The back door! They're headed
to the back door! Corner them!
Yeah.
Is that all you want to say before you die?
We have to find an important
person now, so we're in a hurry.
She said she wouldn't see us after today.
Don't let them get away! Surround them!
With all due respect, even if you
killed me and stopped its restoration,
It also sounds like she's
declaring that she'll do something
We no longer have business here.
that could worsen the situation
before the day is over.
if the blueprints get stolen from you,
wouldn't it be the same thing?
We don't have any business
with you guys, either.
How dare you show your faces
in front of all us guards?!
Be careful when you walk. Or you'll get hurt.
Get off of me!
Look at how big a fuss
Don't make light of the craftsmen at Galley-La!
the attempted assassination of
the mayor caused in this town.
Kalifa, how much time is left?
Your fate was already decided
when you hurt Iceberg-san!
Grandma, Grandma! Aren't we going back yet?
Well...
If it's possible to make the situation worse,
Two minutes.
...let me tell you one more thing.
Well... we've got a nice wind blowing.
Why don't we take the long way?
Just give up!
there's only one thing she can do.
I know this is sudden, but this building
is to be set aflame in two minutes.
This time for sure... Assassinate the mayor...
You can no longer escape, pirates!
You're the ones who got taken in by a plan.
It's just perfect for sobering up.
Give up and show your faces!
--What?
--What?!
We're gonna drag out the rest of the
group using you two! Damn assassins!
It's natural to think that way.
What? When you're still drinking right now?
What'd you say?!
Fire is an effective tool for
destroying various types of evidence.
But we know that she's pinning
her crime on us on purpose,
Say, can you sober up
while you're still drinking?
If you don't wanna burn to death,
you should leave the building immediately.
so it's possible that this could be a trap
to lure us out to the scene of the crime.
Sure I can. I haven't been drinking
for several decades for nothing.
Trap...
Well, of course...
He's gonna do something!
Er... Several decades?! That's weird!
If we're at the spot of the
assassination carried out tonight,
Shoot them!
the crime will easily be pinned on us.
...that is, if you could.
Hey! You already sound
like Robin is really our foe!
That's weird!
That's weird! That's weird!
Oh, that's it!
I'm talking about the possibility.
Looks like they intend to eliminate us.
That's weird!
It's not that I've decided on either.
It also seems that Nico Robin
wants to be on their side.
Ah... it hasn't been several decades.
If I already decide either to believe her or not,
Luffy, were you able to accept
Robin's leaving the ship?
It's been eight years...
I was finally able to get out! That was terrible.
if the truth turns out to
be the opposite of that...
They disappeared... No way...!
Okay, I'll swoop in this time for sure.
What's going on?
...it'll slow down my reaction.
Where'd they go?
I'll go capture Robin. Gum-Gum...
How could I?!
...Rocket!
Well, you don't have to shout like that.
Well then, I'll explain the thought
process leading to our hypothesis.
If something is to happen,
it'll be tonight. Are we going?
Soon, several rooms on the first
floor will burst into flames.
Hey, are you okay?
We are.
First, we have doubts about your
action of passing off the fake to us.
He's strong... What's with that whip man?
Well, the culprits are pirates.
Things like this can happen.
He ran... in the air.
You bastards...!
You guessed that the culprits
who came after the blueprints
No way...
He ran in the air?
were from the Government, so you
indicated where the fake was.
I don't mind going... but there's a problem.
To think that you do as you please
while pretending someone else did it...
Seriously, you people never listen, do you?
However, if it happened to be
someone who had a grudge against you
You sure have bad taste!
You're no match for our martial arts skills.
Sanji-kun saw Robin walking
with someone, right?
You guys are already criminals. No harm done.
Iceberg-san said the same thing.
She was with someone with a mask on.
He jumped off!
and they just came to kill you,
Now, hand it over already...
Moon Walk!
"Mr. Iceberg Falls Victim to Assassin"
the real blueprints would lose their owner
and they'd no longer be passed down.
Well, then...
...or else it'll get dirty with your blood.
But it wasn't any of us.
He's doing it again!
He jumped, in the empty air!
I'll go on ahead and leave now.
Yeah, you completed your job. Thanks.
He must be the reason why
Robin suddenly changed.
You're not stupid enough not
to think about that possibility.
Dammit...
Thorny Road!
I thought... I could defeat you.
Isn't he making Robin do bad things?!
Wait, Robin!
Even though you knew that,
I won't allow it!
you still didn't try to give the
real blueprints to anyone tonight.
That would be fortune.
Goodbye.
If this guy is Robin's real friend,
then that would be misfortune.
Robin!
That means you've already
entrusted them with someone.
But "someone with a mask on"
can't be a clue. That's the problem.
I told you not to, didn't I?
Don't...
To tell you the truth...
At the very least,
you don't have them with you.
...let Nico Robin go.
Ahh! He's coming!
...Iceberg-san told me to run right away.
What's our goal?
Where're you going this time...
when we finally found you?!
The courtyard! He landed in
the courtyard! Go around behind him!
So we think.
We'll capture Robin.
Hey! He went that way! Go ahead of
him and hem him in from both sides!
He told me to drop it quickly and run...
Outta my way, you bastard!
It's no use. Don't act up.
Okay!
Iron Body.
This is still only a possibility.
This must be it.
Of course, no convincing proof
can be found anywhere.
Otherwise, we won't know anything.
...since...
I see...
The past five years of our
surveillance and investigation
So that's the thing
Mr. Iceberg's been hiding, huh?
...it's a complete fake.
True. Thinking about it is a waste of time.
Why are their bodies so hard?!
found no proof in your actions, either.
What?
But, come to think of it...
Give it to us.
...the World Government has been trying
to capture that woman for twenty years,
In addition, the person who is
entrusted with the blueprints
A fake, you said?
Our bodies are well trained.
How foolish...
We can raise our bodies' solidity
to be as hard as iron crust.
has to have proper shipbuilding skills.
You can't appreciate its value.
and yet, it still hasn't happened.
I don't know who you are, but this
means your plan failed, doesn't it?
However... that's not to say
defense is all we can do.
But if we wanna know the truth,
that's the only way.
How pathetic. Sorry, pal.
Who the hell are you bastards?
Well, let me continue with our hypothesis.
I said outta my way!
Where'd you come from?
Okay, I'll do my best, too!
I don't even know what you're looking for.
Now things are getting more interesting.
Well then, let's go...
The darkness.
Paper Art.
These are the fake blueprints
that you passed off on us earlier.
However, we're a group that carries out justice.
...to Galley-La Company!
How cocky... You think that you outwitted CP9?
We are Cipher Pol No. 9,
an undercover intelligence agency.
When I look at it carefully,
there're signatures by the architects.
Dammit! The night is coming at last.
"Tom," "Iceberg," and "Cutty Flam."
In any case, even though you're only a decoy,
No matter where you slipped in from,
we can't keep you alive now
that you've become involved.
Paulie-san! This is it! The backstreets
will become dangerous soon.
At the end, there's a
company name: "Tom's Workers."
you must've encountered
our craftsmen without fail.
Ahh... He's dodging all the
punches... when he's that big!
You might've thought that you outwitted
your enemy by using these fakes.
Did we?
He's fluttering like paper!
Yeah. Let's go back.
We might have... or we might not have...
I'm gonna head to the main office.
Okay!
But you never even dreamed that
your enemy was hiding this close.
Hey, guys! We're going back!
Robin!
I don't really remember the details.
Wait!
That was your miscalculation.
Straw Hat! Show yourself!
To an overnight intruder
who came after the blueprints,
This is no longer something as
simple as an assassination, is it?
I got stuck! Dammit! I got stuck again!
You son of a...!
Where're you hiding?!
these would probably just be trash.
Gum-Gum...
Straw Hat! That bastard...!
Well, I don't recall us calling it that.
Why does this always happen?!
But to us, who lived in this
town for the past five years,
Straw Hat...!
--...Pistol!
--Shave!
Huh?
I thought the guy had at least a bit of mettle.
In any case, please give us that
valuable item of Mr. Iceberg's,
Ah! The rope guy!
He disappeared, too!
these architects' names are very interesting.
What happened to you? Are you okay?
But he doesn't even show himself.
and... since you've learned
something about it...
If your legs are so tremendously strong
that it appears as if you disappeared...
You're covered in blood.
You sure are full of surprises!
But Bro, the entire island holds
a grudge against them right now.
Iceberg-san, you have a guest.
That'd be you! This is the third floor!
...we'd like you to die.
She's right. They must be
running from place to place.
--You bastard!
--Moon Walk.
Tom's Workers, led by the
legendary shipwright Tom,
Straw Hat Luffy...
...you can even kick the air and float.
In the name of justice...
By the way, what's the matter?
What're you guys doing?
So you took the trouble to come
to take the crime upon yourself?
was a shipbuilding company
that was full of mysteries.
Right here... right now...
I think it used to be on this island,
We're vulnerable to strong winds from the front.
Ahh! Masks! Are they masks?!
He's flying! What the...?
but there's no list of workers
or company registration.
Then you people must be the ones
who're making Robin do stuff!
Did you find those two who
disappeared by the back door?!
And... Tempest Kick.
Just finding out the fact that you
were Tom's disciple was quite hard.
More importantly, Bro, the way you're
raging today is different from usual.
Give Robin back to us, you damn bastards!
No! We can't find them anywhere!
Letting stuff build up inside you isn't like you.
What about inside the residence?!
Dammit! Hey! Say something!
A slashing attack?!
There're guards at every window and door!
According to the report by the Government,
You two...!
Tempest Kick.
Shut up! I'm like that this week!
There's no way they could infiltrate!
Duck!
Tom had only two disciples.
Why?!
Dammit, pirates! Where'd they go?!
And a Government official
verified that one of them died
--Bro!
--Hm?
They definitely must be hiding nearby!
--Bro! Bro!
--That's Zambai and the others.
in an accident that happened eight years ago.
Look carefully one more time!
Capture them for sure! Got that?!
Whoa!
Did you know... that Tom's
violent disciple Cutty Flam died?
Bro! Did you beat up those bastards?
Yeah!
No, not yet.
His kicks cut the wall!
There was some crazy
interference. They got away.
He's behind this wall.
Luffy!
What?!
Straw Hat!
However, I remember hearing
this name Cutty Flam before.
They got away from you when you were angry?!
Okay. Now, push me.
Did they just cut the wall by kicking?!
What strong luck they have!
That's possible if you can kick fast
enough to cause a gust of sharp wind.
I see... Since that weak long-nosed guy
was fixing their ship all by himself,
Iceberg-san, you have a guest. He said
you'd know who if I told you "Cutty Flam."
We call it Tempest Kick.
I'm shocked.
I just assumed that you beat up the others.
It was about four years ago, a little while
after we started going undercover here.
What the hell are these?
I knew you'd come sooner or later...
Huh? You found one of them?!
We've got an emergency situation.
...but I never thought
you'd come through there.
We met on your ship, didn't we, Roronoa?
Y... Yes, on their ship.
We don't have time for you.
Did you do the same last night?
There was a man who came through the
Galley-La Company's gate to see you.
I can't move!
I know there isn't any door there.
Hey, restrain that guy, too.
This is no time for fighting.
It's the power of the Door-Door Fruit.
He used that name just once.
If you've found one of them, that makes it easy.
Right...
No matter how hard the wall is,
the area I touch becomes a door.
You aren't a shipwright, then?
We can use him to drag them all out!
I remember it, too.
Me, too.
As long as there's a wall,
I can go in and out anywhere.
Then, could that assessment
of our ship you made be...
B-Bro is showing his bad guy face.
Shall I show him in?
No... turn him away.
Unfortunately... I made the
assessment of the ship seriously.
Well then, you guys! Starting now,
march throughout the town...
What're you doing? We haven't
gotten the signal yet.
You can't call someone weakened
when he's got enough energy to talk.
Click.
That's indeed unfortunate.
...shouting, "We've got Long-nose!
It's me. A problem occurred in our plan.
If you don't want him to sink in the sea,
Just like a good chef wouldn't neglect
to prepare the ingredients beforehand,
In other words...
Everyone, come to the bedroom right away.
come to the warehouse under the bridge!
...Tom's other disciple Cutty Flam is still alive...
Don't shoot Iceberg yet.
pros would be careful to restrain their victim
Franky sends his regards!"
Got that? Don't shoot Iceberg yet.
...and lives in this town...
To make it true, I'm gonna
go kidnap Long-nose.
so that he wouldn't act unexpectedly
before the promised time.
Luffy!
I wouldn't have minded playing
with you a little longer, but...
Okay, Bro! Leave it to us!
So that's... CP9's way of doing things, huh?
...after changing his name to Franky!
...something came up. So, excuse me.
What?! Are you trying to run?!
Don't go, Robin!
No.
What a roundabout way of meeting.
You've got good insight... You're exactly right.
We're not done talking yet!
Yes, we are. I'll never see you guys again.
I did a bad turn to Straw Hat...
Since something came up,
I gave him a finishing blow.
What're these?
Robin!
Hey, they're the blueprints
for the ancient weapon.
Ahhh! Lulu-san is...!
So, as I suspected, he had
nothing to do with this.
--No way...!
--By just one hit?!
--Hold it!
Don't use the name Cutty Flam from now on.
Huh?
You're big, but your baggage is big, too, huh?
You don't have to feel bad, right?
He flew again!
It's only a matter of time before I get targeted.
You just told the truth
that you saw me last night.
Are you... okay?
Luffy! Hurry up and catch Robin!
This is my special bed.
Leave the island with them... Franky.
Aqua Laguna! Aqua Laguna!
This is... nothing!
Seems like there's no mistake about it.
Aqua Laguna is coming!
I see. Straw Hat, why did you come here?
That was also part of your plan?
I never thought that you and that
guy were connected like that.
We're Aqua Laguna!
That's right...
We kept you alive so that the crime
would be pinned on the pirates.
Everyone thinks that you guys are the culprits.
Run!
Roronoa! You're quite confident,
aren't you, taking your eyes off of me?
So what's going on with those culprits?
It's true that no matter
how much we investigated,
I'm sorry... It was all because
of our wrong assumption.
Besides, if we killed you suddenly,
I heard that they haven't been caught after all.
we couldn't figure out his real identity.
Don't worry about it.
We're used to being pursued.
How disturbing. Ahh, what a pain...
we wouldn't know the whereabouts
of what we're after...
But because he was a ship demolition worker
Ah! Zoro!
and because of his behavior,
we paid no attention to him.
The blueprints of a certain ship.
More importantly, a member of our
crew was taken by masked men.
It's said that they might attack again
tonight in the confusion of the storm.
I see... Involving a dead person
was indeed a perfect way to exploit
Finger Pistol.
It's something that has
been secretly passed down
So I came to take her back.
Aqua Laguna is here!
our blind spot, since our speculation
was generated only from the facts.
from shipwright to disciple
shipwright for generations.
But it'll be crazy tonight.
We don't need bullets to
shoot through human bodies.
You're talking about Nico Robin, right?
The Franky Family would come
to the shipyard to sell lumber.
I heard that all the craftsmen
will be guarding the main office.
If you felt your life was in danger,
So there were many chances
for you to make an arrangement
Whoa! That's pretty serious!
you'd try to entrust it with someone for sure.
You're strong when you fight, right?
You...
to give him the blueprints.
How many are there in the Straw Hat Pirates?
Yeah, I am!
Now, come to think of it,
...bastard...! Let me go!
And the one you chose was Paulie,
one of the foremen at Dock #1.
you could say that he was a
neighbor who kept a safe distance.
Some people said 50. Others said 100.
Can you beat them?
Luffy got caught so easily!
Yes, I can!
If you don't have the blueprints with you,
Go, Nico Robin.
Our fellow members are with him right now.
The captain's got a 100 million
bounty on his head, after all.
Then, fight with me! I wanna beat them, too!
it makes sense that you held firm.
Some said that 3,000 of his men
would advance from the sea!
So everything is going... as you planned, huh?
--You do...
--Of course I do!
Why... Why does Iceberg-san have to be
killed by some totally strange idiots?!
If it was your only fellow disciple
whom you entrusted them with,
That sounds totally dangerous!
Robin!
Make sure things are carried out flawlessly.
it's also understandable that you didn't entrust
them with any of the foremen at Galley-La.
Give me a break!
Who the hell are those people?!
Okay.
I'll go deal with the
shipwrights outside the door.
The hell with the undercover
intelligence agency, bastards!
Galley-La Company! Form a line,
and don't leave any openings!
Now, our speculations
are connected as one line.
In addition...
Nico Robin, you finish off this man.
Yeah!
He was... my teacher.
...your pounding blood proved it to be true!
Don't allow even a single rat inside!
Once those two get the blueprints
from Paulie, they'll contact you.
Yeah!
He helped me to become
an established shipwright!
--Hurry!
--Hey!
Why would someone like him be...
Dammit...
But you're too injured to...
Are you really sure this is the right way?
Kill Iceberg at that time.
Don't you say that!
I said I want to beat the
crap out of those idiots!
Who cares what happens to my body later on?!
Our mission is accomplished once we kill Paulie,
They've been hurt quite badly.
who's come to know the truth.
After that, this crime will be
pinned entirely on the Straw Hats.
I'm gonna fight to the
very last bone in my body!
Over there! That door is the one!
There's no mistake!
Bring it on!
Dammit! Take these off!
Many people are down over there, too!
Shut up, coo coo! Be quiet, Tilestone!
Okay! Take them off! Dammit!
Luffy!
Zoro!
Seriously... why can't he
listen to people's advice?!
Hm?
Now, you go ahead! Ahead of us!
Cut down the door and make a dash!
I was told that they weren't on the sea train.
Then they're still somewhere
on this island, huh?
But that's nothing new.
--Go ahead!
--What the hell?! Don't order me around!
But... Robin might be in that commotion, right?
How can they be that strong?!
But they're fools if they really
appear with all these guards around.
Hey, Straw Hat!
What are you people?
What are we gonna do?!
We have to act carefully!
I heard that an idiot plunged in here
in the middle of the day today.
You idiot! Wrong room! It's the next room!
We've lived in a different environment.
But depending on how you
look at it, we've lucked out.
Ever since we, CP9 members, can remember,
Don't think using your common sense.
Well...
When Luffy marches into enemy territory,
Oh, the next room?
we've been prepared to risk
our lives for the Government
Well, it's not your fault.
do you think he'd go around
to the back or the side?!
They don't have to go this far.
Go home!
and trained to surpass the
limits of human abilities.
They're doing it voluntarily.
--Not a chance.
--No chance.
So many things are happening tonight.
I've got nothing I could give you people!
I bet by now he's marched in from the
front by either jumping in or running,
They're treating me like a king.
You're only human. It's just natural that
you couldn't hide your consternation.
If you don't, that puts us in quite a bind.
By the way, why did you put up Nico
Robin's wanted poster in your room?
and now he's getting chased around
As a result,
I appreciate what you've done for us.
with no idea where to go, although he made
it inside the residence, don't you think?!
we've mastered the superhuman
techniques called the Six Powers.
Are you curious?
We're done with you.
What should I tell you first...
Yeah, sure do.
Let's hurry and find Franky.
Yeah, definitely.
I'm sure you've fully learned by now
A little.
Right? From the shipwrights' perspective,
that the four of us, who have been entrusted
with the World Government's vital tasks,
You bastards...!
Luffy is the ringleader of the culprit group.
...when you're about to die?
It's better if you don't know.
Once he jumps in, I bet everyone's
attention will go to him!
Hm?
are in a whole different league
from you guys, a mere pirate group.
You disappointed me.
She is... a devil.
In other words, there's no doubt
that the guard in front of the
residence has lightened up for now!
Lucci!
Where's Robin?!
It's your own fault.
So we'll be able to go across that opening
--Luffy!
and mix in with the crowd of
shipwrights who're in an uproar!
I see. So thanks to Luffy, the best
chance to infiltrate is right now, huh?
You should've given it to the
Government when they asked nicely.
How bothersome...!
This is a world-class top secret.
It's not a matter that people
like you can get involved in.
That's convincing! Then, it should
be okay to jump in, huh?
Kaku!
If possible, I wanted to make this town
part of my memory without hurting you.
Looks like we can jump over that fence!
Are you guys ready?!
Lucci...
Robin! I've finally found you!
Okay, we're gonna go in!
It's about time for the igniters
to go off. We have to hurry, too.
Follow Luffy!
Kalifa...
Hey, Luffy! Where the hell have you been?!
So you also inherited your
master's obstinacy, huh?
Yeah.
But this is a rare occasion.
Blueno, from the bar...
Robin! I'm glad that I could see you again!
Tons of people are guarding the place.
Let me show you something
interesting before we go.
You guys... work for... the Government?
It's a little far.
Hold on a sec... What's going on here?
You can just stretch your arm
and go flying there, right?
But after the commotion starts, okay?
--What?
--Th-This is...
That's right. Going undercover
was a pretty easy mission for us.
Yeah. If we cause a commotion before
they do, they'll just take advantage of it.
What part of this is light?!
Dammit... I can't get out.
In any case, your prudence
leaves me at a loss for words.
Listen up!
Don't miss even the slightest movement!
Well, well, well...
I wanted to jump into
the building, fast and furious...
Lucci... What the hell are you?
Yeah!
Now, Iceberg-san...
...but I'm stuck and can't move!
Straw Hat...
Where're the blueprints of
the ancient weapon Pluton?
Paulie...
He's huge!
I can't get out...
Iceberg-san... What the hell...
I have to hurry...
Please tell us, before many people get hurt.
Just wait... Robin!
...is going on?!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Don't tell me-- you guys are CP9?
Whoa! He's huge!
What was that explosion?!
Nico Robin... I was finally able to see you.
Hey, Robin! Why are you with jerks like them?!
What's with that appearance?!
So they've finally started taking action.
Now, tell us where the blueprints are.
This is how I really look.
We're done with you guys now.
The craftsmen are being
attacked by weird people!
That's right. They work for the
Government, right?! So why?!
I wonder if we're connected by a thread of fate.
Nonsense. If the ancient weapon is restored,
Robin is definitely in that commotion.
We're alike, so...
Goodbye.
Straw Hat, can you defeat him?!
the world will only fight over its power.
Listen. Think that we'll never be able to
see Robin again if we miss this chance!
He's huge, but I'll beat him up!
Wait! I won't accept it! We're not done talking!
What do you mean?
It seems that you don't trust
the power of the Government.
My belongings and your existence
will destroy the world, so...
Hmph! I'll let you experience
my strongest power!
Yes, we are. I'll never see you guys again.
I know. We'll definitely
capture her. Just wait, Robin!
I just know how humans are, that's all, lad.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Straw Hat Pirates Annihilated?
The Menace of the Leopard Model!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"CP9 Takes Off Their Masks!
Their Shocking True Faces"
"Come Back, Robin! Showdown with CP9!"
"Cannon Fire Is the Signal!
CP9 Goes into Action"
"Secret Bond! Iceberg and Franky"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!