Mozu!
Don't go, Robin!
We're not done talking yet!
Yes, we are. I'll never see you guys again.
To think that you left the friends
you traveled together with
Kiwi!
Pardon me... for interrupting.
Have a nice flight off the island!
all the way from the East Blue, for the ship...
You bastard!
What are you guys crying for?
It's just, these two ladies didn't let us in, so...
You bastard!
Luffy! Hurry up and catch Robin!
You dummy! We're not crying, you dummy!
What the hell are you bastards doing here?!
But it's true that I was moved by your
protecting this ship all by yourself
The members of CP9 have
finally made themselves known.
while all those things were happening!
We're not crying! None of us are crying!
Robin!
Lucci, Kaku, Blueno and Kalifa.
--Iron Body!
--Hm? You son of a bitch!
What the heck is their problem?
Luffy and Zoro stood up to them
to put a stop to their scheme.
Anyway, now you know that those guys
and I are no longer friends, right?!
However, Lucci, who has Cat-Cat
fruit powers, crushed them.
Blueno! What's the meaning of...
How can they be that strong?!
Huh? What's this? How cocky...!
CP9 has found out that Franky is Cutty Flam
I'll...
I'll sing about your hardships!
Who do you think I am?!
and has the blueprints for
the ancient weapon Pluton.
Ow...
What are you people?
The song title is, "Severed Friendship!
Northern Wind Chop!"
Who are you trying to pick a fight with?!
I've got nothing I could give you jerks!
We are CP9.
Man, that was rough.
Yay! Bro!
This is a world-class top secret.
Are you making fun of me?!
Dammit! That damn leopard jerk!
Now I'm really pissed!
It's not a matter that people
like you can get involved in.
You're only a dull bar owner!
Bro!
And they caught Franky,
who challenged them, in the blink of an eye.
What's up with that getup?!
Help...
I'll pay him back two times over.
It's about time for the igniters
to go off. We have to hurry, too.
You seem different from your usual self!
Yeah.
Man, that was rough.
Tsk.
But this is a rare occasion.
I'll say hello to "Bro" for you.
Let me show you something
interesting before we go.
Don't, Blueno.
I'll pay him back two times over.
Not until we get what we want,
shipwright Cutty Flam.
We now know the location.
The blueprints are not here!
Dammit!
H-Hey! A-Are you okay?!
Let's go.
--Hang in there!
--We can't kill him yet. Don't forget our mission.
--Sorry.
--Wh-Wh-What's going on?! Hey!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
Stay back!
I thought I saw them working at the shipyard!
with the sun always in our hearts
What the hell? Why was he able to...
As power passes through our clasped hands
A Devil Fruit!
You bastards! What are you people?!
You sure are acting pretty super, aren't you?!
let's grab hold of our wishes
Which one?!
How dare you hurt innocent girls?!
They're like my little sisters, you jerks!
To start with, how the hell
do you know about this place?
Where am I?
Mister, I made some tea.
Why don't you take a break?
Lucci... What the...?
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
This is my secret base!
Dammit!
We don't care about that. I'll keep
this simple. Listen carefully.
Why the hell is this happening?
Hm? Oh, thanks. I'll have some
once I finish fixing this spot.
The Cat-Cat Fruit...
Dammit! I'd better hurry!
Our lives in this town were a cover.
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Leopard Model...
In reality, we are World
Government intelligence agents.
A leopard human...
You must know what that means...
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
H-He's huge!
Okay! Just as I planned.
...as well as the reason we came here.
What's with that appearance?!
Ouch!
Franky... we already know everything.
What the hell are you?!
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
Cutty Flam...
So, brother...
Tom's other disciple, who was said
to have died eight years ago...
Hm?
I'm gonna get to the main issue.
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
What're you gonna do after you fix that ship?
It's all right! Now let's move forward
That's you.
but what you cherish most will be right there
I don't know how you found
that out... but that's splendid.
What am I gonna do?
with the sun always in our hearts
Of course, I'll go on an
adventure with her again,
And if you get into a jam
We were taken in by the Government.
and someday we'll go back
to our home, the East Blue!
As power passes through our clasped hands
At the same time, I'm starting to feel uneasy.
I'll always be there to protect you
They're gonna make us the culprits
for attacking the Judicial Ship...
It's not like we went around the world,
let's grab hold of our wishes
Is that idiot Iceberg doing okay?
It's all right! Now let's move forward
...because they want to question Tom-san
as a criminal to obtain the blueprints.
but this is a ship that went to the Grand Line.
We killed him.
It'll be good enough to
call it a triumphant return.
with the sun always in our hearts
After all this... can you still
say that you're innocent?!
I'll hold my head up and--
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
No, you won't be able to go back...
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
It's all right! Now let's move forward
and gaze at the light beyond
If we can't somehow stop them
from taking Tom-san away...
...to the East Blue.
To begin with, it's too far.
with the sun always in our hearts
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
...I'll never...
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
...forgive you for the rest of my life, Franky!
As power passes through our clasped hands
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
Bro?
let's grab hold of our wishes
So let's grab hold of our wishes
When we pulled up the ship earlier,
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
under the same flag-- together, we're one
I'll never--
Stop it!
I was observing her very carefully.
Tom-san...
Don't blame him, Iceberg.
Stop it, you bastards! What're you
gonna do with the Merry?!
One Piece
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
It's not Franky's fault.
Take off the ropes! Let the ship down!
You're still saying that, even at this point?!
If you do something to the Merry,
my 8,000 men will teach you a lesson!
Tom-san!
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
"Spandam's Scheme!
The Day the Sea Train Shook"
Hey, are you listening, you bikini jerk?!
I'm sorry! I made this harpoon!
but what you cherish most will be right there
If you underestimate me, you'll regret it!
I made it so that it can't come
out once it pierces its target!
And if you get into a jam
I'm Captain Usopp, the king of
the East Blue who is feared by all!
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Dammit!
I'll always be there to protect you
Don't apologize. This is nothing.
--Shut up.
--Ow, ow, ow...
It's all right! Now let's move forward
Don't pinch me.
I see...
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
Look! They're over there!
Be quiet.
So this filthy warehouse used to be
Tom is on the ground!
Shut up! Ouch!
with the sun always in our hearts
Why is he seriously injured like that?!
Sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Tom's Workers shipbuilding
company's main office, huh?
Then, it wasn't them who made the raid?
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
The townspeople are here.
and gaze at the light beyond
That ship is at the end of her life.
but what you cherish most will be right there
A shipbuilding company?
The assessment by Galley-La is correct.
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
Well, then...
And if you get into a jam
As someone who's in the demolition business,
...shall we head to the town, too?
I suggest you demolish her.
Tom, Iceberg, and Cutty Flam...
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
I'll always be there to protect you
You bastard, Spanda!
What? That's ridiculous!
That's "Spandam"...
So let's grab hold of our wishes
So this is a place that holds memories
I'll help you demolish your ship!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
...you criminals...
of the three of you devoting
yourselves to building ships, huh?
under the same flag-- together, we're one
with the sun always in our hearts
What?! What're you saying, you jerk?!
To think that you call it a secret base...
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
One Piece
That's quite adorable.
It's all right! Now let's move forward
Wait! What're you doing?! Stop right there!
and gaze at the light beyond
Shut up!
Bro!
with the sun always in our hearts
I'm just saying I'll help you demolish that ship.
Get out of this place already!
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
As power passes through our clasped hands
Not until we get what we want,
shipwright Cutty Flam.
"The Straw Hat Pirates Annihilated?
The Menace of the Leopard Model!"
Don't be ridiculous! I won't allow that!
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
let's grab hold of our wishes
The blueprints are not here!
The Merry is my ship!
So let's grab hold of our wishes
No...! She's...
Well... That's not surprising.
under the same flag-- together, we're one
...no longer a ship.
--Hey!
--Kalifa!
What?
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Fire!
One Piece
What'd you say?!
Hey, everyone! Wake up!
I asked you earlier what you were gonna
do after you fixed this ship, didn't I?
Dammit...! Is this the pirates' doing?
Ow...!
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
There must still be a lot of people left inside!
If you were going to offer your
life to the sea with this ship,
"Franky's Past! The Day
the Sea Train First Ran"
Where's Iceberg-san?!
What's going on upstairs?!
Wh-Wh-What do I do?!
Let's go check!
I wouldn't have said anything.
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Hurry! The rest of you, put out the fire!
You son of a bitch!
But... you said that you wanted to
go back to the East Blue on this ship.
Don't try to play innocent now...
You don't have to tell us right away.
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
...as we already know everything.
We've got a trump card.
So I'm trying to stop you... brother.
Although this is from eight years ago,
It's only a matter of time before I get targeted.
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
I heard that you committed a crime...
This ship... can no longer
even reach the next shore.
Leave the island with them... Franky.
Looks like the fire has started to spread.
but what you cherish most will be right there
...just like Tom did.
Tom handed them down to Iceberg...
and Iceberg to you.
That's a load of crap! Tom-san wasn't a criminal!
Listen. Ships are born with a promise
And if you get into a jam
Don't talk like you know everything! You brat!
I don't know if you're a
leopard human or what, but...
to carry you across the sea
from one shore to another.
Both of you, come over here.
I'll always be there to protect you
...I won't let you lay a finger on Iceberg-san!
I wanna entrust something
important to you two.
It's all right! Now let's move forward
Our mission took quite a while,
but it's finally checkmate.
In other words, once a ship can
no longer carry you to shore...
Oh, no! Carnivore Zoan types
become more brutal!
with the sun always in our hearts
Now, hand over the blueprints for the
ancient weapon Pluton, Cutty Flam.
Tom-san...!
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
That's right. Logia types,
Zoan types, and Paramythia types...
Hey!
and gaze at the light beyond
Stay back!
Stop it!
Don't make a fuss.
Flam...? That's a strange name.
Once she can't carry you to shore...
You're a criminal. You should
know what will happen to you.
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
Many unique powers exist.
"Franky" would do, right? "Franky" would.
...she's no longer a ship!
Genuine physical augmentation
is the trait of Zoan types.
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
Anything is fine.
Bro!
Can you hear me?
Franky... Don't interfere
in what I'm about to do...
So let's grab hold of our wishes
I'm saying hand them over to us, Cutty Flam.
The more we train, the stronger we get.
No matter what.
under the same flag-- together, we're one
I've got nothing I could give you jerks!
You don't know anything...
Stop it!
Anything about Tom-san...
The Zoan type is the strongest species
when it comes to a close attack.
One Piece
Wha...!
Anything about Water Seven!
Shut up!
"Water Seven, 8 years ago"
I don't wanna hear stuff
about monsters like that!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
"The End of the Legendary Man!
The Day the Sea Train Cried"
Wh-What just happened?! It was so
fast that I couldn't see anything.
We don't want to waste time, either...
with the sun always in our hearts
...since we have to take care of you guys
before we get wrapped up in flames.
Hey! Are you okay?!
As power passes through our clasped hands
The Judicial Ship is coming in three days?
let's grab hold of our wishes
These are the raid culprits.
They're finally having Tom's trial, huh?
Iceberg-san!
Foremen!
I wonder what'll happen?
Please rest easy, everyone.
This is...
He should be okay.
Lucci... the craftsmen are coming upstairs.
We, CP5, brought them down
after they made the raid.
What's the matter, Lucci?
Yeah.
What is this filthy room?
He did fulfill his promise.
Don't worry. They can't make it this far.
They can't cause any more trouble.
A drafting room?
Yeah.
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Tempest Kick!
Oh?
He would've been found
not guilty in today's trial...
It's a good place to hide blueprints. Find them!
Carry the received lumber into the dock!
So then, why did Tom do something like that?
Did the negotiation in St. Poplar go well?
So he was a friend of the
King of the Pirates after all, huh?
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Not yet. They're taking advantage
of us since we don't have materials.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Spandam from CP5.
Go back! The ceiling is...!
It was the same deal with the iron in San Faldo!
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
You happened to be there?
Thank you. You saved us.
Shipyards will end up going into
the red if things are that expensive!
These are... nameplates?
Please hand them over to us,
as we would like to investigate them.
But we'll work it out next time for sure!
Cutty Flam.
Iceberg.
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
Yeah! That's right!
Tom.
This name is...
Nami!
Try making excuses if you like.
Our trustworthiness is worlds apart.
Hm?
This is...
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
Everyone is happy about
being able to cross the ocean,
I'll get the blueprints of the ancient weapon.
Don't you dare touch it!
but what you cherish most will be right there
but I heard that trading with
other islands isn't going well.
--Ribbit, ribbit.
--How terrible...
Chopper!
Don't intrude upon someone's memories!
And if you get into a jam
I wonder if the town won't
change even with the sea train...
Paulie, what're you doing?
I'm taking you out of this place no matter what!
I'll always be there to protect you
This is where we grew up.
First, about the sea train,
all I can say is, splendid.
But people are lively! The results
won't show immediately, Iceberg.
It's not possible! Your injuries
are too severe! How can you...
It's all right! Now let's move forward
The shipbuilding company, Tom's Workers!
I can see it'll contribute greatly
to the growth of Water Seven.
Stop it, Paulie.
Once a man's done everything he could,
It's where the world's best shipwright lived!
with the sun always in our hearts
he should just resolutely keep his head high!
For that, on the previous charge
for building Gold Roger's ship,
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
Don't call my name... as if we're friends!
Yeah.
"Water Seven, 22 years ago"
and gaze at the light beyond
your acquittal today had
pretty much been decided.
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
So then, why did you commit another crime?
That's a load of crap!
Get... out of our way!
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
We're not the ones who
raided the Judicial Ship!
Hello there. Are you Mr. Tom,
a shipbuilding engineer?
It was that Spandam guy who did it!
So let's grab hold of our wishes
Well, I've been looking all over for you.
under the same flag-- together, we're one
He's gonna eat me!
Hm?
Damn you...!
Huh?
Excuse me, but I'd like to...
Take these!
Why did it have to be you guys?!
--Um...
--Don't interrupt! Step back!
One Piece
No way!
What's got into that disciple of Tom's,
suddenly cracking jokes?
--Yes, sir!
--I'd like to have a little conversation with...
I...
...at least...
What would CP5, a Government entity,
gain by sinking a Judicial Ship?
I considered you guys my friends all this time!
"The Man Who Is Loved Even
by His Ship! Usopp's Tears!"
I-I am...
What a stupid thing to say!
That's not possible at all!
...from Cipher Pol No. 5.
Move! Move aside, Iceberg!
I'm Spand...
Cutty Flam, was it?
It was just you.
Spandam-san!
To start with, we caught you
red-handed on one of the raid ships.
Well...! What the hell are you doing, Franky?!
Oh, sorry!
I don't know who you are,
but my cannon salute hit you!
In addition, weren't those raid
ships built by your company?
You bastard! Move away from Merry!
And...
...this is super! The Battle
Franky No. 35 has returned!
Pigeon jerk...!
Well...! What the hell are you doing
instead of helping me with work?!
Straw Hat!
I killed a Sea King!
Ships that would do something like that...
To think that you keep
making unstable stuff like this!
Look at this size! It's a monster
that must be at least 100m in length!
Shut up! It's none of
your business, Stupid-berg!
Finger Pistol.
They're... no longer...
This is my precious battleship,
the Battle Franky!
You son of a bitch!
That idiot... He never learns.
Luffy!
...my ships!
I don't know what that is, but ditch the
whole thing before someone gets hurt!
If you don't get it...
Ahhh, you bastard! Stop it, Stupid-berg!
This is the scrap heap island! It's my
own business to keep whatever I want!
Just wait and see!
How many times do I have to tell you?
Next time for sure, I'll build a
battleship that will beat Sea Kings!
...take a good look at her...
with your own eyes!
To think that you keep building
stupid battleships one after another!
Well...! There's no way you can
beat them! I hope you get eaten!
Tom tore his handcuffs apart!
Enough is enough!
If you can't, I'll destroy all
of them today for sure!
--I can beat them!
--Well...! You can't!
Ready!
--I can!
--Well...! You can't!
Don't you dare!
They're my precious battleships!
Tom-san... hit Franky for the first time...
If you're a man... do it resolutely!
I won't let you mess with my ships!
Well...! Listen, Franky!
You killed a Sea King, right?
What'd you do that for?!
Have a nice flight off the island!
That means that this is quite a lethal weapon!
"They're no longer my ships," you say?
I can't understand your nerve,
just leaving dozens of them out here!
You can say anything but that!
Luffy!
It's not like I'm gonna attack people with them!
What's wrong with saying that?!
I'm regretting it!
You bastard!
It has nothing to do with your intention!
If only those ships didn't exist,
no one would have had to get hurt!
Iron Body.
I'm calling you to account for
creating lethal weapons, Moron-ky!
That concludes the launch ceremony!
E... Excuse m...
No matter what kind of ship it is,
the act of building it...
We were resolutely able
to make a solid, good ship!
Tom-san! Please say something!
Right, Yokozuna?
...is neither an act of good nor evil!
Moron-ky is a disgrace to our company!
Ribbit! Ribbit!
Let's finish it up tomorrow, shall we?
Now, let's go home.
You said "Moron-ky" again!
I don't care what kind of
ships you choose to build,
Zoro!
E-Excuse me... Please hold on a second!
Ribbit, ribbit!
but even if the ships you built hurt someone,
Boy, I'm hungry.
First, I want you to apologize to me!
And then, I want you to listen to me!
--Ribbit, ribbit!
--I wonder what we're having for dinner.
or even if they destroy the world,
Ribbit, ribbit!
Hey, wait up, Tom-san!
You're from the Government,
aren't you? Is it about the trial?
at least the one who created
them must love them!
What? What're you talking about?
Their creator mustn't deny them!
No, I don't know anything about it.
Don't blame the ships!
You too.
A man should be resolutely proud...
of the ships he created!
Hm?
So which Battle Franky did
you build this time, Franky?
Tom-san...
The eighth one! It was close!
What happened to Tom-san?
Don't lie!
Geez... Since you let him do this stuff,
Tom-san, he gets full of himself!
He said he wanted to talk alone.
He's with a man from the
Government in the brick warehouse.
All he makes are weapons!
Shut up, Stupid-berg!
This guy's name is Span... What was that?
What'd you say, Moron-ky?!
It's Spanda-something.
That official isn't from the Judicial Ship.
What disorganized people...
--Now, now, stop fighting, both of you.
--He said "Moron-ky"!
Iceberg...
But Kokoro-san! This idiot was...!
Franky...
I don't know about it! I don't have
any blueprints for something like that!
Don't interfere in what I'm about to do...
Geez...
You too, Tom-san. You're laughing
too hard. What was so funny?
No matter what.
Don't lie!
To think that you're playing innocent
just because I've been acting humble!
It's the World Government
who pinned the crime on us.
Oh... yeah... I just remembered...
We've already investigated by going
back into the history of Water Seven!
It's also the World Government who judges it.
I heard that another trading ship with
lumber on it was attacked by pirates.
Grandma! Grandma! There's a big fire!
If we check your belongings, the actual
article will show up in no time!
There's no way that we'll
get cleared of suspicion.
After the King of the Pirates was executed,
This is it.
the number of pirates grew considerably.
That's Galley-La's main office.
What a terrible thing to do...
Do you guys have the
authority to investigate me?
It's all over for this town. It's being
overtaken by the pirate era.
It must be really tough for you to see
your innocent ships being used like this.
We sure do, Tom!
People are in low spirits.
A terrible thing? Did someone set the fire?
Believe it or not,
our investigation already found out
You must want to beat up
that guy, right, Franky?
"Merchant"
We can now get lumber and iron
Well, I don't know...
that you're a heinous criminal
who built Gold Roger's ship.
only from other islands due to
the floods caused by Aqua Laguna,
Since you're a criminal, we can
do whatever we want with you.
...but often, a bad feeling turns out to be right.
and yet, violent seas and pirates hinder trading.
I hope Iceberg is okay.
The Government already knows it.
Shipyards scramble for customers
due to the shortage of work.
What?!
Tom-san!
Can't be!
Tom started going on a rampage!
Seriously, this is all because of
that thing. It just shouldn't exist.
They start fighting. They lose their jobs.
Then why are you working here as a
shipwright instead of being in jail?!
--Ribbit!
--Oh, my God...
Please stop! If you lay
one more finger on him...!
If nothing is done, Water Seven,
If you are an intelligence agent,
check into it yourself. See ya.
an island that once left its mark
with its shipbuilding business,
Do you...
will become weak-minded,
just waiting for floods to happen.
...understand the pain he's feeling?!
Hey, wait! I'm not done talking!
F-Fire!
Who do you think I am?!
What pirates say cannot be evidence.
That's right! Tom-san built
an incredible pirate ship, too!
Oh, that...
This incident will now be shrouded in darkness.
They shot him...
Say, teach me how to draw
blueprints for a pirate ship!
Tom did fulfill his promise
with the Judicial Ship.
Iceberg-san... No matter how good
of a shipbuilding engineer you are,
His charge will probably be written off
in the trial that will be held in three days.
What's so funny?
or even if you're the mayor of a big city...
Franky, there's no such thing
as blueprints for a pirate ship.
Tom is a great man.
Tom-san!
...you, a mere citizen, shouldn't have disobeyed
This is ridiculous.
the powerful World Government.
If the sailors who board a ship put up
a skull flag, then it's a pirate ship.
Such a serious charge related
to Roger will be written off?
If they put up a seagull flag,
then it's a Navy ship.
So something like that really does exist.
I don't care what you wanna build,
Yes, sir.
Naturally, there are pirates who're
sniffing around for these blueprints.
but a man should be resolutely
proud of the ship he built!
Let's go. We'll find Tom's
other disciple Franky--
If, by chance, someone other than the
Government got their hands on them,
rather, Cutty Flam, and take
the blueprints from him.
Tom-san!
there would no longer be any
means for us to fight against them.
Aren't you going to bed yet, Tom-san?
Tranquillizer bullets, huh?
It's been more than ten years since the
dawn of the so-called Great Pirate Era.
What're you drawing?
Mm... It's this island's hope.
Pirates have been gaining power quickly
and keep increasing in number.
You damn fishman with superhuman
strength! That serves you right!
This is no time for carefree talk
Hope?
Hopefully, it can revive Water Seven.
about things like preventing the
restoration of the ancient weapon!
Tom-san! Why'd you do that?!
Precisely because we uphold justice,
we should have fangs like that!
Hey, guys! What're you doing?!
Hurry up and capture them!
Now, go to bed.
We'll own the ancient weapon
Did you get everyone out of the building?!
Yeah.
We'll take everyone from the ferocious
Tom's Workers company to Enies Lobby!
We can't go inside anymore!
Have each team account for its men!
Hm?
Sorry, Merry.
and repel this Great Pirate Era!
Hmm...
Hey, where's Iceberg-san? Did you see him?
To think that Tom is such a dangerous person...
Times are changing.
There's some truth to what you said.
I'll fix you right away.
What the hell is he thinking?!
Don't tell me he's still in this fire...
I'll fix you right away... I'll...
Then obtain these blueprints
you're talking about first.
He really sold his soul to pirates!
I'm sure he's okay!
Three of our foremen are with him.
There's no way he got left in there.
As many times as you need...
We'll discuss it further afterwards.
He made that many battleships and
waited for an opportunity like this!
Ahh!
We'll leave this matter to you, Spandam.
I'll fix you as many times as you need!
You guys go check around there, too!
You bastards! How dare you
talk like that to Tom-san?!
Yes, sir! Leave it to me, sir.
The Government's Judicial Ship is here!
As many times as you need!
Stop it.
After all my investigating,
I finally got this chance!
This woman...
It's all right.
What's a Judicial Ship?
But...!
She's one of the Straw Hats. There's no mistake!
It's a mobile court.
Who did they come to judge?
Judge...
Hey! Enough already, Long-nose!
Hm?
I'm not just gonna watch it go up in smoke!
I'll confess to the charge of
making a raid on the Judicial Ship.
Did she jump out a window?
You saw the bottom of the ship, right?!
She was probably surrounded by
flames and had trouble escaping.
With the broken keel at the root of her,
What?!
Hey! Tom-san! Don't!
Let's go!
Wait a sec! What did
Tom-san do to deserve this?!
the outer panels are slipping off
and the frames are torn, too!
What do we do with her?
But I have a favor to ask.
Hey! Outta my way, you jerks!
Give us Tom-san back!
When a ship is like that, she'll just fall
apart from the outside with each wave!
Seriously... what a terrible thing they've done.
Shut up, you stupid fishman!
Dammit! If he's not a criminal,
it'll be a problem for me!
I'll be fine. Don't worry.
Who'd listen to a criminal's...
And yet, you think a total
amateur like you can...
Keep your mouth shut, CP5!
We'll make her tell us where the others are!
What?!
Spandam-san!
We'll capture all of them and
hand them over to the Navy!
So, what is the favor?
Tom-san! Tom-san!
If I can get one charge eliminated
for our building the sea train...
Whoa...
The hell with writing off the charge...
How cocky... Just wait and see!
...I'd like today's charge to be eliminated.
Shut up!
What?
I don't want you to tell me anything!
Even if that wish is granted,
you'll just go back to square one.
Blueno... So Franky was at your bar?
Hey! Call in five more intelligence agents!
The King of Pirates, Gold Roger,
was executed the other day.
Keep your mouth shut, or I'll
beat you up, you hooligan!
Yes, sir!
Yeah.
But he rushed out to find Straw Hat.
You'll end up with the crime of building
a ship for the King of the Pirates,
We consider shipbuilding engineer Tom's
act of building Gold Roger's pirate ship,
I see...
which will result in the maximum penalty.
the Oro Jackson, to be aiding and
abetting this vicious world-class criminal.
Spandam-san!
Yeah, I prefer that.
Seems like he doesn't stay in one place for long.
Hence, Tom will be taken to
Enies Lobby to be executed!
About assisting that Roger guy...
But people with bad timing really exist.
I'm resolutely proud of it!
What?!
Look.
Listen, Straw Hat!
How selfish...
We've got Long-nose with us!
To think that he's proud of
assisting the King of the Pirates...
That's right, we do!
At...
Traitor!
If you don't want him to sing in the key of C...
--Ferocious fishman!
--Damn fishman!
Idiot! That's not it! How many
times do I have to tell you?!
At heart...
Tom-san... Why?!
This is terrible! Tom will...
Tom will be executed!
That's "If you don't want him to sink in the sea"!
It's fine.
Listen. Don't blame yourself, okay?
...I know it.
In the key of C...
"In the sea"!
Iceberg. Franky.
Geez, what were you listening to?!
Huh?! What did you say?!
--Hm?
--Both of you, come over here.
They say it's on the charge of
building the King of the Pirates' ship.
I never thought that the Government
would use force to get the blueprints.
What's important is to get the
message to Straw Hat, right?!
I wanna entrust something
important to you two.
So it's finally time, huh?
At heart...
It caused problems for the
entire world. They had no choice.
I was at a bit of a disadvantage
due to the matter with Roger.
We're saying that message ain't gonna work!
Hm?
Bro is gonna beat you up.
At heart...
Normally, no matter whom a shipwright
sells a ship to, it's not a crime.
But even so, you didn't have to--
You say it like, "If you don't
want him to sink in the sea,
Don't worry.
W-Why does something like this...
At heart... I know it all.
come to the warehouse under the bridge!
Franky sends his regards!"
Look at the town. Even if my charge
goes back to what it was 14 years ago,
However, the King of
the Pirates is an exception.
Got that?!
C-C-Can humans make something like this?!
Mind you, even if he comes, Bro is
gonna beat the crap out of him, though.
We consider all those who have
assisted in his pirating activities
everything is different from then.
I... I...
It's the worst monster ever
in the history of shipbuilding.
This island is full of energy now.
to be dangerous individuals!
Hence, he's sentenced to the death penalty!
I know that Merry is at the end of her life!
The Government has become aware
of the existence of these blueprints
This is just the beginning.
Who did you say is waiting for whom where?
Take the offender away.
and has started taking action.
No matter what happens to me,
Yes, sir!
It'd be dangerous to keep them with me.
--Now, let's go.
--Hurry up and walk!
Hm? Who the hell are you?!
I can be of help to the town.
I'm scared... but I understand. We'll keep them.
--What's the matter?
--Go already!
We're busy right now! Get lost!
My dream has...
Hey, what're you doing?!
This is amazing! Hey, Iceberg,
let's try building it!
I'm currently designing...
If you don't wanna die,
answer my question in three seconds.
...finally... begun to run.
...a paddle steamer that resolutely runs
on a railway set on the ocean's surface.
Huh?!
You idiot!
Ouch!
This guy's talking nonsense.
Tom-san!
Think a little before you say things!
--Hey! What're you saying?!
--Why, you...!
Do you know what family we're in?
I'll keep them! If something like
this is brought into this world...
Tom-san!
Suppose this island's decline is due
to trade not happening as we wish it...
Which place do you mean by
the warehouse under the bridge?
Hm?
Iceberg... Franky...
Suppose the hopelessness that people feel
Franky is there, isn't he?
At heart...
Yeah, the world will be finished.
Take care of the blueprints.
I... know...
is coming from the worries
about this sinking island...
What business do you have with Bro?
Kokoro-san... Yokozuna...
If you wanna talk to him, then talk to us first!
Putting a sea train into operation...
When I heard the assessment,
But now, you can do
whatever you want with them.
Thanks for everything.
...will definitely save Water Seven someday!
I was convinced that what I saw
on that day really happened.
You can even ditch them if it gets dangerous.
Tom-san...
While I'm at it...
The tranquilizers have finally started working!
I-I'm sorry! We'll take him out right away!
First, I thought I was dreaming.
Capture those three culprits
for the Judicial Ship raid!
...I'll tell you one more thing
that I'm worried about.
No... wait a moment.
Huh?
Yes, sir!
I thought there was no way
something like that could happen.
Sea train, you said?
Hold it!
--Huh?
--I'm changing the charges.
It's a ship that puffs smoke
To think that you left the friends
you traveled together with
and runs from one island
to another on a sea railway.
On one foggy night...
in a forest under the moonlight,
Hey! Hey, wait, Franky!
For the charge of building the pirate ship
for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates,
all the way from the East Blue, for the ship...
Huh? What is...
It'll carry people and goods as well as ships.
I heard the strikes of a wooden hammer.
What are you guys crying for?
we'll take shipbuilding
engineer Tom to Enies Lobby.
At least put some pants on!
Without having to worry about the weather,
Geez... Didn't you learn a lesson the first time?
everyone will be able to freely cross the ocean.
You dummy! We're not crying, you dummy!
The sound was coming from the ship,
That is all.
If you go to town with only a swimsuit on,
But it's true that I was moved by your
protecting this ship all by yourself
although no one was supposed
to be on her at the time.
there'll be another perv uproar, right?
Stop kidding yourself!
A railway? It'd be destroyed
once Aqua Laguna comes!
Geez... I'm just going shopping.
It came from our ship, which was
scarred and washed ashore.
What got into that old geezer?
while all those things were happening!
We're not crying! None of us are crying!
Now, go already!
That's right! Besides, there are
also Sea Kings in the sea!
Oh, well. I don't have
business with his disciples.
Geez... To think that she's
taking the trouble to prepare
Release those two disciples!
What the heck is their problem?
The sea railway doesn't have to be fixed.
It was very foggy, but I
definitely saw someone there...
celebration dishes just because
Tom-san is being declared not guilty...
He wasn't guilty from the start.
It'll sway a little below the surface of
the water, never resisting the waves.
Anyway, now you know that those guys
and I are no longer friends, right?!
...striking a wooden hammer.
I couldn't figure out who it was.
Tom-san can no longer be saved.
Now...
As if pulling in a rope, the sea train
will just use the railway as a guide.
I'll...
If it's the World Government we're
up against, there's nothing we can do!
Hey, Tom-san! Iceberg! Get up!
I'll sing about your hardships!
But then, when the morning came the next day,
Furthermore, I'm thinking of adding
a mechanism that generates
The song title is, "Severed Friendship!
Northern Wind Chop!"
Bear it. Tom-san saved you two!
Today is the trial day!
the ship was lousily fixed.
Hurry up and go get judged!
a discordant sound that fish hate
between the paddles and the railway.
Yay! Bro!
If you make an enemy of them,
Are you making fun of me?!
The completely broken mast
was also fixed as it used to be.
no matter how many lives
you have, it's not enough!
Then Sea Kings won't come close to the railway.
Hurry to the harbor!
But the really mysterious thing was that...
Enies Lobby is the judicial island
owned by the Government.
Tom's sentence is going to be be handed down!
Is something like that possible?
Hey, is the tea ready yet? I'm thirsty.
...whoever fixed the Merry
knew how she originally looked.
No criminals taken there...
If we connect St. Poplar, Pucci,
San Faldo, and this island,
...have ever returned!
Okay! We'll bring it right over!
industries can grow through trading.
This trial seems to be of
high interest to the people.
Despite the fact that we
had added lots of tweaks,
The sea train is ready! We can take him now!
How wonderful...!
this person put the Merry back
to how she used to look!
A lot of court spectators are getting on board.
I'm exhausted from crying...
Not that I cried, though.
The blueprints will be completed soon,
Good!
but it's not so simple that
ordinary shipwrights can build it.
Yes, it appears so.
Kokoro-san...
Have you seen the sea train, judge?
Hey, you guys! Hurry up and take away...
Is it possible to connect Enies Lobby as well?
Everything was a mystery to us, but...
Yeah, I took a ride once.
Here you go, Bro. It's a little hot.
I...
...for some reason, these words
remained in my heart.
Of course it is!
It's indeed incredible. I'm impressed
that he really made it happen.
...this heavy, crazy fishman!
Once this technology is completed
and eventually crosses the ocean,
Now that the four islands are connected,
I don't even know if this person actually
said it or I was imagining things...
Thanks.
I can't do that!
I imagine no one would oppose his acquittal.
Then, I get it, brother, you know...
Ah!
the relationships among islands all
around the world will resolutely change!
Hey!
Don't worry.
Is Tom here yet?
Ouch, it's hot!
I can't wait for it to start.
The sea train is the hope of Water Seven!
Settle down a little, will you?!
Hurry! The spectators' gallery is gonna fill up!
I'll carry you guys for a little bit longer.
I'm sorry, Bro.
How long will it take?
Yeah! I have to see the moment he is
declared not guilty with my own eyes!
Stop it!
Ten years.
Then build it!
This brings back memories.
It's already been 14 years, huh?
Why don't you take a break
and have some tea, too?
This may sound stupid, but...
As the development period for the sea train,
I give ten years probation
to shipbuilding engineer Tom!
...I feel that it might've been
an incarnation of the Merry.
Spandam-san's face got bent!
This time, Tom's disciple
started going on a rampage!
This is incredible!
I can't blame you. You must be
holding quite a grudge against us
What?!
--Stop it!
--Ribbit, ribbit!
Good luck, Tom!
Capture him! The rest of you, take Tom away!
Please save Water Seven!
for taking 200 million Berries
away from you guys...
I bet the ship was already at her limits then.
What're these explosions?!
Fine by me! I won't let you take him away!
...since it led to such a big fight.
I'm resolutely still alive!
So she might've turned into
that form to let us know it.
You're allowed to shoot him!
This is no laughing matter, Tom-san.
It was meant to happen, that's all.
Give us Tom-san back!
I thought that your time had come
and I got a chill down my spine.
Holding a grudge doesn't do me any good.
Get off the ship!
When I heard the assessment,
that's what I thought.
Hurry! Hurry up!
But anyway, if things go well, they may
let the matter with Roger go, huh?
You're a good sport.
Are you okay?!
What's going on?! A pirate raid?!
I see...
Well...! At any rate, you're great, Tom-san!
Hurry up and run!
That 200 million...
Dammit! Where are they firing from?!
Fire!
To think that you've been
thinking about something like that!
You think I'm crazy, don't you?
You don't have to believe me.
I used it all, though!
Hm?! Over there!
Everyone was overwhelmed!
The sea train really is...
You want me to knock you over?
Now, now... Don't get so upset.
What's that fleet?!
Thanks for the dinner! Come, Yokozuna!
I'll teach you how to do the front crawl!
Bro?
What?!
You've shown me how manly you are.
Believe you?
Ribbit!
Hey, Franky! What's with you?!
You've been sulking for a while now!
Dammit! He got away!
So, now I have to calm my anger
over the complete destruction
This person looked like a sailor
holding a wooden hammer, right?
I've never seen battleships like them!
Which pirate group is that?!
I'll never let that Cutty Flam
brat get away with this!
Shut up! I'm angry at everything!
of the Franky House, which was
my home and demolition factory.
What...? Why...?
Gold Roger's ship is the only ship in the
world that went around the Grand Line!
He is truly a criminal!
Do you know?
What the hell is with those
heavily armed ships?!
Once this case is over,
I'll have him sent to the gallows!
On top of that, you guys
annihilated my subordinates!
Brother...
Why does Tom-san, who built such
a great ship, have to get executed?!
You saw a Klabautermann.
--Spandam-san!
--What do you want?!
How dare you bastards?!
The people there were also
saying that it was just natural,
Get away from the harbor!
I-It's Cutty Flam!
K-Klabau...?
Hurry up and run!
--Bro!
--The anger welled up!
even though those idiots can't even build a raft!
--Hurry!
--Run towards the town!
What?!
Klabautermann.
I also know that the reason
our company is under a bridge
He came this far after us!
You bastards!
Help! My son is stuck!
He's standing on the railway with some weapon!
It's one of the legends known among sailors.
is because you were kicked out by the
townspeople over Roger's ship, right?!
It's a fairy that dwells only on a ship
that's treated with great care.
Why the hell does the world's best
shipwright have to be treated like this?!
Stay there, Yokozuna.
Well, you could say it's a ship's incarnation.
Ribbit...
What's funny, you horned raccoon dog?!
Well, brother, although a lot happened,
Is he stupid or what?
Why...?
Who're you taking it out on, Moron-ky?!
You are not gonna get away with it!
They carry wooden hammers in their hands
let's calm our anger towards
each other on this matter,
What should we do?
and are dressed in sailor's raincoats.
I can't stand that the person
himself is like that, either!
Who the hell... took... took my ships?!
Are you stupid, too?!
and settle it as "Heave-ho! Heave-ho!"
Just keep going; give him what he wants.
Don't be concerned about him!
When danger approaches the ship,
they run around inside the ship
and let people know about it.
You mean "fifty-fifty."
No, no! That's not it!
Tom-san! There's trouble!
You mean "fifty-fifty," Bro.
Y-Yes, sir.
It is said that they sometimes
help sailors quite a bit.
Hm?
Stroke with all your might
to push the water backwards!
Franky's ships are attacking the Judicial Ship!
Well, there you go.
Stop, Puffing Tom!
But to be honest, this is the first time
I've heard someone say they saw one.
Wait! It's not Franky. He's in town right now.
Ribbit! Ribbit!
What're you gonna do now that you're alone?
No! No! Stroke more vigorously like this!
He certainly wouldn't do something
like that! I know that much.
Where are you taking your creator to?!
You have nowhere to go anyway, right?
--Ribbit!
--No! Like this!
--Seriously, what's with him?!
The more care the ship receives,
the more it appreciates the sailors.
That's exactly why this is trouble!
You should just kick out an idiot like him!
If that's the case, I can
take you in. Work for me!
We'll stop them, Iceberg!
Well, don't say that. He's a fellow shipbuilder.
Yeah!
This ship probably wanted to somehow
carry you across to the other shore.
Are they pirates? Or someone
from the Government?
In terms of shipbuilding skills,
I like you.
there's already no big difference between
him and the craftsmen on the island....
No way! I don't wanna
become a demolition worker.
She was able to encounter a crew
that she wanted to carry so badly
Ribbit, ribbit...!
...though what he makes is shaky.
--Evacuate!
--Don't stop! Hurry inland!
Even though I left my group, I'm still a pirate!
He's just always honest, that's all.
I won't let you pass here!
that she'd borrow a human form to appear...
Get away from the harbor!
Please listen to my song.
It's titled "The Pirate Code."
My father is still inside!
I bet she's been very happy.
Yay! Bro!
Give Tom-san back to us!
Bastards! They won't get away with this!
Like I said, are you making fun of me?!
Two years ago, when I saw a kid who had
resolutely appeared on the scrap heap island
Stop! Sea train!
Geez... I'm trying to think what
you should do next, for your sake!
Merry...
Dammit! Who are they?!
Who's screwing around with my ships?!
make a cannon using junk,
I was really surprised.
It's none of your business!
Old man, take me in!
I was abandoned by my parents!
I see. Your parents abandoned you, huh?
Besides, is it okay for you
to relax in a place like this?
I see...
That's so funny!
Then, the one...
He told me that his parents said,
"What an uncontrollable brat,"
A storm surge is coming soon, right?
Hey, you're laughing too hard!
...who talked to me then...
Yeah, that's exactly why...
Judge! Please hurry up!
This ship won't hold out!
Okay, then! Come resolutely to my place!
and threw him off the ship.
...was really you, huh?
When Aqua Laguna comes,
we all have to help each other.
It seems that they were worthless
pirates from some place, though.
Tom-san...
Who does that fleet belong to?
Merry...
I don't wanna build ships anymore!
--That was so funny!
--Tom-san...
The raid on the Judicial Ship was successful.
He's tough, isn't he?
I can't love ships that hurt
the people I really care about!
From now until late into the night,
Despite his circumstances, he isn't crooked.
I see... Then move on to the next
step in the scenario immediately.
houses will be submerged
up to the second floor.
You two will definitely become world-class
shipbuilding engineers someday.
If you're in the backstreets or capes at
a time like this, you don't stand a chance.
But, Tom-san...
This is a sacrifice for justice.
At any rate, for Heaven's sake...
...you're my goal after all!
Yes, sir!
You don't have to worry if
you keep your ship here too.
You should be nice to each other.
You had a big fight with your friends
knowing your ship is at her limits, then?
Franky can't do it. He's crazy
even at the cellular level!
Now, let's start the trial... Tom's Workers...
Oh... Thanks... I appreciate it.
Well, as soon as I finish the blueprints,
we'll start building the sea train!
You dummy! Don't act like we're strangers!
It's not that simple.
In any case, it must be tough to have
flood damage like that every year.
Yeah... but I bet he won't help us.
So I want you to come back
and teach me again...
How inept men are!
Well, everyone's used to this
annual evacuation, though.
The Judicial Ship will sink soon.
He can do as he pleases!
They're fools!
Okay, then! Let's go back
to the scrap heap island!
What's more problematic
Okay.
is that the water level of the sea
has been increasing every year.
...because I want to...
The backstreet area you can see above
the sea now is a town built on the rooftops
Hey, the fleet is withdrawing!
Looks like someone's here.
...build a dream ship someday, too.
Wait... I recognize those ships!
of an old town that existed
several hundred years ago.
"Someone's here"? Who else could
it be but Zambai and the others!
A ship that resolutely and proudly traverses
It's said that the shipbuilding
island and the backstreets
Tom-san! The ships are coming back this way!
Why did they take the trouble
of coming from the sea side?
were completely on one land a long time ago.
even uncharted waves at edges of the earth!
They're close to the shore!
I think we can catch them!
Yeah... when they usually
use the upper entrance...
But now, so much of the area is under
water that it's called a floating city.
A dream ship like that!
They sure went and did
something crazy with those ships!
They might've brought Straw Hat.
All the sidewalks became canals.
Oh, that's right!
Two people are running this way
from the scrap heap island!
Properly speaking, rather than saying
that the water level is increasing,
I forgot that I sent for Straw Hat
and the others with you as bait!
That's Tom.
they say that the foundation
of the island is sinking.
Okay, then! Let's leave the ship.
They won't come. We're no longer friends.
As it stands, the areas in town we can
live in will get smaller and smaller.
I told you so, didn't I?
What we heard about Tom
is that he had good skills,
I see... Even this pretty floating
city has hardships too, huh?
What the...?! No one is on the ships.
but he was a ferocious and intractable
fishman with superhuman strength.
Why aren't they coming in?
This side, too. No one is on any of the ships!
Even if we ask the townspeople,
they just speak ambiguously.
But, well, if push comes to shove,
Okay, okay. I'll open the door now!
you can take the sea train
and go live somewhere.
Well... What's going on?!
It must be tough to be a disciple that has
to defend such a man, huh, Cutty Flam?
You can say that... now.
Okay, okay. Geez, stop ringing the bell!
Those are Franky's, too.
Ahh! Iceberg! Watch out!
That's not even worth responding to.
But it was only a bit over a decade
ago that the sea train was created.
You Government people are all crap!
Before that time, it wasn't quite
that easy to go across the sea.
Brother... Go back to your friends.
What?! Hey, hey...
At that time, more than 100 people,
including marines and officials,
Huh?
were severely injured here in Water Seven.
I can't do that now. I fought
a duel with my captain.
Naturally, people were rarely able to
go back and forth between the islands.
The culprit behind it was you.
On this isolated island,
Dammit...! My Battle Frankys are a mess!
the residents vaguely imagined
their land being submerged someday
Besides, the ship stuff isn't settled yet, so...
You had a lot to answer for, causing the
World Government that much trouble,
but since you were confirmed dead in
the sea train accident on that very day,
What do you mean it hasn't been settled?
and grew completely hopeless.
If you know that your ship can't
sail anymore, it's simple, isn't it?
Ahh...
your charge was annulled.
Now, we'll take you to
Enies Lobby as a criminal.
Iceberg! Tom-san!
Hey! Both of you...!
Leave her with me.
You can take your time there
answering my question...
What's going on?! What happened?!
I'll take care of her in a way
that you'd approve of.
What relieved people's
worries even about the future
...about the whereabouts
of the blueprints for Pluton.
What I did earlier, too, you know...
was the sea train, Puffing Tom.
I tried to destroy the ship thinking
that it would be best for you.
Suicide?
Are you okay?!
You can now go across the sea
whenever you want without a Log Pose.
--Blueno.
--Yeah. It just connected.
I heard that it was the president
of the No. 4 shipbuilding company.
Hey! Ice--
Don't stick your nose
into things! It's my business!
So this was big progress!
It must be because of that accident.
--Hey, I'm trying to solve your problem!
--Is it Zambai?
Since they didn't have materials, he went
to purchase lumber on his own ship
You idiot!
I see... I didn't know.
The sea train really is an incredible thing, huh?
You should appreciate it!
and got fifty people killed on the sea.
When I reported this case to our chief,
I should appreciate it? Give me a break!
Water Seven came back to life.
His shipyard is closed, too.
he said he wanted to talk
to you right away, so...
That intelligence agent
who came the other day...
Don't you get it?! It's a
nuisance for the ship, too!
It's all thanks to a great shipwright
named Tom who created the sea train.
How weak humans are, huh?
Your chief? Hm?
They used your battleships.
Is this really it for this island?
She loves you guys so much that
she appeared in human form.
Please go ahead, Chief.
Hey! Did you guys hear
about the scrap heap island?!
Ouch! It's hot! It's hot! It's hot!
We were all saved by him.
You got hurt by my battleships?!
If she sinks in the middle of the sea
while you guys are on board...
I spilled the coffee!
I told you, didn't I?
Dammit! Stupid coffee!
Over... and over again...
H-Hey, is that true?!
Hey! If that happens, even if she dies,
she'll be filled with regret!
Tom's Workers has finished
building the sea train, you say?!
What the hell?
I can't understand your nerve,
just leaving dozens of them out here!
She won't be able to rest in peace!
Are you there...
Then, when your friends are dying,
can you just leave them saying,
...Cutty Flam?
Whoa! Does a ship like this really run?
Bro!
I'm calling you to account for
creating lethal weapons, Moron-ky!
--Hm?
--It's been a while.
It's a ship built by a criminal. It's dangerous!
"Well, I hope you die
without suffering at least"?!
Help...
I'll get on board!
Tom-san got... hurt by my ships!
I never thought you'd survived that...
If you put it that way,
that's a whole different discussion!
Me too, then.
Tom! You are not gonna explain?!
Listen.
It's hard to believe, but I'm happy to hear it.
We're leaving! Get on board!
No, it's not! It's that kind of matter!
Our skills can bring lethal
weapons into this world...
I'll say hello to "Bro" for you.
You just don't get it, do you?!
...even if you don't intend to do so.
Who the hell are you?
During these past eight years...
every time my scars hurt,
Weapons hurt people despite your intentions!
It's moving!
Huh?!
The paddles are grabbing the railway!
I was tormented by an anger that
I couldn't take out on anyone...
Mozu!
They can even hurt those
who mean a lot to you!
--It's moving!
--Whoa, amazing! It's running!
We now know the location.
We were taken in by the Government.
...because the culprit who hurt me died!
Kiwi!
They're gonna make us the culprits
for attacking the Judicial Ship...
Wh-Who's there?!
I'll ask you again! Who the hell are you?!
Let's go.
...because they want to question Tom-san
as a criminal to obtain the blueprints.
Pardon me... for interrupting.
You don't remember me?
Twelve years ago...
It's just, these two ladies didn't let us in, so...
After all this... can you still
say that you're innocent?!
...leaving a closed, declining town,
I'm the man who was from Cipher Pol No. 5
and arrested Tom's Workers red-handed for
attacking the Judicial Ship eight years ago!
with worried people on board...
If we can't somehow stop them
from taking Tom-san away...
The secretary at Galley-La!
...I'll never...
...the sea train Puffing Tom crossed
the sea for the first time.
...forgive you for the rest of my life, Franky!
What the hell are you bastards doing here?!
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end, we can all surely smile
I see. So this is a place that holds
your memories with Tom, huh?
Galley-La! What the hell are you bastards...
I'm sorry, Tom-san. Because of me...
Hey, Long-nose. What're you
gonna do after you fix that ship?
I've been eagerly looking forward to seeing you.
Shut up, you raiders who defy the Government!
We're Government
intelligence agents, Cutty Flam.
What else? I'll go on an
adventure with her again and...
The blueprints aren't here!
Get out of here already!
Don't tell me... Is that you, Spanda?!
That's nonsense! We didn't do it!
That's not possible. You can't.
Why do you know that name?!
"M"! You're missing the "M"! It's "Spandam"!
Hmph! Well, fine.
You're a criminal, just like Tom was.
You've been entrusted with something
by the legendary shipwright Tom.
Shut your mouth! I have business
with this damn fishman!
--What'd you say?!
--That ship can't even reach
the next island anymore.
Now, Lucci! Hurry up and bring
them to Enies Lobby already!
You should know what'll happen to you.
What're you gonna do with Tom-san?!
Now, could you please hand over your secret?
--Roger.
--Hey, hold it! Let him go!
You don't know anything about Tom-san!
Don't talk like you know everything!
I'll help you demolish that ship.
It's all over for Tom's Workers.
--What'd you say?
--Oh, I'm sorry.
Stop it! What're you doing?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The End of the Legendary Man!
The Day the Sea Train Cried"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Franky's Past! The Day the Sea Train First Ran"
"The Truth Behind Her Betrayal!
Robin's Sorrowful Decision!"
"Spandam's Scheme!
The Day the Sea Train Shook"
"The Man Who Is Loved Even
by His Ship! Usopp's Tears!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!