Have a nice flight off the island!
You bastard!
Ow...
Man, that was rough.
Dammit! That damn leopard jerk!
Now I'm really pissed!
I'll pay him back two times over.
Dammit!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"Spandam's Scheme!
The Day the Sea Train Shook"
I see...
So this filthy warehouse used to be
Tom's Workers shipbuilding
company's main office, huh?
A shipbuilding company?
Tom, Iceberg, and Cutty Flam...
So this is a place that holds memories
of the three of you devoting
yourselves to building ships, huh?
To think that you call it a secret base...
That's quite adorable.
Shut up!
Get out of this place already!
Not until we get what we want,
shipwright Cutty Flam.
The blueprints are not here!
Well... That's not surprising.
--Hey!
--Kalifa!
Ow...!
Wh-Wh-What do I do?!
You son of a bitch!
You don't have to tell us right away.
We've got a trump card.
Although this is from eight years ago,
I heard that you committed a crime...
...just like Tom did.
That's a load of crap! Tom-san wasn't a criminal!
Don't talk like you know everything! You brat!
Tom-san...!
Stay back!
Don't make a fuss.
You're a criminal. You should
know what will happen to you.
Franky... Don't interfere
in what I'm about to do...
No matter what.
You don't know anything...
Anything about Tom-san...
Anything about Water Seven!
"Water Seven, 8 years ago"
The Judicial Ship is coming in three days?
They're finally having Tom's trial, huh?
I wonder what'll happen?
He should be okay.
Yeah.
He did fulfill his promise.
Carry the received lumber into the dock!
Did the negotiation in St. Poplar go well?
Not yet. They're taking advantage
of us since we don't have materials.
It was the same deal with the iron in San Faldo!
Shipyards will end up going into
the red if things are that expensive!
But we'll work it out next time for sure!
Yeah! That's right!
Everyone is happy about
being able to cross the ocean,
but I heard that trading with
other islands isn't going well.
I wonder if the town won't
change even with the sea train...
But people are lively! The results
won't show immediately, Iceberg.
Once a man's done everything he could,
he should just resolutely keep his head high!
Yeah.
Hello there. Are you Mr. Tom,
a shipbuilding engineer?
Well, I've been looking all over for you.
Hm?
Excuse me, but I'd like to...
--Um...
--Don't interrupt! Step back!
--Yes, sir!
--I'd like to have a little conversation with...
I-I am...
...from Cipher Pol No. 5.
I'm Spand...
Spandam-san!
Oh, sorry!
I don't know who you are,
but my cannon salute hit you!
And...
...this is super! The Battle
Franky No. 35 has returned!
I killed a Sea King!
Look at this size! It's a monster
that must be at least 100m in length!
That idiot... He never learns.
Ahhh, you bastard! Stop it, Stupid-berg!
How many times do I have to tell you?
To think that you keep building
stupid battleships one after another!
Enough is enough!
If you can't, I'll destroy all
of them today for sure!
Don't you dare!
They're my precious battleships!
I won't let you mess with my ships!
Well...! Listen, Franky!
You killed a Sea King, right?
That means that this is quite a lethal weapon!
I can't understand your nerve,
just leaving dozens of them out here!
It's not like I'm gonna attack people with them!
It has nothing to do with your intention!
I'm calling you to account for
creating lethal weapons, Moron-ky!
E... Excuse m...
Tom-san! Please say something!
Moron-ky is a disgrace to our company!
You said "Moron-ky" again!
E-Excuse me... Please hold on a second!
First, I want you to apologize to me!
And then, I want you to listen to me!
You're from the Government,
aren't you? Is it about the trial?
What? What're you talking about?
No, I don't know anything about it.
Hm?
Tom-san...
What happened to Tom-san?
He said he wanted to talk alone.
He's with a man from the
Government in the brick warehouse.
This guy's name is Span... What was that?
It's Spanda-something.
That official isn't from the Judicial Ship.
What disorganized people...
I don't know about it! I don't have
any blueprints for something like that!
Don't lie!
To think that you're playing innocent
just because I've been acting humble!
We've already investigated by going
back into the history of Water Seven!
If we check your belongings, the actual
article will show up in no time!
Do you guys have the
authority to investigate me?
We sure do, Tom!
Believe it or not,
our investigation already found out
that you're a heinous criminal
who built Gold Roger's ship.
Since you're a criminal, we can
do whatever we want with you.
The Government already knows it.
What?!
Can't be!
Then why are you working here as a
shipwright instead of being in jail?!
If you are an intelligence agent,
check into it yourself. See ya.
Hey, wait! I'm not done talking!
Who do you think I am?!
Oh, that...
Tom did fulfill his promise
with the Judicial Ship.
His charge will probably be written off
in the trial that will be held in three days.
Tom is a great man.
This is ridiculous.
Such a serious charge related
to Roger will be written off?
So something like that really does exist.
Yes, sir.
Naturally, there are pirates who're
sniffing around for these blueprints.
If, by chance, someone other than the
Government got their hands on them,
there would no longer be any
means for us to fight against them.
It's been more than ten years since the
dawn of the so-called Great Pirate Era.
Pirates have been gaining power quickly
and keep increasing in number.
This is no time for carefree talk
about things like preventing the
restoration of the ancient weapon!
Precisely because we uphold justice,
we should have fangs like that!
We'll own the ancient weapon
and repel this Great Pirate Era!
Hmm...
Times are changing.
There's some truth to what you said.
Then obtain these blueprints
you're talking about first.
We'll discuss it further afterwards.
We'll leave this matter to you, Spandam.
Yes, sir! Leave it to me, sir.
After all my investigating,
I finally got this chance!
I'm not just gonna watch it go up in smoke!
Let's go!
Dammit! If he's not a criminal,
it'll be a problem for me!
Spandam-san!
Whoa...
The hell with writing off the charge...
How cocky... Just wait and see!
Hey! Call in five more intelligence agents!
Yes, sir!
Spandam-san!
Iceberg. Franky.
--Hm?
--Both of you, come over here.
I wanna entrust something
important to you two.
Hm?
W-Why does something like this...
C-C-Can humans make something like this?!
It's the worst monster ever
in the history of shipbuilding.
The Government has become aware
of the existence of these blueprints
and has started taking action.
It'd be dangerous to keep them with me.
I'm scared... but I understand. We'll keep them.
This is amazing! Hey, Iceberg,
let's try building it!
You idiot!
Ouch!
Think a little before you say things!
I'll keep them! If something like
this is brought into this world...
Hm?
Yeah, the world will be finished.
But now, you can do
whatever you want with them.
You can even ditch them if it gets dangerous.
Tom-san...
While I'm at it...
...I'll tell you one more thing
that I'm worried about.
Hey! Hey, wait, Franky!
Huh? What is...
At least put some pants on!
Geez... Didn't you learn a lesson the first time?
If you go to town with only a swimsuit on,
there'll be another perv uproar, right?
Geez... I'm just going shopping.
Now, go already!
Geez... To think that she's
taking the trouble to prepare
celebration dishes just because
Tom-san is being declared not guilty...
He wasn't guilty from the start.
Now...
Hey, Tom-san! Iceberg! Get up!
Today is the trial day!
Hurry up and go get judged!
Hurry to the harbor!
Tom's sentence is going to be be handed down!
This trial seems to be of
high interest to the people.
A lot of court spectators are getting on board.
Yes, it appears so.
Have you seen the sea train, judge?
Yeah, I took a ride once.
It's indeed incredible. I'm impressed
that he really made it happen.
Now that the four islands are connected,
I imagine no one would oppose his acquittal.
Is Tom here yet?
I can't wait for it to start.
Hurry! The spectators' gallery is gonna fill up!
Yeah! I have to see the moment he is
declared not guilty with my own eyes!
This brings back memories.
It's already been 14 years, huh?
What?!
What're these explosions?!
Get off the ship!
Hurry! Hurry up!
What's going on?! A pirate raid?!
Dammit! Where are they firing from?!
Hm?! Over there!
What's that fleet?!
What?!
I've never seen battleships like them!
Which pirate group is that?!
What the hell is with those
heavily armed ships?!
Get away from the harbor!
Hurry up and run!
--Hurry!
--Run towards the town!
Help! My son is stuck!
Why...?
Who the hell... took... took my ships?!
Tom-san! There's trouble!
Hm?
Franky's ships are attacking the Judicial Ship!
Wait! It's not Franky. He's in town right now.
He certainly wouldn't do something
like that! I know that much.
That's exactly why this is trouble!
We'll stop them, Iceberg!
Yeah!
Are they pirates? Or someone
from the Government?
--Evacuate!
--Don't stop! Hurry inland!
Get away from the harbor!
My father is still inside!
Bastards! They won't get away with this!
Dammit! Who are they?!
Who's screwing around with my ships?!
Judge! Please hurry up!
This ship won't hold out!
Who does that fleet belong to?
The raid on the Judicial Ship was successful.
I see... Then move on to the next
step in the scenario immediately.
This is a sacrifice for justice.
Yes, sir!
Now, let's start the trial... Tom's Workers...
The Judicial Ship will sink soon.
Okay, then! Let's go back
to the scrap heap island!
Okay.
Hey, the fleet is withdrawing!
Wait... I recognize those ships!
Tom-san! The ships are coming back this way!
They're close to the shore!
I think we can catch them!
They sure went and did
something crazy with those ships!
Two people are running this way
from the scrap heap island!
That's Tom.
Okay, then! Let's leave the ship.
What the...?! No one is on the ships.
This side, too. No one is on any of the ships!
Well... What's going on?!
Those are Franky's, too.
Ahh! Iceberg! Watch out!
Dammit...! My Battle Frankys are a mess!
Ahh...
Iceberg! Tom-san!
Hey! Both of you...!
What's going on?! What happened?!
Are you okay?!
Hey! Ice--
You idiot!
That intelligence agent
who came the other day...
They used your battleships.
You got hurt by my battleships?!
I told you, didn't I?
Over... and over again...
I can't understand your nerve,
just leaving dozens of them out here!
I'm calling you to account for
creating lethal weapons, Moron-ky!
Tom-san got... hurt by my ships!
Listen.
Our skills can bring lethal
weapons into this world...
...even if you don't intend to do so.
Weapons hurt people despite your intentions!
They can even hurt those
who mean a lot to you!
We were taken in by the Government.
They're gonna make us the culprits
for attacking the Judicial Ship...
...because they want to question Tom-san
as a criminal to obtain the blueprints.
After all this... can you still
say that you're innocent?!
If we can't somehow stop them
from taking Tom-san away...
...I'll never...
...forgive you for the rest of my life, Franky!
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end, we can all surely smile
I'm sorry, Tom-san. Because of me...
Shut up, you raiders who defy the Government!
That's nonsense! We didn't do it!
Shut your mouth! I have business
with this damn fishman!
What're you gonna do with Tom-san?!
It's all over for Tom's Workers.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The End of the Legendary Man!
The Day the Sea Train Cried"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!