You bastard!
The members of CP9 have
finally made themselves known.
Lucci, Kaku, Blueno and Kalifa.
Luffy and Zoro stood up to them
to put a stop to their scheme.
However, Lucci, who has Cat-Cat
fruit powers, crushed them.
CP9 has found out that Franky is Cutty Flam
and has the blueprints for
the ancient weapon Pluton.
I've got nothing I could give you jerks!
And they caught Franky,
who challenged them, in the blink of an eye.
Man, that was rough.
I'll pay him back two times over.
Not until we get what we want,
shipwright Cutty Flam.
The blueprints are not here!
Stay back!
Where am I?
Dammit!
Why the hell is this happening?
Dammit! I'd better hurry!
Okay! Just as I planned.
We were taken in by the Government.
They're gonna make us the culprits
for attacking the Judicial Ship...
...because they want to question Tom-san
as a criminal to obtain the blueprints.
After all this... can you still
say that you're innocent?!
If we can't somehow stop them
from taking Tom-san away...
...I'll never...
...forgive you for the rest of my life, Franky!
I'll never--
Stop it!
Tom-san...
Don't blame him, Iceberg.
It's not Franky's fault.
You're still saying that, even at this point?!
Tom-san!
I'm sorry! I made this harpoon!
I made it so that it can't come
out once it pierces its target!
Dammit!
Don't apologize. This is nothing.
Look! They're over there!
Tom is on the ground!
Why is he seriously injured like that?!
Then, it wasn't them who made the raid?
The townspeople are here.
Well, then...
...shall we head to the town, too?
You bastard, Spanda!
That's "Spandam"...
...you criminals...
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"The End of the Legendary Man!
The Day the Sea Train Cried"
These are the raid culprits.
Please rest easy, everyone.
We, CP5, brought them down
after they made the raid.
They can't cause any more trouble.
He would've been found
not guilty in today's trial...
So then, why did Tom do something like that?
So he was a friend of the
King of the Pirates after all, huh?
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Spandam from CP5.
You happened to be there?
Thank you. You saved us.
Please hand them over to us,
as we would like to investigate them.
Try making excuses if you like.
Our trustworthiness is worlds apart.
I'll get the blueprints of the ancient weapon.
--Ribbit, ribbit.
--How terrible...
First, about the sea train,
all I can say is, splendid.
I can see it'll contribute greatly
to the growth of Water Seven.
For that, on the previous charge
for building Gold Roger's ship,
your acquittal today had
pretty much been decided.
So then, why did you commit another crime?
That's a load of crap!
We're not the ones who
raided the Judicial Ship!
It was that Spandam guy who did it!
Huh?
No way!
What's got into that disciple of Tom's,
suddenly cracking jokes?
What would CP5, a Government entity,
gain by sinking a Judicial Ship?
What a stupid thing to say!
That's not possible at all!
Cutty Flam, was it?
To start with, we caught you
red-handed on one of the raid ships.
In addition, weren't those raid
ships built by your company?
Ships that would do something like that...
They're... no longer...
...my ships!
Tom tore his handcuffs apart!
Ready!
Tom-san... hit Franky for the first time...
What'd you do that for?!
"They're no longer my ships," you say?
You can say anything but that!
What's wrong with saying that?!
I'm regretting it!
If only those ships didn't exist,
no one would have had to get hurt!
No matter what kind of ship it is,
the act of building it...
...is neither an act of good nor evil!
I don't care what kind of
ships you choose to build,
but even if the ships you built hurt someone,
or even if they destroy the world,
at least the one who created
them must love them!
Their creator mustn't deny them!
Don't blame the ships!
A man should be resolutely proud...
of the ships he created!
Iceberg...
Franky...
Don't interfere in what I'm about to do...
No matter what.
It's the World Government
who pinned the crime on us.
It's also the World Government who judges it.
There's no way that we'll
get cleared of suspicion.
This is it.
It must be really tough for you to see
your innocent ships being used like this.
You must want to beat up
that guy, right, Franky?
Tom-san!
Tom started going on a rampage!
--Ribbit!
--Oh, my God...
Please stop! If you lay
one more finger on him...!
Do you...
...understand the pain he's feeling?!
F-Fire!
They shot him...
Tom-san!
Tranquillizer bullets, huh?
You damn fishman with superhuman
strength! That serves you right!
Tom-san! Why'd you do that?!
Hey, guys! What're you doing?!
Hurry up and capture them!
We'll take everyone from the ferocious
Tom's Workers company to Enies Lobby!
To think that Tom is such a dangerous person...
What the hell is he thinking?!
He really sold his soul to pirates!
He made that many battleships and
waited for an opportunity like this!
You bastards! How dare you
talk like that to Tom-san?!
Stop it.
It's all right.
But...!
Judge...
Hm?
I'll confess to the charge of
making a raid on the Judicial Ship.
What?!
Hey! Tom-san! Don't!
But I have a favor to ask.
Shut up, you stupid fishman!
Who'd listen to a criminal's...
Keep your mouth shut, CP5!
What?!
So, what is the favor?
If I can get one charge eliminated
for our building the sea train...
...I'd like today's charge to be eliminated.
What?
Even if that wish is granted,
you'll just go back to square one.
You'll end up with the crime of building
a ship for the King of the Pirates,
which will result in the maximum penalty.
Yeah, I prefer that.
About assisting that Roger guy...
I'm resolutely proud of it!
How selfish...
To think that he's proud of
assisting the King of the Pirates...
Traitor!
--Ferocious fishman!
--Damn fishman!
Tom-san... Why?!
It's fine.
Listen. Don't blame yourself, okay?
I never thought that the Government
would use force to get the blueprints.
I was at a bit of a disadvantage
due to the matter with Roger.
But even so, you didn't have to--
Don't worry.
Look at the town. Even if my charge
goes back to what it was 14 years ago,
everything is different from then.
This island is full of energy now.
This is just the beginning.
No matter what happens to me,
I can be of help to the town.
My dream has...
...finally... begun to run.
Tom-san!
Iceberg... Franky...
Take care of the blueprints.
Kokoro-san... Yokozuna...
Thanks for everything.
The tranquilizers have finally started working!
Capture those three culprits
for the Judicial Ship raid!
Yes, sir!
Hold it!
--Huh?
--I'm changing the charges.
For the charge of building the pirate ship
for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates,
we'll take shipbuilding
engineer Tom to Enies Lobby.
That is all.
What got into that old geezer?
Oh, well. I don't have
business with his disciples.
Release those two disciples!
Tom-san can no longer be saved.
If it's the World Government we're
up against, there's nothing we can do!
Bear it. Tom-san saved you two!
If you make an enemy of them,
no matter how many lives
you have, it's not enough!
Enies Lobby is the judicial island
owned by the Government.
No criminals taken there...
...have ever returned!
The sea train is ready! We can take him now!
Good!
Kokoro-san...
Hey, you guys! Hurry up and take away...
I...
...this heavy, crazy fishman!
I can't do that!
Ah!
Hey!
Stop it!
Spandam-san's face got bent!
This time, Tom's disciple
started going on a rampage!
--Stop it!
--Ribbit, ribbit!
Capture him! The rest of you, take Tom away!
Fine by me! I won't let you take him away!
You're allowed to shoot him!
Give us Tom-san back!
Are you okay?!
Hurry up and run!
Fire!
Dammit! He got away!
I'll never let that Cutty Flam
brat get away with this!
He is truly a criminal!
Once this case is over,
I'll have him sent to the gallows!
--Spandam-san!
--What do you want?!
I-It's Cutty Flam!
What?!
He came this far after us!
He's standing on the railway with some weapon!
Stay there, Yokozuna.
Ribbit...
Is he stupid or what?
What should we do?
Are you stupid, too?!
Just keep going; give him what he wants.
Don't be concerned about him!
Y-Yes, sir.
Stop, Puffing Tom!
Where are you taking your creator to?!
Ribbit, ribbit...!
I won't let you pass here!
Give Tom-san back to us!
Stop! Sea train!
I see. Your parents abandoned you, huh?
That's so funny!
Hey, you're laughing too hard!
Okay, then! Come resolutely to my place!
Tom-san...
I don't wanna build ships anymore!
I can't love ships that hurt
the people I really care about!
But, Tom-san...
...you're my goal after all!
So I want you to come back
and teach me again...
...because I want to...
...build a dream ship someday, too.
A ship that resolutely and proudly traverses
even uncharted waves at edges of the earth!
A dream ship like that!
What we heard about Tom
is that he had good skills,
but he was a ferocious and intractable
fishman with superhuman strength.
Even if we ask the townspeople,
they just speak ambiguously.
It must be tough to be a disciple that has
to defend such a man, huh, Cutty Flam?
That's not even worth responding to.
You Government people are all crap!
What?! Hey, hey...
At that time, more than 100 people,
including marines and officials,
were severely injured here in Water Seven.
The culprit behind it was you.
You had a lot to answer for, causing the
World Government that much trouble,
but since you were confirmed dead in
the sea train accident on that very day,
your charge was annulled.
Now, we'll take you to
Enies Lobby as a criminal.
You can take your time there
answering my question...
...about the whereabouts
of the blueprints for Pluton.
--Blueno.
--Yeah. It just connected.
When I reported this case to our chief,
he said he wanted to talk
to you right away, so...
Your chief? Hm?
Please go ahead, Chief.
Ouch! It's hot! It's hot! It's hot!
I spilled the coffee!
Dammit! Stupid coffee!
What the hell?
Are you there...
...Cutty Flam?
--Hm?
--It's been a while.
I never thought you'd survived that...
It's hard to believe, but I'm happy to hear it.
Who the hell are you?
During these past eight years...
every time my scars hurt,
I was tormented by an anger that
I couldn't take out on anyone...
...because the culprit who hurt me died!
I'll ask you again! Who the hell are you?!
You don't remember me?
I'm the man who was from Cipher Pol No. 5
and arrested Tom's Workers red-handed for
attacking the Judicial Ship eight years ago!
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end, we can all surely smile
I've been eagerly looking forward to seeing you.
Don't tell me... Is that you, Spanda?!
"M"! You're missing the "M"! It's "Spandam"!
Now, Lucci! Hurry up and bring
them to Enies Lobby already!
--Roger.
--Hey, hold it! Let him go!
--What'd you say?
--Oh, I'm sorry.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Truth Behind Her Betrayal!
Robin's Sorrowful Decision!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!