She sacrificed herself in order to protect
us from an attack by the Government!
Give Tom-san back to us!
So, in short, you're no longer
part of the Straw Hats,
but you still haven't quit being a pirate, huh?
Then...
If you're a pirate, then we'll take you.
...after all, Robin was...
Merry!!
...lying?
Of all people,
That was close...
over the lives of everyone in this world,
Th-Thanks...
I'm not gonna let Robin die!
she chose the lives of the six of you.
Look at that. That big schedule
board got torn apart by a wave.
Let me tell you what I know.
You don't even know how much the
World Government messed up my life!
What's with the power of this ebbing?
The speed of the waves of
this Aqua Laguna are abnormal.
It's all right! Now let's move forward
If you hate the Government that much,
then why are you helping them?!
with the sun always in our hearts
Is that right?! So Sanji went
to the station after that?
One-Sword Style! Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
As power passes through our clasped hands
Robin! Get off the train!
Yep!
Because I have a wish I want to come true
even if I have to give up everything.
So, anyway, no matter what means
we take to follow the sea train,
let's grab hold of our wishes
We'll fight for you no matter
who we're up against!
we can't do anything unless
we find Luffy and Zoro first.
The life I once gave up on...
Okay, got it!
Everyone, please help us out!
The heart that I lost...
Wait!
Guys! We're counting on you!
The dream I could no longer have...
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Paulie-san!
They picked them all up for me.
Robin!
Yeah!
Jerry... Aurora Flicker... Jab!
I was able to make friends who
would believe in someone like me.
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Drop Kick!
We're not safe yet!
This is a waste of time.
Then, your wish is...
Brochette!
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
That the six Straw Hats, excluding me,
can leave this island safely!
Where are you, Straw Hat?!
There's nothing to think about.
Answer us!
Let's sail out right away and follow them!
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
Are you saying, for that, you don't
care if the weapon is brought back?!
Hey! Look! Look!
There's no other way.
You don't care what happens to the world?!
Hmm...
That's right. I don't!
Ah! Pirate lady! Hey, look over there!
There's something there!
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
We're off.
So you didn't make it...
but what you cherish most will be right there
Something?
Of all people,
And if you get into a jam
over the lives of everyone in this world,
It's all right! Now let's move forward
I'll always be there to protect you
she chose the lives of the six of you.
Hey, rope guy.
It's all right! Now let's move forward
Luffy...
with the sun always in our hearts
It was for us...
Please let us use a ship. No, rather than a ship,
Hm? That straw hat...
Chopper! Wake up! We have to find everyone!
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
isn't there any other sea train leaving?
Isn't that your King of the Pirates?
Chopper! Hey, wake up!
let's grab hold of our wishes
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
Hey, hey, he's really
seriously injured, you know...
Puffing Tom is the only sea train in this world.
Right?
and gaze at the light beyond
That idiot!
It's a miraculous ship that is the result
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
of the combined efforts of a team
led by a legendary shipwright.
Hey! Where are you going?!
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
Don't go down to the backstreets!
Do you wanna lose your life?!
Then, let us borrow a ship.
The strongest and fastest one in this town!
So let's grab hold of our wishes
Aqua Laguna is already coming! Come back!
under the same flag-- together, we're one
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Enough already, you idiots!
Didn't you see what just happened?!
One Piece
This is crazy! The pirate
woman went down the stairs!
You were almost pulled out to sea by that wave!
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Well, CP9 is coming soon.
Hey! Come back! Don't go down there!
He's right! There's no way you
can set out to sea right now!
Nico Robin, go on ahead
and get on board. Now!
--Wait!
--Don't go to the backstreets!
Are you stupid?!
Don't follow her!
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
Are you fools?!
Even with the usual Aqua Laguna,
no ship has made it through!
Your chief? Hm?
Paulie-san!
Hey, you two! Hurry up and take her away!
It's not like all of you going
is enough to save her!
Yes, sir!
Please go ahead, Chief.
You saw the collapsing backstreets, didn't you?
But...!
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
It's the sea we're up against!
You'll just end up sharing her fate!
Ouch! It's hot! It's hot! It's hot!
The town that had never been
damaged by Aqua Laguna up until now...
I spilled the coffee!
but what you cherish most will be right there
A government official, marines...
and Robin-chan...
If something happens,
I will handle things myself.
...is now wrecked. How terrible...
Dammit! Stupid coffee!
On top of that, the Aqua Laguna
this year is incomparably huge.
And if you get into a jam
You guys just stay back!
What the hell?
Are you there...
If you put out a ship now, even if you
challenge it with the biggest galleon,
Now... how should I play it?
I'll always be there to protect you
...Cutty Flam?
It's all right! Now let's move forward
I carry a darkness within me
that you guys don't know about.
--Hm?
--It's been a while.
it'll shatter the ship immediately.
I can't let you sail out when I know you'll die.
I never thought you'd survived that...
with the sun always in our hearts
No matter how you look at it, it looks
as if she's being taking in by the authority.
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
Wait until morning.
It's hard to believe, but I'm happy to hear it.
If she wants to run,
and gaze at the light beyond
Once the storm passes, there's no
problem letting you borrow a ship.
she should be able to bring
down all those guys by herself.
She jumped off to the backstreets!
Who the hell are you?
Hey, you guys go to the
evacuation site or someplace.
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
You don't remember me?
We're done searching for missing people.
Does she have her own purpose?
It wouldn't be funny if you got taken out to
sea by the wave while just standing around.
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
I'm the man who was from Cipher Pol No. 5
Oh, is there a reason that she can't run?
Yes, sir!
So let's grab hold of our wishes
If...
and arrested Tom's Workers red-handed for
attacking the Judicial Ship eight years ago!
Hm?
under the same flag-- together, we're one
Sorry to keep you waiting, Robin-chan!
Boy, she makes me nervous.
If we are to wait until morning,
can our wish come true?
So, she's headed for Straw Hat?
Oh, I've been waiting for you, my prince!
One Piece
You bastard! Spanda!
I know Enies Lobby.
"M"! You're missing the "M"! It's "Spandam"!
When I heard it was a Government island,
I remembered something.
I'll be very much looking forward
to your arrival at Enies Lobby.
Is she doing it on purpose because
she wants me to rescue her after all?
Isn't that the place...
"Sanji Barges In! Sea Train Battle in the Storm!"
Isn't that the place where
the Gates of Justice are?
It's all right! Now let's move forward
Now, guys! Hurry up and bring
that criminal here already!
with the sun always in our hearts
Hm?
As power passes through our clasped hands
It's all right! Now let's move forward
Ouch! It's hot! It's hot! It's hot! Stupid lamp!
let's grab hold of our wishes
with the sun always in our hearts
--Roger.
--Click.
Ow... Seriously, what's that man thinking?!
As power passes through our clasped hands
Ow, ow, ow...!
Corgy-san!
Dammit! Let me go, you jerk!
let's grab hold of our wishes
CP9 is here!
No matter what he's thinking,
that train was for Government use,
Let's go.
Hm?
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
--You bastard! Let me go!
--I said let me go!!
so he'll get caught and it'll all be over for him.
--How many times do I have to tell you?!
--I'm saying you guys're scary!
--Whoa... That's Rob Lucci-san.
Hm? That's Galley-La's... Paul...
How intimidating...
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
So, they're CP9...
Don't be thoughtless!
Hey, hold it, you bastards!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Let him go!
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
It looks like there's something
going on between them.
--You guys're scary!
--Let me go, you bastard!
Let me go!
Hm?
Train stations are a place for
people to meet or part ways!
Hey! Where are you taking me?!
You guys're not gonna get away with this!
Ah... I'm sorry.
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
As station employees, we should
quietly watch over them, right?!
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Hey! You only shine for a second?!
Just wait and see! I've got eight
thousand men under me and...
Oh, that's right.
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
If I remember right, you are...
one of the Straw Hats, aren't you?
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
Usopp...!
Quietly, got that?
but what you cherish most will be right there
Yeah, quietly.
What?
And if you get into a jam
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
The train left quite a bit early, huh?
It's all right! Now let's move forward
What?!
I'll always be there to protect you
but what you cherish most will be right there
Ah, yes.
with the sun always in our hearts
All the passengers were already here, so...
It's all right! Now let's move forward
And if you get into a jam
As power passes through our clasped hands
Also...
with the sun always in our hearts
...the sea started getting
rougher than we thought.
I'll always be there to protect you
let's grab hold of our wishes
At this rate, we thought Aqua
Laguna would come very soon,
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
It's all right! Now let's move forward
and gaze at the light beyond
so we moved up the departure time.
with the sun always in our hearts
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
This place is dangerous, too.
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
You should evacuate to
the shipbuilding island soon.
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
and gaze at the light beyond
That lady, too.
So let's grab hold of our wishes
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
Yeah...
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
under the same flag-- together, we're one
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
Hey, you... Once the train
has left, we can't stop it.
So let's grab hold of our wishes
One Piece
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
"The Truth Behind Her Betrayal!
Robin's Sorrowful Decision!"
It's not easy to say this,
under the same flag-- together, we're one
but this Enies Lobby place is...
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
One Piece
Are you crying?
"Nami's Soul Cries Out!
Straw Hat Luffy Makes a Comeback!"
Um... well, I do understand how you feel, but...
The only departure left today is
for government personnel, huh?
We're gonna go after them!
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
Oh, she was angry!
To think they have to travel when Aqua
Laguna is about to hit. Must be a pain.
"Another Sea Train? Rocketman Charges Forth!"
but what you cherish most will be right there
Those idiots from the Government!
They're not gonna get away with this!
It's unbelievable that she
can run someplace like that.
Did you know that some real big shots
are gonna get on today's special train?
And if you get into a jam
Hey, let us borrow a ship!
She's really something else!
What's with you, all of a sudden?
Idiots! This is no time to be impressed!
A huge and strong ship!
I'll always be there to protect you
What're you taking about?
Hey! Come back right away!
Isn't that the place where
the Gates of Justice are?
Are you trying to sail out
when the sea is like this?!
This is what I overheard when the
Navy people were talking earlier,
It's all right! Now let's move forward
You'll be swallowed by the sea!
You idiot!
A sea anemone...
but these big shots seem to have been
on a secret mission in Water Seven
Don't say such stupid stuff when you
don't know how awful Aqua Laguna is!
What's that?
with the sun always in our hearts
Enies Lobby is the
Government-owned judicial island.
We will make it through!
for the past several years,
hiding their true identities.
This is a whole other level from the
type of storm surge you're thinking of.
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
A sea anemone...
What's there is a court in name only.
A sea anemone is coming out
of a chimney. Why a sea anemone?
Secret mission?
and gaze at the light beyond
The sea will now get terribly rough!
Yeah. I don't know what they
were actually doing, though.
Being taken to Enies Lobby itself
is considered to be proof of guilt.
You can no longer sail out! If you did,
you'd basically be sailing to your deaths!
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
A sea anemone?
After passing through this
empty court without stopping,
But Robin, too, laid down her life for us and...
Hiding their true identities?
Then it might be people we know, huh?
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
criminals soon reach huge, cold steel doors.
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
To tell you the truth, I kinda
think I know who they are.
These doors are called the Gates of Justice.
One Piece
Once criminals go through them,
What?! Who are they?!
they won't see the sunlight ever again--
they're doors of despair.
Ah...! Hey, wait, reindeer! Not you, too!
Zoro!
This is because there are only
two places that you can reach
--Do you think I'm wrong?
--What?! From the backstreets?!
"The Steam Whistle Forces Friends Apart!
The Sea Train Starts to Run"
after sailing out from the
harbor beyond these gates.
I sometimes see those guys
having secret conversations
"Navy"
in the corner at Blueno's bar.
One is the greatest military force for
justice in the world-- Navy headquarters.
But that's not enough reason
to suspect them, you know.
Hey! Where are you taking me?!
You guys're not gonna get away with this!
But despite the fact that they don't
work much, they're quite prosperous, right?
The other is Impel Down,
the large, deep-sea prison,
Just wait and see! I've got eight
thousand men under me and...
Yeah, that's true.
Nico Robin made a deal with
CP9 by giving up everything...
where torture rooms and gallows stand
side by side, that holds vicious prisoners
They often take the first-class cars.
That was close...
Right? In any case, we'll know who they
are when they get on the sea train later.
who once ran amok all over the world.
Usopp...!
Th-Thanks...
...for a wish that couldn't come
true if she was with you guys.
Paulie-san! Thank you very much!
In other words,
That the six Straw Hats, excluding me,
can leave this island safely!
Enies Lobby is a judicial institution
that criminals are just dumped into
Good work on your
long-term mission, sirs and madam!
We almost got dragged into the sea.
I bet this will be the talk of
the whole town tomorrow.
without being shown any mercy.
Look at that. That big schedule
board got torn apart by a wave.
Lucci-san, here is your coat.
I see...
For that, I don't care if the weapon is
brought back or the world is destroyed.
This looks pompous.
Isn't that right?!
Stop it.
Nothing like this has ever happened before.
Yes, sir. R-Right away!
Robin! Wait! We'll fight for you
no matter who we're up against!
Robin's got a bounty on her head.
No matter where she's taken,
she'll see hell beyond that point!
This isn't working! The wind is too strong!
This isn't a game. Stay focused!
The fire isn't going out at all!
Each moment we sit here talking,
she gets closer to the Gates of Justice!
Robin!
If people are still inside,
they'll be done for if this keeps up!
What's with the power of this ebbing?
Everyone, get on the train!
There's no way we can wait until morning!
Everyone, get on the sea train!
Get ready to leave for Enies Lobby!
It's already this strong
when it's only approaching?
The speed of the waves of
this Aqua Laguna are abnormal.
I said let me go!
Who the hell are they?
If you know that much,
I've got only one thing to say.
Hey... Is the sea train Robin is on okay?
Even if the sea were calm
and you were able to sail out,
It'll probably get through the stormy
area right before the storm surge hits.
Iceberg-san...! Paulie-san!
In any case...
you shouldn't go there.
"Sorry to cause you trouble until the end"?
Don't forget that you guys
yourselves are pirates.
Unless it gets hit directly, it'll make
it through most of the big waves.
Is he trying to cause us trouble
even after he left the group?
A little further to the right! Spray water there!
Pirate lady! You're so amazing!
As you said, Enies Lobby is the front door
that leads to the World Government's hub.
Hey, are you Nami?
Nami... Oh, no...
Run more water!
How foolish!
Hm?
A little bit longer...
An inconspicuous letter
was left in the station plaza.
Naturally, battle lines are
drawn up taking that into account.
You won't make it back in time!
I have to... treat her... right... away...
We're okay here! Go help treat the injured!
It's probably from one of your friends.
Just look offshore! The wave
is almost here already!
No pirate would think to get back
crew members taken to that island...
Okay, got it!
A letter...? From whom?
Is there anyone left inside?!
I'm surprised that you found such a small thing.
Watch your step over there!
Then, it's not that Robin doesn't like us?!
...because it's crystal clear what would happen.
Here! It was left here in
an inconspicuous manner.
Are you trying to pick a fight with
the hub of the World Government?!
That's right!
Oh, shoot! They're gonna die!
I'm so glad!
Hurry! Give them treatment!
They've got terrible burns!
"Nami-san! Please read this!
(Those other than Nami-san don't
have to read it, since they're idiots.)"
They can't make it back anymore!
What?! He turned into a raccoon dog!
Hey! What're we gonna do with this reindeer?!
That idiot...!
He turned into a raccoon dog!
Hey, he turned into a raccoon dog!
Him, too! He saved their lives!
H-He's right! You should give up!
So, Chopper, we have to find
Luffy and the others right away
What does it say?
Y-You're right. Hey! Give me a hand!
Zoro! Zoro! Can you hear me?! It's me!
Hmm... hold on a sec. The first half
is just a pointless love letter, so...
You can't sail out until morning
because of Aqua Laguna!
and go rescue Robin!
Okay! Let's go find them!
Even if you go after them, you'll get killed!
There's no chance of you guys surviving!
She said it's a love letter.
The third man has appeared.
Where are they?
Chopper?
Oh, boy...
I don't know. That's why
we're going to look for them.
Luffy...
No... Judging from the situation,
the third man is actually...
All right...! I'll do my best!
Then, we'll...
He got his butt whipped...
...steal a ship and go!
Whoa! He turned into a gorilla!
This is it. I can't go any further.
We're gonna sail out now!
Hm? Why are you looking at me like that?
So, in short, you're no longer
part of the Straw Hats,
You guys, wait.
Here is the important part.
but you still haven't quit being a pirate, huh?
I don't care if you go after Nico Robin.
Our friends are waiting!
P.S. Since I saw Robin-chan on the
11 o'clock train, I'll get on board, too.
Don't stand in our way!
But the sea train for government
personnel will depart at 11 tonight.
If you're a pirate, then we'll take you.
--Kalifa!
--Yep.
Well... this is just my guess,
What?! Sanji-kun got on that train?!
E-Even the wave got angry, too!
And this ship...
but it's highly possible
that they'll take that train.
And... Usopp?!
You didn't take it down yet, huh?
In other words, Nico Robin will, too.
Also, a big thug with a ducktail... Who's that?
--Wha...
--Does he wanna fight?
Hey! Don't you dare touch her!
What?
Boy, that scared me.
After that train, the sea train will
be suspended for the time being,
There's no one like that except Franky.
Fine. I'll take you on!
Right, there's no one else.
The fourth man... And to think
that the fifth man is Franky...
since Aqua Laguna is coming soon.
Then... that means...
Poor Paulie-san...
Yeah...
What're you doing?! Hey! Are you listening?!
If you miss that train,
you can't sail out, of course,
Hold it, you guys!
Maybe it'd be better if he flatly gives up...
which means there's no
means to leave this island.
What's with you guys?!
Although it was an assumed identity,
we are recognized shipwrights in this town.
Oh, no! This is bad! What time is it now?!
Um... also, this was with that letter.
Kokoro-san!
It's you who's wrong here, Straw Hat.
Luffy!
--10:30.
--What?! We've only got 30 minutes left!
Paulie is right, you idiot.
Hey, can't you do something?
Stop the sea train for a while.
There should be at least one
transponder snail in the sea train.
Shut up! It's none of--
You should listen when we say
it's no good no matter what you do.
None of my business... huh?
Well... Its destination, Enies Lobby,
So I'll get in touch with you as soon as I can.
Well, listen. If we let you be,
you're gonna risk your lives, aren't you?
What the hell are you doing there?!
is an island off-limits to those
other than Government personnel.
So what?! Just leave her alone!
She's not even your ship!
I want you to always keep this portable
transponder snail I got in town with you.
The engine driver is also from the
Government. He won't listen to me.
Look. If there exists a ship that
can get through that Aqua Laguna,
This will release the water, huh?
N... Nami! Are you there behind me?!
That's right. Think of it as
your dear beloved San--
Oh, no...!
Wait! Don't do anything stupid! Hey!
Then... the only way left is
for me to go to the station
I see. So he'll call this one.
it could only be a sea train
built by a legendary man.
Well, hey, listen!
and somehow persuade Robin directly...
--Chopper!
--Hm?
Then he foresaw where Nico Robin
was going to be? That's amazing!
"Nami-san! Please read this!
(Those other than Nami-san don't
have to read it, since they're idiots.)"
At any rate, that pigeon guy sent me flying
But it's not here right now!
That's why we're trying to go in a ship!
I'll tell you the directions in which Luffy
and Zoro flew, so search those areas!
and I flew right into this gap.
Yeah!
If you find them, tell them to
come to the station immediately.
If you're prepared to die, then come with me.
Okay. Got it.
For the time being, Robin has Sanji-kun.
Hey! Stop it!
Hey... guys...!
We'll definitely go to Enies Lobby, too!
I'll give you a ride... on a sea train!
Ah! Paulie-san! You're okay!
Give this girl and her friend a hand.
Don't fool around at a critical time like this!
What?!
G-Give them a hand, you said, Paulie?!
While you've been taking your
sweet time, Robin was taken away!
They're the culprits who
tried to kill Iceberg-san!
Don't worry.
Geez... I can't even have a smoke here.
I'll carry you guys for a little bit longer.
We should restrain these two!
Robin intends to die for us!
Lucci-san and Kaku-san are still missing and...
Is that right?! So Sanji went
to the station after that?
The assassination culprits
are not the Straw Hats!
Yep!
They're innocent!
We were tricked by the real culprits,
and so we falsely accused them!
Usopp is on the same train, too. I'm glad...
--Who's that?
--Beats me.
So, anyway, no matter what means
we take to follow the sea train,
--What...?
--I don't know the true
identity of those masked men,
You fools! What're you doing?!
we can't do anything unless
we find Luffy and Zoro first.
but the Straw Hats fought against them for us!
Merry!!
Besides the criminals,
everyone here is wearing a uniform!
As a matter of fact, Iceberg-san and I
are still alive because of them, right?
Okay, got it!
I'm not mistaken about the direction
they flew to. So search those areas.
She sacrificed herself in order to protect
us from an attack by the Government!
G-Get him!
Everyone, please help us out!
Guys! We're counting on you!
So it turns out this way anyway, huh?
You don't have to look for Lucci and Kaku.
There's no place for me to go or go back to.
Yeah!
Move back! It's gonna collapse!
We may not see them again.
Leave it to us!
Yes, we are. I'll never see you guys again.
Dammit!
What?! You know what happened to them?!
You idiot! Run!
When she knew that she was going
to be killed if she was taken in!
I thought I had a good plan...
They're visiting their hometowns.
That can't be!
Why, during an emergency like this?!
Dammit! Isn't there anything we can do?!
"Operation Play Innocent"...
Just go find the Straw Hat!
Now, how should I quietly infiltrate?
Then...
Hey, you, shameless girl!
Hm?
...after all, Robin was...
That again... Hey, stop calling me that!
What?! S-Sanji!
...lying?
Hold it!
Whoa! What a crazy storm outside!
You're going to the station, right?
I'll show you the way.
Yeah... Thanks...
Yes!
We're not gonna let you pass through here.
Paulie-san! Hey!
Iceberg-san has recovered consciousness!
Good...
Is what you just told us true?!
Twins, huh?
Collier Shoot!
Quit your jabbering and help them already!
Really?! That's great!
Are you trying to hurt Galley-La's name?!
What a relief! He's okay!
Don't worry!
N-No, foreman!
Who are you?!
Iceberg-san!
Collier...
Ahhh!
We apologize!
It's all thanks to that reindeer!
We're sorry!
Tell us what to do! We'll help you guys!
But I heard that he's a pet of the Straw Hats.
...Frit!
I'm not gonna let Robin die!
Bring Yagaras out! Open the cage!
Look at that wave!
Yeah!
What the hell is that? It really is
several times bigger than usual!
Visiting their hometowns, huh?
Hey! This one, too! The woman woke up!
Hey! This is seriously bad!
Sanji! Why are you on the sea train?!
Pirate woman! Give up and run already!
It's probably not good to
give them all the details.
Reindeer!
I wanna ask you the same question.
Wh-What're we gonna do?
We don't have to make them
feel the pain we felt, right?
Should we make her tell us the
Straw Hats' whereabouts now?
But she's severely injured.
And she's a woman, too.
Ow! I'm being torn apart!
But that's...
You aren't coming out!
How'd you get in there, Zoro?!
How about it, you... Well, I don't know
what your name is, but you over there...
Iceberg-san! You shouldn't move around yet!
Owwww! Don't pull me!
Oh, what a load of crap, you jerk!
Hold it.
Hm?
Where do you think you're going?
Hm? Whoa!
Don't move!
There you go, transponder snails!
Guys... give us some space.
I saw his kick earlier.
Phew, all right! Geez,
there are several of them here.
What're we gonna do?!
The huge wave is almost here already!
He's no ordinary civilian!
I wanna talk to this woman alone.
I wonder if this is also a communications room.
Chopper! I'm counting on you!
"What're we gonna do"? How should I know?
If you say...
Those government officials from the car earlier
had only stupid stuff, like masks and costumes!
Hm? Wait a sec. Are you carrying
the Kitetsu by any chance?
Yep! I'll be sure to bring them!
...something like that so openly...
I can finally contact Nami-san using them.
What? One of your swords?
Yes, I am. How'd you know?
...you'll make me blush.
So you two are... pirate friends, huh?
That wasn't a compliment!
For just that one, I can tell,
since it's a cursed sword.
Former friends.
He's mocking us!
Who the hell are you?
Hey! Let Lucci-san know that
a suspicious man infiltrated!
I'm Franky, demolition worker and the
face of the Water Seven underworld.
So you were carrying it
for me, Chopper? Thanks.
Let me hold it in my hand! Hurry up!
Wait!
Hurry up and run!
So you're Franky?! You damn bastard!
Climb up to a high place! Go to a higher place!
This isn't something that
we need to bother CP9 with.
How dare you give our long-nose
a terrible time, then?!
Oh, no, this is it! They're not gonna make it!
Hello! Guys!
I wonder what he wants to
talk alone with her about.
How many pieces do you want
me to cut you into, you jerk?!
Pirate woman!
No matter how violent the suspicious man is,
Beats me.
You're gonna be swallowed!
Ah, wait, wait, wait...
Ow! What'd you do that for?!
Hello!
there's no need to fear, because in this car...
Ah, Sanji, hold on a sec. All sorts
of things happened after that.
Quit standing around! Lucci-san and
the others may still be inside!
Hello! Luffy!
You son of a bitch!
Just you wait till I get untied!
Whoa! It's smoky!
Give us a hand, you idiots!
Aqua Laguna is here!
...you've got me!
Stop saying things like that!
Zoro! Sanji!
Oh, that's right. Hey!
Jerry-san!
Well, he saved the Merry once.
Yeah. Sorry!
Usopp, come back to us.
Everyone, please shout with me!
Well...
Oh, that's right... The Merry is...
I'm a champion on a South Blue
island where karate is popular.
Okay, got it! Guys! Got that?!
First... I'm sorry.
Yeah!
Hello! Luffy!
We falsely accused you of the crime.
Hey, hey, wait a sec!
This is no time to start moping!
I'll clear up the misunderstanding later.
That's right. I'm a boxing champion!
Zoro!
Sanji!
What is this...?
Anyway, mister, please untie me!
Then, do karate.
I wanna talk about Nico Robin.
Usopp, come back to us.
Who'd untie you?! You should stay
captured for the rest of your life!
You can make a comment like
that after you see my punches.
Do you know something?!
Did that woman change after
you guys came to this town?
You bastard! How dare you talk
like that when I asked you nicely?!
Goodbye.
That's cruel!
Turn into that canal!
That's a shortcut to the station!
Yes, suddenly.
Jerry... Aurora Flicker... Jab!
Stop it...! You guys!
After she went out to town,
she suddenly disappeared,
If we don't hurry up, they'll find us, right?!
and by this morning, she was the
suspect of your attempted assassination.
J-Jerry-san! The enemy is behind you!
You're getting on my nerves!
--What'd you say?!
--Shut up, both of you!
Hm? He escaped?
When my friends finally found her,
Just untie me already!
Hey, kid! Just because I'm so tall,
Don't order me around!
We still have twenty minutes
before the train departs.
she said she would no longer come back to us.
Arrrrgh! Stop it already!
don't think that I'm at a
disadvantage in this small car.
Don't go, Robin.
We didn't know what was going on.
To think that you're sacrificing yourself...
So we came here tonight
This is the first time I've been warned
by someone from between their legs.
We're never gonna let that happen!
Ah... Captain T-Bone...
in order to ask her directly again
why she's leaving the ship.
Yagara-chan! Please! Go faster!
My boxing rather puts me at
an advantage in a narrow space.
Aqua Laguna is already so close!
To make my wish come true...
This is a yoga style!
Yoga one, two! One, two!
A wish that can never come true if I'm with you!
What is this?
Your reach has gotten shorter!
So I made it look like, and then...
What is this wish that can never
come true if she's with us...?
Screw...
The last departure at 11 PM...
...Drop Kick!
Let me tell you what I know.
Now you're ignoring the rules of boxing?!
...from Blue Station,
Water Seven, to Enies Lobby...
This is it!
This is a waste of time.
It was probably when you lost
sight of Nico Robin the first time.
--Ouch!
--Ow!
Franky is with them, too, you said?
Brochette!
Stay here quietly.
CP9...
You bastards! Treat us more nicely, you idiots!
Yes... but the sea train has already departed.
The Government's operation
was already in progress.
He's right, you idiots!
All the craftsmen are also looking for
Straw Hat and the other one, but...
You damn Government dumbasses!
Hm? Well, that's...
There is, of course, a reason
for that woman's actions.
There's no limit to their strength
when they know it's okay to save her!
First, the one who leads Government
officials in car #7, the very last car, is...
Due to the approaching storm surge,
But before I tell you about that,
the departure time has been moved
up and the train will leave soon.
I want you to know that Nico
Robin and I both have a means
Ahhh! What the hell?! He broke the buildings!
Dammit! It's already leaving?
to bring back the ancient weapon
that could destroy the world.
In order of increasing strength,
Whoa...
the one who leads forty
marines in car #5 is T-Bone,
Underground!
Destroy the world?
This warehouse has been abandoned
for more than eight years.
That's right.
Our mission is mostly completed, huh?
a Navy Headquarters'
Captain and former knight.
When it comes to the sea train, it's been
untouched for more than twelve years.
A problem occurred in our plan.
Restrain yourself from making such a
frivolous comment until we get there.
Next, the one standing by in car #4 is Wanze,
a martial artist from Cipher Pol No. 7,
Everyone, come to the bedroom right away.
--Let's go, Chopper!
--Yeah!
Zoro!
Idiot.
Don't shoot Iceberg yet.
It may no longer run, though!
Stay back, Chopper!
who is also the head steward on this trip.
Pardon me.
One-Sword Style! Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
Hey! That would be a problem!
And the one standing by in car #3 is
Mr. Nero, the newest member of CP9.
Now, you get it, Nico Robin?
If you miss that train,
there's no means to leave this island.
The blueprints you guys were after are fakes.
Hey, hey, wait for me.
Please! Let me make it in time!
Even if you go in a rush, you can't
get inside without the keys.
Even if I am to be killed, I won't give
those blueprints to the Government!
Ahh! What the hell are they?!
Hm...? What the heck?
Here we go, Nami!
It's open, huh?
But if you're sniffing around
the Poneglyphs on another front
and helping the Government as well,
Whoooa! There it is!
Anyway, though we are escorting criminals,
there's no possibility of a raid.
Franky... Are you safe?
What the hell is this?
then I have to stop you right here, right now.
Rumble! Jumping Point!
This looks cool!
I'm not seeking the Poneglyphs
in order to bring the weapon back.
Amazing!
But just in case, we have military
power ready in each car, so...
Hold on to me, Zoro!
I'm warning you, this is a crazy train.
I just want to know the history, that's all.
Its name is Rocketman.
Such a claim doesn't mean anything!
Straw Hat!
We can't even allow passengers to be on board.
Ahh... The backstreets are...!
Roronoa!
We're on your side! Come out!
I told you, didn't I?
Rocketman!
Luffy!
It sounds fast!
Where are you?!
Over... and over again...
Dammit!
Cool!
Straw Hat! Where are you?!
Hello! Where are you?!
Even if you don't intend to do so...
What's up with that face?
Please come out!
Foreman! It must be hard even to move, right?
Why don't you take a little break?
That shark head is attached as a joke.
Weapons hurt people despite your intentions!
Zoro! Sanji!
Idiot! This is nothing.
Hurry up and find those two!
They can even hurt those
who mean a lot to you!
Hm?
Usopp, come back to us.
Ice pops!
Yes, sir!
Luffy! They're gonna take Robin away!
That which hurts people doesn't
necessarily have malicious intent.
Hey, look at that! It's them!
Did someone let Iceberg-san
know what's going on?
Straw Hat... So you really were okay.
Two men went to give a report to him.
Answer me! Where are you?!
It's just like what the pirate girl said.
If that simple curiosity of
wanting to know the history
So you brought them here, Kokoro-san?
leads to the destruction of the world,
Looks like you survived, huh, Iceberg?
you should die right here,
right now, Nico Robin!
What're you doing here?
Where are you going? Iceberg-san...
The fact that we both are here means
that we were thinking the same thing.
Even after you saw the Ohara devils' fate,
Hm?
I wonder what actions
Luffy and the others took...
you still want to chase
after the world's history?!
Roronoa!
Wow! You did it!
We just can't help giving idiots a hand, can we?
Straw Hat! Answer if you hear us!
Don't talk like you know
everything about Ohara!
Looks like no one will make it here in time.
They'll be safe, since they
got to the Great Bridge.
Luffy!
As big as the wave may be, it can't reach there.
I repeat. The last train will depart soon.
Zoro! Where are you?!
You guys're amazing!
You don't even know how much the
World Government messed up my life!
Use it. I've finished servicing it.
Good going, you guys!
Water and coal have been loaded
and it's storing the steam right now.
Food... you say?
That's right. I want meat! Meat!
If you hate the Government that much,
then why are you helping them?!
So you were getting it ready for us, pops?!
Dammit! Th-Those bastards!
I want you to bring all the
meat you can gather. Hurry up!
Oops.
But why are we being slave-driven like this?
They're never gonna get away with this!
Wait to rejoice until you survive the ride.
After all, this was a failure built
before Puffing Tom was completed.
No, this isn't for that girl.
Because I have a wish I want to come true
even if I have to give up everything.
Let's do our best for Paulie-san,
No matter how much you tune it up,
its steam engine can't control the speed.
who's devoted to her even after being dumped!
I got stuck...
Yeah!
It was a tragedy that I slipped.
I can't guarantee your lives.
In any case, she must be really hungry.
There're two conditions that
CP9 forced on me in this town.
Ahh! It's come this far!
Okay! Thanks, Ice pops!
She's a growing girl, I bet!
What happened to the Straw Hats?!
Dammit!
Did they get swallowed by Aqua Laguna?!
One is to pin the assassination
on the Straw Hats.
All right! Let's go!
I got stuck...
Guys! Get on board!
This one, too. There really
aren't any stores open right now.
The other is to turn myself in
to the Government and obey them.
Granny! We're leaving as soon as Nami comes!
No, look at that!
Luffy! Zoro!
Ooops!
Oh, that's right. How about the kitchen
at the station's employee dining hall?
Sanji! Come out!
Luffy! Are you okay?
Paulie-san!
If you do that, you'll die, too.
We can't take the backstreets.
I bet the area is already flooded.
You've been shaky on your feet for a while.
Let's go rescue Robin!
Why do you accept such conditions
after evading them for 20 years?
He probably bled too much.
Straw Hat!
Then we have no choice but
to search this area, right?
I kinda feel weak. If only we
had some meat or something...
Roronoa!
Dammit!
In this lone instance,
CP9 has been given permission
--But--
--Let's go!
You think that girl would forgive us
if we went back empty-handed?!
to exercise Buster Call against the Straw Hats.
Hurry! This way!
Where are you guys?
Buster Call?
Wait!
You don't have to go to a place like
that, right? Why don't you eat here?
What about this way?!
It's an emergency order to
summon five of the vice admirals
Hello!
That's right! You're starving, right?
Straw Hat!
from Navy Headquarters and
ten battleships to one place.
Zoro!
There's no way I could eat that much!
We still can't find them here.
What?!
Couldn't they be in one of the backstreets?
Once you've been targeted by the
national war-class military power,
Sorry it took so long!
--Nami...
--Hey! What're you doing?!
If that's the case, the area
might already be flooded.
Rain...
nothing will remain of you.
We're not safe yet! Run!
Run to the shipbuilding island!
This isn't good.
Hurry up and get on board, you idiot!
It'd be dangerous to go
there to look for them, too.
When the strong winds are already
interfering with my sense of smell...
Wow, amazing!
Normally, in the Navy, this authority
only belongs to the three admirals
Dammit! Straw Hat! Roronoa!
So this is a sea train, too?
Hurry!
Whoa... I never knew there was
another one in a place like this.
The Great Bridge is gonna collapse!
and the head of the Navy, the fleet admiral.
I'm surprised!
But this time,
Where have you been, Nami?!
Who was it that said we didn't have time?!
through the admiral Aokiji,
What's that stuff?!
CP9 was given the authority
to exercise it just this once.
--Meat and beverages.
--I'm sorry that I complained.
Say, we've been calling out this much,
and yet there's no answer.
If I didn't accept the conditions,
Buster Call was going to be exercised on us.
Lucci-san! Since the waves
are getting quite high,
Here we go.
Could it be...
If you can get on the railway after going out
Stop saying stupid stuff! We'll just do our best!
we're departing a bit early.
When I heard the name Aokiji, I gave up.
to the sea via a canal, that'll be
a success for the time being.
--Could it cause you any trou--
--No. Depart.
Where are you guys? Luffy... Zoro...
I was always able to make good
my escape for the past 20 years
Coo coo!
Don't worry. I'm more experienced
in operating it than you are.
Yes, sir. Well, then...
You guys wouldn't be taken out
by a leopard man like that, right?
Although I lived on this island for five years...
You take it easy and rest here.
because I had nothing to protect...
We finally know why Robin left us.
Because I could betray people
and use them as a shield.
...I don't even feel like it's hard
to say goodbye to this place.
Sorry.
Chimney and Gonbe should be playing
around there. Please take care of them.
But I really can't do that any longer.
What a wave...
Where are you, Straw Hat?!
Yeah... Unbelievable...
This is the shipbuilding island!
Answer us!
Yeah.
Well, I bet he's fine.
Even staying here doesn't seem safe.
The life I once gave up on...
Hm?
Just wait, Robin.
Look! The tide is ebbing again.
The heart that I lost...
We're talking about a guy who
survived being hit by a sea train...
I'm coming to rescue you with
Luffy and the others without fail!
It's just natural. It'll keep coming back.
The dream I could no longer have...
They picked them all up for me.
The second wave... The third wave...
Just like the one we just saw!
On top of that, we have the
King of the Pirates and his friends.
I was able to make friends who
would believe in someone like me.
Hey! Did you just hear a steam whistle?!
Let us evacuate to a higher place, too!
Straw Hat!
Yeah. But it's strange.
It's not the departure time yet.
Then, your wish is...
Hey, what's the matter?!
Ah, Paulie-san! Please take a look!
They are...
That the six Straw Hats, excluding me,
can leave this island safely!
The Franky Family!
Seriously... That was reckless!
But there are no public passengers.
Thanks. You saved us, rope guy.
The more the water ebbs,
It's possible that they'd leave
earlier due to the weather!
At a busy time like this...!
I was shocked! So that's Aqua Laguna...
the bigger the returning wave becomes.
Are you saying, for that, you don't care
if the weapon is brought back?!
Please... take us with you!
Hurry up! We can now see
the station in front of us!
I still can't stop shaking.
If you see how the tide ebbs,
you can tell the scale of the storm surge.
You don't care what happens to the world?!
Please stop! Sea train!
I heard from the Galley-La people
that you're going to Enies Lobby!
If a big one like that had hit us every year,
That's right. I don't!
I'm being blown away!
this island would be long gone.
Now, if we try to see how much lower
the water level goes this year...
Our Bro, Franky, was taken
in by the Government!
This year's Aqua Laguna is different.
Today's last departure
You guys are really crazy.
I'm surprised you survived.
We want to go after them... but we can't
get through Aqua Laguna by ourselves!
Enough of that nonsense!
from Blue Station,
Water Seven, to Enies Lobby...
Look at that, Chimney.
Ah! Monster Granny.
So you were on this island?
It's the World Government you're up against.
Whoa! This is incredible!
The train's leaving. Be seated.
It doesn't matter who it is!
Of course! If we stayed in the middle
of the sea like that, we'd drown!
I couldn't pull the trigger.
...is now departing.
We're gonna get Bro back!
We'd give up our lives for him!
Ah! Pirate guy!
You were incredible! Like, wham!
Please!
Help us out! Straw Hat!
I no longer have a reason to live!
The sea looks as if it dried up.
Yeah, I know.
Please! Bro is in danger!
Leave me here!
Why do I have to listen to you?
Even I haven't seen a sight
like this in the past few decades.
Give me a break! Do you know
what you've been doing to us?!
Are you trying to suffocate me?!
Of all people,
You made me live then when I wanted to die.
This idiot lost consciousness
while holding on to me.
over the lives of everyone in this world,
That's your crime.
she chose the lives of the six of you.
Can the tide ebb this much?
Oh...? Come to think of it, Zoro,
It was for us...
I've never seen something like this before.
why were you also being chased by the wave?
We do!
Now that I might have the weapon's
blueprints taken away by them,
There's no place for me to go or go back to.
Were you in the lower side of town?
We're swallowing our pride and begging you!
What? W-Well, not particularly...
Just how big of a wave is coming this time?
So let me stay on this ship.
I don't have the right to criticize her, though.
We want to save Bro!
He was stuck in a chimney.
The backstreets are gonna
be completely swallowed up.
Oh, I see... Then I guess
we have no choice... Okay.
There aren't any people
in the backstreets, right?
Luffy!
Stuck in a chimney?
Don't worry. She isn't a bad person.
If there are, they'll die instantly.
Hey! What's wrong?!
You're so clumsy, Zoro!
What'd you have to do to be in that situ...
Good...
Are you in any position to be laughing
at others?! You both are super clumsy!
So Robin didn't betray us after all.
--Get on.
--What?!
Hurry!
It couldn't be...!
Could the Rio Poneglyph be...?!
Ah... Then what happened to
Sanji and Uso... I mean, Sanji?
The roar of the sea... has stopped.
I'd better gather everyone
immediately and let them know!
Oh?
Straw Hat...
Which means I, too,
Yeah... There're lots of things I need
to tell you. You listen, too, Zoro.
have to guide the text on those
Poneglyphs that I read in the past...
Thanks, Iceberg-san!
Hey, Luffy!
Wait! Straw Hat and the others were beaten!
Grandma! Look, look! There's something there!
Hm?
Oh, it'll be fine.
What do you think you can do now?!
...to the end of the Grand Line... to Raftel...
Thank you!
"Now"?!
Is that right?
There's something between two houses!
It starts now! Luffy and the others are fine.
We're deeply indebted to you!
This is my big chance.
Hurry up!
It'd take a lot more than that to take them out.
Hey! Look! Look!
Ah! But we don't have to get on the train.
We're gonna get Robin back!
With Buster Call, we can urgently summon
Hmm...
Hm?
When unsure, anyone can be weak.
Kokoro-san!
five of the Navy Headquarters'
vice admirals as well as ten battleships.
We'll jump out to the sea using our
King bulls at the same time you do.
Oh, you're that pirate girl.
There's no limit to their strength
when they know it's okay to save her!
Ah! Pirate lady! Hey, look over there!
There's something there!
So all you need to do is to let us
hold on to the end of the train.
This is thanks to Aokiji for giving us,
CP9, the authority to exercise it.
King bulls?
Thanks for letting us go with you!
Well then, see you later!
Something?
Chopper! Chopper!
Just what is it you're going on about, Chimney?
Don't you think, Funkfreed?
Let's go!
Robin!
Yeah!
Hey...
Chopper! Wake up! We have to find everyone!
Robin! How are you feeling?
What's with this dried-up sea?!
Nico Robin, the woman whom the World
Government has been pursuing for 20 years,
Chopper! Hey, wake up!
Hey, hey, he's really
seriously injured, you know...
has fallen straight into the hands of us, CP9.
Wake up! Chopper!
All right! We can go rescue Bro!
At the same time, along with her,
we're taking in that detestable Cutty Flam,
Chopper...
--Yeah!
--Hurry up!
You go join Luffy and the others and tell
them everything that just happened...
that disciple of Tom's who
has the blueprints for Pluton.
I-It started moving.
...without leaving a single word out.
Dammit! Those damn officials!
Only two people hold the key to
the ancient weapon in this vast world.
What're you gonna do?
We'll part ways here for a bit.
How is this?
Well, don't worry. I won't do anything reckless.
And these two are on the sea train
headed to me right now...
Okay! Well then, let's go, shall we?!
We're here! Thanks, Yagara-chan!
The military force strong enough to
destroy the world is headed to me.
Go down the stairs
through the middle entrance!
What's the matter?
Got it!
I wonder... if Robin doesn't like us anymore.
Robin! Don't go!
Luffy...
Chopper...
Hm?
Remember one thing.
Hm? That straw hat...
Hey, you! Who are you?!
Isn't that your King of the Pirates?
It's dangerous! Stay back!
When a woman lies...
Right?
...a real man forgives her.
That idiot!
Now then...
Robin! Get off the train! We'll fight
for you no matter who we're up against!
For today's last service to
Enies Lobby, departing at 11 PM,
Just wait, Robin-chan!
Hey! Where are you going?!
Your prince on a white horse is coming now!
Luffy!
Don't go down to the backstreets!
please board from the second floor
lobby due to the raised water level.
Zoro!
Backstreets?! Hey, someone! Stop that woman!
Where are you guys?!
Are you saying that Nico Robin
sacrificed herself for us?
Now... pirates! Don't go
getting thrown off, okay?!
--Okay, let's go check them out!
--Yeah!
That's right.
I can't get out...!
And the cook and Usopp are on the same train?
Since this involves a secret operation,
Wait!
What do you wanna do, Captain?
you're forbidden to see them board.
Do you wanna lose your life?!
Oh, darn...
The train...!
Aqua Laguna is already coming! Come back!
There's nothing to think about.
Now departing Water Seven for Enies Lobby...
Wait!
Here comes the sea train Rocketman!
You were chased after for the past 20 years.
Let's sail out right away and follow them!
I'm surprised that you gave up now.
Robin!
All right! Depart!
There's no other way.
Robin!!
We're gonna go...! To get everything back!
Bingo...
We're off... to rescue Robin!
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end, we can all surely smile
Then, it's not that Robin
doesn't like us anymore?!
Luffy! Luffy... Luffy!
Hey! Let us borrow a ship!
A strong and fast one!
Go! Rocketman! Don't be
beaten by Aqua Laguna!
What's this letter? No way!
Sanji-kun is on the sea train?!
Oh, hey, Nami! Well, I got completely
stuck when I got sent flying.
No. You can't make it through this storm.
That's right! We'll all go and rescue her!
Hey, Luffy. Somehow,
there are weird guys in here.
Then Sanji is with Robin right now?
Even if you leave now,
there's no chance you'd survive!
Okay, let's go! Where are Luffy and Zoro?!
Straw Hat! Thank you for helping us,
the fifty members of the Franky Family!
Listen! Robin was lying to us!
Yeah. We have to hurry up
and go to Enies Lobby, too.
It doesn't matter!
Our friends are waiting for us!
We have to hurry up and find them.
What? She was lying?
There's only thirty minutes left
before the sea train departs.
Where did Luffy and Zoro go?
This is good. Everyone here
has the same enemy!
She sacrificed herself in order to protect us!
There's one way-- just one way--
to get through this Aqua Laguna.
Just wait, Robin!
We can't do anything without those two.
We must find them! We must!
We'll fight for you no matter
who we're up against!
Let's go! We'll protect Robin!
We'll work together and beat them up!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Another Sea Train? Rocketman Charges Forth!"
"Rescue Our Friends! A Bond
Among Foes Sworn with Fists!"
"Nami's Soul Cries Out!
Straw Hat Luffy Makes a Comeback!"
"The Steam Whistle Forces Friends Apart!
The Sea Train Starts to Run"
"Sanji Barges In! Sea Train Battle in the Storm!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!