Well, then...
If you're prepared to die, then come with me.
Long-nose!
Although we got in fights back in
town both with the Franky Family
Here goes! Try dodging this!
I'll give you a ride... on a sea train!
"Car #7"
and the Galley-La shipwrights,
we're all going after the same enemy now.
Ramen Kenpo!
Multi-Noodle Spank!
Whoooa! There it is!
Listen. We're comrades.
Its name is Rocketman.
Captain T-Bone... Hiding in a
small place like this would be hard.
Gum-Gum...
The exit is real close now. We'll keep
on going and go down in one shot!
We can't even allow passengers to be on board.
Three-Hundred Pound...
What? No way... What?!
Rocketman!
We're gonna crash!
It sounds fast!
Hm?
Hands and kitchen knives
are sacred to cooks.
Use it. I've finished servicing it.
Good evening!
All right! The sea train has come out!
Water and coal have been loaded
and it's storing the steam right now.
So it's my policy
not to use them in a battle.
Guys! Now we're gonna charge forth, too!
There they are!
They're behind the door!
...Cannon!
So you were getting it ready for us, pops?!
Yeah!
But if this is a kitchen...
We've found three suspicious men,
including the criminals!
W-We got through!
...and my enemy is foodstuff,
then it's a different story.
Jump! Sodom! Gomorrah!
Wait to rejoice until you survive the ride.
I hate crooked sword attacks.
After all, this was a failure built
before Puffing Tom was completed.
I'll show you...
Right-Angle Flash!
Straw Hat!
No matter how much you tune it up,
its steam engine can't control the speed.
Hey, is that you, Luffy?
Oh, Sanji! How's it going
over there? Where's Robin?
Thank you for helping us,
the entire Franky Family!
...the exceptional way
Bone Soir!
I can't guarantee your lives.
that a first-class cook
handles kitchen knives!
Robin-chan is still in their custody.
Okay! Thanks, Ice pops!
Th-They're not here!
Nami-san just told me
the reasons for her actions.
I see.
Yeah... Well... that's what's going on.
Straw Hat!
Don't tell me...
Whoa! Cool!
Please... take us with you!
The cars are detached!
Those must be the highest-grade bulls.
What...
Go ahead and give them hell.
What?!
...the hell...
Our Bro, Franky, was taken
in by the Government!
Don't be reckless, Luffy!
Dammit! They're the ones who did it!
Tell him to wait until we catch up!
You bastards! You'll regret this!
We want to go after them... but we can't
get through Aqua Laguna by ourselves!
I decided to go with you guys.
...are you?!
Hey, Cook! Can you hear me?!
There are crazy guys on that train, so...
The enemy who took your friend away
So it was too late...
Please!
is also the culprit who tried to kill Iceberg-san.
Well then, gentlemen! Watch out
for Sea Kings! Have a nice trip!
That's okay.
We want to save Bro!
Zoro...
What's the matter, Ramen Kenpo guy?
Take care!
You don't seem to be
as lively as you were earlier.
In addition, there are lots of
things that I wanna say to them!
What would you do if it were you?
Get on.
Dammit! You're a criminal!
"Car #4"
Hurry!
Hm?
Well, then...
Don't talk saucy!
Straw Hat...
After hearing that Robin lied and was
taken into custody in order to save us,
My noodle fists are gone!
Although we got in fights back in
town with both the Franky Family
Thank you!
Am I...
We're deeply indebted to you!
and the Galley-La shipwrights,
we're all going after the same enemy now.
an onion or something?!
Well then, let's go, shall we?!
could you just stay put?
I'm Wanze! I'm mad, mad Wanze!
It's pointless to keep fighting.
Accept your loss and let me pass.
This is bad!
It's no use trying to stop him.
Huh?
I told you, didn't I?
Hey, Moss Head! Are you worried about me?
Accept my loss? Why would I?!
My job ended when the train got on the railway.
Now, now, now!
I'm not losing!
I'm Wanze!
Why would I be, you idiot?!
No one can stop it anymore.
I'm Wanze, the ace of CP7!
But sorry...
After hearing what Robin-chan was thinking...
Hey, Luffy!
When we have the same goal...
If you want to pass through this car,
you'll have to defeat me first!
Sorry, but I understand the
importance of this mission.
...even if the Captain orders it,
I'm not gonna stop!
...it's senseless to fight separately.
Now... pirates!
Don't go getting thrown off, okay?!
Nico Robin, one of your crewmates,
is a woman who the Government
has been pursuing for many years.
Listen. We're comrades.
I'm...
Now departing Water Seven for Enies Lobby...
How could I hand her over
so easily, you fool?!
Are you trying to stop us?
Guys! Don't let that big wave beat us!
...not coming.
Here comes the sea train Rocketman!
I will stop you! Now, now, now!
Ramen Kenpo!
We'll all achieve our goal!
Noodle Stake Knocker!
For this escort mission on the sea train,
It no longer has anything to do with me, right?
All right! Depart!
Let's go!
I'm here to deal with attacks
like this just in case they happen!
If the World Government itself
becomes your enemy at last,
Yeah!
I don't wanna be part of it.
We're gonna go...!
To get everything back!
If you want to let the criminal free,
then beat my Ramen Kenpo!
Now, guys! Show me what
you can do about this wave!
First, cut off the stem and the root
without hurting the flesh.
You'll join with Luffy and
the others as well, right?
All right! Fire all the cannonballs
we have at the wave!
I'm sorry, but I'm no longer
honor-bound to go rescue Robin!
When it comes to cannons, leave it to me!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
If you cut the fiber in one shot,
The rear two cars were detached?
Franky Family! Don't be
intimidated by the wave!
the cut surface looks nice
and it retains its gloss.
I left the Straw Hats!
What on earth are you all doing?
with the sun always in our hearts
Prepare the cannons!
Roger!
We're very sorry.
As power passes through our clasped hands
Stop it! Stay back!
The fact of the matter is that even
Captain T-Bone, one of our powerhouses,
Get a move on!
Ramen Beam!
let's grab hold of our wishes
was in one of the detached cars.
See ya.
Yeah!
So, tell me the current situation in the train.
Oof.
Epluchage!
Yes, ma'am! There are five cars
remaining besides the engine room car!
Ah!
Ahhh! I found them!
Oh, shoot!
Metallic Star!
However, all the soldiers in
car #5 have been taken out.
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Ah! The portable transponder snail is ringing!
So that leaves only Mr. Wanze in car #4,
It's from Sanji-kun!
Mr. Nero in car #3,
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Nico Robin in car #1,
Who's there?!
Although he's just a third-class cook
who plays with his food...
and everyone here in car #2!
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
...I'll at least give him credit for taking
good care of his kitchen knives.
It seems like our enemy isn't stupid.
He told me everything.
Wh-What the hell...
However, if there is a problem here for us,
I heard that you guys want
to rescue a mademoiselle.
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It's all right! Now let's move forward
The same thing here!
That alone is reason enough
for me to lend a hand.
it's only that Franky is walking around free.
They were all taken out!
with the sun always in our hearts
Our mission only requires us to bring
Franky and Nico Robin to Enies Lobby.
I will fight alongside you!
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
As power passes through our clasped hands
but what you cherish most will be right there
Other than that, no matter
how the other enemies die,
let's grab hold of our wishes
And if you get into a jam
My name is...
or no matter what happens to who on our side,
...Sogeking!
it won't interfere with our mission.
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
"Sniper Warrior
Sogeking"
It's all right! Now let's move forward
So, did you see our enemies?
with the sun always in our hearts
Working together,
Yes, ma'am! First, there were
the two that were in custody,
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's ride the giant waves
although one of them
was wearing a weird mask.
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
let's grab hold of our wishes
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
Also, a blond guy dressed in a suit,
who we've never seen before.
and gaze at the light beyond
there's the starting signal
So, a total of three!
Hmm, just like the long-nosed man,
that man is probably one of the Straw Hats.
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
Now's the time to set sail--
I was born on the island of snipers
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
let's raise anchor
Naturally, his purpose is to recover Nico Robin.
So let's grab hold of our wishes
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
I never miss my mark
Franky is helping them out.
That's probably about it.
under the same flag-- together, we're one
and head for a sea of adventure
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Lulu lala lu
Lucci, shall I go stand watch over Nico Robin?
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
One Piece
Whether it's a mouse's eyeball, lock on!!
That's not necessary.
but what you cherish most will be right there
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Or even your heart, lock on!!
Think only about recapturing Franky.
And if you get into a jam
It's definitely not possible for them...
"Rescue Our Friends! A Bond
Among Foes Sworn with Fists!"
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
The man who hails from the island of snipers
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
...to get Nico Robin back.
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
Lululu, lulu lala
with the sun always in our hearts
Now... run away!
but what you cherish most will be right there
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
It's all right! Now let's move forward
and gaze at the light beyond
And if you get into a jam
Sogege, soge, soge
with the sun always in our hearts
I'll always be there to protect you
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
Sogeking!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
As power passes through our clasped hands
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
"Sniping"
let's grab hold of our wishes
We're coming out at a place like this?!
with the sun always in our hearts
So let's grab hold of our wishes
It's an underground canal.
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
under the same flag-- together, we're one
and gaze at the light beyond
One Piece
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
Luffy! Are you okay?!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
I-I got some water in my nose.
with the sun always in our hearts
Huh?
So let's grab hold of our wishes
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
That's gonna happen when you stand out there!
As power passes through our clasped hands
under the same flag-- together, we're one
"Rooftop Duel! Franky vs. Nero"
Be careful!
let's grab hold of our wishes
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
One Piece
Boy, I didn't see that coming!
But... it's getting fun!
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It's a star shield.
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
H-H-Hey, monster granny!
What's up with his body?
Hey, aren't we falling?!
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
"Smash the Wave! Luffy and Zoro
Use the Strongest Combo!"
He's no longer human.
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
but what you cherish most will be right there
The exit is real close now.
We'll keep on going and go down in one shot!
More flame?!
Master Nails!
And if you get into a jam
What? No way... What?!
Moon Walk!
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
I'll always be there to protect you
He jumped again!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
This is getting nowhere!
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
I guess it can't be helped
if my Four Powers don't work.
with the sun always in our hearts
Sorry, I'll use some props,
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
Hey, you!
since I haven't mastered
Finger Pistol yet!
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
Yes, Captain T-Bone!
and gaze at the light beyond
That wound... What happened to your arm?
All right!
but what you cherish most will be right there
I'm going to the next car while I can!
Hm...? Oh...
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
Hey, hold it, you bastard!
I got bitten by a bug earlier.
When I scratched the area, it bled.
And if you get into a jam
You can't be too careful with this guy!
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
All right! The sea train has come out!
That's not good! We should
stop the bleeding immediately!
I'll always be there to protect you
Guys! Now we're gonna charge forth, too!
He fell for it.
So let's grab hold of our wishes
Beans Left!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
--Ahh!
--Let's make do with this.
Yeah!
under the same flag-- together, we're one
Y-You tore your precious cape!
Jump! Sodom! Gomorrah!
with the sun always in our hearts
Sorry...
"Justice"
One Piece
Now, this should do.
I knew...
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
Wh-What the heck...?!
When my subordinates bleed,
it's my heart that gets wounded.
...you'd do something like that!
and gaze at the light beyond
Straw Hat!
Captain T-Bone...
Thank you for helping us,
the entire Franky Family!
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
Owww!
May the world be in peace
and kindness again today.
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
"Showdown Between Cooks!
Sanji vs. Ramen Kenpo"
It worked!
So let's grab hold of our wishes
Fire the connection cannons!
You son of a bitch...
Ouch Finger!
under the same flag-- together, we're one
Shave!
His face is super scary.
Dammit...
--Captain!
--What'd you say?!
"Car #4"
He noticed it...
One Piece
I... I haven't said anything.
Tempest Kick!
Whoa! Cool!
If it's something I can do, I'll do it,
even if my body gets destroyed.
It grazed me!
He sure moves around a lot!
Those must be the highest-grade bulls.
At any rate, leave this guy to me.
So your weak point...
Not bad!
Er... Well...
You guys go to the next car.
"A Mysterious Man Appears?!
His Name Is Sogeking!"
...is your back, huh?
The officials in car #6 and #7
have been wiped out.
Dammit! Those bastards!
Don't forget that this is
Operation Rescue Robin-chan.
I've already figured out
your petty nature, too.
In addition, the two criminals
detained in car #6 are missing as well.
You idiots!
Don't be reckless!
Thanks for your help!
Now it's just a matter of time
before I win, isn't it?
"Sniper Warrior
Sogeking"
What?!
"Flour"
That's impossible!
Don't get so carried away!
What a cheerful bunch!
We can't tell whether there's an intruder
or they escaped by themselves.
I... won't... let... you... pass... through!
I have no weak point if I do this.
I was born on the island of snipers
Hey, monster granny!
Is this as fast as it goes?
For Heaven's sake! Save the lives
of the injured immediately,
Franky...
...Invincible! Tada!
It's not fast at all.
and let everyone on this train
know about this situation!
I'll knead alloy flour and...!
Well, just hold your horses.
"Invincible"
Yes, sir!
Is he gonna bring out ramen noodles again?!
Once it gets on the railway, you'll see.
I never miss my mark
Now, do you give up, you weasel jerk?!
Ramen...
Nami-san! Nami-san, can you hear me?
Railway?
Yep, is that you, Sanji-kun?!
Lulu lala lu...
...Beam...!
Where the heck is that?
Things are taking a turn for the worse here.
I don't know what to say to him...
What the heck is he doing?
Looks like it's drifted quite a ways away.
They can prick you!
Well, try to understand his feelings.
Turn for the worse?
But I've observed the sea train
since its development.
Sanji-kun! What was that voice?!
He feels that he can't go rescue
her outright as a friend.
Yikes!
Don't underestimate me!
Hey! What's going on?! Sanji-kun!
So this is his own way of settling things.
What's going on?
Hey, hey...
Cut it out!
The man who hails from
the island of snipers...
Why are you here?!
Oof!
Yeah, because of that idiot...
Geez... what a pain.
How'd you get on board?!
I-Idiot?
Hey! Come over here!
Tsk!
Ah! Again! What?!
I can't answer if you bombard me
with questions like that.
Oh, okay.
--Are you okay?!
--What's going on?!
--Just kidding.
--Are you okay, Sanji-kun?
Well, calm down a little.
Let's go around via the roof!
--But you look panicky.
--Who's the idiot you're talking about?!
Yeah!
I see it! Let's go!
Actually, there are two idiots.
Ah, shall I pour you
some coffee or something?
W-Well then, Sanji-kun! I wish you good luck.
Okay, then. We'll have the meeting
for Operation Rescue Robin-chan now.
Stop fooling around!
Now, now, now!
Urgent message from the engine room!
Demi-Cannon!
They got away so easily!
We've never met before. Don't you
guys have any questions about me?
The train will get on the railway shortly.
Once it does, it'll rapidly accelerate!
What on earth...?
How do you do?
But that's no use...
I'm Sogeking,
the king of snipers.
First of all, the car you guys were in
was #6, so there are five more cars left.
Hold on tight to something so
that your injuries won't be severe.
...because Nero's waiting
for them in the next car.
Take these!
To make a long story short,
I've come to rescue you.
So, we'll get injured regardless?
We're not even making a dent.
Should have expected as much.
Although he's a newbie, he's a member
of CP9, a group of assassins for justice!
You know, like,
"Where is the island of snipers?"
Long-nose...
Robin-chan is in one of those cars.
No! Those puny cannons won't work!
It's not just me.
They'll die! Nero loves to kill!
Why, it's in your heart!
Sanji-kun and a thug named Franky
Guys! Stay back!
are currently engaged
in battle on this train.
Leave it to the Franky Family's special cannon!
Now, now, now, now!
Tsk! I missed it.
But I'm just getting started!
By the way, are you strong?
Flanchet...
During their fights, I found
a chance to come here.
I'm super strong, you idiot!
Furthermore, Luffy-kun and the others
...Shoot!
I'm especially strong this week!
Target! Aqua Laguna!
are also on this railway following
this train using the other sea train...
If we can rescue Robin-chan
in the end, we win, but...
Oof.
Fire! Super Scrap Cannon!
He's bringing a big group.
...there are a lot of enemies.
Hey! Behave!
If we carelessly jump the gun
and get surrounded
in a small space like a train,
that'll be a problem.
Grandma! That was close!
That was close! A little to the right!
So it's probably best if we
avoid any unnecessary fights
Dammit! Don't flinch! Keep firing!
On my way here earlier,
and crush the main forces in turns.
Just wait and see!
I peeked inside
of the train through the windows.
I'll make it next... Huh?!
Makes sense.
Frankly, those four people in the
car behind this one are dangerous.
It's best if we don't fight.
That sure is a good point, Sanji-kun.
Chimney! Gonbe!
I was born on the island of snipers
It'd be best if I could rescue you
You guys came with us?!
"Sniper Warrior
Sogeking"
So, that leads me to a possible strategy.
before Sanji-kun confronts them.
Replenish the cannonballs!
Huh?
Yep, we did!
Got it!
Aim at the front! Focus on one spot!
Look... Listen carefully.
I never miss my mark
Hmm...
Go! Focus pocus!
For God's sake!
If I at least knew which car Robin is in,
Lulu lala lu
Hurry up and
come inside!
Do your best. The railway surfaces a little,
but we can't go over Aqua Laguna.
Now, let's run...
I could just go on the roof
and infiltrate at once.
Or you'll be blown away!
Whether it's a mouse's eyeball, lock on!!
together!
We're okay! We're okay!
What're you mumbling about?!
Hurry up and go, you damn Squidy-king!
Or even your heart, lock on!!
If we directly hit it, even Rocketman
will easily get destroyed.
Th-This is...
Who're you calling "Squidy"?!
Chimney!
What's the matter?
Ahhh! Are we gonna die?!
I'm gonna fall!
The man who hails from the island of snipers
Hmm... Squidy...?
There's no need to worry.
D-Don't let go!
I'm all prepared.
I told you to prepare yourselves, right?
I'm being blown away!
These Octopu-shoes are for you.
Hurry up, you damn idiot!
Lululu, lulu lala
H-Hold on a sec, okay?
I'll stop the train right away!
If you put them on your hands and feet,
Amazing...
What?! That includes us?!
Hey, bikini guy.
you can get out through the window and
stick to the outer panels of the sea train.
Now... run away!
Huh?
I've got a brilliant idea.
Now, put them on before they notice.
I see... Then Robin is still...
Okay! Now I'm ready for battle!
Listen carefully.
Wait.
"Wait"?
Oh, that's right!
At any rate, it sounds lively over there.
Hm? What're you guys doing?
How could this be happening?
The brake doesn't work on this train!
Don't "What're you guys doing?" us!
How dare you so openly change in
front of everyone, you shameless girl?!
I thought I clearly
told you all goodbye.
Say, Sanji-kun...
Oops! Hm? What the heck?
That kinda looks fun.
I'll tell you the reason for Robin's actions
I'll never return to the Straw Hats!
Nice shamelessness.
Tsk...
This'll take forever if you
keep dodging my attacks.
and our current situation, so...
Ah! Straw Hat brother! Hello!
I couldn't help it. We only have one car.
How many times do I need
to tell you I'm in a hurry?
Be quiet!
They know why you are
so insistent about that.
Hide your belly! Belly and legs!
Straw Hat! Hurry and get
Chimney and Gonbe inside!
Well then, here comes my attack!
Listen, Sanji-kun. I'll tell you everything
about the reason for Robin's actions
You guys, too, Square Sisters!
Ramen Kenpo... Noodle Slicer!
Once we get on the railway,
they'll be blown away!
People like you corrupt society!
I heard that Ice pops at the
shipbuilding yard clarified everything.
and our current situation.
So please listen carefully.
Okay!
Shut up, you shy man.
Fire...
Shy man.
So he survived?
Ahhh! We're gonna crash!
You little...
...Skate!
No... Even so, I won't return...
If you like, I'll change, too.
Oh, no! We're gonna die!
We're gonna die!
I'm sorry, but please don't! Seriously!
to you guys...
If you have time to whine, keep firing!
Enough with that!
Find a way out!
What rude guys.
You still don't get it?!
Dammit!
They're not so weak that
you need to worry about them!
Hey, Luffy.
Before you took such a stupid deal,
I wish they had made the pockets
in these black shorts bigger.
Yeah... Let's go, Zoro.
they really wanted you
to talk to them first!
Ow, ow, ow...!
I got kicked about ten times
the moment he dodged my attack!
Don't pack meat in your pockets!
You really think
they'd be happy to be alive
You guys seem refreshed.
You're full of enthusiasm.
Actually, twelve times.
knowing that it was because
their friend had to sacrifice herself?!
Is it possible... that you're super strong?
Now that they know why you left them,
Of course! This is in order to rescue Robin!
they'll follow you
to the depths of hell
Hey! Keep firing at the front!
It's probably just that your
bark is worse than your bite.
We'll beat them all up this time for sure!
What're you guys gonna do?!
Ah! All right! They got on the railway!
and take out your enemies!
Hey, hey! Not even my
old man has said that to me!
You'd better! If you get stuck
somewhere again, I'm not gonna forgive you!
Really?! Hey! Let me see!
You
still don't get what
kind of man Luffy is!
Stop saying that! How rude of you! I'm Wanze!
I'll be fine! I've got a
reason I won't lose this time!
It's you guys who don't get it!
Yeah, you're right. I see, I see...
Even considering that your rare
swirling eyebrows made me dizzy,
A reason...
I don't have the slightest
desire to be rescued!
We'll fire...
Hm? Nami, did you change your weapon?
Just as you'd expect from Kokoro-san!
She's something else!
Don't just do as you please!
...a cannon.
you're actually pretty good!
Hm? No.
Yeah, indeed.
After we came back from the sky island,
What'd you say, you...
For a while, I was afraid of
what was going to happen.
You're one to talk about a rare face!
Usopp improved it and
made it stronger using dials.
Indeed, indeed.
That's exactly right.
What are you making a
racket for, Nico Robin?
It's the Perfect Clima Takt.
With those high waves, it must've
been hard to find the railway.
What's a hundred and eight times two?
I see. So it's Usopp's...
"Flour"
Okay, then! I'll show you
right away why I was chosen
What's the matter?
Yeah, indeed.
You're exactly righ... Ah...
That's right! It's Usopp's...
Now that Enies Lobby
is getting closer,
Two hundred and sixteen.
is it hard for even you to remain calm?
Indeed, indeed, indeed. Ah...
Two hundred and sixteen...
That's long and hard to say.
to be in the team to escort the criminals!
Yeah... It's his last work.
Well, well, well, she's something...
Even if you cry about your destiny now,
Then, pick whatever.
Don't go bumming people out!
She's something else!
it's not like your life
will be saved or anything.
Wh-What are they doing?!
One is weaponless and the other is
using swords. What're they trying to do?
It's nothing.
I-I-Indeed...
They told us to keep firing.
W-We definitely have to let Iceberg-san know.
Enough talking! Just back them up!
What was that?
Ramen Kenpo! Secret technique!
It looks suspicious!
Yeah!
Y-You're right.
I-I'm sure he's worried.
In addition, she seems
different than before.
I'll finish the noodles by beating
them over and over again!
Okay, then... three hundred!
Ready? Well then, let's go.
Okay!
Well, well, well, indeed. Indeed!
Wha...? What the hell is this?
Gum-Gum...
Is it just my imagination?
An intruder?
Three-Hundred Pound...
This is an edible, dream combat uniform!
Y-Yes, sir. That's what I heard.
It's nothing...
It's not possible to get on board
Puffing Tom while it's running.
We're gonna crash!
so leave me alone.
Ra-men's Formal Suit!
If there really is an intruder,
What the hell?
it means that we let him come
on board when we departed.
Why is this
woman goofing around?
Now, now, now!
The secret of Ramen Kenpo
is controlling noodles at will!
Good grief...
Rock...!
Paper...!
Coo coo.
...Cannon!
I agree. It's embarrassing.
A rabbit?
But at the same time, it's not possible
to get off while it's running, either.
You bastard...
Hey! Cut it out!
How dare you play with food all this time?!
The intruder as well as the criminals
are certainly still on this sea train.
Enough with the jokes!
Speed, power, and special abilities...
Be serious!
Get up!
Keep calm and look for them.
I'm at a different level now in all those areas!
Yes, sir!
Watch your mouth, you weasel jerk.
I'll exhibit incomparable strength!
I'm not joking.
Yeah!
Okay, then... three hundred!
In any case, how unlucky...
"Car #7"
Okay!
Gum-Gum...
Enough jabbering. Bring it on already.
Really, how unlucky... you are.
Three-Hundred Pound...
I'll make you eat all
those noodles, so be prepared.
Captain T-Bone... Hiding in a
small place like this would be hard.
We're gonna crash!
You made me angry...
and I happen to be super this week.
Hm?
...Cannon!
Well, I bet he's fine.
Good evening!
Say, buddy...
Do you know a monster
called the centaur?
We're talking about a guy who
survived being hit by a sea train...
There they are!
They're behind the door!
We've found three suspicious men,
including the criminals!
The one that's human from the
waist up and horse below, right?
They're in car #7! Corner and capture them!
What about it?
Did you know... that the violent
disciple of Tom, Cutty Flam, died?
So...
The way you're using the hammer is no good.
Con...vert!
...who are you?
Shut up!
"Convert"
Stop this futile resistance!
Sanji-kun!
"Pervert"
Open the door!
The one waiting on car #3 is a
newbie in CP9, a Four Powers Master,
He was hit by the sea train.
Hurry up and board it up!
I-I know.
We're gonna die!
Iceberg...
Nero the sea weasel. Hiss!
Guys! This way! Suspicious men
were found in car #7!
you can do it.
You're the first disciple of Tom,
the world's greatest shipwright.
You found them?!
At any rate, I guess you're
one opponent I can't kill...
It's finally time.
Let those in car #3 know, too!
Don't tell me he's gonna...
We'll corner them and capture
the criminal Franky alive!
I'm sure you can do it... I'm sure...
...since you're one of our important criminals.
There's no place to escape to!
Seize them carefully!
Hey! Stay back!
Kokoro-san, let's drink
together one of these days...
Hey, buddy! Why are you out on the roof?
Franky...
Whoa! They started shooting!
...Centaur!
...when we have something to drink to.
Hurry up, Soge!
If you had just waited, I would've come to you.
Wrong way!
Well, a little help would be nice!
Your body should be in front!
Yeah.
Well, you can't tell that for sure, right?
You might've cheated and
skipped this car, right? Hiss!
Tom-san... please just watch.
Don't shoot blindly! We can't kill them!
I'll take over your will.
How cautious you are!
Dammit!
Wait to complain
But being on guard is important, huh?
I'll protect... everything...
until you see its attacking power.
Captain T-Bone...
Step aside.
By the way, what's that thing behind you?
This town... and these blueprints as well.
Huh?
"Four years later"
I hate crooked sword attacks.
Iceberg-san, you have a guest.
Right-Angle Flash!
He said you'd know who if I tell you "Cutty Flam."
That was dirty!
Franky...?
Bone Soir!
Shall I show him in here?
Dirty is right! In my town,
I'm the boss of a gang of rogues.
Aren't we catching up
with Bashing Tom yet?!
No...
That's "Puffing"!
turn him away.
Hey, Luffy! Stay inside!
You just changed,
but you're soaking wet again!
That's okay!
What a roundabout way of meeting.
I like this place!
Geez...
Well... anyway, what's up with
that funny looking body of yours?
Gum-Gum...
Hm? Where's Luffy?
Three-Hundred Pound...
Shut up! Since my whole
body came to be of no use,
...Cannon! Boom!
Splash!
Hm...? Beats me.
I rebuilt my body using
iron scraps and escaped death!
Ahh! This is it! Laguna!
More importantly,
This is no time for playing!
"Beats me"?! What if he
happened to fall into the water?!
W-We got through!
I heard that your company contracts to
build ships for the World Government!
We're bored.
I'm not gonna tolerate you doing
things that help the Government!
Polish your weapons or
something, you idiots!
I hate crooked sword attacks.
Oof! It's slippery!
They took Tom-san and...
Can't be. He was right here up
until just now. Right, Chopper?
Well, um...
Right-Angle Flash!
I'll talk to those guys later, so...
And who made the weapons
that caused the incident?!
What? Yeah.
We got through Aqua Laguna!
Bone Soir!
That's no answer! I'm worried because
the person who was here isn't here now!
Hm?
I'm sure you have things you wanna say to me,
Hey, guys!
Maybe he's stuck in the chimney of Rocketman?
but don't think that I've forgiven
you in the past four years.
I thought we were gonna die!
I see a train ahead of us!
He's not me-- Hey, Chopper! You little...!
I'm surprised that you had the nerve
to show your face after what happened!
It's gotta be Puffing Tom, right?!
Th-They're not here!
What'd you say?!
I completely thought that you were dead...
Isn't it too early?
Yay!
...since the Government told me so.
Even if Tom-san forgave you,
I'm not going to forgive you!
Just wait, Robin...! And Usopp.
Are they on the roof?!
Dammit!
What's gonna happen to us?
Welcome to the Ramen Kenpo world!
Hurry up! Our enemy is at
the very end of the train!
Ow...
There's no engine on this car.
Hey! Are you okay, Nami-san?
We have no choice
but to wait to be rescued.
H-Hey! What the hell are these?!
Now! Hurry!
Yeah, somehow...
Whoa! We're rocking!
You call this "powered-up"?
But will someone really come
to rescue us in this storm?
Aren't these the blueprints we
saw for that ancient weapon?!
Now, now, now! Take this!
That was really something. They don't
call themselves pirates for nothing.
Don't tell me...
They have to. Or we're screwed.
Ramen Kenpo! Pork Bone Spank!
Don't use the name Cutty Flam from now on.
All, go back to the front cars! This is a trap!
Hey, guys.
If they were our enemy, they'd be fearsome,
There's something
coming from behind!
The Government couldn't
get this out of Tom-san.
Really?!
A trap?!
but if they're on our side, no one
is more dependable than they are!
It must be a rescue ship!
It's only a matter of time before I get targeted.
Well... it looks like...
--What the...?!
--Go back! This is a trap!
it's coming on the railway.
Leave the island with them... Franky.
What?!
Straw Hat!
Naturally, I was prepared to die.
What incredible guys...
Even if we want to go back, the door is...
Can't be...
Leave this island?
That's a useless punch
that you just made bigger.
There's only
one sea train in the world.
Cutty Flam from Tom's Workers is dead.
Who was that?!
Don't let your guard down.
We are not through the storm yet.
Now, now, now! Another one!
Besides, it was impossible to leave
Water Seven after the last departure.
As long as you don't use that name,
there'll be no connection between us.
The cars are detached!
What?!
Yeah!
In addition, if you leave the island,
Then...
Dammit! They're the ones who did it!
There's nothing that we're afraid of now!
the blueprints' whereabouts
will vanish into the darkness.
You bastards! You'll regret this!
I-It's stuck!
H-Hold on a sec!
What happens if they come after you
when you don't have them?!
...what's coming?
So it was too late...
That was fun!
Hey, that's a sea train,
I've said what I came to say.
Oof!
Well then, gentlemen! Watch out
for Sea Kings! Have a nice trip!
Straw Hat! You're amazing!
Hey! Hey, Iceberg!
but it's just cars
without the engine room!
That was beyond human power!
Now, now!
We may not see each other again.
Take care!
It's sitting motionless on the railway!
Hey! Wait!
What?!
Do you want to end up like Tom-san?
What's going on?!
Two cars' worth...
Oh, sorry.
Does this mean that they got detached?
With this, at least fifty small fries
or so must've been taken care of.
Keep the blueprints with you!
Luffy, come over here.
Ah! Sanji and Usopp may be on them!
If, by any chance, you find that your
life is in danger, just hand them over!
--Hm?
Now, now, now! You dummy!
But, Sanji-kun...
Big Bro Franky, too!
Aren't Straw Hat Luffy and the
others coming on the same railway?
Are you taken aback by my Ramen Kenpo?!
If you don't wanna do that, then you
can even burn them before their eyes!
This isn't good!
If we keep going like this,
we'll collide with them!
Well, they'll probably do something about it.
You look unsightly with your leg
and arm buried in ramen noodles!
If you were me, would you do that?
It's Sanji-kun.
Granny! Where's the brake?!
Y-You bastards! Time to be
blown away along with the door!
I said it doesn't work, didn't I?
Tom-san achieved so many great things,
How dare you beat the crap
out of me like that earlier?!
Do something.
and he gave up everything in order to
preserve these blueprints for the future.
Hey, is that you, Luffy?
We're gonna crash!
Oh, Sanji! How's it going
over there? Where's Robin?
At least, as long as there's a risk
--Ah!
--Hm?
Oh, going somewhere?
Luffy! What're you gonna do?
What?!
that a woman named Nico Robin
can restore the weapon,
Robin-chan is still in their custody.
I'll go check inside!
the world needs those blueprints to fight back.
All right, then. Let's take care of
the remaining five cars, shall we?
Gum-Gum... Rocket!
Nami-san just told me
the reasons for her actions.
Y-You son of a bitch! Don't think
you can get away with this!
If I continue to keep them with me...
Yeah, I heard... everything.
How dare you do such terrible
things to even Captain T-Bone?!
Something is flying towards...
...even if I am to be killed...
I won't give them to the Government!
What're you getting dizzy for, you jerk?!
Hey! Report this to CP9!
I see.
So there are more small fries?
Are you sure?
Yeah... Well... that's what's going on.
I may build this weapon.
You just tried to make me dizzy using
your eyebrows again, didn't you?!
What happened?!
Is it okay to trust me?
I'm not gonna let you get away with it!
Doesn't my giving them
to you answer that question?
Go ahead and give them hell.
Frit... Assorti!
What?!
Whaaat?!
We never change, huh?
Hey!
Don't be reckless, Luffy!
Sogeking... Gunpowder Star!
Whenever we meet face to face,
we yell at each other.
Ow, ow, ow...
Now, now, now!
Tell him to wait until we catch up!
I still won't forgive you... and you
may feel the same about me, too.
All right! I got in!
Wh-Who are you?!
Hey, Cook! Can you hear me?!
There are crazy guys on that train, so...
Dammit! I can't pull out my leg or my arm!
Strong... Right!
Hello! Sanji!
Franky... I'm... really...
That's okay.
I can't fight back like this!
Are you in here?!
Zoro...
--What?
--Huh?
Usopp...
Heavyweight bullets... Fire!
What would you do if it were you?
Hello! Sanji!
...glad that... you're alive.
Whoa!
Noodle Soul Press!
Hm?
Hello!
They hit him!
After hearing that Robin lied and was
taken into custody in order to save us,
I wonder if they're over there.
could you just stay put?
I'm just getting started!
This guy... Could it be...!
Wait! Stupid-berg!
I'm not gonna leave this island!
Another helping! And another!
--Ow...
--Wha...
It's Straw Hat Luffy!
It's no use trying to stop him.
And another! And another!
Fire! Fire!
I'll do what I wanna do!
You know me well.
And another!
I would never do what you
tell me to, even if it kills me!
Take that, and that, and that,
and that, and that, and that, and that!
Hey, Moss Head! Are you worried about me?
Never!
Hello!
Why would I be, you idiot?!
How come the gun isn't working?!
But sorry...
You Moron-ky! Why don't
you get what I'm saying?!
Are you here, Sanji?!
After hearing what Robin-chan was thinking...
They finally came off.
This is in order to protect the blueprints!
Sanji!
...even if the Captain orders it,
I'm not gonna stop!
Hey, shut up!
Shut up! It's you who's not getting it!
Now, now, now! Aren't you
underestimating me, you fool?
I'm not gonna leave no matter what!
Straw Hat!
There's no escape for you!
Ahhh!
Tsk! Why am I remembering
him at a time like this?!
Why'd you break it?! I wanted
to ask Straw Hat something, too!
Where's Sanji?
This is the mad, mad Ramen Kenpo!
Wh-Who's that?
Huh?!
Hey! What the hell are you?!
Sanji! He's my friend!
Is that idiot... Iceberg... doing okay?
Huh...? Who cares?
Hm?
We don't know a guy like that!
To think that I get buried if I attack...
Oh, I'm a cyborg.
We killed him.
You should've told me beforehand.
I see...
Then, see ya.
I guess I can't touch those ramen noodles.
Even if I didn't tell you, it was obvious,
wasn't it?! Don't be so cocky!
A cyborg?!
That's right. Steel and weapons
are built into my body.
Now, I'll keep it coming!
Shoot him!
I'm not being cocky.
If I'm shot, it hurts a little
and sometimes it bleeds too,
Ramen and Pot Sticker Combo! Clapping!
I wonder if he'll be okay.
Straw Hat is coming out!
but, well, it doesn't work.
Granny! Have the train go faster!
Something like that is possible?
He's saying that they're not
in there... while being shot!
Faster?
The world is a big place, huh?
Yeah! Like, more wooosh!
Amazing!
Then, there's only one area that I can attack.
Then, everyone in there is
Government personnel, huh?
Ahh... I thought I'd die.
--How's this?
--Ouch!
Well, obviously!
Geez, I told you, didn't I?!
So what're you gonna do if so?
Don't worry. It's already going
faster than the limits of its speed...
What're you doing, you jerk?!
Unless we move those
cars out of our way,
we'll take a lot of damage, too!
I said you'd get blown away!
Escalope!
What? Isn't a needle small enough
that it doesn't hurt at all?
Ow, ow...
Ramen Beam!
You idiot! How dare you
start a dreadful experiment?!
Anyway, that acceleration sure was crazy.
So fast that it can't stop by itself.
--Geez...
--Yeah, really, that scared me!
Then, I'll tell you this before you
go any further. The back is different!
I hit my lower back.
That's a sea train, after all!
Look. I did the makeover by myself,
so I couldn't reach the back side.
Hold on a sec...
We're gonna be knocked off!
There are weird guys in here.
Well, if things go wrong, it could
possibly cause a huge explosion!
Only the front side is cyborg.
What?! Who are they?!
Stop!
Now, now, now!
I see...
You guys!
So, things like that were happening...
You, too!
It's the Franky Family's
turn to work now.
I've got no blind spot!
Well then, while I'm at it,
I'll tell you one more thing.
...while I was gone?
We'll demolish them
right before we collide!
From what I've been seeing,
your means of fighting is kicking, isn't it?
My belly tends to feel cold.
Why do you think that is?
All right! We'll give
you guys a hand, too!
Robin-chan doesn't know anything
I decided to go with you guys.
How would I know?
Guys! It's time to work!
about the Merry... or about the
huge fight between you and Luffy.
Kicking is the only means you have, isn't it?
That's because I've got a
fridge in my belly to chill cola.
Yeah!
No matter how hard I tried
to stop you, you didn't stop.
Hey! Zoro!
Whoa! That's handy!
Now, now, now! It's no use! It's no use!
That's amazing! That'd be great for hot days!
The enemy you'd go this far
to rescue your friend from
No matter what you do, you'll only
end up being buried in my suit!
Hey, Roronoa.
He's calling your name.
In order for all six of us,
including you, to stay safe,
is also the culprit who tried to kill Iceberg-san.
Cut them.
They're in our way.
she sacrificed herself and obeyed their orders.
Hey! This is no time for a conversation like that!
Sure.
In addition, there are lots of
things that I wanna say to them!
Here goes! Try dodging this!
"Sure"?!
We've beat all the enemies in this car!
It's cleared! Let's go to the next car!
Ramen Kenpo!
She did it for us.
Paulie! We're not gonna
let you steal all the glory!
Multi-Noodle Spank!
Next is car #4.
Thinking that we'd be able to find
Iceberg-san's assassins if we followed you,
"Car #4"
What a moving story!
We're gonna collide!
we hid in the tender together!
Stop!
So... it seems we were right.
Why are you crying?
Let us join you guys in this battle.
You dummy! I'm not crying!
I'm Wanze! I'm mad, mad Wanze!
And, of course...
Dammit! I can't believe it!
...the foes you're gonna get revenge
on took Big Bro Franky as well.
The ego of the entropic world...
Huh?
Nico Robin is said to be a
cruel, inhuman, evil woman!
That's right! And we clearly know who they are!
Now, now, now!
...can be slashed into pieces.
I'm Wanze!
Hey, Galley-La!
But the truth is... she's got touching
affection towards her friends!
How are you gonna take responsibility
if something happens to Bro?!
Shut up! It's Iceberg-san
who's endured the most!
1.4 mm pasta, fedelini...
Robin-chan is within a stone's throw.
Anyhow, I'll go rescue her!
Hey, you guys! Are you hungry?
What're you guys going on about?!
Huh?!
I'm Wanze. I'm the head steward,
so I can cook anything!
Sleight of hand?
Paulie! First, explain it to us! What's going on?!
All right, then! I'm Franky,
the leader of the Franky Family!
Ah! My noodle fists are now in pieces!
Would you like ramen noodles?
Well then, I'll make ramen noodles.
He's right, Paulie.
Two-Sword Style Sword Draw...
I'll give you a hand, mister eyebrow!
You know the true culprit, don't you?
But before that, there's a snippet
of knowledge I want you to have.
To tell you the truth, I've got
a reason for not wanting Robin
Just tell us.
Hands and kitchen knives are sacred to cooks.
My nose hairs look like this!
We're not that dense.
We have a rough idea as to who it is.
to be in the Government's custody, too.
They're reticulate inside, which means
they look like fishnet pantyhose.
Most of all, when I hear such a poignant tale...!
So it's my policy not to use them in a battle.
We're not gonna be surprised.
Keep that in mind!
"Flour"
...Rashomon!
Hey! Let's go, Long-nose!
Okay, then! First, I'll put the flour
in my mouth and knead it well.
Well, I guess you could guess if they
suddenly disappeared for no reason.
But if this is a kitchen...
What?!
I'm...
Whaaat?!
...and my enemy is foodstuff,
then it's a different story.
Then, I'll tell you straight.
--Whaaat?!
...not coming.
The true identities of those masked men are...
You're more troublesome than I thought.
It no longer has anything to do with me, right?
...Lucci, Kaku, Kalifa and Blueno from the bar.
If the World Government itself
becomes your enemy at last,
Thousand Noodle Whip!
It was them who tried to kill Iceberg-san!
I don't wanna be part of it.
Now, bon appetit!
Who'd eat that?!
You'll join with Luffy and
the others as well, right?
That was a waste of time.
What?! You never even guessed that?!
Trying to look cool? How saucy!
After all my blustering,
and after humiliating myself,
Wanze, we're keeping someone waiting.
B-But you said they went
back to their hometowns!
An amateur like you who can't even
cook shouldn't hold kitchen knives!
how could I be with you guys?!
Hey, you guys!
Why would they, during an emergency like this?!
So, we're in a hurry. See ya.
If you were going to
do something like that,
We thought it was Michael and
Hoichael from the backstreets.
you could've at least told us.
Hold it!
You heard me saying,
"Cut them," right?!
They're different from the
knives that delinquents use!
--That's right!
--Who the hell are they?!
Who would think he could?!
I'm sorry, but I'm no longer
honor-bound to go rescue Robin!
What?! You don't know them?!
They're famous in the backstreets!
If you want to pass through this car,
you'll have to defeat me first!
We would've collided
if we didn't cut them, right?!
Pardon me for being saucy.
That's right!
Well, that's true,
How would I know?!
To start with, you guys are--
This isn't quite a token of my apology...
I left the Straw Hats!
but we needed
to be prepared, you know!
All right! Boy, I ate a lot.
I'm finally full.
Even a monster like him
isn't the leader of the group?
Are you trying to stop us?
...but I'll show you...
Oof.
I will stop you! Now, now, now!
He's something else.
See ya.
Well, then...
For this escort mission on the sea train,
Anyway, you're amazing!
...the exceptional way that a first-class
cook handles kitchen knives!
H-Hey! "See ya," you're saying?!
Although we got in fights back in
town with both the Franky Family
I'm here to deal with attacks
like this just in case they happen!
There's no place to escape to!
and the Galley-La shipwrights,
we're all going after the same enemy now.
--That's okay.
--Hm?
If you want to let the criminal free,
then beat my Ramen Kenpo!
Leave him alone.
The strongest one among the guys
we're gonna fight is that pigeon guy.
Hiss!
Shave!
That idiot's being stubborn.
In any case, to think that
there was another sea train...
R-Ramen Kenpo?!
Strong... Hammer!
He's mine. I'm definitely gonna beat him up.
"R-Ramen Kenpo?!"
Search every nook and cranny!
With that speed, they might catch up.
Yeah. This is a battle to get back
what those four took from us.
Paper Art.
There's gotta be some evidence somewhere!
That son of a bitch! He's mocking me!
If, by any chance,
the criminals
under escort are taken away...
Don't be taken in, idiot!
You're playing right into his hands!
Th-This isn't good!
In any case, if we don't
reach them, nothing will end.
Now, now, now! How was my
impersonation of that idiot?
That's not going to happen!
Tempest Kick!
Let's make do with this!
Ahh! Grandma! Grandma!
It's Aqua Laguna!
--Grrr!
--Like I said, don't be taken in!
He is between them and
the preceding sea train!
Wanze-san! The train's in a whole lot of trouble!
Now, now, now, now!
Hiss!
What a restless guy.
Oh? It's already here?!
Shut up! I'm the one who's
in a whole lot of trouble!
That's right!
As long as
we have him in the Navy,
Chimney! Let me see it!
our justice will never sway!
Fresh Fire!
Nero-san! The criminals made an escape!
This is bad!
What?! The bullets grazed him,
Shave!
Hm?
Kokoro-san! Is it okay for you to leave
the engine room at a time like this?!
and yet his expression didn't change.
He even looks relaxed...
Wha...?! What's with him?!
He jumped towards the sea on his own!
How was it over there?
We somehow need to dodge that high wave!
I-I thought my heart would jump out of my skin!
Was there something unusual?
All right! Here goes!
I told you, didn't I?
That we can't control Rocketman.
Two-Sword Style Sword Draw...
Nothing for now.
So you were shocked?!
Don't show confusing expressions!
Moon Walk!
I see.
...Rashomon!
Even when we want to operate it,
nothing works, including the brake.
Hey! You're supposed to be the train!
I'll take care of an annoying jerk like him!
Why me?! You do it!
Hm?
Wait, you guys.
Why did he bounce back
in the air?! I don't get it!
My job ended when the train got on the railway.
No, you do it!
If you're taken in by him like this all
the time, it'll just slow things down.
No! I don't wanna be cut in half!
Get cut in half!
Hence, the train is always
running at full throttle.
No!
Why can't I cut him with Tempest Kick?
There's something weird about his body!
Hey, guys!
Huh?!
I'll make short work of him.
No one can stop it anymore.
We're not done yet.
Oof.
Oh, no... Luffy!
What upsets me is that someone
like you would call yourself a cook!
What the hell is that?!
Ah!
What...
Ahhh! I found them!
If we don't do anything, the train will
crash into the big wave! Hey, Luffy!
It's a Sea King!
...the hell...
Oh, shoot!
Metallic Star!
A huge monster like this was...
I'm talking to you!
When we have the same goal...
Sashimi!
Hey! You've been taken in!
...are you?!
...it's senseless to fight separately.
It's been split in half!
Grilled fish!
Who's there?!
Yeah.
But look! He dodged Sanji's kick easily!
You're right.
Octopu-shoes... Octopu-shoes...
Listen. We're comrades.
What's with his relaxed expression?!
Something that huge was...
Our friends are also in
the train that left before us.
I thought I was a goner!
He told me everything.
It was so huge that it could've
swallowed Rocketman in one gulp!
So you were shocked?!
Stop that pattern!
I heard that you guys want
to rescue a mademoiselle.
Our fighting force will still increase.
That alone is reason enough
for me to lend a hand.
Guys! Don't let that big wave beat us!
I will fight alongside you!
At any rate...
Further ahead on this railway...
We'll all achieve our goal!
Long-nose!
Let's go!
...lies the one who
cut that thing up...!
...leave this guy to me.
Yeah!
My name is...
Why are you here?!
You guys go to the next car.
...Sogeking!
I was--
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross the wildly surging ocean
makes us able to cross
the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring than anyone else
You're braver and more caring
than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end, we can all surely smile
In the end,
we can all surely smile
Hey, look! That wave is really huge! Amazing!
Who the hell is that?!
I'm gonna beat you up using
my mad, mad Ramen Kenpo!
What the hell's up with your body?
We'll now start the meeting for
Operation Rescue Robin-chan.
Ahh! That's the Ship-Slasher!
Sanji-kun, we've never met before.
Don't you have any questions?
Well, I guess I'm probably the only
guy who can chill cola in his belly.
Ahhh! If we don't do something,
it'll collide with Rocketman!
Ship-Slasher?
I hate those who play with food!
Ship-Slasher T-Bone,
a Captain at Navy Headquarters!
First, we'll efficiently reduce
the number of enemies in the train.
Everyone, brace yourself!
I knew it! You aren't human!
Don't talk so saucy when you're
an amateur who can't even cook!
You know, like my origins
or my killer techniques?
Are we gonna die?
He's a crazy guy
who cuts ships like steaks!
But I found your weak point!
And then, we'll crush the main forces in turns.
Well then, let's do it, shall we, Captain?
Hey, hey, buddy. Don't be silly!
Pardon me for being saucy.
Sogeking! "I'll-Do-My-Best" Star!
Interesting.
--Yeah!
--What're you guys gonna do?!
This isn't quite a token of my apology,
Hey! I'll tell you only once!
Hey! Give it a rest already! Just listen to me!
I'm invincible!
We're gonna fire a cannon!
but shall I show you how a first-class
cook handles kitchen knives?
Get out of our way!
Oh, okay. Sorry.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Smash the Wave! Luffy and Zoro
Use the Strongest Combo!"
"Rooftop Duel! Franky vs. Nero"
"Clash! Demon-Slasher Zoro
vs. Ship-Slasher T-Bone"
"A Mysterious Man Appears?!
His Name Is Sogeking!"
"Showdown Between Cooks!
Sanji vs. Ramen Kenpo"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!