Well, then...
Although we got in fights back in
town both with the Franky Family
and the Galley-La shipwrights,
we're all going after the same enemy now.
Listen. We're comrades.
Gum-Gum...
Three-Hundred Pound...
We're gonna crash!
...Cannon!
W-We got through!
Hey, is that you, Luffy?
Oh, Sanji! How's it going
over there? Where's Robin?
Robin-chan is still in their custody.
Nami-san just told me
the reasons for her actions.
I see.
Yeah... Well... that's what's going on.
Go ahead and give them hell.
Don't be reckless, Luffy!
Tell him to wait until we catch up!
Hey, Cook! Can you hear me?!
There are crazy guys on that train, so...
That's okay.
Zoro...
What would you do if it were you?
Hm?
After hearing that Robin lied and was
taken into custody in order to save us,
could you just stay put?
It's no use trying to stop him.
Hey, Moss Head! Are you worried about me?
Why would I be, you idiot?!
But sorry...
After hearing what Robin-chan was thinking...
...even if the Captain orders it,
I'm not gonna stop!
I'm...
...not coming.
It no longer has anything to do with me, right?
If the World Government itself
becomes your enemy at last,
I don't wanna be part of it.
You'll join with Luffy and
the others as well, right?
I'm sorry, but I'm no longer
honor-bound to go rescue Robin!
I left the Straw Hats!
See ya.
Oof.
Ah!
Ahhh! I found them!
Oh, shoot!
Metallic Star!
Who's there?!
He told me everything.
I heard that you guys want
to rescue a mademoiselle.
That alone is reason enough
for me to lend a hand.
I will fight alongside you!
My name is...
...Sogeking!
"Sniper Warrior
Sogeking"
I was born on the island of snipers
I never miss my mark
Lulu lala lu
Whether it's a mouse's eyeball, lock on!!
Or even your heart, lock on!!
The man who hails from the island of snipers
Lululu, lulu lala
Now... run away!
Sogege, soge, soge
Sogeking!
"Sniping"
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"A Mysterious Man Appears?!
His Name Is Sogeking!"
"Sniper Warrior
Sogeking"
♪ I was born on the island of snipers ♪
♪ I never miss my mark ♪
♪ Lulu lala lu... ♪
What the heck is he doing?
Well, try to understand his feelings.
He feels that he can't go rescue
her outright as a friend.
So this is his own way of settling things.
♪ The man who hails from
the island of snipers... ♪
Geez... what a pain.
Hey! Come over here!
Oh, okay.
Okay, then. We'll have the meeting
for Operation Rescue Robin-chan now.
We've never met before. Don't you
guys have any questions about me?
First of all, the car you guys were in
was #6, so there are five more cars left.
You know, like,
"Where is the island of snipers?"
Robin-chan is in one of those cars.
Why, it's in your heart!
By the way, are you strong?
I'm super strong, you idiot!
I'm especially strong this week!
If we can rescue Robin-chan
in the end, we win, but...
...there are a lot of enemies.
If we carelessly jump the gun
and get surrounded
in a small space like a train,
that'll be a problem.
So it's probably best if we
avoid any unnecessary fights
and crush the main forces in turns.
Makes sense.
It's best if we don't fight.
That sure is a good point, Sanji-kun.
So, that leads me to a possible strategy.
Huh?
Look... Listen carefully.
Th-This is...
Amazing...
Okay! Now I'm ready for battle!
Hm? What're you guys doing?
Don't "What're you guys doing?" us!
How dare you so openly change in
front of everyone, you shameless girl?!
Nice shamelessness.
I couldn't help it. We only have one car.
Hide your belly! Belly and legs!
You guys, too, Square Sisters!
People like you corrupt society!
Shut up, you shy man.
Shy man.
You little...
If you like, I'll change, too.
I'm sorry, but please don't! Seriously!
What rude guys.
Dammit!
I wish they had made the pockets
in these black shorts bigger.
Don't pack meat in your pockets!
You guys seem refreshed.
You're full of enthusiasm.
Of course! This is in order to rescue Robin!
We'll beat them all up this time for sure!
You'd better! If you get stuck
somewhere again, I'm not gonna forgive you!
I'll be fine! I've got a
reason I won't lose this time!
A reason...
Hm? Nami, did you change your weapon?
Hm? No.
After we came back from the sky island,
Usopp improved it and
made it stronger using dials.
It's the Perfect Clima Takt.
I see. So it's Usopp's...
That's right! It's Usopp's...
Yeah... It's his last work.
Don't go bumming people out!
Ready? Well then, let's go.
An intruder?
Y-Yes, sir. That's what I heard.
It's not possible to get on board
Puffing Tom while it's running.
If there really is an intruder,
it means that we let him come
on board when we departed.
Good grief...
Coo coo.
I agree. It's embarrassing.
But at the same time, it's not possible
to get off while it's running, either.
The intruder as well as the criminals
are certainly still on this sea train.
Keep calm and look for them.
Yes, sir!
"Car #7"
Captain T-Bone... Hiding in a
small place like this would be hard.
Hm?
Good evening!
There they are!
They're behind the door!
We've found three suspicious men,
including the criminals!
They're in car #7! Corner and capture them!
The way you're using the hammer is no good.
Shut up!
Stop this futile resistance!
Open the door!
Hurry up and board it up!
I-I know.
Guys! This way! Suspicious men
were found in car #7!
You found them?!
Let those in car #3 know, too!
We'll corner them and capture
the criminal Franky alive!
There's no place to escape to!
Seize them carefully!
Hey! Stay back!
Whoa! They started shooting!
Hurry up, Soge!
Well, a little help would be nice!
Don't shoot blindly! We can't kill them!
Dammit!
Captain T-Bone...
Step aside.
I hate crooked sword attacks.
Right-Angle Flash!
Bone Soir!
I hate crooked sword attacks.
Right-Angle Flash!
Bone Soir!
Th-They're not here!
Are they on the roof?!
Hurry up! Our enemy is at
the very end of the train!
Now! Hurry!
Don't tell me...
All, go back to the front cars! This is a trap!
A trap?!
--What the...?!
--Go back! This is a trap!
What?!
Even if we want to go back, the door is...
Who was that?!
The cars are detached!
What?!
Dammit! They're the ones who did it!
You bastards! You'll regret this!
So it was too late...
Well then, gentlemen! Watch out
for Sea Kings! Have a nice trip!
Take care!
Two cars' worth...
With this, at least fifty small fries
or so must've been taken care of.
But, Sanji-kun...
Aren't Straw Hat Luffy and the
others coming on the same railway?
Well, they'll probably do something about it.
Y-You bastards! Time to be
blown away along with the door!
Oh, going somewhere?
What?!
All right, then. Let's take care of
the remaining five cars, shall we?
Y-You son of a bitch! Don't think
you can get away with this!
How dare you do such terrible
things to even Captain T-Bone?!
Hey! Report this to CP9!
So there are more small fries?
Frit... Assorti!
Sogeking... Gunpowder Star!
Strong... Right!
--What?
--Huh?
Heavyweight bullets... Fire!
Whoa!
They hit him!
--Ow...
--Wha...
Fire! Fire!
How come the gun isn't working?!
Huh?!
Hey! What the hell are you?!
Hm?
Oh, I'm a cyborg.
A cyborg?!
That's right. Steel and weapons
are built into my body.
If I'm shot, it hurts a little
and sometimes it bleeds too,
but, well, it doesn't work.
Something like that is possible?
The world is a big place, huh?
Amazing!
--How's this?
--Ouch!
What're you doing, you jerk?!
What? Isn't a needle small enough
that it doesn't hurt at all?
You idiot! How dare you
start a dreadful experiment?!
Then, I'll tell you this before you
go any further. The back is different!
Look. I did the makeover by myself,
so I couldn't reach the back side.
Only the front side is cyborg.
I see...
Well then, while I'm at it,
I'll tell you one more thing.
My belly tends to feel cold.
Why do you think that is?
How would I know?
That's because I've got a
fridge in my belly to chill cola.
Whoa! That's handy!
That's amazing! That'd be great for hot days!
Hey! This is no time for a conversation like that!
We've beat all the enemies in this car!
It's cleared! Let's go to the next car!
Next is car #4.
"Car #4"
I'm Wanze! I'm mad, mad Wanze!
Huh?
Now, now, now!
I'm Wanze!
Hey, you guys! Are you hungry?
I'm Wanze. I'm the head steward,
so I can cook anything!
Would you like ramen noodles?
Well then, I'll make ramen noodles.
But before that, there's a snippet
of knowledge I want you to have.
My nose hairs look like this!
They're reticulate inside, which means
they look like fishnet pantyhose.
Keep that in mind!
"Flour"
Okay, then! First, I'll put the flour
in my mouth and knead it well.
Now, bon appetit!
Who'd eat that?!
That was a waste of time.
Wanze, we're keeping someone waiting.
So, we're in a hurry. See ya.
Hold it!
If you want to pass through this car,
you'll have to defeat me first!
Are you trying to stop us?
I will stop you! Now, now, now!
For this escort mission on the sea train,
I'm here to deal with attacks
like this just in case they happen!
If you want to let the criminal free,
then beat my Ramen Kenpo!
R-Ramen Kenpo?!
"R-Ramen Kenpo?!"
That son of a bitch! He's mocking me!
Don't be taken in, idiot!
You're playing right into his hands!
Now, now, now! How was my
impersonation of that idiot?
--Grrr!
--Like I said, don't be taken in!
Now, now, now, now!
What a restless guy.
What?! The bullets grazed him,
and yet his expression didn't change.
He even looks relaxed...
I-I thought my heart would jump out of my skin!
So you were shocked?!
Don't show confusing expressions!
I'll take care of an annoying jerk like him!
Wait, you guys.
If you're taken in by him like this all
the time, it'll just slow things down.
I'll make short work of him.
What upsets me is that someone
like you would call yourself a cook!
I'm talking to you!
Hey! You've been taken in!
But look! He dodged Sanji's kick easily!
What's with his relaxed expression?!
I thought I was a goner!
So you were shocked?!
Stop that pattern!
At any rate...
...leave this guy to me.
You guys go to the next car.
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end, we can all surely smile
I'm gonna beat you up using
my mad, mad Ramen Kenpo!
I hate those who play with food!
Don't talk so saucy when you're
an amateur who can't even cook!
Pardon me for being saucy.
This isn't quite a token of my apology,
but shall I show you how a first-class
cook handles kitchen knives?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Showdown Between Cooks!
Sanji vs. Ramen Kenpo"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!