Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Throw that gas mask away!
Gum-Gum...
You... damn caterpillar!!
Please, leave the ship, Sanji-san.
"Zeff and Sanji's Dream;
The Illusory All Blue"
You're no longer one of us.
I don't want to kill you.
...Bazooka!!
No way!
Pearl... Cymbals!
Oh, no!
Die!
If I can get my arms and
legs out, the game is mine!
Ghin!!
No matter how incredible he was
in the past, he's now a mere cook.
Chore boy!!
What?!
I won't let you shoot poison gas!
This is gonna end it... for sure!
I took everything away
from that damn geezer...
It's easy to blow his brains out.
Stop scampering about, anchor boy!
Even if hundreds of
weapons are built in,
You want to save this man,
right, Sanji-san?
So that I could live...
he can be defeated by someone
with a spear of blind determination.
Please, leave the ship without a fight.
His power...
His dream...
He can be defeated by someone
with a spear of blind determination.
I don't want to kill you.
I know an idiot who's holding back
that spear for a stupid reason...
D-Dammit!
Leave the ship?
At least...
No way!
Ghin! You don't have to listen
to what that weakling says!
...that kid doesn't have any hesitation.
This restaurant is that geezer's treasure!
Man, do you look stupid,
you damn geezer.
I'm gonna kick his ass now!
Is it a survival instinct?
If you're like that, you can't set
a good example for the fighting cooks.
I... I can't repay the damn
geezer for his kindness
Don't mock Don Krieg!
Or does he not fear death
because he has faith in himself?
Hmph! I don't need a lecture
from a little brat.
All... Blue...
unless I risk my life for him, too!
He's the strongest man.
You can't defeat him.
Where do you get off calling me
"little brat," you damn bastard?!
Faith...
Gum-Gum...
Quit treating me like a kid already!
I'm the strongest man!!
Stop it! Keep your hands off of them!
Come to your senses, you idiot!
That man is trying to kill you!
That darn Sanji...
He sure isn't gonna
forsake Owner, is he?
This is where you die!!
...Battle-Axe!!
Don Krieg... We lost.
I deserve it...
Ghin! Point that gun at me.
since I couldn't fulfill my role,
shamelessly losing to emotion...
Chief Commander!
Are you stupid?! You'll die!
Maybe...
Thanks for everything, Sanji-san.
M-My Mighty Battle Spear is...
What the hell did you do?!
Sanji-san... Why?!
This is... This is a
well-deserved punishment!
"Coolheaded, Coldhearted Demon;
Pirate Fleet Chief Commander Ghin"
When he wakes up, could you tell him...
If you want to die so bad,
I'll kill you in a refined way...
I gave it five punches.
--Ghin!
--Why... Why?
I guess that's it for your spear.
Maybe... I can live
only a few more hours...
Ha! So you showed your pride
at the end... But it's too late.
Don't move if you don't want
your Owner's head blown off.
That kid is pretty good.
It's kind of stupid that I'm resolved
because I don't have much time left,
He might do it...
Die together with that cook!
but this time, I want to do it with
my own will... in my own way...
The Absolutely Natural Pearl... Surprise!
This is bad...
Deadly Poison Gas Bomb... M... H... 5!
I never imagined the Mighty
Battle Spear would be broken...
Then, there'll be nowhere
for me to escape, right?
Sanji! Why aren't you dodging?!
The fin's been smashed!!
You don't have to think about stupid
things like fearing your enemy
If I did, that damn underling
would pull the trigger.
But he's taken that many explosions.
His body can't keep up...
or how to keep from getting hurt...
I learned it from that guy.
"I Won't Die!
Fierce Battle, Luffy vs. Krieg!"
How dare that brat do such a thing?
Why? If you abandon this restaurant,
everyone's life will be saved.
It's a no-brainer, isn't it?!
Well, then! We gratefully
accept the boat.
Is he trying to destroy the ship?!
This restaurant is that
damn geezer's treasure!
Ghin! Blow Zeff's brain out!
We don't have to return it, right?
--It's coming!!
--Dive into the sea!!
Right. If you have the courage
to come here to return it,
Owner! Get inside the restaurant!!
Do it already!
I took everything away
from that damn geezer...
try it, you small fry.
B-But he saved our lives
by giving us 100 meals!
"The Conclusion Of The Deadly Battle!
A Spear Of Blind Determination!"
He's right! Just keep
this in your brain!!
Let me borrow those.
Sanji! Ghin! Use these!
His power...
This is the sea restaurant
Baratie, where cooks fight!
--Chore boy!
--Now for mine!
--Ghin, you son of a bitch!
--Hey!
His dream...
--Prepare yourself...
--Huh?!
Hmph! What a scary restaurant...
Ahh! Everyone dived into the sea!
I didn't really attack
you guys or anything...
This is a big enough foothold.
So... I don't want that damn
geezer to lose anything else!!
...I only broke the fin.
With a foothold this size,
I can kick your ass.
Hey, chore boy!
What do you think you're doing?!
Sanji! Watch out!!
"Set Sail! The Seafaring Cook
Sets off with Luffy"
Pearl... Cymbals!
--I'll sink it.
--What?!
Ahhh! What do I do?! What do I do?!
What do I do?! What do I do?!
What?
With the spear blade broken,
that's just a bomb on a stick.
Sanji!!
I'll sink this ship.
Huh?!
The power is cut by half.
You think so?
That ain't funny!
--The All Blue?
--Yeah!
Yeah, I do.
I was wondering how you'd explain that...
Are you crazy, you damn bastard?!
It's a legendary sea.
It's definitely out there somewhere!
A bomb on a stick? So what of it?
This is force.
Given the shape you're in, it's more
than enough force to blow you away.
If I destroy the ship,
there'll be no reason for them to attack.
What?!
Ahh! My hat! My straw hat!!
With your body falling apart like that,
What do you know?
What do you know about
whatever you say
sounds like just a bluff.
It's right there.
Don't be silly! Though there
is a legend like that.
Huh? Oh, yeah. Here it is.
the significance of
the kindness I received?
It's not a bluff.
So you're awake?
What do you know
about this restaurant?!
Oh? Where're those guys?
Well, we're seafaring cooks, so we've
all dreamed of that sea at one point.
So you're gonna die for the restaurant?
Are you stupid or something?
Just give it up!
The moment you defied me,
--They left... thanks to you.
--Me?
I... I'm saved... Good thing
I found that mask when I did...
What'd you say?!
Ghin said, "I'll see you
again in the Grand Line."
Right? I'll definitely
find that sea some day!
Dying isn't...
you signed your death warrant!
Dying isn't something you
should do to repay kindness!!
I won't die! Bleah!
Ghin did?
You say you'll find it, but...
That's not what he saved you for!
--To you?
--No, to you!!
Do you know what kind of place
the All Blue is to start with?
Wh-What a crazy bastard...
Being given life and yet dying...
is something that a weakling would do!
Hey! I'm over here!
I can't believe he used
poison gas in battle...
Yes, I do! Don't insult my intelligence!
That monkey!
Speaking of which,
since I drove them away,
The East Blue, West Blue,
North Blue, and South Blue...
Then is there any other way
to settle this matter?!
He's a devil...
Ooh ooh ahh!
today is my last day
to do chores, right?
Yeah, no human being
would do something like that!
Congrats.
A sea where fish from
all four seas live...
By the way, will you...
He keeps hopping around!
I'm not going!
I won't become a pirate.
That's the All Blue.
Now, now, you guys... Stop fighting.
To seafaring cooks,
that's an irresistible paradise!
I'll continue to work as a cook here
until I get that damn geezer
to acknowledge my skills.
It's simply disgraceful for you to fight
among yourselves after all this.
It's useless!
That's my dream!
Okay, then I give up.
Oh, yeah! There's all sorts of seafood
from all over the world in that sea.
You can't do any more reckless things
while the hostage is with us anyway.
Just how many built-in
weapons does he have?
Are Sanji and the chore boy okay?
Your hand hasn't given up yet!
Not sure... Look!
The poison mist is clearing up!
It was unfortunate for you guys to have
the Krieg Pirates as your opponent.
Cooks would be itching for
the chance to show their skills!
Yeah. It's worth risking your
life to look for that sea.
I can't leave here...
since they're all undependable...
--That is, if such a sea exists...
--What?
But I'm hoping to go some day...
to the Grand Line.
Gum-Gum... Gatling!
Burn to death with my Fire Pearls!
There's no way a miracle sea
like the All Blue could exist...
It's obvious if you just
give it a little thought...
Ghin!
It's probably a big lie told by some
daydreaming cook somewhere...
Then let's go now.
Let go...
It's not the right time yet.
--What's that?!
--Amazing...
Let go of the mask!
Now, enough with the silly stories.
Go collect plates, Sanji!
Huh?
What the hell is that?
Say... do you know the All Blue?
--Ghin!
--Where's your mask?!
I see a ton of arms...
All right, chore boy!!
No...
Ahh... How wasteful...
leaving this much food...
Get him!!
Oh, you don't?! It's a miracle sea!
Did you... give me your mask?
--Ghin!
--Why... Ghin-san?
This one has barely been touched.
I was sure they'd like it.
Ghin!
The East Blue, West Blue,
North Blue, and South Blue...
Sorry, Pearl. Out of my way...
Customers these days
sure are pampered.
What an idiot.
You're in pain right now
because you feel indebted
Fish from all those
four seas live in that sea!
You guys stop eating
the customers' leftovers.
just because someone
gave you some food.
I ditched food that
looked rotten earlier.
Well, I guess idiots
don't learn until they die...
Ghin! Are you going to betray us?!
To us cooks,
it's a dream-like paradise!
Saying things like that shows you're
still just halfway to being a cook.
Weak!
I'm sorry, Don Krieg.
He saved our lives.
That's what the Grand Line is like.
So, have you heard...
Your punches are powerless
against this wootz Steel Armor!
Don't forget we're seafaring cooks.
The sea is an unpredictable place,
so it's best not to waste food.
That bastard... even after he threw
the gas mask away as ordered...
You can't even make a dent in it.
I don't want him to die this way.
At least... At least...
He looks so happy...
Is that how he talks
to his loyal subordinate?!
Why don't you have some, too, huh?
Gum-Gum Pistol!!
That idiot...
I don't want it!
...please let me bury him with my hands.
Everyone, please calm
down! Calm down!!
Guys!! Meal time!!
Have you lost your mind,
Pirate Fleet Chief Battle Commander?
Don... Don Krieg...
Aw, man...
We can finally eat!
Pirates!
Food! Food! Food!
Don!!
Pirates?!
Are you all right, Owner?
Ghin...
Owner! Please hang in there!
How impudent!!
Chief Battle Commander?
That ship is... The Cook Pirates...
Red Foot Zeff's ship!
Hey, where do we sit?
Ghin... It seems...
Then he wasn't an underling?
Where's our food?
To think that he cracked the
shield guy's shield... How powerful...
It seems that you picked
the wrong man to follow...
So they came back
from the Grand Line!
Useless! Useless! How useless!!
There're no chairs for you.
Sit on the floor and eat.
This armor won't break, even with
hundreds of monkey punches!
No chairs? That can't be true!
This is a restaurant!
See? It worked great...
my plan to lure him out...
So you're actually sympathizing
with that idiot scum?
Liar! You really were going to
break the ship, weren't you?!
--Scum?!
--That's right.
I think I'm pretty close...
Guess we can't help it...
An idiot who loses sight of our
goal and can't follow my orders
They're acting kinda weird...
--Sanji-san!
--What?!
I take it you're the pirate captain
Red Foot Zeff. How can I help you?
I wanted you to leave this ship unhurt,
Hmph! Nothing new...
no longer holds value to me.
He's gone...
I'm right here!
There's no guarantee that
he won't betray me again.
but it looks like that's not gonna happen.
Hey! Who prepared
the soup this morning?!
Steal!
You got that right.
It's out of love that I put him out of
his misery now. Wouldn't you agree?
I can't let you have this restaurant
even if it means risking my life.
Steal all the valuables from them!
Hey, I did it! I did! Isn't it good?
I-I never imagined that Don would
actually kill the Chief Commander...
Now listen. The ultimate force
means the strongest equipment
I made it especially good today!
Then, at least burying you
with my own hands is...
I can't eat damn nasty soup like this!
What is this, pig feed?!
and the strongest power!
C-Can't be true...
There's no way he would!
Dammit! I'm not gonna be killed!
...my way of settling this matter.
The strong one is the one
who survives. The strong one is!
Ghin-san is his right-hand man!
I'm not gonna be killed
by bastards like them!
Hmph! Thanks. To hell with you!
That's right. No one has been more
faithful to Don than Ghin-san!
Whoa!
You too, Straw Hat.
What's this kid?
Hey, is human food not to your liking,
you damn racoon dog?
Hey, kid. Don't swing things
like that around. It's dangerous.
Well... I won't lose
against weaklings like you.
Then, that'll be me! Gum-Gum...
That time, too. When Fullbody's
Navy ship came after us
Ha! When it's this bad, it's art now.
I'm bleeding. It's a serious injury.
Useless! Useless! It's useless!!
right after we escaped
from the Grand Line...
Even pride will only get you so far!
Shut up! I'm not gonna be killed
by bastards like you!
It makes me sick to my stomach!
You bastard!
Yeah... He acted as
a decoy all by himself,
What did you just say
to our Chief Commander?!
I'm sorry, but I'm really
confident about today's soup.
pretending to be Don...
"To hell with you"? "Weaklings"?
How dare you run your mouth like that!
--Sanji!
--Stop it! Don't fight back!
There's something wrong
with your taste buds!
...Bazooka!!
He always risked his life
fighting for Don Krieg...
We're the Krieg Pirates,
the strongest pirates in the East Blue!
Seems he's got a death wish.
Kill that brat already!
I never imagined... that Don
would actually try to kill him...
I don't want to die! If I'm
gonna be killed by you bastards,
Wasn't it just because you had
the biggest number of pirates?
Ugh! This is nasty!
I'd rather kill you first!
I can't eat it!
--How evil...
--Patty! We have an antidote, don't we?!
No good. This is all you can do.
Right, guys?!
Sanji!
Yeah, we do...
but that's for food poisoning.
Oh, boy... You struck at
the heart of the matter...
I can't eat something like this!
--Boy, you did it, Captain.
--You have no mercy.
This is damn nasty soup!
So I was right...
It doesn't matter what it is,
just bring it over here!
What?! The strongest
armor is cracking?!
--You son of a bitch!!
--I'm gonna kill you!!
--Stop mocking us!!
I can't eat soup like this!
Idiot! If you wanna save him,
put the mask on him right away!
This is terrible!
Someone, give me some water!
Back off!!
What do you think
you're doing, you bastards?!
It should have some sort
of detoxifying effect!
Don Krieg!
But it's too late.
You're done for, anchor boy!
But...
You're a sham Sous Chef after all...
Bring him to the second floor
and let him breathe well.
If you get upset when called weak,
that just proves that you are weak.
I'm not gonna die!
You're just an old-timer.
If there's a chance to save him,
that's the only way!
We're sick and tired of you
settling matters with violence!
I...
Hurry up, Patty! Carne!
If the food's bad, we're gonna say so!
It's a trap! Get out!!
The result will decide
if you're strong or weak.
I will find the All Blue some day!
All right already!
Me too?!
What'd you say?!
You've got me. Don't get so worked up!
Ha! It's no use. Even if he stays alive,
it'll be an hour at most...
We're seafaring cooks.
Don't waste even a drop of soup.
Y-Yes, sir!
He said "All Blue"!
Ghin!
Chore boy!!
What an ambitious goal!
Finishing off that cook
is your responsibility.
Don't you dare die, Ghin.
Captain, tell him... that it didn't
exist even in the Grand Line.
I'll take care of that
naive idiot over there...
Don't let someone like him kill you!
Understood, Don Krieg.
That idiot! He's still
spouting that nonsense...
Cling to life! Got that?!
I'll kick his ass for you!
--Hey, brat!
--Hm?
D-Don't. You can't... defeat him...
I'll make you fully experience the true
power that conquered the East Blue.
Owner!!
Is it a survival instinct?
You geezer!
Or does he not fear death
because he has faith in himself?
Cool down! Attacking head-on
What is this damn nasty soup?
It's like sludge!
would be playing right
into his hands. You'll die!
I'm not gonna...
I'll teach you that your devil fruit
or whatever it is means nothing.
If we serve something like this,
our restaurant will go out of business!
I'm not gonna be killed by damn
pirates in a place like this!
--Gum-Gum...
--What?!
I won't die.
Don't be ridiculous,
you damn geezer!
Just how is this soup
different from yours?! Tell me!
--Go ahead and shoot
as much as you want.
--Hey!
All your griping's getting annoying....
Captain! Let's withdraw!
This storm is bigger than we expected!
...Bazooka!!
Such a fool... The easiest enemy
to kill is one who's in a frenzy.
From my soup?
I'll kick your ass. It's as simple as that.
Okay, guys! Hurry up
and take the treasure on board!
The sea is your hell, anchor boy.
You're heading towards...
I'm coming over now.
You just wait there!
Don't flatter yourself!
We're withdrawing!
Owner punched him...
--Here comes...
--Bombs!
He didn't kick...
...your graveyard!
What impudence...
My graveyard?!
It'll be a billion years before you can
give me a lecture on cooking, little brat!
I'm a man who has cooked
on seas around the world.
Oh, no! Get out of there, chore boy!
He got hit!
--This is it for that cook.
--That's right.
--Sanji!
--Dammit!
--All right!!
--Good job!!
--You're the best, chore boy!!
When Ghin-san holds that weapon
in his hands, it means he's serious.
Captain!!
He's dead...
Chore boy...
I win!!
Dammit!
That damn brat!
--You little...
--Gum-Gum...
Don't get carried away, brat!!
That damn geezer! I... I...
His nickname is... Demon...
Ugh! He's still alive!
Hit me...
Captain!!
--Here it comes!
--...if you can!
It doesn't matter if his enemy
is crying or screaming,
I'm not a "little brat" any more!!
Why'd you do that for just one brat?!
Oh, no!
How dirty! That's...
he tortures him to death mercilessly.
He's a demon who doesn't
have a shred of sympathy...
...Pistol!!
Can you escape?! It's a steel net!
What?!
This soup is super good, you know...
I'm sorry, Sanji-san,
but you can't defeat me.
--We know that.
--Huh?
Sanji's cooking skills are
recognized by everyone here.
Just keep saying that, you small fry.
Below us is the ocean.
The game is over, anchor boy!
It's not bad at all.
Yeah, this soup is very well made.
I'm the one who's
getting the last laugh!
Boy, that was scary...
He seriously snapped...
Here I come!
Yeah...
All right! That's our Don!
--Make him fall!
--Get him!!
But that idiot won't listen
unless we go this far...
Don Krieg got beaten!
If I can get my arms and legs out,
the game is mine!
You son of a...
What the hell is he?!
--Say, kid...
--Hm?
Why doesn't he flinch?
You were saying that you wanted
a cook for your ship, right?
He hit him along with the porcupine!
Ouch...
--Why does he go that far?
--What?!
This isn't a favor that I'd
like to ask of you or anything,
Sanji!
but would you take that
little brat with you...
Holy shit...
This is gonna end it... for sure!
We've never even seen
Don brought to his knees...
...to the Grand Line?
I warned you...
that you can't defeat me...
He hit Don in his face! And he did it
through that Porcupine Cape!
The Grand Line... is his dream.
Gum-Gum...
C... Can you believe that?!
Man, Owner, you really
made us put on quite a show.
See you...
Just accept your defeat!
I was worried that he might figure
it out because of your bad acting.
Is this... my graveyard?
...Giant Gavel!!
Your acting was horrible, too.
Yeah! Our Chief Commander
is really incredible!
I'll have another bowl of soup!
Or... your graveyard?
--Me, too!
Crush him, Ghin-san!
--Sanji!
--Sanji! Come on!!
My... graveyard?!
Die!
I can hear everything,
you damn idiots...
So you've come to, little brat?
You're very lucky.
...Giant Gavel!!
Don't think... you can send me
to my grave with stuff like this.
Pirate! Ow, ow, ow...
There's no way you can move!
Whose kicks do you think you took?
What about the ships?
I'm not gonna die here.
Who knows? The sea was very rough.
So what do you say, kid?
I wouldn't be surprised if
they were completely destroyed.
No.
We're the only ones
who washed up here.
What?!
I thought you wanted
a cook for your ship.
There's no fruits or animals
on this rocky mountain.
--Don Krieg...
--Don... Don was defeated! Why?!
Or are you saying that he's
not good enough for you?
There're at least fish in the sea,
--Dammit! Why? Why was Don...
--All right, chore boy!!
--Good job!!
but since the rock has
been curved by the waves,
He's good enough, all right.
I do want him to come with me.
we won't be able to come back up
once we go down. Isn't that sad?
But he says that he wants to
continue working here as a cook.
--He really did it!!
--A-Amazing!!
Hmph! It's all your fault!
I'll kill you!
He's crazy...
Even if you guys ask me to
take him with me, I can't.
Is this real? This is Don Krieg
we're talking about!
That cook landed a blow on Ghin-san...
Just keep complaining. We have no
choice but to wait for help anyway.
So strong! He's too strong!
So you're saying that
you can't agree to it
Don't tell me Ghin-san
is gonna be defeated, too...
If no one comes, we'll just
dry up and turn into skeletons.
until he tells you so himself, huh?
You see idiots like that
every once in a while...
Wh... What's all this fuss?
You fools...
A skeleton?! I will...
Exactly. More, please!
...ones who will fight to the death once
they've set their eyes on a target...
Oh! You've come to!!
What have you seen with
your own eyes all this time?
Well... fair enough.
That bag over there is your share.
He lost! Your Don lost!
But who knows if that twisted
damn brat can just say he'll go...
Ghin is a coolheaded demon
whom I put my trust in.
What?
What?!
Fight... to the death...
That's the food that
luckily washed up here.
That's exactly why I appointed
him as the Chief Commander.
There's no way he can, since he's
an idiot through and through...
You're in trouble if someone
like that becomes your enemy.
It's 5 days worth of food
at most if you eat normally.
More, please!
He'll show his true colors soon.
Use your head and eat.
Good thing that we're both cooks.
But you know, win or lose,
I like guys like him...
Is Sanji really okay?
If you have time to daydream,
go save that kid already!
Wait a second! Is that your share?!
Of course he isn't! Combining
the attacks from that shield guy,
It's huge... at least three
times as large as mine!
he must have at least 5-6 broken ribs.
--Huh?
--He won't be floating up to the surface!
What?!
Those skewered dumplings...
aren't as good... as I thought.
Those with the Devil Fruit power
are hated by the sea
and lose the ability to swim.
Of course! I'm an adult.
My stomach is larger than yours.
What'd you say, you damn geezer?!
Is that the best
the Chief Commander can do?
You should've told me that sooner!
What're you gonna do if it's too late?!
You should be grateful that
I'm even sharing food with you.
Don't expect any pity from me.
--Dammit!
--Sanji!
What is he? A fishman?
He came all the way from the
Fishman Island to eat our dishes?
You damn geezer!
Hm? What's he doing? Is this any
time to be paying attention to others?
Idiot! It's a human and a panshark!
Ah-ha!
Hm? What's going on?
All right! I'll kick his ass
while I have an opening!
Oh? Hey, it's you, Yosaku!
Oh, Big Bro Luffy!
Hm?
You watch the other side of the sea.
--Hey, underling!
--Hang in there!
Where did he go?
Why are you alone?
Where're the others?
As soon as you see a ship, let me know.
What happened to Nami?
Now, breathe!
Breathe in a lot of good air!
Until then, we won't be in contact at all
Don't overexert yourself.
Are you all right? Hey!
Do you want to drink some water? Hey!
because that'd be a waste of energy.
Huh?
Good luck.
It's not that we caught up with her,
That damn geezer!
but from the direction
Big Sis Nami was heading,
This isn't good.
I'm not gonna let him
know even if I see a ship.
we figured out roughly
where she was going.
Do you wanna eat my
special pudding? It's good!
It'll be fine.
I have 5 days worth of food.
Idiot! You want to feed
poison to a poisoned man?!
I see... We can bring her back then.
If I have 5 days, there'll definitely
be a ship or two passing by.
Hey, what do you mean by
poison?! You're one to talk!
Well... If what we're thinking is right,
her destination is a crazy place...
You bastard!!
Do you really intend to fight me?!
But just in case, I'll divide
them up for 20 days for now.
What'd you say?! People say my
meat dishes are the best in the world!
Intend to fight you?
I don't need to do such a thing.
They're considered so delicious
that people think they're in heaven.
If I have 20 days, there'll
be a ship passing by for sure.
What's needed is
a means to kill. That's all.
In any case, we need your help,
Big Bro Luffy. Please come with me.
--Ahh! You can't die on us!
--Hey! C'mon! Don't die, underling!
Hey! Hang in there!!
It'll be all right.
I'll definitely survive. It's easy!
And that's the force that humans have.
Remember it, you damn monkey!
You said you wouldn't die, right?
A-Are you dead? Are you really dead?!
Hey! Really? Are you dead?
Okay! I don't really get it, but got it.
That's your faith, right?!
I'll come with you.
Hey! Are you dead? Really?
Are you really dead?!
What?! If you take a monkey
lightly, it'll scratch you!
Right?!
Shut up!!
I won't die!
Phew, he's still alive...
--Wait!
--Hm?
D... Don Krieg... Is Don Krieg...
Sanji!
We both have foolish dreams.
I'm not gonna die here.
No ship passed by today.
That's all right. I'll just have to
be patient for a couple more days.
Hm?
Really, these guys...
In order to achieve
my goal, the All Blue...
Wh-What's gonna happen to this fight?
All right! His bones
are shattered by now!
Zoro!!
Idiot! That was just dumb luck!
Sanji?
Get him!
There's no way Don would be defeated
by a stupid brat like that! Don't worry!
I don't wanna die...
Yeah. I'll come along...
Dammit! If only he hadn't taken
the damage from the shield guy...
...on your journey to become
"King of the Pirates"!
He should give up his ambition
rather than dying!
He's taken at least 10 hits
of those iron balls by now...
Chore boy...
What?
It should be easy...
to give up your ambition, right?!
I'll be the cook for your ship.
"I'm not gonna die here," you said?
You really do whatever
you want... you small fry!
Is that okay or not?
It's okay!! All right!!
This is the last piece of bread...
It's gotten moldy...
If you won't die here... then...
They're all...
I'm happy for you, Big Bro Luffy!
Yeah!
Yaay! Yaay! We got a cook!
We'll have good food!
Damn... He's really strong...
...who the hell will?!
So that's how it is, everyone.
You will, right?!
Sorry for causing you
all sorts of trouble.
I'll finish you off now!
You will!!
Ha! I don't like it! I wanted to
kick you out from here myself.
Don't struggle any more...
I don't know...
I don't know why, but...
Ahh... How wasteful...
leaving this much food...
...if I withdrew even a step,
What was that?! Pity?
And you decide it so easily?
You guys stop eating
the customers' leftovers.
I feel like those various
important things such as pledges
Don got beaten again!
What the hell is going on?!
Don't underestimate me!
Sorry for making you
resort to bad acting.
I ditched food that
looked rotten earlier.
and promises in the
past will be shattered,
Ah! Ghin-san!
E-Enemies are supposed to die
without even touching Don Krieg...
You knew?!
Why don't you have some, too, huh?
and I won't be able to come
back to where I am now...
I could hear everything,
since you're all stupid.
I don't want it!
Sanji!
What?!
He can be defeated by someone
with a spear of blind determination.
Don's supposed to be
invincible... What the...
That is to say, you're willing
to go that far to kick me out,
Ah! Sanji!
huh, you damn geezer?!
Oh, no! He can no longer bear even
the shock from his own attacks...
I know an idiot who's holding back
that spear for a stupid reason...
What the hell is that brat?!
Why do you always have to
talk like that?! You bastard!
Hmph! That's right, little brat!
I don't like kids to begin with.
Not a single day passed
where I didn't regret
letting a useless one live,
you damn brat.
He's really good!
My last piece of bread...
Ha! Fine by me, you damn geezer!
--All right!
--That's our Ghin-san!
Yeah... I'm blown away...
Enjoy the rest of your life to the utmost.
--He's amazing!
--Get Krieg!
All... Blue...
Yeah, he can do it!
That brat is fighting Don
at his level, without a doubt...
You... damn... bastard...
This isn't a dream, right? Don getting
beaten by someone like him...
Whoa! This is a nice ship.
Is it okay for us to use it?
Don's supposed to be invincible...
Of course! It's Sanji's boat.
As it stands, the legend of
Don Krieg the strongest will be...
Hey, chore boy! Don't you die on me!
You still need more?!
Stop talking nonsense!!
Yeah. Give me more meat.
Just how many days
will you be at sea?
Don't know...
--Kid...
--Hm? Pops!
Do you wanna take this?
Don! What's the matter?!
It's a record of my one-year
journey in the Grand Line.
What the...
Why was Don...
F... Finally, Don Krieg's
strongest weapon...
Don Krieg has been defeated...
Don't need it.
I can't...
The Mighty Battle Spear!
This can't be true...
He's the ruler of the East Blue...
I knew it...
I wonder... if that damn
geezer already died...
I can't... Don Krieg...
What's that? It exploded.
That man is...
That man is... That man is...
I want that marbled meat, too!
Now... I'll see how long you
can keep avoiding this...
Enough already!
That man is...
It'll be a sight, anchor boy.
--Huh?
--I can't...
Even if you say so...
Just take a look at that!
That puny spear from earlier still
left you standing after a few attacks,
I can't do it, Don Krieg!!
His proud armor got shattered
and he's knocked out.
Whoa!! Damn geezer,
is this the sea restaurant?
but this Mighty Battle Spear is different.
He got defeated good.
You're not gonna see it?
As soon as you touch it,
you'll be blown to pieces!!
He's still alive...
Ghin...
I can't... kill this man...
And there's food, too...
"Baratie Employee Guidelines
1. Serving customers... That is 'love'!
And 'love' means 'restaurant'! 2. Motto! Motto! Service motto!"
He's the only man I admired...
I believed he was the strongest!
Wh-What's with that spear?!
There's still that much...
I'll fall, I'll fall, I'll fall...
What'd you say?!
There's that much food!
Wh-What's with that spear?
It was... it was the first time for me...
It explodes every time
he strikes it down?
I'll take it no matter what.
What? My knees...
Hey wait, underling!
If you move around now,
the poison'll pass into your system.
Even when I'm down and out,
I won't take charity from others.
It was all his fault to begin with!
--Don't move around!
I'm saying this for your own good!
--Hey! You're gonna die!
A long battle will be trouble...
For example, Sanji...
I want to live!
He's shed too much blood...
He's not gonna last long...
Take this food away now!
Hm? What is it?
Chore boy! Don't die! Can you hear me?!
Stop whining and eat it already!
Be they arch rogues or jail breakers,
Your overdoing it has
taken its toll on you.
To me, anyone who's
hungry is a customer.
You still have things to do, right?!
You must be reaching your limit...
if these damn bastards
badly want to eat
Sorry, but I'm not a customer.
What did you come here for,
little brat?!
Hey! Don't die! Chore boy!
Darn! With the foothold
rocking like this,
and find their way to this restaurant,
I can understand how a hungry
person feels more than anyone.
I can't fight with full power.
Say... Say something!!
Chore boy! Don't die!!
I'm stumped.
Did you see a ship or something?
there may be a point in our
continuing to fight at this restaurant...
That Mighty Battle Spear
never ceases to amaze me.
You can die for your pride if you want,
but if you eat and survive,
don't you think there's a future for you?
I came to steal your food.
Yeah. The stronger that
big spear is struck down,
Yeah!
We're gonna be busy!
If you think you can kill me, go ahead.
I'll die if I don't eat anyway.
the bigger the explosion it causes.
We'll be fine 'cause I'm here!
It's something that no one
other than Don can handle!
You're such a...
Sorry...
To think you to have this
much food all to yourself...
Ah...
Sorry... Thank you... I thought
I'd die. I thought I was done...
--You're really something else...
--I'm the strongest!!
What?
Uh! Ow! Ouch...
But how powerful he is...
I win! No one defeats my force!!
To think he easily swings around
that super heavy spear,
Delicious... Delicious...
I've never eaten food so delicious.
Geez...
which weighs 1 ton with
those two shoulder guards!
Don! Please stop!
You peeled the skin
too thick, little brat!
Hold him! He's not even conscious!
That's exactly the reason
why Don is the strongest!
That hurt!
It's damn delicious, isn't it?
When someone's cooking seriously,
you should just watch quietly!
--I'll win!!
--Please stop, Don!!
Didn't I tell you that we wouldn't
be in contact until we saw a ship?
I'll win! Using my force!!
What?! Don't get smart,
you little brat!
--Wooaahhh...
--Take this!
I'm not a little brat!
You damn geezer!!
Sorry... You're gonna get yelled at,
because you fed me free, right?
Why? This is all treasure...
Die!!
There's no proof, so there's no
reason for me to be yelled at.
Try this.
It's odd that we can't eat
when we have money.
I... have to win!!
Chore boy!
Did you make it by yourself?
Phew... That was close...
Yeah.
No one had treated me
so kindly before...
How is it?
Cripes, this is damn nasty,
you little brat!
Hey... This bag is filled with treasure...
I'm the strongest man!!
You... damn caterpillar!!
You damn geezer!!
So I can't... kill this man!
Waaahhh!
Come back any time!
Don Krieg... We lost.
What is this?!
What's the meaning of this?!
Where's your food?
You didn't eat anything until today?
I know... I don't intend to betray you.
Chief Commander!
Chore boy!!
Big Bro Cook sure is taking time...
Let's withdraw gracefully
and start afresh.
Yeah...
Hey! Say something!
I don't think what we've done up until
now is wrong or anything, either...
I still respect your power
and I appreciate you as well.
Thanks for everything, Sanji-san.
I was really happy when you
put your trust in my strength
Sure. Don't ever come back!
What happened to your leg?
and appointed me as
the Chief Commander.
--Chore boy...
--Are you all right?!
Sanji-san, when he wakes up,
please tell him I said...
So I've followed your orders
and I will from here on as well...
This is for my longstanding grudge!
Be prepared, Sanji!
Ha! I'm not quite done yet...
You made me angry.
I won't let you die so easily.
But... But...
...I'll see you again in the Grand Line.
That time...
I can't kill... just this one person!
There's no way you guys
can defeat him.
You...
So it wasn't a dream...
In order to save me, you...
When I think about it carefully,
that's the only thing I want to do...
Dammit! That bastard Krieg brings
out weapons one after another...
Don Krieg... If circumstances
allow... is there any way...
It seems that Don Krieg's ambition
became mine as well before I knew it.
There's no way that chore boy can...
What about the food? Did you
give me all the food you had?
Even if hundreds of
weapons are built in,
is there any way you'd let this ship...
this restaurant off the hook...
he can be defeated by someone
with a spear of blind determination.
That's right.
You son of a bitch!
Without that leg, you won't be
able to be a pirate any more!
Let's go.
As if defying my orders wasn't enough,
Maybe... I can live only
a few more hours...
You don't have to say goodbye?
now you're giving me a lecture?!
What's the meaning of this craziness?!
I guess...
--That's okay.
--Sanji!
Why? I didn't ask for your help!
It's kind of stupid that I'm resolved
because I don't have much time left,
Don't catch cold.
How disappointing...
I can't think of any reason
for you to be kind to me!
but this time, I want to do it with
my own will... in my own way...
Morality... Sympathy...
I hate those kinds of things the most.
Why? Why did you?!
Then, there'll be nowhere
for me to escape, right?
Because you...
you had the same dream as me.
Didn't I always say that?!
Hmph! How easy...
Move away, guys...
The hell with loyalty towards Don!
The All Blue...
Don! That's...
I've just been running away using
Don Krieg's name as a shield...
But... even your men
said it doesn't exist...
M... MH5!
Of course it does!
Once you're resolved,
That's the strongest poison gas weapon!
When the time comes,
head to the Grand Line.
Now that makes you worth crushing...
--What?!
--Poison gas?!
you don't have to think
about stupid things
The All Blue surely exists there.
--Ahh! Mask!
--Put the mask on!
--Hurry up!
like fearing your enemy
or how to keep from getting hurt...
As you see, I can't be a pirate any more,
--We'll be killed, too!
--To use a weapon like that...
--That's despicable, you bastard!
I learned it from that guy.
but this time, you can go and find it.
Do you know what's gonna
happen when you use that?!
Stop whining about stupid stuff,
you fools! This is a battle!
Patty! Carne!! Give him the boat
used to go grocery shopping!
H-Hey! Geezer, don't die!
Life or death...
Don't just do as you please
and die as you please!
In a pirate battle, if you fear death
for even a moment, you'll fall to pieces.
What?! Are you stupid?!
Winning is the only goal.
Why do we have to
give our boat to pirates?!
I wonder...
Foul play? Dirty?
What's wrong with that?!
What're you talking about?
What's gonna happen to our
grocery shopping?! You idiot!
At least...
I wonder how many people
died cursing the sea...
He's right! Let those guys swim!
Might makes right.
...the grandness of the sea...
No matter what means we take,
the result is everything.
Just bring it out already!!
Owner Zeff!!
Using poison gas or whatever...
Winning is all that matters.
I've experienced crises like
this where I couldn't eat.
Thank you for all the damn things
--Okay, we got it...
--Don't yell at us...
you've done for me
over all these years!!
At least...
And each time I wish...
That's power.
...that there was a restaurant
in the middle of the sea...
I'll never forget your kindness...
for the rest of my life!!
Okay, okay, we'll bring it out!
...that kid doesn't have any hesitation!
What a horrible bastard...
Restaurant?
Yeah. I was thinking that if
I could leave this place alive,
I'd build a restaurant as
my final purpose in life...
Throw that gas mask away!
It's gonna sink!
All right, then, I'll help
you do that. So don't die!
You're no longer one of us.
Ha! It's impossible for
a weak little brat like you!
Is it a survival instinct?
Die!
I'll become strong, too!
You asshole!!
Or does he not fear death
because he has faith in himself?
So... don't die!
Why did I hesitate?
What was I so worried about?
I won't let you shoot poison gas!
I'll miss you, dammit!
When I think about it, I feel stupid...
Faith...
Stop scampering about, anchor boy!
I'll miss you!!
Hey!!
Y... You son of a bitch!!
Help!! Help the geezer!
D-Dammit!
Well, then! We gratefully
accept the boat.
I'll miss you!!
Help the damn geezer!!
I feel sad, dammit!
Ghin! You don't have to listen
to what that weakling says!
We don't have to return it, right?
--Alright! You're amazing!
--Chore boy! Go for it!!
--Get him!
Right. If you have the courage
to come here to return it,
I'm gonna kick his ass now!
Hey!! Hey!! Hey!!...
try it, you small fry.
Don't mock Don Krieg!
I told you... that this is where you die!!
You idiots!
He's right! Just keep this in your brain!!
Men should part without a word.
He's the strongest man.
You can't defeat him.
This is the sea restaurant
Baratie, where cooks fight!
I am the strongest man!!
Yeah!!
Come to your senses, you idiot!
That man is trying to kill you!
Hmph! What a scary restaurant...
That damn geezer gave up
his leg so that I could live.
I deserve it...
Let's go!! Set sail!!
...since I couldn't fulfill my role,
shamelessly losing to emotion...
I'll see you again, you damn bastards!
Wha?!
The fleet Krieg gathered...
His hundreds of weapons and poison...
This is... This is a
well-deserved punishment!
I... I can't repay the damn
geezer for his kindness
If they're all force...
--Ghin!
--Why... Why?
unless I risk my life for him, too!
Ha! So you showed your pride
at the end... But it's too late.
...then that kid's spear is also force...
As long as you don't fear even death
because you have faith in yourself,
Why do you get up... Sanji-san?
Die together with that cook!
The spear held in his heart...
you'll find the All Blue... for sure...
Deadly Poison Gas Bomb... M... H... 5!
In order for this place to be
a restaurant as long as possible...
I know an idiot who's holding back
that spear for a stupid reason...
Guys! Customers are
gonna show up soon!
That idiot...
Is he trying to get killed?
Get to work already!
Dive into the sea!!
You damn brat!
Owner! Get inside the restaurant!!
They were nice guys...
Ha! That's such a refined line.
I wonder if they'll let me join them
again when I see them next time...
M-My Mighty Battle Spear is...
What the hell did you do?!
But this restaurant will be closed now...
Let me borrow those.
Sanji! Ghin! Use these!
...and it will change into a pirate ship!
--Chore boy!
--Now for mine!
Ahh! Everyone dived into the sea!
Stop it, you idiot!
Keep your hands off of them!
I gave it five punches.
What's he trying to do?!
Oh, boy... Oh, boy... Oh, boy...
I guess that's it for your spear.
I wonder if I'll be able
to see them again...
Gum-Gum...
...Battle-Axe!!
Prepare yourself...
I wanna be free...
Bellemere-san...
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
It sounds like Nami-san
headed to Arlong Park.
I'll show you whose
graveyard this place is!
Though they call themselves the
strongest pirate group in the East Blue,
Now I'm free from the chores
since pops promised me.
Why is he fighting when
his body's falling apart?
What's that?
You can't stop my ambition
with a silly weapon!
it was just because they had so many
pirates. That's all. Right, pops?
--That's right.
--By the way, will you...
It's a place dominated
by fishman pirates.
Is he trying to get himself killed?!
No, he isn't even thinking about dying.
You talk very candidly.
How come you don't flinch?!
I'm not going. I won't become a pirate.
She couldn't be...
Look. It seems like Ghin
can't defeat Sanji, either.
You don't know?
Are you stupid or what?
Considering her cuteness...
she might be a mermaid...
Okay...
Not quite.
Hey, you haven't given up yet!
Risking life for an ambition and dream...
I used to have a dream like that!
What'd you say? Say that again!
--A water imp?
--I'll kill you!
What're those weapons that
look like skewered dumplings?
But I'm hoping to go to
the Grand Line some day.
"Nami"
--Are you stupid or what?
--Don't repeat it!
--Then a half fishman?
--No meals for you!
He wasn't an underling?
Why?!
--This is it!!
--Chore boy! Don't die in a place like this!
You're the one who told me to say
that again. How selfish you are...
Then let's go now.
On the next episode of One Piece!
It's not the right time yet!
"Coolheaded, Coldhearted Demon;
Pirate Fleet Chief Commander Ghin"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Worst Man in the Eastern Seas!
Fishman Pirate Arlong!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"I Won't Die!
Fierce Battle, Luffy vs. Krieg!"
"The Conclusion of the Deadly Battle!
A Spear of Blind Determination!"
"Set Sail! The Seafaring
Cook Sets Off With Luffy"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!