Geez... Why are all of you
being so stubborn
How could this be happening?
I'm a captain at Navy Headquarters!
even towards your friends?!
I thought I clearly told you all goodbye.
I will not live on in disgrace!
Luffy and the gang have arrived in Enies Lobby.
It's okay... Robin.
I'll never return to the Straw Hats!
I'll stop you guys
by slashing you in two!
This is...
You really think they'd be happy to be alive
I can't allow that…
You'll be fine.
If we can't recover Nico Robin
and Franky on this straight path
a perfect chance to run, right?!
"Iron Fence" "Main Gate"
knowing that it was because their
friend had to sacrifice herself?!
...as our destination lies
beyond where you stand!
You're still hiding something, aren't you?
from the main gate to the Gates of Justice,
Now that they know why you left them,
"Courthouse" "Main Island Front Gate"
"Gates of Justice" "Tower of Law"
they'll follow you to the depths
of hell and take out your enemies!
we will have lost.
That's okay.
Why?! No matter where Robin is taken to,
Bring it on!
we can just keep going after
them until we get her back!
But a pirate... cannot leave their group...
It's you guys who don't get it!
I explained this before we
left Water Seven, didn't I?!
I don't have the slightest desire to be rescued!
Wait!
The only destinations beyond those gates
I won't run away!
I hate crooked sword attacks!
Don't just do as you please!
...without their captain's... permission.
are Navy Headquarters and the deep-sea prison.
Right-Angle Flying Bird…
Wait, Robin-chan.
So we have to settle this matter
before that at any cost.
Three-Sword Style…
Why are you acting like that
at this point?
What are you making a racket for, Nico Robin?
Bull Demon!
So...
Ramen Kenpo!
We came to rescue you
knowing all the circumstances!
She's right.
Noodle Stake Knocker!
...believe...
That being said, even if we all rush in,
If we just do something about the
Government's attack, Buster Call,
…Bone…
Phoenix!
if we encounter CP9, you guys are
the only ones who can defeat them.
...in Luffy.
there shouldn't be a reason that
you have to obey them, right?!
F... Frog!
After the train ride together, I now
know well how strong you guys are.
Ribbit!
That Buster Call is...
So, you guys stay and wait
on the sea for five minutes
Epluchage!
He discerned it?!
Since...
...that day eight years ago...
Bold Hooves!
and charge in to the main island in
Rocketman through the main gate.
...indeed the problem.
Since that incident where
Tom-san was taken away...
We'll go in first and break open the
main gate and the main island front gate
Con...vert!
...you've been challenging
the sea train every single day.
"Convert"
so that the train can pass through.
"Pervert"
Tempest Kick!
After that, we'd like you to keep on
moving no matter how many of us fall.
So that you won't lose those you love again...
R-Roronoa!
Don't tell me he's gonna...
So that you can protect those you love...
Sanji!
He defeated Ship-Slasher!
We're only a little over 60 people,
Ribbit...
but our enemy's forces are
probably well above 2,000 to 3,000.
Yokozuna... Then now's the time for
you to show the result of that training!
To think that he
followed the sea train
Franky...
What happened?
from the detached cars
in this storm…
We'd like you guys to go after only CP9,
avoiding unnecessary battles.
...Centaur!
He appeared from nowhere!
Ribbit?
Wrong way!
How admirable!
Your body should be in front!
At any rate,
But we can't stop here.
Okay, got it.
the Government has now successfully
obtained the two keys...
Okay, guys! We're now
at the front of the island!
I'm sure your justice is deep, too,
Two-Sword Style Sword Draw...
Me, who owns the weapon's blueprints,
but we also shoulder
all sorts of things.
Take a good look at the sky behind Enies Lobby.
This is bad...
I have to do something.
and you, who can revive the existing weapon.
Dang it!
Hiss! You're the very definition
of "all bark but no bite."
Those are the Gates of Justice.
Hold it!
What're you doing?!
So, even if I could escape,
it's pointless if it's just me alone.
Just stay back!
Whoooa! That's huge!
Hey, you! I'll take you...
...Rashomon!
You, too, somehow go back to Straw Hat!
Huh?! He's gone!
That's not possible.
Now, there's no time to lose!
Wh-When did he...?!
Now, now, now, now!
I hurt them just by being with them.
Wh-Where'd he go?!
Aren't you guys being
deceived by that woman, too?!
Where is he?!
Well then, as we planned,
we're gonna go in first!
The people from the Government
say your existence is a sin,
We're not done yet.
She's the lowest of the low,
who lived one betrayal after another,
What the hell is that?!
Leave the backup to us!
It's a Sea King!
and survived until today
in the underground!
but no matter what weapons you're carrying,
your being there isn't a sin.
Hey, you two! Aren't you
supposed to be with us?!
Further ahead on this railway...
I'll take your life!
All fired up to get back Robin, Luffy has...
Take this!
...lies the one who cut that thing up...!
Decoupage!
Hm? Where's Luffy?
It's all right! Now
let's move forward
What? He was right here up until now.
Your existence isn't a sin!
with the sun always in our hearts
Open the main gate!
As power passes through
our clasped hands
Hmph!
let's grab hold of our wishes
Is that Straw Hat?
All, go back to the front cars!
What?!
If you like,
This is a trap!
Whoa...! What the hell is this place?!
Oof!
A trap?!
why don't you add your last
words to them while you're at it, buddy?
What?!
What the...?!
Why the hell is he doing things on his own?!
Working together,
Ultimate Hammer!
That man doesn't have a
clue about the plan at all!
To think that I fell for the enemy's scheme...
let's ride the giant waves
What a blunder!
The gravest blunder of my life!
Is this... a waterfall?!
That was a waste.
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
Well then, gentlemen! Have a nice trip!
He said he got it, didn't he?
there's the starting signal
He's not the type who can wait five minutes.
We should've known.
Now's the time to set sail--
I have to catch up... with the sea train!
...infiltrated Enies Lobby by himself.
I can't see the bottom!
If the criminals
we're supposed to escort
let's raise anchor
Gum-Gum...!
are set free upon the world again...
How noisy.
Cut through
the rainbow-colored wind
Meanwhile, Spandam,
the chief who leads CP9, was...
and head for a sea of adventure
How much blood and how many
Hey, where on earth
did you come from?
Well...
Today is a joyous day when all
eight members of CP9, including me,
Looks like Lucci and the
others are headed this way...
tears will civilians have to shed?!
Yow!
It'll be a journey
fraught with injury
Did you finish taking
care of the ramen guy?
I'll show them that there's justice
even in this unfair world!
are to gather together in one place
for the first time in five years.
but what you cherish most
will be right there
Yeah, I did, just now.
...bringing the best possible gift to us.
And if you get into a jam
And yet, what's up with this article?!
Even if my arms and legs are
torn off by these raging waves...
It's suddenly become noisy.
I'll always be there to protect you
The orders to assassinate
the heads of the local branches
So the soldiers for this escort mission
were annihilated after all, huh?
It's all right!
Now let's move forward
...I will be sure to protect the
innocent citizens' future!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
of the revolutionary army only
required you to kill three of them,
We didn't expect much, though.
but twenty-three of them are dead!
with the sun always in our hearts
If you have an excuse, I'd really like to hear it!
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
They're the ones who
kidnapped Robin-chan, aren't they?
It's all right! Now let's move forward
Yoyoi!
and gaze at the light beyond
Be careful.
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
...waiting for Lucci and the
others in the Tower of Law,
They use strange martial arts.
with the sun always in our hearts
If we gather up
the pieces of our dreams
the back room of Enies Lobby,
with other members of CP9.
As power passes through our clasped hands
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
they'll make a map
leading to tomorrow
...my fault!
let's grab hold of our wishes
"CP9 [Six Powers Master]
Jabra"
Stop it, Kumadori!
So let's grab hold of our wishes
A man shouldn't apologize so easily!
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
under the same flag--
together, we're one
I'll explain what happened
to Chief, so just sit tight!
Who's this?
"CP9 [Six Powers Master]
Fukurou"
He's probably that CP9 newbie
that Corgy was talking about.
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
Iron Body.
One Piece
Working together,
If I remember right,
How regrettable...! I can't die.
he's a Four Power
Master named Nero or something.
let's ride the giant waves
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
Just die already, you jerk!
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Dammit!
we will be able to make it through
You guys, that's enough...
You're gonna get it now!
"The Judicial Island!
Full View of Enies Lobby!"
Now's the time to set sail--
People call me a fighting genius!
Ouch! I spilt my coffee! Dammit!
Always!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
I don't care anymore…
let's raise anchor
Also, they said that Nero was useless.
I'm gonna kill you!
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
Oh, well...
Hey, newbie.
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
and head for a sea of adventure
Y… You must be Rob Lucci, right?
Whoa! What the heck is this place?!
Blueno disappeared?!
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
What a huge hole! It looks
like the island is floating.
It's not that he's disappeared.
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
Sorry that I didn't
introduce myself sooner.
He only made a door
out of the wall of air
Please wait a moment.
but what you cherish most will be right there
I'll kill him first and…
I see a town there, too. I wonder
if Robin is around there...
by using "Air Door,"
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
We're capturing Franky alive.
And if you get into a jam
the true value
of the Door Door Fruit, that's all.
We can't stop here
To think you let your feelings take
control and lost sight of our mission...
You can't escape from us...
I'll always be there to protect you
Around the world
Well, forget it.
There's someone up there!
It's simply not possible.
It's all right! Now let's move forward
Start me up!
I'll give you three seconds.
It's an intruder! Shoot him down!
So hurry up and run.
Oops, they found me.
with the sun always in our hearts
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
Three…
Run…? From whom?
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
Two…
He went inside the gate!
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
What…? Hey!
and gaze at the light beyond
You're kidding, right?!
Luffy passed through the
main gate in one shot and...
One.
Let Robin...
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
Stop it! Don't be foolish!
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
This is the main gate! This is the main gate!
go...
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
This is a report to Chief and
the main island front gate!
Finger Pistol.
What is it? What's going on?
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
So let's grab hold of our wishes
It's all right! Now
let's move forward
An intruder went over the main gate
and is currently dashing towards
the main island front gate!
under the same flag--
with the sun always in our hearts
Brand New World
Oh... It's just an intruder.
Calm down and take care of him.
together, we're one
Start me up!
As power passes through
our clasped hands
Usopp!
One Piece
Iron Body.
Yes, but...
let's grab hold of our wishes
This is the main island front gate.
We confirmed the intruder.
"Landing Operations Start!
Charge in, Straw Hats!"
Did my attack earlier work?
That's a weak kick.
...was approaching the main island
front gate by charging straight ahead.
Hey, hey. Stop.
"Clash! Demon-Slasher Zoro
vs. Ship-Slasher T-Bone"
Working together,
Do you know what this place is?
Deal with him carefully. If my eyes
didn't deceive me, that man is...
let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
Hurry!
Can't we go any faster?!
...Straw Hat Luffy!
How stubborn.
there's the starting signal
Stop it!
Now's the time to set sail--
I won't run away.
What?! What did you just say?!
That should be enough.
let's raise anchor
I think that's Straw Hat...
They're the ones who keep
attacking me.
Hey... Hey, then, Big Bro Franky
sacrificed himself and...
Cut through
the rainbow-colored wind
A pirate with a 100 million-Berry
bounty on his head!
I can't help it.
and head for a sea of adventure
Then let's hurry up and leave.
Yeah, that's right.
It'll be a journey
fraught with injury
He tried to save Robin-chan.
Robin...
Wait!
but what you cherish most
will be right there
And if you get into a jam
It's okay...
What an amazing guy Bro is!
I'll always be there to protect you
Robin.
You'll be fine.
It's all right!
Now let's move forward
We'd better hurry up or it'll be too late.
You're still hiding something,
aren't you?
with the sun always in our hearts
Where is Robin?!
Hey, we can now see the lights of
the nightless island! It's Enies Lobby!
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
What?! Is that true? All right!
What is that?
and gaze at the light beyond
We can go rescue Bro!
That's okay.
If we gather up
the pieces of our dreams
A sea train?
Nightless island?
But a pirate...
Yeah. They don't have nights on that island.
It's also called a day island.
they'll make a map
leading to tomorrow
Is that a new sea train?
cannot leave their group...
That's the judicial island.
So let's grab hold of our wishes
Day island?
under the same flag--
together, we're one
...without their captain's...
There's something there!
permission.
We found them! Huge Yagaras!
One Piece
Hm? What's that?!
So...
--Ribbit!
--Ahoy!
A person?
...believe...
There's someone there!
A-Another report from the main gate!
...in Luffy.
Luffy!
That's Ship-Slasher!
What is it this time?!
--Ribbit! Ribbit!
--Ah! Sanji!
What?!
S-Seriously?!
"Scramble over Robin!
A Cunning Plan by Sogeking!!"
Ship-Slasher?
Huh? Who's that?
He's Ship-Slasher T-Bone,
a Captain at Navy Headquarters!
It's been a while...
A suspicious group on a monster carriage
It's Straw Hat!
has just passed over the front iron fence!
He cuts pirates ships up like steaks!
I'll give you three seconds.
So hurry up and run.
Oh, yeah?
That's amazing!
Please send reinforcements!
It seems that we were able to
join up with them smoothly, huh?
"Amazing"?!
Three…
You're talking
like it's someone else's problem!
Run…? From whom?
Looks like they're ready and willing
Please send...
We can't just sit around like this.
Two…
to march into the entrance
to the World Government!
What…? Hey!
Hey, guys!
Get ready to fire!
That sounds reassuring!
You're kidding, right?!
Hurry up!
Yeah!
One.
Stop it! Don't be foolish!
What happened?!
Shave!
Okay! Enies Lobby has come into sight!
Gatekeeper!
Come in!
What is going on?!
Everyone, get ready for the showdown!
Wait!
What is it?!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
We'd better hurry up
or he'll slash Rocketman!
What were you watching all this time?
Leave it to Zoro.
Don't interfere!
What?
A person like you who does
everything halfway
Well...
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
Today is a joyous day when all
eight members of CP9, including me,
Wait, Robin-chan!
is unfit for CP9!
It's no use.
I'll tell you only once!
Nico Robin will
not break the agreement.
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
are to gather together in one place
for the first time in five years.
Get out of our way!
How can you say that?
And yet, what's up with this article?!
Many years ago,
an island ceased to exist.
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
They couldn't have simply
passed by my subordinates' cars
The orders to assassinate
the heads of the local branches
This island was burned to the ground
without a trace by a Buster Call
Unless you've mastered all Six Powers,
you aren't superhuman, boy.
that were on the same railway.
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
of the revolutionary army only
required you to kill three of them,
What did these guys do to my subordinates?
that was issued by the Navy.
Kalifa.
but twenty-three of them are dead!
Yes.
Inform our chief later…
The only survivor of that
They must be Nico Robin's crewmates...
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
If you have an excuse, I'd really like to hear it!
...that the newbie was so
weak that he was useless.
was the child Nico Robin.
...which means that that
swordsman is the pirate hunter!
Yoyoi!
I am very sorry, Chief!
What?!
Okay.
we will be able to make it through
This path leads to the origins of justice!
Five vice admirals and
ten battleships...
It is all...
Always!
These guys are supposed
to be working for justice?
To that woman who witnessed
their overwhelming military power,
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
I'm a captain at Navy Headquarters!
Can't tell which side is evil, huh?
...my fault!
"CP9 [Six Powers Master]
Jabra"
I will not live on in disgrace!
Stop it, Kumadori!
Buster Call is an
inexpungible nightmare.
A man shouldn't apologize so easily!
I'll stop you guys by slashing you in two!
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
If the terror planted in
her heart during her childhood
I'll explain what happened
to Chief, so just sit tight!
I can't allow that...
"CP9 [Six Powers Master]
Fukurou"
...as our destination
is directed towards her friends,
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
Yoyoi! I'm sorry, Chief!
lies beyond where you stand!
she can no longer
have the spirit to resist us.
Officials from the World
Government sure are ill-mannered.
"CP9 [Six Powers Master]
Kumadori"
Now that it's come to this, I'll take
responsibility by committing hara-kiri!
Don't tell me...
This guy is strong!
This is my duty, so…
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
...you're doing this
knowing all that...
We can't stop here
--Don't be ridiculous!
--Yoyoi!
See?!
Of course.
Around the world
My sense of smell
is absolute, Nico Robin!
You've got it wrong, Chief!
Bring it on!
On the instructed day, we infiltrated
them to carry out the assassinations,
I want you to take off that cape.
Start me up!
You bastards...
but somehow they managed
to find out about our plans.
Now! Now! Now!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
Just how depraved are you bastards?!
I talked about the assassination
plan in town, chapapa!
I hate crooked sword attacks!
Dammit! This is it!
Everything is for the sake of justice.
Right-Angle Flying Bird...
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
What?! You again, Fukurou?!
Three-Sword Style...
I do deeply sympathize
with that woman.
Bull Demon!
What's the point of that zipper on your mouth?!
W… Wait!
Don't give me that crap!
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
And when will your
"foot-in-mouth" problem go away?!
My name is Sogeking.
We're intelligence agents who
have to strictly keep top secrets!
...Bone...
I'm the man
who hails from the island of snipers.
Phoenix!
I talked about it, chapapa!
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Soge?
--Don't "chapapa" us!
--Yoyoyoi!
Wait!
You think you can
get away with this?!
Brand New World
Please don't blame Fukurou!
That's right!
Start me up!
Don't underestimate the resolution
of a man who is willing to go this far.
I'll take responsibility by committing hara-kiri...
L… L… Lucci-san!
"Luffy Cuts Through!
Big Showdown on the Judicial Island!!"
You damn bastards!
Iron Body.
He discerned it?!
How regrettable...! I can't die.
Bold Hooves!
Just die already, you jerk!
Hm? Y... You...!
You guys, that's enough...
I guess I don't have to ask
why you are here, intruder.
Ouch! I spilt my coffee! Dammit!
Hurry up and sit down, Nico Robin.
Given the way you opened the door,
We'll soon arrive in Enies Lobby.
Also, they said that Nero was useless.
it doesn't seem like
you have a lot of patience.
Oh, well...
R-Roronoa!
Yeah, I'm ill-bred, so…
H... Hey!
Wait a sec!
If this is about Nico Robin…
I said wait!
Hey!
…give it up.
What's the matter, Nico Robin?
"Sniping"
This is too big of an issue for you
guys to get yourselves involved in.
Is it okay to let those two
be in the same car?
He defeated Ship-Slasher!
Don't stop.
It won't be too long
before we get there.
There are people in the world who
were born under an unlucky star...
To think that he followed
the sea train
What could happen?
People who are better off
dead for everyone's sake.
from the detached cars
in this storm...
We're not gonna let
them escape anymore.
How admirable!
They are both criminals
who'll be executed shortly.
I was born on the island of snipers
What are you talking about?
But we can't stop here.
For example…
Let them grieve over their
fate as much as they can.
"Sniper Warrior
Sogeking"
I'm sure your justice is deep, too,
"Courthouse" "Tower of Law"
I never miss my mark
Suppose there exists a devil that
would burn the world to the ground.
but we also shoulder all sorts of things.
"Main Gate"
Lulu lala lu
If the person who
can raise this devil
Whether it's a mouse's eyeball, lock on!!
is an innocent girl
who's only eight years old...
Or even your heart, lock on!!
…don't you think…
Hurry! Hurry!
Captain T-Bone, who jumped
out to sea, is in danger!
Are you guys ready?
…that someone
should kill
this girl for everyone's sake?
He could've been hit by that sea train by now.
The man who hails from the island of snipers
Are you hurt?
F... F...
You bastard!
I'm fine, because...
Be careful about what you say!
Huh? What's your point?
Ribbit!
Our captain would slash a sea train
like that into two, you jerk!
...I'm Sogeking!
F...
I'm telling you
that is Nico Robin's life.
Lululu, lulu lala
Frog!
But that swordsman was quite skilled!
Ribbit!
In four minutes... the sea train
Rocketman will charge in!
Now... run away!
Don't "ribbit" me, you jerk!
Full speed ahead!
She is a real criminal now,
Our captain protected us
with his life
The train got derailed
because of your slap!
from a Sea King
that stood in the way!
but it started simple like that.
Sogege, soge, soge
Save our captain!
"Sniping"
Sogeking!
Ahhh! Step aside! Step aside!
Yeah!
Ever since she can remember,
"Main Island Front Gate"
"Main Gate"
We're gonna collide!
her existence itself was a sin.
Ribbit!
We were finally about to catch
up with Sanji and the others!
She can make others happy
only by disappearing.
What're you gonna do about it?!
Ribbit!
That's the misfortune she carries.
You little...!
I'm gonna eat you, jerk!
Roronoa Zoro...
Essentially,
she should've died 20 years ago.
Sogeking from the island of snipers?!
How vexing...
Ribbit!
I'm really glad that this
woman will be put to death.
That's right. I'm Usopp-kun's best friend.
Excuse me, but... please let me pass.
Ow, ow, ow...
I'm here because he requested that I assist you.
What on earth
is going on with this sea train?
Hey…
H-Hero!
I-Is that right?
Hey, are you guys okay?
Even if you ask nicely...
Enough of your crap!
That's right!
Since you're wearing a cape,
I thought that might be the case...
I'm sure it's Sanji-kun and
the others who detached that sea train.
...no means... no!
You son of a bitch!
Amazing! I've never seen a hero before!
Somehow...
Then, are we gonna catch up with them soon?
Don't say anymore!
M... My lower back...
I see... He's a hero because
he's wearing a cape?
Probably.
However, the Government
will probably spend years...
All right!
That's right! Cape buffalos are heroes, too!
We're closing in on our enemy!
Yeah!
Okay. Then...
Really?!
What the hell?!
--Yeah, if someone is wearing a cape,
--Hey, that's Usopp.
...be prepared, okay?!
Our King Bulls disappeared!
--they're usually a hero.
--Usopp... I'm glad he was okay.
How dare you, pirate?!
Gum-Gum...
What?!
Go, Rocketman!
That's the long nose who
marched into the Franky House.
…squeezing out all
of Nico Robin's knowledge,
They disappeared?!
We're gonna
beat up the pigeon guy!
Well, it's probably us
who disappeared.
...Ally Robot!
experience and intelligence.
That's the long nose who got caught with Bro.
We probably got derailed.
Yeah.
How much agony she'll experience
before she dies...
Whoa! That's worse!
N-Nice to meet you.
Ah, yes.
What're we gonna do?!
That's one of the guys I met at Shift Station.
you just watch and--
"What're we gonna do?!"
We can't do anything about it.
We're not gonna let that happen!
Whoa! That's dirty!
Hey, hey, wait, Robin!
May I have your autograph?
We can't attack him like that!
Sure.
You shouldn't go that way!
Zoro!
"To Chopper-kun"
Hey! Seriously! Seriously! Wait!
Wha...
Such an obvious trick! Don't flinch!
But then, where did Usopp go?
You're kidding me...!
Hey, I said, wait!
He's fine. You don't have
to worry about him at all.
Ally Robot... Punch!
Whoa!
Anyway, he told me to put all my
energy into rescuing Robin-kun and left.
Robin-chan!
M-Miracle...
Ahh! Sorry!
Th-This isn't good…
Good! Are you okay?!
Ally Robot... Kick!
Are you hurt?!
Yep. He's right.
Wh... Where is this island of snipers?
Oh, shoot!
Ahhh! I'm so sorry, sir!
When I went to all the trouble
of getting in from outside,
Here we go.
Yeah...
and even brought
that official down!
That's enough! Your back is wide open!
Geez, that darn Yokozuna!
It's...
♪ I was born on... ♪
He's sure got bad timing.
So that's Nico Robin?
Are you guys okay?
She indeed bears a resemblance to
the picture in the wanted poster.
...in your...
Yeah, somehow.
...hearts.
Darn Yokozuna!
We somehow...
--♪ ...the island... ♪
--Our hearts...!
pulled it off?
Well, looks like you guys're okay.
Let's go back together this time!
♪ ...of snipers... ♪
You bastard!
Hey!
I'll bring these guys down
right away, so…
Hm?
Where's that?!
Are we okay?!
Okay, Robin-chan?!
We'd better still
be able to get to Enies Lobby!
No...
Shut up!
there's something different after all.
Bring him down! It's just one unarmed man!
Just wait a sec!
That being said...
Usopp!
What're you doing, Robin-chan?!
we got into a
weird current.
What's going on?
♪ I was born on... ♪
Kokoro-san.
Hm?
Do you know which
direction the island is?
♪ "...the island of snipers..." Go! ♪
Yeah,
Ow…
the sea train comes already
equipped with Eternal Poses
That's right! This smell...!
♪ ...the island of snipers... ♪
This place is filled with the
smell of those filthy pirates!
Even if I explain, you guys
just won't get it, will you?
for the islands with stations.
--Nami-san...
--Hm?
What is it, Sanji-kun?
Then it'll be fine!
I'll check the sea,
so please control the train!
Something is definitely wrong!
And all you idiots here with Nami-san...
Hm?
What're you gonna...
Yikes!
Before we go rescue Robin-chan,
let me tell you one thing.
What's with his agility?!
Me?
I'm a navigator!
I'm in a hurry.
Oh, I see!
More people are coming later, so... See ya!
That's reassuring!
Is something wrong?
Oh, before that...
That Buster Call is indeed the problem.
What?
Hey, Yokozuna!
Get over here!
What?! Wh-Why?!
Hey... stop!
What're you doing, Robin-chan?!
H-He's coming back!
He went inside! Hurry inside!
Ribbit!
He entered the main island!
He jumped!
Let Chief know!
Many years ago, an island ceased to exist.
This is main island front gate,
reporting to Chief!
Ow…
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit!
S-Straw Hat Luffy has entered the main island!
Five vice admirals and ten battleships...
You're glad that we're okay?!
Even if I explain, you guys
just won't get it, will you?
What?! You let him enter the main island?!
Geez...
To that woman who witnessed their
overwhelming military power,
I didn't get kidnapped!
What the hell is going on?!
You jumped the gun.
Buster Call is an inexpungible nightmare.
What are Oimo and Kashii doing?!
Ribbit?
Did those two get taken out, too?!
I-I got slashed!
If the terror planted in
her heart during her childhood
No, sir! Since it's currently
in the middle of the night...
Grandma's talking with Yokozuna?
is directed towards her friends, she can
no longer have the spirit to resist us.
...they're probably sleeping.
Oh? I didn't get slashed!
This is no time for sleeping!
Get them out of bed!
What're you guys doing?
Furthermore, if you lack love in
something as small as peeling skins,
All the guards sleeping on the main island, too!
That frog from earlier
and granny are talking.
Don't tell me...
...you're doing this knowing all that...
no matter what dish you make, it'll taste bad.
Y-Yes, sir!
Franky-kun!
What?! Then granny is a frog?!
Detach car #3!
It's just an intruder.
Of course.
Kitchen knives aren't swords,
It's true that she's
more frog than human.
What're we gonna do?!
You don't have to make
such a ruckus, right, Chief?
so I won't cut people with them.
You guys're gonna get
beaten up later.
We're gonna run!
However, you should notice
that you lost your armor.
Yeah, you are.
You've got us.
Hello!
Kitchen Knife Throw!
Run?!
Straw Hat! Rocketman!
Don't be ridiculous! This is the judicial island,
Hey, what do you mean?!
You son of a...
Do you see them?!
You, too, hurry up!
Oeil!
No, I don't!
which acts as a sacred symbol of the
entrance to the World Government.
One moment will decide the game!
That damn huge frog!
Don't let Franky get away.
M-My eyes are caving in!
Any idiot should know what
it means to invade this place!
Where did he send Straw Hat
and the others flying?!
Right.
Let them.
Guys!
Now, stop fighting and give up.
This is no time for grumbling!
Sogeking…!
So, CP9 is taking advantage of the root
cause of Robin-chan's vulnerability.
We set out to sea in order
to rescue Big Bro Franky!
And yet, he entered even the main
island just to get a crew member back.
Smoke… Star!
You fool! Why would I?!
That's right!
We just have to
believe that Rocketman will be back
It's not that I'm trying to make excuses
for not being able to get her back.
I don't get why the heck you
want to rescue a woman like that!
It's shameful! How dare they mock us?!
and keep moving forward
to Enies Lobby!
But even if we march into our enemy's territory,
Damn those Straw Hats and their subordinates!
What a petty thing to do!
You guys don't actually know
Nico Robin's true nature, do you?!
Hurry!
Sodom! Gomorrah!
it doesn't necessarily mean
that she'll let us help her.
That woman is...
Nez!
Hm?!
We got Nico Robin!
Joue!
Hey! Guys! Look ahead!
Bouche!
Yes, we are. I'll never see you guys again.
Dents!
I've found more detached cars!
Menton!
Hey!
Whether they're friend
or foe is unknown!
Let me go!
If you keep talking,
I'll reshape your body.
Everyone, prepare for battle!
That doesn't matter!
Gatekeeper! Explain what's
going on at the main gate!
All right!
Yeah!
I'm not gonna stand for this!
H-H-Hold on a sec!
Run!
Ahoy!
Hey, gatekeeper!
I-I feel like my face shrank!
Is anyone in there?!
That darn Robin!
Stop it!
How many enemies are we looking at?!
We're the Franky Family!
Why Robin?!
Turn back!
Show your face!
Why not?! Why the heck doesn't
she want us to come rescue her?!
What's their current location?!
I-If you don't know
about her, I'll tell you.
Hey, someone came out!
Come in, main gate!
Everyone knows it!
She's suffering thinking about what
might happen to us after she's rescued!
Hey, what's the matter?!
She's a depraved devil!
That's... spring eyebrows!
Come in, gatekeeper!
Who cares about that?!
Hey, he said we're turning back.
Parage... Shot!
If we don't do anything, she'll be killed, right?!
This is Enies Lobby
Department of Management.
Oh, yeah?
There's no way she wants to die,
so we'll rescue her!
Rope Action! Figure-of-Eight Knot!
Is everything in order?
That's a relief.
Of course that's true, but...
Well then, we should get
ready to turn back, huh?
Yes, we're bringing the two
criminals without any delay.
Don't bother. Either way,
what we have to do is the same.
Bazooka Bat!
Yeah.
Since we can now see the
island ahead, we'll arrive shortly.
What?!
We'll just rescue her.
We'll bring down the whole place!
I don't wanna waste bullets on this!
Whaaat?!
Understood.
Well then,
we'll be awaiting your return.
Why?! When we came this far?!
Go inside through the side
doors and open the gate!
There's a technique that I wanna try, too!
What about Robin!
What about Usopp?!
D-D-Dammit!
After five years of absence,
naturally, it makes me feel nostalgic.
My face caved in!
Hey! What're we gonna do
about them?!
Mirror! I need a mirror!
Dinner time?
Don't let them open it!
The nightless island, Enies Lobby...
What's that guy thinking?!
Guys, take a look at this.
Get out of our way!
Straw Hat!
I've been to that island once
for railway maintenance.
Mozu! Go to the left!
Why are we turning back?!
Got it!
Straw Hat!
That's right!
I drew this based on my vague recollection of it.
I won't let you!
H-He's alive?!
Tell us why!
I-Is it really... true?!
Whoa! Bed-head is coming out of my nose!
You've got it wrong!
This is a rough sketch of what the
geography of Enies Lobby looks like.
Y-Y-You bastard!
You should pay attention!
What?
Yeah, so I was told.
I was telling
H-How dare you dent my proud eyes and nose?!
that frog that jumped
on the railway to turn back!
Hurry up!
Thanks!
The Gates of Justice are
in the back of the island,
I see...
Ribbit! Ribbit! Ribbit!
and they seem to be accessible
only via the Tower of Law.
It's Yokozuna!
I'm glad...
Yokozuna?
What the hell is this? What's this dark area?
Serves you right!
That darn Stupid-berg!
What the heck is that huge frog?!
You are evil!
It indicates a waterfall.
I was totally
convinced that he was killed!
Keel Breaker!
A waterfall?
Watch out!
I see...
Oh, hey, they went back to how they were.
Well, you'll know what I
mean once you go in there.
I'm glad.
Step aside, frog!
CP9 might be thinking
that they killed him.
Ah! Y-You're right!
If we can't recover Nico Robin
and Franky on this straight path
Ribbit!
"Iron Fence" "Main Gate"
We're gonna collide!
I felt like
they went back a little just now.
It's better if you
keep it to yourself.
from the main gate to the Gates of Justice,
"Courthouse" "Main Island Front Gate"
Aren't they unlocked yet, Mozu, Kiwi?!
"Gates of Justice" "Tower of Law"
Th-That was just an illusion.
we will have lost.
Why?! No matter where Robin is taken to,
Isn't what you're doing
called "kindness"?
Ship demolition is the Franky Family's job.
Picking locks like this is...
You're guilty of three sins.
All right!
we can just keep going after
them until we get her back!
What?
We got Robin back!
First,
I explained this before we
left Water Seven, didn't I?!
you claimed to be a cook in front of me.
This side is unlocked!
The only destinations beyond those gates
This side, too!
Second,
At any rate,
that sure surprised me.
Okay, then! Open the gate,
Herculean Destroyers!
are Navy Headquarters and the deep-sea prison.
you treated food with no respect.
To think that we suddenly switched
to a "Running Away" strategy.
At any rate,
So we have to settle this matter
before that at any cost.
Third...
the Government has now successfully
obtained the two keys...
A smoke screen is so stupid
...you insulted our friend.
that people wouldn't normally
think of using it.
She's right.
Me, who owns the weapon's blueprints,
That being said, even if we all rush in,
It's best
if we encounter CP9, you guys are
the only ones who can defeat them.
and you, who can revive
the existing weapon.
if we can achieve our goal
without fighting scary guys like them.
But…
Hiss!
After the train ride together, I now
know well how strong you guys are.
You're the very definition
of "all bark but no bite."
When that power actually
appears in this world,
Don't let them open it! Defend it at all costs!
...I don't know if things
are gonna be that simple.
So, you guys stay and wait
on the sea for five minutes
Move! You're in our way!
Yeah.
I can't tell what part became stronger
after becoming four-legged,
Don't let your guard down
until the cars are really far apart.
the Government will
naturally end this pirate era.
and charge in to the main island in
Rocketman through the main gate.
centaur!
We'll go in first and break open the
main gate and the main island front gate
After that,
this military power will become
too much to handle, and will shake
the world to its core and destroy it.
What the hell…?!
so that the train can pass through.
The ancient weapon
is that much of a threat.
After that, we'd like you to keep on
moving no matter how many of us fall.
I-I-I'm gonna fall!
Thorny whips?!
Our master didn't lay down his
life protecting the blueprints
Rush in!
I caught it…
Blueno.
for such a stupid future!
We're only a little over 60 people,
Okay.
You look pathetic.
but our enemy's forces are
probably well above 2,000 to 3,000.
Is he gonna use the whips
to cross over?
We broke through the first gate, the main gate!
Dammit!
So,
We'd like you guys to go after only CP9,
avoiding unnecessary battles.
even if I could escape,
it's pointless if it's just me alone.
Shall I give you a hand?
Whoa! What the hell is this hole?!
You, too, somehow go back
to Straw Hat!
Ahhh! Waaah!
They pulled us back!
We don't have time! Ignore that! Move forward!
Okay, got it.
That's not possible.
You bastard!
Just keep moving and run towards
the main island front gate!
What power!
Okay, guys! We're now
at the front of the island!
I hurt them just by being with them.
Take a good look at the sky behind Enies Lobby.
It's a waterfall!
A smoke screen?
What a worthless thing to do…
Not quite...!
Ever since she can remember,
I guess it couldn't
have worked after all.
her existence itself was a sin.
Those are the Gates of Justice.
We did it!
Whoooa! That's huge!
Hey, guys! This way!
Give me a hand right away!
Don't kill any Straw Hats.
It's not you who hurts them, is it?
That was the condition.
They never open all the way.
Sogeking!
The people from the Government
say your existence is a sin,
Ah, yes.
Kashii-san! Oimo-san! Get up right away!
When criminals go through them,
they open just a little.
Protect Robin-chan
at all costs, okay?!
You're gonna give me a hand?!
Hm…? Yeah!
I'm doing just fine, you fool!
but no matter what
weapons you're carrying,
Sorry, but I'm going to…
Th-The main gate has been forced
open by suspicious people!
your being there isn't a sin.
And, behind those doors is a nest of
large Sea Kings, just like the Calm Belt,
…make you let go!
I've finally caught you.
Now tell me if you still think my
being four-legged was pointless!
Hm?
the sea areas that lie on
both sides of the Grand Line.
No matter what kind of ship it is,
Hey, he said the main gate
was forced open, Oimo.
Why is his body so hard?
the act of building it...
Shut up, you jerk!
So no ordinary ships can go in there.
I told you that they use
strange martial arts, didn't I?
...is neither an act of good nor evil!
Give me my characteristics back!
Yeah, that's not good, Kashii.
I don't know how, but the Navy has a
means of passing through there safely.
So...
You stupid jerk!
Her existence itself was a sin.
In other words, just like the pirate girl said,
No...!
Concasser!
I hate having to get up.
My friend is waiting to be rescued on
the other side of the door behind you.
if you want to get back
the criminals taken away,
Your existence isn't a sin!
But it's work. Let's go.
you've got until the moment before
they go through those gates to do it!
If you get it, get out of my way.
Oof!
Now, there's no time to lose!
He's got quite a heavy kick.
When I say I won't let you
go through, I really mean it!
Well then, as we planned,
we're gonna go in first!
What?!
Iron Body almost got broken down.
Ramen Kenpo! Secret technique!
Seriously, what
happened to your body?
Noodle Cutter Poisonous Kitchen Knife!
Leave the backup to us!
It's full of scars!
Hey, you two! Aren't you
supposed to be with us?!
If you touch it, you'll die!
Blueno, don't take him lightly.
Since...
Now, now, now, now!
...that day eight years ago...
He doesn't have a bounty on him,
Aren't you guys being
deceived by that woman, too?!
but he's one of their main forces.
Since that incident where
Tom-san was taken away...
"Kashii
'Main Island Front Gate'
Gatekeeper, Enies Lobby"
She's the lowest of the low,
who lived one betrayal after another,
Hm? Where's Luffy?
You just noticed that,
you damn jerks?
I didn't get enough sleep.
What? He was right here up until now.
...you've been challenging
the sea train every single day.
and survived until today in the underground!
Whoa, R-Robin!
Hey, hold on a sec!
I'm gonna get rid of them
quickly and go back to bed.
I'll take your life!
Ow… Wh-What're you doing?
Take this!
Me, too.
G-G-Giants!
Ocho Fleurs!
Hmph!
Clutch!
I don't know what you guys
came all the way here for,
Three-Spot...
Is that Straw Hat?
Long-nose!
Decoupage!
What?!
but I suggest you go home before we crush you.
Oof!
You... wanted to
become strong, right?
What?!
Hey! Why, Robin-chan?!
Right, Oimo?
Yeah, Kashii. I think so, too.
Why the hell is he doing things on his own?!
So that you won't lose
those you love again...
How many times
do I have to tell you?!
We're gonna squash you to your bones.
That man doesn't have a
clue about the plan at all!
Leave me alone!
So that you can protect
those you love...
Giant gatekeepers?! This isn't fair!
That was a waste.
Ribbit...
He said he got it, didn't he?
They're huge! Our Herculean
Destroyers look small.
Can't be…
He's not the type who can wait five minutes.
Yokozuna...
Hey, pay attention.
Then now's the time for
you to show the result of that training!
We should've known.
Now, go back!
What an impatient guy he is.
I'm not gonna let you go through this gate!
Ribbit?
Me neither!
Go! Pirate guy!
Franky, the one you love so much,
They're coming!
Eyebrows!
No matter who we're up against,
don't flinch, Franky Family!
has been taken away
just like Tom-san was.
Ribbit, ribbit!
Don't fall behind! Sodom! Gomorrah!
This is for Bro!
Geez… Why are all of you
being so stubborn
This train is currently headed
towards where he is, too.
Yeah!
Climb up the iron fence and
break open the main gate!
even towards your friends?!
Do you wanna come along?
Hey, you get it, right?
This is…
Ribbit...
Yeah!
Yeah.
a perfect chance to run, right?!
Ribbit!
All right!
Straw Hat!
We've got one more comrade!
If we don't go, who will?!
Okay, got it!
Gum-Gum... Rocket!
Just as we'd expect
from Monster Granny!
The Herculean powers we
gained working in ship demolitions
Or, are you actually Frog Granny?
Hm? What was that?
are a match for those Giants!
Which one is it?
Destroyers!
I just saw something flying!
Ah!
Who cares?
Whoa! What the heck is this place?!
Kokoro-san!
I found a good current!
It's in the eight o'clock direction!
What a huge hole! It looks
like the island is floating.
Hiss!
All right!
I got my hands and legs blocked!
We've wasted quite a bit of time.
I see a town there, too. I wonder
if Robin is around there...
I let my guard down!
We'll recover it in an instant!
You let your guard down?
Let's go! Frog!
Go ahead and make excuses.
Ribbit!
There's someone up there!
It's an intruder! Shoot him down!
O-Our Herculean Destroyers are...!
CP9 has arrived.
Oops, they found me.
If you like,
Hurry up!
In an instant...!
why don't you add your last words
to them while you're at it, buddy?
Good work on your
long-term mission, sir!
Franky!
Bring the criminals out!
They're in car #1!
We're born warriors!
He went inside the gate!
Are you thinking that you can
still keep fighting, by any chance?
The blood in our veins is different
You bastard!
from that of small humans who
happen to be a bit bigger than others.
Stop it!
Treat me with care!
What?!
This is the main gate! This is the main gate!
Well, it's just natural,
since you dodged all my attacks...
Who do you think I am?!
This is a report to Chief
and the main island front gate!
I'm not gonna let even a single person pass!
Whoa! Don't come this way!
This is the main gate! Please come in!
That was uncalled for.
Me, neither!
Ahh! Be careful! He'll bite you!
Since you don't know how
destructive my blow really is...
Didn't expect that, did you?
What is it? What's going on?
What a noisy man...
An intruder went over the main gate
Why are you taking sides
with them in the first place?
D... D-D-Don't get cold feet! Don't give up!
and is currently dashing towards
the main island front gate!
Coo coo.
Ultimate Hammer!
Oh... It's just an intruder.
Calm down and take care of him.
I just can't bear to watch
those guys act like that.
That's right! Big Bro Franky is
on the other side of that gate!
Not when there's a team that couldn't
go back even if they wanted to!
Just as you'd expect from CP9.
Yes, but...
How intimidating.
This is the main island front gate.
We confirmed the intruder.
I wonder who you're talking about.
He's Cutty Flam, right?
Show them a fight worthy
of Bro's name, Franky Family!
Yow!
We'll take care of him right away.
Please do not worry.
You guys, don't worry about me!
Then that woman is...
I've got a plan!
...Nico Robin?!
Once you've joined up with Straw Hat,
get back to town somehow!
Hey, hey. Stop.
What a beauty!
Open the main gate!
"Main Gate"
Do you know what this place is?
Franky!
Wait!
Deal with him carefully. If my eyes
didn't deceive me, that man is...
I won't run away!
Wait, Robin-chan.
Two more minutes...
...Straw Hat Luffy!
Why are you acting
like that at this point?
Ribbit!
We came to rescue you
knowing all the circumstances!
What?! What did you just say?!
"Main Island Front Gate"
"Main Gate"
I think that's Straw Hat...
If we just do something about the
Government's attack, Buster Call,
"Courthouse"
"Main Island Front Gate"
A pirate with a 100 million-Berry
bounty on his head!
there shouldn't be a reason that
you have to obey them, right?!
Whoa...!
What the hell is this place?!
Robin...
Hey, Straw Hat Luffy.
That Buster Call is…
How many friends did you bring?
Hey, where on earth did you come from?
Is this... a waterfall?!
There are 10,000 soldiers in Enies Lobby!
Yow!
Did you finish taking
care of the ramen guy?
Yeah, I'm by myself.
…indeed the problem.
Yeah, I did, just now.
Where is Robin?!
What the hell's with this island?!
Get out of my way!
Wha…
They're the ones
who kidnapped Robin-chan,
aren't they?
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We had a dream that day
We'll become No. 1
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
Our belief in ourselves
an era created by risking everything
We always try our best, let's go!
makes us able to cross
We had a dream that day
If we want to achieve glory,
now is the time--don't be afraid
the wildly surging ocean
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Our belief in ourselves
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
You're braver and more caring
makes us able to cross
We can take off with unknown powers
We don't fear, and we don't waver
the wildly surging ocean
than anyone else
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
If you ever depart this ship
You're braver and more caring
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
than anyone else
and live in a different world
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
If you ever depart this ship
In the end,
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
we can all surely smile
Charge ahead
and live in a different world
Let's start running towards tomorrow
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
In the end,
we can all surely smile
We're not gonna let even
an ant pass through this gate!
We can finally see Enies Lobby!
Stop it! Let Robin-chan go!
What?! You let Straw Hat
enter the main island?!
Robin-chan!
Why aren't you saying anything?!
So that's the entrance of
the World Government, huh?!
What the hell is going on?!
If you don't give up and go back,
we're gonna stomp on you!
Robin, you're still hiding
something, aren't you?
Outta my way! Outta my way! Clear the way!
Guys!
Get ready for the final battle!
Is he trying to pick a fight
with the World Government
That's okay.
Dammit! We can't afford to be delayed here!
Sanji-kun and Uso--
But
I mean, that Sogeking guy
have joined us, so now...
a pirate cannot leave their group
without their captain's permission.
just to get one crew
member back?! How stupid.
Robin-chan! I wanted to see you!
Don't flinch! Open the path for Rocketman!
We'll bring down the whole
place and rescue Robin!
So, Robin…
Robin, just wait!
Let's go back together this time!
believe in Luffy!
On the next episode of One Piece!
Sanji-kun, it seems that she's
objecting to your opinion.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Landing Operations Start!
Charge in, Straw Hats!"
"Luffy Cuts Through!
Big Showdown on the Judicial Island!!"
"Battle Against Giants! Open the Second Gate!"
"The Judicial Island!
Full View of Enies Lobby!"
Why, Robin-chan?!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
I've got a plan.
Look.
One moment will decide the game!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Scramble over Robin!
A Cunning Plan by Sogeking!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!