How could this be happening?
I thought I clearly told you all goodbye.
I'll never return to the Straw Hats!
You really think they'd be happy to be alive
knowing that it was because their
friend had to sacrifice herself?!
Now that they know why you left them,
they'll follow you to the depths
of hell and take out your enemies!
It's you guys who don't get it!
I don't have the slightest desire to be rescued!
Don't just do as you please!
What are you making a racket for, Nico Robin?
Ramen Kenpo!
Noodle Stake Knocker!
Epluchage!
Con...vert!
"Convert"
"Pervert"
Don't tell me he's gonna...
Franky...
...Centaur!
Wrong way!
Your body should be in front!
Two-Sword Style Sword Draw...
...Rashomon!
We're not done yet.
What the hell is that?!
It's a Sea King!
Further ahead on this railway...
...lies the one who cut that thing up...!
All, go back to the front cars!
This is a trap!
A trap?!
What the...?!
To think that I fell for the enemy's scheme...
What a blunder!
The gravest blunder of my life!
Well then, gentlemen! Have a nice trip!
I have to catch up... with the sea train!
If the criminals
we're supposed to escort
are set free upon the world again...
How much blood and how many
tears will civilians have to shed?!
I'll show them that there's justice
even in this unfair world!
Even if my arms and legs are
torn off by these raging waves...
...I will be sure to protect the
innocent citizens' future!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together,
let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail--
let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag--
together, we're one
One Piece
"Clash! Demon-Slasher Zoro
vs. Ship-Slasher T-Bone"
What is that?
A sea train?
Is that a new sea train?
There's something there!
Hm? What's that?!
A person?
There's someone there!
That's Ship-Slasher!
What?!
S-Seriously?!
Ship-Slasher?
He's Ship-Slasher T-Bone,
a Captain at Navy Headquarters!
He cuts pirates ships up like steaks!
Oh, yeah?
That's amazing!
"Amazing"?!
You're talking
like it's someone else's problem!
We can't just sit around like this.
Hey, guys!
Get ready to fire!
Hurry up!
Yeah!
Wait!
What is it?!
We'd better hurry up
or he'll slash Rocketman!
What were you watching all this time?
Leave it to Zoro.
Don't interfere!
What?
I'll tell you only once!
Get out of our way!
They couldn't have simply
passed by my subordinates' cars
that were on the same railway.
What did these guys do to my subordinates?
They must be Nico Robin's crewmates...
...which means that that
swordsman is the pirate hunter!
This path leads to the origins of justice!
I'm a captain at Navy Headquarters!
I will not live on in disgrace!
I'll stop you guys by slashing you in two!
I can't allow that...
...as our destination
lies beyond where you stand!
This guy is strong!
Bring it on!
I hate crooked sword attacks!
Right-Angle Flying Bird...
Three-Sword Style...
Bull Demon!
...Bone...
Phoenix!
He discerned it?!
Bold Hooves!
R-Roronoa!
He defeated Ship-Slasher!
To think that he followed
the sea train
from the detached cars
in this storm...
How admirable!
But we can't stop here.
I'm sure your justice is deep, too,
but we also shoulder all sorts of things.
Hurry! Hurry!
Captain T-Bone, who jumped
out to sea, is in danger!
He could've been hit by that sea train by now.
You bastard!
Be careful about what you say!
Our captain would slash a sea train
like that into two, you jerk!
But that swordsman was quite skilled!
Full speed ahead!
Our captain protected us
with his life
from a Sea King
that stood in the way!
Save our captain!
Yeah!
Roronoa Zoro...
How vexing...
I-Is that right?
That's right!
I'm sure it's Sanji-kun and
the others who detached that sea train.
Then, are we gonna catch up with them soon?
Probably.
All right!
We're closing in on our enemy!
Yeah!
Go, Rocketman!
We're gonna
beat up the pigeon guy!
We somehow...
pulled it off?
No...
there's something different after all.
That's right! This smell...!
This place is filled with the
smell of those filthy pirates!
Something is definitely wrong!
Yikes!
Is something wrong?
What?! Wh-Why?!
H-He's coming back!
I-I got slashed!
Oh? I didn't get slashed!
Furthermore, if you lack love in
something as small as peeling skins,
no matter what dish you make, it'll taste bad.
Kitchen knives aren't swords,
so I won't cut people with them.
However, you should notice
that you lost your armor.
Kitchen Knife Throw!
You son of a...
Oeil!
M-My eyes are caving in!
Let them.
Now, stop fighting and give up.
You fool! Why would I?!
I don't get why the heck you
want to rescue a woman like that!
You guys don't actually know
Nico Robin's true nature, do you?!
That woman is...
Nez!
Joue!
Bouche!
Dents!
Menton!
If you keep talking,
I'll reshape your body.
H-H-Hold on a sec!
I-I feel like my face shrank!
Stop it!
I-If you don't know
about her, I'll tell you.
Everyone knows it!
She's a depraved devil!
Parage... Shot!
D-D-Dammit!
My face caved in!
Mirror! I need a mirror!
Y-Y-You bastard!
H-How dare you dent my proud eyes and nose?!
Serves you right!
You are evil!
Oh, hey, they went back to how they were.
Ah! Y-You're right!
I felt like
they went back a little just now.
Th-That was just an illusion.
You're guilty of three sins.
What?
First,
you claimed to be a cook in front of me.
Second,
you treated food with no respect.
Third...
...you insulted our friend.
Hiss!
You're the very definition
of "all bark but no bite."
I can't tell what part became stronger
after becoming four-legged,
centaur!
I-I-I'm gonna fall!
You look pathetic.
Dammit!
Shall I give you a hand?
Ahhh! Waaah!
You bastard!
Not quite...!
You're gonna give me a hand?!
I'm doing just fine, you fool!
I've finally caught you.
Now tell me if you still think my
being four-legged was pointless!
Shut up, you jerk!
Give me my characteristics back!
You stupid jerk!
My friend is waiting to be rescued on
the other side of the door behind you.
If you get it, get out of my way.
When I say I won't let you
go through, I really mean it!
Ramen Kenpo! Secret technique!
Noodle Cutter Poisonous Kitchen Knife!
If you touch it, you'll die!
Now, now, now, now!
Aren't you guys being
deceived by that woman, too?!
She's the lowest of the low,
who lived one betrayal after another,
and survived until today in the underground!
I'll take your life!
Take this!
Three-Spot...
Decoupage!
Hiss!
I got my hands and legs blocked!
I let my guard down!
You let your guard down?
Go ahead and make excuses.
If you like,
why don't you add your last words
to them while you're at it, buddy?
Are you thinking that you can
still keep fighting, by any chance?
What?!
Well, it's just natural,
since you dodged all my attacks...
Since you don't know how
destructive my blow really is...
Ultimate Hammer!
Hey, where on earth did you come from?
Yow!
Did you finish taking
care of the ramen guy?
Yeah, I did, just now.
They're the ones
who kidnapped Robin-chan,
aren't they?
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross
the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring
than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end,
we can all surely smile
Robin-chan! I wanted to see you!
Let's go back together this time!
Sanji-kun, it seems that she's
objecting to your opinion.
Why, Robin-chan?!
I've got a plan.
Look.
One moment will decide the game!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Scramble over Robin!
A Cunning Plan by Sogeking!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!