Geez... Why are all of you
being so stubborn
even towards your friends?!
This is...
a perfect chance to run, right?!
Wait!
I won't run away!
Wait, Robin-chan.
Why are you acting like that
at this point?
We came to rescue you
knowing all the circumstances!
If we just do something about the
Government's attack, Buster Call,
there shouldn't be a reason that
you have to obey them, right?!
That Buster Call is...
...indeed the problem.
Tempest Kick!
Sanji!
What happened?
He appeared from nowhere!
This is bad...
I have to do something.
Dang it!
Hold it!
What're you doing?!
Just stay back!
Hey, you! I'll take you...
Huh?! He's gone!
Wh-When did he...?!
Wh-Where'd he go?!
Where is he?!
It's all right! Now
let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through
our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together,
let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail--
let's raise anchor
Cut through
the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey
fraught with injury
but what you cherish most
will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right!
Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up
the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map
leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag--
together, we're one
One Piece
"The Judicial Island!
Full View of Enies Lobby!"
Blueno disappeared?!
It's not that he's disappeared.
He only made a door
out of the wall of air
by using "Air Door,"
the true value
of the Door Door Fruit, that's all.
You can't escape from us...
It's simply not possible.
Let Robin...
go...
Finger Pistol.
Usopp!
Iron Body.
Did my attack earlier work?
That's a weak kick.
How stubborn.
Stop it!
I won't run away.
That should be enough.
They're the ones who keep
attacking me.
I can't help it.
Then let's hurry up and leave.
Wait!
It's okay...
Robin.
You'll be fine.
You're still hiding something,
aren't you?
That's okay.
But a pirate...
cannot leave their group...
...without their captain's...
permission.
So...
...believe...
...in Luffy.
Wait, Robin-chan!
It's no use.
Nico Robin will
not break the agreement.
How can you say that?
Many years ago,
an island ceased to exist.
This island was burned to the ground
without a trace by a Buster Call
that was issued by the Navy.
The only survivor of that
was the child Nico Robin.
What?!
Five vice admirals and
ten battleships...
To that woman who witnessed
their overwhelming military power,
Buster Call is an
inexpungible nightmare.
If the terror planted in
her heart during her childhood
is directed towards her friends,
she can no longer
have the spirit to resist us.
Don't tell me...
...you're doing this
knowing all that...
Of course.
You bastards...
Just how depraved are you bastards?!
Everything is for the sake of justice.
I do deeply sympathize
with that woman.
Don't give me that crap!
You damn bastards!
Hm? Y... You...!
Hurry up and sit down, Nico Robin.
We'll soon arrive in Enies Lobby.
H... Hey!
Wait a sec!
I said wait!
Hey!
Is it okay to let those two
be in the same car?
It won't be too long
before we get there.
What could happen?
We're not gonna let
them escape anymore.
They are both criminals
who'll be executed shortly.
Let them grieve over their
fate as much as they can.
F... F...
Ribbit!
F...
Frog!
Ribbit!
Don't "ribbit" me, you jerk!
The train got derailed
because of your slap!
Ahhh! Step aside! Step aside!
We're gonna collide!
Ribbit!
We were finally about to catch
up with Sanji and the others!
What're you gonna do about it?!
Ribbit!
You little...!
I'm gonna eat you, jerk!
Ribbit!
Ow, ow, ow...
What on earth
is going on with this sea train?
Hey, are you guys okay?
Somehow...
M... My lower back...
What the hell?!
Our King Bulls disappeared!
What?!
They disappeared?!
Well, it's probably us
who disappeared.
We probably got derailed.
Whoa! That's worse!
What're we gonna do?!
"What're we gonna do?!"
We can't do anything about it.
Zoro!
Wha...
You're kidding me...!
M-Miracle...
Here we go.
Geez, that darn Yokozuna!
He's sure got bad timing.
Are you guys okay?
Yeah, somehow.
Darn Yokozuna!
Well, looks like you guys're okay.
Hey!
Hm?
Are we okay?!
We'd better still
be able to get to Enies Lobby!
Shut up!
Just wait a sec!
That being said...
we got into a
weird current.
What's going on?
Kokoro-san.
Hm?
Do you know which
direction the island is?
Yeah,
the sea train comes already
equipped with Eternal Poses
for the islands with stations.
Then it'll be fine!
I'll check the sea,
so please control the train!
Hm?
What're you gonna...
Me?
I'm a navigator!
Oh, I see!
That's reassuring!
Oh, before that...
Hey, Yokozuna!
Get over here!
Ribbit!
He jumped!
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit!
You're glad that we're okay?!
Geez...
I didn't get kidnapped!
You jumped the gun.
Ribbit?
Grandma's talking with Yokozuna?
What're you guys doing?
That frog from earlier
and granny are talking.
What?! Then granny is a frog?!
It's true that she's
more frog than human.
You guys're gonna get
beaten up later.
Yeah, you are.
Hello!
Straw Hat! Rocketman!
Do you see them?!
No, I don't!
That damn huge frog!
Where did he send Straw Hat
and the others flying?!
Guys!
This is no time for grumbling!
We set out to sea in order
to rescue Big Bro Franky!
That's right!
We just have to
believe that Rocketman will be back
and keep moving forward
to Enies Lobby!
Hurry!
Sodom! Gomorrah!
Hm?!
Hey! Guys! Look ahead!
I've found more detached cars!
Whether they're friend
or foe is unknown!
Everyone, prepare for battle!
Yeah!
Ahoy!
Is anyone in there?!
We're the Franky Family!
Show your face!
Hey, someone came out!
That's... spring eyebrows!
This is Enies Lobby
Department of Management.
Is everything in order?
Yes, we're bringing the two
criminals without any delay.
Since we can now see the
island ahead, we'll arrive shortly.
Understood.
Well then,
we'll be awaiting your return.
After five years of absence,
naturally, it makes me feel nostalgic.
The nightless island, Enies Lobby...
H-He's alive?!
I-Is it really... true?!
Yeah, so I was told.
I see...
I'm glad...
That darn Stupid-berg!
I was totally
convinced that he was killed!
I see...
I'm glad.
CP9 might be thinking
that they killed him.
It's better if you
keep it to yourself.
Isn't what you're doing
called "kindness"?
At any rate,
the Government has now successfully
obtained the two keys...
Me, who owns the weapon's blueprints,
and you, who can revive
the existing weapon.
When that power actually
appears in this world,
the Government will
naturally end this pirate era.
After that,
this military power will become
too much to handle, and will shake
the world to its core and destroy it.
The ancient weapon
is that much of a threat.
Our master didn't lay down his
life protecting the blueprints
for such a stupid future!
So,
even if I could escape,
it's pointless if it's just me alone.
You, too, somehow go back
to Straw Hat!
That's not possible.
I hurt them just by being with them.
Ever since she can remember,
her existence itself was a sin.
It's not you who hurts them, is it?
The people from the Government
say your existence is a sin,
but no matter what
weapons you're carrying,
your being there isn't a sin.
No matter what kind of ship it is,
the act of building it...
...is neither an act of good nor evil!
So...
Her existence itself was a sin.
No...!
Your existence isn't a sin!
Seriously, what
happened to your body?
It's full of scars!
Since...
...that day eight years ago...
Since that incident where
Tom-san was taken away...
...you've been challenging
the sea train every single day.
You... wanted to
become strong, right?
So that you won't lose
those you love again...
So that you can protect
those you love...
Ribbit...
Yokozuna...
Then now's the time for
you to show the result of that training!
Ribbit?
Franky, the one you love so much,
has been taken away
just like Tom-san was.
This train is currently headed
towards where he is, too.
Do you wanna come along?
Ribbit...
Ribbit!
Straw Hat!
We've got one more comrade!
Okay, got it!
Just as we'd expect
from Monster Granny!
Or, are you actually Frog Granny?
Which one is it?
Who cares?
Kokoro-san!
I found a good current!
It's in the eight o'clock direction!
All right!
We've wasted quite a bit of time.
We'll recover it in an instant!
Let's go! Frog!
Ribbit!
CP9 has arrived.
Hurry up!
Good work on your
long-term mission, sir!
Bring the criminals out!
They're in car #1!
You bastard!
Stop it!
Treat me with care!
Who do you think I am?!
Whoa! Don't come this way!
Ahh! Be careful! He'll bite you!
What a noisy man...
Coo coo.
Just as you'd expect from CP9.
How intimidating.
He's Cutty Flam, right?
Then that woman is...
...Nico Robin?!
What a beauty!
Open the main gate!
Whoa...!
What the hell is this place?!
Is this... a waterfall?!
What the hell's with this island?!
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross
the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring
than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end,
we can all surely smile
We can finally see Enies Lobby!
So that's the entrance of
the World Government, huh?!
Guys!
Get ready for the final battle!
Sanji-kun and Uso--
I mean, that Sogeking guy
have joined us, so now...
We'll bring down the whole
place and rescue Robin!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Landing Operations Start!
Charge in, Straw Hats!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!