"Tower of Law"
In the Tower of Law,
Riding on Rocketman,
the Straw Hat Pirates have infiltrated
the Enies Lobby main island.
Robin realized that Luffy and
the others had come to rescue her.
We're not gonna let even
an ant pass through this gate!
So, you guys stay and wait
on the sea for five minutes
and charge in to the main island in
Rocketman through the main gate.
Gatekeeper giants Oimo and Kashii
showed up at the main island front gate
By the way, where's that idiot
who rushed out by himself?
We'll go in first and break open the
main gate and the main island front gate
Franky and Robin have been
taken to the Tower of Law.
Beats me... This island isn't small,
so if we are to find him...
and stood in the way of the
Franky Family. However...
so that the train can pass through.
We'd like you guys to go after only CP9,
avoiding unnecessary battles.
What was that?!
Timber Hitch Tug!
Okay, got it.
That's definitely where he is!
I feel on top of the world!
Ow...! Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
Wait! That's not what we agreed upon!
As for Luffy, who went ahead of the others,
I'm surprised to see you survived that
accident eight years ago, Cutty Flam.
he still hasn't been able
to reach the courthouse.
In return for my cooperation, you were
supposed to let them escape safely!
Oof!
What?!
Why the hell is he doing things on his own?!
Goals can't be achieved without sacrifice.
...the situation was reversed
by Paulie and Zambai,
That man doesn't have a
clue about the plan at all!
We're working in order to
ensure peace for all of humanity.
and the gate was about to be broken open.
How dare you, pirate?!
Meanwhile, Luffy, who had already
passed the main island front gate,
He jumped onto the tree!
You're crazy!
Tom-san put his life on the line
to protect the blueprints
was being slowed down by an
overwhelming number of soldiers.
They came here after leaving
Water Seven safely, right?
Those jerks! This is endless!
I can't move forward!
because idiots like you exist!
What's the matter?
They're hopeless scum. They don't
have a shred of morality in them.
Take the reins.
Yoi!
I'm in a hurry.
Hm? You guys...
Huh? What'd you say?
More people are coming later, so... See ya!
Around that time, Luffy was
fighting against 10,000 soldiers
When you see... those guys, tell them...
Five are down?! So it was
actually just five guards?!
Shut up, you trash!
on the main island of Enies Lobby.
To start with, we don't even have to
keep our promises with you criminals!
Geez... You can't even make a report properly?
"You guys're fired."
Five... hundred guards...
Sure will.
Take this! Take this! You bastard!
Jump on to it!
"Tower of Law"
You too!
Lucci and the others,
with Franky and Robin in tow,
We won't let you!
Don't get so cocky, you bitch!
Chief Spandam! Please come in!
Please advise us on countermeasures!
Half Knot Air Drive!
headed to the Tower of Law,
where Spandam was waiting for them.
We can't stop Straw Hat Luffy!
Welcome back! Lucci, Kaku, Blueno, and Kalifa!
You dirty coward...
Don't let them open it! Defend it at all costs!
That's sexual harassment.
Move! You're in our way!
Just calling your name is?!
The receiver is off.
Anyway, you've done a great
job over the past five years.
Rush in!
We'll take Cutty Flam to Impel Down
and Nico Robin to Navy Headquarters.
Ahhh! S-Some Watchdogs were taken out!
Oh, that's right... This isn't really a
reward for your efforts or anything,
As soon as the escort ship is ready,
Meanwhile, Zoro and the others,
who had been waiting on Rocketman
We'll take care of these guys.
We broke through the first gate, the main gate!
we'll go through the
Gates of Justice and sail off.
but I do have something I wanna give you.
Meanwhile, Robin and Franky
were facing a desperate situation.
You guys go back to your rooms
and take it easy for the time being.
for the gates to be opened, charged in
after thorough preparation and...
Well, I'll do that later.
So, in any case, let me meet...
the "hope" of the entire world!
Look! Both triggers for the
ancient weapon's revival are here!
What?! This is terrible!
We're gonna crash into the gate!
Hey, Sogeking.
What're we gonna do?! What're we gonna do?!
--Dodge it, Kokoro-san!
--What're we gonna do?!
Hey!
What dependable guys my subordinates are.
And the Straw Hats on Rocketman
were getting ready to charge in.
Hey, that hurt!
About how to use this takt for chilled air...
Don't worry. There's a way.
Do you get it? The winds the entire
world over are blowing in my favor.
As long as I have them, I feel like I can't lose!
Hm? Let me see...
Now, guys! It's time!
Do not ask me!
Let's go, shall we?
A power strong enough to give me control
over any large country I might desire
I wonder... if everyone is okay.
Samurai-man! Take care of the iron fence!
is in my hands now!
...they passed over the main gate
and headed straight to
the main island front gate.
Meanwhile, urging the King Bull
on in pursuit of Luffy,
"Courthouse" "Main Island Front Gate"
Just sit and wait patiently, Chopper.
Leave it to me.
Why did Aokiji give you the
authority to exercise Buster Call?
the Straw Hats were moving
forward without a hitch, however...
It's bad enough our captain has no patience.
Huh?
Don't get on without permission!
Things are going smoothly! Good thing
we've got you guys on our side!
We're counting on you to
get us to Luffy, King Bulls!
Go in already!
Wh-Who are those two?!
You too!
You're in no position to ask me
questions, you insolent woman!
He's asking, "By the way, was it
okay that the guy with the mask
"Kashii
'Main Island Front Gate'
Gatekeeper, Enies Lobby"
"Oimo
'Main Island Front Gate'
Gatekeeper, Enies Lobby"
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
I didn't get enough sleep.
didn't get on with you guys?"
Coo coo?
--What?!
--Hm?
I'm gonna get rid of them
quickly and go back to bed.
--What?
--Hm...?
Me, too.
What?! I-I can't find Sogeking anywhere!
G-G-Giants!
Chapapa... Chapa!
Big bazooka unit, step forward!
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
"Courthouse" "Main Island Front Gate"
Hey, Straw Hat Luffy.
L-Lieutenant Commander!
I have to hurry up or Robin will...
There's trouble!
How many friends did you bring?
What's the matter?!
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
Straw Hat Luffy...!
I feel on top of the world!
I guess I'll try that thing.
There are 10,000 soldiers in Enies Lobby!
I'm surprised to see you survived that
accident eight years ago, Cutty Flam.
We lost Straw Hat Luffy!
Just give up, Straw Hat!
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
Yeah, I'm by myself.
And also... the woman whom
the world considers dangerous
Find him! Find Straw Hat at any cost!
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
Fire!
Get out of my way!
and has been trying to capture, Nico Robin...
As for Luffy, he finally reached
the rooftop of the courthouse.
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
--Did we do it?
--He fell into the waterfall!
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
That must be the last building.
we will be able to make it through
Hey, look! He's still clinging onto the edge!
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
Always!
All right.
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
What the heck?
Air Door.
Straw Hat! If you surrender
peacefully, we can pull you up.
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
Why would I?!
How stubborn! Fall into the waterfall already!
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
You bastard!
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
Hey, guys! Give me a foot here!
Ah! You're that bull guy
who was with the pigeon guy!
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
Yeah!
I did think that there was no way
there'd be only five casualties.
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
Hey, he went over to your side!
We can't stop here
This way! This way!
Boy, that was a big surprise!
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
Around the world
Since the start of the World
Government, it's unprecedented...
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
Start me up!
we will be able to make it through
...for a man to step this far
into the Government's entrance.
I got lucky!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
we will be able to make it through
Always!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Always!
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
It's Straw Hat! Fire!
How long are you planning to keep fighting?
Boy, what a crazy place I wandered off into.
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
But since I was able to take care of a
lot of them at once, I guess it's okay.
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
If I remember right, I should move forward
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
towards that serious looking building, right?
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
--All right!
--He went that way! After him!
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
Brand New World
We can't stop here
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
Start me up!
H-Heavy...
Until I die.
Around the world
We can't stop here
C-Climb up in order,
starting with those at the bottom!
Start me up!
Around the world
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Slowly, okay?! Slowly!
Start me up!
Don't shake!
If I hadn't recognized
the value of your existence,
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
It's not me! It was a wind gust!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
It's just wind! Stop it with your willpower!
it would've been practically worthless!
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
So you should appreciate me.
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
You, the repugnant kin of Ohara,
the land of devils...
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Nico Robin...
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Brand New World
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
Start me up!
Brand New World
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
"Main Island Front Gate"
"Main Gate"
"Courthouse" "Tower of Law"
"Find a Way Out!
Rocketman Takes Flight!"
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
we will be able to make it through
"Battle against Giants!
Open the Second Gate!"
Always!
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
"Robin Betrayed! The Motive
of the World Government!"
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
I'm feeling great! However...
...unfortunately, the public doesn't know
we will be able to make it through
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
how truly valuable and great
what we've achieved today is.
Always!
Now, listen good.
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
From here on, you'll suffer pain so severe
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
It'll be several years...
We're not gonna let you through this gate!
that you will wish many
times for death to come,
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
...before it actually comes to be known.
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
so prepare yourself.
We can't stop here
We'll hurt you, use you,
and throw you away into the sea.
In my opinion, the justice those old geezers
in the current Government dole out
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
Around the world
If you don't give up and go back,
is too lenient!
Start me up!
That is how deeply sinful
your existence itself is!
we're gonna stomp on you!
Goals can't be achieved without sacrifice.
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
We can't stop here
We're working in order to
ensure peace for all of humanity.
Around the world
Oh, that's right. I got a call earlier.
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
It's fine if we have to sacrifice some
fools in our way to maintain peace...
Start me up!
They reported that some morons
have infiltrated our island
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
Don't flinch! Big Bro Franky is
on the other side of that gate!
...including that fishman who didn't
hand over what we told him to...
just to get back worthless trash like you.
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Don't tell me...!
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Well, they should all be caught by now.
He deserved to be killed...
as a rebel against justice.
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
Brand New World
It's Straw Hat Luffy and his crew.
Start me up!
Show them a fight worthy of
Bro's name, Franky Family!
He deserved it. He did!
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Why do those kids...
You're crazy!
Tom-san put his life on the line
to protect the blueprints
They seemed no better than trash in
front of the 10,000 Enies Lobby soldiers.
Brand New World
"Give Robin Back! Luffy vs. Blueno!"
because idiots like you exist!
Don't give in! Open the path for Rocketman!
Start me up!
Well, we're about to send a ship to the prison.
"Catch Up with Luffy!
The Straw Hats' All-Out Battle"
They are a good gift.
Wh-What're you guys doing?! Help me! Hey!
I'll take them to Impel Down
together with Cutty Flam.
Break open the doors!
Ahhh! Wh-Wh-What're we gonna do?!
Ow, ow, ow, ow! Ow!
Kumadori!
We're not gonna let even
an ant pass through this gate!
Yoyoi!
In any case, we don't have the option
of going back to get him at this point.
H-Hey! I know who that swordsman is!
Roger!
I'm sure he'll work things out on his own.
Yeah, he's one of Straw Hat's
underlings, Pirate Hunter Zoro!
--Destroyers!
--Everyone...!
But there are guards everywhere on this island.
Hurry up and help me, hey! Hey!
Dammit! How dare you bring down
some of our strongest forces?!
He isn't Luffy. If he's by
himself, his life will be...
They called you an underling.
Now... now... now...!
Then, you're even lower
than that, right, "Pirate A"?
After surmounting each island,
we got stronger without knowing.
Go!
Wait! That's not what we agreed upon!
Yoi!
Huh?!
Then, "B."
In return for my cooperation, you were
supposed to let them escape safely!
Huh?! If I had a bounty, it'd be
at least twice as much as yours!
He, too, always survived
life-or-death situations on each island.
Yo...!
Ow!
No one in our group would die so easily.
Then, "C."
What the...?!
Hey, listen to what I'm saying, you bastard!
--Zambai!
--Kiwi! Mozu!
Hey, stop it, you two.
Galley-La!
"Always"? "In our group"?!
What're you talking about, Zoro?!
Sogeking, they can't hear you.
Oh? Where did Chief Spandam go?
This is part of my plan, Chopper-kun.
Sogeking came here to help us rescue
Robin because Usopp asked him to!
--Oh, I didn't know.
--Hm?
Sorry that we're late!
There are more of them in the train!
It took longer than I thought to switch
Sodom and Gomorrah to land mode!
I... I'm here. I'm right here. H-H-Hey...
What are you flying off the handle for?
They found us!
There have to be more!
Blow it up before they come out!
Lucci! Tell us exactly what the
condition that we offered her was.
Zambai! The Destroyers are...
He is an invincible hero, right?
Hey, hold it! Nami-san is still in there!
I know.
Fire!
That the six Straw Hats, excluding Nico Robin,
would leave Water Seven safely.
We have no time to patch them up right now.
Gum-Gum... Gatling!
That's right!
In order to get to where Bro is,
Gum-Gum... Whip!
Yeah, that's right.
There's no mistake in that, right?
we have to open this gate at any cost!
Those bastards! I'm gonna
cut them into three pieces!
Sogeking is a super hero
for justice. He'll definitely...
Hold on, Pirate A.
"Main Island Front Gate"
Giant Scythe!
What?!
An attack like that isn't enough
to take someone like her out.
You're only "Pirate A" because you
don't get something as obvious as that.
Bell!
They came here after leaving
Water Seven safely, right?
You damn Moss Head!
I failed to get on the King Bull...
Mallet!
Let's go!
Yeah!
What am I gonna do? I'm way behind now.
Bazooka!
Boy, that scared me!
Let's make him lose his balance, Mozu!
What?
Battleship Cannon!
Roger, Kiwi!
Don't tell me... that you're going to
break the deal using such twisted logic!
Are you okay, Sogeking?
Gum-Gum... Stamp!
I-I-I'm okay, Chopper-kun.
They're hopeless scum. They don't
have a shred of morality in them.
Stop firing!
What's the matter?
This is the main island, reporting to Chief!
At any rate, those shipwrights are amazing!
--Look at that!
--Hello!
Hull... Dismantler Slash!
Chief Spandam! Please come in!
Huh? What'd you say?
Stop it! I'm a senior citizen!
It's no good! I can't get through!
In any case, I left the group. Shall I just run?
Shut up, you trash!
Rope Action...
I'm a child and here is a
small animal! We're weak!
Does he have the receiver off again?
To start with, we don't even have to
keep our promises with you criminals!
...Timber Hitch Tug!
Not again, at a critical time like this, seriously!
The Straw Hat Pirates threatened me
and made me operate the train!
Ow...! Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
Take this! Take this! You bastard!
Hey, where did Straw Hat go?
You too!
N-N-No! Running is the last thing I'll do!
He's right underneath you!
They did!
Don't get so cocky, you bitch!
I'm Usopp! I'm a man! I went so far
as to hide my identity to follow them!
What?! Right underneath us?!
Even the Navy openly uses
tricks to capture pirates!
Attack him at once!
We're facing a crisis where Robin is
sacrificing herself to protect all of us!
Kashii!
Who lets their hostages drink?
There he is! He's down there!
Dammit! I've been boxed in!
I have to do it at all costs!
That was close! We almost
killed the hostages, too!
All right... There's only
one way to get to everyone.
Of all people, to think that those
pirates took a senior, a child,
Tilestone!
Yeah!
and a small animal hostage... How despicable!
I'll carry out "Operation Disguise Myself
as One of the Government Personnel
Hm?
Gum-Gum... Volcano!
What's that?! That smoke looks like clouds.
and Pass by Them Unnoticed"!
You dirty coward...
Using cool balls and heat balls,
Yeah, that'd be good.
Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
the moisture in the air is turned into clouds.
To think that you're still talking back...
Trunnel Lock!
Huh?!
Nami-san! So you escaped the attack!
Work completed!
Whoa! What?! What?!
Are they trying to drown me?!
You've been betraying people all this time.
Don't think that you can
choose an ideal way to die now.
Enemy attack! Enemy attack!
Hey, the cloud is getting bigger and bigger.
How regrettable!
Grandma, Grandma. The cloud is getting bigger.
Ahhh! The giant woke up!
You bastards...!
That cloud looks a little dangerous.
We screwed up in our 50th year!
I'm sorry, bosses!
I'm gonna crush you!
You guys can all die together.
Th-The wall is... The wall is falling!
Chimney, Gonbe. Come this way.
Bosses?
All are powerless before
the supreme power of justice.
It sure wasn't named the
"Perfect Clima Takt" for nothing.
Get out of here!
We are a disgrace to Elbaf!
Ahhh! Kashii!
It develops much bigger clouds now,
and it does it much faster too.
E-Elbaf?
Gum-Gum...
Now, I'm gonna see how
powerful its thunderbolt is.
After him! Don't let him get away!
The enemy is alone! Surround him!
Elbaf... Bosses...
...Gatling!
All right!
Don't tell me...! I-Is it possible that
you're from Elbaf, that warriors' village?!
That lady's gonna do something!
We might wanna get out of here!
Ah! Watch out!
Stop!
Get outta my way!
Who are you?!
Here it comes!
Don't get in my way!
How dare you...?!
I-I-I am Sogeking from the island of snipers.
Chief Spandam! Please come in!
Please advise us on countermeasures!
Guys! Let's take the other one down!
Thunderbolt... Tempo!
Yeah!
We can't stop Straw Hat Luffy!
Could you explain to me what
you're talking about in detail?
You bastards!
You're a total stranger from God knows where!
Straw Hat Luffy is headed to the courthouse!
Commander! He's really scary!
Why do I have to tell you?!
Strengthen defenses! Hurry up!
Don't flinch, you idiot! Go!
Calm down! Warriors from Elbaf
are the proudest men in the world!
So what's the current status?
Be quiet!
What's this ruckus?!
Sir. Kashii and Oimo should be
dealing with them right now
You guys woke me up!
in front of the main island front gate.
And yet, you're crying a river here.
It must be a big deal.
Commander!
Ch-Chief Justice!
So I don't think there'll be any issues.
So I want to know why.
"'Three-Headed Baskerville'
Chief Justice, Enies Lobby"
That's right! As a matter of fact,
I am the Chief Justice of Enies Lobby!
I see. So did you capture Straw Hat,
the one who infiltrated the main island?
Grandma, Grandma. That's an
incredible thunderbolt, isn't it?
That... looks like a dead end.
Please...
Well... Er...
There's no use in telling you about it, but...
On the left, I am Left Baskerville!
You'd better still be there...
...this is just an estimate,
but it's about four hundred...
That girl is something else.
On the right, I am Right Baskerville!
Robin!
Me and Kashii were pirates
up until 100 years ago
Grandma, are we gonna be
okay under this umbrella?
Four hundred? What're you talking about?
Trust me. You'll be fine as long as you're here.
And in the center, I am "Central Freeway"!
Our casualties, sir!
Well then, guards, keep these two in chains.
and we ran amok all over the world.
Yes, sir.
Say what?!
Don't ever take the Sea Prism Stone
handcuffs off of Nico Robin, okay?
--What?
--But one day on some island...
Ch-Chief Justice! A pirate is going
on a rampage on the main island,
Huh?! Our casualties?!
Nooo!
We'll take Cutty Flam to Impel Down
and Nico Robin to Navy Headquarters.
Cheers!
Are you saying that four hundred
guards have been taken out?!
but they said that they can't
get in touch with Chief Spandam.
Each one of 'em bagged an
insanely huge Sea King, after all!
As soon as the escort ship is ready,
It looks like there are a hundred more down...
Please give us instructions on his behalf!
we'll go through the
Gates of Justice and sail off.
It's attacking everyone! We'll die, too!
A pirate! Pirates are guilty!
Even though we're Elbaf giants,
Yes, sir! Understood, sir!
Ahh! Sogeking!
Well, I'm sorry. I need to correct the number.
nobody can take down those jumbo-sized
beasts except for our bosses!
Why'd you hit Sogeking, Nami?!
Also... let me tell you guys one thing.
Obviously! Our guards
are not trash or anything.
Hmm...
Don't worry about it.
Oh, come on. Why don't
we make him not guilty?
Right, men?!
I'll be damned if that
many have been taken out!
D-Don't take it out on me.
The problem lies in how you're using it.
Cutty Flam is violen--
If there are casualties,
make sure you get the details right!
Hmm... Then, let's split the
difference and give him...
--He's biting into my head! Hey, Kalifa!
--So Straw Hat showed up?
Those ones were definitely the biggest ones...
Besides, Usopp-kun says that he
doesn't remember adding that feature!
...the death penalty!
--That's sexual harassment.
--Yeah...
Say what?!
Yeah! The biggest ones we've ever caught!
At any rate...
--Hey! Hey! Someone! Someone! Help! Hey!
--A call came in earlier. Chapapa.
There's trouble, Chief Justice!
Er... well then, here is the report.
...that thing is crazy powerful!
You brought down a bunch of them.
--What're you doing?! Hey!
--The Chief was so upset,
it was almost embarrassing.
We got a report that Kashii was taken out
The current casualties we
have here are five... Gahh!
So which one was bigger?
at the main island front gate
by the Straw Hat's comrades
--Let the Chief go!
--But the report said
--Ah...
--Hey, Nami!
--Which...
--...one?
--Give up already, you bastard!
--that there were only five casualties then.
and that Oimo is losing, too!
Five are down?! So it was
actually just five guards?!
What?! Don't let them past the gate!
What the hell did you do that for?!
Hm?
Apologize to him, Sogeking!
You apologize, idiot!
Send 100 Watchdogs immediately!
Geez... You can't even make a report properly?
The receiver is off.
Nami-san! That reminded me of the
shock I had the first time I met you!
Mine is slightly bigger!
Five... hundred guards...
Yes, sir!
Don't give us trouble! Walk already!
What's with those pirates?
You wish! Mine's a whole
three centimeters bigger!
Looks like Straw Hat Luffy isn't fighting;
he's just running around the island.
I thought that girl was here just
for support, but she sure can fight.
Dammit! The promised five minutes is up!
Say what?!
What's your problem?!
This is bad! Hurry up and open
up the path for Rocketman!
Well, that's just natural. No one is
stupid enough to fight that many guards.
Bosses!
Looks like it's over.
Please stop!
I'm not gonna let you through this gate!
Pirate lady, you're incredible!
The two bosses started a duel.
It's just a matter of time before he's captured.
You guys go back to your rooms
and take it easy for the time being.
We unlocked the gate!
Looks like you guys're okay, too, Granny!
It's a battle in which they put their
pride on the line. It can't be helped.
Now we can push the doors open!
It's no accident that I've lived
for several decades, you know!
Thanks to this, it's a sure thing that we,
CP9, will see our status rise incredibly.
Welcome back, sirs and madam.
What?! Shoot!
All right! Good going!
Chief, Mr. Lucci and the others are here.
Go!
That's the signal for the duel.
Why don't we drink a toast on the ship?
Don't touch this gate!
So they're back?
By the way, where's that idiot
who rushed out by himself?
Show them in here.
Rope Action!
The group was split up
and everyone ended up
going back to their hometown.
Beats me... This island isn't small,
so if we are to find him...
Top Knot! Take this!
I don't feel like drinking a toast...
The central mountain... That's Little Garden...!
...since I'm not interested
in status or authority.
What was that?!
Whoa! Just what you'd expect
from a Galley-La foreman!
It was a life-or-death battle between warriors.
That's definitely where he is!
What?
What?! This is just a rope!
Our justice exists in the World Government.
At the very least, the winner was
supposed to come back to the village,
Well, then...
Franky Family! Pull it!
So long as the Government
recognizes you as CP9's commander,
but even after several decades,
neither of them came back.
...let's go after him, shall we?
Yeah!
Just leave it to us! Let's go, Sodom!
Gomorrah! Grab the rope!
we just fulfill our duty with perfection, that's all.
After 50 years passed, me and Kashii
thought something was wrong,
We don't have to support your ideology.
They're mere pirates...
How dare they make a ruckus...?!
so we set out to sea to go get those two.
But on our way, we got caught by the Navy
and they made us tell them everything.
They won't get away with this!
Th-That's a sound argument.
Charge into the gate!
Then what is it that you seek?
Then, in return, we were told a shocking story.
H-Hey! Hold on a sec! I'm feeling dizzy!
They said that our bosses,
who were very strong,
Push the doors!
were confined in the government's large prison!
Blood... perhaps.
It's been a while, Chief.
--Huh?!
--That was about 50 years ago.
Yeah...
Look! The doors are...!
Take this!
Cutty Flam, the criminal who is responsible
Hm?
The doors are opening!
The Government presented conditions.
What's Oimo doing?!
for assaulting Government officials
in Water Seven eight years ago...
If me and Kashii worked for
the Government for 100 years--
A little bit more!
As long as we belong to CP9,
even killing can be justified.
Nico Robin, the criminal who
was involved in the incident
in other words, if we could protect this
gate in Enies Lobby for 100 years--
They give me the creeps.
where Navy battleships were
attacked in Ohara in the West Blue...
they'd release our bosses
and let us all go home to Elbaf.
They're, indeed, the only group
of assassins in the Government.
Gum-Gum... Spear!
We've completed the escort
of these two without a hitch.
The gate has been opened!
What dependable guys my subordinates are.
Since a giant's life span is 300 years,
we thought 100 years was nothing.
They're both behind those doors.
As long as I have them, I feel like I can't lose!
Welcome back! Lucci, Kaku, Blueno, and Kalifa!
So we accepted the conditions and
have kept fighting for the past 50 years.
He jumped onto the tree!
But the gate was broken open today by pirates!
Those jerks! This is endless!
I can't move forward!
That's sexual harassment.
Just calling your name is?!
To think something like this happened...!
Hey, this way!
Dammit! Our bosses will now be
imprisoned for the rest of their lives!
They're running in the opposite direction?!
Long time no see, Lucci.
Half of you guys, head to
the main island front gate!
"Main Gate"
It appears that your audacity
has increased considerably.
Pirates broke open the gate and
are invading! Stop them at any cost!
Hey, hey! H-H-Hold on a sec!
There's something funny about that story.
It appears that your stupidity has as well, Jabra.
There's nothing funny about it!
If you're gonna laugh at our pride, then...
They must be here! Good!
That makes things quite a bit easier!
What'd you say?
No, no, I didn't mean it that way!
I meant that it's weird!
Stop it, both of you. We just got back.
All right!
"Tower of Law"
Sorry, you missed!
"Courthouse" "Main Island Front Gate"
Weird, you said?!
He's over there! Fire!
Because during our journey before
we came here, we met those two!
Yoyoi! He's right. Stop it, you two.
If I remember right, it was this way, wasn't it?!
Hey, it wouldn't be good if you led the way.
Hey, what's that commotion?
We have been reunited after five years!
Why not?!
It'll be fine if we go straight!
The two you're talking about,
the Elbaf warriors Dorry and Broggy,
have been fighting an evenly matched duel
on that island for the past 100 years!
Seriously, that darn idiot!
He rushed out by himself, as usual!
H-Hey...! Hey!
Something is coming!
Hey...
Well, our sticking with that idiot
makes us quite the idiots as well.
What?! How come you know their names?!
That's... a sea train?
But thanks to Luffy, it seems that the
marines are scattered for the time being.
Chapapa...
What?! That can't be right!
What's going on?
If you wanna hear more proof,
I'll tell you as much as you want!
So all we have to do now is
head straight to the courthouse!
Chapa...
All right, Sodom, Gomorrah!
Keep charging ahead!
Cha... pa...
Oh, no, my chronic disease is coming back...
If you wanna die, you can remain here.
Ow...
--It's cured now!
--That's more like it.
I thought you'd get on it right away, Fukurou.
Dammit! So they're the pirates who
broke open the main island's gate?!
And...
Six Powers Skill, Competition!
What?! It's rushing straight towards us!
Fire! Keep firing!
Wh-What's the matter?
Ribbit, ribbit!
Suppose an armed guard's
strength is Power Level 10.
Don't tell me they're trying
to jump onto the main island...!
If you don't wanna die, get out of our way!
We have guests.
"Power Level 10"
Can't be! There's no way they
can jump over that iron fence!
Take this! Take this!
Your power levels are...
You still don't believe me?! What do I
have to tell you to get you to believe me?!
I'm gonna reveal them.
I'm gonna reveal your strength.
Withdraw briefly and restore formation!
First, Kalifa. She is Power Level 630.
You're mere pirates! Don't get so cocky!
We Watchdogs are ordered
to guard the front gate!
About their weapons?!
Blueno is Power Level 820.
Kaku is Power Level 2,200.
No one can cross this line!
Lucci is...
Their techniques?!
73,466 duels...
Just give up, you damn rogues!
Be prepared, pirates!
Nooo!
I know everything!
...Power Level 4,000!
73,466 draws...
4,000?! Hey, did you measure it properly?!
Hurry up! Don't let them charge in!
Doggie policemen, this time?
I'm gonna eat you!
We really met them!
I've never heard of such a high Power Level!
Don't get on without permission!
Don't think that it's just us, pirates!
Close the gate!
That was accurate! They've all
gotten stronger! Chapapa!
Things are going smoothly! Good thing
we've got you guys on our side!
We're counting on you to
get us to Luffy, King Bulls!
Since I measured Jabra and
Kumadori's too, I know who's stronger!
Hey, granny!
Hm? What is it?
Hey! Objection, Fukurou!
There are still so many...
This is endless, dammit.
Change of plans! Have the
train go as fast as it can!
Looks like we're completely surrounded.
Setting Lucci aside, what's the deal
with me being weaker than even Kaku?!
Now that I look a little closer,
there are too many enemies!
Hm?
I got boxed in!
Chapapa!
Roger!
Kaku has gotten stronger, too!
He's headed your way!
Now, the jig is up, pirates.
You fought desperately to protect our pride.
Guys, looks like we're changing our plan.
It's Straw Hat! Capture him!
Hey, don't be so sure of yourself, Kaku!
The samurai-man says that everyone
should hold on tight to the car.
Don't let him go any further!
As such, no matter what
manner of enemy there may be...
So what?
"Competition" is a technique that just
measures one's martial arts ability.
When I have to hurry up and find Robin...!
He said that!
You sure are cocky! Guys, get them!
...we will not let them
destroy your pride, friends!
Hold on tight?!
I can't move forward like this!
In real battles, my Devil Fruit
powers are added to my abilities.
Why?
Have faith in us, and continue straight ahead!
Hey, idiot swordsman! Did something happen?!
Attack him from both sides!
Just don't forget that you can't defeat me.
Think whatever you like. I'm not
interested in things like that.
He ran to the side! Chase him!
They closed the main gate.
Let's meet again someday.
Grab hold!
What?!
That's right. Don't listen to a stray dog.
What?! This is terrible!
We're gonna crash into the gate!
Without fail.
Dammit! He escaped to the rooftop!
What're we gonna do?! What're we gonna do?!
A stray dog, Lucci?! You damn goblin cat!
--Dodge it, Kokoro-san!
--What're we gonna do?!
Straight ahead! Straight ahead!
Don't worry. There's a way.
We've already been eaten!
Hold it!
Straight ahead! Straight ahead!
That's our Zoro!
Boy, they're stubborn! There's no end to this!
We're not gonna let you get away!
Hey, stop it, both of you!
Hey, you could've at least
let us have a little fun...
Just give up!
Well then, I'll go in one breath!
Hit the fence with a thrust, frog!
At any rate, Jabra is lashing
out at us quite a bit, isn't he?
You idiot!
Gum-Gum...
What?!
Hakoku Sovereignty!
Don't forget why you came here.
All the guards on the island
Ribbit!
We're not gonna let you get away!
This isn't where you should
be focusing your energy.
Capture him!
are talking about Jabra getting rejected
by the waitress Gatherine yesterday.
It's true that it'd take a whole
day to fight this many enemies.
...Rocket!
Ribbit!
We're flying out of it!
See ya!
They cut... the very sea itself...
Oh, that's why.
Dammit! That damn pirate!
H-Hey, hold on a sec! Why does
everyone know about that?!
This is the strength of Elbaf warriors!
They're quite energetic. Don't die, okay?!
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit!
"Courthouse" "Main Island Front Gate"
Don't let the pirates go any further!
I told the guards on the
main island about it. Chapapa!
Slay them!
Charge ahead!
Bring down every single one of them here!
So you're the one?!
Now go!
Fire! Send the Navy packing!
Guards! Get back!
"Gatherine"
I swore to myself to look
up to them as my masters
Geez...
That's a King Bull from Water Seven!
Prepare the cannons immediately!
Don't tell me...!
If we keep on going like this,
we're gonna run ashore on the iron fence!
This is all because you started
right in on that stupid ranking stuff.
and become a man of great
pride like them some day!
Uh-huh, uh-huh...
Having mastered the Six Powers,
Dammit!
And yet, you don't believe me?!
Take this!
you all have far surpassed average people.
It's a big fat lie that they
got caught 50 years ago!
Power Level 500 would be enough for
you to be called superhuman, right?
No way!
You... bastards!
We've got one more!
Chief is Power Level 9,
less than one guard. Chapapa.
The sea train is...
...flying!
Don't say that! It's okay because
I'm your Commander in Chief!
Uh-huh... Uh-huh, uh-huh...
Watchdogs! Get back in formation!
Noo! We're gonna die!
What?! Are we gonna die?!
Yeah!
Besides, I have a highly valued sword, right?!
We won't let you go!
Our dogs are faster than your fish!
Our bosses are alive...
Ahhh!
Got it.
Nami-san! Quickly, into my arms!
I've always known that you're weak, Chief.
And, when the brothers Sodom
and Gomorrah were going to die
Yep, yep...
There's a huge hole where
we're gonna land, you idiot!
This is bad! They're gonna try jumping on!
H-H-Hey, you shouldn't be so blunt, Kalifa.
in a Sea King's stomach, the Franky
Family saved them and said to them,
No way!
I see... I'm relieved... I'm so relieved.
--Can't we go faster?!
--Hey, cook guy.
That's sexual harassment.
Zoro! You'd better have
thought about the landing!
Hm?
What?! Because I responded to your comment?!
"We're full, so we're not gonna eat you guys."
What's the matter?
Take the reins.
Since then, they've pledged loyalty
to Franky, who saved their lives.
Chief...
Wh... What is it?
Just leave it to...
That's sexual harassment!
Whoa...
"Main Island Front Gate"
Hm? You guys...
You mean my existence?!
"Courthouse"
Well, it was just that they just happened
to be in the stomach of the Sea King
Yoyoi! Kalifa! How rude of you!
that the Franky Family was eating, right?
--...luck.
--Ribbit!
So it's up to luck?!
Chief! I will... I will take
responsibility by committing hara-kiri!
Probably.
Well, whatever...
But would you watch where
you're going? You make me nervous.
Look! We're almost to the courthouse!
Hara-kiri! Iron Body!
Ahh! Oimo is down!
When you see... those guys, tell them...
How regrettable...! I can't die.
He says, "I'll be faithful to Big Bro
Franky for the rest of my life!"
Bring them down without fail!
"You guys're fired."
I said just die already, you jerk!
He must be really happy that
someone understands his language.
Could it be that it was you, Mom,
up in heaven, who made me stay alive?!
Sure will.
Crap! King Bull!
Jump onto it!
All right! We brought down one of them!
We won't let you!
Is that right?
We'll leave them to you, Galley-La!
Sodom!
I see... So your mother was...
He's asking, "By the way, was it
okay that the guy with the mask
We'll skewer you!
A-Are you... the Straw Hats?!
Jabra, so you understand how I feel?
Half Knot Air Drive!
Sodom!
didn't get on with you guys?"
This is bad! I have to treat him right away!
--That's right!
--We are?!
--What?!
--Hm?!
Sodom! Stand firm! Don't fall yet!
--What?
--Hm...?
Yeah, especially since I got rejected recently,
That's not important.
What?! I-I can't find Sogeking anywhere!
I understand well how someone
who lost their loved one feels.
Guys! Move over right away! Hurry it up!
Let's hurry and move ahead!
Ahhh! S-Some Watchdogs were taken out!
All right! Guys! Now move
ahead as far as you can!
Sodom can't go on much longer!
Those fools! They let their guard down!
Mom!
Why?! Why?!
Gatherine! Am I not good enough for you?!
Yeah!
Did he fall off?
There's no way ordinary people
can match our speed. Go!
His pectoral muscle got hurt by a trench mortar!
No... Come to think of it,
he wasn't riding with us from the start!
Move over now before he falls!
Mom!
Yeah!
No one's gonna be saved
unless you guys move forward!
Don't tell me he ran...!
We'll pierce you before you notice!
"Courthouse" "Main Island Front Gate"
Chief.
What? Wh-What is it?
Paulie!
Looks like the short play is... over.
Dammit!
More went down!
Who are you, bastards?!
O-Oh, okay.
We're the first-class guards of Enies Lobby,
You bastard! Stop blocking the path!
He said, "Go!"
What's with them?!
the Watchdogs of the Law,
Watchdogs for short!
Get out of our way already!
Anyway, you've done a great
job over the past five years.
They're strong!
"'Watchdogs of the Law'
First-Class Guards, Enies Lobby"
On the orders of Chief Justice Baskerville,
If you want to go through here, beat me first!
we'll cast judgment on you
and bring you down at this gate!
Get out of our way!
To think that you caught not only Nico Robin,
but you were even able to capture
that annoying Cutty Flam...
Dammit! They send one guard
after another to block us!
It's coming down!
We'll take care of these guys.
I'm not gonna make it so easy!
Well done!
Oimo! What're you doing?!
Once the good news gets out,
the entire world will praise your efforts.
How could you let pirates
like them open the gate?!
Battleship Cannon!
Ow!
Can you guys tell how proud I am
as your Commander in Chief?
Dammit! It's only three men! Do something!
I passed out!
Oh, shoot! He came around!
It seems that your temperament
hasn't changed at all, huh, Cutty Flam?
Oh, that's right... This isn't really a
reward for your efforts or anything,
You're strong when you fight, right?
I won't forgive you!
You're not gonna get away with this!
If I had realized sooner that you
were alive and had the blueprints,
but I do have something I wanna give you.
No one's riding it!
What?!
Well, I'll do that later.
Can you beat them?
I wouldn't have had to go
through all this trouble...
Hey...
Yes, I can!
So, in any case, let me meet...
...since we could just have brought
you in for your past crimes!
Let's go, Gomorrah!
...the "hope" of the entire world!
What?!
So Robin is in that building behind you, huh?
On the contrary, your older fellow
disciple Iceberg was a hassle.
Get out of my way, bull guy!
When unsure, anyone can be weak.
It seems that you guys haven't noticed...
After Tom died,
he brought the shipbuilding
companies in Water Seven together
There's no limit to their strength
when they know it's okay to save her!
...that what you're doing is a world-class crime.
and organized a big company
by himself. And then,
Wh-Why the hell...
did Rocketman come from the sky?!
he approached the World Government,
which he must've had a grudge against,
Hm?
We'll bring down the whole place!
There was no point in us opening the gate!
and soon his company established its position
There's a technique that I wanna try, too!
as a purveyor to the World Government.
He'll definitely...!
He's the president of the
shipbuilding company Galley-La
and the mayor of the
city of water, Water Seven.
Bring down that rope guy!
Just get to the point already.
Wh-What just happened?!
Not gonna happen!
After he became a figure
that everyone supported
Are they okay after charging in here like that?!
The World Government is a
huge, powerful organization
Shrouds and Ratline Knot!
and that was indispensable to the Government,
we couldn't meddle with him carelessly.
Oh, shoot!
that counts more than 170 countries
around the world as its members.
This is a dead end. Give up.
Th-They aren't coming out...
Invading this island,
which is under its possession,
I heard that your company contracts to
build ships for the World Government!
"Courthouse" "Main Island Front Gate"
L-Lieutenant Commander!
is an act of revolt against all those countries!
There's trouble!
Give me a break! I'm not gonna tolerate it!
--What's the matter?!
--Straw Hat Luffy...!
Upon their dignity, the Government
will expose all of you to public ridicule
So that's why he's been
contracting with the Government...
Now, guys! It's time!
We lost Straw Hat Luffy!
He was a smart man.
and bestow a merciless death upon you.
Let's go, shall we?
How could that be possible?!
How many guards do you think there are?!
You guys are only a few dozen people.
They should've opened those two gates by now.
But we can't find him anywhere!
However, the winds started blowing in my favor.
That is nowhere near enough.
Charge ahead! Charge ahead!
Hey, what happened?!
Don't tell me... he's already
inside the courthouse?!
All I did was tell you to get out of my way.
Just when I couldn't wait any longer and
was about to take forceful measures...
Samurai-man! Take care of the iron fence!
No, sir! We haven't let even
a single bug through here!
My point is that you who entered the gates
of Enies Lobby already have no future,
Wh-Who are those two?!
...Admiral Aokiji sent me the good news...
Leave it to me.
Find him! Find Straw Hat at any cost!
whether I move out of
your way or not. That's all.
...that Nico Robin was headed
to Water Seven on a pirate ship.
Fighting is a waste.
Hmph!
Ouch!
I thought you got a good taste of our
Six Powers at Galley-La's mansion...
Huh? Should we have
introduced ourselves first?
Hurry up! We don't have much time left!
Hurry up and open the gate!
I drank a cup of coffee to calm myself down
That's stupid. Why should we?
That must be the last building.
...as well as the difference in
our levels of fighting ability.
and put all the conditions, including
Buster Call, into the plan of operations.
Roronoa and the others are here!
We've been waiting!
Don't flinch! Go!
All right.
Yeah, that's true...
Well, there was a bit of change in the plans,
But there's no path.
But for some reason, I don't feel
like I'm gonna lose at all now!
Where am I?!
Although it's a bit far, I guess I'll try jumping.
but look! Both triggers for the
ancient weapon's revival are here!
It was just as I instructed.
Really?!
Gum-Gum... Storm!
This street is hard to walk on!
Gum-Gum...
What the heck?
Iron Body.
Air Door.
Do you get it? The winds the entire
world over are blowing in my favor.
...Rifle!
Whoa! Ow!
He went that way!
Dammit!
Don't let him get away!
Just wait, you darn Robin!
Hold it!
Don't think that you can leave
the Straw Hats so easily!
Ah! You're that bull guy
who was with the pigeon guy!
A power strong enough to give me control
over any large country I might desire
He came out!
What?! I don't remember him
being as powerful as he is now
Gum-Gum...
The actual situation seems quite
a bit different from the report...
Capture him!
is in my hands now!
...Yo-Yo!
when I fought him at the mansion!
Hey! How'd you do that?!
Why did Aokiji give you the
authority to exercise Buster Call?
That was amazing! Is that a magic trick?
Gatling!
We've finally cornered him!
...although I did think that there was
no way there'd be only five casualties.
Shave!
Boy, that was a big surprise!
Since the start of the World
Government, it's unprecedented...
Huh?
...for a man to step this far
into the Government's entrance.
The Commander in Chief wants
to see you. Both of you, go inside.
Y-You have nowhere else to run!
You're in no position to ask me
questions, you insolent woman!
Get out of my way, bull.
How long are you planning to keep fighting?
If I hadn't recognized
the value of your existence,
The world this, the Government that...
it would've been practically worthless!
It's not my problem.
You guys...!
So you should appreciate me!
You, the repugnant kin of Ohara,
the land of devils...
Don't get in my way!
We just came here to get Robin back!
Until I die.
Nico Robin...
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We'll become No. 1
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
an era created by risking everything
We always try our best, let's go!
If we want to achieve glory,
now is the time--don't be afraid
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
We can take off with unknown powers
We don't fear, and we don't waver
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Charge ahead
Let's start running towards tomorrow
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
Are you guys all ready?!
We're gonna charge into Enies Lobby!
Get out of my way.
Wait! That's not what we agreed upon!
Gomorrah!
Seriously, that idiot! He rushed out by himself!
Don't you get what it means to
attack the World Government?
This is bad. Enemies are gathering
from the front and the back.
What we agreed?
We're changing our plan.
They closed the main gate.
That the Straw Hats would
leave Water Seven safely!
What else is new?
This is terrible! There're thousands of enemies!
What?! What're we gonna do?!
That's right!
But what're we gonna do?!
We're surrounded by a ton of enemies!
The world this, the Government that...
Unless we do something,
we're gonna crash into the gate!
They left Water Seven safely...
and so, now, they're here, right?
If we get surrounded in a place
like this, we can't move forward!
It's not my problem.
Hey, do something!
That's fine. I've been waiting for this.
You guys already have no future!
No need to worry. There's a way.
--What?!
--What's the matter, Chopper?!
Why don't we have some fun, too?
--That's our Zoro!
--Just leave it to... luck.
We just came here to get Robin back!
Gomorrah... Gomorrah's saying something!
No...
So it's up to luck?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Catch Up with Luffy!
The Straw Hats' All-Out Battle"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Robin Betrayed! The Motive
of the World Government!"
"Don't Stop! Hoist the Counterattack Signal!"
"Give Robin Back! Luffy vs. Blueno!"
"Find A Way Out! Rocketman Takes Flight!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!