Riding on Rocketman,
the Straw Hat Pirates have infiltrated
the Enies Lobby main island.
By the way, where's that idiot
who rushed out by himself?
Beats me... This island isn't small,
so if we are to find him...
What was that?!
That's definitely where he is!
As for Luffy, who went ahead of the others,
he still hasn't been able
to reach the courthouse.
He jumped onto the tree!
Those jerks! This is endless!
I can't move forward!
What's the matter?
Take the reins.
Hm? You guys...
When you see... those guys, tell them...
"You guys're fired."
Sure will.
Jump on to it!
We won't let you!
Half Knot Air Drive!
Ahhh! S-Some Watchdogs were taken out!
We'll take care of these guys.
Meanwhile, Robin and Franky
were facing a desperate situation.
Look! Both triggers for the
ancient weapon's revival are here!
Do you get it? The winds the entire
world over are blowing in my favor.
A power strong enough to give me control
over any large country I might desire
is in my hands now!
Why did Aokiji give you the
authority to exercise Buster Call?
Huh?
You're in no position to ask me
questions, you insolent woman!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
we will be able to make it through
Always!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
We can't stop here
Around the world
Start me up!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Brand New World
Start me up!
If I hadn't recognized
the value of your existence,
it would've been practically worthless!
So you should appreciate me.
You, the repugnant kin of Ohara,
the land of devils...
Nico Robin...
"Robin Betrayed! The Motive
of the World Government!"
Now, listen good.
From here on, you'll suffer pain so severe
that you will wish many
times for death to come,
so prepare yourself.
We'll hurt you, use you,
and throw you away into the sea.
That is how deeply sinful
your existence itself is!
Oh, that's right. I got a call earlier.
They reported that some morons
have infiltrated our island
just to get back worthless trash like you.
Don't tell me...!
Well, they should all be caught by now.
It's Straw Hat Luffy and his crew.
Why do those kids...
They seemed no better than trash in
front of the 10,000 Enies Lobby soldiers.
Well, we're about to send a ship to the prison.
They are a good gift.
I'll take them to Impel Down
together with Cutty Flam.
Wait! That's not what we agreed upon!
In return for my cooperation, you were
supposed to let them escape safely!
What are you flying off the handle for?
Lucci! Tell us exactly what the
condition that we offered her was.
That the six Straw Hats, excluding Nico Robin,
would leave Water Seven safely.
Yeah, that's right.
There's no mistake in that, right?
They came here after leaving
Water Seven safely, right?
What?
Don't tell me... that you're going to
break the deal using such twisted logic!
They're hopeless scum. They don't
have a shred of morality in them.
Huh? What'd you say?
Shut up, you trash!
To start with, we don't even have to
keep our promises with you criminals!
Take this! Take this! You bastard!
You too!
Don't get so cocky, you bitch!
Even the Navy openly uses
tricks to capture pirates!
You dirty coward...
To think that you're still talking back...
You've been betraying people all this time.
Don't think that you can
choose an ideal way to die now.
You guys can all die together.
All are powerless before
the supreme power of justice.
After him! Don't let him get away!
The enemy is alone! Surround him!
Stop!
Get outta my way!
Don't get in my way!
You bastards!
Commander! He's really scary!
Don't flinch, you idiot! Go!
Commander!
That... looks like a dead end.
You'd better still be there...
Robin!
Well then, guards, keep these two in chains.
Yes, sir.
Don't ever take the Sea Prism Stone
handcuffs off of Nico Robin, okay?
We'll take Cutty Flam to Impel Down
and Nico Robin to Navy Headquarters.
As soon as the escort ship is ready,
we'll go through the
Gates of Justice and sail off.
Yes, sir! Understood, sir!
Also... let me tell you guys one thing.
Cutty Flam is violen--
--He's biting into my head! Hey, Kalifa!
--So Straw Hat showed up?
--That's sexual harassment.
--Yeah...
--Hey! Hey! Someone! Someone! Help! Hey!
--A call came in earlier. Chapapa.
--What're you doing?! Hey!
--The Chief was so upset,
it was almost embarrassing.
--Let the Chief go!
--But the report said
--Give up already, you bastard!
--that there were only five casualties then.
Hm?
The receiver is off.
Don't give us trouble! Walk already!
You guys go back to your rooms
and take it easy for the time being.
Thanks to this, it's a sure thing that we,
CP9, will see our status rise incredibly.
Why don't we drink a toast on the ship?
I don't feel like drinking a toast...
...since I'm not interested
in status or authority.
What?
Our justice exists in the World Government.
So long as the Government
recognizes you as CP9's commander,
we just fulfill our duty with perfection, that's all.
We don't have to support your ideology.
Th-That's a sound argument.
Then what is it that you seek?
Blood... perhaps.
As long as we belong to CP9,
even killing can be justified.
They give me the creeps.
They're, indeed, the only group
of assassins in the Government.
What dependable guys my subordinates are.
As long as I have them, I feel like I can't lose!
"Tower of Law"
"Courthouse" "Main Island Front Gate"
Hey, what's that commotion?
Something is coming!
All right, Sodom, Gomorrah!
Keep charging ahead!
Dammit! So they're the pirates who
broke open the main island's gate?!
Fire! Keep firing!
Ribbit, ribbit!
If you don't wanna die, get out of our way!
Take this! Take this!
Withdraw briefly and restore formation!
You're mere pirates! Don't get so cocky!
Be prepared, pirates!
Nooo!
I'm gonna eat you!
Don't get on without permission!
Things are going smoothly! Good thing
we've got you guys on our side!
We're counting on you to
get us to Luffy, King Bulls!
There are still so many...
This is endless, dammit.
Hm?
I got boxed in!
He's headed your way!
It's Straw Hat! Capture him!
Don't let him go any further!
When I have to hurry up and find Robin...!
I can't move forward like this!
Attack him from both sides!
He ran to the side! Chase him!
Dammit! He escaped to the rooftop!
Hold it!
Boy, they're stubborn! There's no end to this!
We're not gonna let you get away!
Just give up!
Well then, I'll go in one breath!
Gum-Gum...
We're not gonna let you get away!
Capture him!
...Rocket!
See ya!
Dammit! That damn pirate!
"Courthouse" "Main Island Front Gate"
Don't let the pirates go any further!
Slay them!
Bring down every single one of them here!
Fire! Send the Navy packing!
Uh-huh, uh-huh...
You... bastards!
Uh-huh... Uh-huh, uh-huh...
Got it.
And, when the brothers Sodom
and Gomorrah were going to die
in a Sea King's stomach, the Franky
Family saved them and said to them,
"We're full, so we're not gonna eat you guys."
Since then, they've pledged loyalty
to Franky, who saved their lives.
Well, it was just that they just happened
to be in the stomach of the Sea King
that the Franky Family was eating, right?
Probably.
Well, whatever...
But would you watch where
you're going? You make me nervous.
He says, "I'll be faithful to Big Bro
Franky for the rest of my life!"
He must be really happy that
someone understands his language.
He's asking, "By the way, was it
okay that the guy with the mask
didn't get on with you guys?"
--What?!
--Hm?!
--What?
--Hm...?
What?! I-I can't find Sogeking anywhere!
Why?! Why?!
Did he fall off?
No... Come to think of it,
he wasn't riding with us from the start!
Don't tell me he ran...!
"Courthouse" "Main Island Front Gate"
You bastard! Stop blocking the path!
Get out of our way already!
If you want to go through here, beat me first!
Get out of our way!
I'm not gonna make it so easy!
Battleship Cannon!
Dammit! It's only three men! Do something!
You're strong when you fight, right?
Can you beat them?
Yes, I can!
When unsure, anyone can be weak.
There's no limit to their strength
when they know it's okay to save her!
We'll bring down the whole place!
There's a technique that I wanna try, too!
He'll definitely...!
Bring down that rope guy!
Not gonna happen!
Shrouds and Ratline Knot!
Oh, shoot!
This is a dead end. Give up.
"Courthouse" "Main Island Front Gate"
L-Lieutenant Commander!
There's trouble!
--What's the matter?!
--Straw Hat Luffy...!
We lost Straw Hat Luffy!
How could that be possible?!
How many guards do you think there are?!
But we can't find him anywhere!
Don't tell me... he's already
inside the courthouse?!
No, sir! We haven't let even
a single bug through here!
Find him! Find Straw Hat at any cost!
Hmph!
That must be the last building.
All right.
But there's no path.
Although it's a bit far, I guess I'll try jumping.
What the heck?
Air Door.
Ah! You're that bull guy
who was with the pigeon guy!
The actual situation seems quite
a bit different from the report...
Hey! How'd you do that?!
That was amazing! Is that a magic trick?
...although I did think that there was
no way there'd be only five casualties.
Boy, that was a big surprise!
Since the start of the World
Government, it's unprecedented...
...for a man to step this far
into the Government's entrance.
Get out of my way, bull.
How long are you planning to keep fighting?
Until I die.
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We'll become No. 1
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
an era created by risking everything
We always try our best, let's go!
If we want to achieve glory,
now is the time--don't be afraid
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
We can take off with unknown powers
We don't fear, and we don't waver
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Charge ahead
Let's start running towards tomorrow
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
Get out of my way.
Don't you get what it means to
attack the World Government?
The world this, the Government that...
It's not my problem.
You guys already have no future!
We just came here to get Robin back!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Give Robin Back! Luffy vs. Blueno!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!