Sogeking, who was left alone
at the main island front gate,
There's a dead end ahead!
He'll crash into it and die!
Every single thing those guys do is interesting.
Robin!
You can go ahead and say
you wanna die or whatever,
heard something shocking from
one of the giant gatekeepers.
Those who have common sense
wouldn't meddle with this island.
Gomorrah! Stop! Don't run randomly!
In pursuit of Luffy, four of the
Straw Hats and the Franky Family
but say those things... by our side!
One day on some island...
Stop!
Just wait and see, Chimney.
were nearing the courthouse. However...
...the two bosses started a duel.
Dead end? Do you see one?
Whether they end up surviving this or dying,
Just leave the rest to us!
Take us to the courthouse, Gomorrah!
Nope... I don't see anything of the sort.
It's a big fat lie that they
got caught 50 years ago!
the entire world will be shocked
to learn of this incident...
They've come all this way
after crossing Aqua Laguna.
Something that no one has been able
to do in the past several hundred years.
"Main Island Front Gate"
When you think about it, it's incredible.
Meanwhile, just when the courthouse
came into view for the Straw Hats
"Courthouse"
Seems like they've at least got good luck.
After this battle,
Gomorrah!
on the back of the King Bull...
This time, we have permission to kill them.
the name of that straw hat kid will
be known throughout the whole world!
It's easy when we don't have to
worry about going easy on them.
Dammit! Who are they?!
Crap! King Bull!
Drawbridge?
Sodom!
Yeah. The Franky Family is
currently fighting to bring it down.
Sodom! Stand firm! Don't fall yet!
Once it comes down, we can go
over to the other side at once.
"Guilty"
Guys! Move over right away! Hurry it up!
Robin!
Geez... When it's right in front of us...
Not gonna be that easy... you damn trash.
This report is for all units!
The King Bull with the pirates on it broke
through the encirclement in Block D!
He's here!
It's coming down!
They've just reached the courthouse plaza!
Luffy...
Around that time, Luffy and Blueno were
facing off on the courthouse rooftop.
"Courthouse"
I've come to get you!
All right! The second one is down, too!
I repeat! The pirates...!
To all units on Enies Lobby!
If we get surrounded in a place
like this, we'll be goners!
You idiot...
Chief! A guy in a straw hat is shouting
something on the courthouse rooftop!
All soldiers! Head to the
courthouse plaza immediately!
So Robin is in that building behind you, huh?
Seriously, just how terrible is
the burden this woman is bearing?
"Courthouse" "Rocketman"
Meanwhile, Sogeking was
around the main island front gate.
The pirates have reached the courthouse plaza!
Get out of my way, bull guy!
I think it's Straw Hat Luffy,
the captain of the Straw Hat Pirates!
Hey, CP9! Listen!
It seems that you guys haven't noticed...
Don't be ridiculous! When I checked
earlier, Blueno was on the rooftop!
Huh?
I give you permission to kill them,
but take them on here at the Tower of Law!
Also, the giant gatekeepers
at the main island front gate,
...that what you're doing is a world-class crime.
Oimo and Kashii, went over to the pirates' side!
Wasn't he standing watch?! That idiot!
The most important things of
all are my life and promotion.
They're currently around the center of the
main island running towards the courthouse!
Hm?
What's he doing at a critical time like this?!
All right! Oimo and Kashii are back in business!
The Government will expose
all of you to public ridicule
Get outta our way!
If I let them do as they want,
who'll protect me when something happens?!
and bestow a merciless death upon you.
The casualties of our guards are...
Oh, no...
Gum-Gum...
...over 2,000!
I did quite a bit of fighting, so...
We don't have much energy
left to fight guys like them.
And the captain, Straw Hat Luffy,
who beat over 1,000 all by himself,
Iron Body.
...Rifle!
I'm starving!
You stupid pirates!
Is this it for us?!
Get it in your heads that putting on
a brave front doesn't change anything!
For a time like this, I packed...
suddenly disappeared, so we're
searching for him right now!
...a meal!
You're up against the power
of the assassin group CP9
This is probably unprecedented--
the worst situation we've had
How...
I'm so glad that I had these in my pockets!
...dare you...
and the weight of the Gates of Justice
that can't be opened by human strength.
in the history of Enies Lobby!
What?! I don't remember him
being as powerful as he is now
Huh?
This is yummy!
...deceive us?!
And above all things, right now...
when I fought him at the mansion!
What's going on?
What the hell is happening
on this island right now?!
...I have the authority to exercise Buster Call
Gatling!
Shave!
Before we rejoice over
the safety of our bosses...
by using this golden transponder snail!
So he is the one? Straw Hat Luffy...
Before we grieve over our wasted years...
What the hell is going on?
Buster Call...!
We'll take out all our anger
on them in a furious rampage!
That's right.
What's Blueno do...
It's the power that wiped out your hometown
Let's go together... king of snipers!
You jerk!
exactly twenty years ago, Nico Robin.
Don't tell me... He couldn't have...
He jumped!
Sogeking is now headed to Luffy
and the others with Oimo and Kashii.
I remember that the following year, the name
"Ohara" had been wiped off of the map.
He's a member of CP9.
Finger Pistol!
Shave!
He's a Six Powers master
with Devil Fruit powers.
No need for formality! Hoist the
counterattack signal this time for sure!
Iron Body! Smash!
Blueno, a superhuman with
a Power Level of over 800...
Robin's hometown?
Hurry to our comrades!
That damn masked jerk!
Gum-Gum... Bullet!
Okay! My power's back!
We just came here to get Robin back!
There's no place for me to go or go back to.
Iron Body!
--This tastes terrible.
--You'll soon notice how big the change is.
...was taken out by a brat like that?!
The battle against CP9 has finally begun!
Don't!
Not that!
Tempest Kick!
This is the birth of new
Devil Fruit power-holders.
I like that reaction. It gives me a chill.
I look forward to seeing those powers.
Ch-Chief! What should we do?!
Get a handle on your own powers
at least, while you have a chance.
What? Does it mean that you
want me to press this button
Lucci... Where's Lucci?
That's...
"Courthouse"
Around the same time, Luffy was
waging a fierce battle against Blueno
Geez... They're reckless, aren't they?
to activate Buster Call? Hm? Does it?
Call in Lucci and the others!
Gather everyone here!
Grandma! Grandma!
on the rooftop of the courthouse.
I'll order CP9 to annihilate
Straw Hat Luffy and his crew members!
Do you really understand what'll
happen when you press it?
Not like this.
Hm?
I'm no good like this.
I do. It'll eliminate the possibility of
the pirates escaping from this island!
What is it, Chimney?
Y-Yes, sir! Right away!
Iron Body!
Listen... Listen!
Tell the Baskervilles, too!
When Aokiji defeated me, I thought...
Tell them that if the pirates bring
down the drawbridge by some chance,
Wheel!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Just with this single button.
"If I am to encounter more
strong guys like him in the future,
I'll cut off all of their heads!
It's that simple.
Yes, sir!
It won't be that simple!
I won't be able to protect my friends...
unless I become stronger."
Are you remembering something?
Raise your head, Nico Robin.
Door-Door!
If you like, shall I try pressing it?
I have friends I want by my side
even if they're not strong.
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
They finally made it this far.
Right here, right now?
A-A door just opened on the ground!
Hey, this is really crazy.
Door-Door.
So if I don't get stronger
than anyone, I'll lose all of them.
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
I now know that you accepted
the Government's terms
What're you doing?! Stop it!
Wh-What the heck?!
Were there small doors here?!
Then what're you gonna do?
to save your friends and got brought in here.
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
You sure talk cocky, don't you?
But that agreement was casually
broken by that moron chief earlier.
I came up with a way to
fight with all my might...
Crap! I got stuck! Dammit!
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
...so that I won't lose anyone...
It's not like someone will be saved just
because you meekly stay captured here.
Revolving Door.
So that no one will go far away.
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
What?! What?!
Wh-What's going on?! I feel dizzy!
So the only thing you can do is
accept their help and escape from here.
What's he doing?
What's happening inside his body?!
we will be able to make it through
Wh-Wh-Which way is forward?! Stop!
And yet, you're looking quite gloomy...
Tempest Kick!
You'll now... no longer be
able to keep up with me.
You said that "Ohara" had
been wiped off the map.
Always!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
...as if you're still running
away from something.
Can you see humans on a map?!
What?
All my techniques will evolve one step further.
Because you guys see the world that way...
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Are you afraid of your friends
dying here or something?
...you can do such a cruel thing!
Second... Gear!
Hey, Cook!
If you turn your eyes away
from them, they can't rescue you.
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
Yeah, I saw it.
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Luffy's already fighting CP9.
Hey! Isn't anyone there?!
What?!
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
We can't stop here
Buster Calls are a heartless power that
even makes you lose sight of your goal.
Around the world
I'll have you meet Straw Hat.
There's only one path left!
Start me up!
You mustn't use it. Not that.
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
Yeah, we're gonna make
a dash for the courthouse!
What?!
Never...! Not that!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
That's the only choice we have.
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
All right, let's go, guys!
"20 years ago - 'West Blue'
Ohara"
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
--Yeah!
--Wait!
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
All of you, don't get off!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
Chopper?!
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Hold on tight!
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
Brand New World
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
we will be able to make it through
Start me up!
Gomorrah... Gomorrah says so!
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
Always!
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
"Don't Stop! Hoist the Counterattack Signal!"
Go! Gomorrah!
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
"Courthouse" "Rocketman"
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
we will be able to make it through
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
Always!
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
We can't stop here
we will be able to make it through
Around the world
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Start me up!
Always!
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
It's coming! Aim well!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
head past everyone else
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
Let it get closer!
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
That's a trench mortar! Dodge it, Gomorrah!
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
We can't stop here
This center path isn't good. They're fully
prepared and waiting in ambush!
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
Around the world
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
We're gonna change the route!
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
Start me up!
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
We can't stop here
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
we will be able to make it through
Around the world
Brand New World
Start me up!
Always!
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Start me up!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
We're not gonna let you get away!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
"Everything Is to Protect My Friends!
Second Gear Activated!"
Sodom...
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Stop right there!
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
everything we see before us,
Baskerville! Chief Justice
Baskerville! Come in! It's me!
Brand New World
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
Start me up!
Whoa! Chief Spandam!
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
"Courthouse"
We can't stop here
This is Left Baskerville on the left!
Chopper...
Around the world
This is Right Baskerville on the right.
Brand New World
Hm?! The portable
transponder snail is ringing?!
Start me up!
And in the center, I am "All Alone
Traveling the Central Main Line"!
Start me up!
Hello? Who is it?
"Give Us Your Answer, Robin!
The Straw Hats' Outcry!!"
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
It's me.
--Who the heck is that?!
--Give me a status report!
That's Granny Kokoro.
What're you calling for?
I heard that the pirates have already
made it to the courthouse plaza!
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Sounds like you guys are still alive.
Where are you right now?
"Robin's Past! The Girl
Who Was Called a Devil!"
Listen good!
Status?
We'll shut Nico Robin away
from Straw Hat immediately!
We're getting closer to the courthouse. Why?
Hmm... Status...
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
We're gonna head to the
Gates of Justice right away!
Good timing. There's something
I forgot to tell you.
Bring those two!
As for the status...
Ch-Chief!
Hey, Robin's there!
Get her!
Just do it! Now!
Something you forgot to tell us?
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
More than the plaza,
the inside of the courthouse is...
I'm sure you guys are busy,
so I'll make it quick. Listen carefully.
But...
Ow!
Franky's butt is inflating!
...in the most terrible state!
All right!
Brand New World
What?!
On the map drawn by Paulie,
Hey, monster!
Ahhh! What the hell is that?!
there's no path from the courthouse
to the Gates of Justice, right?
Start me up!
You're creepy!
Oh, hey, Spanda!
Monster! Monster! Monster! Monster!
That's right. I was just thinking about that.
I realized that this is it for me,
so I've chosen to explode myself.
Ch-Chief Justice! I have a report!
"Almost to Luffy!
Gather at the Courthouse Plaza!"
Look at the courthouse.
There's a tower on each side, right?
The courthouse's huge stone
doors were finally cut through
What?!
At least I'll get to take some
detestable guys like you with me.
Yeah, there is.
Ahh! The monster hit me!
There's a lever on the top floor of each tower.
and the pirates have invaded!
Idiot! Wait, you idiot!
I can see that already, you idiot!
She's creepy!
I'll end my life with a big explosion
3 km in diameter. So don't stop me.
When you pull them,
a drawbridge will come down
We'll get you for this!
I thought we'd see more enemies in here.
from the courthouse to the Gates of Justice.
Looks like we can move straight ahead,
but what the heck is that?
Granny, how come you know that stuff?
Don't do it! Help! Don't take me with you!
I came here with Tom-san to
fix the bridge a long time ago.
What?! His head...!
Three... Two...
That damn ungrateful, stupid Government!
He's like that guard dog from hell
I heard about in some story!
Don't take it out on me.
Dammit! I can't die here!
Berberus?!
You mean Cerberus!
Chimney wants to talk to you, too.
One...
Men! Order!
Hey, Gomorrah! Why are you
trying to crash yourself into walls?!
Stop it!
Hello, pirate lady! Can you hear me?
This is a sacred chamber of law!
Whoa! What is it, Chimney?
What's going on? So he can't go on after all?!
We'll now cast judgment
on your inevitable fate!
Let's go, Nico Robin!
Listen. I saw the rubber pirate guy
on the rooftop of the courthouse.
Coup de Boo!
Ribbit!
Th-That's not it! He can't see!
All right, guys, head to the
rooftop where Straw Hat is!
Hey, you!
Really?! Luffy was there?
--What?!
--His eyesight has weakened
because his retinas got hurt!
I saw rocks collapsing there, too,
so it looks like he's going on a rampage.
A group of us along with Yokozuna
will stop pursuers at the doors.
All right! It broke the chains, too.
My children came home crying,
saying that you hit them for no reason.
Ahh! I'm falling!
What?! You can't see?!
We've got your back, so just charge ahead!
On the rooftop? Got it. Thanks.
Stay away from my children.
Pirate girl, keep the
transponder snail connected
Got it.
Super!
Pfft!
--Hey, look at that.
Looks like the trial has started.
--Their crime is as follows!
It started running like crazy!
so that I'll know what's going on over there.
Why don't you say something?!
Don't break the encirclement!
Stop the monster!
--First, the act of stepping into Enies Lobby,
--Ignore it. It's just a bother!
Which way do we go?!
Geez... You really are a creepy child.
Okay...!
So they said.
--which belongs to the World Government, is...
--Straight ahead! There are stairs on both sides!
What're you doing?!
Fire the trench mortars already!
Now we know where we have to go.
We'll take them to the upper floors!
Yeah!
Hey, wait!
All right!
I'm not done with you yet!
Ahh! How rude! They ignored our sacred trial!
All right, you guys go straight to
the courthouse and join Straw Hat.
Stop, Gomorrah!
That was close.
You're in no shape to keep running anymore!
Good thing there was a fence.
That's unforgivable! How dare
they mock the judicial island?!
Hey, you aren't hurt, are you?
Okay.
Damn you! Die!
He says that he promised Sodom!
Mommy, Mommy, what're we
having for dinner tonight?
We're gonna split into two
and bring the drawbridge down.
What'd you like to eat?
He said to Sodom, "Leave the rest to me!
If I had another bottle of cola,
Um... Um...
I could've also taken us to the
other side using Coup de Vent...
What's going on? His swords
look like they're bending!
I'll run with everyone on my back for you!"
Rice omelet!
Take us to the courthouse, Gomorrah!
You sure like rice omelets, don't you?
Oh, well. Hey, Straw Hat's there.
Enbima Yonezu...
--Yep!
--We have to buy lots of eggs, then.
Gomorrah...
Now, respond to him.
All right!
...Oni Giri!
Ahh! We were tricked!
Chief! Franky and Nico Robin broke
the chains and went out to the balcony!
They were inside its stomach?
Gomorrah!
I can't eat anymore. I'm full.
You fools! What're you doing?!
Capture them already!
Is he the one who cut open the door?
Let's take them back
with us for emergency food.
I'm back. I'm sorry I'm late.
If you let them get away,
I'll have you all hanged!
What?!
Bro! There's trouble! Some pirates
beat up Sodom and Gomorrah!
Dammit! Who are they?!
Aunt Roji?
Okay, let's go. The path is now open!
Yep!
You've got some nerve
messing with my underlings!
So why is a guy who's that
strong not their captain?
Oh, hey, Robin! Good! You're still there!
Wait! Wait! Wait! Outta my way!
Reindeer! Moron swordsman!
"To Robin. Today is..."
Hey! You're injured!
Don't dance! Sodom! Gomorrah!
...our daughter's birthday.
"Guilty"
Luffy...
Capture them again! Don't let
them get away, no matter what!
Suit guy...
So we decided that the three of us
would go out for dinner as a family.
This is a dangerous enemy camp!
You small fries! Stay out of my way!
I'll clear the path for Nami-san
to move forward! Outta my way!
Not gonna be that easy... you damn trash.
Weapons Left!
There's some bread,
so just have that for dinner.
--Whoa!
--Hey, watch it!
What?! Why is he starting a fight?!
Looks like Franky's there, too.
There's a dead end ahead!
He'll crash into it and die!
Don't use too much jam.
All right! The second one is down, too!
All right! Just wait right there.
You jerk! Are you picking a fight?!
Gomorrah! Stop! Don't run randomly!
After dinner, before we get home,
do the dishes, clean the house,
Shut up! Don't you guys
get in Nami-san's royal way!
It's far, but I'll try shooting myself there.
Stop!
The pirates no longer have
a way of getting around!
Nami-san, this way! Follow only me!
Dead end? Do you see one?
Surround them and bring them down!
and take the laundry in, then go upstairs early.
Hey, we came to rescue Robin, right?
To all the guards in Enies Lobby!
Nope... I don't see anything of the sort.
At the center of Block D in the southeast area,
Ah! That's right, Robin-chan is
waiting for me to rescue her!
we brought down the King Bull
that the pirates were riding on!
Call in all the soldiers
and fully blockade Block D!
Could she be crying right
now out of loneliness?!
Mommy, Mommy, what're we
having for dinner tonight?
Seriously...
Hm?
Gum-Gum...
I repeat! All guards, fully blockade Block D!
Ahhh!
What'd you like to eat?
We take our eyes off Zoro
for a second, and now he's...!
Wait!
Um... Um...
Looks like the jury delivered the verdict.
What?!
Rice omelet!
Wait, Zoro! That's the wrong way!
You sure like rice omelets, don't you?
What?!
No one can beat them.
I said the stairs! Just what made
you think you should go that way?!
--Yep!
--We have to buy lots of eggs, then.
I've told you so many times already!
I won't return to you guys!
What're you?! A fantasista?!
All right!
Say something!
Shut up! It was because
you didn't explain it well!
--Yes, sir!
--We'll capture them right away!
Go back! I don't wanna see your faces again!
There's no way it was my fault!
"Courthouse"
Zoro, I'll try making some medicine...
Why did you come to rescue me?
...that works on hopelessness.
The guards that we passed are
now catching up. This isn't good.
Why did you come to rescue me?!
Hopelessness...? Hey!
--Chopper.
--Hm?
This isn't what I want.
--Robin-chan! I'm coming now!
--Make sure it works on that guy, too.
More and more are coming
from the front and the sides.
Er... Yeah, okay, got it.
The trench mortars are aiming at us, too.
When did I ask you guys to rescue me?!
It's the courthouse, Gomorrah!
Ahhh! This is terrible!
There are thousands of them!
I wonder if Bro will be rescued safely.
Oh! There she is! Robin's here!
They're the type that gets it
together when the going gets tough...
If we get surrounded by them in
a place like this, we'll be goners!
Looks like she came to return a book.
W-We're here! Gomorrah!
...probably... I'm sure... yeah...
Everyone, to your positions.
"Courthouse" "Rocketman"
This is a big crime.
This report is for all units!
I just want to... die!
The King Bull with the pirates on it broke
through the encirclement in Block D!
This is a huge crime.
"Courthouse" "Tower of Law"
Good evening, Professor Clover!
I came to return the book I borrowed.
Then, we'll pick the one in the middle...
They've just reached the courthouse plaza!
--Death penalty!
--Agreed!
I repeat! The pirates...!
One, two...!
What?! An earthquake?
Are you okay, Zoro?! This way, okay?
Congratulations, Robin!
Look at this... Funkfreed.
I know!
This is interesting!
What the heck are they doing?
--You're amazing, Robin!
--Just as we'd expect from a genius!
I'm the Chief Justice. Don't ignore me!
What're you doing?!
Th-They're...
We've got a cake for you!
It's a golden transponder snail.
They risked their lives to come
all the way here! And you...
Amazing!
Robin, the exam for the doctoral
degree you took the other day...
Just like the authority to exercise Buster Call,
They did it on their own.
You quite amazingly got 100% on it!
What?! Don't be ridic--
this shiny transponder snail
is indeed a valuable item
Hence, from today on,
we acknowledge you as an archaeologist.
Hey, look!
that can only be carried with the permission
of someone ranked admiral or
above in Navy Headquarters.
Now you're one of us and
we'll do research together.
You're in my way.
All right! Oimo and Kashii are back in business!
Chopper. Nami. Go on ahead.
In order for me to exercise Buster Call,
Aokiji temporarily entrusted it to me.
Kaku! Did you do that to vent your rage?!
Here, this proves that you're
a scholar. Take this, Robin.
Oh, no...
I'll follow you after I take care of this guy.
To vent your rage over eating a weird fruit?
We don't have much energy
left to fight guys like them.
You think you can defeat me?
What a cocky pirate!
Shut up! I do like its powers!
I'm happy for you, Robin.
Just wait and see! Once the revival
of the weapon becomes reality,
Congratulations!
I'll show you how fearful I am!
I'll be able to carry this myself, instead of
having some admiral entrust it to me,
Is this it for us?!
Listen, Robin. You must understand well
what it means to be an archaeologist.
Oh? Is it just Straw Hat that's our enemy?
and control troops at will.
Yoyoi! Even if he's alone,
Hurry up and stomp on them!
Take care of those three, giants!
Yes, Professor Clover!
Pull!
it's admirable that he made it this far.
Knowledge comes from the past.
Buster Call...
S-Stop it!
This Tree of Knowledge is 5,000 years old.
I'm exercising a Buster Call.
Go, Kashii!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho...!
A massive amount of literature
has been brought to this tree
Oh, yeah. Blueno is down.
Commence concerted fire!
Beat the crap out of them, Oimo!
We're targeting everything on Ohara,
the island of archaeology!
from all over the world over
a very, very long period of time.
What a fool!
I guess being a bar owner for five
years would make one weaker, huh?
It's an irreplaceable treasure for all humanity.
S-Stop...
Now, crush those three, giants!
Even if he became weaker,
could he be defeated, though?
Just by pressing this button,
an entire island can be wiped out.
This is the biggest and oldest library in
the world whose pride is its knowledge.
He's been defeated. Chapapa.
And superior archaeologists
from all over the world
Authority can be like a weapon too, huh?
All right! I'm glad that you're here, CP9!
How...
gathered under this Tree of Knowledge.
We'll take you on, Cerberus!
Chief Spandam!
But wait a little longer. The Straw Hats
have just started imploding!
...dare you...
When using these books,
Ahhhh! That scared me!
Franky Family!
there's no historical mystery
that we can't solve.
What's your problem?! Knock on the door first!
Let's watch it.
How dare you...?!
Huh?
Let's go!
Ah... yeah.
This is really interesting!
...deceive us?!
I almost accidentally pressed the button!
Got that, Robin?
Yes!
I-I'm sorry. But I was told
that this is an emergency.
I'd like to see you contribute to the
world by researching various cultures.
There's a call from the Enies Lobby main island!
Wh-What the heck?! Those two
went over to the enemy's side!
What?! A call?! They should've
called this room directly!
Professor! I'd like to solve
the mystery of "Blank History"!
Gear? Your techniques will evolve?
Before we rejoice over
the safety of our bosses...
Are you trying to imitate a
steam engine or something
Before we grieve over our wasted years...
Hm? Hey! The receiver is off!
Wha... No! You shouldn't! I forbid
you to do it, just as I always have.
by blowing off steam from your body?
We'll take out all our anger
on them in a furious rampage!
This happens all the time! Who's behind it?!
What kind of bluff is that?
What? Why? If we research the Poneglyphs,
Hm? You just said that it's an
emergency or something, didn't you?
Let's go together... king of snipers!
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit...!
we'll know what happened during
the "Blank Century," right?
Yes, sir.
I...
Ribbit?!
Why do you know that much?
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit...
Did you peek into the
basement using your powers?!
I'm glad that I met you guys here.
Good job, Yokozuna! Keep it up!
No need for formality! Hoist the
counterattack signal this time for sure!
Ribbit.
But...
Spanda!
Hm?!
Ribbit!
You should know that trying to decipher
the Poneglyphs is a criminal act!
Hurry to our comrades!
Thanks to that, I won't have to lose my friends.
What...?
But... you guys have been
researching the Poneglyphs
--Guilty!
Hey, Nico Robin!
There seems to be an emergency report
from the Enies Lobby main island.
Whoa! "Guilty" juries!
in the basement late at night!
Step aside. We'll pass down
the verdict for that frog's crime.
Robin! How come you know that?!
It's probably not really an emergency,
but you can guess what it's about, right?
Explain yourself! Are you saying that
you've been spying on that, too?
Ribbit!
What happened to Straw Hat Luffy,
Answer me, Robin!
I'm glad that I met you guys here.
Guilty.
That's because...
who worked hard to beat up
a whole five soldiers...
Guilty!
You're a lucky person.
Thanks to that, I won't have to lose my friends.
...you wouldn't let me in the room
even if I openly came and asked!
Most people don't get a
rescue squad, you know.
How your friends got stomped
Refrain from talking!
What're you saying? I don't get it.
by the strongest gatekeepers,
Oimo and Kashii...
I thought... you'd let me be part of your
research if I became an archaeologist.
Got it!
Isn't it because you met us that
you're about to lose your friend?
Well, it's not like I'm jealous that my
underlings aren't here to rescue me.
Let's hear together what happened to the idiots
You're starting to say weird stuff now.
So I studied very hard!
who went against the World Government!
Seriously! What the heck are these guys?!
Have you become confused or something?
You're so low!
Robin...
Guilty! Guilty!
Shut up, you punk!
Gum-Gum...
Let's go, Chopper!
It's true that you've acquired enough
knowledge to be called a scholar.
No, I mean, go, Chopper!
What?! Just me?!
Hey, guard!
Are you trying to aim and attack?
It'll only give me a chance to dodge.
This is Spandam.
I never thought that someone
like the Chief Justice
But you're still a child.
Oh, is this the Chief?! Good!
I can finally give you a report!
would exist on this island in the first place,
Hmph! Why don't you aim
well and hit me if you can?
If they find out what we're doing,
our heads will roll.
since I heard that those taken to Enies
Lobby were already considered guilty,
--Shave!
--...Jet Pistol!
Oh, wait a minute, you guys.
I forgot something.
We're doing it fully aware of the risk.
I don't know where to start.
Ever since it became law 800 years ago,
Calm down, you idiot! You wanna
talk about the Straw Hats, right?
so they'd just pass through an
empty court without stopping.
Take these with you.
What happened after the
last report? Oh, wait! Listen.
there actually have been numerous
scholars who lost their lives.
That's wrong, pirates.
Ahh! Wait a sec! Those are Devil Fruits!
When you report, summarize
the crucial points briefly
This is the most authoritative,
fair court in the world.
This is a good opportunity,
so let me tell you this.
and explain them clearly with a loud voice.
Rifle!
One is judged fairly in trial.
We of Ohara are the only ones in history
--Yes, sir! The invaders--
--Did you accidentally kill them?
Yoyoi! Is that...
However...!
Well, that's their own fault for being so weak.
who managed to decipher the ancient texts.
That is, except for the fact that the juries
who judge guilty or innocent
...true?!
The pirates, who number about sixty,
We cannot go back.
are former pirates who're on death row,
I can't see him at all!
Chapapa...
have invaded and pushed
into the courthouse plaza,
Swear to the Tree of Knowledge!
and they wish to take you down with them.
I've never seen them before!
the farthest point in the
Enies Lobby main island!
If you try to approach the basement again,
Me neither!
Stamp!
I'll forbid you from entering the
research lab and the library! Got that?
This is bad! Keep them away from me!
And Spear!
Us, go down with death-row convicts?!
What's the big fuss, Jabra?
To all units on Enies Lobby main island!
Hence, in this town, no one...
Missile!
You idiot! You don't know?!
All soldiers! Head to the
courthouse plaza immediately!
...in history...
Those with Devil Fruit powers have
a devil dwelling in their bodies!
Robin!
...has been found not guilty!
She's following in her
mother's footsteps in every way.
Kiwi!
For example, if I get closer to one of the Fruits,
You did a good job, Gomorrah!
She still doesn't know about
the incident from the other day.
We won't waste the boost
you two brothers gave us!
a devil jumps out of the Fruit and starts
fighting the devil inside my body,
Can't be...!
Guys!
Robin's mother, Olvia, has been captured.
--Guilty!
which then causes my body to explode!
We're gonna attack, guys!
We'll rescue Big Bro Franky!
No, there's no mistake about it.
You can tell what fate awaits her.
Dammit! They're...
Is that true?
I'm glad that I met you guys here.
Don't flinch!
Yeah!
How foolish...
If we don't get through here,
we can't bring down the drawbridge!
It takes a pretty sloppy intelligence
agent to be misled by a rumor.
That man has a good command
of Shave, one of the Six Powers!
The pirates have reached the courthouse plaza!
We left Bro's rescue to Straw Hat!
Grand Line scientists have already clarified
If we get stuck here,
the Straw Hats can't move forward!
the transmission conditions
of the Fruits' powers.
Air Door!
What you're talking about is an example
of those who have eaten two Fruits...
Yokozuna!
"The following day"
...in which case, the person dies
because his body bursts into pieces.
He disappeared...
To think that you got hit directly
several times with those big iron balls!
Greedy idiots bring ruin upon themselves.
You bastards!
If they think about the risk that
they carry with just one Fruit,
Don't bother! We've still got
more than 6,000 soldiers.
you'd think that they could
guess how much of a curse
This is impossible!
To think that a mere pirate has
a good command of Shave...?!
the second one would bring them.
Now, surge into the courthouse!
Coo coo!
Crush the pirates!
What?! Is that right?!
No... Besides the fact that he used Shave,
In any case, I'm surprised that you were
able to obtain two Devil Fruits, Chief.
he strengthened his body enough
to be able to use Shave easily.
Ribbit...!
Where on earth did you get them?
Can you see Luffy?
Does this mean that he's had that
much potential from the start?
I have all sorts of connections.
No.
Eat them to prepare for the future.
What a bad joke.
Become stronger, CP9!
If the rooftop is that high,
we can't just climb up there.
Grrr!
But there's no way someone could
be faster than a Six Powers master!
But let me tell you one thing.
Wh-What's going on? Why are the giants...
I don't know what kind of
devils dwell in those Fruits.
No... It's not like we're made of rubber.
Frog!
A Six Powers master can't lose!
Hey! Tell me what's going on!
How many CP9 members did you see?
It's hard to believe that these
are fruits from this world.
If I turn his body into a door and
contain his movements, it'll be easy.
It was only the big horn guy we saw.
I feel a mysterious power,
kind of like gravity, from them.
Ah... You're with the Straw Hats.
What the heck is going on?!
W... Wa...
They're not listed in encyclopedias, either.
It's hard to believe that all of
them are in a place like that
I'll go all-in and end this battle in an instant!
That seems to be how they normally are.
To think that he's been holding
back this many guards...
with Robin-chan and Franky.
Worms?
It's said that you can tell the name
of the Fruit from the powers you gain,
Yeah! That frog is something else!
In any case, we have to
catch up with Luffy quickly!
Door-Door!
but what kind of powers you'll gain is a gamble.
We have to hurry up and rescue Robin!
Hurry to the courthouse plaza!
It'll be a terrible life if you gain
weird powers with this gamble.
The drawbridge isn't down yet! Corner them!
That hit the spot!
When you guys moved as
if you were disappearing,
On top of that, to think that
you'll become unable to swim...
Where the hell are they? They got
lost again. We don't have time for this.
I saw you moving by kicking the
ground over ten times in a moment.
No matter what powers they are,
it all depends on how you use them.
In all likelihood, you won't become weaker.
I got the hang of it, too.
I somehow survived...
Hm? Oh, yeah...
I'm glad I came to know a technique
for moving like that exists.
There's no inconvenience in
becoming unable to swim, either.
Basically, so long as I get to the upper floors,
it doesn't matter how, right?
Ribbit!
I wonder if she's okay, too.
I'm glad that I met you guys here.
There are tons of sailors who'd sail out
Dragon Twister!
Thanks to that, I can continue
to protect my friends.
to find just one Devil Fruit
and die without any success.
I'm saved for now. Thank you.
What?! What's going on?!
Whoa! What an amazing frog!
Is there a town or something on this land?
Why don't you eat them? It's interesting.
That's the iron ball that knocked
down Gomorrah! Who did that?!
Yeah.
Gum-Gum...
Kalifa, don't do it!
Nothing good will come of this.
I see.
This area is dangerous, too!
Ribbit!
If I was going to drift to somewhere,
I would've liked an uninhabited island.
It tastes like crap. Crap!
Over there! They're running away!
There are three of them!
I'll take it... with the strongest Iron Body!
Jabra doesn't want Kaku and Kalifa
to get stronger. Chapapa...
Why are they running away?
They're the ones who started the attack.
Iron Body! Strength!
You idiot! It's a waste of time chasing
after each enemy who runs away!
That's right! Jealousy hurts a man's name.
...Jet Bazooka!
You can stay there if you want,
but nothing's gonna happen.
As I thought, you guys are no ordinary people!
To think that you subdued the giants.
What a fearful man you are!
My leg got injured, so I'll stay put here.
Yoyoi!
Shut up, you jerks!
Hm? Er... Well...
Hey, you two! Think about it carefully!
I'm planning to make a raft or
something and leave here eventually.
Oh, yeah. All of your friends
headed to the rooftop.
If you sell them in the right way, you can
get several hundred million Berries!
One bite of Fruit will become a
problem for the rest of your life!
--Rooftop?
--You should hurry there, too!
This your first time seeing a giant?
Shut up. I just went to check.
Your body sure is made tough, huh?
King of snipers. Leave it to me.
Yep.
I'm telling you, don't lump me
in with those guys from Elbaf.
Huh?
It wouldn't hurt to know what kind
of enemies would attack us, would it?
Well then, I'll show you more
interesting stuff. Just watch!
Whoa! He brought him down!
Third...
There are peaceful giant tribes, too.
You wanna die?!
What is this guy?!
That's right!
He must have Herculean strength
to swing around something like this!
I see...
Chapapa...
I know it's a long shot, but I'll ask you anyway.
Does he belong to a special
unit like the Watchdogs?
That sounds interesting.
Hey, Chief. If we go over there
quickly and eliminate that guy,
When you get home, I don't want
you to tell anyone about me.
There may be more hiding. Be careful.
If this is a winner, I'll welcome it.
wouldn't that end this whole thing?
Well, wait. A captain who came all
this way to rescue his crew member
Ahh! They ate them, dammit!
Okay.
Now, let's hurry up.
The guards are closing in on us.
That was too easy. She'll definitely tell.
Coo coo! Coo coo!
and yet finds them turning down
his rescue at the very end...
Corner them!
Chapapa...
I won't tell.
They're not gonna be able to open the
courthouse's heavy stone doors anyway!
Have you guys seen something
that interesting before?
Bring them down here in the plaza!
That's a lie! There's no way
that a child can keep a secret.
Come to think of it, these are huge doors.
I'm so exhausted.
Robin!
What's the matter?!
As I thought, my body can't keep up yet.
You wanna die?!
Yoyoi! Have you noticed
any changes in your body?!
I won't tell because I'm not interested in you.
How will we...
Listen to his pathetic shout!
I can only imagine the look on his...
Well, I don't care about my body right now.
...get them open...?
Chapapa...
I got set back quite a bit.
What the heck are you talking about?
Get a move on! I'll go on ahead!
"Gates of Justice" "Tower of Law"
Wh-Wh-What?!
H-He cut through that thick stone!
H-He's picking his nose!
"Courthouse" "Main Island Front Gate"
Dammit! What's going on?!
Zambai!
This tastes terrible.
Listen, Robin.
We'll split up and go to both sides
Couldn't you say that sooner?!
Cannons! Fire the cannons!
They're gonna stomp on us!
We've already come this far.
It tastes terrible.
We've already heard that. Chapapa!
in order to pull down the drawbridge's levers!
"Dereshi"?
Don't say it after you ate the whole thing!
What does that mean?
O-Okay! I'm counting on you guys!
That's useless! I'm not gonna stop,
you shorty guards!
What does it mean? I'm just laughing.
All right! We'll split into three groups!
Hey, try doing something!
What kind of powers did you get?!
Me, neither! You can't stop me!
Those who come with me will thoroughly
clean house inside the courthouse!
You're laughing?
So, we're gonna rescue you anyway.
You're a funny girl.
I don't feel like anything changed.
I don't need many!
Good luck, guys! Disperse!
Really, I can't believe it!
--Landed.
--Oof!
You'll soon notice how big the change is.
To think that the troublesome
gatekeepers are now on our side!
If you still wanna die after that,
That's a weird way of laughing.
This is the birth of new
Devil Fruit power-holders.
It's thanks to the bond between warriors!
you can die then.
I look forward to seeing those powers.
Now, my brothers!
The courthouse is very close now!
Get a handle on your own powers
at least, while you have a chance.
I've always been told that
I'm not good at laughing.
"Courthouse" "Tower of Law"
Ow, ow, ow...
Move forward!
Depending on the Chief's command,
You're cute when you laugh.
"Main Island Front Gate"
Huh?
Are you okay, Chopper?
"Courthouse" "Tower of Law"
What're you doing?! Hurry up and go in!
you may be able to try them
in a real battle immediately...
Also, the giant gatekeepers
at the main island front gate,
Yeah, I'm all right.
--What?
--You should laugh more.
Oimo and Kashii, went over to the pirates' side!
The pirates are inside
the courthouse, aren't they?!
...though it seems that Blueno couldn't
wait and joined the festivities before us.
But what just happened?
They're currently around the center of the
main island running towards the courthouse!
Hmm, I have some idea.
Yeah, but a frog is stationed at
the main door and we can't go in!
My name is Saul. Jaguar D. Saul.
Get outta our way!
"Courthouse"
A frog?!
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit...!
"D"?
Don't let even a single person inside!
Stand firm, Yokozuna!
Yeah. I don't know why, but everyone
in my family has it in their names.
The casualties of our guards are...
If this defense line gets broken,
thousands of guards will surge in here!
I should've come up here
like this from the start.
...over 2,000!
Zoro! So it really was you!
Bear it until the drawbridge comes down!
What's your name?
N-Not five...?
Robin.
We were okay because we
were on the outskirts of it,
Ribbit!
I see. To tell you the truth, Robin,
I'm being pursued right now.
And the captain, Straw Hat Luffy,
who beat over 1,000 all by himself,
but if we had been right in the middle
of your attack, we would've died!
"Courthouse Right Tower"
Huh? What happened to you guys?
suddenly disappeared, so we're
searching for him right now!
So if people find me, I'll be in trouble.
Even just one of us would do!
Get to the top floor!
Hiyaa!
I underestimated you.
I said I wouldn't tell!
Dash! Boar Stew Shoot!
We have to pull the lever there to bring
down the drawbridge, no matter what!
Don't!
This is probably unprecedented--
the worst situation we've had
"Three days after the giant drifted ashore"
I never thought that he'd
keep up with the speed of Shave.
Yeah!
I'm the first to arrive, without a doubt.
I'll fight with my guard up.
"Courthouse Left Tower"
in the history of Enies Lobby!
Now, I've kept Robin-chan waiting.
I'm coming to rescue...
Since he's a rubber man,
hitting him wouldn't work, right?
Moss!
This is yummy!
Moss-head! How come
you got here before me?!
Here's another one.
Moon Walk!
Blueno...
Big Sis Mozu!
Oh? What took you so long? Did you get lost?
What's he doing in a place like that?
Don't worry about me! Just go!
Bring down the bridge
Gum-Gum...
I appreciate the thought,
but you go ahead and eat it.
H-H-Hey, where'd you learn that phrase?
and let the Straw Hats go over
to the Tower of Law without fail!
Tempest Kick!
I'm not hungry, since I caught some
fish and ate them during the night.
Stop them! Whatever you do,
don't let them get through!
What's going on?
What the hell is happening
on this island right now?!
Get out of our way!
Ahh...! Sogeking!
Iron Body!
Okay.
Wheel!
Well, it'll be completed soon.
I'll keep working on building a raft.
Why did the swordsman and the
others from earlier head upstairs?!
What?! He's flying!
Amazing!
Where's he been all this time?
I don't owe you any answer!
Door-Door!
In any case, you sure have lots
of time on your hands, huh?
What?!
Forget that! You'd better hope
that Big Bro Franky is okay!
You've been with me all day
long for the past several days.
Is he... gonna land okay?
A-A door just opened on the ground!
"Upper Floors of the Courtroom"
Your friends and parents will get suspicious.
Door-Door.
After them! Bring down the pirates!
I don't have parents.
Whoa... They're gathering one after another.
Those damn guards! I didn't realize
that there were still a bunch inside!
Wh-What the heck?!
Were there small doors here?!
Well, I do have a mother,
Yoyoi! In any case...
but she set sail for work when
I was small and hasn't come back.
Crap! I got stuck! Dammit! These things...
There they are! Attack them!
So I don't even remember her face.
Sogeking!
Outta our way!
...to think that they've
marched into headquarters...
I like those archaeologists, but they
don't let me be part of the research,
You! What's this?! What'd you do?!
Is this a Devil Fruit power?!
My face door finally closed!
Hey! Don't throw them my way, Chopper!
Although they're our enemy, that's admirable!
Of course. An opened door is meant to close.
I'm a Door human with
Door-Door Devil Fruit powers.
so I'm being left out.
I'm surprised that you could
dodge the tempest kick.
Guilty! Guilty! Guilty! Guilty! Guilty...
Kids in town say that I'm creepy,
so I won't play with them.
A Door human?!
I can change all things that partition into doors!
Yeah. Well, it's a piece of cake.
A-A-A bunch of pirates have made it this far!
What the hell are you?
I resent that.
Oh, so you're a Devil Fruit power holder, huh?
Actually, where the hell am I?!
Revolving Door.
You jerk!
"Tower of Law"
You aren't scared?
What?! What?!
Wh-What's going on?! I feel dizzy!
I used to travel in the Grand Line,
He jumped!
so I saw many dreadful
Devil Fruit power holders.
Finger Pistol!
Wh-Wh-Which way is forward?! Stop!
Shave!
We're taking Franky and Nico Robin
to the Gates of Justice already?
I see... I envy you.
Iron Body! Smash!
Tempest Kick!
That's right! Just do as I said!
That looks convenient!
Gum-Gum... Bullet!
But the escort ship departing from
the Gates of Justice isn't ready!
I'm begging you, Robin!
Iron Body!
That's fine! We can wait on the other
side of the gates as long as we need!
You can go ahead and say
you wanna die or whatever,
In any case, we first have to
take away the pirates' goal!
but say those things... by our side!
You really do laugh in a weird way.
Tempest Kick!
After all, once we go
through the Gates of Justice,
Weird or not...
Hey, Cook!
Yeah, I saw it.
He's right, Robin-chan!
they can no longer do anything at all!
...you know...
Luffy's already fighting CP9.
...if you laugh, it'll make you happy.
Robin! Come back!
Also, gather all the members of CP9!
--What?!
--I-Is that true?!
Why?
Yes, sir!
Dammit! We got off to a late start!
"Why?" When you're having fun, you laugh.
But how do we get through
this complete encirclement?!
He's completely keeping up with my speed.
Which means if you laugh, it'll become fun.
Now... stand up, you two!
Gomorrah was hit with iron balls
and can no longer move!
He changed the course of the Tempest Kick!
I'll take you to hell immediately.
Although you're only a child,
you seem to be having a hard time.
Fire! Shoot all the pirates
down from the monster!
He's got unbelievable physical abilities!
After that, we can take our time
and drive the pirates into a corner.
So laugh. When you're
having a hard time, just laugh.
No good.
Hm?
It seems stupid to laugh
when you're having a hard time.
I'm no good like this.
Hey, Sogeking. Can you stand up?
That's not true.
There's only one path left!
Hm...?
When Aokiji defeated me, I thought...
Yeah, of course. This kind of wound is nothing.
Now, you try, too.
Yeah, we're gonna make
a dash for the courthouse!
"If I am to encounter more
strong guys like him in the future,
Giants! Giants!
That's the only choice we have.
The giants are on our side!
I won't be able to protect my friends...
unless I become stronger."
All right, let's go, guys!
--Giants! Giants! The giants are on our side!
--Every single thing those guys do is interesting.
Dereshi.
--Yeah!
--Wait!
Don't worry. I'm all right.
That's right! Do it like this!
All of you, don't get off!
I have friends I want by my side
even if they're not strong.
Those who have common sense
wouldn't meddle with this island.
Chopper?!
Just wait and see, Chimney.
So if I don't get stronger
than anyone, I'll lose all of them.
Hold on tight!
Whether they end up surviving this or dying,
That's good! That's good!
the entire world will be shocked
to learn of this incident...
Then what're you gonna do?
Something that no one has been able
to do in the past several hundred years.
I came up with a way to
fight with all my might...
This is Navy Headquarters.
Chief Spandine, please come in.
...so that I won't lose anyone...
After this battle,
They want to talk to you, Chief.
the name of that straw hat kid will
be known throughout the whole world!
Just ignore it. I'm sure they
just want a status report.
So that no one will go far away.
Gomorrah... Gomorrah says so!
What's he doing?
What's happening inside his body?!
We'll contact them when we see the shore.
Th-The monster is...
I don't care whether it's Ohara or Opera--
...still alive!
Fire! Kill it with trench mortars!
why do I have to come all
the way to the West Blue?
You'll now... no longer be
able to keep up with me.
Robin!
Shoot the monster!
Fight back! Back up Gomorrah!
Seriously...
What?
What a worthless mission...
He's here!
All my techniques will evolve one step further.
"The following day, four days
after the giant drifted ashore"
Luffy...
I've come to get you!
Second... Gear!
Go! Gomorrah!
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
Just leave the rest to us!
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We'll become No. 1
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
an era created by risking everything
We always try our best, let's go!
We'll become No. 1
If we want to achieve glory,
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
now is the time--don't be afraid
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
an era created by risking everything
We always try our best, let's go!
We can take off with unknown powers
If we want to achieve glory,
now is the time--don't be afraid
We don't fear, and we don't waver
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We can take off with unknown powers
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We don't fear, and we don't waver
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
Charge ahead
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
Let's start running towards tomorrow
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Charge ahead
Let's start running towards tomorrow
I have a report! The pirates who invaded
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
Why did you come to rescue me?!
I'm glad that I met you guys here.
Go back! I don't wanna see your faces again!
have pushed into the courthouse plaza!
Hmph! What kind of bluff is that?
Our casualties are already over 2,000!
You'll now... no longer be
able to keep up with me.
What the heck are you talking about?
Huh? What do you mean?
Like I said, I wanna die!
Can't be...! I can't see him at all!
This is the worst situation we've
had in the history of Enies Lobby!
Listen, Robin. We've already come this far.
You stupid pirates!
So you don't even remember your mom's face?
You won't be able to put on
a brave front for long!
Gum-Gum...!
What the hell is happening
on this island right now?!
No, but I wanna see her.
So, we're gonna rescue you anyway.
I have power!
On the next episode of One Piece!
Is your mom also an archaeologist?
"Everything Is to Protect My Friends!
Second Gear Activated!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
--Don't tell me...
--That's right!
"Give Us Your Answer, Robin!
The Straw Hats' Outcry!!"
"Almost to Luffy!
Gather at the Courthouse Plaza!"
The power that wiped out your hometown
Ohara exactly twenty years ago...
Yep. She's traveling in search of
the history no one knows about.
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
Wh-What's your mom's name?!
Buster Call!
Don't! Not that!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Fated Mother and Daughter!
The Mother's Name Is Olvia!"
"Robin's Past! The Girl
Who Was Called a Devil!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!