Wealth, fame, power...
Hey, is it true that a Navy ship came?
Stop it! Saul!
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
Be prepared!
What? A Navy ship did?
Has the Buster Call order been issued?
attained everything this world has to offer.
If you make an enemy of me,
I'll make you pay for it!
Yeah, I heard that it was
anchored here when day broke.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
No, we still have to be on standby.
Why would the Navy come...
Hurry!
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
...to such a remote island?
Run to the evacuation ship!
But no one has seen any marines on it.
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
What the heck?
So this is a Poneglyph, huh?
Not even a single person can be found.
It's like a ghost ship.
Yeah. I heard that even if we tried to
blow it up, it wouldn't even get a scratch.
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
That's ridiculous.
What's going on?!
It's Vice Admiral Saul!
--Professor!
--Professor Clover!
What a creepy stone... To think that
this stuff is scattered around the world...
Vice Admiral Saul, who deserted
with Olvia, is attacking us!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
Did something happen?
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Why is he here?!
I hope it's nothing to worry about,
but a Navy ship is anchored at the seashore!
W-We don't know!
and set out in search
of something to find
They might be here for an investigation.
We should be cautious, just in case!
This is the end of this island!
Everything will be burned down!
ONE PIECE!
Don't give up! Preserve the books!
We have to pass down the history!
Let the scholars know.
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
The raft is finished!
Drop them to the lake through the windows!
Compasses only cause delays
It'll be better than them being
burned up and gone! Hurry up!
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
Now!
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
Then... you're leaving already?
What's wrong? You've got
"I'm lonely" written all over your face.
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
Saul! Stop it now! You'll die!
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
Throw the books out of the library!
Come to think of it, I was thinking
of attaching a flag or something.
Save as many books as we can!
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
So I'll stay here a little longer.
Preserve as many sentences as we can!
When it comes to personal storms,
So that our predecessors' words from
the past several thousand years...
we will be able to make it through
...will reach the future!
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
Always!
To sea? So you wanna set out to sea, too?
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Robin! What're you doing?!
Yep.
and pretend it isn't there!
My mom has been busy with her
archaeological research all this time.
Run to the evacuation ship while you can!
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
You can no longer survive
if you remain on this island!
But when she comes back
to this island next time,
I'm going to ask her to take me with her to sea.
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
and set out in search
of something to find
So I studied hard and I was finally
able to become an archaeologist.
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
An archaeologist? When you're still so small?
We can't stop here
Around the world
Yep.
We are, We are on the cruise!
But... you don't even remember
your mom's face, right?
Start me up!
We are!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
Right... but she's still my mom.
Sogeking.
Hm?
I wanna see her.
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Shoot through that flag.
The drawbridge is coming down!
Looks like they pulled through. Good timing.
Roger.
--Say, Saul...
--Hm?
Huh?
Do you know that the world has a blank history
of 100 years that no one knows about?
This is my new weapon,
a huge slingshot... named Kabuto!
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
Mom!
Have a good look at its power!
Yeah. It's called the "Blank Century."
I-I'm trembling with anticipation!
Special Attack... Firebird Star!
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
I'm curious about it, but the Government
prohibits people from investigating, so...
Robin!
We're gonna rescue you for sure!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Brand New World
Yeah. I heard that my mom is traveling
around the world investigating it.
Lower that bridge already.
Start me up!
He looks evil.
But don't tell anyone about it,
since it's actually a crime.
Oh, no...!
What?!
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
C-Could it mean that she's traveling in
search of those stones called Poneglyphs?
Mission accomplished.
"The Tragedy of Ohara!
The Terror of Buster Call"
I hear you're a bad guy.
Are you insane?! Don't think
that you'll be able to survive
Are you still here?
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
Being stuck out here for all to see...
Are you really strong at all?!
after making the entire world your enemy!
So you know about Poneglyphs?
Bring it on!
Of course I do! But don't talk
about it in front of people, okay?!
Is that right?
Mind your own business!
Yes, they deserve the death penalty.
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
Since we seized the evidence,
we'll carry out your orders.
Seriously... just because I teamed
up with Luffy, I've come this far.
Not to mention, about your
mom traveling in search of... Ah!
Robin!
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
It cannot be helped. This is quite unfortunate;
We still haven't heard you say it!
What's wrong?
however, they violated the
world's laws. We cannot overlook it.
Robin... Do you know your mom's name?
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
"The Ways of Men!
Zoro's Techniques, Usopp's Dream"
Stop the blatant superficial talk,
Five Elder Stars.
Say you want to live!
Olvia.
we will be able to make it through
Wha...! Don't be rude! You're talking
to the leaders of the world!
It's Nico Olvia.
Always!
Robin...
Is this Ohara's Professor Clover,
the authority of archaeology?
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Robin!
Saul?!
I know your name well, since you've
contributed to the world's culture.
Robin is Olvia's daughter...!
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
To live...
Then... could this place be...
an island called Ohara?!
To think that someone of your
caliber would take the wrong path...
I thought it was something I dared not wish for.
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
The past belongs to all mankind.
--Yeah.
--Ahh! This is terrible! Oh, no!
You're still as weak as ever, Zoro!
No one ever let me wish for it.
No one has the right to stop one from
wanting to know our unspoken history!
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
So I drifted to Ohara?!
I promised her...
The sea is vast, so someday, definitely...
We can't stop here
I can't afford to die in a place like this!
Around the world
Professor...
This is no time to be sitting around talking!
Reading the Poneglyphs makes it
possible to revive the ancient weapon,
...you'll come across friends who'll protect you!
Start me up!
--Robin!
--What is it?
This might shock you, but listen to me carefully!
which puts the world in danger.
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
Even if your research has the best of intentions,
Navy battleships should be
headed to Ohara right now.
all it takes is for someone to
come along and use your research.
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Navy? Why?
If... it's really okay for me
to utter my wish for once...
You again? You sure have lots of free time.
No matter what happened in the past,
if humans created that history,
In order to eliminate the scholars on this island!
I'll untie you, so join my crew!
we should accept it all.
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
Eliminate them?
Say what?!
I...
If we don't succumb to fear
and learn all of history,
I'm looking for people to join my pirate crew.
Don't tell...
we can take countermeasures
no matter what happens.
Forget it! Me, stooping to a
criminal's level?! Screw that!
I want to live!
--That's a lie...
--Don't tell the Government you're a scholar!
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
That's an idealistic argument.
Is that so? Isn't that reasoning
just a convenient excuse for you?
Take me to the sea with you!
--That's a lie...!
--Got that?!
Brand New World
What's wrong with being a pirate?!
That's a lie!
It's true! I'd never lie to you!
Pirates are despicable! As if I'd wanna be one!
Start me up!
Out of what is still left to us,
Oh, come on! You're already
known as an evil bounty hunter!
Go to town now and see if anything
strange has been happening!
what interests us the most are the contents
of the Poneglyphs, along with their reason
It's possible your mom might be back, too!
People can say whatever they want,
but I ain't done anything I regret.
for existing in the first place.
"Say You Want to Live! We Are Your Friends!!"
What?!
Why did the ancients take the trouble
to inscribe the text on hard stones
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
I will live through this
and accomplish what I want!
in order to pass it down to the future?
Shoot Saul!
They inscribed history on unbreakable stones
Robin! Hurry up and run!
What was your mom's wish?!
and scattered them around the world.
You guys...! I love you guys, dammit!
Yeah?
But I've decided you're gonna join me!
Is it not because they thought that
their message would be eradicated
Live, Robin!
Quit deciding on your own!
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
I hear you use swords.
if they wrote it on paper or in books?
Let's go!
Yeah. But that stupid son took my stuff...
We're sailing the evacuation ship out!
In other words, it is the proof that
those who left the Poneglyphs
The drawbridge is coming down!
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
Wait! Someone's coming!
--I'll go get it back for you!
--What?!
Looks like they pulled through. Good timing.
So if you want your sword, join my crew!
clearly had an enemy.
That's...!
Ah! Isn't that the monster?!
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
You're really getting on my nerves!
Yeah, it is!
What're you trying to say, Professor Clover?
Robin!
Go away, monster!
Is he planning to bust into the base by himself?!
We're gonna rescue you for sure!
Hey! Don't be ridiculous!
If we assume that they were
defeated by some kind of enemy
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
The drawbridge is coming down! Go! Straw Hat!
Well... Wait!
After him! Don't let him escape!
and so ceased to exist,
Isn't she the daughter of Olvia,
a criminal, who was in the paper before?
Captain! There's someone
in the crucifixion yard!
this enemy must've remained
in history from that point on.
How dare those damn pirates?!
What?!
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
We're not gonna let it happen!
That's right! If we let her on the ship,
it might cause us trouble!
Get the trench mortar ready!
Stop the drawbridge! Break it if you have to!
Coincidentally, just when the
"Blank Century" ended 800 years ago,
Don't be ridiculous! She's only a child!
Hurry up and get her on the ship!
It's one traitor after the other...
we will be able to make it through
Yes, sir!
Evacuation ship! Don't let
that brat come on board!
Please escape, Zoro-san!
the World Government was founded.
Always!
What?
You'll be killed for doing that, you know!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Although she's a child, she's an archaeologist.
I can't stand to watch
the Navy like this anymore.
She's a target of our attack!
The drawbridge stopped coming down?!
If the current World Government was
the "enemy" of those that ceased to exist,
I want to be an honorable marine!
Chief Spandine! I-Is that true?!
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
How dare they get in our way?! Damn bastards!
See? If we let her come on board,
we'll be in danger!
Stop! I can't escape! I only got ten days until--
Who's doing this?!
one could think that the "Blank Century"
is an inconvenient history
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
Robin!
Hey, pirates!
You're going to be executed tomorrow!
that was hushed up by the World Government.
That must be CP9! How absurd!
What?!
What?! Kokoro-san?!
Helmeppo never once intended
to honor your agreement!
Chief! Vice Admiral Saul is coming this way!
By analyzing the ancient
documents and some Poneglyphs,
I heard everything!
What're you guys wasting time for?!
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
Really?! I guess we didn't have to
ask Olvia about his whereabouts.
We can't stop here
So Luffy-san got angry and punched him!
Wasting time? But the
bridge is only halfway down.
Around the world
we eventually noticed
the existence of a country.
Fire! Fire! Fire the cannons at him!
Jump with all your might towards the falls!
Start me up!
He did?
What the documents brought to light
was the existence of a grand kingdom.
The Navy is after Luffy-san now.
Ice Block!
The sound of the sea train?
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
Partisan!
I won't ask you to be a pirate.
Huh? What's the meaning of that smile?
Although it seems to have
boasted much power in the past,
But please, help Luffy-san!
Saul!
the information on this country
has obsessively been erased.
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
They probably sensed they'd be
defeated by the allied countries,
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
Luffy-san is the only one who can save you.
later to become the World Government,
Here we go!
Kuzan-san!
and so inscribed all the truth on
stones to pass it down to the future.
I knew it!
Kuzan...!
And I think you're also the only
one who can save Luffy-san now.
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Oh, my, my...
It doesn't look good
if a Buster Call is blocked by
a former marine, now does it?
Indeed, those stones are the Poneglyphs
that remain to this very day.
Nooo!
Brand New World
End of the line!
Start me up!
Kuzan!
I see. That's a bold hypothesis.
Can you take pride in this attack?
I wasn't gonna take you anyway!
It's true that the ancient weapon
would threaten the world.
You'll never be a pirate!
Pull back!
I will too!
This isn't right! You should know it, too!
However, isn't it actually that the
World Government is more threatened
Someday, I'm gonna gather a
crew every bit as good as yours,
"Fated Mother and Daughter!
The Mother's Name Is Olvia!"
This is some interesting
stuff you guys've pulled!
This is a warning!
They're wiping out Ohara
to make an example of it!
and I'm gonna find the
greatest treasure in the world,
Were you two and that straw hat kid
plannin' a coup or something?!
by people becoming aware of that
kingdom's existence and ideology?
and I'm gonna be King of
the Pirates! I'll show you!
If it is for the future of the world,
it can't be helped.
I've always fought alone.
In fact, these scholars are
violating the laws, right?
We still have to analyze what this threat is,
When I was a kid, I swore that I'd
gather a crew and become a pirate...
It's been a while, everyone.
Unlike arrogant bastards like you
who use soldiers as cronies!
Justice changes its form
depending on the position you're in.
but the name of this once-prosperous
kingdom that holds the key to everything is...
--Olvia...
--Olvia-san...!
So it was you who came on that Navy ship!
...like the pirate who protected me.
So I won't criticize your sense of justice.
Roronoa Zoro...
We thought you had been caught by the Navy...
Don't you dare underestimate me!
But if you're in our way, I can't let you be.
You're already one of my crew.
You may be strong, but before my
authority, you're as good as scum!
Robin...
Eliminate him!
Just like the pirate who protected me,
Aim!
I'll protect you, too!
I'm sorry that I came back bearing bad news.
I...
But what I just said is true.
Ah! The evacuation ship got blown up!
So the government has finally
set its sights on Ohara?
...can't afford to die here!
Professor!
Wh-Why...?
It was cannon fire! From one of the battleships!
Did you read the newspaper?
"Jump Towards the Falls! Luffy's Feelings!!"
The Poneglyph search team that set off
from Ohara six years ago was annihilated.
You're still as weak as ever, Zoro!
It was from Vice Admiral Sakazuki's ship!
Ohara has...
That idiot...!
Gum-Gum...
All of them except for me...
A total of 33 members...
If we're gonna do it, we'll do it thoroughly.
--You bastards!
--How dare you...!
...Rocket!
Fire!
Professor Clover!
If even a single scholar is hiding
on that ship by some chance,
I was also temporarily captured.
...come to know too much.
The government evaluated
my fellow scholars' belongings
the sacrifices made in this
operation will all be in vain.
--What are you--?!
--Luffy-san!
Straw Hat?!
Give the attack signal.
We need to eradicate
even the possibility of evil.
and figured out that we came from Ohara.
Then take me on your next voyage, Shanks!
Don't move!
Is this something "justice" would do?!
Can you still keep your head high?!
Don't let even a single person escape.
That doesn't work!
This is inexcusable! To think that this
island is now in danger because of us!
I wanna be a pirate too!
I don't intend to go as far as that idiot does!
As if you could ever be a pirate!
Stop it! It's no one's fault!
I told you I was strong!
Why not?!
We're gonna run, Robin!
He's abnormally strong!
Those who set out to sea and those
who stayed here--we're all one team!
Well then, using this golden transponder snail
W-Who the hell are you?!
Luffy. Just bein' a good swimmer
doesn't mean you'd make a good pirate.
Saul ran away!
entrusted to me by Admiral Sengoku...
He's taking a scholar with him!
It was you guys who experienced a terrible time.
I'm Monkey D. Luffy!
Professor!
I'm good at fighting too!
My punches are like pistols!
Robin...
The man who's gonna be King of the Pirates!
You fool! You shouldn't be here. Run!
We put you through a terrible ordeal.
Ice Time Capsule!
The King of the Pirates?!
Oh, really?
What's that mean?!
Do you even know what that means?!
...I'll initiate a Buster Call!
Professor...
He means you're too much of a kid, Luffy!
Ohara is a place where talented
scholars from all around the world
Take care of the rest.
King of the Pirates is King of the Pirates!
Seriously, you're as old as my own kid!
Saul! Are you okay?!
He did something!
Are there any other meanings?
I'm not a kid! I'm a grownup!
gather and continue to study history.
Robin, run away!
Now, now. Don't get so mad.
Here! Have some juice!
Hurry to the evacuation ship, Robin.
The Government has been
considering us a threat.
I was shocked, too! But Luffy-san
is serious! That's how he is!
No! I don't wanna be alone!
Wow! Thanks!
They must be thinking that they
finally found something on us.
Don't say such a foolish
thing at a time like this.
Run with all your might!
See, you are a kid! Ha!
He intends to become the King of the Pirates
They're not gonna pass up this opportunity.
You'll die if you stay on the island!
Sail out on my raft!
That wasn't fair, Shanks!
and obtain this world's
ultimate treasure... the One Piece!
Yes, but we were able to get
that information without delay!
Robin...
Don't laugh!
What about you, Saul?
In the end, everyone in Ohara who
claims to be a scholar will be eliminated!
Stupid cheapskate Shanks!
This is it for me. I got caught.
That's the Buster Call request!
All battleships, to your positions!
Prepare to open fire!
Here's your treasure!
So, everyone, get out of Ohara immediately!
Go!
Which is yours? I couldn't tell,
so I brought three of 'em.
No! There's no one on the sea!
Yeah... This time, we probably won't
be able to slip past their investigation
Hey...
Listen carefully, Robin!
All three are mine. I use the Three-Sword Style.
Look!
You're alone now, but you'll
meet friends someday for sure!
like we usually do...
The Tree of Knowledge is on fire!
Pardon us.
...if they are trying to kill us.
Hey, World Government! What're you doing?!
You'll take 'em, right?
If we fight together now, you'll be
a government-defying villain!
Taking our lives should be enough!
Then, hurry up and...
Oh... So these are "pirates."
Look pretty damn dumb.
But you know, Olvia...
Friends?
Don't look at me. It must've caught
fire from the explosions earlier.
Would you prefer that, or being
killed by the Navy like this?
Right. The sea is vast, so someday, definitely...
I can't run away leaving this
treasure of mankind behind.
What are you, the devil's son?!
You should know that.
Well, whatever. I'll be your pirate,
if I'm just gonna die here instead!
...you'll come across friends who'll protect you!
This isn't a joke!
We feel the same way, Olvia.
Do you realize how many important
documents there are in there?!
Welcome...
No one is born into this world to be alone!
You guys...
Hey! Don't move!
Ah... We don't need guns anymore.
We don't know what the Government is up to.
Hurray! So you'll join my crew?!
We're mountain bandits. But we
ain't here to tear up the place.
But if we run, the precious history
that exists here won't be protected.
Those from the Government, pull out.
Alright! Woo-hoo! This is great! Alright!
Sell us some booze. Ten barrels oughta do.
Run, Robin! Don't look back!
Okay! Now untie these stupid ropes already!
We'll try whatever we can,
just like we always have.
Hurry up and get the books!
When you're having a hard time,
laugh like this, just like I taught you!
More importantly...
I'm sorry. I just ran out of alcohol.
What... is he?
Put out the fire in the library!
He flung the bullets back!
...there must be something
weighing on your mind.
That's odd.
Watch out, Saul!
He's no ordinary human, that Straw Hat...
These pirates seem to be drinking
something... What is it, water?
But I can't see her.
Must've eaten one of
those rumored Devil Fruits!
Ice Time.
Make up your mind, Olvia! Are you
gonna come aboard the ship or not?
No, what they're drinking is the last of it.
A Devil Fruit?!
Hurry! Hurry!
Saul!
My apologies. Looks like we
drank the whole place dry.
If you have a lingering attachment
to your child, don't come with us.
Damn! These knots are tight!
Circulate water!
Go meet the friends
who're surely waiting for you
If this is about your husband's
unfinished business, we will...
Hey! Quit wastin' time!
No matter who they are, everyone
who opposes me gets executed!
Sorry!
Take the books out of the library!
No! I'll come with you!
somewhere at sea, Robin!
You can have this, if you'd like.
It hasn't been opened yet.
I'm a scholar from Ohara. I can't
abandon our predecessors' will!
If guns won't work, then chop them to death!
Live together with them.
I'm sorry, Robin.
I'll solve all the mysteries
and come back for sure!
Huh, that's weird! It got tighter instead!
There's an eight-million-Berry
bounty on my head, you know.
Give me a damn sword!
One bottle ain't even enough for
a bedtime drink! Don't insult me!
Bring that woman with us.
Luffy-san!
Come.
Mommy... Where's Mommy?
Where did Mommy go?
There's a piece of information
that only she knows.
Now the floor's all wet.
This is it!
Your mom set out to sea for work.
You'll stay here with us for a while.
This is also the history that humans chose.
It'll cause a problem if she dies here.
Sorry about that, Makino-san.
Do you have a rag?
Roronoa Zoro!
You're noisy! Be quiet or I'll hit you!
How thoughtless humans are...
Oh, I'll do that!
So cool!
Mommy.
Hey, stop it. She's only two.
I'm sorry, Robin.
Move and you're dead.
Our daughter is two, too.
I don't care whether she's your
big sister's child or whatever--
Too scary!
Robin...! Please... make sure you escape.
I couldn't even give you...
Seems you like to clean. Then maybe
you'll find this more fulfilling.
how dare you take in such a burden?!
Don't die, no matter what!
I'll be a pirate. I promise you that.
...any parting words as a mother.
Not worth our time if they're
out of booze. Let's go!
Wow...
Your nose!
The Tree of Knowledge... is coming down!
Who's there?! Don't move!
I'm officially a criminal,
now that I've fought the Navy.
But I'll tell you this right now.
I'm only going to fulfill my ambition!
Robin! Hurry!
U-Um... I... Um...
Later, wimps!
Get out of here now!
Ambition?
To be the world's greatest swordsman!
I'm sorry!
Absolute justice can
sometimes drive people mad.
--Robin-chan!
--Robin!
If I wind up having to give that up,
When you wanna read books, just let me know.
I've decided to let you escape from this island.
you'd better accept responsibility
and apologize to me!
But I don't have money, so...
Are you all right, Captain? Are you hurt?!
What on earth will sprout
from the seed Saul protected?
Oh, I'm fine. No problem at all.
You don't have to pay.
You can read them all for free.
The world's greatest swordsman?
That sounds great!
Are you... my mom?
Who you bear a grudge against is up to you,
The King of the Pirates would
need no less than that on his crew!
--Free?
--Yeah, since this is the best library in the world.
but for now, just be happy you're alive.
He got you good, boss!
You sure talk big.
Talk about lame!
--The best one in the world?
--That's right.
Live as quietly as possible.
At this point, whether it's
as a criminal or whatever else,
Olvia! Are you gonna come
aboard the ship or not?
By the way, you're Olvia's daughter, right?
I drew lines on the sea with ice.
I will spread my name throughout the world!
Why are you laughing?!
Mommy!
If you just go straight on that
small boat, you'll reach land.
Do you like books?
--I'll hold her, so go already!
--Mommy! Don't go! Mommy!
That was so uncool!
Why didn't you fight them?!
What're you standing around for?!
Slaughter them this instant!
Yeah.
And remember this.
No matter how many there are
or how strong they seem,
She looks just like you did
when you were a child.
Mommy! Mommy!
Duck, Zoro!
you're not men--or pirates--if you
laugh after something like that!
And like you were at that age,
she's a rare genius, too.
I'm sorry, Robin.
I'm not your ally.
Gum-Gum Whip!
I can never call myself your mother again.
I'm your enemy. I'll be the first to
come after you if you cause trouble.
So long as I know she's okay...
I can understand how you feel,
but he only spilled some booze on me.
I can't be allowed... to be your
mother after all these years.
I've stepped into this line of work.
So I have to give up my attachment to her,
Y-You did it! Incredible!
My mom is on the island!
It's nothing worth getting mad over.
No one will survive.
What the hell are you?
since I can't make her a "criminal's daughter."
Whatever!
If that pain makes you want to die,
you're free to do that as well.
I ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Professor Clover! This time, a ship flying
the World Government's flag has come!
Gum-Gum Fruit?
A rubber person!
This is the best library in the world.
So he does have Devil Fruit powers!
A Government ship has come
all the way to the West Blue...
--Monster!
Do you like books?
Captain! We don't stand a chance against them!
Eating out of frustration, Luffy?
Her mom abandoned her!
Shut up!
Today is Robin's birthday!
It indeed seems quite serious.
These guys are crazy!
Robin! Those are my daughter's clothes!
We can't even handle Zoro by himself!
Happy birthday, Robin!
Wait, what're you eating?!
I'm sorry, Aunt Roji! I wanted
to try them on just once!
Be proud, Robin! Ohara is honorable!
Everyone, listen.
That box! Did you eat what was in that box?!
You eat a lot for someone who lives here free.
This is a direct order!
You guys and I are neither fellow
scholars nor acquaintances.
Everyone who spouted weakness just now
We cannot give up the future
you young ones will live in!
Y-Yeah...
must now shoot themselves in the head!
Spit it out! Right now! Every last bite!
I have no need for weakling soldiers!
Keep that in mind... no matter what happens!
W-What're you doing, Shanks?!
So laugh. When you're
having a hard time, just laugh.
Wait, Olvia! What're you going to do?!
These troops are mental!
Are you...
Hey, let the headquarters know
that we arrived at our destination.
It seems stupid to laugh
when you're having a hard time.
Luffy-san!
That's not true.
...my mom?!
Now, go, go, go! Keep on moving!
Crush this navy!
Geez... What a pain.
What... was that?
What you ate was the Gum-Gum Fruit!
Hmm? What? You have a kid?
In any case, this work'd
better get me a promotion.
The Gum-Gum Fruit is known as a Devil Fruit!
Hey, go get all the scholars and restrain them.
Eating it turns your body to rubber,
No.
and makes you lose the ability
to swim for the rest of your life!
Rankless, low-status bums have
no right whatsoever to defy me!
Yes, sir!
Olvia-san...
--What's going on?!
--A woman with a gun is running around!
Eh?! No way!
I'm sorry...
I am Navy Captain "Axe-Hand" Morgan!
You dumbass!
...but I think you're confusing
me with someone else.
I'm Luffy! Nice to meetcha!
Forgive me, Robin! I don't wanna
make you a "criminal's daughter"!
Die!
Olvia...
What a weird brat.
Hey, let's go!
T-The captain!
For Heaven's sake! I'm sorry, Robin!
R-Runt...
What's the idea, boy? People were
drinkin' and havin' a nice time.
Vice Admiral Kuzan!
Die!
Hm? What is it?
No thanks!
Dammit! Apologize! How dare you
make fun of Shanks and his crew?!
We've been notified that CP9's
Chief Spandine has arrived in Ohara.
C-Captain Morgan is...
I'm Robin!
Did I say something to offend you?
What? Is that something so important
that you had to wake me up to tell me?!
...being trounced completely...
I've grown, but don't you remember me?!
You did! Now apologize!
Go meet the friends
who're surely waiting for you
And you call yourself a navy?!
You've destroyed Coby's dream!
Mayor!
I-I'm sorry!
I've been waiting for you to return all this time!
somewhere at sea, Robin!
Are you...
Hold it, Straw Hat! Check this out!
You see the looks on those pirates' faces?!
...really not...
He got covered in booze, but didn't
say a word! Talk about pathetic!
...my mom?
I said hold it! Are you stupid?!
I wanted you...
Pay attention! I have a hostage here!
Pirates are just a bunch of wimps.
They're nothing but talk.
...to hold my hand...
Helmeppo-sama!
Hey.
Stop it!
...and walk with me someday...
If you value this guy's life, don't move!
One move and I'll shoot!
So I studied hard and was able
to become an archaeologist!
Stop making fun of Shanks and
the others! They are not wimps!
What's the matter, Robin?
Did my mom come here?
Stop, Luffy!
I can read Poneglyphs, too!
What're you saying? There's no way
that your mother is in Ohara, right?
Stop making fun of Shanks and
the others! You stupid bandits!
That brat can?!
Survivors?
Stop it, Robin!
There's no possibility of that.
So...
I have to give up my attachment to her,
Luffy-san! I don't want to get in
your way! Even if it means dying!
...please let me stay... with you!
--Hey!
--Hm?
You oughta watch your mouth, boy.
Take a look at this lake.
since I can't make her a "criminal's daughter."
Mom!
No one who's ever made me
mad has lived to tell the tale.
Th-This is...
What's this about all of a sudden?
Yeah, I know!
Robin...!
Y-Yeah...
Give it up, stupid son!
Coby really is ready to die!
Please...
Oh, that's right! There's trouble!
Wait!
Let the boy go! Please!
...don't leave me...
I heard that Navy battleships
are coming to this island
There are enough books
to fill the lake completely.
Don't move! I told you not to move! I-I'll shoot!
...alone anymore!
in order to capture all
the scholars on this island.
Was this by chance?!
I don't know what Luffy has done,
nor do I intend to fight with you!
Is there a disturbance or
something happening in town?
Yeah, this is the brat!
There's no doubt about it!
Behind you!
Gum-Gum...
If you're not offended, I'll even pay you!
What?
I am Navy Captain "Axe-Hand" Morgan!
It's not a battleship.
Where'd you find her?! Did you capture her?
Just, please! Spare the boy's life!
No, sir! Keeping in mind to
look out for "a suspicious girl,"
We heard that a Government
ship just came to this island.
Mayor!
we found a girl on a passenger
ship that was leaving an island
Leave it to senior citizens
to know how the world works.
Dad! Kill him, quick!
It'll probably be a more
rigorous investigation than ever.
...Pistol!
far northeast of Ohara,
But no, it's too late for him now.
but we lost her right after that.
Listen, Robin. Even if the
Government people come,
After all, he's made me angry...
Nice!
She's got the devil's luck.
don't tell them you're an
archaeologist no matter what.
What?! What the hell is this attack?!
I definitely saw a brat escaping
from burning Ohara on a small boat!
You're the bad guys! You mountain apes!
I'm exercising a Buster Call.
Since you're small, no one will think
that you're a scholar. Got that?
You're a lost cause, kid. You can
regret all this in the next life!
Commence concerted fire!
We're targeting everything on Ohara,
the island of archaeology!
Zoro.
I wanted to go after her, but the helm
suddenly got stuck as if it was frozen!
--Luffy!
--Please! Let him go!
My pleasure, Captain.
Out of our way!
The research by the Ohara scholars
has reached a level we never imagined.
I was wondering why the bar was empty...
Stop what you're doing!
Get outside with your hands in the air!
I bet Mr. Saul must've let her
escape right before he died!
Looks like it's those
mountain bandits from before.
You're being quite violent!
Knowledge can be transferred.
Don't let it out of that island.
To think that she can decipher Poneglyphs...
Captain!
This Ohara lab is suspected of a
serious crime--deciphering Poneglyphs!
Although she's still small, she's dangerous.
Annihilate the devils living in Ohara!
In the name of justice!
It requires a thorough search,
so all of you, go outside immediately!
Shanks!
This operation will go down
the drain unless we capture her
as soon as possible--I don't care how!
Treat this place with care.
The value of everything in here
is beyond your imagination.
Dammit! What's going on?!
We haven't gotten off of the island yet!
Are they trying to kill us?!
We don't have to listen to what you say!
79 million Berries?!
Take them outside!
Such a high bounty for an eight-year-old child?!
Yes, sir!
The Tree of Knowledge is directly
being hit by cannonballs, too!
To all the townspeople!
They said that she's a
survivor of those Ohara devils
We now suspect that this island's scholars
are devils who wish to destroy the world!
There's no mistaking that this
is Headquarters' military power.
The drawbridge stopped coming down?!
How dare they get in our way?! Damn bastards!
who planned the world's annihilation.
The government was probably going
to do this from the start. How foolish.
Ohara?
Who's doing this?!
What?! Why?!
I don't know how, but they said
that she sank six Navy battleships.
So you pirates are still here, huh?
Chief. That brat said that she's an archaeologist.
They're world-class scholars
and the pride of this island!
Do not worry, Robin-kun.
Yeah, she did say that.
I don't know if it's true or not,
Have you been scrubbing the
village clean this whole time?
So that's why her bounty is so high.
I'm just trembling with anticipation!
Consequently, we'll conduct a
large-scale search of the entire island!
Luffy!
I heard that the Government and
Navy Headquarters are going after her.
but when we don't know,
eliminating them solves the problem.
I thought your punches
were as strong as pistols?
We will... rescue you for sure!
During that time, those who have
nothing to do with archaeology
Remember her face well so that
you don't let her leave the island.
S-Shut up!
She seemed to have inherited the
ideology of the executed scholars.
I dunno why you're here, but you'd
best leave before you get hurt.
are expected to take an ID with them
There's a whole bunch of bad guys, right?
Retreat!
Then I'll take Olvia.
It'll be a problem if she's left at large.
and temporarily take refuge on the
evacuation ship at the west seashore!
"Scared" is written all over your face.
Any closer and he'll shoot your head off, wimp.
She is a child of the devil
who shouldn't be allowed to live!
An evacuation ship?!
Why are you going that far?
Forget her! No time for that now!
Just leave her here!
M-Me, scared?! I'm perfectly okay
with lots of bad guys or whatever!
If it's the scholars' problem,
we have nothing to do with it.
If we stay here, we'll get killed, too!
Thank you for always helping me.
He said no closer!
Don't make me blow your head off!
Because I'm Captain Usopp,
brave warrior of the sea!
So there should be no need
for us to leave the island.
My life is the most important thing!
Sure. Thank you for letting me work.
It's our duty to pass that message to you.
All, retreat! Go back to the ship!
By the way, before lunch, you have guests.
No matter what happens later
to those who ignore our advice,
Dammit! Dammit! This isn't a show!
What?!
Put your life on the line.
it's none of our concern.
Don't let her get away!
These are Klahadore's
pirates we're dealing with!
Huh?!
Now, give me the money!
I reported her to you, right?!
Of course I'm scared! What's wrong with that?!
Now that you've drawn your pistol,
put your life on the line.
Do something about the fire in the library!
I don't want your sympathy!
You guys can leave! Leave!
She works very hard, although she's still small.
Protect the Tree of Knowledge!
What the hell're you talkin' about?
--Leave town!
--Evacuate to the west seashore!
I'm saying those aren't for threatening people.
We ain't laughing! We're helping
'cause we think you're honorable!
The World Government is up to something!
Oh? You're still up?
We have to get up early tomorrow
morning to go purchase stock.
Go to sleep now.
Ahhh! I got shot!
As if we'd risk our lives because of sympathy!
Okay.
She's a good kid, but if we're
with her, we'll be in danger, too.
Th-This is it for me! I'm a goner, dammit!
Tell the top... that I want my son
to take over the position of chief!
Besides, look at this bounty amount!
Oh... You guys...!
Honey! She isn't in her room!
N-Now you've done it!
Chief, please take a close look.
These bastards fight dirty!
Dammit! That little brat picked up on it!
Usopp!
The bullet just went through
the sleeve of your jacket.
--Dirty?
--Cut the crap.
I wanted to do this...
Oh, I see.
What, do you think you're
dealing with saints or something?
D-Dammit...
...all this time!
You're looking at pirates!
I won't miss next time.
I... can't... move...
Shut up! You got nothin' to
do with this in the first place!
I'm sorry, but I don't have any food.
Well, well... To think that a heinous
criminal who splendidly escaped
Robin!
Listen, bandits.
Though, even if you did catch up with Jango,
Whether I'm splattered with
alcohol or food or even spit on,
the Navy's prison is coincidentally
visiting this island... Nico Olvia.
Mom!
you'd be no match for him anyway.
I know about you, Nico Robin!
You kept denying your connection to
the Ohara scholars, and yet, here you are.
most of the time I'd just
laugh and forget about it.
This way is probably safest for you!
It's my fault... Robin...
But...!
I'm a wanted man, too.
Even if I am no match...
No matter what the reason,
It seems as if you're declaring
that this is your hometown...
Is it true that you can read Poneglyphs?
anyone who hurts my friends has to pay!
If you do chores, I'll feed you.
Even if I am no match for him...
I will protect them!
Shanks...
If I had properly kept an eye on you...
That the scholars here are committing
the same crime that you guys were.
--Captain!
--Contact Navy Headquarters!
Has to pay, huh?!
Where's Robin?! Hand her over, dammit!
I'm sorry. I wanted to be able
to read them at any cost, so--
I'm captain of the Usopp Pirates...
Lousy pirates! Kill 'em, men!
My being here alone isn't proof of those things.
...and a brave warrior of the sea!
I'm really surprised to know that you've
become able to do things like that.
That darn jinx!
I'm sure you have all sorts of
excuses ready. You're a smart woman.
I'll handle this. Should be easy enough.
I won't let you lay a finger on the village!
You must've tried hard and studied a lot.
Your sin is being alive!
But it doesn't matter anymore.
It's not something anyone can do.
That's amazing, Robin!
What?! Nico Robin is in this town?!
Your connection to Ohara
doesn't need to be proved.
Find her! Hand her over to the Government!
--What's with him?
--He's yellin' somethin'!
If we dig through every nook and corner,
Check it out, he's cryin'!
Don't get cocky, bandit.
evidence of your research on
Poneglyphs will turn up in no time.
If you wanna fight us, then go
drag a warship here or somethin'.
I found one...! A Poneglyph...!
Fortunately, the officials from earlier
are the only ones who know about it.
The Government thinks that
the probability of this is 100%.
Don't come inside! I've got nothing to sell you!
So strong!
This is no time to be sitting around here.
Being able to capture you guys,
who were on the run for six long years,
H-Hold on! The kid attacked us!
Olvia! Take Robin and run!
I'm sixteen. I'll do anything.
Please let me be part of your organization.
If you can somehow sneak
Robin onto the evacuation ship,
You are a wanted man.
just gave the Government a small push.
What's so funny?!
You betrayed me, Robin!
you can leave the island!
Damn it!
There are plenty of Poneglyph
researchers around the world.
A smokescreen!
Luffy!
Nico Robin. I want you to help me.
Me and Usopp are gonna chase
that hypno-freak! That a problem?!
Robin! There you are! I looked all over for you!
Each time we captured one, we always
searched for their connection to Ohara.
Luffy!
Nope! Hurry!
Saul!
I heard that you can read Poneglyphs.
Do you know why that is?
So you were able to see Olvia!
I made a clean getaway!
Saul! What are you doing on this island?!
They'll never expect a mountain
bandit to escape onto the sea!
Don't tell me... In order to
use Ohara as a warning...?!
Looks like you're one step too late, Haramaki!
Exactly! If Ohara, the holy land
of archaeology, is crushed,
By some twist of fate, I got shipwrecked
and saved by Robin on the beach.
Dammit! Let me go,
you stupid ape! I hope you die!
If... you exercise a Buster Call
right here, right now,
I wouldn't say so!
it'll send shockwaves throughout academia.
You wish! You're the one who's gonna die!
More importantly, the situation is terrible!
then together with Enies Lobby...
We can make the world realize
Yes! That branch was in the way!
After all, you've made me mad!
You have to leave the island immediately!
what happens to those who
research the "Blank Century."
Please take care of Robin!
So long!
What?!
Please let my daughter escape
from the island at any cost!
Usopp-san...
...you guys, too, will disappear.
Then the battleships from Headquarters
under standby order are...
Special Attack: Exploding Star!
What?! No! What about you, Mom?!
Aren't you gonna come with me?!
Dammit! Dammit!
D-Don't be ridiculous!
Those guys are scum, but I couldn't
even hit them once! Dammit!
Whoa... Just how much do you know?
There's no way we'd be eliminated
by our own people's attack!
Olvia... What are you gonna...
What're you saying?!
That's right.
There's still something
that I have to do here, so...
So you are taking to the ocean, Usopp-san?
They're used to ensure that not
even a single criminal escapes.
Twenty years ago,
everything was taken away from me
Mom! I don't wanna be separated!
I was finally able to meet you!
Sorry! I got no use for you anymore!
Yeah. I've decided to get going
before I start to change my mind.
But as a matter of form,
we need to verify the crime.
and many people's lives were ruined.
I'll stay here, too!
Robin...
After all, we're not pirates.
It was caused by a single attack--Buster Call.
You're an Ohara scholar,
so you should know this very well.
Don't stop me, now.
So I came all the way here to conduct
a compulsory investigation on the island
I won't. I could just tell somehow.
History is the treasure of mankind.
That attack is now...
That's kind of sad, too!
It'll certainly light up the future
you young ones will live in.
...targeted on the friends I was finally
able to find, whom I can be myself with.
and to send off those who have
nothing to do with the matter.
W-What the hell?!
The next time I come to this village,
But the history we received
from the past will disappear
The more I wish to be with you,
Yeah, I came all this way.
I'll tell you adventure stories that
seem even more lie-like than lies!
unless we pass it on to the next era.
Take her down.
the more my fate will show its fangs to you!
--Put out the fire!
--Protect the books!
Okay! I look forward to it!
Help...!
No matter how far I go on the sea,
Revealing the history isn't
what Ohara was trying to do.
You guys take care, too!
Let's meet again sometime!
I have a huge enemy that I can't shake off...
We just wanted to accept the voices
of the past and protect them.
--How come?
--Huh? How come?
...because the world and
its darkness are my enemy!
Our research will end now,
but even if Ohara is obliterated...
Man, you're antisocial...
Hey, stop it! The books
here are a world treasure!
The incident with Aokiji, as well as this time...
I'm gonna be a pirate too, so we'll
meet on the high seas eventually!
There's still someone here? Take him outside!
--Come!
--Dammit, you bastards!
...we cannot give up the future
you young ones will live in!
I've already dragged you
into my troubles twice!
What're you talkin' about? Get on already.
There's gotta be a hidden room!
Make sure we find it!
Shanks!
If this continues forever, even though
you guys're good-natured...
--Eh?!
--We're friends now, aren't we?
I don't understand!
You will understand someday.
...you'll eventually feel that I'm a burden!
This is terrible...
I'm sure you'll betray me
one day and abandon me!
Get lost!
The battleships are already within sight!
Now, go, Saul!
That's what I'm most afraid of!
I...
That's why I didn't want
you to come to rescue me!
Is this all of them?!
I get to be captain, right?!
Are you sure about this?
Now, gather all the scholars here!
If I'm going to die someday anyway,
Don't be dumb! I'm the captain!
Yes.
I want to die right here, right now!
No! I'll stay here, too! Mom!
Look. The scholars have been captured.
What on earth did they do?
Mom!
They said that the goal of the scholars'
research is to destroy the world!
I was happy to hear you call me that.
Robin...
That can't be right.
Robin-chan...
Where's the evacuation ship?!
I'm in your debt, Luffy...
Makino-san told me everything.
Thank you!
It's at the west seashore! Hurry!
Robin...
From now on, for you and me both...
Hurry up and go! Hurry to the west seashore!
Now it makes sense.
Hey, pirates! What're you
guys wasting time for?!
You fought for us.
Live, Robin!
Robin... It seems that
there's an evacuation ship.
I see! That indeed is a sound argument!
We can no longer tell what
the Government will do.
Wasting time? But the
bridge is only halfway down.
Hey, don't cry! You're a man!
That's true. No one is stupid enough
to think that having you isn't a burden.
You hurry up and go there, too.
Halfway is good enough!
But... Shanks...!
No! Even if I get on that ship,
there won't be nice people!
We'll be there in four seconds.
Your arm!
I'll stay here with you guys!
Jump with all your might towards the falls!
Look at that symbol, you damn pirates!
--Robin...
--Just like you guys, I'm a--
It's only an arm. It's no big deal.
Just go already!
Is that Granny? What does she mean?
I'm just glad you're alright...
What?! Vice Admiral! Vice Admiral Kuzan!
That logo indicates the unity
of over 170 member countries
I don't know. But she said
jump towards the falls.
Are you guys working hard?!
What?!
Thank you for taking the
trouble to come here, Chief!
spanning the four seas and the Grand Line!
On the island... Yes, there's no doubt about it!
Anyway, I didn't expect that a ferocious
animal would appear on this island.
The sound of the sea train?
So what's the matter?! Just spit it out!
This is the world!
Huh? What's the meaning of that smile?
It's the deserter, Vice Admiral Saul!
Do you now realize how completely
powerless you guys are to fight against it?!
Saul! Go back! Please!
No! I can't do that!
Do you realize how huge of an organization
this woman has been pursued by?!
I was nearly killed.
Robin! Be proud, Robin!
Olvia...!
Your mom is honorable! Ohara is honorable!
Olvia-san...!
Here we go!
You're leaving, then?
Yeah. It was a long stay, but now we part ways.
I knew it!
All right, listen carefully.
This woman is an escaped prisoner.
Someday, pass down this island's history, Robin!
I now understand well the
identity of Robin's enemy.
The group she belonged to
Bet you'll miss me, huh?
Ohara fought against the world!
Well, yeah, but I won't
ask you to take me anymore.
was recently eliminated for the crime
of deciphering the ancient texts.
Sogeking.
Nooo!
Hm?
However, we still don't know the ringleader.
Shoot through that flag.
I've decided to become
a pirate on my own now!
Well, if you guys are connected to this woman,
it'll make matters quite simple.
Stop it! Capturing them is enough!
Roger.
Huh?
"Straw Hat Theater"
I wasn't gonna take you anyway!
They're not even violent pirates! Are you
so weak that you can't suppress them?!
This is my new weapon,
a huge slingshot... named Kabuto!
You'll never be a pirate!
"Part 2"
Have a good look at its power!
How terrible of them to hurt a woman like that.
I will too!
We've caught history
exploration ships many times,
Special Attack... Firebird Star!
Someday, I'm gonna gather a
crew every bit as good as yours,
Robin, go to the evacuation ship. Hurry!
"A report on Luffy's eating habits
before Sanji joined the gang."
but I don't understand why they had to die.
and I'm gonna find the
greatest treasure in the world,
Robin...
and I'm gonna be King of
the Pirates! I'll show you!
Vice Admiral Saul! We found one survivor!
This is "On-Location Tsubaki," a crooked
reporter who'll help us on this report.
How dare you kill my fellow scholars?!
Robin...!
"His favorite words:
You're gonna surpass us, huh?
His favorite words are:
"I'm so happy that words fail me."
Oh, no...!
"His favorite words:
'I'm so happy that words fail me'"
Do you really want the weapon?
You've...
What pitiful people...
Mission accomplished.
In that case...
Err... This is On-Location Tsubaki.
You don't have your own will
and yet you cast judgment on us...
Luffy, you set sail all by yourself, right?
Hey! He's a Vice Admiral!
...I'll leave this hat with you.
...not doubting laws and saying it's
to prevent the revival of the weapon!
...grown so much!
Th-They've gone and done it!
Tell everyone how an idiot like you survived.
It's dear to me.
Do they understand what it
means to attack the flag?!
Olvia...
Take good care of it!
You're just frightened by the
history that you don't even know!
Sure!
I took lots of meat and water that I got
in the village with me when I set sail.
The pirates declared war
against the World Government!
Wh-What have they done?!
This is a top-secret mission.
But I ate them all right away.
Have they no respect for the library?!
Buster Call?
Are you insane?! Don't think
that you'll be able to survive
To think that they'd take
such drastic measures...!
I'm so dumbfounded that words fail me.
Five Vice Admirals command
ten battleships in a Buster Call.
Well, after that I was starving
and thirsty. It was really tough.
after making the entire world your enemy!
Whoa... They've made a big show.
Bring it on!
I want you to be one of them.
They are just scholars.
Why do we have to go that far?
But I was saved by eating mushrooms
and stuff that someone left in the boat.
--Click.
--Hello? Is this the Chief?!
Yeah, it's me.
Those scholars that we've captured, too!
Ten years later,
Hey, the mushrooms just grew
because of the ample humidity.
We've found it!
I sailed out and became a pirate.
They look like they just really
want to know the history to me!
There's a secret room in the basement,
But then, big fish would sometimes
jump out of the sea, trying to eat me.
and in there, we found a huge stone
that's probably a Poneglyph
Just like Shanks protected me,
I'll protect my friends!
If their research is so dangerous,
the Government should help them, too!
and research documents clearly
discussing the ancient texts!
So I beat them up and...
Robin!
All right, well done!
We're the ones who actually have to kill people!
Ate them?! You could've died.
Click.
We still haven't heard you say it!
Give me the proof that they're completely evil!
It sounds like you were living hand to mouth.
Well, scholars of Ohara!
But it was okay! I had confidence in myself!
Are you doubting the Government?
Don't fight! Just follow orders!
Your death sentence has now been decided!
H-Hey, hey... That's so
powerful that words fail me.
Say you want to live!
Nooo!
It's indeed regrettable...
Err... And then, that stupid
Zoro became a crew member.
...that the world's best archaeologists
lose their lives together today.
I'd like to ask you some questions.
Robin...
Just wait, Robin!
I guess I can't expect much from you, either.
This is an emergency! Vice Admiral
Saul took a criminal and deserted!
You both are idiots. How were
you able to make it this far?
"Straw Hat Theater"
Robin!
I set sail before he did,
so I was more experienced.
He knows everything about the operation.
See? What a letdown. That was all I had to do!
"Part 1"
To live...
I was used to sailing.
After them! Capture Saul and Olvia without fail!
The only thing I have left to do is
report this to the Five Elder Stars.
You shouldn't be allowed
to live in this world, Robin!
Our captain is like this, so I had
to be the one who got it together.
Roger.
You can shoot them if needed!
Your existence itself is a huge crime, Robin!
Professor! Are they really gonna
kill all of you?! That's a lie, right?
Pursuers are coming! I'll deal with them!
Big fish would sometimes jump out of the sea,
trying to eat us. So I beat them up and...
That bastard...!
"Usodaba Gang's base of evil"
Why would they do that just because
you read the ancient texts...?!
You'll never be able to
go back to the Navy, Saul.
That detestable Chopper Man!
I thought it was something I dared not wish for.
I'm not gonna let him thwart my plans
to take over the world anymore!
I've been caught in the chains of
disappointment and can't move.
Idiot! You brat! The purpose of their
research is to revive a powerful weapon
That's fine. I can't stay in the
Navy having this sense of distrust.
"Evil Incarnate, Usodaba"
In other words, you could've
starved to death then,
This is Dr. Usodaba, evil incarnate!
No one ever let me wish for it.
which could've led to the
end of your adventures, huh?
He leads the evil Usodaba Gang
and schemes to take over the world!
and commit mass murder!
Even if they're obeying the law,
this operation is too tyrannical.
Yeah. But if we had died, that would mean
we weren't man enough to make it.
That's not true! They aren't
thinking about anything like that!
I want to die!
He's an evil scientist who produces evil
phantoms, monsters, robots--anything!
I'm just following my sense of justice.
Robin, stop it. It's pointless to discuss
the matter with an errand boy like him.
Right. The sea is vast, so someday, definitely...
Now, hurry to your hometown
to let people know.
H-Hey, hey... That's so manly that words fail me.
Those are some of his underlings behind him.
I'm not gonna thank you for this.
...you'll come across friends who'll protect you!
What'd you say?!
I'll lure him out to my base and
wait for him here, ready to strike.
Okay, then. Come on,
Nami the gangster woman.
Good luck.
Is it really the weapon itself that
the Government is afraid of?
Really, I was surprised by their lack
of planning or any sense of danger.
And then, I'll crush him with
my gang's full fighting power!
--Professor!
--Professor Clover!
It's connected, Chief.
Fire!
Okay.
Swoosh!
--This is good timing.
--Huh?!
That's why I managed the food
after we set sail together...
His weakness is...
They're aiming at me!
Let me speak to the Five Elder Stars,
the world's leaders, before I die.
Believe in Luffy.
That's right, his assistant, Namifia!
"Pretty Assistant, Namifia"
This is Namifia, a pretty assistant!
...while being careful about properly preserving
She efficiently manages
Chopper Man's missions.
If... it's really okay for me
to utter my wish for once...
We, the scholars at Ohara, have continued
our research for a long time,
cheese, bread, dried meat, etc. and water.
Saul!
Now, men, go!
They might've died if it wasn't for me.
and although the research isn't completed yet,
First, bring me a hostage!
Ah! It hit him!
I'm sorry!
we formed a hypothesis
about the "Blank Century."
So...
Dabada!
I...
Don't apologize! He's already
those evil people's accomplice!
...they owe me.
So I'd like to report it to them.
We brought one!
H-Hey, hey... That smile is so
scheming that words fail me.
--'Sup!
--Hey, you brought him?!
I'm sorry, Robin. That must've scared you.
I want to live!
What rubbish...
"Champion of Justice, Chopper Man"
This is Chopper Man, our hero
and champion of justice!
--Hey.
--Yes, sir.
Take me to the sea with you!
Now, we have Usopp the scaredy-cat
who was next to join the gang.
Robin, get out of here immediately.
He flies around using his Chopper
cape and fights for world peace!
Hold on a sec.
Listening to what I'm about to say is a crime.
The Straw Hats finally got a bigger ship
That must be it! Firing this close?
What if you had hurt Robin?!
by obtaining the Going Merry when
you left your village, didn't you,
His weapon is his cuteness!
Professor...
"Cute Spark!!"
even though you're all idiots?
With his killer "Cute Spark,"
he can make any enemy's heart melt.
Hey, it seems like the scholars
have been found guilty.
That's right. I want them to
appreciate me for that first.
Vice Admiral! Please stop! What're you doing?!
If that doesn't work, he uses "Chopper
Violence" to beat the crap out of them!
Is that true?!
It wasn't you who gave it to us.
I don't know what justice is in this situation,
so I'll just protect my friend!
Hey! Navy battleships are moving
toward here from the eastern sea!
He's right. It was Kaya.
That was because I was good
friends with Kaya, wasn't it?!
They're gonna do something!
Let's hurry to the evacuation ship!
Stop it! Saul!
I want tea.
If you wanna fight, do it later.
Did something change in your life?
Hey, what's the big deal, relaxing at my base?!
Be prepared!
Wh-What the...?!
If you make an enemy of me,
I'll make you pay for it!
Oh, yeah! Usopp is good at fishing,
so we ate quite a bit of fish.
Hm?! What's that big thing in the garden?!
It's a giant!
It's my secret weapon!
Stop checking it out, you jerk!
But the fish you catch,
like sauries and sardines, are small.
Where are you, Robin?!
You guys...! I love you guys, dammit!
Can I try riding on you?
You dummy! I like seasonal fish
better than the meat of sea monsters!
Sure, go ahead.
Escape from this island right away!
Hey! Why are you making
friends with him, Luffybomber?!
"Secret Weapon, Giant Robot,
Giant Luffybomber"
This is Giant Luffybomber, a giant
robot and their secret weapon.
We had a kitchen, so I
cooked for you guys, didn't I?
Let's go!
It's a giant robot that's fifty meters tall.
Usopp's got lots of seasonings for some reason.
When Usodaba comes on board,
it becomes your worst, strongest enemy.
To tell you the truth, Nami's homemade
food was quite good, but it wasn't free.
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
Special traits: It can speak.
So we never asked her to cook again.
Personality: It does its own thing!
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
I'm an expensive woman.
There are devils everywhere in the world.
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
And now, we finally have a damn filthy
man who always says "damn, damn."
We'll become No. 1
"Rice Ball Monster, Zorokiller"
This is the rice ball monster, Zorokiller!
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
To be honest, I wanna cook just
for Nami-san. My hobby is Nami-san!
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
When he demands rice balls,
if you don't have any,
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
he gets angry and says, "Make sure
you have some from now on!"
Since Sanji joined us,
an era created by risking everything
"Flower Monster, Robiflowern"
meals have become something
we really look forward to.
This is the flower monster,
Robiflowern. She's an evil woman
We always try our best, let's go!
who's been defeated by Chopper Man's
killer "Cute Spark" time after time.
If we want to achieve glory,
If we catch things like birds or fish,
he'll turn them into really yummy food!
"Naughty Monster, Sanjiropus"
This is the naughty monster, Sanjiropus.
now is the time--don't be afraid
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
He insists that he isn't naughty, but he's
always thinking about naughty stuff.
Since he's a pro, he considers
nutritional balance, too, so that's helpful!
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
He shows no mercy to guys.
"The Usodaba Gang's Evil Three"
--Mellorine! Mellorine! Love hurricane!
--I was finally able to focus
on my job as a navigator.
They are the Usodaba Gang's Evil Three.
We can take off with unknown powers
They have nothing to do
with this story, though...
That's the only redeeming trait
you have, so you can do your best.
Thus, the evil gang has been wiped out.
We don't fear, and we don't waver
What'd you say, you bastard?!
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
Well then, at any rate,
why don't I try telling everyone
Whoa! Amazing!
You're cool, Luffybomber!
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
how the food you eat
during your journey tastes?
Darn straight I am!
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
Chopper Man! There's trouble
in one of the eastern towns!
Okay! I'll head there in Luffybomber,
the giant robot I obtained the other day!
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
--It's not here!
--I sold it.
Charge ahead
--What?!
--Go! Go! Our Chopper Man!
Words fail me...
Let's start running towards tomorrow
What a useless reporter!
Fight for world peace!
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
Robin! We still haven't heard you say it!
Saul, please take care of Robin!
Robin... It must've been really hard.
D-Don't worry, Robin-kun.
Y-You've got us on your side.
When I was a kid, I swore that I'd
gather a crew and become a pirate...
Please let my daughter
escape from here at any cost!
But you're not alone anymore.
Say you want to live!
He says, while trembling in his boots.
...like the pirate who protected me.
What?! What about you, Mom?!
Aren't you gonna come with me?!
Just wait, Robin. You've got us.
Robin!
Robin...
So, just like he protected me
that time, I'll protect you, too!
I-I'm just trembling with anticipation!
--Robin...
--Robin-chan!
There's still something
that I have to do here, so...
So have faith in us... in Luffy!
Yeah? Well then, let's hurry up and take
care of these World Government guys!
Robin!
You're already one of us, Robin!
No! I don't wanna be separated!
I was finally able to meet you!
He'll respond to your feelings without fail.
I... I...
Then we'll rescue Robin-kun without fail!
I'm gonna rescue you without fail!
Mom!
On the next episode of One Piece!
Let's go!
"A Bond of Friendship Woven
by Tears! Nami's World Map"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Ways of Men!
Zoro's Techniques, Usopp's Dream"
"Say You Want to Live! We Are Your Friends!!"
"The Tragedy of Ohara!
The Terror of Buster Call"
"Jump Towards the Falls! Luffy's Feelings!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!