Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
The drawbridge is coming down!
Looks like they pulled through. Good timing.
I-I'm trembling with anticipation!
Robin!
We're gonna rescue you for sure!
Lower that bridge already.
He looks evil.
I hear you're a bad guy.
Are you still here?
Being stuck out here for all to see...
Are you really strong at all?!
Mind your own business!
Seriously... just because I teamed
up with Luffy, I've come this far.
"The Ways of Men!
Zoro's Techniques, Usopp's Dream"
You're still as weak as ever, Zoro!
I promised her...
I can't afford to die in a place like this!
You again? You sure have lots of free time.
I'll untie you, so join my crew!
Say what?!
I'm looking for people to join my pirate crew.
Forget it! Me, stooping to a
criminal's level?! Screw that!
What's wrong with being a pirate?!
Pirates are despicable! As if I'd wanna be one!
Oh, come on! You're already
known as an evil bounty hunter!
People can say whatever they want,
but I ain't done anything I regret.
I will live through this
and accomplish what I want!
Yeah?
But I've decided you're gonna join me!
Quit deciding on your own!
I hear you use swords.
Yeah. But that stupid son took my stuff...
--I'll go get it back for you!
--What?!
So if you want your sword, join my crew!
You're really getting on my nerves!
Is he planning to bust into the base by himself?!
After him! Don't let him escape!
Captain! There's someone
in the crucifixion yard!
What?!
It's one traitor after the other...
Please escape, Zoro-san!
You'll be killed for doing that, you know!
I can't stand to watch
the Navy like this anymore.
I want to be an honorable marine!
Stop! I can't escape! I only got ten days until--
You're going to be executed tomorrow!
What?!
Helmeppo never once intended
to honor your agreement!
So Luffy-san got angry and punched him!
He did?
The Navy is after Luffy-san now.
I won't ask you to be a pirate.
But please, help Luffy-san!
Luffy-san is the only one who can save you.
And I think you're also the only
one who can save Luffy-san now.
End of the line!
This is some interesting
stuff you guys've pulled!
Were you two and that straw hat kid
plannin' a coup or something?!
I've always fought alone.
Unlike arrogant bastards like you
who use soldiers as cronies!
Roronoa Zoro...
Don't you dare underestimate me!
You may be strong, but before my
authority, you're as good as scum!
Aim!
I...
...can't afford to die here!
You're still as weak as ever, Zoro!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Fire!
--What are you--?!
--Luffy-san!
Straw Hat?!
That doesn't work!
I told you I was strong!
W-Who the hell are you?!
I'm Monkey D. Luffy!
The man who's gonna be King of the Pirates!
The King of the Pirates?!
Do you even know what that means?!
King of the Pirates is King of the Pirates!
Are there any other meanings?
I was shocked, too! But Luffy-san
is serious! That's how he is!
He intends to become the King of the Pirates
and obtain this world's
ultimate treasure... the One Piece!
Here's your treasure!
Which is yours? I couldn't tell,
so I brought three of 'em.
All three are mine. I use the Three-Sword Style.
You'll take 'em, right?
If we fight together now, you'll be
a government-defying villain!
Would you prefer that, or being
killed by the Navy like this?
What are you, the devil's son?!
Well, whatever. I'll be your pirate,
if I'm just gonna die here instead!
Hurray! So you'll join my crew?!
Alright! Woo-hoo! This is great! Alright!
Okay! Now untie these stupid ropes already!
What... is he?
He flung the bullets back!
He's no ordinary human, that Straw Hat...
Must've eaten one of
those rumored Devil Fruits!
A Devil Fruit?!
Hurry! Hurry!
Damn! These knots are tight!
Hey! Quit wastin' time!
No matter who they are, everyone
who opposes me gets executed!
If guns won't work, then chop them to death!
Huh, that's weird! It got tighter instead!
Give me a damn sword!
Luffy-san!
Roronoa Zoro!
So cool!
Move and you're dead.
Too scary!
I'll be a pirate. I promise you that.
I'm officially a criminal,
now that I've fought the Navy.
But I'll tell you this right now.
I'm only going to fulfill my ambition!
Ambition?
To be the world's greatest swordsman!
If I wind up having to give that up,
you'd better accept responsibility
and apologize to me!
The world's greatest swordsman?
That sounds great!
The King of the Pirates would
need no less than that on his crew!
You sure talk big.
At this point, whether it's
as a criminal or whatever else,
I will spread my name throughout the world!
What're you standing around for?!
Slaughter them this instant!
Duck, Zoro!
Gum-Gum Whip!
Y-You did it! Incredible!
What the hell are you?
I ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Gum-Gum Fruit?
A rubber person!
So he does have Devil Fruit powers!
Captain! We don't stand a chance against them!
These guys are crazy!
We can't even handle Zoro by himself!
This is a direct order!
Everyone who spouted weakness just now
must now shoot themselves in the head!
I have no need for weakling soldiers!
These troops are mental!
Luffy-san!
Crush this navy!
Rankless, low-status bums have
no right whatsoever to defy me!
I am Navy Captain "Axe-Hand" Morgan!
I'm Luffy! Nice to meetcha!
Die!
T-The captain!
R-Runt...
Die!
No thanks!
C-Captain Morgan is...
...being trounced completely...
And you call yourself a navy?!
You've destroyed Coby's dream!
Hold it, Straw Hat! Check this out!
I said hold it! Are you stupid?!
Pay attention! I have a hostage here!
Helmeppo-sama!
Hey.
If you value this guy's life, don't move!
One move and I'll shoot!
Luffy-san! I don't want to get in
your way! Even if it means dying!
Yeah, I know!
Give it up, stupid son!
Coby really is ready to die!
Don't move! I told you not to move! I-I'll shoot!
Behind you!
Gum-Gum...
I am Navy Captain "Axe-Hand" Morgan!
Dad! Kill him, quick!
...Pistol!
Nice!
Zoro.
My pleasure, Captain.
The drawbridge stopped coming down?!
How dare they get in our way?! Damn bastards!
Who's doing this?!
Do not worry, Robin-kun.
I'm just trembling with anticipation!
We will... rescue you for sure!
There's a whole bunch of bad guys, right?
"Scared" is written all over your face.
M-Me, scared?! I'm perfectly okay
with lots of bad guys or whatever!
Because I'm Captain Usopp,
brave warrior of the sea!
Dammit! Dammit! This isn't a show!
These are Klahadore's
pirates we're dealing with!
Of course I'm scared! What's wrong with that?!
I don't want your sympathy!
You guys can leave! Leave!
We ain't laughing! We're helping
'cause we think you're honorable!
As if we'd risk our lives because of sympathy!
Oh... You guys...!
Usopp!
D-Dammit...
I... can't... move...
Though, even if you did catch up with Jango,
you'd be no match for him anyway.
This way is probably safest for you!
Even if I am no match...
Even if I am no match for him...
I will protect them!
I'm captain of the Usopp Pirates...
...and a brave warrior of the sea!
I won't let you lay a finger on the village!
--What's with him?
--He's yellin' somethin'!
Check it out, he's cryin'!
What's so funny?!
Luffy!
Me and Usopp are gonna chase
that hypno-freak! That a problem?!
Nope! Hurry!
Looks like you're one step too late, Haramaki!
I wouldn't say so!
Yes! That branch was in the way!
What?!
Usopp-san...
Special Attack: Exploding Star!
So you are taking to the ocean, Usopp-san?
Yeah. I've decided to get going
before I start to change my mind.
Don't stop me, now.
I won't. I could just tell somehow.
That's kind of sad, too!
The next time I come to this village,
I'll tell you adventure stories that
seem even more lie-like than lies!
Okay! I look forward to it!
You guys take care, too!
Let's meet again sometime!
--How come?
--Huh? How come?
Man, you're antisocial...
I'm gonna be a pirate too, so we'll
meet on the high seas eventually!
What're you talkin' about? Get on already.
--Eh?!
--We're friends now, aren't we?
I...
I get to be captain, right?!
Don't be dumb! I'm the captain!
Hey, pirates! What're you
guys wasting time for?!
Wasting time? But the
bridge is only halfway down.
Halfway is good enough!
We'll be there in four seconds.
Jump with all your might towards the falls!
Is that Granny? What does she mean?
I don't know. But she said
jump towards the falls.
The sound of the sea train?
Huh? What's the meaning of that smile?
Here we go!
I knew it!
Nooo!
"Straw Hat Theater"
"Part 2"
"A report on Luffy's eating habits
before Sanji joined the gang."
This is "On-Location Tsubaki," a crooked
reporter who'll help us on this report.
"His favorite words:
His favorite words are:
"I'm so happy that words fail me."
"His favorite words:
'I'm so happy that words fail me'"
Err... This is On-Location Tsubaki.
Luffy, you set sail all by yourself, right?
Tell everyone how an idiot like you survived.
Sure!
I took lots of meat and water that I got
in the village with me when I set sail.
But I ate them all right away.
I'm so dumbfounded that words fail me.
Well, after that I was starving
and thirsty. It was really tough.
But I was saved by eating mushrooms
and stuff that someone left in the boat.
Hey, the mushrooms just grew
because of the ample humidity.
But then, big fish would sometimes
jump out of the sea, trying to eat me.
So I beat them up and...
Ate them?! You could've died.
It sounds like you were living hand to mouth.
But it was okay! I had confidence in myself!
H-Hey, hey... That's so
powerful that words fail me.
Err... And then, that stupid
Zoro became a crew member.
I guess I can't expect much from you, either.
You both are idiots. How were
you able to make it this far?
I set sail before he did,
so I was more experienced.
I was used to sailing.
Our captain is like this, so I had
to be the one who got it together.
Big fish would sometimes jump out of the sea,
trying to eat us. So I beat them up and...
I've been caught in the chains of
disappointment and can't move.
In other words, you could've
starved to death then,
which could've led to the
end of your adventures, huh?
Yeah. But if we had died, that would mean
we weren't man enough to make it.
H-Hey, hey... That's so manly that words fail me.
Okay, then. Come on,
Nami the gangster woman.
Really, I was surprised by their lack
of planning or any sense of danger.
That's why I managed the food
after we set sail together...
...while being careful about properly preserving
cheese, bread, dried meat, etc. and water.
They might've died if it wasn't for me.
So...
...they owe me.
H-Hey, hey... That smile is so
scheming that words fail me.
Now, we have Usopp the scaredy-cat
who was next to join the gang.
The Straw Hats finally got a bigger ship
by obtaining the Going Merry when
you left your village, didn't you,
even though you're all idiots?
That's right. I want them to
appreciate me for that first.
It wasn't you who gave it to us.
He's right. It was Kaya.
That was because I was good
friends with Kaya, wasn't it?!
If you wanna fight, do it later.
Did something change in your life?
Oh, yeah! Usopp is good at fishing,
so we ate quite a bit of fish.
But the fish you catch,
like sauries and sardines, are small.
You dummy! I like seasonal fish
better than the meat of sea monsters!
We had a kitchen, so I
cooked for you guys, didn't I?
Usopp's got lots of seasonings for some reason.
To tell you the truth, Nami's homemade
food was quite good, but it wasn't free.
So we never asked her to cook again.
I'm an expensive woman.
There are devils everywhere in the world.
And now, we finally have a damn filthy
man who always says "damn, damn."
To be honest, I wanna cook just
for Nami-san. My hobby is Nami-san!
Since Sanji joined us,
meals have become something
we really look forward to.
If we catch things like birds or fish,
he'll turn them into really yummy food!
Since he's a pro, he considers
nutritional balance, too, so that's helpful!
--Mellorine! Mellorine! Love hurricane!
--I was finally able to focus
on my job as a navigator.
That's the only redeeming trait
you have, so you can do your best.
What'd you say, you bastard?!
Well then, at any rate,
why don't I try telling everyone
how the food you eat
during your journey tastes?
Words fail me...
What a useless reporter!
Robin... It must've been really hard.
But you're not alone anymore.
Just wait, Robin. You've got us.
So have faith in us... in Luffy!
He'll respond to your feelings without fail.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Bond of Friendship Woven
by Tears! Nami's World Map"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!