Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything this world has to offer.
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
If the dusty treasure map
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
has been verified,
it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Robin!
Wealth, fame, power...
We're gonna rescue you for sure!
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
The drawbridge is coming down!
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around
the world to the seas.
drove people around the world
to the seas.
Looks like they pulled through. Good timing.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
To think that you were going to die alone...
Find it!
Robin...
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
That's heartbreaking, Robin-chan.
It must've been really hard.
I don't want to see people
sacrificing themselves anymore!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
But you're not alone anymore.
They've come all this way
after crossing Aqua Laguna.
You've got us.
When you think about it, it's incredible.
That's...
Nami would never kill Usopp!
Hey... don't tell me...
Twenty years ago,
everything was taken away from me
Seems like they've at least got good luck.
I can't think of any reason
for you to be kind to me!
We're friends!
This time, we have permission to kill them.
and many people's lives
were ruined.
...those are the ancient
weapon Pluton's blueprints...!
It's easy when we don't have to
worry about going easy on them.
Who're friends, Luffy?
Why...? Why did you?!
Nami!
It was caused by a single attack--
They're the real deal.
Drawbridge?
Why are you here?
Yeah. The Franky Family is
currently fighting to bring it down.
Buster Call.
Do you believe me?
What're you talking about?
You're our friend! We came to get you!
That attack is now...
"Parting Builds a Man's Character!
Sanji and Chopper"
...targeted on the friends I was finally
able to find, whom I can be myself with.
Once it comes down, we can go
over to the other side at once.
You're a big problem.
Nami?
Hey, Spanda.
Friends? Don't make me laugh!
Geez... When it's right in front of us...
The more I wish to be with you,
What Tom-san and Iceberg
risked their lives to protect is...
You're just a pathetic bunch of
people cooperating with each other.
the more my fate
will show its fangs to you!
Hand them over to me already!
...the wish of this weapon's architect--
"A Bond of Friendship Woven
by Tears! Nami's World Map"
No matter how far I go on the sea,
that is, if the ancient weapon fell
into the hands of an idiot like you
I have a huge enemy
that I can't shake off...
What happened to your leg?
and started being used to cause trouble,
...because the world and
its darkness are my enemy!
CP9...
Without that leg, you won't
be able to be a pirate any more!
he would want another weapon
to be built in order to stop it.
The incident with Aokiji,
as well as this time...
I guess...
I thought I gave up everything...
It's true that if you use Nico Robin,
you can revive the ancient weapon.
I've already dragged you
into my troubles twice!
Why...? I didn't ask for your help!
I didn't want you to come to rescue me.
Even if she doesn't want to help you,
If this continues forever, even though
you guys're good-natured...
I can't think of any reason
for you to be kind to me!
as long as there's a chance
that she could be used,
You really know how to trash a place.
Why do you come after me?
she's still dangerous.
Why...? Why did you?!
What's wrong, Nami?
...you'll eventually feel
that I'm a burden!
But she's got friends
Nothing. I'm just here to rest a little.
Because you...
I'm sure you'll betray me
one day and abandon me!
who would be willing to risk
their lives to protect her.
"Everything Is for Her Friends!
Robin in the Darkness!"
You had the same dream as me.
That's what I'm most afraid of!
Breaking glass and furniture
just to rest is a bit much.
So I'll...
That's why I didn't want
you to come to rescue me!
...take a chance.
I wanna talk about Nico Robin.
The All Blue...
If I'm going to die someday anyway,
Do you know something?!
I want to die
right here, right now!
You have that treasure map open,
even though nothing's wrong?
But... even your men said it doesn't exist...
Did that woman change after
you guys came to this town?
Of course it does! When the
time comes, head to the Grand Line.
Something happened to make me mad, that's all!
Yes, suddenly.
After she went out to town,
she suddenly disappeared,
I see!
Them, huh? Who are they?
The All Blue surely exists there.
That indeed is a sound argument!
and by this morning, she was the
suspect of your attempted assassination.
You met them?!
That's true.
Yeah. Some Captain Something-or-Other.
As you see, I can't be a pirate anymore,
but this time, you can go and find it.
No one is stupid enough
to think that having you isn't a burden.
You bastard! What're you doing?!
He seemed kind of liar-ish, though.
When my friends finally found her,
It's burned black!
I hear you smiled happily when
you were traveling with them.
Look at that symbol,
you damn pirates!
she said she would no longer come back to us.
H-Hey! Geezer, don't die!
Now, there's no longer power to
fight back against the ancient weapon.
Don't just do as you please
and die as you please!
We didn't know what was going on.
Even though I haven't
seen you like that in years.
That logo indicates the unity
of over 170 member countries
So we came here tonight
If nothing is done and Nico Robin
falls into your hands, it'll be hopeless.
in order to ask her directly again
why she's leaving the ship.
spanning the four seas
and the Grand Line!
That damn geezer gave up
his leg so that I could live.
Talk to me! Who are those guys?
But if the Straw Hats win...
This is the world!
To make my wish come true...
...there won't be
anything left to you at all.
Do you now realize how completely
powerless you guys are to fight against it?!
A wish that can never come true if I'm with you!
We agreed you could tell
me anything, remember?
Wha...?!
I made a bet on their victory.
I...
Do you realize how huge
of an organization
What is this wish that can never
come true if she's with us...?
Cutty Flam...
I can't repay the damn geezer for his
kindness unless I risk my life for him too!
this woman has been pursued by?!
How dare you...
I had planned to forget about them...
Let me tell you what I know.
...burn my blueprints?!
I now understand well the
identity of Robin's enemy.
It was probably when you lost sight
of Nico Robin the first time.
Dying isn't something you
should do to repay kindness!!
I thought I had erased them from my mind.
Sogeking.
That's not what he saved you for!
Who do you take your friends for?!
Shoot through that flag.
CP9...
Being given life and yet dying...
is something that a weakling would do!
Roger.
Ahhh! Bro!
The Government's operation
was already in progress.
Bro is falling into the falls!
This is my new weapon,
a huge slingshot...
Then is there any other way
to settle this matter?!
named Kabuto!
Have a good look at its power!
There is, of course, a reason
for that woman's actions.
Franky!
Hey, pirates!
Special Attack... Firebird Star!
But before I tell you about that,
What the hell is that?!
I want you to know that Nico
Robin and I both have a means
Jump with all your might
towards the falls!
Chore boy!!
to bring back the ancient weapon
that could destroy the world.
R-Rocketman?!
Destroy the world?
Oh, no...!
That's right.
I honestly felt like always being
with them, if it were possible.
Mission accomplished.
A problem occurred in our plan.
It's flying again!
Everyone, come to the bedroom right away.
Th-They've gone and done it!
Don't shoot Iceberg yet.
Do they understand what it
means to attack the flag?!
Chore boy...
Are you all right?!
Now I see...
This brings back memories,
doesn't it, Tom-san?
Ha! I'm not quite done yet...
The pirates declared war
against the World Government!
Now, you get it, Nico Robin?
Yeah, that'd hit you hard.
You made me angry.
I won't let you die so easily.
The blueprints you guys were after are fakes.
To think that someone
really showed up for her...
About assisting that Roger guy...
Are you insane?!
Don't think that
you'll be able to survive
I'm resolutely proud of it!
Even if I am to be killed, I won't give
those blueprints to the Government!
after making the entire
world your enemy!
Friends, huh?
Bring it on!
I'm Luffy. I'm the man
who'll be King of the Pirates.
But if you're sniffing around
the Poneglyphs on another front
Really?!
Dammit! That bastard Krieg brings
out weapons one after another...
The most painful word for her...
Yeah.
Roger was an idiot
and helping the Government as well,
There's no way that chore boy can...
Robin!
then I have to stop you right here, right now.
like him, too, wasn't he?
Even if hundreds of weapons are built in,
We still haven't heard you say it!
And you helped him out.
What's wrong, girlie?
I'm not seeking the Poneglyphs
in order to bring the weapon back.
he can be defeated by someone
with a spear of blind determination.
Seems like we didn't learn our lesson.
I just want to know the history, that's all.
Everyone in Tom's Workers
is helping this pirate kid.
Say you want to live!
Do you want me to return
the village that badly?
Such a claim doesn't mean anything!
Robin...
I told you, didn't I?
Then how's this? Let's make an agreement.
You would've done the same,
wouldn't you, Tom-san?
Over... and over again...
Life or death...
Agreement?
That's right.
Even if you don't intend to do so...
Robin!
In a pirate battle, if you fear death
for even a moment, you'll fall to pieces.
Gather up 100 million Berries and bring it here.
Weapons hurt people despite your intentions!
To live...
Do so and I'll let the village
go and give you freedom.
They can even hurt those
who mean a lot to you!
What're you talking about?
I thought it was something
I dared not wish for.
We're gonna collide!
Honest?!
Honest!
W-We're gonna crash!
I'd die before I'd break an
agreement concerning money.
That which hurts people doesn't
necessarily have malicious intent.
No one ever let me wish for it.
It doesn't matter how many years
it takes. I'll honor our agreement.
The sea is vast,
If that simple curiosity of
wanting to know the history
leads to the destruction of the world,
At least...
so someday, definitely...
"Obtain the Five Keys!
The Straw Hat Pirates vs. CP9"
...you'll come across friends
who'll protect you!
you should die right here,
right now, Nico Robin!
...that kid doesn't have any hesitation!
I absolutely will save up 100 million Berries!
Even after you saw the Ohara devils' fate,
Arlong!
you still want to chase
after the world's history?!
Is it a survival instinct...?
Don't talk like you know
everything about Ohara!
Believe in Luffy.
Oh? What's wrong, skilled surveyor
of ours? Why the angry look?
Or does he not fear death
because he has faith in himself...?
If...
it's really okay for me
to utter my wish for once...
You don't even know how much the
World Government messed up my life!
The Navy men you have under
your control stole all my money!
Faith...
I...
What happened to dying before
breaking promises about money?!
I want to live!
If you hate the Government that much,
then why are you helping them?!
The fleet Krieg gathered...
Take me to the sea with you!
Why?!
When did I break our promise?
Run!
His hundreds of weapons and poison...
If they're all force...
Don't play dumb! You teamed
up with the Navy to--!
Because I have a wish I want to come true
even if I have to give up everything.
...then that kid's spear is also force...
When did I break our promise? Let's hear it!
The spear held in his heart...
There're two conditions that
CP9 forced on me in this town.
They're here...
I know an idiot who's holding back
that spear for a stupid reason...
One is to pin the assassination
on the Straw Hats.
Damn you... Damn you! Damn you!
Yoyoi!
The other is to turn myself in
to the Government and obey them.
I see! So your money's been stolen?
How unfortunate.
You guys...!
I love you guys, dammit!
They're here!
Dammit!
Hey, come with me!
But an agreement is an agreement.
If you do that, you'll die, too.
Let's go!
If you can't gather up
100 million Berries for me to see,
If only I could get these
Sea Prism Stone handcuffs off...
Why do you accept such conditions
after evading them for 20 years?
What?!
I'm afraid I can't give you the village back.
This is gonna end it... for sure!
"I'm Not Gonna Hand over
the Blueprints! Franky's Decision"
Now, I'm freeing you
of any restrictions, CP9!
In this lone instance,
CP9 has been given permission
Scum!
to exercise Buster Call against the Straw Hats.
Beat the crap out of them
here at the Tower of Law!
It's only 100 million Berries!
Just start saving up again!
Gum-Gum...!
Buster Call?
I'll give you permission
to slaughter them!
It's an emergency order to
summon five of the vice admirals
Lucci! Come with me!
from Navy Headquarters and
ten battleships to one place.
Or are you gonna run out on me?
Protecting my life is your
top priority!
Got that?!
Once you've been targeted by the
national war-class military power,
But if you do run away, I'll kill
everyone in Cocoyashi Village.
Funkfreed!
...Giant Gavel!!
nothing will remain of you.
Normally, in the Navy, this authority
only belongs to the three admirals
Nami...
We pretended we didn't know.
and the head of the Navy, the fleet admiral.
Because our hopes would keep you
from running away from Arlong
All right, good boy.
But this time,
--Wait!
--Hm?
if you ever decided to.
We both have foolish dreams.
through the admiral Aokiji,
An elephant...
CP9 was given the authority
to exercise it just this once.
who ate a Devil Fruit
with sword powers?!
Okay! We pulled the lever!
Hm?
No, it's actually the other way around.
All right!
In order to achieve my goal, the All Blue...
If I didn't accept the conditions,
Buster Call was going to be exercised on us.
This is a sword that ate
the Elephant-Elephant fruit.
No more of this! Take up
your weapons! Let's fight!
In other words, it's an elephant sword.
When I heard the name Aokiji, I gave up.
Eight years ago, we swore
not to throw away our lives!
Sanji?
I've got this treasured sword,
in addition to CP9.
Yeah. I'll come along... on your journey
to become "King of the Pirates"!
No matter how painful and insulting
it was to be ruled by them,
I was always able to make good
my escape for the past 20 years
When I think about it calmly,
I've got nothing to be afraid of.
we swore to fight the patient fight
as long as Nami was cheerful!
What?
Looks like Mozu and the
others did okay, too.
because I had nothing to protect...
Now, let's head to the Gates of Justice!
I'll be the cook for your ship.
Go, Straw Hat!
Because I could betray people
and use them as a shield.
But this is their answer!
Go ahead and get this woman
back if you can, Straw Hat!
Now that our village's chance for
freedom is gone, we have no hope!
But I really can't do that any longer.
The drawbridge is coming down!
Big Bro Franky is okay!
Is that okay or not?
The Straw Hats have finally
reached the Tower of Law!
Looks like they pulled through.
More than that,
It's okay!! All right!!
we must make those fishmen pay
for toying with that girl's kindness!
Good timing.
Bro is no longer a prisoner!
The life I once gave up on...
I'm happy for you, Big Bro Luffy!
Looks like he's gonna join in the fight!
Yeah!
The heart that I lost...
Any objections?!
Yaay! Yaay! We got a cook!
We'll have good food!
That's right!
He's that kind of person!
Of course not! Let's go!
The dream I could no longer have...
They picked them all up for me.
Get them, Bro!
I-I'm trembling with anticipation!
Wait, everyone!
So that's how it is, everyone.
Go! Straw Hat!
Lower that bridge already.
I was able to make friends who
would believe in someone like me.
Sorry for causing you all sorts of trouble.
Nami!
We're leaving the rest
to you, Straw Hat.
He looks evil.
Ha! I don't like it! I wanted to
kick you out from here myself.
Just a little more! Just wait a
little more! I'll work hard again!
Robin!
Then, your wish is...
Hey, are you guys okay?!
We're gonna rescue you for sure!
And you decide it so easily...?
Old Hag Kokoro?!
Little ones?!
I'll save up the money again!
What'd you come here for,
That the six Straw Hats, excluding me,
can leave this island safely!
Stay there!
It'll be easy this time!
bringing out a dangerous thing
like Rocketman?!
Sorry for making you resort to bad acting.
They're in high spirits.
I'm used to it! I'll be fine!
There's no need to worry at all!
W-Well, it saved me, too, but...
You knew?!
To think that they don't fear
the flag of the Government...
I could hear everything, since you're all stupid.
Hey! Hey, old hag!
Hang in there!
This is nothing compared to back then!
Are you saying, for that, you don't
care if the weapon is brought back?!
How pointless.
There's no way
that they could defeat us.
Hey! I beg you! Don't die!
What?!
You don't care what happens to the world?!
That is to say, you're willing to go that far
to kick me out, huh, you damn geezer?!
Don't die!
Please, no more dying!
Stay there!
That's right, I don't!
The drawbridge is coming down!
Everyone! I'm fine! I'm just fine!
Why do you always have to
talk like that?! You bastard!
Go! Straw Hat!
How dare those damn pirates?!
We're not gonna let it happen!
Hmph! That's right, little brat!
Get the trench mortar ready!
I don't like kids to begin with.
I've got a nosebleed.
You can stop now...
Stop the drawbridge!
Break it if you have to!
How could you walk away from this
sort of crash with just a nosebleed?!
Even you know there's no point now...
Not a single day passed where I didn't regret
letting a useless one live, you damn brat.
Yes, sir!
You fought very well, carrying our
lives on your back all this time...
All right! We're here!
I'm not gonna let you do that!
Pipe Hitch Knives!
Ha! Fine by me, you damn geezer!
Straw Hat...!
Joining them must've been
even more painful for you
This is the end of you!
Hello!
Enjoy the rest of your life to the utmost.
Thanks, monster granny!
Demolition Chop!
than being cut through the heart...
Hey, you guys!
Get up already!
You fought very well.
That was nothing!
You're rubber. Don't lump us with you.
Luffy!
Gen-san...
Whoa! This is a nice ship.
Is it okay for us to use it?
Us flesh-and-blood humans were
forced to charge in like that.
Of course! It's Sanji's boat.
You think we're okay...?
Leave the village now.
No way!
Let's go.
You don't have to say goodbye?
Gen-san?!
What the hell are you doing there?!
That's okay.
Yup, they're all fine.
Do it, Nami.
Sanji!
You guys are all weirdos, too, so...
W-What?!
Don't catch cold.
Nacchan...
N... Nami! Are you there behind me?!
Just sayin'.
Nami...
There are stairs over there!
You're crafty, and you have a dream.
Let's hurry up and catch up to Robin!
Chief Justice Baskerville!
Well, hey, listen!
Nojiko! Everyone!
At any rate, that pigeon guy sent me flying
I won't let you go!
Too bad!
We're actually
the Chief Justice trio!
and I flew right into this gap.
Stop it, everyone! I don't want to
see anyone else get hurt by them!
Wait.
What?!
I, the Left Baskerville,
am named Bas!
What the heck is that?!
Chapapapa...
You'll die, you know!
We got invaded.
I, the Right Baskerville,
am named Kerville!
We know.
Even if you go
to the room you saw earlier,
And I, the Center Baskerville,
go by the name...
Nico Robin isn't there anymore,
...Princess!
since Lucci took her to
the Gates of Justice.
Don't fool around at a critical time like this!
What the heck?!
What?!
So those three were just
sticking together? That's all?
It's no use! We've made up our minds!
Oh, and our Chief did, too.
While you've been taking your
sweet time, Robin was taken away!
What for?!
We're good friends!
Oh, is that right?!
Thanks for giving us
such valuable information.
Get out of our way, Nami!
Shut up!
Chapapa... I spilled the beans...
Fire the trench mortar!
Robin intends to die for us!
Let's go, everyone!
What a funny guy.
Even if we can't win,
let's show 'em what we're made of!
Oh, well...
They're headed there right now,
but I won't tell you how to get there,
and we, CP9,
won't let you go there, either.
We have an order to annihilate you guys.
The drawbridge
stopped coming down?!
How dare they get in our way?!
Annihilation order...?
Damn bastards!
Unless you guys defeat us,
Who's doing this?!
Owner Zeff!!
She sacrificed herself in order to protect
us from an attack by the Government!
you won't be able
to set Nico Robin free.
Thank you for all the damn things
you've done for me over all these years!!
Chief Spandam!
Yeah.
Please evacuate
from the Tower of Law!
You don't have to tell us that.
We're gonna do it anyway.
Chapapa...
I'll never forget your kindness...
for the rest of my life!!
What a high-spirited guy.
When she knew that she was going
to be killed if she was taken in!
But let me tell you one more thing.
What?! Do as you wish.
All right! Good job!
Ah, thanks.
Then...
I'm gonna head to the Gates of Justice
before they come over to this side!
Then, I'll speak frankly.
...after all, Robin was...
Look at this!
Come, Nico Robin!
...lying?
A key?
Someone! Bring Cutty Flam!
What for?!
Robin!
This is the key to unlock
Yes!
Those pirates are just nobodies.
Arlong! Arlong!
the Sea Prism Stone
handcuffs on Nico Robin!
Good...
Sea Prism Stone?
I've got the assassin group
CP9 on my side!
It's a stone that cancels out
Devil Fruit powers.
Arlong! Arlong!
You asshole!!
Arlong!
I heard that it's as effective as when
Devil Fruit power holders fall into the sea.
Nico Robin, a survivor
of the island of scholars
I'll miss you, dammit!
So that's why Robin isn't fighting now,
I'll miss you!!
who schemed to bring back
the weapon...
despite how strong she actually is.
Cutty Flam, who inherited
the weapon's blueprints...
Whoooa! There it is!
Yeah.
Luffy...
Under normal circumstances,
she isn't so weak that she'd helplessly
stay held captive by guys like that.
This looks cool!
I'm definitely not gonna stand back and
miss this opportunity to gain big power!
What do you want?!
You don't even know anything!
Amazing!
She must be feeling frustrated.
You don't even know what's happened
on this island the past eight years!
I see.
I'm warning you, this is a crazy train.
Even if you guys can rescue
Nico Robin by some chance,
Yeah. I don't know.
I'll miss you!!
Its name is Rocketman.
Cutty Flam...
I feel sad, dammit!
since the Sea Prism Stone
is hard like diamonds,
This has nothing to do with you!
We can't even allow passengers to be on board.
the handcuffs will be on her forever.
I told you, leave the damn island already!
Okay! Well then, let's go, shall we?!
Yeah. You told me.
Chapapa...
Leave! I don't need you!
I spilled the beans again.
You idiots!
He really is funny.
Leave! Leave! Leave! Leave!
That's...
Men should part without a word.
If that's okay, keep on going to
rescue Nico Robin.
Hey... don't tell me...
Leave! Leave! Leave!
Chapapapapa!
Leave!
...those are the ancient
weapon Pluton's blueprints...!
Well, then...
...give that to us!
They're the real deal.
Let's go!! Set sail!!
Do you believe me?
I'll see you again, you damn bastards!
Lucci... Kaku...
You guys can tell, right?
Looks like he can use
that technique, too.
Don't be so hasty.
I didn't say that this is the right key.
What?!
Now departing Water Seven for Enies Lobby...
Here comes the sea train Rocketman!
Luffy...
It might be
As long as you don't fear even death
because you have faith in yourself...
I thought it was unlikely...
Help me...
for different handcuffs.
So you were hiding them
inside your body, huh?
Chapapa papa!
All right! Depart!
...you'll find the All Blue... for sure...
There are five CP9 members,
including me, in this tower.
T-The real ones?!
We're gonna go...! To get everything back!
Are those the real ones?!
Guys! Customers are gonna show up soon!
Each one has a key
One, two, come on!
Hand them over...
Hand them over to me!
Get to work already!
Of course I will!
One, two, bad!
and is waiting for you.
Those are my long-sought
blueprints!
Nico Robin.
Yow?!
Then, until we defeat you all
and get the keys,
Don't touch my treasure!
Rumors are such unreliable things,
aren't they?
and try them on Robin's handcuffs,
Luffy...
we won't know which one
is the right key?!
While we were being
brought to this damn place,
How stupid... Buying time?
I came to realize
that you aren't the evil
While we're fighting,
you guys are trying to take Robin-chan
to the Gates of Justice, aren't you?!
who's trying to misuse the weapon.
Whoa! Cool!
Let's go.
That's right!
Yeah!
I spilled the beans again...
How to build the weapon isn't
what the Water Seven's shipwrights
Robin has been alone all this time...
just like I used to be.
Catching up with Robin
quickly should be our priority.
We'll first get Robin back
and then worry about the key.
have been inheriting for
generations in the first place.
You've been shot? We need to stop
the bleeding right away or you'll die!
Let's ignore that weirdo and hurry!
Chapa!
Tom-san achieved
so many great things,
"That weirdo"
Chapapa!
You're smart.
and he gave up everything in order to
preserve these blueprints for the future.
What the...?!
You can! You can!
But if you do that,
At least, as long as there's a risk
You can! You can be a great doctor...
I'll ditch this key
into the sea! Chapapa!
that a woman named Nico Robin
can restore the weapon,
Which one of you is Arlong?!
Doct... I can't breath...
the world needs
those blueprints to fight back.
...because you have such a kind heart...
We're giving you a chance.
Hey, Spanda.
See ya.
I wonder if Robin didn't
have anyone like Doctor...
Ah! Wait, you jerk!
What Tom-san and Iceberg
risked their lives to protect is...
Hey, wait!
A power strong enough to give me control
over any large country I might desire
You wait!
Hand them over to me already!
...the wish of this
weapon's architect--
is in my hands now!
Really, there are some strange
creatures in this world.
Stop! Just a little bit longer!
You can no longer escape.
that is, if the ancient weapon fell
into the hands of an idiot like you
Just wait until we decide
what each of us will do!
You must really have spent your
whole life disliked by everyone.
Why did Aokiji give you the
authority to exercise Buster Call?
This is the top floor of Arlong Park.
and started being used
to cause trouble,
Ah! Let me go!
You poor monster. Why's a loner
like you trying to save this country?
What's this room?
he would want another weapon
to be built in order to stop it.
Calm down, Straw Hat.
Full of papers...
Let me go!
Is Lucci that pigeon guy?
These're not just ordinary papers.
Don't make me laugh!
It's true that if you use Nico Robin,
you can revive the ancient weapon.
Shut up! Even if I don't
have friends, I can still fight!
This room is where I make that
woman draw sea charts. It's...
Yeah, that's right.
Huh?
If he's with Robin-chan,
Even if she doesn't
want to help you,
As long as Doctor's flag exists, I will...
as long as there's a chance
that she could be used,
...the survey room!
we should let at least
Luffy go on ahead.
Nami's room...
she's still dangerous.
You do have friends!
Luffy.
These're all sea charts that Nami drew.
At any rate, you just
beat up the pigeon guy.
But she's got friends
Let me go! Let me go!
who would be willing to risk
their lives to protect her.
I am your friend!
She's going to continue drawing
sea charts! For my ambition!
There are six of us excluding Luffy.
So I'll...
You're in no position to ask me
questions, you insolent woman!
He said there are five CP9 members here.
...take a chance.
And once her charts give me full
knowledge of all the world's seas...
We'll get the five keys for Robin-chan's
handcuffs from them and go after Luffy.
I can think
If I hadn't recognized
the value of your existence,
of only one way that I could
uphold the architect's wish in this situation.
...we fishmen will be invincible,
and the world will become our empire!
If Robin-kun goes through
the gates, it'll all be over.
it would've been practically worthless!
Hey, let's be pirates together! Okay?!
Just shut up and hand them
over to me already!
It's all a race against time!
Our first stepping stone is
this island... and the East Blue!
Those are mine!
If we lose against them,
that means we lose time!
So you should appreciate me!
It's not possible.
Yes, it is, since it's fun!
Hey, you don't make sense.
Everyone! Take them down
even if it costs you your life!
Tom-san...!
You, the repugnant kin of Ohara,
the land of devils...
Could you use the girl as efficiently as that?!
In this situation,
I'm sure you'd also...
Yeah!
But...
Good luck!
Nico Robin...
But I'm a reindeer! I have antlers and hooves!
"Use"?!
Hurry!
Run to the evacuation ship!
What's that?!
I even have a blue nose!
--Put out the fire!
--Protect the books!
A desk...
It's true... that I wanna be a pirate, but...
Revealing the history isn't
what Ohara was trying to do.
What do you think you're doing?!
We just wanted to accept the voices
of the past and protect them.
Let me go! Let me go!
I'm not even a human! I'm a monster!
What in the...?! There's an
awful lot of stuff flying!
No! I'll stay here, too! Mom!
There are six of us excluding Luffy.
I can't become your friend! So...!
He said there are five CP9 members here.
Mom!
We'll get the five keys for Robin-chan's
handcuffs from them and go after Luffy.
I can think
So I just came to say thank you...
of only one way that I could
uphold the architect's wish in this situation.
Live, Robin!
If Robin-kun goes through
the gates, it'll all be over.
I do appreciate you guys.
Just shut up and hand them
over to me already!
Stop that!
It's all a race against time!
Those are mine!
Thank you for asking me to join you.
The charts!
If we lose against them,
that means we lose time!
M-My charts!
Tom-san...!
In this situation,
I'm sure you'd also...
Everyone! Take them down
even if it costs you your life!
I'll stay here, but...
Yeah!
Good luck!
Listen carefully, Robin!
...one day... if you feel like it, stop by agai...
Pirate guys!
You're alone now, but you'll
meet friends someday for sure!
This... is a pretty intense fight!
Shut up! Let's go!
Yeah! Looks like a fight to the death!
Definitely!
Chimney? Gonbe?
Friends?
Where did they go?
Right. The sea is vast, so someday, definitely...
They were there up until just a bit ago!
You bastard!
What're you doing?!
I'm sure I'll bump into them somewhere!
Thank you...
...you'll come across friends who'll protect you!
You don't ask people to join you
by telling them to "shut up."
It's burned black!
I'm not gonna let you go to
the Gates of Justice!
--Monster!
Robin!
Dammit!
I'm gonna kill you!
Her mom abandoned her!
A secret passage!
Our five-year mission...
A secret passage! A secret passage!
No one is born into this world to be alone!
A secret passage!
That felt good! Hey, do it again!
Geography!
Physics!
The blueprints were kept in order
to create a weapon to fight back...
You've gone too far, you damn rubber man!
You idiot! We're setting sail right away!
You will understand someday.
Stigma!
I-I thought I'd die...
Marimba!
Hm? Where am I?!
And you, the Government,
came after them a second time.
"Fishmen are great" and "sea charts" this,
"circumstances" that...
Ah, Sanji-san! You came to?
They said that she's a survivor
of those Ohara devils
Essentially, something like
this should remain a secret,
who planned the world's annihilation.
and so once it's revealed,
it has to be eliminated.
Doctor! It wasn't just a fantasy, right?!
I don't know much about any of that stuff...
Don't let her get away!
Now, give me the money!
I reported her to you, right?!
Your research was completed then, right?!
But I finally figured out how to save her!
Now, there's no longer power to
fight back against the ancient weapon.
Bats...?
Your sin is being alive!
Or was that a lie, too?
If nothing is done and Nico Robin
falls into your hands,
I-I wonder how far this goes...
I did it, Chopper! My research succeeded!
it'll be hopeless.
Go meet the friends who're
surely waiting for you
But if the Straw Hats win...
She can't go because this room is here!
Did you lie because I'd be sad
if you died without saying so?
somewhere at sea, Robin!
...there won't be anything
left to you at all.
If she doesn't want to be here,
then I'll just destroy it all!
I can hear something.
"Nothing is impossible for the man
who raised a flag with a skull!"
I made a bet on their victory.
Please say it again, Doctor!
Gum-Gum...
I've got nothing to be afraid of!
How dare you mock me...?
Seems like you want
to die here, too, huh?
...Battle-Axe!
Let's go there!
Are you ready, young men?!
--Yes, Ma'am!
--Fire!
Bro!
Listen, Kureha. This dust is...
Help won't come, Nico Robin.
Big Bro Franky!
Hey look!
They don't know how to get to the
Gates of Justice in the first place!
Bro is at the Tower of Law!
Dr. Kureha! What in the world...?
Good! He's fine!
Just shut up and watch.
Sogeking.
That's Bro!
Impossible! It's gonna collapse!
Hm?
Bro!
This is dangerous! Everyone, get away!
Shoot through that flag.
We came to rescue you!
Dr. Kureha! We shot all of them!
Big Sis Nami! Hurry!
Roger.
We came with the Straw Hats!
But Luffy's still inside!
Huh?
--Big Sis!
--Luffy! Luffy's still...!
Light them up!
Sodom and Gomorrah
fought hard, too!
This is my new weapon,
a huge slingshot... named Kabuto!
Bro!
Have a good look at its power!
Let's go back together!
Luffy!
Are you hurt?!
Special Attack... Firebird Star!
Y... You guys...
Come out! You pigeon jerk!
Amazing...
You idiots...
Is it this way?!
Yeah...
Who asked you to come...
It's so beautiful...
To come rescue me?!
Luffy...
Oh, no...!
Is it that way?!
I will make cherry blossoms bloom.
Which one won?!
Once my invention is complete,
this country will be saved!
Given all this debris... Don't tell me it was--!
Which way is it...?!
Mission accomplished.
You idiots!
Which way is it?!
Are you insane?! Don't think
that you'll be able to survive
Bastards! I'm not crying!
Luffy...
Listen. This red dust isn't ordinary dust.
Ooops.
after making the entire world your enemy!
That way?!
This will attach to the white snow in the air
Bring it on!
Which way...?!
and make vivid pink snow fall.
Which way?!
Shut up, you bastards!
Is it this way?!
What are you, a demon?!
Luffy!
Robin's waiting!
Big Bro!
Robin!
Hurry up
and bring down the bridge!
Doctor...!
Oh, yeah, right.
We still haven't heard you say it!
Doctorine...!
This way! Robin!
Hurry up, you bastards!
That's right!
Hurry up, you guys!
Or I'm gonna beat you up!
Even he shouldn't be able
to follow us this far.
Say you want to live!
Y-Yeah, you're right.
Is he okay?!
I like you when you're contradictory
like that, too, Nami-san!
To live...
Hey, Straw Hat!
You shouldn't be allowed
to live in this world, Robin!
That's a weird room.
Looks like you helped
my underlings.
I have to do this and do this
one like this... and like this.
Nami!
Your existence itself is a huge crime, Robin!
But this time,
I wonder what he's doing.
I, their boss, the great Franky,
I thought it was something I dared not wish for.
will add my super fighting power
to you guys!
Whatever!
You're my friend!
I'm still holding what
you did to Usopp against you!
No one ever let me wish for it.
The sea is vast, so someday, definitely...
Err... well,
he's right next to you...
Cutty Flam...
I will never shoot you!
...you'll come across friends who'll protect you!
Open, doors!
How dare you...
My name is Dr. Hiriluk! I'm a doctor!
Yeah!
...burn my blueprints?!
Tony Tony Chopper. That's a cool name,
isn't it? That's what I'll call you.
If... it's really okay for me
to utter my wish for once...
My friends helped me.
Whoa...
Chopper, you'll be able to become
a good doctor. I'll guarantee it.
This time, I'll fight for one of my friends, too.
I...
Ahhh! Bro!
So, Robin, have faith in us... in Luffy!
This is bad... Before I fight...
I want to live!
Bro is falling into the falls!
Where's the kitchen?!
Take me to the sea with you!
He'll respond to your feelings without fail.
Even if I disappear, my dream will come true.
Coup de Boo!
Franky!
I had... such a good life!
Hey, pirates!
Because I used a bottle and
a half of cola for Coup de Boo,
Hey, pirates! What're you
guys wasting time for?!
What?! Kokoro-san?!
I've used more than two bottles today!
I heard everything!
What're you guys wasting time for?!
Thank you, Chopper!
Unless I fill up all three bottles,
I can't fight CP9!
Wasting time?
But the
bridge is only halfway down.
Halfway is good enough!
Huh? What's the meaning of that smile?
That area looks like a kitchen!
We'll be there in four seconds.
What the hell is that?!
Now, have a safe trip, my stupid son...
Let's go!
Jump with all your might
towards the falls!
Here we go!
Chapapapapa...
That's... from earlier...!
I knew it!
I'm Silent Fukurou!
Come, Nico Robin!
Is that Granny?
I like rumors!
What does she mean?
Nooo!
I've got the assassin group CP9 on my side!
I don't know.
Do you want the key?
But she said
jump towards the falls.
Dammit!
Robin...!
I still haven't refilled my cola yet!
You're not alone anymore, got that?!
Chapa...!
"Straw Hat Theater"
We'll rescue you for sure, so just wait!
"Part 3"
A-A sea train?!
[Obahan: Middle-aged Woman]
I wonder what this
dungeon-like hallway is?
Why is it coming into the courthouse?!
Cutty Flam...
Chimney, sound the
whistle with gusto.
"If the Straw Hats were
all middle-aged women..."
Okay!
The sound of the sea train?
Yoyoi!
"...who would be the strongest?!"
You damn pirate!
Here we go!
The sound of the sea train?
I knew it!
You're doomed now that
I've caught you here!
"Luffizaki"
What's the meaning of that smile?
Oh, dear! I'm out of soy sauce!
Chief Justice!
And here I was gonna make
soy sauce meat steak,
Please get out of here!
Wait...
meat salad and meat miso soup today...!
"Today's menu
soy sauce meat steak
meat salad (no veggies)
meat miso soup (without soup)"
Stop!
"Straw Hat Theater"
a second...!
Here we go!
Pardon me, I'm coming in, okay?
I knew it!
Hey, Zoroyama-san, I'm out of soy sauce.
"Part 5"
Now, be a dearie and spare
me some, would you? Whoa!
Yoyoi!
That gave me a start!
Hey, are you in the middle of training?
"Straw Hat Theater"
What a noisy guy...
Oh, dearie me, if it isn't Luffizaki-san.
Here we go!
My, no, I'm not training.
We're having sashimi today...
I knew it!
"Part 4"
Rodusa is wearing sunglasses because
she's a monster known as the Gorgon
"Ruthless Time"
...so I was just cutting some raw fish.
who turns people to stone
when they look her in the eyes.
Nooo!
My, my, seems like you cut the whole kitchen.
No one was in there.
Oh, that's right, soy sauce!
We're... all out, too.
But she didn't have eye contact with
anyone today for a different reason.
Rocketman can still run!
Oh, my, your bottle's been cut in two.
--I'm bored.
--Yeah.
Don't underestimate Tom's Workers,
No one's in here.
"Supermarket Isoflavone"
"Moai"
"[Bored]"
Ma'am, you can't do that.
a legendary ship-building company!
Bring me some meat or I'm
gonna frickin' kill youse guys!
There you go again, monster!
Hmm, no one's in here.
Oh, my word... My word...!
This ham is the bee's knees!
"Don Luffione, Luffione Family"
This one with the cheese wrapped
in ham is simply to die for!
Why do I smoke cigars, you ask?
All right, no one's in here.
Now, Dragon. Give me those mystical horns.
Be a dear and get me some jam.
R-Rocketman?!
What's going on?
I can't find anyone anywhere!
'Cuz the air in this frickin'
world stinks, that's why!
"Sampling"
"Half Price"
"Ham"
You're always shooting at me.
It hurts, you know!
Ma'am, you can't bring rice
into the sampling section!
(Dandy)
If no one's around, that's fine, though.
You're a monster, too!
"Centaur
Usoppaka"
Why?! Come now,
Luffizaki-san does this all the time!
I called youse guys here today for one reason...
"Dragon
Lugyao"
If you've got time, why don't you fish?
It's flying again!
She's always causing us trouble, too!
I think it's time we made clear who's
boss of this town once and for all!
Mystical fish live in this sea.
Can it! Now bring me some
sweet jam for this ham!
They must've gotten scared of me...
It's me, you dumbass!
--I want the mystical horns, not mystical fish.
--This is a village called
Monston in a monster forest,
No way, any idiot would realize it's me!
Make it sweet and tasty!
Ahhh...!
"Don Zorocia, Zorocia Family"
--Like I said, catch some fish.
--I'm gonna make bugle horns out of them.
--where monsters live free from care.
Someone's here!
It's the grabby fiend, Sanjida!
"Don Sanjino, Sanjino Family"
Sanjino, a bonehead like you who
doesn't even slick his hair back
My, my! Just what is the problem?
We're all ladies here.
Hey, you have a bite.
Oh?
isn't even qualified to be boss of this town.
He's sleeping...
What?!
Hey, you! Let me touch your butt!
Ahh! I got tricked by the sweet bait!
I've got my reasons, okay?!
It's slicked back on one side, isn't it?!
They're coming!
"Kraken (Giant Octopus)
Choperken"
Is he part of CP9, too?
You again, Choperken?!
--Enough of that, you two!
--Oh, no, Mellorine...
One side?! Don't make me laugh! That's like
saying you've got half a pair of balls!
H-He's sleeping with the
key right in front of him!
Oh, good! It's the middle-aged woman
of once-a-month justice, Namijima-san!
"Liquor"
What're you doing on the sea floor?!
--What'd you say?!
--That's the last straw! This calls for all-out war!
It's a waterfall!
Couldn't this be a huge,
lucky chance?!
I'm looking for a mystical treasure
that's on the sea floor right now!
She forgets her own faults and tells off
the middle-aged woman pirate gang
once a month for some reason!
Why the hell are you starting the war?!
More importantly, give me
more of those sweet baits!
This brings back memories,
doesn't it, Tom-san?
What about this room?!
Anyway, war it is.
Hey, hey, hey, hey...!
Make him eat lead, Usotooya.
Dammit...
Imma gonna take out Zorocia.
Hey, Choperken!
Hey, hey, Luffizaki-san!
Have I got news for you!
"Mermaid
Stronamie"
About assisting that Roger guy...
If you lay your hands on that
mystical treasure, you'll pay for it!
No one's here, either.
The supermarket in front of the train
station has some super bargains!
I'm resolutely proud of it!
Usotooya failed!
The meat is freakin' cheap, too!
Huh? It's laying on the sea floor,
so first come, first served.
"Usotooya of the Luffione Family died in battle."
Meat is?! Usokawa-san,
you aren't fooling me, are you?!
Oh? You've got some nerve.
You wanna compete with me?
Yeah, I was lying. I brought you the circular.
I'm Luffy.
"Circular"
I'm the man
who'll be King of the Pirates.
Go take out Luffione while he
don't have his men to protect him!
--Oh, phooey!
--But forget that, I have terrible news!
--Scary!
--Hiya!
Really?!
Yeah.
Chopamori-san and Sanjida-san
were caught at the supermarket.
I'm gonna take out Luffione.
Please make yourself at home.
Roger
What idiot is troubling my love, Stronamie-san?!
"Water Imp
Sanzaler"
--Ah, I need some tea!
--Oh, dear! Could it be that
Namijima-san is at it again?
Chopalini failed!
was an idiot like him,
too, wasn't he?
Shall I... make some tea?
"Chopalini of the Sanjino Family died in battle."
I'm gonna beat him up!
Hey, hey, hey...!
And you helped him out.
Know your enemy well, Namimore.
Robino-san! Let us hide here!
Namijima-san's gonna kill us!
Hey, what're you doing?
Are you trying to catch me?
I'm gonna take out Sanjino.
Seems like we didn't learn our lesson.
Oh, my, good timing.
A mystical fish.
Everyone in Tom's Workers
is helping this pirate kid.
Mamma mia!
I'm not a fish! I'm a water imp.
The Sanjino Family has been taken out!
"Don Sanjino of the Sanjino Family
ascended to heaven."
I've been warning you guys
about sorting your trash.
More like a naughty monster who lives
in the sea despite being a water imp.
Please stop insisting that
everything is burnable trash.
Now, where's his safe?
Give yourself up!
"Minotaur
Zoromilk"
You would've done the same,
wouldn't you, Tom-san?
What about you?! You're a minotaur,
and yet you're a Holstein!
Oh, wow! He sure was loaded!
What's with that nonsense?!
It's burnable if there's enough spirit!
Yes, please!
Why, good point, Luffizaki-san! She's right!
Shut up. I'm gonna get that mystical
bowl on your head today for sure!
Namimore failed!
"Namimore of the Zorocia Family
died from happiness."
It's a matter of spirit... The incinerator's.
What silly nonsense.
I'm not gonna let you have it.
It'll endanger my life.
Oh, well. She still killed Sanjino.
Oh? Pickled vegetables?!
More importantly, I heard that that
iron rod you have is a mystical thing.
Your pickled vegetables are
the best, Robino-san! I love them!
Robita, go take out Luffione.
We're gonna collide!
You've already drawn your swords?
Oh, my! Then let's take a break and have
this barley tea I found in the fridge!
--I'm not interested.
--What?!
Why don't you try and get it?
W-We're gonna crash!
Shut up, you guys!
Yeah, since they're
crying out for blood.
Zorocia has been betrayed!
"Don Zorocia of the Zorocia Family
died thinking, 'I never thought
my ally would kill me.'"
Mystical this, mystical that...
You guys are all mystical beasts!
Click.
Hello?
Gasp!
Why, yes, they're here. Sure.
No! They actually shot each other!
"Robita of the Zorocia Family died thinking,
'It wasn't supposed to be like this.'"
But, you know, Rodusa.
You were crying the other day
Robita failed!
Oh, Robino-san? Who just called?
saying that you lost your mystical earrings,
Namijima-san.
Ahh! Where'd you come
falling from, Zoro?!
As it stands,
Robin will be in danger.
so we decided to give
something even rarer to you.
Hell yeah, I'm the boss!
We have to do something before
they go through the Gates of Justice.
Why the hell are you with a wolf?!
Hey, hey! Don't spill the beans!
Now I can stuff myself with as
much meat as I want in this town!
So that means we have to defeat
CP9 and get those five keys, huh?
What?!
You're with a giraffe, too.
So... mind telling me what
happened to this month's rent?
So this means that both of
them have Devil Fruit powers.
The reason why she doesn't
look in everyone's eyes
Big landowner, Namijima-san...
In any case, we don't
have much time.
What's with CP9?!
Could you be a dearie and wait
until tomorrow's town raffle event?
What the hell...
Everyone! Take them down
even if it costs you your life!
is in order to hide her happiness,
embarrassment, and tears.
Hey, hey... What is this place?! A zoo?!
To think that meat tastes
terrible when I eat it by myself...
Just wait, Robin!
No! I'm gonna go to your employers
and collect the money directly from them.
On the next episode of One Piece!
I... I finally realized just now
what the most important thing is...
"Obtain the Five Keys!
The Straw Hat Pirates vs. CP9"
"Devil Fruit Powers! Kaku
and Jabra Transform"
No, Namijima-san! Not that!
Everyone...
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
Tomorrow is gonna mark the end of our lives!
...thank you!
I feel lonely... I feel lonely...
--Fine by me.
--What?!
Stone...!
If this is a dream, I wanna wake up.
Even if they're all middle-aged women,
--This is Monston,
a village of carefree monsters.
--Why...?
the strongest one is Namijima-san!
--Oh, that was a dream.
--Who the hell are you?! And that was a dream?!
Robin! Sorry to have kept you waiting!
I'm coming for you now!
Robin has been alone all this time...
just like I used to be.
The more I wish to be with them,
the more I make them suffer.
Th-The pirates are coming here!
We have to go to the Gates of Justice now!
But our paths crossed and we became friends.
I thought it was something I dared not wish for.
You're not alone anymore, Robin-chan.
Franky?
Cutty Flam...
But, Saul...
He's right. You've got Luffy and all of us!
Don't tell me... What you have in your hand is...
...you were right.
We're not gonna let
anyone sacrifice themselves.
I was able to meet friends who will protect me!
Just wait, Robin!
H-Hand those blueprints over to me!
We'll rescue you for sure!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Parting Builds a Man's Character!
Sanji and Chopper"
"Everything Is for Her Friends!
Robin in the Darkness!"
"I'm Not Gonna Hand over
the Blueprints! Franky's Decision"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!