Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Robin!
We're gonna rescue you for sure!
The drawbridge is coming down!
Robin...
It must've been really hard.
But you're not alone anymore.
You've got us.
Nami would never kill Usopp!
We're friends!
Who're friends, Luffy?
Nami!
Why are you here?
What're you talking about?
You're our friend! We came to get you!
You're a big problem.
Nami?
Friends? Don't make me laugh!
You're just a pathetic bunch of
people cooperating with each other.
"A Bond of Friendship Woven
by Tears! Nami's World Map"
You really know how to trash a place.
What's wrong, Nami?
Nothing. I'm just here to rest a little.
Breaking glass and furniture
just to rest is a bit much.
You have that treasure map open,
even though nothing's wrong?
Something happened to make me mad, that's all!
Them, huh? Who are they?
You met them?!
Yeah. Some Captain Something-or-Other.
He seemed kind of liar-ish, though.
I hear you smiled happily when
you were traveling with them.
Even though I haven't
seen you like that in years.
Talk to me! Who are those guys?
We agreed you could tell
me anything, remember?
I had planned to forget about them...
I thought I had erased them from my mind.
Who do you take your friends for?!
I honestly felt like always being
with them, if it were possible.
Now I see...
Yeah, that'd hit you hard.
To think that someone
really showed up for her...
Friends, huh?
The most painful word for her...
What's wrong, girlie?
Do you want me to return
the village that badly?
Then how's this? Let's make an agreement.
Agreement?
That's right.
Gather up 100 million Berries and bring it here.
Do so and I'll let the village
go and give you freedom.
Honest?!
Honest!
I'd die before I'd break an
agreement concerning money.
It doesn't matter how many years
it takes. I'll honor our agreement.
I absolutely will save up 100 million Berries!
Arlong!
Oh? What's wrong, skilled surveyor
of ours? Why the angry look?
The Navy men you have under
your control stole all my money!
What happened to dying before
breaking promises about money?!
Why?!
When did I break our promise?
Don't play dumb! You teamed
up with the Navy to--!
When did I break our promise? Let's hear it!
Damn you... Damn you! Damn you!
I see! So your money's been stolen?
How unfortunate.
But an agreement is an agreement.
If you can't gather up
100 million Berries for me to see,
I'm afraid I can't give you the village back.
Scum!
It's only 100 million Berries!
Just start saving up again!
Or are you gonna run out on me?
But if you do run away, I'll kill
everyone in Cocoyashi Village.
Nami...
We pretended we didn't know.
Because our hopes would keep you
from running away from Arlong
if you ever decided to.
No more of this! Take up
your weapons! Let's fight!
Eight years ago, we swore
not to throw away our lives!
No matter how painful and insulting
it was to be ruled by them,
we swore to fight the patient fight
as long as Nami was cheerful!
But this is their answer!
Now that our village's chance for
freedom is gone, we have no hope!
More than that,
we must make those fishmen pay
for toying with that girl's kindness!
Any objections?!
Of course not! Let's go!
Wait, everyone!
Nami!
Just a little more! Just wait a
little more! I'll work hard again!
I'll save up the money again!
It'll be easy this time!
I'm used to it! I'll be fine!
There's no need to worry at all!
This is nothing compared to back then!
Please, no more dying!
Everyone! I'm fine! I'm just fine!
You can stop now...
Even you know there's no point now...
You fought very well, carrying our
lives on your back all this time...
Joining them must've been
even more painful for you
than being cut through the heart...
You fought very well.
Gen-san...
Leave the village now.
Gen-san?!
Do it, Nami.
W-What?!
Nacchan...
Nami...
You're crafty, and you have a dream.
Nojiko! Everyone!
I won't let you go!
Stop it, everyone! I don't want to
see anyone else get hurt by them!
You'll die, you know!
We know.
It's no use! We've made up our minds!
Get out of our way, Nami!
Let's go, everyone!
Even if we can't win,
let's show 'em what we're made of!
Arlong! Arlong!
Arlong!
Luffy...
What do you want?!
You don't even know anything!
You don't even know what's happened
on this island the past eight years!
Yeah. I don't know.
This has nothing to do with you!
I told you, leave the damn island already!
Yeah. You told me.
Leave! I don't need you!
Leave! Leave! Leave! Leave!
Leave! Leave! Leave!
Leave!
Luffy...
Help me...
Of course I will!
Don't touch my treasure!
Luffy...
Let's go.
Yeah!
What the...?!
Which one of you is Arlong?!
You can no longer escape.
This is the top floor of Arlong Park.
What's this room?
Full of papers...
These're not just ordinary papers.
This room is where I make that
woman draw sea charts. It's...
...the survey room!
Nami's room...
These're all sea charts that Nami drew.
She's going to continue drawing
sea charts! For my ambition!
And once her charts give me full
knowledge of all the world's seas...
...we fishmen will be invincible,
and the world will become our empire!
Our first stepping stone is
this island... and the East Blue!
Could you use the girl as efficiently as that?!
"Use"?!
What's that?!
A desk...
What do you think you're doing?!
What in the...?! There's an
awful lot of stuff flying!
Stop that!
The charts!
M-My charts!
This... is a pretty intense fight!
Yeah! Looks like a fight to the death!
Definitely!
Thank you...
You've gone too far, you damn rubber man!
"Fishmen are great" and "sea charts" this,
"circumstances" that...
I don't know much about any of that stuff...
But I finally figured out how to save her!
She can't go because this room is here!
If she doesn't want to be here,
then I'll just destroy it all!
Gum-Gum...
...Battle-Axe!
Impossible! It's gonna collapse!
This is dangerous! Everyone, get away!
Big Sis Nami! Hurry!
But Luffy's still inside!
--Big Sis!
--Luffy! Luffy's still...!
Luffy!
Luffy...
Which one won?!
Given all this debris... Don't tell me it was--!
Luffy...
Luffy!
Big Bro!
Is he okay?!
Nami!
You're my friend!
Yeah!
My friends helped me.
This time, I'll fight for one of my friends, too.
So, Robin, have faith in us... in Luffy!
He'll respond to your feelings without fail.
Hey, pirates! What're you
guys wasting time for?!
Huh? What's the meaning of that smile?
Here we go!
I knew it!
Nooo!
"Straw Hat Theater"
"Part 3"
[Obahan: Middle-aged Woman]
"If the Straw Hats were
all middle-aged women..."
"...who would be the strongest?!"
"Luffizaki"
Oh, dear! I'm out of soy sauce!
And here I was gonna make
soy sauce meat steak,
meat salad and meat miso soup today...!
"Today's menu
soy sauce meat steak
meat salad (no veggies)
meat miso soup (without soup)"
Pardon me, I'm coming in, okay?
Hey, Zoroyama-san, I'm out of soy sauce.
Now, be a dearie and spare
me some, would you? Whoa!
That gave me a start!
Hey, are you in the middle of training?
Oh, dearie me, if it isn't Luffizaki-san.
My, no, I'm not training.
We're having sashimi today...
...so I was just cutting some raw fish.
My, my, seems like you cut the whole kitchen.
Oh, that's right, soy sauce!
We're... all out, too.
Oh, my, your bottle's been cut in two.
"Supermarket Isoflavone"
Ma'am, you can't do that.
Oh, my word... My word...!
This ham is the bee's knees!
This one with the cheese wrapped
in ham is simply to die for!
Be a dear and get me some jam.
"Sampling"
"Half Price"
"Ham"
Ma'am, you can't bring rice
into the sampling section!
Why?! Come now,
Luffizaki-san does this all the time!
She's always causing us trouble, too!
Can it! Now bring me some
sweet jam for this ham!
Make it sweet and tasty!
It's the grabby fiend, Sanjida!
My, my! Just what is the problem?
We're all ladies here.
Hey, you! Let me touch your butt!
--Enough of that, you two!
--Oh, no, Mellorine...
Oh, good! It's the middle-aged woman
of once-a-month justice, Namijima-san!
She forgets her own faults and tells off
the middle-aged woman pirate gang
once a month for some reason!
Hey, hey, hey, hey...!
Hey, hey, Luffizaki-san!
Have I got news for you!
The supermarket in front of the train
station has some super bargains!
The meat is freakin' cheap, too!
Meat is?! Usokawa-san,
you aren't fooling me, are you?!
Yeah, I was lying. I brought you the circular.
"Circular"
--Oh, phooey!
--But forget that, I have terrible news!
Chopamori-san and Sanjida-san
were caught at the supermarket.
--Ah, I need some tea!
--Oh, dear! Could it be that
Namijima-san is at it again?
Hey, hey, hey...!
Robino-san! Let us hide here!
Namijima-san's gonna kill us!
Oh, my, good timing.
I've been warning you guys
about sorting your trash.
Please stop insisting that
everything is burnable trash.
What's with that nonsense?!
It's burnable if there's enough spirit!
Why, good point, Luffizaki-san! She's right!
It's a matter of spirit... The incinerator's.
What silly nonsense.
Oh? Pickled vegetables?!
Your pickled vegetables are
the best, Robino-san! I love them!
Oh, my! Then let's take a break and have
this barley tea I found in the fridge!
Click.
Hello?
Why, yes, they're here. Sure.
Oh, Robino-san? Who just called?
Namijima-san.
So... mind telling me what
happened to this month's rent?
Big landowner, Namijima-san...
Could you be a dearie and wait
until tomorrow's town raffle event?
No! I'm gonna go to your employers
and collect the money directly from them.
No, Namijima-san! Not that!
Tomorrow is gonna mark the end of our lives!
--Fine by me.
--What?!
Even if they're all middle-aged women,
the strongest one is Namijima-san!
Robin has been alone all this time...
just like I used to be.
But our paths crossed and we became friends.
You're not alone anymore, Robin-chan.
He's right. You've got Luffy and all of us!
We're not gonna let
anyone sacrifice themselves.
Just wait, Robin!
We'll rescue you for sure!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Parting Builds a Man's Character!
Sanji and Chopper"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!