Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Looks like they pulled through. Good timing.
To think that you were going to die alone...
That's heartbreaking, Robin-chan.
I don't want to see people
sacrificing themselves anymore!
I can't think of any reason
for you to be kind to me!
Why...? Why did you?!
"Parting Builds a Man's Character!
Sanji and Chopper"
What happened to your leg?
Without that leg, you won't
be able to be a pirate any more!
I guess...
Why...? I didn't ask for your help!
I can't think of any reason
for you to be kind to me!
Why...? Why did you?!
Because you...
You had the same dream as me.
The All Blue...
But... even your men said it doesn't exist...
Of course it does! When the
time comes, head to the Grand Line.
The All Blue surely exists there.
As you see, I can't be a pirate anymore,
but this time, you can go and find it.
H-Hey! Geezer, don't die!
Don't just do as you please
and die as you please!
That damn geezer gave up
his leg so that I could live.
Wha...?!
I...
I can't repay the damn geezer for his
kindness unless I risk my life for him too!
Dying isn't something you
should do to repay kindness!!
That's not what he saved you for!
Being given life and yet dying...
is something that a weakling would do!
Then is there any other way
to settle this matter?!
Chore boy!!
Chore boy...
Are you all right?!
Ha! I'm not quite done yet...
You made me angry.
I won't let you die so easily.
Dammit! That bastard Krieg brings
out weapons one after another...
There's no way that chore boy can...
Even if hundreds of weapons are built in,
he can be defeated by someone
with a spear of blind determination.
Life or death...
In a pirate battle, if you fear death
for even a moment, you'll fall to pieces.
What're you talking about?
At least...
...that kid doesn't have any hesitation!
Is it a survival instinct...?
Or does he not fear death
because he has faith in himself...?
Faith...
The fleet Krieg gathered...
His hundreds of weapons and poison...
If they're all force...
...then that kid's spear is also force...
The spear held in his heart...
I know an idiot who's holding back
that spear for a stupid reason...
What?!
This is gonna end it... for sure!
Gum-Gum...!
...Giant Gavel!!
--Wait!
--Hm?
We both have foolish dreams.
Hm?
In order to achieve my goal, the All Blue...
Sanji?
Yeah. I'll come along... on your journey
to become "King of the Pirates"!
What?
I'll be the cook for your ship.
Is that okay or not?
It's okay!! All right!!
I'm happy for you, Big Bro Luffy!
Yeah!
Yaay! Yaay! We got a cook!
We'll have good food!
So that's how it is, everyone.
Sorry for causing you all sorts of trouble.
Ha! I don't like it! I wanted to
kick you out from here myself.
And you decide it so easily...?
Sorry for making you resort to bad acting.
You knew?!
I could hear everything, since you're all stupid.
What?!
That is to say, you're willing to go that far
to kick me out, huh, you damn geezer?!
Why do you always have to
talk like that?! You bastard!
Hmph! That's right, little brat!
I don't like kids to begin with.
Not a single day passed where I didn't regret
letting a useless one live, you damn brat.
Ha! Fine by me, you damn geezer!
Enjoy the rest of your life to the utmost.
Whoa! This is a nice ship.
Is it okay for us to use it?
Of course! It's Sanji's boat.
Let's go.
You don't have to say goodbye?
That's okay.
Sanji!
Don't catch cold.
Owner Zeff!!
Thank you for all the damn things
you've done for me over all these years!!
I'll never forget your kindness...
for the rest of my life!!
You asshole!!
I'll miss you, dammit!
I'll miss you!!
I feel sad, dammit!
You idiots!
Men should part without a word.
Let's go!! Set sail!!
I'll see you again, you damn bastards!
As long as you don't fear even death
because you have faith in yourself...
...you'll find the All Blue... for sure...
Guys! Customers are gonna show up soon!
Get to work already!
Robin has been alone all this time...
just like I used to be.
You've been shot? We need to stop
the bleeding right away or you'll die!
You can! You can!
You can! You can be a great doctor...
Doct... I can't breath...
...because you have such a kind heart...
I wonder if Robin didn't
have anyone like Doctor...
Really, there are some strange
creatures in this world.
You must really have spent your
whole life disliked by everyone.
You poor monster. Why's a loner
like you trying to save this country?
Don't make me laugh!
Shut up! Even if I don't
have friends, I can still fight!
As long as Doctor's flag exists, I will...
You do have friends!
I am your friend!
Hey, let's be pirates together! Okay?!
It's not possible.
Yes, it is, since it's fun!
Hey, you don't make sense.
But...
But I'm a reindeer! I have antlers and hooves!
I even have a blue nose!
It's true... that I wanna be a pirate, but...
I'm not even a human! I'm a monster!
I can't become your friend! So...!
So I just came to say thank you...
I do appreciate you guys.
Thank you for asking me to join you.
I'll stay here, but...
...one day... if you feel like it, stop by agai...
Shut up! Let's go!
You don't ask people to join you
by telling them to "shut up."
That felt good! Hey, do it again!
You idiot! We're setting sail right away!
I-I thought I'd die...
Hm? Where am I?!
Ah, Sanji-san! You came to?
Doctor! It wasn't just a fantasy, right?!
Your research was completed then, right?!
Or was that a lie, too?
I did it, Chopper! My research succeeded!
Did you lie because I'd be sad
if you died without saying so?
"Nothing is impossible for the man
who raised a flag with a skull!"
Please say it again, Doctor!
Are you ready, young men?!
--Yes, Ma'am!
--Fire!
Listen, Kureha. This dust is...
Dr. Kureha! What in the world...?
Just shut up and watch.
Dr. Kureha! We shot all of them!
Light them up!
Amazing...
Yeah...
It's so beautiful...
I will make cherry blossoms bloom.
Once my invention is complete,
this country will be saved!
Listen. This red dust isn't ordinary dust.
This will attach to the white snow in the air
and make vivid pink snow fall.
Doctor...!
Doctorine...!
I will never shoot you!
My name is Dr. Hiriluk! I'm a doctor!
Tony Tony Chopper. That's a cool name,
isn't it? That's what I'll call you.
Chopper, you'll be able to become
a good doctor. I'll guarantee it.
Even if I disappear, my dream will come true.
I had... such a good life!
Thank you, Chopper!
Now, have a safe trip, my stupid son...
Robin...!
You're not alone anymore, got that?!
We'll rescue you for sure, so just wait!
The sound of the sea train?
Here we go!
I knew it!
"Straw Hat Theater"
"Part 4"
"Ruthless Time"
--I'm bored.
--Yeah.
"Moai"
"[Bored]"
Bring me some meat or I'm
gonna frickin' kill youse guys!
"Don Luffione, Luffione Family"
Why do I smoke cigars, you ask?
'Cuz the air in this frickin'
world stinks, that's why!
(Dandy)
I called youse guys here today for one reason...
I think it's time we made clear who's
boss of this town once and for all!
It's me, you dumbass!
No way, any idiot would realize it's me!
"Don Zorocia, Zorocia Family"
"Don Sanjino, Sanjino Family"
Sanjino, a bonehead like you who
doesn't even slick his hair back
isn't even qualified to be boss of this town.
I've got my reasons, okay?!
It's slicked back on one side, isn't it?!
One side?! Don't make me laugh! That's like
saying you've got half a pair of balls!
--What'd you say?!
--That's the last straw! This calls for all-out war!
Why the hell are you starting the war?!
Anyway, war it is.
Make him eat lead, Usotooya.
Imma gonna take out Zorocia.
Usotooya failed!
"Usotooya of the Luffione Family died in battle."
Go take out Luffione while he
don't have his men to protect him!
I'm gonna take out Luffione.
Chopalini failed!
"Chopalini of the Sanjino Family died in battle."
Know your enemy well, Namimore.
I'm gonna take out Sanjino.
Mamma mia!
The Sanjino Family has been taken out!
"Don Sanjino of the Sanjino Family
ascended to heaven."
Now, where's his safe?
Oh, wow! He sure was loaded!
Namimore failed!
"Namimore of the Zorocia Family
died from happiness."
Oh, well. She still killed Sanjino.
Robita, go take out Luffione.
--I'm not interested.
--What?!
Zorocia has been betrayed!
"Don Zorocia of the Zorocia Family
died thinking, 'I never thought
my ally would kill me.'"
No! They actually shot each other!
"Robita of the Zorocia Family died thinking,
'It wasn't supposed to be like this.'"
Robita failed!
Hell yeah, I'm the boss!
Now I can stuff myself with as
much meat as I want in this town!
What the hell...
To think that meat tastes
terrible when I eat it by myself...
I... I finally realized just now
what the most important thing is...
I feel lonely... I feel lonely...
If this is a dream, I wanna wake up.
--Oh, that was a dream.
--Who the hell are you?! And that was a dream?!
The more I wish to be with them,
the more I make them suffer.
I thought it was something I dared not wish for.
But, Saul...
...you were right.
I was able to meet friends who will protect me!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Everything Is for Her Friends!
Robin in the Darkness!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!