Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
once attained everything
The words he uttered just before his death
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure?
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
Were going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, its not a legend!
has been verified,
it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
simply ride aboard someone elses biorhythm
and pretend it isnt there!
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
Were going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
and do you wanna be my friend?
A coin in my pocket,
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around
the world to the seas.
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure?
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
I left everything
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Let me go!
Now, what're you gonna do?
You bastard...
Is Lucci that pigeon guy?
Are you mocking me?
Take me to the shore already
so that I can knock you out!
I can see the Gates of Justice now,
Yeah, that's right.
Whoa... I'd expect no less from you.
but is it possible to go there
on a regular boat?
If he's with Robin-chan,
Third Gear!
If you're in that much of a hurry,
I'll show you...
I don't have much time anyway.
I guess I'll try something.
we should
let at least Luffy go on ahead.
You don't have to tell me!
I'll shut you up right here, right now!
...my new powers.
Here we go!
Luffy.
At any rate, you just
beat up the pigeon guy.
Whoa! Pirate guy!
Let me go! Let me go!
It's collapsing!
What're you doing?!
Super Cartwheel, Iron Ball!
There are six of us excluding Luffy.
Oh, shoot!
I'll slam you into the corner of
the tower using this momentum!
I was gonna stop the transformation
He said there are five CP9 members here.
when I reached my human-beast form,
but I became a giraffe!
We'll get the five keys for Robin-chan's
handcuffs from them and go after Luffy.
A talking giraffe is falling towards us!
I see. It indeed looks like
I'll get smashed into pieces.
Sanji-kun...
Were you really
not able to defeat her?
If Robin-kun goes through
the gates, it'll all be over.
Kaku!
Franky Centaur!
Did you really fight seriously?
That power of yours is too cool!
It's all a race against time!
A wolf?!
It was that woman who
you fought, wasn't it?
If we lose against them,
that means we lose time!
What is this place?! A zoo?!
--Chapa!
--I've got both your legs!
You're soft with women.
How dare you all...?
Now you can't move around at will in the air!
Everyone! Take them down
even if it costs you your life!
I'm sorry about the key.
So what?! Even if you do that,
you can't stop this momentum!
Yeah!
Experience the fighting
power of a power holder...!
That's not it!
Good luck!
They opened...
I'm saying that because
of that stupid chivalry,
you're gonna lose your life!
Tempest Kick!
That's not totally true.
Help won't come, Nico Robin.
You're gonna stick to it even
after getting hurt like this?!
70 mm 0.2 Cola Cannon!
A bit of Coup de Vent!
What're you gonna do if you die?!
--Huh?!
--All right! I'm heading there now!
Whoa! What's that?!
They don't know how to get to the
Gates of Justice in the first place!
It's not like...
He's gonna do something!
I want to die.
What?! How come you're small now?!
Sky Slicer!
Ahh! The momentum has died down!
But
I grew up having the idea that
I shouldn't kick women beat into me.
The rotation stopped! Damn you!
Oops!
This isn't good.
Come out! You pigeon jerk!
So...
Duck, Usopp!
But this is enough!
We're already above the shore!
All right! My body's back to normal!
even if it costs me my life...
Just wait, Robin!
Now, take this!
...I won't kick a woman!
I'll be sure to beat the crap
out of that pigeon guy!
70 mm 1.5 Max Cola Power!
Chapapapapa...
Solid Beast Secret Technique...
Coup de...
I'm Silent Fukurou! I like rumors!
What're you doing?!
You're a fool.
Fool!
...Owl Thrashing!
Hey! What're you doing, Nami?!
Do you want the key?
Dammit!
I still haven't refilled my cola yet!
If running away is also
against your chivalry,
Give up already, you bastard!
Chapapapapa!
Chapa...!
at least ditch that chivalry!
Coup de...
Beans Left!
"I Won't Kick Even If It Costs
Me My Life! Sanji's Chivalry!"
It's not worth dying in vain over.
...Vent!
Yoyoi!
Leave that woman to me.
You damn pirate!
Also...
Super!
You're doomed now that
I've caught you here!
What was that?!
I think a little more of
your chivalry than I did before.
What?!
Did she just say
that she loves me more?
Ahh! This is terrible!
That's right! He's on our side right now!
I see...
No, she didn't!
They must've gotten scared of me...
The point is the length--
in other words, the reach.
I'll do what he told me to.
Ahhh...!
That's cola! Cola without doubt!
With the power coming from that huge
body in addition to centrifugal force,
Someone's here!
What about this room?!
I'm not kind.
his attack is deeper
and sharper than before.
Thanks!
Yoyoi!
Super!
Neither am I.
Dammit...
That voice... Don't tell me
he broke the fridge door...
Sounds like we can get along.
No one's here, either.
Wh-What the heck?!
Hey, I don't see any damage.
Chapapa... What's the deal?
Look at the ceiling.
I... I... I... I...
It's not like drinking cola would
make a difference or anything.
Huh? The ceiling?
Oh?
I... I... I... I... I...
Please make yourself at home.
I can see the blue sky.
Guard yourself.
Chapa? What a fool.
Whoa...
Yoyoi!
Are you gonna give me another pathetic punch?
I wonder why... Hm...?
I had a feast!
Hold it!
Don't tell me the Tower
of Law has been cut in two!
The octopus guy!
Strong... Hammer!
I won't...
I won't let you get away!
He got a little fatter!
Hey, hey, hey, hey...!
This is dangerous!
Just how much stuff in that fridge did you eat?!
Agh!
"Devil Fruit Powers!
Kaku and Jabra Transform"
How shameful!
Nami, you go deal with that woman!
I'll do something about this guy!
To think that you showed
your emotions in a battle!
--Hm?
--That's...
Shut up.
Okay!
Yooo!
I like being a giraffe.
Yoi! Yoi! Yoyoyoi!
Yoyoi...! Yoyoi!
I love giraffes.
Are you going to be in my way?!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Cloven...
Now... are you...
Whoooa! Amazing!
Cross!
Even if your attacks are sharp,
Snap!
that's not threatening to me at all.
Listen, Sogeking. Don't lose your posture.
...prepared?!
You are a sword!
S-Stop it, Zoro!
Someone get me a lawyer! I'll sue you for sure!
Prepared?!
That hurts! What're you doing?!
Why are you pulling my arm?!
No matter how I look at it,
I'm at a disadvantage.
Obtaining the key is my
priority here! Okay, then!
Huh...? Pulling my arm?
Suit yourself.
How dare she?!
Sorry. My punches earlier
were indeed pathetic.
I'm gonna try this out first, okay?
Hey, assassin! Where's the key?!
She got away again!
What? What?
Ahh! This is a dream! This is a dream!
If you don't know...
You're dealing with me!
Whoa! It's locked tight!
Come on!
Yeah, it is.
Morning, come already!
...I'll tell you where!
"Zoro Busts Out a New Technique!
The Sword's Name is Sogeking?"
Those guys sure do some weird stuff.
"Fukurou's Miscalculation!
My Cola Is the Water of Life"
Hey! What're you doing?!
The key is...
It's not my fault, is it?!
Yep, yep. The key is...?
This is interesting!
This happened because you charged at me!
The key is...
I did that because you were standing
there in a daze when he attacked!
Yes, yes. And...?
Just unlock these handcuffs!
The key is...
Oni...
I'm listening!
Hey! Wait! Hey! Are you really gonna do it?!
...right here!
You're the demon here!
What're those guys doing?
Seriously, there's no way you can cross
water like this on a boat, now is there?
...Giri!
Oh...?!
Beats me.
Where did my key go?!
Are you an idiot?!
To put it simply,
this means that we're
in the same situation as Robin is.
But Robin was taken to those gates!
Ow, ow, ow... Stars are coming out of my eyes.
He's loud, and a pain to boot.
Oh, that's right. Franky, I want
to tell you something while I can.
Then, the key is...
Unless I hurry up, I won't
be able to bring her back!
...in the hands of one
of the CP9 members.
Just don't move!
Tiger....
We have no choice but to get
the key by defeating them.
Hm?
Huh? Tiger? Tiger?
I'm in trouble! I'm in trouble!
Zoro and Sogeking got connected
by Sea Prism Stone handcuffs, and...
Don't be unreasonable!
There's no way we can fight like this!
That's no good.
What?
I should be able to reach the
building right in front of it, right?
Dammit!
Mademoiselle.
Our prey got connected.
That water is too lukewarm
to make good tea.
Okay then, Jabra.
That hit me good. Stars are
coming out of my nose, too.
Hey! What're you doing?!
Just stay back
and leave those two to me.
Wait, pirate guy!
I said don't move!
Calm down!
If I can't cross the sea,
then I have no choice but to jump!
Don't be unreasonable!
Are you trying to kill me?!
What?! Are you trying to steal my prey?!
Here are the golden rules
for making black tea.
Are they idiots?
We came to tell you how to
get to the Gates of Justice!
First, boil fresh water
Are they going to fight us seriously?
Then, do you want us to work
together and fight them?
and pour it into a teapot
that was warmed beforehand.
After all, it seems like we have no
choice but to play rock-paper-scissors.
What?
Even if it costs me my life,
the answer is no.
When coin-size bubbles start appearing,
that's when you should stop heating it.
And I'll cut off the hand of the loser.
Me, neither.
Wait! Like I said, don't you
have any better ideas?!
Hey, you two!
What?!
By doing so,
Then we can't do anything unless
we find that #2 key first?!
the leaves move around
due to the circulation of hot water,
Tell us the number on those handcuffs.
Number?
No, I don't.
which brings out their scent and color.
The handcuffs and the keys have numbers
You don't have to be so blunt!
Yeah. That's right.
Then, cover the teapot
immediately and steam it well.
How stupid...
This is no time for stupid arguments.
so that we know which key
unlocks which handcuffs.
Well, at least I know what's going on.
If those handcuffs can be unlocked
by one of the keys we have,
Once it's done,
pour it into warmed teacups.
What's this place?
we'll unlock them right away.
A basement?
What?! Really?!
Just give it up, nose.
It's an undersea passage.
Just a little bit of consideration
makes a difference in the taste.
Chapa!
To get to the
Gates of Justice, you go under the sea.
The number... Where's the number?
"Just give it up, nose"?
Here it is! It's 2!
Chopper! Please hurry up!
You sure do know your stuff.
I'm really angry now! Chapapa!
Unlock these!
I see.
I'm a cook, so...
Okay, then!
Not the right one.
Hey, wait!
Do you know how to get there?!
Thanks for the lesson.
Mine isn't, either.
"Uncontrollable! Chopper's Forbidden Rumble"
He sure is tough. He's up now.
Sorry.
What?! You got my hopes up, you jerks!
You're so beautiful!
Dammit!
Stay there and watch.
Then, it means one of the other three
CP9 members has the right one, huh?
In any case, you're amazing.
Franky...
I'm impressed that you knew
about a passage like this!
It can't be helped.
The early bird gets to kill the worm.
I saw Lucci's servant going down
the stairs laughing very loudly.
Seems like that's the only way.
...Destroyer Cannon!
Yoyoi!
Wow...
This is probably the place.
What?!
Ow, ow, ow...! I don't like this attack
because it dislocates my joints!
I finally made it.
So I followed them.
Yoyoi!
"The servant"
I had to go
up and down all those stairs.
What?!
What?! You shouldn't do it, then!
If they don't know where the entrance is,
they can't come after us!
Robin!
Chapapa! What a moron.
Hey! Robin!
Serves them right!
I've never seen anyone with
so little self-discipline as him.
I'm a Six Powers master.
Cannonballs would never hit me!
Lucci and that black-haired lady
went through the doors, too.
It's me!
To think that he gained weight in the
few minutes I took my eyes off of him...
Whoa! What's with these stairs?!
Robin!
No matter how much you run around,
They're sliced in two and shifted.
You don't... need to be...
need to be... need to be...
Where are you?!
you can't escape from my
Franky Destroyer Cannon...
Dammit!
The impact from earlier...
So they really did leave already.
...because it's got chasing cannonballs!
As I suspected,
something must've happened.
I'm not concerned! Just speak normally!
Is this building okay?
That damn pigeon guy!
Chasing cannonballs?!
Oh, yeah...!
That's "need to be concerned," right?!
So these are the ones, huh?
Could it be that the cannonballs
sense the enemy and follow them?!
I know where they're headed.
Well...
Thank you!
So I just have to head to the
Gates of Justice, too, right?!
These are quite strong iron doors.
That's exactly what I was... I was... I was...
Do you know how to open them?
Hey! Are you okay?!
You have the key
to Robin's handcuffs, right?
The servant was touching around here,
I got it, so you can cut that out!
Anyway, there's no need
to be concerned, then?
Want to give it to me
before I take you down?
so I bet you can operate
them with this keyhole...
Come back here!
That's a foolish question.
I've never heard of such technology!
I was... I was... That's right!
...though we don't have the key.
Ah! Zoro! Sogeking!
I was disappointed that I didn't
get to see your real ability
What the heck is he?
As for why...
at the Galley-La mansion.
Ah! Hey! Chopper!
I never thought that pirates
would come this far, either, so...
...just look! Life Return!
Huh?
What's going on? They're waving to me.
You guys, stay back.
Hold it!
Huh? What're you gonna do?
It looks kinda fun.
So it's you who chases the enemy?!
Be careful, as I'm far
stronger than that time.
Wh-What the heck?!
You jerk! Hold it!
H-Hey, guys!
Digest!
We can go to the Gates of
Justice through here, right?
I can imagine,
with all that energy you've got...
Absorb!
Er... Yeah...
Idiot!
Chapapa... I'm being fooled! That bastard!
Energy like that of a beast.
Now, I'm back to normal!
Pay attention to these handcuffs!
Find the key for handcuffs #2!
Ahhh! What?! What are you?!
What a fearsome man you are.
Huh? A key?
But
What did you just do?!
my swordsmanship is the best in CP9.
Do it again.
He disappeared again.
If you wish...
Don't underestimate me.
Third Gear!
What the hell is this?!
Where are you hiding?!
Two-Sword Style, huh?
Life Return!
I just assumed that there'd
be a bridge or something.
It's no use searching for me.
Digest!
I'm an expert at Shave, one of the Six Powers.
Absorb!
What crazy huge swirls!
Tempest Kick.
Amazing! One more time!
In addition to my lightning speed,
I can see the Gates of Justice now,
but is it possible to go
there on a regular boat?
O-One more time?
I make no noise when moving about,
just like owls when they hunt.
I don't have much time anyway.
Life Return!
I guess I'll try something.
Digest!
I carry out a perfect assassination.
Here we go!
So, no... Sorry, but I use four swords.
Absorb!
Just wait, Robin!
No problem.
Come to think of it,
your entire body is a weapon.
You're amazing! How does that work?!
Yaay! Yaay!
An owl, huh?
I've found the path to those gates!
My target won't see me until
the very moment he gets killed.
Glad you asked!
I'm gonna tell everyone!
A thousand years at sea, and a
thousand years in the mountains...
Ooops!
Take this!
That was close!
Breathing in the wind and drinking dewdrops,
He was hiding here.
They opened...
I trained myself, living as a hermit!
Looks like that attack caught
you completely off guard, huh?
What's this?
After all that, I've... I've... I've...
I've acquired this "Life Return"!
How impertinent!
I've never experienced such humiliation!
Stare...
I'm a CP9 member!
All right! I'm heading there now!
Stare...
Essentially, if you extend
your consciousness everywhere,
What?! How come you're small now?!
Shave!
Th-This is...
from your hair to your internal organs,
toes, even the tip of your downy hair,
Don't tell me...
Whoa!
Iron Ball!
there's no part of your body
that you can't manipulate.
Click.
Seventy-two...
Ahhh! What's going on?!
Tempest Kick.
Ah! Watch out!
Extending your consciousness
even to the tip of your hair?
--...Pound Phoenix!
--White Thunder!
That pirate guy sure is interesting!
Dammit! We're above the sea!
I've read about that kind
of ability in a book before.
It's called something like biofeedback...
Shave!
Now, let's get back to work, too!
All right!
Then your hair moves around like
an octopus because of that ability?!
I found another secret passage!
Franky!
I-I just heard a loud noise.
Yoyoyoi! An octopus?! How terribly rude!
Was that my imagination?
No, it couldn't have been.
Yaay!
This is terrible!
Could that noise have been one of
the pirates destroying the doors?
Where are we?!
If he gets swept away...
Call me... a valiant...
What?! That's not possible!
...he'll be headed straight
to the basin of the waterfall!
Those are thick iron doors!
This is fun!
Since he's in the sea, I can't go rescue him.
...lion... will... will you?!
Whoa! Pirate guy!
Besides, there's no way that
they could find those doors!
What're you doing?!
Franky! Hang in there!
I don't have time to have fun!
Well, they should know where they are,
since a child and her pet were following us.
Why does it matter which one?
Then you just have to take me down.
I see.
Chapapa!
What?!
Life Return!
So the handcuffs and the keys
have numbers on them.
Even if I get thrown into the
waterfall, I can use Moon Walk.
I-If you knew that,
why didn't you kill them?!
Hair Bind!
Tempest Kick.
Slaughter!
What?!
This is bad! I can't stop falling!
That's what's happening here?
Then I'll fight those guys!
Because...
What a strong current! I can't
keep holding my breath, either!
Don't be ridiculous!
Yoyoi!
...I was given no such order.
There are
two of them! If you get taken out,
Wh...
I have to go up, at any rate!
with these handcuffs on, we won't
be able to do anything but get killed!
Chapapa! Sink deep!
What?! You idiot!
For something so trivial,
use your own discretion!
Please! You're our only hope!
To think that he uses
slashing attacks so freely...
Can't you tell what'll happen if
you don't do anything about it?!
Hope?
Yoyoyoi!
It's not like I'm
happy to hear that, you jerk!
So what're you saying?!
Are you saying that
someone's headed this way?!
Sanji, Nami, and Franky...
Yoyoi!
I would say that's the case.
Dammit!
If any of them
get the #2 key, bring it here right away!
That voice... Don't tell me
he broke the fridge door...
Ahh! I'm scared!
If I get caught by that, it'll be all over for me!
You bastard... Are you mocking me?
Oh, shut up!
We're counting on you!
Shave!
Oh, that was me.
Whoa... I'd expect no less from you.
Where did he go?!
The one who's likely to get
the key first is... Maybe Sanji?
Listen, Lucci!
If you're in that much
of a hurry, I'll show you...
Your main priority
is to protect my life!
I... I... I... I...
...my new powers.
I'll go look for Sanji.
Finger Pistol! Q!
You got that?!
I... I... I... I... I...
Also, kill anyone
who tries to get in my way!
I'm their only hope!
Defying me is an act of rebellion
against the World Government!
When that stick doesn't
even have a pointed tip...
I had a feast!
They deserve to be killed!
Q! Q! Q!
Now...
He got a little fatter!
Heavy Gong!
Huh?! What's that look?!
...I've caught you!
Iron Body!
Just how much stuff in that fridge did you eat?!
Yoi!
Wh... What the hell?!
Let me go!
Ow, ow, ow...
You have no time to worry
about others, Nico Robin.
What's the matter?!
Yoyoi!
Just...
Hell is already around the corner.
give up!
I don't wanna drown in a place like this!
Lucci! Bring her already.
Dammit!
As I thought, he won't budge unless
I attack with Arm Point or Horn Point.
Ahhh! I'm almost at the basin of the falls!
At any rate, what the heck is this room?
Die!
I'll die! I'll die! I'm falling! Ahhh!
But rumble balls are potent drugs.
Franky Butterfly!
One in six hours is a proper dosage.
No matter how you look at it,
someone went nuts on the gardening.
If I take more than that,
it'll be a huge strain on my body.
I'm no match for him at all!
This is practically outside!
No, no...
On top of that... the second one will
alter the transformation wavelength,
More importantly, I have to get
the key to Robin's handcuffs right now!
Franky...
and so it'll be hard to
control my transformations.
That key...!
All right! My body's back to normal!
Chapapa! I'm not gonna let you do that!
Iron Body!
...Boxing!
With the third one, I'll lose consciousness
and hardly be able to fight.
Tiptoe...
Moon Walk!
Just wait, Robin!
Tiptoe...
What do I do? I can take just
one more and get strengthened.
No need to hesitate!
Shave!
I'll be sure to beat the crap
out of that pigeon guy!
Solid Beast!
Carefully, tiptoe...
What's with your punches?
I'll roast you on a skewer!
You're no ordinary human!
Move step by step
without making noise...
No matter how much you harden
your body to make it like iron,
That son of a bitch!
Well, it was his own fault
that Sanji-kun lost...
Shishi Kabob!
my fists are real iron.
...but what in the world
did she do to him?
Hiyaaa!
Yoi! Yoi!
"Wolf"
N-No!
--Chapa!
--Weapons Left!
That was close!
Yoi!
This is no time for having tea!
Okay, I'll try again!
Paper Art!
If I quietly grab it,
Witchcraft!
I was drawn in by your witchcraft!
Slime!
then quietly run away...
If I don't do anything, I'm just wasting time!
I almost got swept up in a
high tide called "love trap"!
Chapapa.
I'll accomplish my mission.
Rumble!
Dammit! What the hell was that?!
It'll be a victory without wounds!
This is high-risk, but it'll give me a chance!
That's right.
You've already had three cups.
--Yoyoi!
--This is all or nothing!
I'm a lucky king!
Oh, so close!
Shut up, witch!
I'll somehow settle this within three minutes!
This is really bad.
I'm not gonna
be caught in a trap again!
Take this! Horn Point!
At any rate, I'd better get to the shore!
CP9 insulted Robin-chan
terribly on the sea train.
1.0 Cola Cannon! Coup de Boo!
--What?!
--Yoyoi!
I'm not gonna forget about it.
Wrong one!
What's with this woman?
Ow, ow, ow...!
Kabob!
Hey, heart!
Chapa.
Now...
You're beating too loud!
Did you learn your lesson?
She's got some nerve.
Jumping Point!
It takes more than just strength
to defeat a Six Powers master!
give me the key!
Stop!
Ah! Wrong one!
--Strong Hammer!
--Paper Art.
That's too bad...
It seems like you're in a hurry.
Ahh! My heart stopped!
Go ahead and take the key.
H-Hey! What're you doing?!
Start beating!
Fall into the falls!
Yoyoi! Yoyoi!
You can't stop!
Oh, yeah, at a time like this,
I have to perform a heart massage!
Strong Right!
Where is it?
Well...
What...?
Where on my body do you think I hid it?
What?!
Boy, that scared me.
As I was afraid, I can't control
my transformations. Dammit!
Calm down. Calm down.
Now, come!
Dammit! When I have to refill
my cola as soon as possible...
Why don't you try finding it?
Do your best!
If only I could somehow use Arm Point,
I'm a man who makes
everything he does work out...
I could give him a cloven
attack with all my might!
I'd be happy to!
For someone with such a large body,
he sure does like to jump around.
...probably...
This room is dangerous with the fire spreading.
This is no time for me to be stuck
with a guy with no key on him!
That was a bad start, huh?
I can do it...
You stupid Sanji.
Chapapa... I'm right here.
I can do it...
I'd better hurry up and get the #2 key...
I can do...
Wh-What?! A bee?!
Stay away! Go away! Huh?
Seems like you're at least quick
when it comes to escaping.
...and free Zoro and Sogeking!
What're you doing?!
Chapapa...
The tip of my nose
isn't a flower!
I'm under no obligation
to take your proud punches.
Or we can't rescue Robin!
There's no honey there!
Chapa!
Go somewhere else!
Franky Triangle Jacker!
That's right... Robin...
I'm saying go somewhere else!
Let go of me, you bastard!
Moon Walk with just one leg
can't support two people!
That's right! I'm...
Chapapa.
I'm...
No way...
Nico Robin is steadily
approaching the Gates of Justice
I'm fighting in order to save our friend!
We're gonna fall!
Wh-Why are you looking at me?
What's with that sparkle in your eyes?!
I'd get
hit by sideburns like that!
Yeah, seems like it.
D-Don't tell me... you're going to...
Don't do it! Don't!
I've got you!
while we're here fighting like this.
So why don't you bring both of us
back to the shore before we fall?
Don't! Don't!
What a tough animal!
Weapons Left!
Or maybe should I say that from
her perspective, she's approaching hell?
Life Return!
My nose! My nose!
Or do you wanna try fighting me
while supporting our weight?
It hurts!
I know that.
That's right.
Seems like I'm almost out of cola.
Robin-chan's life is at stake!
It's clear how it'll turn out,
Dammit!
I'd better go to the kitchen now!
but in that case, my life will be in danger, too.
If you're gonna be in my way,
I came back to where I was earlier.
Hold it!
I won't go easy on you,
even if you are a woman!
Dammit! He dodged my attack!
At any rate, to think that he
still hasn't woken up yet...
His hair changed into the shape of hands!
Hand over that key to me
before you get hurt!
We're certainly in the same boat.
Let's go back to the shore.
Damn wimp, you're an
expert at running away!
He's quite a sleepyhead.
I have to do it! I can't be
defeated in a place like this!
Chapa!
If I take the time to do it properly,
it'll be fine this time for sure!
What'd you say?!
I'm their only hope!
Even if you shout,
the key won't turn up.
Shishi Finger Pistol!
What's the matter, wimp?
Okay! That's right!
You don't have to treat me
like I'm a woman.
You're not running away this time?
Good job, good job.
Tiptoe...
You bastard!
Let's go back to the shore together.
I don't live in such a delicate world.
Tiptoe...
You made me mad with that word!
Chapapa! But I think the fight
will end the moment we get there.
Tiptoe, tiptoe...
Since we've got an annihilation order,
Take my killer fist!
I'll just take your life,
that's all.
Oh? You think so?
It's a super heavy punch combined
with Finger Pistol's speed!
Chapapapapapa!
Solid Beast!
Yeah, because I just thought of a way
to finish you off with just one blow.
I won't let you take my life.
What I want is...
Oh? So did I, Fukurou-kun.
Chapapa...!
...the key to Robin-chan's handcuffs.
Tiptoe...
Such a modest, ineffective punch...
Chapa...
Then I guess teatime is over?
Strong...
Iron Body!
I'm almost there...
Shave!
...Hammer!
I'm almost there...
I'm almost there...!
Your power is indeed
that of a superhuman.
That was a pathetic punch.
Robin! Robin! Can you hear me?!
Solid Beast!
A-A chicken this time?!
Yoyoi!
We're gonna rescue you for sure!
Showing mercy is never... part of a lion's fury!
Oh, no! What is the noisiest
bird of them all doing here?
We're gonna rescue you for sure. We promised.
We'll take you back no matter what!
Oh, no!
If it crows, it's all over!
Ouch...
Robin!
If it crows, he'll get up,
find me, and kill me!
An opening!
Taking the second rumble ball is like gambling.
Hey
What're you looking at?!
Your punches are flabby.
Are you trying to crow?
Are you?! Are you?!
There are seven transformations in total.
I landed a blow.
Shhh! Shhh!
In other words, the probability of
getting Arm Point is one in seven.
No.
Isn't the #2 key here yet?
Chicken-kun! Chicken-san!
Chicken-sama! Please!
Your punches are limp.
Zoro-kun! This is it for me! I'm exhausted.
Please don't crow!
Ow!
Then, your punches are flimsy.
Don't crow!
Don't! Don't!
Carry me on your back.
If I could get it, I could hammer
my strongest attack into him.
Why would I?!
Your underpants are lazy.
No chicken would crow like that!
Tempest Kick.
Hey! How could you?!
That's my only chance!
Underpants?
Oh, you're here, pirate.
Isn't that what you call
"landing a blow"?
Arm Point!
Th-That damn chicken!
Shishi Kabob!
Finger Pistol!
They're not punches!
Well then, why don't
I give you a beatdown?
How dare you...? You little...
What're you doing?!
Underpants! That's what you are!
That damn chicken!
You just aimed at me while pretending
to attack those two, didn't you?!
Moon Walk!
You damn bra jerk!
Shut up, socks!
Long johns!
That's a false accusation,
but if you want, we can fight.
For my friends... Arm Point!
Loose shorts!
Loincloth!
Chapapapapa!
I've been frustrated for a while now
that you've been in my way.
Yoyoi!
Arm Point!
What'd you say?! That's what I
wanna say, you stupid herbivore!
Yoyoi!
No, I'd have to say I prefer meat.
Wrong one!
Wrong one! Why doesn't it come out?!
Get off of me, you bastard!
Giraffes should just eat tree leaves!
Shut up, change purse!
My body is at the end of its rope.
I somehow have to get Arm Point out!
H-He's strong...
All right!
I was able to enter the kitchen!
Looks like we can't avoid fighting, huh?
Yoyoi!
So you're the one who came?!
There it is! A huge refrigerator!
Okay, then, you just wait here.
I'll go kill our prey.
Hm?
He's fast!
You're the one who shot through
the Government flag, right?
--Yoyoi!
--Whoa!
I've just stomped you.
"Liquor"
Don't worry. It won't take long.
It's out! I didn't notice it!
That means you lost!
Wait! I don't object to us fighting,
but I won't let you have my prey!
Be prepared!
Now, give the key to...
It seems that you're skilled at sniping.
I'll put everything I have
into this... into this attack!
Is that him?
Finger Pistol!
A gorilla
power holder... probably...
Wow, I'm so curious!
Dammit!
Cloven...
Zoro-kun, which do you think is stronger,
Mr. Giraffe or Mr. Wolf?
Three minutes have already passed?
Shishi Finger Pistol!
Tempest Kick!
He delivered a punch like that
right after he woke up?
I used the rumble ball too soon.
Sorry for attacking you half-assed.
Hm?
What am I gonna do?
What a disappointing guy.
Don't you wanna see?
Forgive me.
--Not really.
--I see! So you wanna see their fight, too, huh?!
Yoyoi!
You're a pirate...
If I back off now, I won't get another chance!
It must've hurt.
...and yet, you're quite the coward!
Disappear from this world!
Cloven...
Hey, shut up!
No, like I said...
Iron Body! Strength!
Leave things to me here.
This is the finishing blow!
Give me the key!
"Liquor"
...Roseo Metel!
Zoro-kun used to be a
well-known pirate hunter,
Yoyo...!
Huh?
I've had enough of your
transparent threats.
Don't worry.
You bastard!
and is now the swordsman of the Luffy Pirates.
According to his prediction...
I may not look like it,
but I'm not into tormenting my opponent.
Good! It's got a lock!
Go down!
Oh, I see! He says the wolf is stronger after all!
Chapa! Kumadori!
That was my best attack!
A-A devil fruit...!
Shall I try something fun on you?
That's just natural.
All right! I locked him in!
The Dog-Dog Fruit, Model Wolf!
Unless you fight back,
you won't survive.
How dare you...?
What is it? I see. Still, it's hard
to ignore Mr. Giraffe, he says.
Hey, hold on a sec, gorilla!
I'll just tear up your windpipe
and that'll be it.
Ahh...
I need that fridge!
You'll die anyway.
I see, I see. That Sky Slicer, was it?
That was incredible, wasn't it?
Ahh! CP9 and the punk!
You don't have to suffer.
I'm Franky! I'm on your side, remember?!
Isn't that right?
He's not coming after me...
Ahh... Splendid...!
Who'd you call a gorilla?!
W-Wolf...!
They know their stuff.
You're too slow!
Listen.
It was indeed a beautiful blizzard of...
cherry blossom petals.
Wolves are just sly, that's all.
The fact is, they aren't that capable at all.
Just like Luffy,
I haven't forgiven you yet.
D-Dammit!
Good!
What?! Are you gonna fight?
If I had gotten caught again,
I would've been killed.
The reason Usopp left us was...
You son of a bitch! I can't take it anymore!
You don't look strong, though.
I'll just run and...
S-Strong or not, I'm gonna fight!
Do you wanna fight right here right now?
It all goes back to you!
I can't...
Life Return!
Good, good. All right,
now is our chance, Zoro-kun.
Give us Usopp back!
Shut up!
I can't...
Like I said, you guys
were with him earlier.
Oh, I see!
I came to rescue Robin!
Yoyoi! Yoi! Yoi! Yoyoi!
It'd be good for us if we can get
them to fight and kill each other.
Did I do it?
That's not important right now!
Don't you wanna save Nico Robin?!
Whoa! The ceiling is...
At the least, we'll get a chance
to run while they're fighting, huh?
Oh, shoot!
I do! Robin!
Now, shall I...
...collapsing!
Hey! You're just noticing it now?!
Then get three bottles of cola from
that fridge and give them to me!
And don't say it so clearly!
I can't bear it anymore!
Oh, shoot!
...pierce you to death
I was gonna
stop the transformation
With cola, I can power up!
We almost got tricked into it.
I will give you hell! Yoyoyoi yoi!
when I reached my human-beast form,
but I became a giraffe!
or choke you to death?!
I'll take care of these guys in
an instant and take their keys!
A talking giraffe is falling towards us!
Our prey come first, after all.
In this life, a cold wintry wind blows.
Zoro-kun! What do I do with you?
What kind of idiot actually
gets stronger with cola?
Kaku!
You will die here peacefully
before the spring comes.
That power of yours is too cool!
Shut up! That'd be me!
You completely ruined my plan!
Tempest Kick! Lotus!
A wolf?!
It wasn't that great of a
plan from the start, was it?
Just how long...
What is this place?! A zoo?!
are you gonna
keep up the comedy act?!
Ah! Here is survival plan #2!
This is it... I no longer have
energy left to fight back.
On top of that, you were trying to
have a tea break during a battle?
Zoro-kun. Please make sure you
keep your mouth shut this time.
I'll at least let you bloom
in lovely bright red petals
one more time
How rude!
Chopper!
I wonder which one is cool, a giraffe or a wolf?!
Solid Beast Secret Technique...
Chopper, what in the world did you do?
The Ox-Ox Fruit, Model Giraffe!
before you fall!
Hm?
That's my compassion!
Being strong isn't enough!
...Owl Thrashing!
I don't remember.
You poor guy!
To think that you'll be
a giraffe-man for the rest of your life!
True strength means one is beautiful and cool!
Chapapapapa!
"I don't remember" doesn't cut it.
What's wrong with giraffes?!
Beans Left!
I said I like it!
When you arrive in the afterlife,
It was good that no one died, at least.
Hmm, I wonder which one.
That pigeon guy
was a leopard, wasn't he?
please tell my late mother...
Even while you were sleeping,
Hmm, he indeed has a point.
To think that there are two more power
holders who transform into animals...
the entire country was making
a big fuss about that night.
...that I'm... I'm doing fine...
What was that?!
There's nothing to discuss. It's obvious
that wolves are stronger and cooler.
How are we going to settle that?
Is CP9 that kind of group?
killing people!
So I did something that terrible?
Ahh! This is terrible!
What're you saying?!
That's right!
He's on our side right now!
Now, die!
S-So he is a Zoan-type power holder...
You almost destroyed an entire village.
Giraffes are definitely more popular
among kids in a zoo than wolves!
I'll do what he told me to.
It's fine that you love experiments,
just like your old man did,
Now... Now... Now!
A wolf-man and a giraffe-man?
What crazy guys we're facing!
but for something like that, you have
to do it only after thorough planning.
So giraffes are cooler!
If I open and close the door
within a second, he can't come out!
No!
Song of Spring Feeling!
But it was good that Zoro
fell with that giraffe.
As expected, it seems we
fight like cats and dogs.
Thorough planning...
Yoyoi!
I'm a giraffe, okay? Not a cat.
While it appears to be a
two-versus-two fight, I'll just wait for Zoro...
The door has...
Hoofprint... Roseo!
You were not doing it for
fun at all. I know that much.
...to pretty much take them both down.
"I said I like it"?!
Now is our chance, Zoro-kun!
All right!
Franky!
But that's exactly why you
need to be even more careful.
A trick like that won't last for long.
I'm sure you do!
Thanks!
Th-Then are you saying that
you've got a different plan?
Giraffes are cool, aren't they?!
Wh-What're you talking that way for?!
We'll play rock-paper-scissors, Sogeking.
Nami! Are you okay?!
At any rate, for comrades,
they sure don't work together.
Doctors are always
entrusted with people's lives.
--What?
--The problem is these handcuffs.
Fresh!
There's a way to get them off of us.
Chopper...
Thanks. You saved me.
Small mistakes can become irreversible.
What?! Does it have anything to do
with playing rock-paper-scissors?
What's that?
What the...?
What's with that guy?
It looks like a safe
with the door left opened.
Is he a power holder?
We're always walking on
the edge of a cliff like that.
I'll cut off the hand of the loser.
Whoa!
I don't know.
Freshness is most important!
Vegetable Punch! Take this!
Could those
weird-looking handcuffs be...?!
His hair moves like
an octopus, so I can't do anything.
If you can't even imagine what kind of result
Solid Beast.
Wh-What's with you coming up with
such a scary idea with a serious look?!
I said don't laugh!
More importantly,
now is our chance, Chopper.
careless actions can cause, then you
should give up on becoming a doctor.
Hey, giraffe!
Hey! That was vegetable juice!
I'm not done! Listen further!
Let's get out of here right away.
Just how long are you gonna
stand there arguing with him?
Why?!
So the one who got the handcuffs off like that
I thought I told you
that I don't have much time.
Why would I want health to
be a priority, you bastard?!
Unless we defeat him,
we can't get the key.
will hurry to Chopper with the cut-off hand
Give me cola!
You mean this, right?
If it's okay for you to stay like that,
I'll just cut you down like that.
Oh, so it wasn't because he was thirsty.
and have Chopper put it back
by re-connecting it to his wrist!
Yoyoi! The door...
I stole the key without him noticing,
but I just couldn't get away from him.
How foolish... Don't underestimate a
giraffe's limitless destructive power!
Seriously, you inherited
everything from that quack,
We're not stuffed animals! Don't be ridiculous!
Here you go!
Thanks!
Do you know what's going on
with the others?
including his predisposition for causing a fuss.
Say, Nami.
Transform...
What number does it have on it?
Human-beast form!
I'm feeling good!
I've got another idea.
Number?
It says 3.
Ahh! Ahh! I don't wanna hear it!
I'll show you
Wrong one.
The world always has its
troublesome seeds, huh?
What is this number?
Well...
the power I gained when I was reborn!
I'm tired of arguing.
...let me sit.
I'm sorry, Doctorine.
My work in
the field is done for now.
I can start anytime. The winner can
keep the prey all to himself, so...
Something fell down!
I won't do it again.
Stop being so upset.
I'll never do it again,
so please don't kick me out.
Is this... a doll?!
Don't fight.
Why don't you have some tea?
No...
Tea wouldn't...
You're such a fool. Hurry up and get better.
Sanji!
...give me energy! You moron!
How lame!
Why does he look like this?!
Or I can't even go out shopping.
Gasp!
What'd you just...?
Sanji!
He's... funny.
Hey! What happened?!
Hey!
Why is your body like this?!
Life Return!
What's with that "I wonder what
happens with other drinks" look?!
--Hm?
--That's...
Are you okay, Sanji-kun?!
What a shallow thing I said!
Hair Bind!
This'll be the last time, you damn deer!
That was bad!
I was so shocked
that it just came out of my mouth!
Sanji!
So it doesn't depend
on how you're feeling?
Don't lose your composure, Zoro!
Or your techniques will weaken!
Don't cry. Don't cry.
I need only cola!
Snap!
That's cola! Cola without a doubt!
Sorry... I lost.
If you do, it'll be a disgrace to your manhood.
Just how long are you gonna
continue to laugh, Jabra?!
Listen, Sogeking. Don't lose your posture.
He's gonna kill me...
Thanks!
I couldn't get the key.
S-Sorry.
This isn't an evening in a mountain
village where you can hear the cicadas.
You are a sword!
Hold on a sec, Sanji.
I'll give you first aid.
I don't know what the deal is,
but I'm not gonna let you have your way!
Someone get me a lawyer! I'll sue you for sure!
I never thought that Sanji-kun
would get taken out...
This is a journey to hell
that you knew could come.
Tempest Kick!
I can't stop after all!
Franky!
Now, what're you gonna do?
Take me to the shore already
so that I can knock you out!
The leaves I broke off of a willow tree
branch to give to you as a parting gift,
At any rate, it's interesting.
hoping for your return someday,
are colored crimson!
How in the heck did his square
parts get reflected like this?!
You don't have to tell me!
I'll shut you up right here, right now!
Sanji-kun...
Take it! Now, now, now, now!
Super!
Were you really
not able to defeat her?
Did you really fight seriously?
Wh-What're these handcuffs?!
Crimson... Song of Willow!
Ahhh!
It was that woman
who you fought, wasn't it?
Super Cartwheel, Iron Ball!
Shoot! I'm sorry, Zoro-kun!
You're soft with women.
I'll slam you into the corner of
the tower using this momentum!
Hey! What're you doing?!
I'm gonna die...
Th-They're probably Sea Prism
Stone handcuffs just like Robin's!
I'm sorry about the key.
I see. It indeed looks like
I'll get smashed into pieces.
That's not it!
I'm saying that because
of that stupid chivalry,
Robin... That's right. I can't give up!
Since our enemies are both
Devil Fruit power holders,
you're gonna lose your life!
Franky Centaur!
I thought they'd get weak if
they were handcuffed with them!
You're gonna stick to it even
after getting hurt like this?!
So why are they on me, you idiot?!
What're you gonna do if you die?!
He slipped away from my Hair Bind!
--Chapa!
--I've got both your legs!
B-Because...
It's not like...
Rumble...
Now you can't move around at will in the air!
I want to die.
Chapapa... What's the deal?
I'm sorry, Doctorine.
...the giraffe's face is so
funny that I just lost my grip.
So what?! Even if you do that,
you can't stop this momentum!
But I grew up having the idea that
I shouldn't kick women beat into me.
It's not like drinking cola would
make a difference or anything.
Just like Doctor put his life on the
line in order to save the country...
A giraffe with square parts everywhere...
So...
That's not totally true.
Guard yourself.
Chapa? What a fool.
even if it costs me my life...
He's right!
...I want to put my life on the
line in order to save my friend.
70 mm 0.2 Cola Cannon!
A bit of Coup de Vent!
...I won't kick a woman!
Are you gonna give me
another pathetic punch?
How dare you all...?
Strong... Hammer!
If I'm gonna die anyway, I'll do it!
Experience the fighting
power of a power holder...!
Ahh! The momentum has died down!
You're a fool.
Just please, nobody come into this room.
Fool!
The rotation stopped! Damn you!
Hey! What're you doing, Nami?!
Tempest Kick!
But this is enough!
We're already above the shore!
If running away is also
against your chivalry,
at least ditch that chivalry!
I used three Rumble Balls.
Whoa! What's that?!
Now, take this!
He's gonna do something!
It's not worth dying in vain over.
70 mm 1.5 Max Cola Power!
Then I lost consciousness and after that...
Sky Slicer!
Coup de...
Leave that woman to me.
You could say that your Devil Fruit
powers went out of control.
What're you doing?!
Whoooa! Amazing!
This isn't good.
Also...
Duck, Usopp!
I think a little more of
your chivalry than I did before.
Don't ever go down that path, okay?
Give up already, you bastard!
What?!
Did she just say
that she loves me more?
It's an excessive power that destroys
foes, friends, and even your own body.
Coup de...
No, she didn't!
...Vent!
What you turned into was just like a real...
I'm not kind.
Super!
Neither am I.
...monster.
Sorry.
Sounds like we can get along.
My punches earlier were...
...indeed pathetic.
Boss! Big news! Big news! Big news!
Oh, what's the big news today, Usopp?
No! This is no time for having tea!
Doctorine...
Zoro-kun, what's your idea
to get these handcuffs off?
Hey! Don't you wanna save Nico Robin?!
We're going to appear again after a long while!
I promised you that I wouldn't
use the third rumble ball...
Hurry up and get me the cola!
Yeah. Now that it's come to this,
we'll play rock-paper-scissors
Oh, that's too bad.
Are you in a hurry?
I haven't forgiven you yet!
And that Buggy guy and his men will go
wild noisily, messily, tiredly, disorderly...
Just do it already!
to decide whose wrist
we'll resolutely...
Robin-chan's life is at stake.
...but I want to save Robin.
If I have cola, I can power up!
Ahh! What's with you coming
up with such a scary idea?!
If you're gonna be in my way,
I want to put my life on the
line to save our friend, too.
Now, now, now... Why don't you
eat and calm yourself down? Here.
I won't
go easy on you, even if you are a woman!
What kind of idiot actually
gets stronger with cola?!
There's no way we could do that!
Really?
Then I guess teatime is over?
Shut up! That'd be me!
Then, I've got another idea.
Doctorine... I'm sorry.
Okay. Ahh! Anyway, this is big news, Boss!
Just watch.
Ahh! Ahh! I don't wanna hear it!
I'll finish him off in an instant!
Rumble!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"I Won't Kick Even If It Costs
Me My Life! Sanji's Chivalry!"
"Zoro Busts Out a New Technique!
The Sword's Name is Sogeking?"
"Fukurou's Miscalculation!
My Cola Is the Water of Life"
"Boss Luffy Returns! Is it a Dream
or Reality? Lottery Ruckus!"
"Uncontrollable! Chopper's Forbidden Rumble"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
I'm gonna be a policeman!!