Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
You... damn caterpillar!!
Chore boy!!
Even if hundreds of
weapons are built in,
he can be defeated by someone
with a spear of blind determination.
At least...
...that kid doesn't have any hesitation.
Is it a survival instinct?
Or does he not fear death
because he has faith in himself?
Faith...
This is where you die!!
M-My Mighty Battle Spear is...
What the hell did you do?!
I gave it five punches.
I guess that's it for your spear.
That kid is pretty good.
He might do it...
This is bad...
I never imagined the Mighty
Battle Spear would be broken...
But he's taken that many explosions.
His body can't keep up...
"The Conclusion Of The Deadly Battle!
A Spear Of Blind Determination!"
--Prepare yourself...
--Huh?!
This is a big enough foothold.
With a foothold this size,
I can kick your ass.
What?
With the spear blade broken,
that's just a bomb on a stick.
The power is cut by half.
You think so?
Yeah, I do.
A bomb on a stick? So what of it?
Given the shape you're in, it's more
than enough force to blow you away.
With your body falling apart like that,
whatever you say
sounds like just a bluff.
It's not a bluff.
Just give it up!
The moment you defied me,
you signed your death warrant!
I won't die! Bleah!
Hey! I'm over here!
That monkey!
Ooh ooh ahh!
He keeps hopping around!
It's useless!
Just how many built-in
weapons does he have?
Gum-Gum... Gatling!
--What's that?!
--Amazing...
What the hell is that?
I see a ton of arms...
All right, chore boy!!
Get him!!
Weak!
Your punches are powerless
against this wootz Steel Armor!
You can't even make a dent in it.
Gum-Gum Pistol!!
Don!!
How impudent!!
Useless! Useless! How useless!!
This armor won't break, even with
hundreds of monkey punches!
I think I'm pretty close...
He's gone...
I'm right here!
Now listen. The ultimate force
means the strongest equipment
and the strongest power!
The strong one is the one
who survives. The strong one is!
Then, that'll be me! Gum-Gum...
Useless! Useless! It's useless!!
Even pride will only get you so far!
...Bazooka!!
No good. This is all you can do.
What?! The strongest
armor is cracking?!
But it's too late.
You're done for, anchor boy!
It's a trap! Get out!!
Chore boy!!
Is it a survival instinct?
Or does he not fear death
because he has faith in himself?
--Gum-Gum...
--What?!
...Bazooka!!
--All right!!
--Good job!!
--You're the best, chore boy!!
I win!!
Don't get carried away, brat!!
Ugh! He's still alive!
Oh, no!
Can you escape?! It's a steel net!
Below us is the ocean.
The game is over, anchor boy!
I'm the one who's
getting the last laugh!
All right! That's our Don!
--Make him fall!
--Get him!!
If I can get my arms and legs out,
the game is mine!
Why doesn't he flinch?
--Why does he go that far?
--What?!
This is gonna end it... for sure!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Gavel!!
--Don Krieg...
--Don... Don was defeated! Why?!
--Dammit! Why? Why was Don...
--All right, chore boy!!
--Good job!!
--He really did it!!
--A-Amazing!!
Is this real? This is Don Krieg
we're talking about!
So strong! He's too strong!
Wh... What's all this fuss?
Oh! You've come to!!
He lost! Your Don lost!
What?!
If you have time to daydream,
go save that kid already!
--Huh?
--He won't be floating up to the surface!
What?!
Those with the Devil Fruit power
are hated by the sea
and lose the ability to swim.
What'd you say, you damn geezer?!
You should've told me that sooner!
What're you gonna do if it's too late?!
Where did he go?
Hey! Hang in there!!
You said you wouldn't die, right?
That's your faith, right?!
Right?!
I won't die!
I'm not gonna die here.
Really, these guys...
Zoro!!
He should give up his ambition
rather than dying!
It should be easy...
to give up your ambition, right?!
They're all...
I don't know...
I don't know why, but...
...if I withdrew even a step,
I feel like those various
important things such as pledges
and promises in the
past will be shattered,
and I won't be able to come
back to where I am now...
He can be defeated by someone
with a spear of blind determination.
I know an idiot who's holding back
that spear for a stupid reason...
All... Blue...
Hey, chore boy! Don't you die on me!
Don! What's the matter?!
Why was Don...
Don Krieg has been defeated...
This can't be true...
He's the ruler of the East Blue...
That man is...
That man is... That man is...
Even if you say so...
Just take a look at that!
His proud armor got shattered
and he's knocked out.
He got defeated good.
You're not gonna see it?
He's the only man I admired...
I believed he was the strongest!
Hey wait, underling!
If you move around now,
the poison'll pass into your system.
--Don't move around!
I'm saying this for your own good!
--Hey! You're gonna die!
Chore boy! Don't die! Can you hear me?!
You still have things to do, right?!
Hey! Don't die! Chore boy!
Say... Say something!!
Chore boy! Don't die!!
You're such a...
--You're really something else...
--I'm the strongest!!
I win! No one defeats my force!!
Don! Please stop!
Hold him! He's not even conscious!
--I'll win!!
--Please stop, Don!!
I'll win! Using my force!!
I... have to win!!
I'm the strongest man!!
Don Krieg... We lost.
Chief Commander!
Let's withdraw gracefully
and start afresh.
Thanks for everything, Sanji-san.
Sure. Don't ever come back!
Sanji-san, when he wakes up,
please tell him I said...
...I'll see you again in the Grand Line.
You...
When I think about it carefully,
that's the only thing I want to do...
It seems that Don Krieg's ambition
became mine as well before I knew it.
Maybe... I can live only
a few more hours...
It's kind of stupid that I'm resolved
because I don't have much time left,
but this time, I want to do it with
my own will... in my own way...
Then, there'll be nowhere
for me to escape, right?
The hell with loyalty towards Don!
I've just been running away using
Don Krieg's name as a shield...
Once you're resolved,
you don't have to think
about stupid things
like fearing your enemy
or how to keep from getting hurt...
I learned it from that guy.
Patty! Carne!! Give him the boat
used to go grocery shopping!
What?! Are you stupid?!
Why do we have to
give our boat to pirates?!
What's gonna happen to our
grocery shopping?! You idiot!
He's right! Let those guys swim!
Just bring it out already!!
--Okay, we got it...
--Don't yell at us...
Okay, okay, we'll bring it out!
It's gonna sink!
Why did I hesitate?
What was I so worried about?
When I think about it, I feel stupid...
Well, then! We gratefully
accept the boat.
We don't have to return it, right?
Right. If you have the courage
to come here to return it,
try it, you small fry.
He's right! Just keep this in your brain!!
This is the sea restaurant
Baratie, where cooks fight!
Yeah!!
Hmph! What a scary restaurant...
They were nice guys...
I wonder if they'll let me join them
again when I see them next time...
I wonder if I'll be able
to see them again...
I wanna be free...
Bellemere-san...
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Now I'm free from the chores
since pops promised me.
--That's right.
--By the way, will you...
I'm not going. I won't become a pirate.
Okay...
Hey, you haven't given up yet!
But I'm hoping to go to
the Grand Line some day.
Then let's go now.
It's not the right time yet!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Set Sail! The Seafaring
Cook Sets Off With Luffy"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!