Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
"Boss Luffy Returns! Is it a Dream
or Reality? Lottery Ruckus!"
"A Big Rice Cake Tossing Race
at the Castle! Red Nose's Plot"
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
A joyous new year has arrived
in the country of Grand Jipang.
This is Grand Jipang.
The words he uttered just before his death
It resembles a certain era of
a certain country quite a bit,
Well, what a blessing that is.
drove people around the world to the seas.
but, well, let's not get too specific.
We wrapped up the restless days at the end
of the last year. Why don't we take it easy?
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Although there were some troubles last year
after some rogues wandered into this country,
The new year has just started.
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
peace reigns over this land for the most part.
People are fully enjoying peace
and spending cheerful days.
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
What's going on?
I just said we should take it easy,
and now things already seem restless!
However...
Who the heck is causing it?!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Outta our way! Outta our way!
Outta our way! Make way for us!
Well, you don't have to
shout like that, Onami-san.
Idiot! Watch where you're going!
Wait!
He slipped away from my Hair Bind!
Ouch! You're the ones who bumped into me!
What you're holding is...
Huh?
Rumble...
There's no one around here.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry, Doctorine.
Hm, yeah. Oh, shoot! I don't have time for this!
Tempest Kick! Lotus!
Oh... you're right.
Whaaat?!
Just like Doctor put his life on the
line in order to save the country...
Come to think of it, Dr. Bluenose
hasn't shown up lately.
Take this! Song of Willow!
The sun is already high, and yet
this town is like a ghost town.
Yeah, I don't know what's going on,
but he seems quite busy.
...I want to put my life on the
line in order to save my friend.
"Navy"
The silver transponder snail
has received a signal!
I wonder if everyone's still in bed.
Oh, come on, Doctor, wake up!
A Buster Call has been requested!
If I'm gonna die anyway, I'll do it!
A Buster Call has been
requested by Admiral Aokiji!
They've already gone to the castle.
Hm? Who are you?
Just please, nobody come into this room.
In any event, today is the day they
hold Grand Jipang's popular event,
Where?
Y-You are...
Enies Lobby!
Ah! You guys are from that clown group!
the New Year's Big Rice Cake Tossing!
Have five of the Vice Admirals
near the destination respond!
These guys are dangerous.
They're always hanging out with Straw Hat.
If you were a resident of this town,
you'd rush straight to the castle.
Considering the distance,
I think it's quicker to head
there from headquarters.
What about me?!
Oh? Is that right?
How quick?
You sure are making a
racket out in broad daylight!
Anyway, it's a rice cake tossing event.
They can't start it without rice cakes.
It's possible to get there within 30 minutes.
"Purveying to the Castle"
Immediately have ten battleships
get ready to set sail,
It can affect our business reputation, too.
Please rush to the castle!
What'd you come here for?
and summon five Vice Admirals!
Straw Hat! Why are you here?!
Be swift!
Wh-What the hell...
Okay!
Yes, sir!
What're you saying when you're
the one who came in here?
But don't they usually do the rice
cake tossing at temples and shrines?
A Buster Call has been requested!
...is this?!
If you're here to pick a fight, I'm up for it.
The destination is Enies Lobby!
"Bubble Master Kalifa!
The Soap Trap Closes in on Nami"
Hey, let's get out of here.
He doesn't seem to be here anyway.
Have ten battleships get
ready to set sail immediately!
Here, our lord tosses them at the castle.
Y-Yeah. Looks like we were given a bum steer.
Every year the scramble for them is
so crazy that there are even casualties.
Hey! Hey!
Yo...
W-We're leaving now! Let's go!
What?!
Yes, Chief.
Oh, he's just joking, Doctor.
There're no casualties.
Dammit! Oh, crap! This one is
the portable transponder snail.
Yeah.
What on earth was that?
But when it comes to that Boss
Straw Hat, he might go that far.
Yoyoi...
What have I done? I wasn't careful.
Seriously, we don't get decent customers.
Of all things, I pressed the button
on the golden transponder snail!
Sanji-kun! Scatter some salt!
A voice...?
Okay!
Of all things...
I wonder if someone's talking about me.
What's the deal, Onami?
Were there more annoying customers?
...I requested a Buster Call!
I don't know what's going on,
but the way you firmly stand like a devil...
It's no use saying anything
to someone who's oblivious.
Hm?
Setting aside Boss, I didn't know that
people in this town were so gluttonous.
Hey, hurry up!
Boss. Where's your payment?
Why are you stopping, Nico Robin?!
Oops! That's right! I have to get going!
Everyone! Leave the island!
I like it, my friend!
A Buster Call has been
requested on Enies Lobby!
Hey, are you listening, you woman
whose very life is a crime?!
Sorry! Put it on my tab!
It's not like that, Doctor.
Thanks! That was delicious!
If you stay on the island, you won't survive!
What they're after are not regular
rice cakes, but a jackpot rice cake.
Seriously... Maybe I should
report this to the police soon.
Hey, Lucci! Drag her along!
This isn't your concern!
Whether you're a devil or a demon-god,
Grab her by her hair!
Huh? Jackpot?
On second thought,
don't worry about it, Sanji-kun.
a real man wouldn't withdraw even a step!
They'll keep coming back anyway.
That's right.
Besides, come to think of it,
salt is expensive these days.
Tens of thousands of rice cakes will be
tossed from the top of the castle tower.
On my honor as Kumadori the lion,
It's an order.
Okay!
And among them is a single jackpot rice cake.
Get moving, Nico Robin.
I'll bring you down!
A Buster Call has been requested!
In this rice cake, there's a
treasure called a diamond.
Battleships are coming!
Straw Hat again?
Shave!
Don't tell me... you still think that the
Straw Hats are coming to your rescue?
Get off of Enies Lobby!
W-Well, he just happened
to be in that eatery, that's all.
Finger Pistol! Q! Q! Q! Q! Q!
And believe it or not, it's worth
more than 10 million Ryo-Berries!
It's not like he's gotten in our way yet.
What was that?!
That sure is magnificent, don't you think?
Arrrgh! How irritating!
Where was Robin speaking from?!
How stupid!
I'd definitely like to get it.
Ever since we came to this town,
our earnings have dropped considerably!
Are you seriously still laying your
hopes on such weak-looking pirates?
"New Year
Big Rice Cake Tossing Event Held Here"
The other side of these doors.
But how do I figure out
which one contains the jackpot?
Then we should go to a different town.
Moon Walk!
Beats me. I've never seen one before, so...
--You idiot!
--Ow!
Shishi Kabob!
How could I, the great Buggy,
just get my butt whipped and leave?!
The only feeling you'll have is a sense of guilt.
Hey, do you know?!
I can't let you pass. At least
give me time to say that.
Ah... No, I don't.
Hey, who's saying I got my butt whipped?!
I never did, you bastard!
You'll endlessly atone for your
sin of having lived until today.
In any case, I think you just have to grab
I'm gonna slice you into three and eat you!
whatever you can lay your hands on
and break them to see inside.
His mood is quite nasty, isn't it?
Right, Nico Robin?
He's really getting into the habit of losing, so...
It kind of sounds like a wild goose chase.
In any case, we'd better find him quickly
If I get the jackpot one, I'll buy lots of books!
and shake him down, or we won't
be able to welcome in the new year.
Y-Y-Yoyoi!
N-Now that it's come to this,
I'll use my specialty attack!
I wanna take a trip to a health spa
with everyone at the row house.
Take this! Life Return!
Hair Bind!
Hey!
Hey! You're open for business
already this morning?
Orika! How's he doing?
Yes. Since today is the 7th, I'm selling rice
porridge mixed with seven spring herbs.
Oh, hi, Boss!
He seems to be getting quite a bit better.
Would you like a bowl, too?
He ate some rice porridge earlier, too.
Coo coo.
Robin!
Yeah, sounds good.
Hey, Usopp! It's not fair that you're
eating by yourself! I'll have some, too!
Get out of my way.
Robin's behind those doors, right?!
I see. That's good.
You can't, Boss! You have to
stay there and stand watch!
Orika, Pepper and the others
are worried about you.
So she's there. So what?
You won't be able to see her...
Hair Bind!
Let's go and play with them.
This is rice porridge, so I can't
throw it to you. So just give up!
...ever again.
Well, but...
No... I'll go there to see her!
That's fine, Rika. I'll watch pops.
Whoa! Wh-Wh-What the hell is this?!
H-Hair Bind!
I'll be right there, Robin!
Wh-Wh-What was that?! I just heard a voice!
All right, here it comes! Thanks!
Boss! Once you finish eating it, please go
to the front and stand watch, okay?!
Hey! What was that voice?!
What? What is it?
My God! My consciousness,
all the way to the tip of my hair,
"Five Namis? Nami Strikes Back with Mirages!"
Yeah... Yeah... Okay.
Geez...
Pops tells me to go, too.
Your duty must be tough.
Good.
is screaming that the best thing
to do here is to run away.
Hold on a minute, okay?
Well, the jackpot is worth
10 million Ryo-Berries, right?
♪ It's warm on the southern islands! ♪
Someone blinded by greed
could be up to no good, so...
Hm? The space has opened up. Where am I?
Even so, please don't stop me, Mother!
♪ Pineapple-ple! Their heads
are nice and warm! ♪
There you are! Pigeon guy!
♪ They're all idiots! ♪
A man... A man...
Stand up, Nico Robin!
Stand up already, you bitch!
Next, the second verse!
Yeah!
A man has battles that he must face head-on!
Sitting around and waiting for the jackpot
when you don't know where it's gonna fall
♪ It's cold on the northern islands! ♪
"Resounding Bad News! Buster Call Invoked!"
What's that look in your eyes?!
is just a pain in the neck! I can't do that!
♪ Freezing, real freezing!
Their heads are shivering... ♪
Cancel the Buster Call right away!
There may still be time!
There's a way to get it for sure.
Shave!
Tempest Kick! Lotus!
In short...
Shut up! You're still saying that?!
I'm impressed... I'll say that much.
Hm?
...we'll get all the rice cakes
before they toss them at the castle.
What the heck is this?
I'm the Chief of CP9! There's no way I can say,
Beats me.
To think that you've come
this far... all by yourself.
Take this! Song of Willow!
A horse...? No, it's not a horse, is it?
Then, we'll get the jackpot one
for sure. Yeah, that's my plan!
"I made a careless mistake and
requested a Buster Call" now, you idiot!
I know what it is! It's called a camel!
I didn't come by myself!
You're right!
Hm?
Men! Get them flashily!
There's no way I could come this far by myself,
What do I care how many casualties it'll cause?!
He doesn't look very tasty.
and I wouldn't even wanna come by myself.
So... what's he doing here?
Once I hand you over to the World Government,
There's nowhere to escape on the bridge!
Unlike you guys, I'm not alone!
What's wrong? Does it hurt somewhere?
Geez... When we're almost to the castle...
my future is all set!
That's all that matters, right?
We don't have time to turn back, guys!
Soon all my friends will come here!
He seems to have a slight fever.
That won't happen. Never!
Boss, could you carry him to my house?
Let's go, Doctor!
Yeah!
What?
I feel bad leaving him here.
He seems to be hungry, too.
Everyone is... Luffy is...
That's no problem, but with pops, too,
your place is too small for all of you.
...right behind us.
Don't get the wrong idea.
There isn't even a shred of hope for you.
That was close!
Dammit!
But...
Not bad.
I'm super this week, and yet I still
had a harder time than I thought.
Tempest Kick!
It might be okay to just leave him by
the well at the row house on the back alley.
The one who's fighting Straw Hat
right now is CP9's strongest member,
But if he's hungry, then we should...
Onami...
Rob Lucci, whose Power Level is 4,000!
That was cruel.
Hm?
But, well...
Even so, don't just bring anything to our place!
Take this, too!
Don't tell me you seriously
think that brat can defeat him...
Shave!
...I got his key.
Doctor! Watch your back!
I'm really starting to get the hang of this.
We're running a business, you know?!
Oh, come on! Your place
is pretty empty anyway.
Even if a Buster Call is invoked
or Straw Hat is right behind us,
I'm starting to feel kinda sick.
Mellorine! Mellorine!
#4...
That's none of your business!
You're a sailor. Don't say
pathetic things like that!
Dr. Bluenose isn't around when we need him.
that doesn't change the situation at all!
The key the swordsman and
the nose wanted was #2, right?
Richie!
I-I'm not a sailor. I'm a hero who
hails from the island of snipers...
Do you get that, you bitch?!
You son of a bitch!
You can leave things to Orika.
She's used to taking care of the sick.
This guy had #4.
Stop, you bastards!
That guy had #3.
...although my best friend
Usopp-kun is a sailor.
If you don't wanna die,
leave all the stuff on the cart here!
I thought a camel would be cooler than this.
And there's only one left.
Stop talking nonsense. Here.
The one who has the #2 key
is that secretary woman!
Me, too.
Luffy... Everyone...
Boss!
I'd better hurry up.
They dodged!
There's trouble! There's trouble!
Th-Th-That was close!
I'll go help them out!
There's trouble, Boss!
Hm? What the hell is that?!
Don't let your guard down!
O-Okay.
And don't do things that are uncalled for!
It's a camel.
O-Okay.
Orika took him in and is nursing him.
Hm?! What's that supposed
to mean?! How rude!
Orika is?!
Boss! They got away!
More importantly, what's the
matter, Usopp? What's going on?
You sure are rude!
Oh, yeah! There's trouble at Orika's house!
It's not gonna work anymore!
They'll enter the castle
before we catch up with them!
--Come with me right away, Boss!
--What...?
At my house...
Don't be ridiculous! It's 10 million
Ryo-Berries we're talking about!
This is no good... It's so
slippery that I can't stand.
Hey, walk briskly!
To think that you were
hiding in a place like this...
I'm not gonna give up!
Even still...
But...
Did you really think that you could outrun us?
...what a creepy power.
...I'm not gonna let them get away...
Pops!
You guys don't have much time, right?
...as I've already prepared my next move.
Please stop it. He's a sick man!
That sounds like a bunch of sour grapes.
Shut up! He's a guarantor of a loan.
If you wanna complain,
I thought you weren't going to go easy on me.
If you get it, come back
up already and get ready!
Since you don't come close to me
when it comes to strength and beauty...
do so to the guy who skipped town,
forcing the deed on him!
Did I hear you wrong?
Yes, sir!
We're just collecting the money as agreed.
...I gave you the gift of silky skin
How dare you mock me?!
I won't let you get away with it!
so that you can at least come
a bit closer to my beauty.
Hey, don't bother with her! Let's go!
Then, bring it on.
--Yes, sir!
--Hold it!
You should appreciate it.
Robin!
That's very sweet of you. But...
Let go of pops!
You don't have to wait. The battle
has already started, you know.
Father.
Looks like it's getting lively down there.
...there's a limit to how far you
can go, right?! There's a limit!
I'm surprised that a power holder
could take a bath in front of her enemy.
Yes. They seem like they can't wait.
Is there a limit to women's desire?
Yeah... By the way, looks like we still
haven't received the rice cakes yet.
You bastard! You think
you can get away with this?
If your body is halfway submerged,
you shouldn't have full use of your powers.
"Ticked!"
Then why don't you do it to yourself?!
Shut up! You guys are the ones
who're doing something terrible!
Are you saying that I'm
leaving myself wide open?
Right...
Oh? I don't need it, because
I'm already beautiful enough.
I'm having someone stand watch,
but I haven't received any report yet.
We've got the deed.
Come back when you get a clue!
A deed for such a large
amount can't be possible!
Whoa, what a bitch.
You don't have to worry about it,
I'm a little worried that something
might've happened on their way here.
If you're still gonna take pops, I'll take you on!
Did you say something?
because just like me, you can't
exert your strength, either.
No, nothing.
You blockhead! There's this
thing called interest.
Oh, that's right.
Pardon me for a bit.
Just you wait. I'm about to get you back!
You know the people we're
getting the rice cakes from well.
We're gonna make him work for
the rest of his life to repay us.
This is no time for you, a policeman, to butt in.
I wonder if we should send someone for them.
Pops!
Stop it! Let pops go!
Ahh... Since she said, "We don't
need guards, so pay us generously instead,"
What'd you do to me?!
Ow, ow, ow... That damn deer-gorilla!
How dare he mock me?!
--Orika!
--Wh-Who's this brat?
You had a kid?
I didn't send any guards. I hope
Onami-san and the others are okay.
Isn't solving a mystery like that one of
the true joys of fighting a power holder?
But more importantly, the key! The key!
Okay, then. We'll take you too and sell you off.
Hm? There they are!
I'd better hurry to that secretary woman.
Come!
What took Onami so long? Rice cakes
taste better right after they're made.
--Rika!
--Boss!
Gum-Gum...
Hm?
It was definitely this woman
who put Sanji-kun in that state.
...Billy Club!
What's that kite doing?!
Deer-gorilla! Wait, you jerk!
All right, Boss!
I have to be careful. Or there's no
point in me taking his place to fight.
Hey! What's going on?!
D-Dammit! How dare you...?!
Whoa! We're floating in the air!
You won't get away with this!
Hold on tight!
Yaay! All right! Get out of
here and don't come back!
They're waiting in ambush again?!
The strength that ebbed away
is coming back little by little.
But this isn't good.
It's a Buster Call!
Those bastards!
It's hard to think that clown would
back down without doing anything.
Battleships are coming!
Who are you?! Actually, you're from
the Buggy Family, aren't you?!
Hurry up, or we'll be burned to a crisp!
Don't worry. It'll work out okay.
You're left... I mean, you're right!
I'll show you the power
of the Perfect Clima Takt!
Get out of here!
That sounds terrible.
So what happened to pops?
By order of Boss Buggy,
I came to take all the rice cakes.
You're mistaken if you think
I'm just a cute beauty!
Gather those who can still fight to
the front of the Courthouse! Do it now!
He's resting at home.
My name is Hachi. Nice to meet you.
He's almost better, but he tries
to push himself and go out.
"And there's one more person right here!"
That looks funny!
Don't flinch! Capture the traitors!
So I scolded him, saying that
he should lay down and rest.
I can move my legs, too!
"I, the martial artist Gedatsu
of the Buggy Family!!"
But no one's come here, when I
thought I'd show them the way.
You call us traitors?! Don't make me laugh!
You can twist even pops
around your little finger, huh?
It was you, the Navy, who's been
betraying us for the past 50 years!
Well, don't worry. Once I get the
rice cakes, I won't even touch you guys.
Here I come!
Mr. Camel got his energy back!
Thunder Charge!
It looks fun over there.
Oh? Good timing. I made his food
using leftovers. You can have it.
I'll make sure to put you
back on the ground safely.
Chimney. Gonbe. What're you two doing?
We're pirates to start with!
Don't be ridiculous!
Swing Arm!
Thanks, Sanji-san!
If we can't deliver them after coming this far,
What's wrong with pirates
fighting against the Navy?!
Oh, Grandma!
What, Sanji? Isn't my food ready yet?
our business reputation will be
totally ruined! Do something, Sanji-kun!
You ate just a bit ago!
Well, I found a weird hole.
Well, I can't do anything like this.
--Here you go!
--Thank you!
Then, I took the pirate guy there.
Whoa! You're making some tasty-looking food!
--Argh!
--Ahh! Help!
Let's go, Oimo!
Yeah, Kashii!
And then, and then,
the pirate guy became small!
Hey, hey. Don't move around.
Don't blame me if you fall.
Ouch!
That's an amazing weapon.
We'll change our strategy and
bring them down individually!
These are expensive dishes
for delivery, you damn jerk.
Small?
Attack unit! Concentrate
your fire on Kashii's feet!
Don't touch them.
But, but, he did wham!
You rice cake thief! Surrender peacefully!
These are...
Wham?!
...clouds?
What's wrong, Mr. Camel?
There's no way I'd just lay on
the floor doing nothing, is there?
Aren't you gonna eat? I'm sure you're hungry.
Now! Charge!
If you don't eat, you can't get better.
Gum-Gum...
Thunderbolt... Tempo!
Right?!
Idiot! Don't cling to me!
We bow to nobody in human
wave attacks! Keep on going!
He doesn't want them? Then I'll...
Oh? That pirate kid did?
No!
What's the matter?
I don't quite understand,
H-Hey! Kashii!
but it sounds like it's getting
more and more interesting.
Oh? What is it?
Hmm... Why am I falling too?
Oimo is next! Prepare to fire!
You bastard! I made these dishes using
expensive food! They're for delivery!
Things have suddenly started happening, huh?
It's your own fault for acting so confident.
Oh, that's right! I should've let the
kite string go! How careless of me!
Hey! You bastard!
Sounds like if I stay in this tower
too long, I may lose my life.
I'm gonna slice you into three!
Just as you'd expect from Sanji!
To think that he can make
such tasty food with leftovers!
If you're gonna run, then leave the key here.
--Ow, ow, ow...
--Well, we're okay now.
The situation outside has changed?
No, we aren't! The cart is...!
Shave!
The giants who changed sides
have been trying hard for us,
I'm sorry.
but I guess they are at the end of their rope.
I wanted to spend more time playing with you.
Those guys...!
You bastard! I'm mad! I'm seriously
gonna slice you into three!
Wait, Sanji-san! Please don't blame Mr. Camel!
Look at that, guys! The rice
cakes are coming our way!
That was a surprise.
I'm sure he ate those
because they looked tastier.
The jackpot's gonna be mine!
I never thought I'd be hit by lightning indoors.
Shoot!
Even so...
You bastard! Who do you think
you are?! You're just a camel!
What was that thing that
guarded you from the lightning?
I'm sorry, Sanji-san, Onami-san.
Igaram-san!
Chaka! Pell! Get the cart!
It turned into bubbles and disappeared.
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
Yes, sir!
You have no chance against me
unless you solve that mystery.
Onami, you sure are generous today.
How dare you get in my way?!
Hey! Hey, hurry up!
But we have to evacuate quickly, too, so...
Normally, you'd have beaten
the crap out of the person by now.
It doesn't matter who they are!
Take them down!
I wonder if you can do it.
Dammit! What a disaster.
To tell you the truth, I'm thinking this
might be some sort of turn of fate.
It was as if soap turned into bubbles.
To think that a pirate would get this far...
What're you guys doing?!
A soap human with
Bubble-Bubble Fruit powers...
But, Boss... We're carrying
this heavy stuff on a slope.
This. Take a look at this.
Golden Bubbles!
I wonder if it's something like that.
Hey, everyone, come in!
I bought a Year-End lottery ticket.
CP9! What the hell are you all doing?!
Let's take a little break.
B-But even if, for example, you figured
out what kind of powers they are,
Stop whining! Just go after them!
A lottery ticket? What does
that have to do with this?
A pirate has gotten this far!
it's not like you have a
chance to win! How insolent!
Onami-dono!
"Camel"
Ah! Camel, 1356?
Are you okay?
Hey, are you listening?! Say something!
So that was right on the mark.
Now I kinda feel guilty.
Yes! Well then, we certainly
delivered what you ordered.
So you think it might be good luck?
This is the same attack that got Sanji-kun.
Even though I was being careful...
You got it!
You're right. My selling point is cleanliness.
Yes. Thank you.
Today is the drawing day.
What about the payment?
I can get it right here and now, right?
I ate the Bubble-Bubble Fruit
Wait!
I asked Usopp to go there and check.
The task was more dangerous than we thought.
and became a soap human
whose entire body lathers.
What you're holding is...
Oh, about that...
I can't hold the Clima Takt.
Third prize! Camel, 1356!
Hey... This is business with the castle.
You can't put it on a tab.
My entire body is slippery! I can't stand up!
Isn't it wonderful?
Princess Vivi said that she
herself will bring it to your place.
Whoa! How sexy! To be honest,
I'd be happy to have a secretary like her.
Whaaat?!
A million Ryo-Berry third prize?!
So wait until then.
Hey! What am I, a middle-aged guy?!
A... A... A golden transponder snail!
Yeah. I checked many times!
There's no mistaking it!
How dare you make my body like this?!
But isn't that poorly suited for fighting?
That doesn't look very strong.
Well then, goodbye.
Although it has the downside
of reducing your curves,
Tell Vivi to stop by any time!
I-It's true...? It's like a dream!
But I can freely manipulate the
bubbles that come out of my body.
it does give you the most beautiful skin.
All right! We can now welcome in
the new year without any problem!
They still haven't given up yet?!
I envy you.
Don't worry about them, Sanji-kun!
Let's go to the event site.
We'll be out of our desperate
financial situation!
But in return, your fighting
power is reduced by half.
That's amazing!
What? What's going on?
"Navy"
You should just give up on the key I have.
Now my bills will all be wiped out, right?
I'll show you.
Just leave the rest to the
castle people. It'll be fine.
The silver transponder snail
has received a signal!
It wasn't you who hit the lottery.
The bubbles from the bathtub are...!
I... I can't do that!
A Buster Call has been requested!
Bubble Master!
Thank you, camel!
Hey, Boss! If it turns out that they can't
do the rice cake tossing or something,
You really were a good-luck camel!
A Buster Call has been
requested by Admiral Aokiji!
Cool Charge!
Soap Sheep!
you'll be forbidden to come to our eatery!
Where?
So work hard, got that?!
That's no use. Playtime is over.
Enies Lobby!
I'll let you eat whatever you like,
since this is definitely thanks to you!
This is...
Yeah...
Have five of the Vice Admirals
near the destination respond!
How's this? Isn't it wonderful?
Tempest Kick!
Considering the distance,
I think it's quicker to head
there from headquarters.
You're an idiot, aren't you?
What?
Boss! They're already going into the castle!
How quick?
Mirage Tempo. I'm right here.
You shouldn't be deceived by my appearance.
It's possible to get there within 30 minutes.
Shut up! It doesn't matter!
We'll force our way through!
What?
When did you...?! What's going on?
Immediately have ten battleships
get ready to set sail,
Sheep Cloud! Relaxing Bubbles!
Who said you could eat the lottery ticket?!
We'll do it flashily!
Finger Pistol!
and summon five Vice Admirals!
Spit it out! Spit it out!
A million Ryo-Berries! Spit it out!
You did lose your strength at the
entrance of the room. Why was that?
Be swift!
Yes, sir!
They've started the rice
cake tossing? I got a late start!
A Buster Call has been requested!
He must really like expensive stuff.
Another fake! Where are you this time?!
The destination is Enies Lobby!
That's right...!
This is no time to be impressed.
Intruders!
That must've been her powers, too.
This way! Right here!
Hey! Spit it out! A million Ryo-Berries!
Have ten battleships get
ready to set sail immediately!
Don't let them get away!
Bubbles!
Give it back to me at any cost!
Come to think of it, when I
stepped into this room...
It's the Buggy Family!
Hey! Hey!
They're after these rice cakes!
Mr. Camel...
Yes, Chief.
Got it. Please hurry!
What's that?!
A good-luck camel? What a joke.
Dammit! Oh, crap! This one is
the portable transponder snail.
Sh-She grew huge?!
...there were bubbles all over the floor!
Hey! Where's the event site?
What have I done? I wasn't careful.
What?
Hm? Oh, it's you!
I came to check just in case...
They sure are connected by fate.
Of all things, I pressed the button
on the golden transponder snail!
So you were a power holder, too!
Shoot!
Good timing! Give us a hand.
Of all things...
Seriously, I wish they wouldn't
pull me into things like this.
She's a ditz.
--Huh?
--A rice cake thief showed up!
...I requested a Buster Call!
I heard that he's going
on a rampage in the castle!
You noticed it too late.
What?! I've been looking forward to
those rice cakes! Where's the thief?!
My strength is ebbing away.
--Over there!
--All right!
This happened earlier, too, because I
stepped on the bubbles on the floor.
Trying to get them all
to himself?! How despicable!
Those rice cakes are mine!
You'll learn the horror of
this power little by little.
I don't want you to call me out so easily.
What? Hey, hey... You too?
A Buster Call has been requested.
Hurry up!
Well, don't be like that.
Go! Renowned sword, Nose Storm!
Of all things...
Rice cake thief! I'm gonna
capture you at any cost!
In order to join hands, we have to settle things.
...I requested a Buster Call!
I've been having a hard time with that tomboy.
Where are the rice cakes?!
Tempest Kick!
Finger Pistol!
This is a good chance.
You don't have to hold back.
The bubbles that come out of my
body scrape away all sorts of things...
Then, Commissioner, it's okay
to flashily get rid of Straw Hat?
B-Buster Call? D-Don't tell me...
We're not gonna let him
destroy the castle any more!
Obviously filth and spots, but also
your strength, among other things.
What's this? Some internal communication?
Okay! Good job!
It shouldn't be a big deal for a
policeman or two to disappear.
Well, I have an idea as to where he's headed.
How foolish! Cancel it right away!
Tempest Kick!
I know a short cut. Leave it to me!
Let's catch up with them quickly, Mr. Monk!
Finger Pistol!
And I don't want you to forget that I'm
an assassin from a secret organization.
Again?! Ahhh! No!
Fortunately, it's he who's at fault this time.
That's Robin's voice!
Hey, Usopp. Who have you
been talking to all this time?
Or it'll be a disaster!
I can help you without any hesitation.
Robin!
Hm? Oh, Boss! Who've I
been talking to? Of course...
I can move my body! Her kicking
me made the bubbles go away!
What? "Cancel it"?
--Gulp.
--That's reassuring.
Huh?! He's gone! When did that happen?
Hey, hey. Who do you think you're talking to?
I'm not gonna take this anymore!
After I get rid of him, you and I will
control this town and do as we please.
Thunder Ball!
Anyway, I'm going on ahead, okay?
What the heck is this broadcast?
Zoro-kun! This plan really is reckless!
Hey! Don't move!
We can't move!
That weapon's power alone...
That's right.
At any rate, that monk
isn't reliable. Where did he go?
I suggest you stop this immediately.
Well, then...
...is still an unknown quantity to me.
"Confectionery
Carefully Produced"
These are golden-colored confectioneries.
No, wait.
What?
Buster Call is great, isn't it?
What's wrong with it?!
Our enemies are totally seized by fear
You're bad.
Not as bad as you are.
Where are the rice cakes?!
after seeing the power of the
renowned sword, Nose Storm.
Ahhh!
What?! I-Is that right?
That's Chief Spandam's voice, right?
H-H-Hey...
I'm back!
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
To think that he turned his friend into a sword...
What's the matter, Cabaji?!
That's right... There's no problem.
Amazon-dono! Are you okay?!
He sure attacks recklessly.
My strength is ebbing away.
Well... Seems like it was my imagination.
Someone!
This happened earlier, too, because I
stepped on the bubbles on the floor.
I'm the chief of Cipher Pol No. 9.
Ha! He's just desperate.
It's just pointless resistance.
Don't scare me like that, you moron-ji!
What's going on?!
I-I'm sorry.
A deviant is in here!
In order to hand you over
to the Government smoothly,
You'll learn the horror of
this power little by little.
Zoro-kun! I've made up my mind! I'll do it!
How rude!
I'm so busy! I'm so busy!
I requested a Buster Call.
Th-There's trouble! There's trouble!
This is the turning point of this fight!
Let's keep the plan going!
I see no problem in that!
Boss! There's trouble!
No matter what happens here,
Go ahead and fight with no restraint!
I sent Boss out for delivery with that camel.
we'll be able to annihilate
the pirates for sure in the end.
What did I do?!
That's what I wanted to hear!
What's the matter?
What bad timing! Orika got
kidnapped by the Buggy Family!
Hold it!
The bubbles that come out of my
body scrape away all sorts of things...
Renowned sword, Nose Storm!
Killer Attack, Makie!
How foolish...!
"Makie"
What?!
I told you, didn't I?!
That won't be the end of it!
"Makie"?!
Obviously filth and spots, but also
your strength, among other things.
I heard that she got caught by them
out of the blue on her way home.
"Makie [lacquer]"
All right! Just go ahead and charge in!
Oh! That's a beautiful,
splendid killer attack name,
Seems like they were after Orika from the start.
There's no humanity in that attack!
And I don't want you to forget that I'm
an assassin from a secret organization.
suited for the renowned sword Nose Storm.
Boss!
Hey, Straw Hat.
That's the Chief... but who's the woman?
It's all over for you, Buggy Family!
Hm? Ah! You guys are...!
I like it, Zoro-kun!
Is it really okay with you? That girl
will be sold off to repay the loan.
I won't allow any more violence in the castle!
The attack will completely burn
Enies Lobby to the ground!
Huh?
I can move my body! Her kicking
me made the bubbles go away!
What? Um...
Be prepared!
Buildings, people... the very island itself!
What'd you say about Orika?!
Oh, my, my... Princess.
Hm?
She should be leaving the harbor soon.
I'm not gonna take this anymore!
Thank you very much for greeting me yourself!
Shouldn't you be on your way to rescue her?
Thunder Ball!
What's that? It looks as if
he's asking us to kill them.
Let me go!
It's a nightmarish concentrated fire that
sacrifices everything to achieve its goal!
That weapon's power alone...
Give up.
O-Oh...? Hmmm?
You don't know the Chop-Chop Fruit's powers?
...is still an unknown quantity to me.
You are an important piece
of bait to trick Straw Hat.
This is your own fault for butting in.
That's Buster Call!
Z-Zoro-kun, what on earth are you doing?
Golden Bubbles!
This time, we're collecting
money based on a deed.
You don't know what happened in
Ohara twenty years ago. That's why...
I'll get them first!
If he tries to raise his hand against
me in front of the commissioner,
I'll be the first!
Oh, don't get me wrong.
he can immediately get fired and be exiled.
What're you doing?!
I didn't come here for her. I came
here to get the jackpot rice cake!
Shave!
On top of that, I'll get
money from selling you off.
Bring the rice cake cart here right away!
I can't stand!
What?! What's wrong with my legs?!
I'll exchange her for the cart. Move it already!
Dammit! To think that you used
that masked idiot as a decoy...
Just you wait, Straw Hat!
Don't blame me if the
princess's neck gets broken!
Wait! We get it.
That was close.
They look pretty, don't they?
We have no choice but to do what he says.
Buggy! What're you gonna
do with Orika?! Let her go!
Everything I touch gains a beautiful gloss.
So by "Makie," you meant
"bait" instead of "lacquer"?!
"Makie [lacquer]"
That's fine. It means that this is
very important to the Government.
Oh? So a lackey realizes the situation
faster than the samurais, huh? Okay, then!
"Makie [bait]"
I'm not tasty.
Sorry, Straw Hat. I'm taking this girl
as collateral for that man's loan.
Am I bait? A decoy?
What a horrible man you are!
I'll make your skin shiny...
You go and bring the cart here.
Now that that idiot Cutty Flam has
burned the blueprints for Pluton...
Well, the jackpot rice cake isn't on that cart.
Every inch of your body.
One more time. Killer Attack, Makie!
There's no reason for you to butt in
this time! Mind your own business!
I don't even have a say in this?!
Then, where is it?
Let's go, men!
Besides, you're using those
words "killer attack" wrong!
--Yes, sir!
--Help me, Boss!
The jackpot rice cake is...
Don't!
...with our lord!
I said...
Aren't I the one who'll get killed here?
Oh...?
...let her go!
Is that right?
...your existence is the only
clue to the ancient weapon.
It's over there.
Zoan type... So is that your trump card?!
A military power that can turn this
whole era upside down is at stake.
What?! I-Is it okay to take it so easily? Huh?
Seriously, that's not me!
If it improves our chances of killing
those idiots trying to get you back,
That's fine.
At any rate, this form...
You interfered with us, Straw Hat!
It looks like a reindeer, and I know that
hat and the mark on it without a doubt.
A policeman beating up commoners
over personal matters?
even if it causes the death
of thousands of soldiers,
I-I-It...
What's your problem?!
we can say that it's an unavoidable
sacrifice for our glorious future!
But I can't believe...
It's empty!
Hey, what do you think about
his act?! Commissioner?
...this is Chopper!
Oh? So that's where big nose was?
Above all things, my promotion is at stake, too.
I'm disappointed in you, Straw Hat.
What savage beast's power does she hold?!
What?! What's he saying?!
You son of a bitch! You flashily deceived me!
What have you done?
Moon Walk!
He's gonna sacrifice us?! You gotta be kidding!
Ack! The commissioner?
What's he doing in a place like this?!
Yep.
Tempest Kick!
What do you think of people's lives?!
Buggy, was it? Look outside
the window. On the ground are...
Hey! Stop it!
The commissioner?
Don't forget that CP9 is the
Government's secret organization.
Yeah. Just like our boss, Koza-sama,
What?!
Chopper! Hey, you're Chopper, right?
he's a town commissioner and
the top person in this town.
How did you become like that?!
If we need 100 deaths in
order to save 1,000 lives,
Hey! Don't break the castle!
Whoa...
To think that you'd use violence
Iron Body!
Hey, big nose! We're not gonna let
you have the jackpot, you bastard!
towards commoners who
are not at fault like this...
we'll kill those 100 without
hesitation on the spot.
Like I said, it's empty!
I'm gonna beat you till you cry!
As a commissioner, I cannot overlook this.
Straw Hat Luffy! I hereby strip you of
your role as policeman. You're fired!
Well, listen. On the ground
are this town's residents
I wonder if he can't recognize me,
since I look like this.
Aren't you Chopper?!
Mercilessness is also
a necessity for true justice.
who have been looking forward
to this rice cake tossing event.
Leave this country immediately
and never set foot here again!
Let me tell you something!
I didn't think that was you!
This event is held for them so that
they can start the new year cheerfully.
--What?!
--Why?!
Besides, those incompetent soldiers
who couldn't stop the invading pirates
This is a gathering in which
they try their luck, so to speak.
Chopper!
Got that, Straw Hat?!
Sh-She ignored me! How insolent!
It all depends on your luck
whether you get a prize or not,
It's your punishment for meddling
in our business all the time!
are better off dead, you idiot!
but the chance of winning
should be equal for everyone.
I don't know what's coming next,
Thanks for all your hard work!
Chopper! What's wrong?!
so I'm gonna go ahead
and replenish my cola first.
So I can't give it to you alone now.
If you get it, then hurry up and leave!
Take a good look at me! It's me! I'm Nami!
That portable transponder snail...
The line is connected.
Come to think of it, I wonder
how that deer's doing.
What're you guys talking about?
What?
If you want the prize, then go down there
Why do I have to leave here
just because I tried to save Orika?
and wait with everyone for
the rice cake tossing to start.
Ahhh! Shoot!
What the heck's going on?!
Did everyone hear what I just said?!
I don't get it.
Chopper!
You're still talking like that, you blockhead?!
Just as we'd expect from you, my lord.
Splendid persuasion. I'm impressed.
It's unseemly, Straw Hat.
Are you trying to talk your way out
after everything you've done?
Chopper! Stop it!
S-So... my name is Straw Hat Luffy.
Yep.
Say, my lord. Let's start it already.
I can immediately call the constables in
and have them arrest you, you know.
If we don't hurry up, Onami is gonna beat me.
Yeah, right!
Wh-What the hell...
Hey! You're being rude! To think
that you speak to our lord that way!
Everyone! Leave the island!
You're the one who should
be arrested, Commissioner!
...is this?!
A Buster Call has been
requested on Enies Lobby!
Hm?
If you stay on the island, you won't survive!
A town commissioner joining hands
with criminals? It's quite inexcusable!
I give up!
This isn't your concern!
I won't need such a small thing!
How dare you mock me?!
That's the CP9 guy who was in the fridge!
I'm removing you from your position right away!
What? Who are you?
What?! Did this monster bring him down?!
Sanji-kun is downstairs!
You sure talk like a big shot.
I found something better, my lord.
Where did such a monster stray in here from?
Do you say that knowing that
I'm the North Town Commissioner?
Forget the 10 million Ryo-Berry jackpot!
Don't hurt him! He's my friend!
--B...
--Buster Call...
Oh? That's...
If I kill you, I'll have this
entire country all to myself!
How insolent! Kneel down!
It sounds like Buster Call has been requested.
What the hell is this?
Now that it's come to this,
I'm gonna blow you up flashily!
Who do you think this is?
Men! Prepare the Special Buggy Ball!
What the hell is that man doing?
She's the daughter of Shogun Cobra! Vivi-sama!
Yes, sir!
Sounds like there's some sort of danger.
I feel like that deer was
wearing the same kind of hat...
Ack!
It's me who's in danger!
I'll teach you a lesson for
deceiving me! Be prepared!
You're being disrespectful! Kneel down!
I feel sorry for you guys.
Hey! You're not that deer-gorilla, are you?!
Even your hope is gone now.
It's ready.
Don't worry.
We're used to situations like this.
--Vivi!
There's no need for formality.
Go ahead and fire now!
So it was really you, Vivi!
What happened to Chopper?
It's been a while, everyone.
Pirate kid, what kind of
destiny were you born with?
B-But... what's the princess doing here?
This is terrible. I have to stop him right away.
Hey... This can't be happening...!
My investigation has shown
that you took a bribe
That's your friend? You pirates
sure own a creepy pet, huh?
This is getting even more interesting!
There's no mistake.
and are working with the
clown to trick Boss Straw Hat.
Kumadori-san!
Chopper!
He flew from the Tower of Law?!
Give up peacefully.
A Buster Call has been requested!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
She ignored me again! How insolent!
Can't be...! Who on earth could...?
Battleships are coming!
--Rice cakes!
--The rice cake tossing has started!
Don't "Yes ma'am" her, you stupid jerk!
Get off of Enies Lobby!
You're free to go stop that monster,
Dammit! Now that it's come
to this, I'll flashily withdraw,
Seriously... what the hell is he?!
but I have a duty to stop you, too.
taking the loan collateral with me!
Ah! You bastards!
Battleships are coming? Why are
the Navy soldiers running away?
--Like I said...!
--Huh?
I'm gonna hurry up and finish it here.
The one with the jackpot might've
been among the ones we just tossed.
Orika can't be collateral for the loan!
The woman said that the island
will be burned to the ground.
Tempest Kick!
Well, he said he didn't want it anymore.
This is bad! Even the soles
are slippery. I can't dodge it!
Because she isn't pops' daughter.
But this is the Government's island!
You bastards! It was a slip of the tongue!
How should I know why?!
--Huh?
--This way! Hurry up!
Hey, hey! If you guys're running away,
at least untie us first!
She called him pops!
They're clearly father and daughter!
Huh?! I could dodge it!
You're causing trouble!
Time for you to go flying!
Ah... My right leg went back to normal.
A voice...?
There they are! Hey, Boss! I brought him here!
Why? What caused it?
Good job, guys!
Oh, thanks!
It's a Buster Call!
Hm?
We'll be dead if we stay here!
It's wet...
Hey, hurry up!
Oh, hey, pops!
It got wet in the earlier
commotion. Oh, that's right!
Why are you stopping, Nico Robin?!
Bring some ships to the front!
Get ready to sail out!
I heard you collapsed. Are you okay now?
The Navy is coming to attack this place!
Water! I can wash off
the soap power with water!
Hey, are you listening, you woman
whose very life is a crime?!
Don't push yourself, pops!
You guys got it, right?!
Find the jackpot no matter what!
Things just aren't the same
at Pinwheel without you!
Hey, Lucci! Drag her along!
--Wh-What?
--Let's have a drink together again soon, pops!
Alrighty!
Grab her by her hair!
We got left behind...
In this town, everyone calls him "pops."
Hey! What're we gonna do?!
Isn't this dangerous?!
There's nothing odd about
Orika calling him that, right?
It's been dangerous ever since
we set foot in this place.
It's an order.
Get moving, Nico Robin.
What about Bro?! What's gonna
happen to Big Bro Franky?!
But he was sleeping at her house!
This one-thousand-year-old famous
Alabasta Castle now has three big holes
Aren't you being too optimistic?
Pops made his cold worse and
collapsed the other day on the street.
Even if you figured out how
to undo Golden Bubbles,
Yeah. If he doesn't come back here,
we can't go back together!
Don't tell me... you still think that the
Straw Hats are coming to your rescue?
in its castle tower. This is all because of...
there's no way I'd let you do that.
The Straw Hats, too!
And Orika happened to pass by.
So what about us?!
Hey, Straw Hat!
She's the kind of girl who can't
just leave someone like that.
Luffy-san has already gone
down to pick up rice cakes.
Sheep Cloud! Relaxing Bubbles!
How stupid!
What will... happen to all of us?!
Are you seriously still laying your
hopes on such weak-looking pirates?
Yummy! Yummy!
I'll blow away those bubbles with wind!
Then this girl has nothing to do with the loan!
We can't afford to waste time, either.
What's the matter, Igaram?
Why don't you toss the rice cake, too?
I told you so!
That explosion earlier was
surely just our imagination.
Cyclone...
Yeah, we have to take them out quickly
and hurry to the Gates of Justice.
Which means that...
This is no time for that, my lord!
There's no way that they can come here!
You're just a kidnapper!
Shoot!
The castle tower is the stronghold of the castle!
I've got an idea.
Shock!
While you're enjoying your little dream,
we'll pass the Gates of Justice.
Wh-What? What idea?
Showing such a pitiful figure is unprecedented!
O... Oh, no... My strength is...
This'll hurt the country's dignity, too!
A way to get the handcuffs off?
Or a way to escape from here?
Mom!
Rika!
Where are you saying the damage is?
"Underground passage
(current location)"
The Bridge of Hesitation lies
in front of the Gates of Justice.
You are the renowned sword, Nose Storm.
Huh?!
You get it now? Then I'm
gonna do it this year again.
Supple Finger Pistol!
"Bridge of Hesitation
(halfway)"
Look at them, Igaram.
They all look like they're having fun.
First we'll cross half of the bridge.
Takt...
This is no time to give me a nice name!
Whip!
Time to get blown away, Buggy!
When the gates are opened,
the other half will rise from the sea,
Gum-Gum... Bazooka!
A country is its people.
Chopper! What's taking so long?!
People's vitality is indeed the
source of the country's dignity.
"Gates of Justice
(cross-section)"
and we'll finally go through
the Gates of Justice.
Good job, guys!
The country wouldn't decline
for a reason as small
Once the gates are closed again,
as the appearance of the castle falling apart.
you'll never have the feeling of hope...
Here you go!
If people are full of energy,
the country will become full of energy,
Our lord's pet?! This camel is?!
How dare you open your mouth
and say such stupid stuff?!
That was helpful.
...ever again.
Helpful?
That's right. Lashes has been lost for a while,
so we've all been looking for him.
and that will become our vitality, too.
The only feeling you'll have is a sense of guilt.
If the pirates really get away...
If you blow me away like that,
Although there was some trouble,
everyone is rejoicing.
...how are you going to...
The reward is a million Ryo-Berries.
You'll endlessly atone for your
sin of having lived until today.
the annoying bubbles on my
body get blown away, too.
That's all we ask, right?
What?!
...take responsibility for it?!
Vivi! You don't mean...
That's a bluff. If you so wish,
I'll keep blowing you away until you die.
A country is its people.
Right, Nico Robin?
Yes, we'll definitely pay the reward.
That certainly is true, right, Igaram?
Ahhh! All right!
Since this is becoming a routine,
it's hard to tell you this,
What was that?!
The weather forecast is cloudy!
but isn't it Orika who deserves the credit?
Where was Robin speaking from?!
Cloudy Tempo!
Indeed...
That's okay. Let's share it. We all
took care of him, so... Right, Mom?
The other side of these doors.
But my lord, how will you come up
with the repair cost for all this?
This is different from the
magic show stuff I used to do!
Yeah, you're right.
Do as you see fit.
Geez... I love you, Orika!
Clouds? More lightning?
Okay, then! Let's have some fun today!
Yes, sire.
I can't let you pass. At least
give me time to say that.
We'll celebrate pops'
complete recovery as well!
Now, let's hurry.
You're too avaricious, Boss.
Thunder doesn't get generated
from such thin clouds.
Come on already!
This isn't the one.
Come to think of it, what're these decorations?
Instead, they'll condense!
Where's the jackpot?!
You don't know?! Today's called
Christmas Eve in foreign countries,
Onami... I can't eat anymore.
Don't tell me...! No, she might do that!
Robin!
and it's a joyous day.
Thanks for waiting! I gathered more!
It's nice to be cheery like
this once in a while, right?
The weather forecast is rain!
No way!
--Cool Ball!
--Shave!
I see...
Say, Onami-san. Can I ask you a favor?
Come to think of it, Father,
where's the one with the jackpot?
Pour down! Rain Tempo!
--What is it?
--Orika took in someone who
collapsed on the street again.
Oh, that's right.
We've already brought him here and
he's outside. Can we bring him inside?
--Oh, my...
--I almost forgot.
Wh-Wh-What was that?! I just heard a voice!
Let's see who'll get it.
Collapsed on the street?
Hey! What was that voice?!
You're not sweet at all. After I was nice
enough to make your skin silky smooth.
There!
Chief, please take Nico Robin
and hurry on ahead.
If being sweet means not
putting up a fight, then I'll pass.
I'm starving...
Hey, monk. If a foreign celebration is
okay with you, why don't you come in?
Cool Charge!
Whoa!
Hm? Doors?
We've got lots of yummy food.
Yeah, sounds good.
I finally got a rice cake! Thank heavens!
They don't look like iron this time.
What?
All right, then! Let's really
whoop it up, shall we?!
Coo coo.
Mirage Tempo!
Get out of my way.
Robin's behind those doors, right?!
What's this? A rice cake with a seed?
Come to think of it, where's Dr. Bluenose?
She disappeared?!
I can't eat something like this!
Now I understand... your powers...
So she's there. So what?
You won't be able to see her...
Seems like he's still busy.
Since he can understand animal languages,
Oh, boy...
...ever again.
Lashes' problem could've been solved
right away if he had been around.
He sure doesn't have any interest in money.
...as well as the strength of CP9.
Hm? The space has opened up. Where am I?
No... I'll go there to see her!
What's this?!
Now that you mention it, you're right.
There you are! Pigeon guy!
Mirage Tempo...!
I'm telling you, today is a
really busy day for reindeers!
Fata Morgana!
I'll be right there, Robin!
"Happy New Year"
I'm glad you came.
Boss! There's trouble! There's trouble!
My strength... is ebbing away.
What'd you do to me?!
Hey! Come in, CP9!
What's this?! My entire body is slippery!
Hey, is that really Chopper?
For some reason, there's always trouble!
Oh, eat a rice cake or something
and calm down, Usopp.
How come he doesn't recognize us?!
A pirate strayed in!
I'm sorry. Now that Buster Call has
been requested, playtime is over.
Can you figure out the mystery of my powers?
Who else has those antlers and wears that hat?!
This is about rice cakes!
They're gonna have a
rice cake tossing event at the castle,
Geez... Hey, are you listening?!
and one of them will have
an amazing treasure inside!
I'll let you fully experience them now.
Hm? Hey, wait a sec, Franky-kun!
That attack pose...
Wait! What you're holding is...
Tempest Kick!
I wonder how big of an uproar it'll cause!
Oh? You thought I'd stay
on the floor without fighting?
What? A-A fake?
Hm?!
Oh, that. Our lord is asking us to protect it.
What're you trying to fire?! He's one of our...
Ahhh! I pressed the button on
the golden transponder snail!
Mirage Tempo. I'm right here!
Just watch! You're mistaken if
you think I'm just a cute beauty!
Oh, that'd be a lot of work. Hey, we are?!
D-Don't be reckless!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Five Namis? Nami Strikes Back with Mirages!"
"Resounding Bad News! Buster Call Invoked!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Big Rice Cake Tossing Race
at the Castle! Red Nose's Plot"
"Nami's Decision!
Fire at the Out-of-Control Chopper!"
"Bubble Master Kalifa!
The Soap Trap Closes in on Nami"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
I'm gonna be a policeman!!