Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Tempest Kick! Lotus!
Take this! Song of Willow!
Wh-What the hell...
...is this?!
A voice...?
Hm?
Hey, hurry up!
Why are you stopping, Nico Robin?!
Hey, are you listening, you woman
whose very life is a crime?!
Hey, Lucci! Drag her along!
Grab her by her hair!
It's an order.
Get moving, Nico Robin.
Don't tell me... you still think that the
Straw Hats are coming to your rescue?
How stupid!
Are you seriously still laying your
hopes on such weak-looking pirates?
The only feeling you'll have is a sense of guilt.
You'll endlessly atone for your
sin of having lived until today.
Right, Nico Robin?
Robin!
Wh-Wh-What was that?! I just heard a voice!
Hey! What was that voice?!
Hm? The space has opened up. Where am I?
There you are! Pigeon guy!
"Resounding Bad News! Buster Call Invoked!"
I'm impressed... I'll say that much.
To think that you've come
this far... all by yourself.
I didn't come by myself!
Hm?
There's no way I could come this far by myself,
and I wouldn't even wanna come by myself.
Unlike you guys, I'm not alone!
Soon all my friends will come here!
Tempest Kick!
Shave!
I'm really starting to get the hang of this.
I'm starting to feel kinda sick.
You're a sailor. Don't say
pathetic things like that!
I-I'm not a sailor. I'm a hero who
hails from the island of snipers...
...although my best friend
Usopp-kun is a sailor.
Stop talking nonsense. Here.
They dodged!
Th-Th-That was close!
Don't let your guard down!
O-Okay.
And don't do things that are uncalled for!
Hm?! What's that supposed
to mean?! How rude!
You sure are rude!
This is no good... It's so
slippery that I can't stand.
Even still...
...what a creepy power.
That sounds like a bunch of sour grapes.
Since you don't come close to me
when it comes to strength and beauty...
...I gave you the gift of silky skin
so that you can at least come
a bit closer to my beauty.
You should appreciate it.
That's very sweet of you. But...
...there's a limit to how far you
can go, right?! There's a limit!
Is there a limit to women's desire?
"Ticked!"
Then why don't you do it to yourself?!
Oh? I don't need it, because
I'm already beautiful enough.
Whoa, what a bitch.
Did you say something?
No, nothing.
Just you wait. I'm about to get you back!
Ow, ow, ow... That damn deer-gorilla!
How dare he mock me?!
But more importantly, the key! The key!
I'd better hurry to that secretary woman.
Deer-gorilla! Wait, you jerk!
Gather those who can still fight to
the front of the Courthouse! Do it now!
Don't flinch! Capture the traitors!
You call us traitors?! Don't make me laugh!
It was you, the Navy, who's been
betraying us for the past 50 years!
We're pirates to start with!
What's wrong with pirates
fighting against the Navy?!
Let's go, Oimo!
Yeah, Kashii!
We'll change our strategy and
bring them down individually!
Attack unit! Concentrate
your fire on Kashii's feet!
Now! Charge!
We bow to nobody in human
wave attacks! Keep on going!
H-Hey! Kashii!
Oimo is next! Prepare to fire!
The situation outside has changed?
The giants who changed sides
have been trying hard for us,
but I guess they are at the end of their rope.
Hey! Hey, hurry up!
Dammit! What a disaster.
To think that a pirate would get this far...
Hey, everyone, come in!
CP9! What the hell are you all doing?!
A pirate has gotten this far!
Hey, are you listening?! Say something!
Wait!
What you're holding is...
Whaaat?!
A... A... A golden transponder snail!
"Navy"
The silver transponder snail
has received a signal!
A Buster Call has been requested!
A Buster Call has been
requested by Admiral Aokiji!
Where?
Enies Lobby!
Have five of the Vice Admirals
near the destination respond!
Considering the distance,
I think it's quicker to head
there from headquarters.
How quick?
It's possible to get there within 30 minutes.
Immediately have ten battleships
get ready to set sail,
and summon five Vice Admirals!
Be swift!
Yes, sir!
A Buster Call has been requested!
The destination is Enies Lobby!
Have ten battleships get
ready to set sail immediately!
Hey! Hey!
Yes, Chief.
Dammit! Oh, crap! This one is
the portable transponder snail.
What have I done? I wasn't careful.
Of all things, I pressed the button
on the golden transponder snail!
Of all things...
...I requested a Buster Call!
B-Buster Call? D-Don't tell me...
What's this? Some internal communication?
How foolish! Cancel it right away!
That's Robin's voice!
Or it'll be a disaster!
Robin!
What? "Cancel it"?
Hey, hey. Who do you think you're talking to?
What the heck is this broadcast?
Hey! Don't move!
We can't move!
Buster Call is great, isn't it?
What's wrong with it?!
That's Chief Spandam's voice, right?
That's right... There's no problem.
I'm the chief of Cipher Pol No. 9.
In order to hand you over
to the Government smoothly,
I requested a Buster Call.
I see no problem in that!
No matter what happens here,
we'll be able to annihilate
the pirates for sure in the end.
How foolish...!
I told you, didn't I?!
That won't be the end of it!
There's no humanity in that attack!
That's the Chief... but who's the woman?
The attack will completely burn
Enies Lobby to the ground!
Buildings, people... the very island itself!
It's a nightmarish concentrated fire that
sacrifices everything to achieve its goal!
That's Buster Call!
You don't know what happened in
Ohara twenty years ago. That's why...
That's fine. It means that this is
very important to the Government.
Now that that idiot Cutty Flam has
burned the blueprints for Pluton...
...your existence is the only
clue to the ancient weapon.
A military power that can turn this
whole era upside down is at stake.
If it improves our chances of killing
those idiots trying to get you back,
even if it causes the death
of thousands of soldiers,
we can say that it's an unavoidable
sacrifice for our glorious future!
Above all things, my promotion is at stake, too.
What?! What's he saying?!
He's gonna sacrifice us?! You gotta be kidding!
What do you think of people's lives?!
Don't forget that CP9 is the
Government's secret organization.
If we need 100 deaths in
order to save 1,000 lives,
we'll kill those 100 without
hesitation on the spot.
Mercilessness is also
a necessity for true justice.
Besides, those incompetent soldiers
who couldn't stop the invading pirates
are better off dead, you idiot!
That portable transponder snail...
The line is connected.
What?
Ahhh! Shoot!
Did everyone hear what I just said?!
S-So... my name is Straw Hat Luffy.
Yeah, right!
Everyone! Leave the island!
A Buster Call has been
requested on Enies Lobby!
If you stay on the island, you won't survive!
This isn't your concern!
--B...
--Buster Call...
It sounds like Buster Call has been requested.
What the hell is that man doing?
Sounds like there's some sort of danger.
It's me who's in danger!
I feel sorry for you guys.
Even your hope is gone now.
Don't worry.
We're used to situations like this.
Pirate kid, what kind of
destiny were you born with?
This is getting even more interesting!
A Buster Call has been requested!
Battleships are coming!
Get off of Enies Lobby!
Battleships are coming? Why are
the Navy soldiers running away?
The woman said that the island
will be burned to the ground.
But this is the Government's island!
How should I know why?!
Hey, hey! If you guys're running away,
at least untie us first!
It's a Buster Call!
We'll be dead if we stay here!
Bring some ships to the front!
Get ready to sail out!
The Navy is coming to attack this place!
We got left behind...
Hey! What're we gonna do?!
Isn't this dangerous?!
It's been dangerous ever since
we set foot in this place.
What about Bro?! What's gonna
happen to Big Bro Franky?!
Yeah. If he doesn't come back here,
we can't go back together!
The Straw Hats, too!
So what about us?!
What will... happen to all of us?!
We can't afford to waste time, either.
Yeah, we have to take them out quickly
and hurry to the Gates of Justice.
I've got an idea.
Wh-What? What idea?
A way to get the handcuffs off?
Or a way to escape from here?
You are the renowned sword, Nose Storm.
This is no time to give me a nice name!
Chopper! What's taking so long?!
How dare you open your mouth
and say such stupid stuff?!
If the pirates really get away...
...how are you going to...
...take responsibility for it?!
What was that?!
Where was Robin speaking from?!
The other side of these doors.
I can't let you pass. At least
give me time to say that.
Coo coo.
Get out of my way.
Robin's behind those doors, right?!
So she's there. So what?
You won't be able to see her...
...ever again.
No... I'll go there to see her!
I'll be right there, Robin!
What's this?! My entire body is slippery!
I'm sorry. Now that Buster Call has
been requested, playtime is over.
Tempest Kick!
What? A-A fake?
Mirage Tempo. I'm right here!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Five Namis? Nami Strikes Back with Mirages!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!