Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
You should pay attention to the
weather forecast by a navigator.
It really took a long time.
Chopper! What's wrong?!
Oh, that's right. I get it!
But I'm finally here.
Take a good look at me! It's me! I'm Nami!
Come on!
What is it?
Once I've gone through those gates,
I can be the Government's...
We can save her... As long as they
have me, we can save Robin! Dammit!
The one from earlier...!
No, the world's hero!
"Dammit"?! You don't have
to get upset or anything!
Let's hurry, Nami-kun!
As I promised, I'll kill you in
an instant. Die without pain.
Lucci, huh? So you're having
a tough time against him?
Thunder Lance Tempo!
Chopper!
Don't make me repeat it.
Where's Nico Robin? I brought two keys.
Too bad. If you'd stayed connected with
that shepherd and had him protect you,
There isn't even a shred of hope left for you.
No matter how strong you are...
Chopper! Stop it!
Shall I give you a hand?
you would've been okay.
No. More importantly...
I heard some voice in the passage earlier,
...my forecast is never wrong.
Now, this is it for you!
...please stop Robin.
but no one showed up after all, did they?
Don't kill him! Please! We don't need your key!
Lucci might be killing him right about now, huh?
You can get to the Gates of Justice
through the doors behind the pigeon guy.
Now, die!
Usopp!
It seems that we disagree.
Robin has already been taken away.
My friends are waiting. I'll be taking your key.
I guess there's no point in discussing it.
I'll restrain him.
I don't have much time, either.
Just super leave it to me, you jerk!
I'm gonna hurry up and finish it here.
Gum-Gum... Gatling!
Tempest Kick!
Stamp!
This is bad! Even the soles
are slippery. I can't dodge it!
What're you doing, Chopper?! It's us!
Whip!
Spear!
Ahh! Stop it!
Thanks for waiting!
Hey, is that really Chopper?!
How come he doesn't recognize us?!
Huh?! I could dodge it!
Ah... My right leg went back to normal.
Arms, legs, and neck...
If I can control their reach at will,
I don't know, but it must be Chopper!
Who else has those antlers and wears that hat?!
Why? What caused it?
I can swing my swords vigorously!
Who the hell are you?!
I'm a wolf. I'll keep going
after you until I chew you up.
Step aside, you guys!
It's wet...
--Huh?
--That guy...!
It got wet in the earlier
commotion. Oh, that's right!
I'm a Four-Sword Style swordsman.
Franky! What're you trying to do?!
I can now make full use of the giraffe's power!
Water! I can wash off
the soap power with water!
This is one of our...
I know! Just be quiet.
Oh? You're still alive.
You no longer have any chance against me!
I don't intend to run...
I don't intend to be killed...
This is the only way that I
can think of to deal with him.
The giraffe's power is very strong...
Power holders have a weakness...
And I don't intend to forgive.
I'll push him off to the sea.
You can store your obstructive neck away...
Forgive?
I'll go easy, so bear with me!
A hunter.
You use the Four-Sword Style...
Are you sympathizing with Nico Robin?
Aren't you being too optimistic?
Coup de...
Even if you figured out
how to undo Golden Bubbles,
A distracted mind just creates
openings during a fight.
...Vent!
Hmph!
I-I'm sorry, Sanji-kun.
there's no way I'd let you do that.
If you have time to pity that ill-fated woman,
What?!
He stopped my sword attacks?!
You bastard, Franky! That's reckless!
I...
you should think of a way
to save your neck here.
Sheep Cloud! Relaxing Bubbles!
What're you doing to our friend?!
After all... I...
None of those things...
can be a basis for my defeat.
Watch your mouth.
Don't worry. He discussed
this with me beforehand.
You're still alive. That's all that matters.
I'll blow away those bubbles with wind!
What?
Everyone has things that they
can do and things that they can't.
I'm the kind who heats up with anger.
Cyclone...
Sanji...
"Demon God Zoro! An Incarnation
of Asura Born from Fighting Spirit"
Shoot!
Look outside, both of you.
O... Oh, no... My strength is...
So you're finally released?
No way...
Its destructive power is just like that of a devil.
You'd better stop laughing and start regretting.
Supple Finger Pistol!
Never again...
Diable Jambe!
Takt...
...will you get a chance like
you had earlier to slay me...
Whip!
What? W-Wait!
Flambage...
World Government!
What a useless retort.
Then show me your "basis"!
...Shot!
"Hunter Sanji Makes an Entrance?
Elegy for a Lying Wolf"
The Gates of Justice are about to open.
Three-Sword Style...
Battleships are coming to attack!
That was helpful.
Robin...!
Get off of Enies Lobby!
...Leopard...
Helpful?
They're gonna start firing cannons!
...Spinning...
Everyone, get off of the island!
If you blow me away like that,
God creates food...
We'll get dragged into the Buster Call!
He's gonna fly towards me!
We'll die if we stay here!
the annoying bubbles on
my body get blown away, too.
...Shot!
Once those gates are opened
and Robin-chan goes through there,
...and the Devil creates spice.
Paper Art!
That's a bluff. If you so wish, I'll keep
blowing you away until you die.
the sea beyond hosts a nest of Sea Kings
and we have no means to cross it.
I guess I made it a little too spicy.
Past that, there's a large
prison and Navy Headquarters.
Stop, Nico Robin!
Can't be...! I'm sure I saw through his attack!
Soon Robin-chan will be taken
to a place beyond our reach.
The weather forecast is cloudy!
Even if you go back the way we came,
all you'll find are the corpses of pirates!
"Fierce Sword Attacks! Zoro vs. Kaku,
Powerful Sword Fighting Showdown"
Cloudy Tempo!
Oh, no... Luffy didn't make it in time?
Don't tell me...
This is different from the
magic show stuff I used to do!
Enough already.
Teach her a lesson, Funkfreed!
Did he actually foresee my reaction?!
Clouds? More lightning?
Teach her a lesson, Funkfreed!
Luffy is just ahead.
Oni... Giri!
Thunder doesn't get generated
from such thin clouds.
What are you so surprised about?
Don't hit her vital spots, got that?
Instead, they'll condense!
Don't tell me you've never been cut before...
Don't hit her vital spots, got that?
Ivory...
Don't tell me...! No, she might do that!
...Dart!
Ivory...
Hmph! I see... So it looks like
it wasn't just an empty boast.
The weather forecast is rain!
...Dart!
Whoa! Damn that giraffe and Moss Head!
Cool Ball!
I underestimated you a bit. But no longer.
Shave!
Are they trying to destroy this tower?
Pour down! Rain Tempo!
I've mastered the Six Powers. On top of that,
I now have the wild powers of a giraffe.
Techniques, power, speed...
There's no way you can beat me in any of them!
I won't let you escape, you dumb woman!
I won't give you any more openings to attack!
You're not sweet at all. After I was nice
enough to make your skin silky smooth.
This is...
Don't underestimate me!
I won't let you escape, you dumb woman!
"Gates of Justice"
"Underground passage"
Tempest Kick Throwing Stars!
Now, let's go through the
doors to our dreams together.
Gates of Justice?
Don't underestimate me!
If being sweet means not
putting up a fight, then I'll pass.
So I can get there by following this?
Now, let's go through the
doors to our dreams together.
Leave getting his key to me.
Cool Charge!
I hope Nami-san and Usopp are
already headed to Robin-chan by now.
Giraffe Blast!
Are you changing fighters? That's fine by me.
What?
Shoot!
He went back to normal.
Mirage Tempo!
I'll do what you can't do.
I have to hurry up too
and bring this #1 key to her.
My neck can become a whip...
Whiplash!
And you do what I can't do!
She disappeared?!
Now I understand... your powers...
I'd better get going!
What?
He'd better not be dead.
Think carefully.
I didn't expect that even his friends
wouldn't know how to handle that.
...as well as the strength of CP9.
Grasp the situation!
And now for the faster version...
Fierce Whiplash!
You bitch! Come on already!
What's this?!
Don't you wanna save Nico Robin?!
As long as we have you, we can
save Robin-chan for sure! Usopp!
I do!
Mirage Tempo!
How's this?! Can you still talk big?!
Well, anyway, the fact still remains
that he took out a member of CP9.
Fata Morgana!
I want to live!
We're finally on the Bridge of Hesitation!
Wh-What I can do...
The four-sword attacks
will not stop. Just give it up!
"Nami's Decision!
Fire at the Out-of-Control Chopper!"
In consideration of your friends who
defended you even after you turned
into such a terrible form,
I'll forgive you for attacking me.
Look, Nico Robin!
Fury Slash!
"Fiery Kicks! Sanji's Full
Course of Foot Techniques"
We'd better hurry.
The mirage from earlier...
In the end, you've only got one body.
Here I come...!
But... even if I hurry, I still don't know
how to get to the Gates of Justice.
That's right. One of them is the real me.
As long as they have me... we can save Robin?
The other four are illusions
being reflected by the chilly air.
You can see the opened
Gates of Justice, can't you?
What a vigorous attack!
Well, well! What's the matter?!
All you can do now is block!
We'll be your guides!
What's that? What does that mean?
Illusions, you say?
You can't defeat me!
Little ones!
That sounds mysterious and lovely.
I found Franky!
It took a long time... It really took a long time.
But when you think about it calmly,
What?! You guys know where the
passage to the Gates of Justice is?!
it becomes obvious that illusions
don't have offensive power.
But I'm finally here.
You guys are mere pirates.
It was a mistake to go up against the
World Government in the first place!
Once I've gone through those gates,
I can be the Government's...
Yep, we do! We're here to be guides!
In other words, this is just an empty threat.
No, the world's hero!
Now that it's come to this, in the
name of justice, you'll have to die...
That's right.
Grandma's over there, too.
So you turn defiant? You're not sweet.
Shave!
Tell me where it is right away!
...just like that woman!
Go!
And I'll give you and old hag Kokoro
instructions as to what you should do!
The bridge that continues onto the other
side of the doors has indeed risen up,
Thunder Charge!
O-Okay! Usopp!
Ow, ow! My wounds hurt!
Roger.
Only one of the five of me is real.
Bear it! It's better than
being killed here, right?!
and is now waiting for
the hero to come and cross.
You bastard...
So what?
He's unconscious, but seems to be okay.
Good point.
And... Thunder Ball!
Only 20% of my attacks are real as well.
Why don't you try dodging them?
You drank too much, old hag! Are you okay?!
This is wonderful! Just take a look
at the path to my bright future!
Oh, no! I have to bring the keys
to Nico Robin as soon as possible!
Oh, shoot! I have to guard myself!
Which ones are the real ones?!
Iron Body Kenpo!
Wolf Repel!
Well, for you, I guess it's the path to hell, huh?
Its power, on the other hand, is 100%.
You guys come later, too, with that deer!
I told you... that I'd throw
you off your guard, didn't I?
What was that?!
--Okay.
--Got it! Go, Franky!
Right? You think so too, right, Nico Robin?
For a moment, he looked like a demon
god with three faces and six arms!
What the hell is with this guy?!
So, we have no choice but
to stop Chopper that way.
You're getting carried away.
--No!
--Hey, what're you doing?!
Some hunter you are. You just talk big.
And then, after that, take these
#3 and #4 keys and hurry to Robin.
This is very different from the old Clima Takt.
You talk too much.
Ow!
A mere Thunder Ball attack
has this much power.
You're tired of listening to me?
One of them might unlock her handcuffs.
Hey! Stop!
Then I'll use my strongest
Tempest Kick, Sky Slicer,
With my next powerful attack, you'll fall.
If so, call me using this portable
transponder snail that secretary had.
Oh, that's right. I get it!
the one that slashed this tower...
You... Enough already, you bitch!
What kind of prediction is that? How cocky...
What is it?
Okay.
We can save her... As long as they
have me, we can save Robin! Dammit!
You still don't get it?!
It's pointless to try and struggle!
It's not a prediction. It's a forecast.
Leave freeing Zoro and Nose-king to me.
...and end this battle by splitting you into two!
"Dammit"?! You don't have
to get upset or anything!
I've controlled both humidity and temperature.
That's fine, but what will we do after that?
So give it up. You have nowhere to escape.
Do you really get who I am?!
Let's hurry, Nami-kun!
The weather in this room belongs to me!
Hey, wait up!
We've come this far, but even if
we're able to rescue Nico Robin,
It's on a completely different level from
the demonstration I showed you earlier!
I got it! I got it!
I'm the world's hero. I'm the
world's hero, you got that?!
What's the big deal with
controlling the weather?
Hey, be quiet. That wolf's gonna come after us!
there's still no bridge between this tower
and Enies Lobby. So we can't go back.
The Six Powers are techniques
that exceed human abilities.
You're in the worst situation without a
shred of hope left! I'm different from you!
How insolent!
Yeah...
You fool...
That wasn't the real one!
Now that a Buster Call has been requested,
I have a bright future full of hopes and dreams!
The possibility of catching
the real one today is again 20%.
Maybe I should kill them after all.
we don't have time to go back
the way we came in the first place.
You're the one who has to give up.
Then...
Do you get it, you dumb woman?!
So there's no question about it, right?
Dumb! Dumb! Dumb!
Demon Aura... Nine-Sword Style...
Behind us is a deadly waterfall.
Ahead of us is a mysterious path.
According to today's sky forecast,
although atmospheric pressure is stable,
Which would you pick?
Well, ahead is the only way, but...
small dark clouds with violent
air currents will remain stationary
Then, when we're done with
what we have to do in this tower,
...Asura!
for a while, and soon they will shoot
thunderbolts through your chest.
Luffy...
we'll all gather at the Gates of Justice!
Everyone...
As for what's after that, just leave it to...
The demon god I saw earlier...!
Everyone...!
Please watch out for paralysis of the heart!
--To you?!
--To luck!
He can show such a powerful
illusion with his fighting spirit?!
Luck?!
Dark Cloud Tempo!
Splendid! But it's too late!
If this is lightning, I showed you at
the beginning that I can guard myself.
Gotta hurry! Gotta hurry!
You're the one who's too late.
It'll be meaningless if I
can't make it in time! Hm?
Now you've gone and done it...
As long as I'm being careful...
I can see something up ahead!
The flaw in that technique is that
you can't move around while using it.
We've...
Wait until you dodge this
Tempest Kick to make such a boast.
...wasted quite a bit of time.
Damn straight!
I can't believe you guys have been
acting so dumb at a tough time like this!
We'll reach our destination
in about ten minutes!
Sky Slicer!
That's because this guy was doing stupid stuff.
Hurry up and check the formation of all ships!
You sure take me lightly. Are you
telling me to break it with an attack?!
Ten Finger Pistol!
You both are super stupid!
Hurry up and get their keys already!
Yes, sir!
Troisième... Haché!
Hey! Stand up already, you bitch!
Then... Soap Sheep!
Iron Body!
Tempest Kick...
Now, let's go, Nico Robin!
Straight Line!
I don't have to know which one is the real one.
I'll swallow everything with a
big wave of Relaxing Bubbles.
That's just as I instructed. Nice job, Zoro-kun!
Fight! Zoro!
Is this the exit?!
You guys fight, too!
Sheep Cloud!
That doesn't work on me, you fool!
Tidal Wave!
My slash attack...
That long neck of yours...
What's with his kicks?
...was turned into mist?!
You... Straw Hat!
You'd better hope it doesn't
become your weak point.
Ah! Franky!
No need to worry about that.
That technique you guys use
to make your body like iron...
Hardships are fine by me!
What're you doing here, you jerk?!
I'll be a goner if I get hit by that.
I choose to walk the path of Asura!
The one on the floor after I
swallow everything is the real one.
You idiot! Enough with the attitude already!
...is really a pain in the ass.
The muscles I gained are strong enough
that I can even freely control my neck.
Tempest Kick Lone Wolf!
That's not gonna happen!
I'm on your side right now! Just give it up!
Cyclone Tempo!
And bullets, too!
Nose Pistol!
Lucci, huh? So you're having
a tough time against him?
She used wind to blow the bubbles away!
Basses Côte!
Where's Nico Robin? I brought two keys.
Longe!
Asura... Silver Mist!
Tendron!
Flanchet! Quasi! Queue! Cuisseau! Jarret!
Shall I give you a hand?
Wh-What the heck?
No. More importantly...
But it looks like the one who got
through it is the real one, huh?
To think we'd feel this much impact from here...
...please stop Robin.
You can get to the Gates of Justice
through the doors behind the pigeon guy.
Veau... Shot!
Iron Body Kenpo!
Robin has already been taken away.
I'll restrain him.
I said your kicks don't work on me, didn't I?!
That made a square-shaped hole in a rock!
Wolf Fang!
Just super leave it to me, you jerk!
That nose is more amazing than Sogepp's!
Wh-Wh-Who're you calling Sogepp?!
Finger Pistol!
And don't make uncalled-for
comparisons like that!
Now that attack worked, didn't it?!
Oh? I thought it was another illusion.
Well, at any rate...
That was Iron Body Kenpo! Wolf Fang Stance!
--Eek!
--...Kaku's gotten quite
proficient at using his powers.
I won't let you run around anymore.
I'll just turn your body into Swiss cheese.
W-Wolf! I-I'm the one you have to deal with!
I'm the only one of the Six Powers Masters
who can move around while using
Iron Body on my entire body.
I'm saying that if I had to choose,
I like meat better!
Hm? Well, don't get so worked up.
Stop your rambling!
You guys wanna save your friend, right?
You've already forgotten it, haven't you?
Deuxième Haché!
Th-That's right! I'll take your key!
You should pay attention to the
weather forecast by a navigator.
And I'm saying it doesn't matter, herbivore!
Hm?
I've got...
In any case, I'll hurry up and take your key.
Huh?
...a message for you from
the junior boss of Galley-La.
Hurry up and take it to her.
From the dark clouds to the Clima Takt...
What?
If I can't make it in time,
it'll be the same as defeat.
Go save Nico Robin.
It appears to have worked,
but it actually didn't?
...a thunderbolt will burst forth...!
When you see... those guys, tell them...
Wh-What on earth are you...
Two-Sword Style... Nigiri...
To be honest, I don't wanna
kill people. I hate blood.
He said you guys're fired.
Well, did it or didn't it?!
Come on!
Hm?
You get stronger when you
wear a towel on your head?
Th-Then, I'll just...
The one from earlier...!
Well done.
Who knows...?
...take the key and...
I've been waiting for a man like you.
No! Watch out!
Thunder Lance Tempo!
Tower Climb!
Hm?
Ten Finger Pistol!
Tower Climb Return!
Would you save her... Save Robin?
No matter how strong you are...
Don't let your guard down.
...my forecast is never wrong.
What?! What're you saying?
I considered you guys my friends all this time!
Flash!
I'm a wolf. I get people off
their guard and chew them up.
I kept quiet about this, but... Robin is...
Ripple!
If you jump, you'll have blind spots.
Giraffe Scythe!
...actually my little sister... whom I
was separated from a long time ago.
Paulie, huh?
I see... I'm in trouble.
What?!
Assassination skills aren't very
helpful in other lines of work.
Is that true?!
Usopp!
D-Dammit! What am I doing?
I didn't know.
Iron Body. No Blind Spots.
My friends are waiting. I'll be taking your key.
She never told us anything like that, so...
You can still work in a zoo.
That's just natural...
What?!
...but it's true.
What an unbelievable masked idiot!
Why don't you just run
around like you did earlier?
Hey, be nice...
It was over twenty years ago.
You're fast as lightning
when you're running away.
That son of a bitch... Damn deer-gorilla!
I'll never forget.
Stop mocking me.
I've become square with no blind spots.
Huh?
On an island in the West Blue,
We no longer have that kind of time.
Shut up! What the hell are you doing?!
on a sunny, pleasant summer day,
You're so naive.
Robin and I went to a beach to play.
Have you not noticed...?
New weapon, Kabuto!
Special Attack! Sunflower Star!
What?
Giraffes have four legs.
--Big brother!
--My sister and I were close.
Oh?
This entire island is a mess!
--Robin!
--So we always played together.
Tempest Kick!
Like I said, are you gonna fight or not?!
They all had better be okay.
Where are you looking?
My attack has already started.
--Look!
--On that day, too, we both were happy...
Sorry.
Oh, I see. Fireworks, huh?
The slash attacks I directed upwards...
...until those guys came.
Hey, Navy! Come back!
Usopp!
...will deflect off the ceiling...
Moon Walk!
Take us with you!
...and pour down on you!
Giraffe Shower!
When I took my eyes off of her for a second...
Hm?
Tempest Kick!
Sky Slicer!
Stop it!
Iron Body.
Hey, Moss Head! Where's the key?!
Chopper! What's taking you so long?!
...those pirates kidnapped Robin!
Yeah...
I just got it.
Slash attack pellets...
I see.
Dammit! I can't block them!
Robin! Give Robin back!
At any rate, looks like you
guys really put on a show.
Didn't you guys cause the tower
to slip even more? Is it okay?
Who cares? That's not important.
As I promised, I'll kill you in
an instant. Die without pain.
After that day, I never saw her again.
Too bad. If you'd stayed connected with
that shepherd and had him protect you,
Anyway, we now have all the keys.
When I found out that she
escaped from those pirates,
you would've been okay.
You see what happens when a
lamb wanders off all by himself?
--Robin...
--...it was too late.
Nose Pistol!
Yeah.
He gets eaten by a scary wolf.
Let's hurry to Robin.
It was all my fault.
Now, this is it for you!
So I wanna save her at any cost,
What do you think you're doing?!
Run!
Hey, stop it, wolf! You bastard!
Hold it, Nico Robin!
but I can't do anything due to
the position I'm in right now.
Don't kill him! Please! We don't need your key!
Just run! Keep running at full speed!
So... I'll entrust everything to you.
You fool! You'll die next!
It's our duty to survive so that we won't
worry our Bro and the Straw Hats!
Please, save her!
Okay, I got it. Just leave it to me.
Tempest Kick!
Ribbit!
Run in order to live! Even if it breaks your legs!
Dammit!
I'll take this key and save her without fail.
Now, die!
You bastard...!
What a tough guy you are.
Yeah!
I'm flabbergasted.
Run!
You think I'd buy that crap?!
Coo coo!
We're counting on you, giants!
I've trained my body, you damn gi-riff-raff!
Usopp!
You guys... If you guys are just gonna
ride on there, then at least be quiet!
Gi-riff-raff? I am a giraffe!
Gi-riff-raff.
Robin-chan is your little sister?
That's wrong! I'm not gi-riff-raff!
Yeah, I agree!
You dumbass! If you're gonna lie,
try to make it more believable.
Go! In the name of Elbaf!
--Shut up!
--Hm?
Shut up!
Gi-riff-raff... Gi-riff-raff...
Stop rambling... I could care less!
Grandma! Hurry! Hurry up! Hurry up!
Hey, Chimney! I'm old! Show a little kindness!
If you're mocking me, you'll pay for it.
Seriously, I can't keep running
unless I refuel myself.
Likewise. You'd better prepare
yourself. Playtime is over.
Who the hell are you?!
Whoa!
First, I'm gonna break through... that Iron Body!
Grandma! He's gonna fall off!
Pull him up! Pull him up!
Seriously, after coming this far,
you're still causing me trouble,
Boy, you sure are demanding, geez...!
you dumb woman!
Grandma!
"Hurry up," right? I know!
Dumb! Dumb! Dumb! Dumb woman!
I'm getting pretty exhausted because of you!
Walk on your own, bitch!
Don't make me repeat it.
A hunter.
There isn't even a shred of hope left for you.
All right!
You sure do say funny things.
I heard some voice in the passage earlier,
You are going to break through Iron Body?
but no one showed up after all, did they?
You think you can do it?
Lucci might be killing him right about now, huh?
Yeah, of course.
Want me to try?
Now, die!
One-Sword Style...
Usopp!
You bitch! You made me
have to do all that coughing!
Coo coo!
Dumb! Dumb! Dumb! Dumb woman!
...Lion Strike!
Dumb! Dumb! Dumb! Dumb woman!!
Tempest Kick!
Dragon Cut!
You should have realized by now.
No matter what tricks you play,
you can never go through these doors.
Would you have been able to cut if it was iron?!
The bridge is finally completely connected!
You're wrong! I'll do whatever
it takes to go through there!
It's my call as to whether or not I
use Iron Body to block your attack.
I can't stop laughing!
Hey! Guards at the Gates of Justice!
Are you guys ready?!
Deer-gorilla! Where'd you go?!
It seems that we disagree.
What? Franky! What are you doing there?!
Sanji-kun!
Yes, sir! The escort ship is already
in front of the third column and...
I guess there's no point in discussing it.
I see. I guess it's not that simple, huh?
Oh, hey, lady.
Sanji...!
That's not it! Why aren't you
coming out to salute me?!
I don't have much time, either.
How did you get out of that state?!
Gum-Gum... Gatling!
That monster deer-gorilla in
your group came here, didn't he?
Great Spandam the hero is passing through!
A bathtub fell from the sky
and the spell got broken.
Ah! Y-Yes! We'll be right out!
Stamp!
Deer... You mean Chopper?
One Gorilla!
Whip!
Geez, those idiots! They can't
do anything on their own!
It's probably because I got water all over me.
Yeah, that deer-gorilla.
Spear!
Two Gorilla!
Yeah, he did. What's the deal?
What happened to him?
Now, bring it on!
Hey, Nico Robin. Look at that.
How should I know?! I wanna
ask that question myself!
That small gate is the actual entrance.
Three-Sword Style...
He isn't someone who can
transform into something like that?
A strength contest this time?
When you pass through it, you'll cross
the border between heaven and hell.
More importantly, Nami-san...
How interesting.
How would I know?!
I've never seen him in that form.
Nose Pistol!
I see... I thought you guys
might know how to deal with that.
Didn't you fall in love with me again?!
Two Gorilla Slash!
And that's the moment my name
will be engraved in history!
Then, I guess I'll just kill him anyhow.
I wish the bathtub had hit you directly.
Did it work a little this time, wolf?
If you say that again, I'm gonna kill you.
What strength...!
Whoa! You bastard! The key...!
I-I'll never say it again. Ever again.
You gave it to me!
Nose-sopp!
So now it's at the point where you're not
using any part of Sogeking in my name.
How dare you...?!
But we still need to do something.
You still haven't learned your lesson?
If he rampages about while he's that huge,
Iron Body!
You speak in an arrogant manner.
you never know how long this tower will last.
I-I'm sorry, Sanji-kun.
You're the type who can't even
imagine your own fall, aren't you?
Yeah. He isn't in a state
where he'll listen to us.
--See ya!
--Ahh! Hold it!
I...
I'm the one who has the trademark on foul play!
After all... I...
It seemed like he didn't recognize me,
so I think he's lost his memory.
How dare you mock me?! Shave!
How haughty you are!
Oops. Where're you trying to run away to now?
You're still alive. That's all that matters.
So are you!
Everyone has things that they
can do and things that they can't.
What's causing it?
I'm not totally sure,
I'm actually sympathizing with you, at least.
Sanji...
but it may have something to
do with his Devil Fruit powers.
Gum-Gum... Gatling!
Party Table...!
But it can't be helped, right?
Your life has no value.
Then there's only one way
to solve this problem...
Iron Body Kenpo!
Look outside, both of you.
Paper Art.
Hm?!
Cuisseau Shoot!
Hurry up and die.
By the way, you're not bad at all.
You took this woman down?
No way...
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
Brochette!
That bitch!
Shave!
Her key is important. The #2 key is.
Key... Hold on a sec. I was searching for it.
I don't wanna die...
Dammit! I'm pissed!
I don't wanna die...!
Key! Key! Where'd you hide it?
If you wanna get hurt that badly... that's fine.
I don't wanna die!
Yow! Nice scandalous action!
Straw Hat!
I'll show you the true power
of my Iron Body Kenpo!
Ahh! Stay back! Stay back!
Tsk!
The Gates of Justice are about to open.
Listen, you guys! To tell you
the truth, 8,000 men are under m...
Tempest Kick!
Iron Body Kenpo! Wolf Plantain Stance!
I mean, under my close friend Usopp-kun!
Robin...!
S-So, this island is already surrounded.
Wolf Hunt High-Speed Scratch!
I've had enough, you bitch!
Stop the useless resistance and surrender!
Weapons Left!
Whoa! A slashing attack?!
Stand up already and...
Shave!
Eight thousand guys? It'll be
worthwhile killing all of them, huh?
Once those gates are opened
and Robin-chan goes through there,
What? She isn't moving. What's going on?!
What?!
Hurry up and call them in here.
Gum-Gum... Rocket!
the sea beyond hosts a nest of Sea Kings
and we have no means to cross it.
Don Po Ro!
Don't be a fool. He's clearly lying.
Past that, there's a large prison
and Navy Headquarters.
To think that you easily fell
for such an obvious lie...
What?!
She's biting into the stone bridge!
Gum-Gum... Bazooka!
You're a disgrace to CP9.
Soon Robin-chan will be taken
to a place beyond our reach.
Who's the fool here? I knew it was a lie;
I was just making fun of him.
She just doesn't know when
to give up! How irritating!
Oh, no... Luffy didn't make it in time?
Straw Hat!
What do you think of the
power of an Iron Body punch?
Okay, stay like that and don't move!
It's detestable how she clings to life!
I can't stand how ridiculously honest
and incredibly serious you are.
It's incomparably powerful, isn't it?
Wait!
It's pitiful and vulgar!
Moon Walk!
Don't waste your time on this guy. Go already!
What's wrong with being serious and honest?
You're a criminal! The only way you
can make others happy is by dying!
Coo coo.
I'm saying the "ridiculously" and
"incredibly" parts are bad, blockhead!
I said I'd restrain him, didn't I?!
Tempest Kick! Lupus Fall!
Why must you act so miserable
until the very last minute?!
Restrain him?! But you're barely
holding your own against him!
Dammit! I can't get through here!
When Robin's waiting for me...!
We should work together and...
I fear death so much...
My plan worked. Yay...
Franky!
He's my opponent! I'm the
one who has to restrain him.
Give it up. You'll never see her again.
But now...
The Buster Call is imminent, so...
I'll say it one more time.
Hurry up and go to Robin!
I don't wanna die...!
You can't go beyond these doors.
Eek!
We've wasted too much time, but...
Help me, everyone...
And stop her!
Let's both get serious and...
You were naive to think that you
could steal the key from me and run.
Or she'll be gone forever!
Luffy...!
Huh?
--...settle this, shall we?
--...settle this, huh?
We won't be able to get her back!
What?! H-Hey, hold on a sec. Calm down!
I'm a wolf. I'll keep going
after you until I chew you up.
Finger Pistol!
We're calm!
You...
I told you that doesn't work...!
Stop! Sea Train!
Tempest Kick!
Yellow Lotus!
Give Tom-san back to us!
Oh, shoot!
Gum-Gum...
Straw Hat!
Oh? You're still alive.
...Gatling!
No...
I don't intend to run...
I don't intend to be killed...
--Pick it up!
--Okay!
That's not possible.
My mission is to go past those
doors as soon as possible!
That attack doesn't work on me.
Finger Pistol--!
Finger Pistol!
I won't let you get away.
Looks like playtime is over.
Don't let your guard down.
And I don't intend to forgive.
Straw Hat!
It's no use. You can't pass through here.
Forgive?
Hurry!
Oh no...
Go!
Shut up! Strong...
Shave!
Are you sympathizing with Nico Robin?
You...
--Iron Body.
--...Hammer!
Ow, ow, ow...
A distracted mind just creates
openings during a fight.
Okay!
This is bad. They're pretty fired up.
I thought I said I wouldn't...
If you have time to pity that ill-fated woman,
We'd better hurry up and take these off.
...let you get away!
Now, come!
Chopper! Hurry up!
Moon Walk!
you should think of a way
to save your neck here.
I said come! We're going to the bridge!
What the hell is this monster?!
Shave!
Watch your mouth.
There was another Zoan type power holder?!
What?!
Finger Pistol!
I'm the kind who heats up with anger.
What? He doesn't budge an inch...
Am I gonna make it in time?
Does that mean that this
guy's also part of CP9?!
I hope either the #3 or #4 key frees Nico Robin!
Come to think of it, I feel
like I've seen him before.
If you're under strain, there's no
chance you can bring me down.
...when it was strong enough
to blow Chapapa away.
I'm sure my attacks have done
quite a bit of damage to you by now.
Anyway, I have to stop them at any cost!
I see. You came after defeating Fukurou, huh?
Ch-Chopper?!
I thought I told you.
If that wasn't enough, then...
I'm your opponent!
But sorry. My Power Level
is five times as strong as his.
It's this way!
Iron Body Kenpo! Devil Wolf!
Is it this way?
What're you doing, Chopper?! It's us!
--Chimney! Hurry up!
--It's this way!
I still haven't shown you...
Ahh! Stop it!
--This tower will get hit by cannon fire, too.
--Is it this way?
...a giraffe's real wild strength!
Wait, Grandma! They'll get
lost if I don't put guide marks.
Hey, is that really Chopper?!
How come he doesn't recognize us?!
Stop talking! Just show it to me.
I don't know, but it must be Chopper!
Who else has those antlers and wears that hat?!
Sure thing!
It's splendid that you
were able to defeat Fukurou.
Have a good look at the giraffe's power!
It can be said that you're already
in the boundary of superhumans.
Then, what about our hope and the #2 key?!
Go ahead and laugh while you can.
As I suspected, he's incomparably
stronger than the others.
Who knows? This is it! We're gonna die.
Giraffe Cannon!
But... die.
But something is wrong.
There's no giraffe like that.
Gum-Gum...
Extreme Nose Pistol!
...Jet Pistol!
Isn't he the one who looks
like he is about to die?
Picking me as your opponent
was your downfall, huh?
Giraffe Blast!
Hm?
It seems as if his vitality is rapidly dimming.
It stretched?!
If you were fighting Jabra, you might've
had a slight chance of winning.
I don't know what's so fun
about spinning like that, but...
See? What did I tell you?
Wh-Wh-What does that mean?
That long neck is your weak point.
It may be that him staying in that form
uses up too much energy or something.
That's not totally true. Tempest Kick!
When you see... those guys, tell them...
Spinning White Blade!
What the hell?! What do we do
about him and the other two?!
What the hell did you...
Hm? What's with him?
One of his feet is now red!
What's that steam?!
Hey, what's gonna happen
to the key? The #2 key?!
"You guys're fired."
Devil's foot...
I don't know what happened,
It's you who has an opening.
Diable Jambe!
Sure will.
Tsk! Just what kind of creature is he?!
but he must've fought incredibly hard...
The heat generated from spinning
will make my fast kicks even more...
Second Gear.
No, I'm glad it's you.
I won't miss next time.
So hard that he transformed into that.
Enough with your bluffing.
#2...
Giraffe Cannon!
It's glowing!
Wha...
Oh, shoot! I pushed my neck in so
much that my arms and legs got longer!
This can't last too long.
We got interrupted. What's that monster?
What kind of setup does your body have?!
But I'll stop him, so you go on ahead, Franky!
When the Buster Call is imminent...
It's as if flour got crammed in
and got pushed out as noodles.
Ow, it burns!
Of course he'd interrupt us.
It seems like he's one of those pirates.
Hurry!
Robin's waiting!
Get out of here!
Its destructive power is just like that of a devil.
Just like a pasta machine!
Okay, Straw Hat!
Hey! Let us get on board!
Anything that gets in our way...
I don't know what's going on,
but finish him off with that!
...should be eliminated.
That's not possible! The sea train is full!
Hm?
Get some ships from the outlying island!
Pasta Machine!
Although this is a small fry...
Don't just make that into an attack name!
...we've got another prey now.
I said I wouldn't let you do that...
You bastard! I thought you were strangely calm!
I like my long neck, but long arms
and legs are easy to use, too.
Dammit! They're gonna attack Chopper!
So you pretended to be
tied up using your own rope?!
...didn't I?
Straighten your back,
renowned sword Nose Storm.
Whoa! So you are a power holder, too?!
I'm an expert at fighting who turns
an unexpected situation into a chance.
Yeah. I was waiting for a chance.
It burns! Ow, ow, ow...!
H-Hey! What're you gonna do?!
First, I'll kill you, Franky.
You were waiting?! When the
island is about to be burned down
Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
I-I got burned! Even my bones
feel hot! They're broken!
Just watch... The technique
using this long reach...
and we were all left behind?!
You bastard!
Jet Whip!
To put it another way, we could escape
from the Navy because of that, right?
Iron Body isn't working at all!
Step aside, you guys!
What's with that kick?! Dammit!
--Huh?
--That guy...!
Giraffe Blast!
You couldn't come up with a new attack?!
Don't be so calm, Galley-La!
Franky! What're you trying to do?!
This is one of our...
They said Buster Call or something.
Enough is enough!
I know! Just be quiet.
Did you forget, Straw Hat Luffy?
Considering how panicky they got,
there's only a little time left.
How stupid!
Three-Sword Style...
To think that he jumps into the air
when he's fighting a Six Powers Master!
...Dragon Twister!
You went down with a single
thrust I gave you in this form.
Iron Body!
What about Big Bro Franky?
What about the Straw Hats?
This is the only way that I
can think of to deal with him.
Diable Jambe!
Power holders have a weakness...
--Première Haché!
--Moon Walk!
Those people are unstoppable!
They don't need us to worry about them!
Oh, that... I got better after I ate meat.
How powerful...!
I'll push him off to the sea.
Shave!
I'll go easy, so bear with me!
We're gonna hurry up
and escape from this island!
How stupid!
Shave!
You're really stupid!
Yeah!
Finger Pistol!
You got carried away and became
hasty trying to finish the fight!
Coup de...
"Navy"
Gum-Gum...
I win!
Moon Walk!
What?
Iron Body!
...Vent!
Ten battleships have set sail for
the judicial island, Enies Lobby!
...Jet Bazooka!
Take this! Moonlight Ten Finger Pistol!
He jumped into the upper floor!
Pasta Machine!
Franky!
One of my hands got repelled.
You were close, huh?
You bastard, Franky! That's reckless!
Please save Robin!
Thanks for waiting!
The situation couldn't be worse.
If you were fast enough
to get another kick in,
What're you doing to our friend?!
Just super leave it to me!
you could've completely
stopped the Finger Pistol.
But in the worst situation,
there's always a chance.
Don't worry. He discussed
this with me beforehand.
Arms, legs, and neck...
If I can control their reach at will,
Well, I couldn't help it...
What?
...because the other kick is...
for finishing you off!
I can swing my swords vigorously!
Sanji...
I'm a Four-Sword Style swordsman.
Leave getting his key to me.
Diable Jambe!
You bitch! You still don't get it?!
I said this is useless!
What? W-Wait!
I can now make full use of the giraffe's power!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
Flambage...
Are you changing fighters? That's fine by me.
You no longer have any chance against me!
There's no hope left for you!
What're they doing, attacking their own?
I'm not going anywhere!
I'll do what you can't do.
They sure do make a big fuss.
They'll all come to rescue me for sure!
The giraffe's power is very strong...
...Shot!
And you do what I can't do!
You can store your obstructive neck away...
What?
Think carefully.
You use the Four-Sword Style...
Grasp the situation!
So you're finally released?
Hmph!
God creates food...
As long as we have you, we can
save Robin-chan for sure! Usopp!
What?!
You'd better stop laughing
and start regretting.
...and the Devil creates spice.
He stopped my sword attacks?!
Never again...
I want to live!
...will you get a chance like
you had earlier to slay me...
None of those things...
can be a basis for my defeat.
Wh-What I can do...
I guess I made it a little too spicy.
...World Government!
What're you doing?
My attack has already started.
I'll use my strongest Tempest Kick, Sky Slicer,
Why don't you run around like you
did earlier, you stupid masked man?!
If you have time to sympathize
with that stupid woman, Nico Robin,
Listen good, marines. Just watch carefully!
--What?!
--Kirin Shower!
and cut down that useless retort of yours!
why don't you think of a way to
save your neck here or something?!
Please! Don't kill Usopp!
This is the great first step of the hero Spandam
You have nowhere to escape.
You fool! You'll die next!
I can't block them!
Hardships are fine by me!
Watch your mouth.
who will be engraved in histo...
Now, this is it for you!
I'm just starting to show a
giraffe's real wild strength!
I choose to walk the path of Asura!
Listen good. I'm the kind
who heats up with anger.
Don't!
What?! Who's that?!
--No way...
--Who the hell are you?!
What's that illusion?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Fierce Sword Attacks! Zoro vs. Kaku,
Powerful Sword Fighting Showdown"
"Fiery Kicks! Sanji's Full
Course of Foot Techniques"
"Hunter Sanji Makes an Entrance?
Elegy for a Lying Wolf"
"Spandam Frightened!
The Hero on the Tower of Law"
"Demon God Zoro! An Incarnation
of Asura Born from Fighting Spirit"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!