Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
You should pay attention to the
weather forecast by a navigator.
Come on!
The one from earlier...!
Thunder Lance Tempo!
No matter how strong you are...
...my forecast is never wrong.
My friends are waiting. I'll be taking your key.
What're you doing, Chopper?! It's us!
Ahh! Stop it!
Hey, is that really Chopper?!
How come he doesn't recognize us?!
I don't know, but it must be Chopper!
Who else has those antlers and wears that hat?!
Step aside, you guys!
--Huh?
--That guy...!
Franky! What're you trying to do?!
This is one of our...
I know! Just be quiet.
This is the only way that I
can think of to deal with him.
Power holders have a weakness...
I'll push him off to the sea.
I'll go easy, so bear with me!
Coup de...
...Vent!
You bastard, Franky! That's reckless!
What're you doing to our friend?!
Don't worry. He discussed
this with me beforehand.
What?
So you're finally released?
You'd better stop laughing and start regretting.
Never again...
...will you get a chance like
you had earlier to slay me...
World Government!
"Hunter Sanji Makes an Entrance?
Elegy for a Lying Wolf"
Battleships are coming to attack!
Get off of Enies Lobby!
They're gonna start firing cannons!
Everyone, get off of the island!
We'll get dragged into the Buster Call!
We'll die if we stay here!
Stop, Nico Robin!
Even if you go back the way we came,
all you'll find are the corpses of pirates!
Enough already.
Teach her a lesson, Funkfreed!
Luffy is just ahead.
Don't hit her vital spots, got that?
Ivory...
...Dart!
I won't let you escape, you dumb woman!
Don't underestimate me!
Now, let's go through the
doors to our dreams together.
He went back to normal.
He'd better not be dead.
I didn't expect that even his friends
wouldn't know how to handle that.
Don't you wanna save Nico Robin?!
I do!
Well, anyway, the fact still remains
that he took out a member of CP9.
In consideration of your friends who
defended you even after you turned
into such a terrible form,
I'll forgive you for attacking me.
We'd better hurry.
But... even if I hurry, I still don't know
how to get to the Gates of Justice.
We'll be your guides!
Little ones!
I found Franky!
What?! You guys know where the
passage to the Gates of Justice is?!
Yep, we do! We're here to be guides!
Grandma's over there, too.
Tell me where it is right away!
And I'll give you and old hag Kokoro
instructions as to what you should do!
Roger.
He's unconscious, but seems to be okay.
You drank too much, old hag! Are you okay?!
Oh, no! I have to bring the keys
to Nico Robin as soon as possible!
You guys come later, too, with that deer!
--Okay.
--Got it! Go, Franky!
So, we have no choice but
to stop Chopper that way.
And then, after that, take these
#3 and #4 keys and hurry to Robin.
One of them might unlock her handcuffs.
If so, call me using this portable
transponder snail that secretary had.
Okay.
Leave freeing Zoro and Nose-king to me.
That's fine, but what will we do after that?
We've come this far, but even if
we're able to rescue Nico Robin,
there's still no bridge between this tower
and Enies Lobby. So we can't go back.
Yeah...
Now that a Buster Call has been requested,
we don't have time to go back
the way we came in the first place.
Then...
So there's no question about it, right?
Behind us is a deadly waterfall.
Ahead of us is a mysterious path.
Which would you pick?
Well, ahead is the only way, but...
Then, when we're done with
what we have to do in this tower,
we'll all gather at the Gates of Justice!
As for what's after that, just leave it to...
--To you?!
--To luck!
Luck?!
We've...
...wasted quite a bit of time.
Damn straight!
I can't believe you guys have been
acting so dumb at a tough time like this!
That's because this guy was doing stupid stuff.
You both are super stupid!
Hurry up and get their keys already!
Tempest Kick...
Straight Line!
That's just as I instructed. Nice job, Zoro-kun!
Fight! Zoro!
You guys fight, too!
That long neck of yours...
You'd better hope it doesn't
become your weak point.
No need to worry about that.
The muscles I gained are strong enough
that I can even freely control my neck.
And bullets, too!
Nose Pistol!
Wh-What the heck?
To think we'd feel this much impact from here...
That made a square-shaped hole in a rock!
That nose is more amazing than Sogepp's!
Wh-Wh-Who're you calling Sogepp?!
And don't make uncalled-for
comparisons like that!
Well, at any rate...
--Eek!
--...Kaku's gotten quite
proficient at using his powers.
W-Wolf! I-I'm the one you have to deal with!
Hm? Well, don't get so worked up.
You guys wanna save your friend, right?
Th-That's right! I'll take your key!
Hm?
Huh?
Hurry up and take it to her.
What?
Go save Nico Robin.
Wh-What on earth are you...
To be honest, I don't wanna
kill people. I hate blood.
Hm?
Th-Then, I'll just...
...take the key and...
No! Watch out!
Ten Finger Pistol!
Don't let your guard down.
I'm a wolf. I get people off
their guard and chew them up.
Usopp!
D-Dammit! What am I doing?
What an unbelievable masked idiot!
Why don't you just run
around like you did earlier?
You're fast as lightning
when you're running away.
Stop mocking me.
Huh?
We no longer have that kind of time.
New weapon, Kabuto!
Special Attack! Sunflower Star!
Oh?
Oh, I see. Fireworks, huh?
Usopp!
Moon Walk!
Stop it!
As I promised, I'll kill you in
an instant. Die without pain.
Too bad. If you'd stayed connected with
that shepherd and had him protect you,
you would've been okay.
You see what happens when a
lamb wanders off all by himself?
He gets eaten by a scary wolf.
Now, this is it for you!
Hey, stop it, wolf! You bastard!
Don't kill him! Please! We don't need your key!
You fool! You'll die next!
Tempest Kick!
Dammit!
Now, die!
Usopp!
Who the hell are you?!
A hunter.
Now, die!
Usopp!
Sanji-kun!
Sanji...!
How did you get out of that state?!
A bathtub fell from the sky
and the spell got broken.
It's probably because I got water all over me.
More importantly, Nami-san...
Didn't you fall in love with me again?!
I wish the bathtub had hit you directly.
Nose-sopp!
So now it's at the point where you're not
using any part of Sogeking in my name.
I-I'm sorry, Sanji-kun.
I...
After all... I...
You're still alive. That's all that matters.
Everyone has things that they
can do and things that they can't.
Sanji...
Look outside, both of you.
No way...
The Gates of Justice are about to open.
Robin...!
Once those gates are opened
and Robin-chan goes through there,
the sea beyond hosts a nest of Sea Kings
and we have no means to cross it.
Past that, there's a large prison
and Navy Headquarters.
Soon Robin-chan will be taken
to a place beyond our reach.
Oh, no... Luffy didn't make it in time?
Coo coo.
Dammit! I can't get through here!
When Robin's waiting for me...!
Give it up. You'll never see her again.
You can't go beyond these doors.
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
That attack doesn't work on me.
Now, come!
I said come! We're going to the bridge!
Am I gonna make it in time?
I hope either the #3 or #4 key frees Nico Robin!
Anyway, I have to stop them at any cost!
It's this way!
Is it this way?
--Chimney! Hurry up!
--It's this way!
--This tower will get hit by cannon fire, too.
--Is it this way?
Wait, Grandma! They'll get
lost if I don't put guide marks.
Picking me as your opponent
was your downfall, huh?
If you were fighting Jabra, you might've
had a slight chance of winning.
When you see... those guys, tell them...
"You guys're fired."
Sure will.
No, I'm glad it's you.
Enough with your bluffing.
Hurry!
Get out of here!
Hey! Let us get on board!
That's not possible! The sea train is full!
Get some ships from the outlying island!
You bastard! I thought you were strangely calm!
So you pretended to be
tied up using your own rope?!
Yeah. I was waiting for a chance.
You were waiting?! When the
island is about to be burned down
and we were all left behind?!
To put it another way, we could escape
from the Navy because of that, right?
Don't be so calm, Galley-La!
They said Buster Call or something.
Considering how panicky they got,
there's only a little time left.
What about Big Bro Franky?
What about the Straw Hats?
Those people are unstoppable!
They don't need us to worry about them!
We're gonna hurry up
and escape from this island!
Yeah!
"Navy"
Ten battleships have set sail for
the judicial island, Enies Lobby!
The situation couldn't be worse.
But in the worst situation,
there's always a chance.
Sanji...
Leave getting his key to me.
Are you changing fighters? That's fine by me.
I'll do what you can't do.
And you do what I can't do!
What?
Think carefully.
Grasp the situation!
As long as we have you, we can
save Robin-chan for sure! Usopp!
I want to live!
Wh-What I can do...
If you have time to sympathize
with that stupid woman, Nico Robin,
why don't you think of a way to
save your neck here or something?!
Watch your mouth.
Listen good. I'm the kind
who heats up with anger.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Fiery Kicks! Sanji's Full
Course of Foot Techniques"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!