Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Fire!
What are you--?!
Luffy-san!
Straw Hat?!
That doesn't work!
I told you I was strong!
W-Who the hell are you?!
I'm Luffy!
The man who's gonna
be King of the Pirates!
"Morgan vs. Luffy!
Who's the Mysterious Pretty Girl?"
W-What?!
The King of the Pirates?!
Do you even know
what that means?!
King of the Pirates
is King of the Pirates!
Are there any other meanings?
I was shocked, too!
But Luffy-san is serious!
That's how he is!
He intends to become the King of the Pirates
and obtain this world's
ultimate treasure... the One Piece!
Here's your treasure!
Which is yours?
I couldn't tell, so I brought three of 'em.
All three are mine.
I use the Three-Sword Style.
You'll take 'em, right?
If we fight together now, you'll
be a government-defying villain!
Would you prefer that, or
being killed by the navy like this?
What are you, the devil's son?!
Well, whatever.
I'll be your pirate,
if I'm just gonna die here instead!
Hurray! So you'll join my crew?!
Alright! Woo-hoo!
This is great! Alright!
Okay! Now untie these
stupid ropes already!
What... is he?
He flung the bullets back!
He's no ordinary human,
that Straw Hat...
Must've eaten one of
those rumored Devil Fruits!
--A Devil Fruit?!
--The hidden treasures of the sea?!
The Devil Fruits...
Whoever eats one is said to
gain seemingly unworldly abilities.
The power to breathe fire...
The power to cause tsunamis...
There are all sorts of rumors,
but there are many types, and
almost nothing is known about them.
It's said the secrets to
them lie in the Grand Line...
but there's no question
Straw Hat just displayed a devil power!
Hurry! Hurry!
Damn! These knots are tight!
Hey! Quit wastin' time!
No matter who they are,
everyone who opposes me gets executed!
If guns won't work,
then chop them to death!
Huh, that's weird! It got tighter instead!
Give me a damn sword!
Luffy-san!
Roronoa Zoro!
So cool!
Move and you're dead.
Too scary!
I'll be a pirate. I promise you that.
I'm officially a criminal,
now that I've fought the navy.
But I'll tell you this right now.
I'm only going to fulfill my ambition!
Ambition?
To be the world's greatest swordsman!
If I wind up having to give that up,
you'd better accept
responsibility and apologize to me!
The world's greatest swordsman?
That sounds great!
The King of the Pirates would
need no less than that on his crew!
You sure talk big.
At this point, whether it's as
a criminal or whatever else,
I will spread my name throughout the world!
What're you standing around for?!
Slaughter them this instant!
Duck, Zoro!
Gum-Gum Whip!
Y-You did it! Incredible!
What the hell are you?
I ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Gum-Gum Fruit?
A rubber person!
So he does have Devil Fruit powers!
Captain! We don't stand
a chance against them!
These guys are crazy!
We can't even handle Zoro by himself!
This is a direct order!
Everyone who spouted weakness just now...
must now shoot themselves in the head!
I have no need for weakling soldiers!
These troops are mental!
Luffy-san!
Crush this navy!
Rankless, low-status bums have
no right whatsoever to defy me!
I am Navy Captain
"Axe-Hand" Morgan!
I'm Luffy! Nice to meetcha!
Die!
T-The captain!
R-Runt...
Die!
No thanks!
C-Captain Morgan is...
being trounced completely...
And you call yourself a navy?!
You've destroyed Coby's dream!
Hold it, Straw Hat!
Check this out!
I said hold it! Are you stupid?!
Pay attention!
I have a hostage here!
Helmeppo-sama!
Hey.
If you value this guy's life, don't move!
One move and I'll shoot!
Luffy-san! I don't
want to get in your way!
Even if it means dying!
Yeah, I know!
Give it up, stupid son!
Coby really is ready to die!
Don't move!
I told you not to move!
I-I'll shoot!
Behind you!
Gum-Gum...
I am Navy Captain
"Axe-Hand" Morgan!
--Dad! Kill him, quick!
--...Pistol!
Nice!
Zoro.
My pleasure, Captain.
Captain Morgan's been beaten!
--Unbelievable!
--These guys are insane!
If anyone else still wants
to catch us, come forward!
--Hurray!
--We're free!
--Yahoo!
--Morgan's reign is over!
Hurray for the navy!
Huh? Everyone's happy
their captain's been beaten...
Everyone was just afraid of Morgan!
What's wrong, Zoro-san?!
Are you hurt?!
I'm... hungry...
Sorry!
Just endure it for a while!
Doesn't seem to be in here, either...
Yes! A chart of the Grand Line!
I knew they had one!
"I've flashily taken the map! Buggy"
T-This isn't a chart!
What is this mark?!
Captain Buggy...
The man known as Buggy the Immortal...
I'm stuffed!
I was definitely at my rope's end,
having not eaten for three weeks!
Huh? You're finished already?
How the heck can you have
a bigger appetite than me?!
It tastes good! Right, Coby?
Thank you for treating me to food, too...
It's no problem!
The town has been saved, after all!
You really are amazing!
Yep, I am!
And I'm gonna be even more amazing!
'Cause I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
And I even have a crew!
So, how many others have
you gathered besides me?
You said you were in the
middle of gathering a crew.
To be King of the Pirates,
you must have
a good number gathered.
Just you.
Huh?! Then...
Yep! Just us two!
We're gonna call just
us two a pirate crew?!
What's wrong with that?
We are strong!
What about a ship?
Where's your pirate ship?
There.
That?
We'll have a ship this big before long!
And how's that?!
And I'd like a pirate flag, too!
Yeah! Yeah, yeah! So cool!
I think Luffy-san was born
without any sense of planning.
Did I really make this guy my captain?!
Well, we'll get more
crew members before long!
Hey, hey! Where are you guys gonna go to now?
Isn't it obvious?! The Grand Line!
You still only have two members!
There's no way you can go there!
No way! No way! No way!
Is the Grand Line that terrible of a place?
Naturally!
You know this world
has two oceans, right?
And the giant continent that cuts
them right in two is the Red Line.
Supposedly, there's a town right
in the middle of the Red Line,
and the Grand Line goes
through it at a right angle...
and stretches around the world.
It was said that Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates,
once obtained everything
this world has to offer,
and before he died, he said he left
the great One Piece treasure there,
so pirates everywhere have
since set sail for the Grand Line!
It's now an intense battlefield,
and even called a pirate graveyard!
I've heard from patrons before...
that whoever enters the
Grand Line never comes out alive...
But the One Piece is somewhere there,
so we're going there!
Guess it can't be helped!
Not you too, Zoro-san?!
What's it matter?
You're not going, are you?
N-No, but I'm worried about you!
Is that so wrong?!
Luffy-san and I haven't
known each other long,
but we are friends!
Right?
Yeah! We're gonna part ways,
but we'll always be friends!
Since I was a little kid,
I've never had friends...
Much less anyone who
would fight for my sake...
But more than anything,
I never tried to fight for anything...
But you two taught me
how to live for my beliefs!
I've decided to make
my childhood dream come true!
I want to join the navy!
Shouldn't you be more
worried about yourself, then?
Even if you were just a chore boy,
you did spend two years
on Alvida's pirate ship.
Don't underestimate the
navy's info-gathering skills.
If they find out about that,
you'll never get to join.
N-Now that you mention it...
Pardon me!
Is it true that you are pirates?!
Yeah. We gained a member
and became a pirate group just now!
We appreciate that you saved our
base and this town from that tyrant!
However, now that we know you are pirates,
in the name of the navy,
we cannot stand by quietly!
You will leave this town at once!
Out of obligation, we will refrain
from contacting headquarters.
Hey, navy guy!
How can you talk like that?!
Even you guys were
subdued and terrified of Morgan!
We owe these people our lives!
Yeah! Yeah!
Well, guess we should go!
Thanks for the food, lady!
You guys are leaving already?
Yeah.
Aren't you part of their crew?
Eh? I...
I'm...
Hold it!
Well? Is he?!
I know what he's done until now.
Luffy-san! You wouldn't!
There was this really fat pirate lady,
I think her name was Ahiruda.
Luffy-san!
If they find out I was on a pirate ship,
I'll never get to join the navy!
And she had this iron club.
Man, she was an ugly hag!
And for two whole years, this guy was her--
Please don't!
Please don't, Luffy-san!
Now you've done it, you bastard!
Damn you! Damn you! Damn you!
Stop that!
We won't allow you to cause
any more trouble in this town!
Hey! You've gone too far.
That's enough.
It's very clear that you
guys aren't crewmates!
Now leave this town at once!
On purpose...
He did that on purpose...
For me...
He purposely got me
riled up to make me hit him...
Even in the very end,
I wound up relying on him!
Nothing's changed at all!
Am I an idiot?!
Please!
Please... let me join the navy!
I'll gladly do chores or anything else!
If it means I can be a marine!
Lieutenant Colonel! I'm against the idea!
I still don't fully trust this kid!
There have been cases of
marines being pirate spies!
We'll first need to
conduct a background check...
I'm a man who will become a navy officer!
Countless comrades of ours
have been killed by pirates.
Don't take the navy lightly.
Then...
Permission to join granted!
Yes, sir!
"I've flashily taken the map! Buggy"
That was a pretty lame act.
Wouldn't be shocked if they saw through it.
Coby'll handle the rest on
his own now. I just know it.
It's a nice way to leave, though.
Being unable to turn back
'cause everyone hates you--
it's pirate-like!
That's true!
Luffy-san!
Thank you! I'll never
forget all you've done for me!
I've never heard of a pirate
being thanked by a marine...
Let's meet again sometime, Coby!
--Luffy-san...
--Bye!
All hands, salute!
See ya!
That's a great friend you have there.
Yes, sir!
Our salute just now is
in violation of naval law!
Therefore, we will all go without
food for three days! Understood?!
Yes, sir!
I'm sure...
I'm sure we'll meet again
sometime, somewhere, Luffy-san!
Even if we're divided
as pirates and marines...
let's meet again someday!
Alright!
Our pirate crew finally sets sail!
Looks like some pretty good
adventures'll be waiting for us.
I will be King of the Pirates!
You really seem obsessed
about this King of the Pirates thing.
Is there some sorta reason for it?
No reason. It's just...
It's just?
I swore to a certain man that...
...someday I would gather a great crew,
find the world's greatest treasure,
and become King of the Pirates!
This straw hat knows!
I see...
Alright! Let's go!
Set sail for the Grand Line!
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else
could beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Geez, you don't even
know how to navigate right?!
--Do you know how?
--No!
Ahh! Hey, stop rocking the boat!
My hat'll fall off!
Is your straw hat that important?
Yeah! It's my treasure!
I have to return it to him
after I'm King of the Pirates!
Who's "him"?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy's Past!
Enter Red-Haired Shanks"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!