Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
It really took a long time.
But I'm finally here.
Once I've gone through those gates,
I can be the Government's...
No, the world's hero!
Lucci, huh? So you're having
a tough time against him?
Where's Nico Robin? I brought two keys.
Shall I give you a hand?
No. More importantly...
...please stop Robin.
You can get to the Gates of Justice
through the doors behind the pigeon guy.
Robin has already been taken away.
I'll restrain him.
Just super leave it to me, you jerk!
Thanks for waiting!
Arms, legs, and neck...
If I can control their reach at will,
I can swing my swords vigorously!
I'm a Four-Sword Style swordsman.
I can now make full use of the giraffe's power!
You no longer have any chance against me!
The giraffe's power is very strong...
You can store your obstructive neck away...
You use the Four-Sword Style...
Hmph!
What?!
He stopped my sword attacks?!
None of those things...
can be a basis for my defeat.
"Demon God Zoro! An Incarnation
of Asura Born from Fighting Spirit"
What a useless retort.
Then show me your "basis"!
Three-Sword Style...
...Leopard...
...Spinning...
He's gonna fly towards me!
...Shot!
Paper Art!
Can't be...! I'm sure I saw through his attack!
Don't tell me...
Did he actually foresee my reaction?!
What are you so surprised about?
Don't tell me you've never been cut before...
Hmph! I see... So it looks like
it wasn't just an empty boast.
I underestimated you a bit. But no longer.
I've mastered the Six Powers. On top of that,
I now have the wild powers of a giraffe.
Techniques, power, speed...
There's no way you can beat me in any of them!
I won't give you any more openings to attack!
Tempest Kick Throwing Stars!
Giraffe Blast!
Shoot!
My neck can become a whip...
Whiplash!
And now for the faster version...
Fierce Whiplash!
How's this?! Can you still talk big?!
The four-sword attacks
will not stop. Just give it up!
Fury Slash!
Here I come...!
What a vigorous attack!
Well, well! What's the matter?!
All you can do now is block!
You can't defeat me!
You guys are mere pirates.
It was a mistake to go up against the
World Government in the first place!
Now that it's come to this, in the
name of justice, you'll have to die...
...just like that woman!
You bastard...
What was that?!
For a moment, he looked like a demon
god with three faces and six arms!
What the hell is with this guy?!
You're getting carried away.
You talk too much.
You're tired of listening to me?
Then I'll use my strongest
Tempest Kick, Sky Slicer,
the one that slashed this tower...
...and end this battle by splitting you into two!
So give it up. You have nowhere to escape.
It's on a completely different level from
the demonstration I showed you earlier!
You fool...
You're the one who has to give up.
Demon Aura... Nine-Sword Style...
...Asura!
The demon god I saw earlier...!
He can show such a powerful
illusion with his fighting spirit?!
Splendid! But it's too late!
You're the one who's too late.
Wait until you dodge this
Tempest Kick to make such a boast.
Sky Slicer!
My slash attack...
...was turned into mist?!
Hardships are fine by me!
I choose to walk the path of Asura!
Asura... Silver Mist!
I've got...
...a message for you from
the junior boss of Galley-La.
When you see... those guys, tell them...
He said you guys're fired.
I considered you guys my friends all this time!
Paulie, huh?
I see... I'm in trouble.
Assassination skills aren't very
helpful in other lines of work.
You can still work in a zoo.
Hey, be nice...
Sorry.
Hm?
Hey, Moss Head! Where's the key?!
Yeah...
I just got it.
I see.
At any rate, looks like you
guys really put on a show.
Didn't you guys cause the tower
to slip even more? Is it okay?
Who cares? That's not important.
Anyway, we now have all the keys.
Yeah.
Let's hurry to Robin.
Run!
Just run! Keep running at full speed!
It's our duty to survive so that we won't
worry our Bro and the Straw Hats!
Ribbit!
Run in order to live! Even if it breaks your legs!
Yeah!
Run!
We're counting on you, giants!
You guys... If you guys are just gonna
ride on there, then at least be quiet!
Yeah, I agree!
Go! In the name of Elbaf!
Shut up!
Grandma! Hurry! Hurry up! Hurry up!
Hey, Chimney! I'm old! Show a little kindness!
Seriously, I can't keep running
unless I refuel myself.
Whoa!
Grandma! He's gonna fall off!
Pull him up! Pull him up!
Boy, you sure are demanding, geez...!
Grandma!
"Hurry up," right? I know!
The bridge is finally completely connected!
I can't stop laughing!
Hey! Guards at the Gates of Justice!
Are you guys ready?!
Yes, sir! The escort ship is already
in front of the third column and...
That's not it! Why aren't you
coming out to salute me?!
Great Spandam the hero is passing through!
Ah! Y-Yes! We'll be right out!
Geez, those idiots! They can't
do anything on their own!
Hey, Nico Robin. Look at that.
That small gate is the actual entrance.
When you pass through it, you'll cross
the border between heaven and hell.
And that's the moment my name
will be engraved in history!
Oops. Where're you trying to run away to now?
I'm actually sympathizing with you, at least.
But it can't be helped, right?
Your life has no value.
Hurry up and die.
That bitch!
I don't wanna die...
I don't wanna die...!
I don't wanna die!
I've had enough, you bitch!
Stand up already and...
What? She isn't moving. What's going on?!
She's biting into the stone bridge!
She just doesn't know when
to give up! How irritating!
It's detestable how she clings to life!
It's pitiful and vulgar!
You're a criminal! The only way you
can make others happy is by dying!
Why must you act so miserable
until the very last minute?!
I fear death so much...
I don't wanna die...!
Help me, everyone...
Luffy...!
Finger Pistol!
I told you that doesn't work...!
Yellow Lotus!
Straw Hat!
No...
My mission is to go past those
doors as soon as possible!
It's no use. You can't pass through here.
Shut up! Strong...
--Iron Body.
--...Hammer!
What? He doesn't budge an inch...
...when it was strong enough
to blow Chapapa away.
I see. You came after defeating Fukurou, huh?
But sorry. My Power Level
is five times as strong as his.
It's splendid that you
were able to defeat Fukurou.
It can be said that you're already
in the boundary of superhumans.
As I suspected, he's incomparably
stronger than the others.
But... die.
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Pistol!
What the hell did you...
What's that steam?!
Second Gear.
This can't last too long.
But I'll stop him, so you go on ahead, Franky!
Robin's waiting!
Okay, Straw Hat!
I don't know what's going on,
but finish him off with that!
I said I wouldn't let you do that...
...didn't I?
Whoa! So you are a power holder, too?!
First, I'll kill you, Franky.
Jet Whip!
Did you forget, Straw Hat Luffy?
You went down with a single
thrust I gave you in this form.
Oh, that... I got better after I ate meat.
Shave!
Finger Pistol!
Gum-Gum...
Iron Body!
...Jet Bazooka!
Franky!
Please save Robin!
Just super leave it to me!
You bitch! You still don't get it?!
I said this is useless!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
There's no hope left for you!
I'm not going anywhere!
They'll all come to rescue me for sure!
Listen good, marines. Just watch carefully!
This is the great first step of the hero Spandam
who will be engraved in histo...
What?! Who's that?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Spandam Frightened!
The Hero on the Tower of Law"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!