Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
"Boss Luffy Is the Culprit?
Track Down the Missing Great Cherry Tree"
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
Spring has come here in Grand Jipang, too.
The words he uttered just before his death
They say one sleeps right
through the dawn in spring.
drove people around the world to the seas.
So you'd think the townspeople
must be taking it easy,
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
but it's not really the case.
It's finally tomorrow! With this weather,
it'll be the perfect time to view them.
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
Yeah, it puts me in a good mood.
On my way here, I ordered catered
box lunches from Pinwheel for my family.
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
What a treat!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
And this is what the townspeople
are all worked up about.
Under this millennium cherry tree,
which is the pride of Grand Jipang,
--Sogeking!
--There's no time to lose!
they hold a huge party once a year
that everyone in town attends.
Jump down from there!
I won't take my focus off of you.
Just watch carefully!
Demon Aura... Nine-Sword Style...
This is the first step of a hero
that will be engraved in histo...
Hm?
That's enough to get anyone excited.
No matter what they're going through
right now, they'll survive for sure!
Usopp!
Sounds like I can expect lots of offerings.
...Asura!
But if I let you get away now,
you'll go kill my friends!
Even a hungry monk can get antsy.
Sky Slicer!
Shut your trap.
I won't take my focus off of you!
A-Anyway, even at a time like this,
Tower of Law?! What can
he do from that far away?!
Can you really defeat me?!
there are also those who have
more pressing matters to deal with.
Hey... He couldn't have... right?
Hardships are fine by me!
I can't protect anyone unless I win!
Hey! Usopp!
I choose to walk the path of Asura!
Influenza? What the heck is that?
Ahhh!!
It's also called the flu...
It's a kind of infectious disease.
Gum-Gum...
--Snap!
--Who the hell is that?!
You called?!
...Rifle!
It's contagious, so don't go outside,
just stay in bed, okay?
--♪ I was born... ♪
--He's aiming at us from that distance
without the slightest error, in this wind?!
Iron Body. Empty Tree.
Asura... Silver Mist!
What?!
Oh, no! We promised to go to the cherry
blossom viewing together tomorrow.
Hey, you're alive!
--♪ ...on the island of snipers ♪
--Who the hell is that?!
Hey! Don't you guys have
the kindness to catch a hero
I thought I was able to meet a man
with some backbone. How disappointing.
Long-nose!
That's out of the question!
Second Gear.
making a desperate jump
off of the rooftop?! Morons!
If he does that, he'll get worse,
and he could even die.
Nico Robin is getting away!
Don't let her get away!
Idiots! You can shoot her!
Did you run out of strength from
your doping earlier after all?
There's an escort ship on the
other side of the bridge, huh?
Oh, no... Carrot's been
looking forward to it, too.
Jet Whip!
--Yes, sir!
--Shoot her dead enough to keep her alive!
Don't you think that is the key to our escape?
Doc! Please do something!
You're a doctor, right?!
Huh?!
Looks like stealing that ship
is our only chance of surviving.
Don't be unreasonable.
Even a doctor can only do so much.
Fire!
If it's backbone you want, I'll show you...
Franky...
Shave!
I'm sorry, guys.
...Convert!
Finger Pistol!
...another tactic!
Gum-Gum...
It's my fault that I got sick.
Don't blame Dr. Bluenose.
--Iron Body!
--...Jet Bazooka!
Third... Gear!
Don't worry about me.
Franky Centaur!
You guys go to the cherry
blossom viewing tomorrow.
Franky!
What?!
Hold it, you bastards!
Please save Robin!
Bone Balloon!
Bone?
Although your physical ability
indeed spikes, exceeding its limits,
What the hell is he?!
Just super leave it to me!
The power that moves
from one bone to another...
Geez...
You are...
your physical strength itself just can't
keep up with that intensification.
Take a look! My left arm is...
"We are accepting box lunch
orders for cherry blossom viewing"
You bitch! You still don't get it?!
I said this is useless!
My body is strong because it's iron.
Everyone's talking about the cherry
blossom viewing. How annoying!
...the arm of a giant!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
That landmine wasn't nice, Spanda!
That's not really smart.
You're shortening your life, you know that?
Oh, don't say that.
There's no hope left for you!
Eek!
If it's all show, don't even bother!
Thanks to the cherry blossom viewing,
we have a flood of box lunch orders.
It's better than losing all sorts
of things right before my eyes!
They came off!
I'm not going anywhere!
Gum-Gum...
The millennium cherry tree is a blessing for us.
They'll all come to rescue me for sure!
Iron Body!
That's right.
I'll do whatever I can do!
...Giant Pistol!
Ha! Put yourself in my shoes.
You're too ambitious!
This is Franky! Hey, Long-nose!
While everyone else's out partying,
we have to patrol the town.
Tempest Kick!
"Spandam Frightened!
The Hero on the Tower of Law"
I got the handcuffs off of Nico Robin.
What're you saying?
The entire town becomes empty.
All right!
Thank you, Long-nose!
You policemen have to work hard
at a time like this. Right, Boss?
You can thank those who fought hard
to gather the keys when this is all over.
"Shivering Past! Dark Justice and Rob Lucci"
That naive idea of yours that you
can save everyone and escape...
Isn't there something we can do...?
You are, without a doubt,
one of Luffy-kun's gang!
Yeah, I wonder...
Let's see how far it gets you.
You can now do as you wish!
I wish there was some way I could
show him the millennium cherry tree...
What're you doing, you jerk?!
Ahh!
I wish there was some way
I could cure his disease...
Behind the fog...
Yes.
...we can see the outline of the ships!
I feel like I'm about to pass out.
I can't fall into the sea like this...!
What's up with those two?
Everything went according to my plan.
H-Hey, don't run away! Wait!
Beats me. But they've been like this for a while.
No good. I can't come up
with a single good idea.
Hm? What's that?
Me neither.
H-Hey, look at that!
I've never seen this before!
Hey, you two! Are you leaving?
Oh, no...
Did I hear something just now?
Yeah... I've never even heard
anyone talking about it!
See you later, Dr. Bluenose.
This serves you right!
Yeah.
They're here! They're finally here!
"Robin Freed! Luffy vs. Lucci,
Showdown Between Leaders"
To see that the Gates of Justice
have completely opened!
Oops...!
Hey, that's not like him, and tomorrow is
the long-awaited cherry blossom viewing day.
It's so that the battleships from
Headquarters can come here!
To think that Boss didn't finish his food...
It's for the Buster Call's cannon attack!
What was that?
And... the day of the cherry blossom
viewing event has come at last.
Hurry up and help the injured!
Granny Kokoro surely said
that those doors never
open all the way, and yet...
Who are you?!
--A beast?!
--No, he's a power holder!
What's this air of intimidation?
What on earth is Buster Call?
What...?
Your medicine is ready, Carrot.
A fleet of battleships!
The Buster Call has begun!
What the heck?
So I landed on the deck of
a battleship. That was close...
The Straw Hats picked a fight with the world.
What the hell is this?!
So they really are going to blow them
away along with the entire island!
He flew from the direction of the bridge.
"I Can't Protect Anyone Unless I Win!
Third Gear Activated!"
Is he a pirate?
Can't be...!
Bastards!
The millennium cherry tree is...
gone without a trace!
I saw a huge hand, too!
Don't die, Bro!
Stop! Stop! I said stop!
This is indeed quite mysterious.
Was that cannon fire from a battleship?!
Yeah!
It's dangerous ahead of here!
Water is rushing towards us!
Come back alive!
What reason could there be
for stealing such a huge thing?
The stockade was...
Straw Hat!
Good point. If it was about stealing money,
I'd have an idea who did it...
C-Can't you guys hear the sound of water?!
Listen, if the water flows into
an underground passage like this,
"Justice"
...but my guess is that...
Vice Admiral! The cannon
fire earlier hit the stockade
we'll have no choice but to drown.
Zoro-kun, can't you hear the sound of water?!
...our lord is the culprit!
in front of the main island at 4 o'clock!
Hmm, it's true that
something doesn't feel right.
Our lord?!
--So, what about it?
--Huh?
I entrusted Franky with saving Robin.
I'm asking, what about it?
Then let's stop, you guys!
Yeah. In order to take the
townspeople's pleasure all for himself,
There's no other passage. We have
no choice but to keep on this path!
Yes, sir. Well, nothing really, sir!
This is an indiscriminate attack.
I could care less where we hit.
he must've moved the tree
to his estate during the night!
It was careless of me. I never
expected him to be this powerful.
He wouldn't do such a thing!
I knew it!
Yes, sir...
Granny and the others
are being chased by water!
Our mission is to burn everything down.
It seems that you're really out of breath.
Seriously, I should never have asked you.
Ah! Pirate guys!
Start with the Tower of Law.
Isn't it because of that steam?
Where's Straw Hat during
an emergency like this?!
Once Enies Lobby comes within firing range,
we'll launch a concerted attack.
Guys! Do something about this water!
W-Well, I went to get him, but he wasn't there,
Do something?! What're we supposed to do?!
Yes, sir.
so I just assumed he was already here.
See, I told you! This passage is
gonna be flooded with water!
If that's clear, instead of
wasting time on reports like this,
Defeating you is all that matters.
N-Nami-san is...
I wish there was some way I could
show him the millennium cherry tree...
why don't you start preparing
the next attack already?!
...rushing into my arms!
Y-Yes, sir!
How positive!
This is bad! We're gonna be shut in here!
I see... You're tough.
The millennium cherry tree...
I repeat. Our targets are Straw Hat Luffy
and his gang of about sixty pirates!
They busted the fence
that surrounds the island.
Don't tell me...
I'd better make it!
I can't cut it! So this isn't iron or stone?!
That was a huge explosion.
Completely destroy Enies Lobby!
Don't go yet, Nico Robin!
If a bunch of battleships come and
rain down cannon fire like that...
This is an undersea passage.
Hey! Is Boss here?!
It must be made of some damn thick steel
that can bear the water pressure!
Ah... H-Hey!
You look so stupid!
Wh-What? What happened?
Also, look.
Then there's nowhere to escape!
Hey, look at that, you guys! Don't run!
That's because of your pointless
resistance, you dumb woman!
The whirlpools that were surging so violently
Well, since the cherry tree is gone,
Ahh! It's here!
See? The battleships are ignoring
the bridge--they aren't attacking us!
that they prevented ships from
coming here are now completely gone.
we had a flood of box lunch order cancellations.
Now, stand up!
I said, stand up!
It's because the Gates of Justice were
opened all the way to allow attacks.
Thanks to the cherry tree thief,
we're taking a huge loss.
Seriously, the gate is right there, and yet
you're causing me all sorts of trouble!
"Sea Currents"
"Tower of Law"
Those whirlpools were generated by the
This might be the end of Pinwheel.
It isn't safe here! We're gonna die!
sea currents blocked by the huge gates.
Hurry!
I'm sorry to hear that.
This is no good! The sea train won't start!
That's because I'm here!
Now that the gates are open
and nothing is blocking them,
Hey...! Hey, got a minute?
That's right. My old man said it, too.
the sea currents went back to normal
Aren't there any engineers?!
Even the indiscriminate cannon fire avoided him!
and the whirlpools disappeared, huh?
The attacks will reach here soon! Hurry up!
Which means, the battleships...
Guards! Go outside!
--What is it?
--Well...
...will have no trouble coming this way.
Yes, sir!
However, the bridge the criminal
Nico Robin is on is an exception for now.
--Sogeking!
--There's no time to lose!
Boss is the cherry tree thief?!
Hey! Look at this! This bridge is safe!
Shhh! It's not like I know anything for sure yet,
Jump down from there!
Vice Admiral!
What do we do about capturing
Nico Robin on the Bridge of Hesitation?!
That's because I'm the Chief of CP9!
Guards at the Gates of Justice,
but he was acting
strange yesterday, wasn't he?
Don't say a reckless thing like that!
and marines on the escort ship
sent by Navy Headquarters...!
--Leave her alone.
--But...
Come to think of it, he wanted to
show the cherry tree to someone.
To start with, it's not like I have
superhuman strength like you guys,
As long as that man is on this island
Cipher Pol's Chief Spandam is currently
taking a criminal of utmost importance
Yeah, exactly!
and is given the mission
of escorting Nico Robin,
or the courage not to fear death!
I haven't seen him this morning,
so my guess is...
What a crazy sight...
we don't have to get involved.
across the bridge from the Tower of Law.
I'm just an ordinary superhero!
Who'd you say was the cherry tree thief?
We'll just burn everything down
except the Bridge of Hesitation.
Hm? Hey, are you...
Hm?
That damn Straw Hat!
All line up and salute!
Yes, sir!
Vice Admiral...
W-Well, like I said, I don't know for sure yet!
Usopp!
Yes, sir!
Could this man you mentioned be...
Mr. Rob Lucci of CP9?
The Tower of Law is...
You guys! You know what
you're supposed to do, right?!
I can't stop trembling.
Long-nose!
It doesn't matter if it's the Boss or not--
Long-nose...!
Look! This time, they fired at the Tower of Law!
just arrest the culprit and resume
the cherry blossom viewing event!
The Tower of Law is...!
Look at that. They're all ready to set sail now.
As we suspected, he's a power holder!
Get going!
Are they okay?!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
There's no longer anything standing in my way.
Who the hell are you?!
We're asking who you are! Answer us!
Oh, yeah, Nico Robin.
As I suspected, the explosion
earlier was no ordinary explosion!
Stop it, you idiots!
I'll let you in on a little secret.
I'm exercising a Buster Call.
Captain?!
That was cannon fire!
Put down your guns!
Commence concerted fire!
Hurry up and leave the island!
Before we crossed the bridge,
I turned on the landmine
Who do you think you're talking to?!
We're targeting everything on Ohara,
the island of archaeology.
set on the upper part of the
stairs that we just ascended.
He is... Mr. Rob Lucci of CP9!
Hey, did you find him?!
--No, no luck.
--What about Dr. Bluenose's place?
If, by any chance, someone
tries to make their way here,
Annihilate the devils living in Ohara!
In the name of justice!
I haven't checked Doc's place yet,
but someone saw the boss
going into Carrot's house earlier,
they and the stairs will both go boom!
so I'm on my way there right now.
R-Rob Lucci-san...
Carrot's house?!
Wha... That...
What do you think? Isn't that interesting?
We're sorry! Please spare our lives!
Yeah. It seems that he was mumbling
about cherry blossoms as he walked.
But, well, don't worry about it,
Shut your mouths. Your whining hurts my ears.
since no one's gonna make
it to those stairs anyway.
What?
♪ Cherry blossoms! La la la...
Cherry blossoms! La la la... ♪
I've heard a lot about Mr. Rob Lucci,
But I won't go through... the gate...
so he is really that good?
♪ The March sky... La la la... ♪
Huh?
It was fifteen years ago...
♪ As far as the eye can see is... La la la... ♪
In some kingdom,
there was an incident where 500
soldiers got captured by pirates.
Buster Call...
--♪ Hazy like a mist... ♪
--Ahhh!
Merciless, indiscriminate cannon fire...
...because they said they'd rescue me.
Hey... He couldn't have... right?
Hm?
Oh, hey! What're you two doing here?
"15 years ago"
No one will come, you dumb woman!
Hey! Usopp!
Don't "What're you two doing here" us!
It destroys anything and everything.
Everyone will burn to death in
the raging fire of Buster Call!
Ahhh!!
Hey, Straw Hat! Where'd you
get that cherry tree branch?!
It's hellfire.
Guys! Don't hold back! Go wild!
You called?!
Hm? Oh, this?
That tragedy is... That grisly event is...
It'll even erase the utter humiliation of the fact
that pirates shot through our sacred flag!
Kill anyone who resists! Show no mercy!
Don't play dumb! Where'd you hide
the actual millennium cherry tree?!
The actual millennium cherry tree?
...happening again...
Don't flinch! Protect this
country from the pirates!
Hey, you're alive!
You just don't know when to give up, Boss.
Hey! Don't you guys have
the kindness to catch a hero
Just like in Ohara twenty years ago,
when that giant marine attacked us.
Surely you wouldn't say the millennium
cherry tree's disappearance
making a desperate jump
off of the rooftop?! Morons!
has nothing to do with that branch, would you?
The kingdom put up unrelenting
resistance against the pirates.
What?! The millennium cherry tree is missing?!
Now, walk!
Franky! Robin-chan! We're okay here.
We're heading over there right away!
Say, Boss, you can trust me,
so just tell me the truth!
Walk with your own two feet!
However...
Saul...
Good.
Truth? All I did was pick this up at the door.
Well then, let's do something
about things here.
Those damn pirates...!
You bitch!
Hey, can I count on you to help fight?
Are you trying to talk your way out of it?!
I've lost respect for you, Boss!
Chief! Please hurry!
Of course.
I left it there in the middle of the night!
Hurry up, soldiers! Take care of them
before the attack goes into full gear!
I know! Shut up! I'm a hero!
See, I told you?! "I left it there..." Huh?
Yes, sir!
You probably think that I don't
know anything about it, don't you?
You said, "I"?
There's an escort ship on the
other side of the bridge, huh?
Let's hurry, you guys! Be quick!
The misconduct by Jaguar D. Saul,
a former Navy Headquarters Vice Admiral!
Don't you think that is the key to our escape?
I'm sorry.
Looks like stealing that ship
is our only chance of surviving.
Your mother, Olvia...
What happened in Ohara at that time...
Stop bossing us around, you jerk!
Get them!
Trench mortars...?!
If I may say one more thing,
this is affecting my wounds.
Could you carry me a little more softly?
This is it for you! If you don't wanna die,
just give up and surrender!
I know about it all!
Dieciseis Fleurs!
Don't ask too much! Besides,
you're contradicting yourself.
Why do you think that is?
Fire!
If you resist, we'll blow you away
with these trench mortars!
That's because I was told.
The one who commanded a raid on
the land of Ohara, where devils lived,
As the price I paid for my great work,
it's no exaggeration to say that
I have wounds all over my body!
What the hell?!
exposed their terrible crime
and issued a Buster Call
Strong...
After we left here,
Ahh! All my ribs got broken! All six of them!
we were thinking we really wanted to
show the millennium cherry tree to Carrot.
They're all our hostages!
There are more than that, so don't worry.
was my old man, then-CP9 Chief Spandine!
So Pepper, Onion, and I went
to the millennium cherry tree.
Throw them all in a warehouse!
Seriously, you're such a pain!
By the way, would you like to know
the secret of my new weapon, Kabuto?
In exchange for the hostages' lives,
the pirate captain demanded the throne.
...Face-Slap!
I shall explain it for you. Kabuto,
the weapon that belongs to Sogeking, is...
Are you okay?!
Well, scholars of Ohara!
We're all right! Don't worry!
Your Majesty. For the sake of the citizens,
--Sparkle!
--Shut up, you jerk! Or we'll make you run!
Your death sentence has now been decided!
you should firmly refuse the
pirates' despicable demand!
Okay, let's get this one.
Second group! Go!
Please! Spare me! My ribs
got broken! A-All ten of them...
He's right!
Yeah!
With the power of the kingdom's
main military and the Imperial Guards,
I'm sorry, but please let
us have this one branch.
Eliminate him!
Treinta Fleurs!
--There are more than that.
--What?
Then 20... 30?
we don't have to fear those pirates!
How about 100?!
Your Majesty!
There are more than that!
But those soldiers who fought risking their lives
No way that's true!
Master Nails!
Someone's coming!
and ended up being taken
hostage are also my people.
Professor!
What?!
Both of you! Come down quickly!
I can't just sit back and let them die.
Ohara has...
Th-Third group! Go!
But...
We don't have time to go down!
Even if this throne is taken away,
it's possible to take it back.
Fourth group! And fifth group, too!
All together, get them!
Take that branch and go on ahead!
No! Come down already!
...come to know too much.
Is that cannon fire?
But you can't take back people's lives!
Don't worry! Once they go past,
we'll come back right away!
I'll initiate a Buster Call!
The Navy sure does put on a big show.
Geez... One after another...
They're such a pain in the ass.
Your Majesty...
Just leave it at the door
of Carrot's house, okay?
Take care of the rest.
But even if we accepted the pirates' demands,
Amazing! Amazing! Cannon fire! Cannon fire!
Don't get caught.
Hey, stand back a little.
O-Okay.
Hey, they aren't festival fireworks, you know.
I find it hard to believe that they'd
release the hostages as they promised!
Hurry!
Weapons Left!
Anyway, where's Luffy right now?
You know, pirate lady, that iron
door we came through...
Fresh Fire!
Now, go, Saul!
Your Majesty!
The pirate guy broke it.
Are you sure about this?
Luffy did?
Your Majesty! An emissary from the
World Government has just arrived!
It was amazing... though he became small.
Franky Boxing!
Yes.
I see... So you left that
cherry tree branch after that.
No! I'll stay here, too! Mom!
S-Small? Luffy did?!
Is that right?! From the World Government...
Mom!
Yow!
I'm sorry.
Yep!
H-H-Hold on a sec!
I was happy to hear you call me that.
Show him in immediately.
Then, the culprit for
stealing the cherry tree is...
So these are the ones, huh?
What offensive power...!
Yes, your Majesty!
Thank you!
There's no way it's Pepper and Onion,
and obviously it's not me, either.
We can't possibly fight back.
To the kingdom that was about
to surrender with its hands tied
From now on, for you and me both...
So those who came later
are the true culprits, huh?
Third Gear!
over its concern for the hostages,
the World Government sent a boy.
Live, Robin!
Not enough for you? Then... Franky...
This is bad, Boss!
Before we came here, I stopped
by Pepper and Onion's houses,
A-A child?
...Convert!
Dammit! That blasted World
Government! How insulting!
but they weren't there! Which means
they're gone along with the cherry tree!
They all thought that everyone
in Ohara at that time died, but...
What?!
Hm?
Ahhh!
They opened...
...the Government missed
one brat who escaped then.
Where's the prey?
All right! I'm heading there now!
Franky Centaur!
Prey? You mean the pirates?
What?! How come you're small now?!
How was it?
He's a horse!
They're occupying the western
harbor and making it their hideout.
Who knows how many times this
eight-year-old brat almost got killed
No, wait. He's not a horse.
His upper body is attached in the back!
Boss!
Okay.
Don't worry! Just leave it to us!
by adults who wanted money...?
Third Gear?
Then he's a monster!
Well then, I'd like you to leave the rest to me.
He opened the iron doors and
became small? What the heck?
Orika! Take care of the rest, okay?
O-Okay!
Wait!
You couldn't trust anyone who came near you.
That must've been fun!
Hold it, you bastards!
Please give the highest priority
to the hostages' lives.
Oh, hey, Dr. Bluenose!
Please take care of Carrot!
Yep, Grandma! That pirate guy is fun!
You had nowhere you could sleep safe
and sound. You didn't have food, either.
What's going on?!
I said hold it, bastards!
Oh, Doc! Good timing! Please check on Carrot!
Are you trying to tell the
World Government what to do?
Hey, you idiots! Don't run away! Fight him!
She's not making any sense!
I don't even wanna imagine how crappy
the last twenty years were for you.
O-Okay!
Hey, Boss! Couldn't the information
in that letter on the arrow be fake?
Anyway, let's hurry and...
Wh-Why does this boy make me so intimidated?
No, this isn't fake!
Oh? Grandma, I can hear something down there.
So you were so unhappy it'd make you cry?
Anyway, let's hurry to the harbor!
The person who put a bounty
on your head twenty years ago...
Now that you mention it, yeah.
Ow, ow, ow...!
H-Help!
We don't have time to stop here right now.
The World Government...
Wh-Wh-What's gonna happen to us?!
...was my old man!
Good work, guys!
No matter what it is,
we just have to keep on going!
I'm scared!
He did it for world peace!
Eat and drink to your heart's content
and have a good time tonight!
Now, let's go resolutely!
What do you think, my foreign brother?!
Yahoo!
I bet you've never seen such
amazing cherry blossoms before.
Grandma! You're cool!
Now, after twenty years...
his son hunts down the only survivor,
A kingdom ain't actually a big deal!
Hey, escort ship! Send some
reinforcements in! Now!
Isn't that right, "Silver Fox" Foxy,
collector of rare items
No, it ain't!
Now the kingdom will be all ours!
Yes, sir! How many do you need?
Hooray for the boss!
and the battle of Ohara comes to an end.
How many do I need?! You idiot!
who travels the world and
always obtains what he desires?
Idiot! He's the new king!
Th-That's...
Oh, that's right!
Listen! Two vicious criminals
have removed their handcuffs
Ohara lost!
Booze! We're running out of booze!
and escaped, and are
now going on a rampage!
Indeed, Buggy, my brother.
Us, too! Someone, bring some more!
Water!
Its prettiness makes it a
perfect fit for my collection.
The ship's captain, navigator,
signalmen, corpsmen...
Robin! Be proud, Robin!
What the heck is going on?!
I'm sure Porche, who's waiting back in
our country, will be very pleased, too!
Today's booze is especially tasty!
Your mom is honorable! Ohara is honorable!
All of you! Come out and...
Understood, sir! We'll all work
together and capture the...
Why is there water?! What?!
Why?! We have no way out!
So this means our contract has
successfully concluded, huh?
--You guys...
--Huh?
Someday, pass down this
island's history, Robin!
...protect me!
Who's your captain?
Help!
With the money from this, I can start
my big advancement this time for sure!
Who are you?
Ohara fought against the world!
So this is about you?!
In the name of the World Government,
I've come to arrest you all.
Now, as promised, pay me
the 10 million Berries.
Oh, I don't have any money.
Arrest?! Me?! A brat like you will arrest me?
What?!
Y-Y-You don't have any money?!
It seems like the Government
is really hard up for people.
Not while I'm still alive!
Wh-Wh-What the hell are
you tryin' to pull here?!
Seriously, don't make me laugh!
But you're gonna die, aren't you?! Right?!
Do you have any idea how hard we
worked to bring it here, you jerk?!
Whether there's someone in the passage or not,
Chimney! Gonbe! Let's hurry!
What can one little brat do?
no one can now reach this place.
Grandma! You're fast!
You bastard!
If you wanna pretend to be some
government big shot, do it somewhere else!
Are you saying you deceived me
when you were flat broke?!
Soon this room will be submerged in the sea.
The power of alcohol is amazing, huh?!
Beat it! We got no time
to play games with a brat.
No, no... I've got lots of money.
I'm loaded with money.
The truth is, it's not really
because of the alcohol.
Whoa! What?!
Beat it already!
Before you get hurt!
--What?
--I'm having fun, so...
And if I sell this cherry tree to
another country, I'll get tons more money.
Coo coo!
You're in my way. Move.
You son of a bitch!
This is the first time I've felt this
way since Tom-san was still alive.
It's you who's gonna move!
C-Cutty Flam! What is he doing here?!
Thing is, I've got no money,
not even a single Berry, to give to you.
But that's okay. He fell for it! How stupid!
Iron Body.
What'd you say?!
What's funny, you horned raccoon dog?!
That idiot got caught in the landmine!
How dare you mock me so flashily?!
Who're you taking it out on, Moron-ky?!
You are not gonna get away with it!
Guys! Prepare a Buggy Ball!
He came to rescue me!
It's already ready!
Oops. This isn't good. It was
good that I made doubly sure.
What's with him?!
He used a weird technique!
You'll regret it.
I see. Not too bad.
We've gotta hurry. Come!
This place is located above the sea.
The seawater won't reach here.
It might not be a total lie that
you're from the World Government.
I can't even put it in words...
Coo coo!
But if you do any more weird stuff,
we can't guarantee the hostages' lives!
Hey! Set sail, marines! I'm gonna jump on!
Whoa!
You can hear the sounds of the
battleships' cannon fire, right?
Oh, she's...
Y-Yes, sir! Roger!
Thanks! You sent me this letter, right?
Where's the cherry tree?
We're setting sail!
How about you guys?
Yes, sir!
Yeah! It's kinda exciting!
I'm so angry that I can't stop my tears!
So long as you obey us,
we'll keep you alive for a while
This is fun! This is fun! The pirate guy is fun!
It's hiding behind that island.
The entire tree is on a big ship.
as a hostage for the World Government.
It's such a fine cherry tree.
What happened to your pirate crew...
What happened to Nico Robin...
Just watch carefully!
Kokoro-san! Chimney! Gonbe!
They're probably planning to
sell it to some other country.
This is the first step of a hero
that will be engraved in histo...
Now no one can defeat us!
Thanks for the guide marks!
Fortunately, there's a river ferry
available. You should hurry there.
Throw that brat in the same
lockup where the others are!
You must be worried.
Pirate lady!
That's the island where the Government
is turning the surrounding sea
into reclamation ground so
that people can live there.
I felt quite a shock just a moment ago.
Right now, there's nobody there,
so it's true that it's inconspicuous, Boss.
Looks like it's finally gonna start, huh?!
If you wanna go rescue them, go right ahead.
Cannon fire! Cannon fire!
At any rate, why don't we go there?
Thanks!
I won't take my focus off of you.
Huh?
Whoa! She's gone!
What a mysterious woman!
Well, whatever. Let's go!
No matter what they're going through
right now, they'll survive for sure!
What?! Hey, wait up, Boss!
Just watch carefully!
Lady...
But if I let you get away now,
you'll go kill my friends!
Get in there!
This is the first step of a hero
that will be engraved in histo...
We'll have you stay in here, too.
I won't take my focus off of you!
Wha-cha houie ouchie owow!
Wh-Who's that boy?
He's a "Great Emissary"
from the World Government.
Are you okay, Chief?!
Y... o... u...
He said he came to rescue you.
What was that?! Who did this?!
There's no one on the bridge!
Now the Government will
do whatever we tell them to.
There must be! They must be
hiding somewhere! Find them!
This is my power--the power
of the Slow-Slow Fruit!
No one can defeat us!
Where are they?!
This is a perfect technique to mark the
end of you idiots' lives, don't you think?
Well, you guys are all hostages.
Try and get along in there!
Shave!
You jerk!
Don't worry. You'll be able
to move in 30 seconds.
I'd like to verify one thing.
Now, your precious cannon ball
will be wasted if you stay there.
Hm? What is it?
Hey! What're you guys doing?!
Why aren't you attacking?!
Jet Pistol!
Why don't you move to the center?
Are all of the hostages here?
There, in the middle!
Yeah.
But, Chief, we can't find the enemy!
The cannon attack has begun.
I see.
By the way, I can hear a
strange sound ahead of here.
Jet Whip!
How... dare... you...?
Ah! There he is!
Shut your mouth!
Shave!
Hurry!
Wh-What was that? What's going on?
Shave!
Tempest Kick!
Ah... Ow, ow, ow...
Pepper and Onion had better be okay.
Finger Pistol!
Hm?
Yellow Lotus!
Pops, thanks! We can go on our own from here.
Run with all your might!
Oh, you will? I'm sorry I
couldn't take better care of you.
You'll die if you stay on the island!
Sail out on my raft!
Jet Stamp!
What about you, Saul?
This is it for me. I got caught.
Once the boy infiltrated the
pirates' hideout, right then and there,
How does it feel to be
attacked by your own men?
--Go!
--No! There's no one on the sea!
As I thought, I sense something odd...
he killed all 500 of the kingdom's
soldiers who were taken hostage.
You bastard!
I hate to say this, but unlike you two,
I'm delicate and cautious.
You're not gonna get away
with this! Guys! Get him!
Listen carefully, Robin!
K-Killed all of them?
And my sense is telling me...
Yeah!
You're alone now, but you'll
meet friends someday for sure!
Can't be...! Is something like that permissible?!
...this sound is probably...
Morons!
Ah...
Even if it's the World Government...
Even if it's for justice...
Slow-Slow Beam!
Hey!
Wait up!
Friends?
P-Pardon me!
Ah! Boss!
Right. The sea is vast, so someday, definitely...
Whoa!
"Justice"
My ribs got broken again! Wait up, you guys!
Listen up. Justice isn't all warm and fuzzy!
...you'll come across friends who'll protect you!
I'm severely injured with
broken bones all over my body!
You guys, too, remember it!
Yes, sir!
No one is born into this world to be alone!
Naturally, the pirates got
angry and rained bullets
upon the boy who was standing on the
mountain of bodies with his back turned.
Nooo!
Grandma! What's going on?!
Boy, that was a surprise!
His physical ability is as good
as that of a Six Powers Master.
Run, Robin! Don't look back!
Who cares?! Hurry up and run!
Hey, are you okay?
But the boy stood up in the flame of explosions,
killed the boss of the pirates,
Boss!
When you're having a hard time,
laugh like this, just like I taught you!
He surely seems like a different person
from the time I met him at Galley-La.
Ah! Hamburg!
Hey, hey, who are you guys?!
Hm? Ah! Cherry tree!
and settled that incident all by himself.
That rising steam...
That strange red tint his body has...
Watch out, Saul!
Are you the cherry tree thief?!
What?! You sure run your mouth
for someone who broke my ship!
Boss!
Ice Time.
What's going on in his body?
Boss! Boss! Boss!...
Pipe down! What's the problem?!
Saul!
Oh, I get it!
Who are you?!
I'm Straw Hat Luffy! I'm a policeman!
Boss...!
You have a high caliber, befitting a boss.
Go meet the friends
who're surely waiting for you
That brat is going on a rampage in the lockup!
I'd like for a certain idiot to hear that.
Don't resist, Split-Head!
somewhere at sea, Robin!
What?!
But I wonder... if your abilities are
good enough to back up that decision!
Split-Head?
What's with him? He got depressed big time.
Wh-What the hell is this?!
Live together with them.
More importantly, Boss...
there's someone we know over there.
Razor!
The result will be the same if you die!
How dare you... kill our important hostages...?!
Hm?
Ah! Buggy! You again?!
They committed a crime.
Jet Pistol!
So I executed them in the name of justice.
Give us the cherry tree back!
A crime?
As soldiers of the kingdom,
being weak is a crime.
Chief! Please look at that!
Huh?! What?! Where?!
What the heck?
They surrendered to evil and
plunged the kingdom into a crisis.
Ahh!
What're you doing?
Soldiers like that don't have the right to live.
Thanks to my Slow-Slow Beam,
his reaction is slow, too, you moron!
On top of the Tower of Law...!
They deserve to die.
You bastard! And you call yourself
an official of the World Government?!
Tower of Law?! What can
he do from that far away?!
Be careful, Boss! He uses weird techniques!
Hey! Capture Nico Robin already!
I see...
Pepper! Onion!
Justice would never surrender to evil.
Once this is all over, I'll be able
to become the world's hero!
Guys! Bring him down!
So, it's basically like doping.
You accelerate your blood circulation
by using your legs as a pump.
Huh?! What's with him?
He just got blown away!
The Buster Call sounds like a gun salute for me!
--Snap!
--Who the hell is that?!
The blood pressure gets so high that
a normal person's heart would explode,
I'll make you experience the same thing.
--♪ I was born... ♪
--He's aiming at us from that distance
without the slightest error, in this wind?!
My name is Foxy! I obtain whatever I desire.
but since your internal organs and veins
are all rubber-made, you can bear it.
--♪ ...on the island of snipers ♪
--Who the hell is that?!
That's a technique only a rubber man can use.
That serves you right, you damn brat.
Long-nose!
Don't stand in my way, you lowly policeman!
Don't treat us like fools!
See that?! Our sniper is amazing, isn't he?!
Although your physical ability
indeed spikes, exceeding its limits,
Slow-Slow Beam!
Dammit! After all the trouble we
went through, our plan got ruined!
your physical strength itself just
can't keep up with that intensification.
--♪ Or even your heart... ♪
--Damn well serves them right!
Ah! Boss!
Robin-chan! Run!
♪ ...lock on!! ♪
That's not really smart.
You're shortening your life, you know that?
H... How could he have survived that?!
I don't care if you're a
policeman or a diseased man--
Does he really have to sing?
How dare you...?!
it's a thousand years
too soon to go against me!
It's better than losing all sorts
of things right before my eyes!
Razor!
In any case, looks like a bunch
of nuisances got on board.
I'll do whatever I can do!
Finger Pistol!
Chief!
Shave!
You're too ambitious!
I guess I'll get rid of them
all at once with a cannon.
Tempest Kick! Leopard Tail!
Dammit! What're you guys doing?!
Shoot him dead already!
I'm not gonna let him!
Did you feel the explosion earlier?
Boss...
That was probably a Navy Headquarters
battleship doing some trial fire.
How noisy...
Finger Pistol.
We're trying, but our bullets won't
reach that far, much less hit him!
Geez...! I can't even sleep in.
Can you really defeat me?!
Before too long, they'll all start firing at once.
--Mr. Monk!
--Is it morning already?
That sniper's got really incredible skills!
I can't protect anyone unless I win!
Oh, yeah, today's the
cherry blossom viewing day.
Your friends who are in the
Tower of Law will die there.
Nico Robin is getting away!
Boss...
Hey, where the hell am I?! What's going on?!
Don't let her get away!
Idiots! You can shoot her!
H-He's a monster!
Even if there are some lucky ones
What're you doing there?
Gum-Gum...
who are running this way in the
underground passage right now...
Help!
--Yes, sir!
--Shoot her dead enough to keep her alive!
We got kidnapped along with the
cherry tree in the middle of the night.
This is no time for cherry blossom viewing.
...Rifle!
Huh?!
The boy, who had several
bullet marks on his back,
What?! Then what about the
offerings?! What about food?!
Tempest Kick!
Iron Body. Empty Tree.
was a CP9 intelligence agent at the age of 13.
People call him the strongest
and cruelest mass killing machine
Give us the cherry tree back!
Why would I?!
What?!
in the history of CP9,
whose mission is dark justice.
He stopped in the air!
Fire!
To think that he was capable of
all that when he was only 13...
Dammit!
Special Attack! Exploding Star!
That's exactly why all we have
to do is fulfill our own duty.
Here you go!
This seawater will gush into the passage,
Razor!
Didn't work! Dammit!
Hey, are you the one...
Gum-Gum...
ensuring that anyone in there will drown.
Rocket!
...who ruined the cherry blossom viewing event?
What is it this time?!
Geez... There's no end to these guys...
Something came out!
I'll give you credit for having the guts to
pick a fight with the World Government.
What?!
That's Straw Hat Luffy, whose
bounty is 100 million Berries!
Enough already!
What?!
I didn't think he'd be that fat.
That's exactly what I wanna say to you!
There you are! Pigeon guy!
Gum-Gum...
But in the end, you're just like any other pirate.
Shoot him down!
Hm? It's been 30 seconds?
It seems your level is nowhere
near enough to put up a good fight.
You...
I'm not gonna let him get away!
That won't work! The Bone Balloon is tough!
Nothing is going well for you, Straw Hat.
Double Slow-Slow Beam!
That naive idea of yours that you
can save everyone and escape...
Chop-Chop Festi...
Gum-Gum... Giant Axe!
What the hell is he?!
Let's see how far it gets you.
What're you doing, you jerk?!
You are...
Ahhh!
My body is strong because it's iron.
What the hell?! Is it a giant?!
He repelled it with his sword!
That landmine wasn't nice, Spanda!
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
Eek!
Well... Franky-kun, Franky-kun.
This is Sogeking.
Hm? Oh? This transponder
snail is supposed to...
Oh?
Flying Finger Pistol...
I got it from Nami.
More importantly, you should find a
red cloth bundle on the ground near you.
How dare you take away what
everyone was looking forward to?!
Pick!
Dammit! They're persistent.
I'm definitely not gonna forgive you!
Red cloth?
Yeah, I see it!
I'm the one who won't forgive you!
How dare you do such a terrible thing to me?!
Based solely on the head count,
they're like a first-class military force.
It's got two keys in it.
Hurry up!
Together with your keys,
you should have all the keys.
Don't yell so much. It'll come back soon.
All you have to do is capture Nico Robin
and put her on the escort ship!
All the keys?!
What'll come back?!
Move it! The battleships are coming!
My right hand.
Gum-Gum... Giant Whip!
Looks like it's too late.
I delivered them to you without fail.
Three Picks!
Ahh!
...Billy Club!
What'd you say?!
Ah!
Mission accomplished.
Ahh!
Let's hurry. This isn't good.
Whoa! Watch out!
Behind the fog...
#1...
The masts got broken!
#3...
They're falling down!
...we can see the outline of the ships!
Whoa! He sure went flying pretty far!
#4... Doesn't work!
H-Hey, don't run away! Wait!
The fight between those two is just crazy!
#5!
So, Boss, what do you wanna do with this one?
They came off!
Finger Pistol...! Pick!
You're such an idiot.
What'd you come out for this time?
Oh, no...
Not possible! Th-They're the real keys?!
It seems that as your power increases,
your speed decreases.
Come back when you get a clue!
Hey, hey... Pull yourself together!
This serves you right!
Flying Finger Pistol...
Gum-Gum...
They're here! They're finally here!
Oh, no... Does this mean...
Billy Club Bodhisattva!
Fire Pick!
Tempest Kick... Victory Bird!
Ahhh! You guys defeated everyone
in CP9 in the Tower of Law?!
Okay, then, shall we go back?
Yeah.
You're coming to view the cherry
blossoms too, right, Mr. Monk?
Yeah.
The iron outer shell got cracked...!
Good job, guys!
This ship won't last long!
No, that can't be true!
You must've stolen them and run! Dammit!
Th-They're here! The cannon fire has started!
That was close. I almost got split in two.
This is Franky! Hey, Long-nose!
I thought I was able to meet a man
with some backbone. How disappointing.
I got the handcuffs off of Nico Robin.
This is strange. Theoretically, it should work.
Watch out!
All right!
Run!
Did you see that, Cutty Flam?!
Thank you, Long-nose!
Carrot! Carrot!
Get us out of here!
Did you run out of strength from
your doping earlier after all?
It's all over for you guys! Or rather,
it was all over from the start!
I know!
You can thank those who fought hard
to gather the keys when this is all over.
Carrot!
Hey!
It's a bit early to say that
when the fight isn't over yet!
Ah...!
You are, without a doubt,
one of Luffy-kun's gang!
The one who is fighting Straw Hat is Lucci.
A Buster Call has been invoked!
Ah!
Our targets are Straw Hat Luffy
and his gang of about sixty pirates!
He's the strongest man in the history of CP9!
If it's backbone you want, I'll show you...
You can now do as you wish!
You might've been able to
get rid of the others okay,
However, due to a private agreement with
Admiral Aokiji, the criminal Nico Robin,
but Lucci's another story entirely!
Yes.
...another tactic!
last sighted on the Bridge of Hesitation,
Once Straw Hat is taken out,
you're next, Cutty Flam!
Third... Gear!
Seis... Fleurs!
is a sole exception to this
and is not one of our targets.
What?! What's going on?!
There's no need to assess the current situation!
I'm counting on you, Straw Hat!
Slap!
Completely destroy the
judicial island, Enies Lobby!
Hey! We brought the millennium cherry tree!
What's going on? Give me a report.
All battleships, take your positions!
Yes, sir, Vice Admiral!
Isn't this incredible?!
Take a look at this and cheer up!
Whoa...
We heard that Straw Hat Luffy and
Mr. Rob Lucci of CP9 are currently fighting.
Bone Balloon!
Let's play together soon!
Bone?
I'll do this to my heart's content.
As a result, the #4 ship got wrecked!
The power that moves
from one bone to another...
You dummies!
Rob Lucci isn't gonna die.
You guys worried me!
Take a look! My left arm is...
To the gunners on all ships, aim at the #4 ship!
...the arm of a giant!
Fire all cannons together in five seconds!
If it's all show, don't even bother!
Wha... Vice Admiral, you must be kidding.
Gum-Gum...
One thousand of our men are onboard!
Chief!
Iron Body!
Okay, guys! Hurry up and get over here!
...Giant Pistol!
Here you go! Thanks!
I'll get things ready for our escape!
There! There! Heave ho!
Roger!
Thank you! I'll get better soon!
Come down already, Sogeking!
A moment's indecision can allow
vicious criminals to slip away.
This is bad! The Sea Prism Stone
handcuffs are off of the criminal!
Can you protect our future from them?
Capture her again!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
Oh... he's fine.
I wonder if the medicine
finally started working...
Everything went according to my plan.
Hm? What's that?
No... This must also be
a form of medical science.
Fire!
Did I hear something just now?
A fleet of battleships!
The Buster Call has begun!
Boss! There's trouble! There's trouble!
We were finally able to free Robin-chan,
but if we don't do anything, we'll drown!
Justice would never surrender to evil.
I don't care if my body falls apart.
I thought I was able to meet a man
with some backbone. How disappointing.
Oh, what's the matter?
Did you get hay fever or something?
I'll do whatever I can do!
For example, if there's a soldier
who can't protect what he should,
I-I can't breathe... I can't hold my breath!
Yeah. My nose tickles and my eyes are itchy.
I really don't know what to do!
That's not really smart.
Did you run out of strength
from your doping earlier?
That technique of yours is
shortening your life, you know that?
that alone is a crime.
Oh... Am I dreaming?
Hey, that's not it!
If it's backbone you want,
I'll show you... another tactic!
Everything I do is in the name of justice!
The famous millennium cherry tree is gone!
You're too ambitious!
How beautiful... you are...!
In the past... and in the future, too!
What'd you say?! That really is trouble!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Robin Freed! Luffy vs. Lucci,
Showdown Between Leaders"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Mystical Mermaid Appears?
As Consciousness Fades Away..."
"Shivering Past! Dark Justice and Rob Lucci"
"I Can't Protect Anyone Unless I Win!
Third Gear Activated!"
"Boss Luffy Is the Culprit?
Track Down the Missing Great Cherry Tree"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
I'm gonna be a policeman!!