Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Stop! Stop! I said stop!
Those ranked Lieutenant
Commander or below, stay put!
Are you insane?! Don't think
that you'll be able to survive
It's dangerous ahead of here!
Water is rushing towards us!
To the two hundred elite Captains and
Commanders, go take them out quickly!
What's that?
after making the entire world your enemy!
Don't...
Finger Pistol!
C-Can't you guys hear the sound of water?!
I'll pursue that woman to the very
ends of the earth and eliminate her...
Get them!
Listen, if the water flows into
an underground passage like this,
...die!
we'll have no choice but to drown.
I want to live!
Recapture Nico Robin!
Zoro-kun, can't you hear the sound of water?!
After all, your ridiculous attacks wouldn't...
Hmm, it's true that
something doesn't feel right.
...Jet... Gatling!
I'm part of the Straw Hats, too.
When we fight, we fight together.
Then let's stop, you guys!
There's no other passage. We have
no choice but to keep on this path!
Is Nami-san okay?
You guys are as tough as ever.
I-I got stuck!
I knew it!
I'm glad you're alive!
Hold strong until Luffy comes!
Granny and the others
are being chased by water!
This is bad!
Ahhh! So it was real!
Mermaids really don't exist!
Ah! Pirate guys!
Sorry, but die in that stupid state, Straw Hat!
Guys! Do something about this water!
I'll pursue that woman who threatens
the World Government's plans
So the tales were true about
people seeing a mermaid
Ahh! It's here!
Finger Pistol! Spots!
then realizing it was actually a dugong!
to the very ends of the
earth and eliminate her...
You morons! She still hasn't
said she's a mermaid yet!
...in the name of dark justice!
Go back to normal, body!
Hurry! Hurry! I'm gonna be killed!
We came to take Robin away from all that!
Don't give up on the dream yet!
Gum-Gum...
I'm an icefish mermaid.
...Rocket!
Stop it! Don't say "icefish"!
Jet Stamp!
What is it this time?!
Something came out!
The damage I took earlier is affecting my legs!
Dammit!
Six King Gun!
Oh? I'm going back...!
I'm going back to normal!
That won't work! The Bone Balloon is tough!
Luffy!
Dammit!
It's a cannon attack!
Luffy...!
Bro!
The first column is...!
Gum-Gum... Giant Axe!
Luffy!
Th-This is a report to all ships.
--I got him!
--Watch out!
See? My attacks...
This is a report to all ships!
Hey! Now's not the time
to be spacing out, Soge...
...did a number on you after all.
Mr. Rob Lucci of CP9 has just...
Has just been defeated...
by pirate Straw Hat Luffy!
At the front gate, we identified about
fifty pirates, including the giants.
Those guys...!
That's Zambai and the others!
See, I told you! They escaped the island okay!
We have to do something...! Or we'll all drown!
Gum-Gum... Giant Whip!
I wasn't worried about them at all!
When we still haven't really
gotten Robin-chan back yet...!
Luffy...
Really, they wouldn't die
even if you killed them!
I can't breathe...! Everything's going dark!
It's over...
The other day, too...
We'll be okay now.
Help!
We have finished eliminating them
with a barrage of cannon fire.
Finger Pistol...! Pick!
You'll be fine. Get ahold of yourselves!
I'm not gonna let you die!
Luffy!
All are dead.
What're you doing?!
We're gonna go back together!
Tempest Kick... Victory Bird!
Under the circumstances, no one could
possibly survive on the main island.
Get up!
What?! What's going on?!
Hence, the number of survivors on
Enies Lobby's main island is zero!
Robin!
Luffy!
My body is being pulled by something!
Is it really okay...
The iron outer shell got cracked...!
"Fists Full of Emotion!
Luffy Unleashes Gatling with All His Might"
...for people to die so easily like this?
This ship won't last long!
You can't see people on the map.
Oh... Am I dreaming?
Weapons Left!
They just erase a small island from the
world map, without a shred of emotion.
That was close. I almost got split in two.
I must be...!
"From the Sea, a Friend Arrives!
The Straw Hats Share the Strongest Bond"
Several sailors are drowning in the sea...
That's what Buster Call is.
As their consciousness fades away,
they see an elegant tail fin...
Super...!
Th...
Hurry up! Straw Hat!
Th-This can't be happening!
When they look up, they see
long hair swaying in the sea...
Commander!
Mr. Rob Lucci, the leader of
the current CP9, is considered
Your friends are waiting for you here!
Fire!
What's with those pirates?!
to be the strongest in the history of Cipher Pol.
What a crazy brawl! They're holding
their own against Captains!
She's so beautiful.
Don't you dare die on us!
To think that even he has
been defeated by a pirate...!
This is the mermaid legend...
It's like we're seeing a fantasy...
"A Mystical Mermaid Appears?
As Consciousness Fades Away..."
If I'm dreaming... please don't let me...
Is that woman a power holder?!
...wake...
I'm gonna go super express!
Make sure you hold your breath tight!
I'll take care of her. Stay back!
Du...
This will be the last time!
I'm shrinking!
Cien Fleurs!
--Du...
Until I bring you down, I won't stop it.
Du... A dugong?!
Luffy won!
Are you gonna try to use up
all your power and die?
Flip!
I don't know what's gonna happen.
Coo, coo, coo...
That was close!
Coo, coo.
Second... Gear!
"Cannon Fire Sinks the Island!
Franky's Lamentation"
Here we go! Thunder Ball!
Why did they fire at their
own battleship? Are they idiots?!
"Wait for Luffy! Mortal Combat
on the Bridge of Hesitation!"
But in any case, I got shrunk again.
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Third Gear is such an interesting
idea and it's really powerful,
but how my body reacts is a problem.
Done!
Since I was pumped up for about a minute,
I'll probably stay shrunk for about a minute.
He had me worried there.
I'd better hide until I go
back to normal or I'll be killed!
Sorry, marines! We're gonna
use this ship to escape.
So you finally did it, Straw Hat!
Luffy...
So I guess these guys aren't
the typical small fries, huh?
Luffy!
Hurry up and get here!
Everyone! Get on the escape ship
right away! We're gonna set sail!
Two-Sword Style...
Now, we've finished cleaning out our
escape ship, the former escort ship.
You did it! Luffy!
I can't tell if he's serious or fooling around...
But in the end, he's still alive.
...Hawk Wave!
You did it, Straw Hat!
Yes.
Well, it'd be disappointing if he died from
a small cannon attack like that anyway.
All we have to do now is wait
for Straw Hat and the others.
Hm?
Y-You morons! They can hear us!
Who's next?!
That's okay! We'll let him know!
Hey! Who're those voices?!
We don't know! They're coming
from somewhere via transponder snail!
Usopp...
Bro!
What's that?
Don't...
Gum-Gum...
...die!
Luffy!
...Jet Pistol!
What?! This voice...
We can now see the main island front gate!
We're almost there!
He jumped backwards to reduce the impact!
Luffy!
Moon Walk!
Hurry!
Finger Pistol!
Franky, the one you love so much,
has been taken away just like Tom-san was.
Luffy!
Stop it! If we had just taken off,
we would've been considered dead!
Battleships 6, 7, and 8 identified
pirates in front of the main gate.
Get up!
Do you wanna come along?
You guys...
Okay.
Those guys...
Jet Bullet!
Hey, you guys! Wake up!
Are they possibly the pirates
we took out at the main gate?
Ribbit!
Hey!
Twin Jet Pistol!
Well, they can't be...
I'm sure they all fell off the cliff!
There's no way they could've survived.
Straw Hat was going on a rampage
on that battleship just a bit ago,
U-Usopp...
Gum-Gum...
but now he's been blown to pieces!
This can only be described as a miracle.
S-So... you came?
I'll show you...
Dammit! It's a cannon attack!
Serves you guys right! Your captain has died!
They must've... They must've
received a tremendous shock.
...my strongest technique, one that
pushes the Six Powers to their limit!
Bro!
Hey, hey... They fired at the ship
while their own men were on it.
D-Don't get the wrong idea!
Six Powers Secret Technique!
They all stopped breathing,
so they didn't swallow much water.
This is the power of a Buster Call,
the attack I set in motion!
I came here to rescue Robin!
This is justice, Cutty Flam!
Six King Gun!
Good thing they're all okay... but...
Now, hand Nico Robin over to us.
I didn't come here to see your face!
In return, I could make your charges go away.
...what on earth could have shocked them
enough to make them stop breathing?
Geez... He's such a...
Why do you have to protect
that woman in the first place?
It was you.
Hey, you! Boss cat of CP9!
Hm?
You're not even a pirate.
Are you saying you'd trust that dangerous
woman who carries Ohara blood in her veins
You must be the friend that
pirate king kid came to rescue.
I'm talking to you!
Now, I'll take you on! Bring it on!
over the World Government that
protects you ordinary people every day?!
It's like... the Impact Dial from the sky island...
I saw you at the Shift
Station, right? I remember.
If you disobey us,
just like Tom, you'll end up dy...
Th-That's right! I'm your opponent!
Back then...
But it's several times more
powerful than the Impact Dial...
Hey, idiot! Don't push!
...I never thought that you guys
would pull something like this.
Now, don't be surprised when I tell you this!
Don't move!
--We're gonna fall!
--The ropes are gonna rip!
Tempest Kick! Victory Bird!
I'm the great Captain Usopp,
a pirate among pirates,
Put some clothes on, you damn old hag!
M-My face can't get any more swollen!
You morons! Galley-La's ropes never tear!
the great warrior of the sea who
has 8,000 men under his command!
I laughed when I heard him say he
was gonna be King of the Pirates...
Seriously, after I told you
to keep your mouth shut...
Luffy...!
Can it! I've heard enough of your crap!
We're all okay!
Our friends are waiting!
Lucci is strong.
Don't stand in our way!
The giants took all the cannon fire for us!
If Straw Hat hadn't kept him
restrained in that place,
I've traveled all over the Grand Line
and wreaked havoc on every single island!
...but who knows? It might actually happen.
He drew the elephant sword, Funkfreed!
Ribbit!
Whoa! They sure are tough.
That thing is powerful!
I don't know how many of us
would've died, to be honest.
Listen, Funkfreed. To ensure they
won't be able to resist any longer,
Grandma! They're all alive!
Anyone who falls into my hands...
You know, I sometimes feel...
we'll fatally wound Nico Robin,
whose guard is down right now.
Sodom and Gomorrah are okay, too!
...even you guys, the World Government...
...that Luffy always seems to know
whom he has to fight from the start.
I'm so glad to hear that!
Take this! Elephant Chop!
...will be crushed by the tip of my little finger!
Now, if we take our sweet time here,
the battleships will come again!
Is Nami-san okay?
You guys are as tough as ever.
Let's hurry up and get out of here!
I'm definitely gonna beat up the pigeon guy.
Anyway... we have a means to escape,
so don't worry about us!
If that pisses you off, then bring it on!
You no-good little kitten!
I'm glad you're alive!
Bastard!
He just has animal instincts...
even better than yours.
Ahhh! So it was real!
Mermaids really don't exist!
We'll see you after we
make it out of here alive!
That's right!
Let's hurry!
You guys need to hurry up and climb already!
So the tales were true about
people seeing a mermaid
Hey...
The blood is rushing up to my head!
Hey... don't! Don't! Hey!
then realizing it was actually a dugong!
I have a report, sir!
Actually, it's rushing down!
He stopped it...!
Straw Hat Luffy is in the first column!
You morons! She still hasn't
said she's a mermaid yet!
Okay, climb up!
Leave him alone!
So he's alive...
Don't give up on the dream yet!
Tell all ships to take up positions
around the Bridge of Hesitation!
Climb up slowly!
You've already lost.
I have no business with you.
I'm an icefish mermaid.
We're gonna fall!
--Ribbit!
--Don't shake!
Stop it! Don't say "icefish"!
--Yes, sir!
--Let's go! Hurry up!
They're all gonna be killed anyway.
You guys...! Dummies...!
He's so pathetic in every respect.
But I've never heard of a mermaid with legs.
You just stay there and watch.
I wasn't worried about you guys! You dummies!
He won't... die, right?
All right, come on, boss cat!
I'm gonna blow you away!
Funkfreed! You're an elephant!
You shouldn't be losing to him!
I have an objection, too!
Those idiots are alive!
I'm glad...! I'm glad! I'm so happy!
Are you an idiot?
Go crazy and cut them up!
What'd you say?!
Are you stupid?! Stop it, Usopp! He'll kill you!
Only an idiot calls others idiots!
Mermaids should be more...
Mermaids should be more like...
Put your nose back to normal, elephant,
Shut up! What can you do
when you're almost dead?!
Yeah. It's really a relief.
unless you want me to shoot
you right between the eyes.
A well-proportioned sexy body...
But there's no point if you die here, is there?
Smooth white skin and flowing hair
that's beaming and beautiful...!
All right. That's good. You're smart.
He's mine! I'm gonna beat him up!
Yeah. You're right.
Nico Robin, will Straw Hat
and the others come here?
Then get up already!
Should we head over to
the main gate right away?!
Everyone will... for sure.
Then don't look like you're about to die!
Do it later. Right now, we have
to focus our efforts here.
What're you all doing?!
Carry out your duty already!
Spandam, I thought I told you that
I'm betting everything on them.
What's going on?
It's not like you!
The wall is...
Yes, sir!
What?
The first column is now cut off!
I never thought a day like this would come.
Hey! Bring on as many guys as you'd like!
Even though there's nothing but smoke
above us, we can still see the sky!
Stop it!
If I had had power on that day...
When mermaids are around 30,
their tail fins fork into two
Thunderbolt Tempo!
I'm changing the charges.
We can see the sea, too!
They destroyed half of the bridge!
For the charge of building the pirate ship
for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates,
and they become able to live on land.
They're a mysterious species.
Why did they do that?!
Tiger Trap!
we'll take shipbuilding
engineer Tom to Enies Lobby.
Oni Giri!
Mr. Rob Lucci of CP9 and Straw Hat
Luffy are in the first column!
If you go to the Fishman
Island one day, you'll see.
Pound Phoenix!
This isn't... This isn't hell!
Hm? Fork into two...? Oh, I see!
That is all.
They say when a cat lives 100 years, its tail
splits into two and it becomes a monster.
The battleships are coming this way!
What got into that old geezer?
Cien Fleurs!
Oh, a goblin cat, huh?!
Oh, well. I don't have
business with his disciples.
Don't lump me in with monsters!
Don't look like you're about to die, you jerk!
Release those two disciples!
Couldn't you at least say
thank you for what I did?!
All ships! Take up positions
around the Bridge of Hesitation!
Keep an eye on Straw Hat in the first column!
Thank you very much, Kokoro-san!
Don't make us worry, you bastard!
On the bridge and the escort ship,
Y-Yes, sir, but...
Tom-san can no longer be saved.
we've identified nine pirates,
including pirate hunter Zoro and Nico Robin!
Hm?
No problem.
Pirate Straw Hat Luffy also
appears to be severely wounded!
If it's the World Government we're
up against, there's nothing we can do!
It appears that they're the main force
that defeated CP9 in the Tower of Law!
Bear it. Tom-san saved you two!
He isn't moving at all!
If you make an enemy of them,
What?!
Are you done?
They're coming to take Robin again.
no matter how many lives
you have, it's not enough!
You'd better be prepared.
Enies Lobby is the judicial island
owned by the Government.
We're not gonna let them!
No criminals taken there...
At any rate, they're unbelievable.
...have ever returned!
Robin-chaaan!
I know...
The 800-year-old legend of the
impregnability of Enies Lobby
This isn't hell or anything.
came about due to the reign
of many generations of CP9.
Is he stupid or what?
Huh? Where am I?
What should we do?
And yet, to think that a pirate
group defeated its members
Are you stupid, too?!
Luffy...!
Robin!
Just keep going; give him what he wants.
Don't be concerned about him!
and their captain is vying with
Mr. Rob Lucci, of all people...
I'm so glad we made it in time,
Robin! So you're okay!
Hey, Luffy!
It seems that Straw Hat Luffy
wasn't a mere rookie.
What're you doing?! Hurry up
and get your butt over here!
Y-Yes, sir.
Robin!
Yes, all thanks to you guys.
But he can't defeat Mr. Lucci.
We have to run or we won't survive!
Stop, Puffing Tom!
Defeat him! We'll all go back together, Luffy!
And it's very clear that their
group will be annihilated here.
Thank you.
Don't worry about it!
Where are you taking your creator to?!
Of course!
This is the end of the road for those villains.
What's the matter! We're almost there!
Hey, look over there!
Grandma! That's amazing!
So you were a mermaid all this time?!
Use your Gum-Gum to shoot yourself over here!
So you can still move...
Once you're here, I'll carry you!
I was thinking you were different,
since you have fins and scales!
I never said... I gave in.
Ribbit, ribbit...!
You should've noticed, grandkid!
We're surrounded by the sea
and a bunch of battleships!
Chopper?!
I won't let you pass here!
If we stay here, we're gonna be killed!
Until I defeat you...
Are you okay?
Oh...?
It seems that the pirates are trying
to escape using the escort ship.
Luffy-kun!
...I won't... sink to the ground ever again!
I can't move my body.
We're here!
Give Tom-san back to us!
Yeah.
It's not surprising. We'll tell you
what happened when this is all over.
Luffy!
We all got to the bridge safely!
I wanted to get Tom-san back at any cost.
I'm terminating Life Return.
We're okay!
Zoro!
Those who know the myth of
the impregnable Enies Lobby...
You don't have to worry about us, Luffy-kun!
I've had enough with you guys' farce.
Luffy! Can you hear me, Luffy?!
We rescued Robin-chan, too!
Those who know the power
of the World Government...
I'll crush you with pure power once and for all!
All that's left is for you to defeat him!
The Straw Hats overturn their
common sense and advance.
Don't worry about your friends, Straw Hat.
I-I can't...
Defeat him, Luffy!
We'll all make it through this...
As you wish... to be together with them again...
...and leave this place!
My body...
What?
...I'll send you all to the same hell!
Zoro! I mean, Zoro-kun!
In order to rescue one friend,
they make the world into their
enemy without a second thought.
...isn't moving at all.
Hey, look at that.
It isn't moving...?
It's exhilarating.
Don't be ridiculous! You defeated the enemy!
Now it's just a matter of how
long we can hold them off.
We got Robin back, too!
All that's left is for us to go back!
Up to this very day, I've never once
forgotten about Tom-san's death.
It's hard to believe that's the island
we were on up until just a bit ago.
Please! Try hard!
Spots!
The stupid face of that official...
As you said, they're all still alive.
That's incredible.
What's with this attack?
It's already a sea of flames!
Every time it went through my mind...
...I hoped...
But we'll see if you can still keep
that face a few minutes later.
I hoped that...
Usopp!
Hey, stop it, you idiot! Stop it! Hey!
It seems like they've been ordered
not to kill Nico Robin in their attacks.
Let's take the ship to
the column where Luffy is!
Evil cannot thrive in this world!
...one day I'd be able to crush him...!
Everyone! Hurry up and get on the ship!
Those ranked Lieutenant
Commander or below, stay put!
So that's why this bridge
isn't being targeted right now.
Fire!
To the two hundred elite Captains and
Commanders, go take them out quickly!
They've given us quite a bit of trouble!
Their trying not to kill her must mean
they still intend to get her back.
If we're just careful about that thunderbolt...
C-Captains from Headquarters?!
After completely destroying Enies Lobby,
They're in the same class as that smoke freak!
Ahhh! There's another cloud!
they'll probably engage in some
close combat to get her back.
We're facing that many guys of that level?!
Guys, don't gather in one place!
Spread out and attack all at...
No! Our escape ship is...!
H-Hey, isn't that bad?
We're all physically wrecked,
That's proof that they're scared of us.
...like this.
What is it, at a time like this?!
and on top of that, there are lots of crazy
powerful guys on those battleships, right?
Grandma, I'm scared.
Thanks to them, my wish came true.
Oh, crap...! Now it's hopeless...
What'd you do that for?!
Where's Luffy right now?
--Guys!
--Hm?!
I see the dust of combat still coming up
from the top of this bridge's first column.
Besides that ship, there's no other
way for us to escape from here!
When the lightning strikes,
please be careful not to get electrocuted!
Weapons Left!
Thunder Ball!
I'm someone who once died in the past.
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Kokoro-san... Chimney... Gonbe... Chopper!
If it enables the Straw Hats
to leave this place alive,
Hm? Where's Sanji?
I don't mind sacrificing my life!
His opponent is, of course,
that pigeon guy, Rob Lucci.
He was right there just a moment ago.
What? Where'd that idiot
cook go at a time like this?
It's not far from here! If we give him a hand...
Good job, pirate ladies!
Don't bother.
All hands prepare for battle! Let's go!
The pigeon guy is no ordinary man.
We're okay, so go up there
and help the guys already!
Hand over the escort ship to us!
Yeah!
What's the point if we get dragged
into the fight and get separated again?
I'll prepare an escape route for them!
Leave the raccoon dog guy to us!
Enough talking--bring it on already!
O-Oh, no...
I'm not a raccoon dog. I'm a reindeer.
To make sure we still have an escape route
Interesting. I'll go wild one more time.
Okay! Then we'll leave Chopper to you!
regardless of when that group
of battleships turns this way,
I'll fight, too. I'm okay now.
--Robin!
--Yeah.
we'll wait for Luffy right here.
We'll stand our ground here
with everything we've got!
That's all we need to do.
Hold your ground until
Luffy comes, at any cost!
When everyone's fighting so hard,
to think that I can't do anything...
We have to get off the ship! If they hurt
the ship, we won't be able to escape!
It's frustrating...!
I'm gonna die!
Everyone! Hang in there!
Run with all your might!
I'll never get caught again!
You'll die if you stay on the island!
Sail out on my raft!
H-Hey! What do you mean run away?!
They're okay somehow!
It's our duty to guard this place!
I can't... move!
The storm is just beginning.
What about you, Saul?
Outta our way!
This is it for me. I got caught.
Good!
Understood.
This isn't the time for that!
This island will be entirely eliminated!
Get them!
Go!
Click. Beep...
No! There's no one on the sea!
--Beep... beep... beep...
--Dammit!
Listen carefully, Robin!
Sanji-kun! Where on earth have you been?!
You're alone now, but you'll
meet friends someday for sure!
Well, sorry about that.
I had to take care of something.
Those ranked Lieutenant
Commander or below, stay put!
Bingo!
Friends?
But at any rate, this is terrible.
We're in serious trouble!
Right. The sea is vast, so someday, definitely...
To the two hundred elite Captains and
Commanders, go take them out quickly!
Since we have Robin-chan,
I thought they weren't gonna
attack this area. But the ship was...
Your legs are being affected after all.
...you'll come across friends who'll protect you!
Get them!
No one is born into this world to be alone!
I see. Looks like your ridiculous way
of fighting isn't just playing around.
That's it, you bastards!
Release the old lady now and...
Recapture Nico Robin!
This is no time for that!
We've come this far! We're not
gonna let them take her back!
But don't underestimate the inner
strength of a Six Powers Master.
Mermaid Kick!
Run, Robin! Don't look back!
Two hundred elites from
Navy Headquarters... Fine by me!
Luffy...
In order to master the ultimate techniques,
But there are so many of them!
you need the ultimate inner strength!
Fire.
Weapons...
Live together with them.
So what?!
...Left!
This is different from Ohara... From that time.
Dealing with one or two at a time is too
much of a pain. Attack me all at once!
Tempest Kick! Victory Bird!
They're even firing on their own people!
Corner them at the second column!
There's nothing to be afraid of...
Fire!
...because... I'm not... alone anymore!
Experience the power of Sogeking!
Victory Bird!
Watch out! Run! Run!
Sunflower Star!
Fire!
Dammit! What's the deal
with them?! I can't hit them!
So you want me to fight
with guns and cannons?!
Franky... your guys are...
Take this!
Hey! I beat them!
Those things won't work on me! Weapons Left!
Oh, I see! All my shots
must've actually hit them!
That's right! I'm the king of snipers, Sogeking!
I won't let you get away! Strong Right!
Hurry!
You damn idiot!
They've got the luck of the devil!
♪ I was born on the... ♪
The entrance to Enies Lobby...
The main gate is around the corner!
They're fine. I'm sure they've escaped okay!
Take this!
We're almost there!
Go! Giants!
Leave it to us!
I'll show you the power of the Berry-Berry Fruit!
We'll be able to get off the island!
We'll be able to escape!
Dammit! They've finally
taken out the entire bridge!
Hey! Whoa! Hey! Time out! Time out!
We're cornered on this column!
Dammit! I can't make a wrong move here!
All right!
Y-You bastard! If you're using a sword,
go to Zoro! Go to Zoro!
We're out of options!
There, we did it!
So how about it--were you
impressed by our giant guts?!
We have no choice but to
fight them all from here!
That's how it should be, right?!
You can't do anything, can you?!
Ah...!
Don't be stupid! There's gonna be
wave after wave of stronger guys!
What's that?!
Thanks!
Gunpowder Star!
Hey you, hold on a sec.
Prepare all cannons to fire on the first column!
All right! My feint strategy was a success!
What?!
If you like flying so much...
Hey... What the heck is this?!
Hey! D-Don't!
Oh, no...
I almost fell off!
Weapons Left!
Three battleships!
"Phew"
That was close!
At any rate, more and more
keep crawling out... What a pain!
They arrived here ahead of us!
Be careful! There are some
power holders among them!
Look! They really came!
Dammit!
I'm sure we tied them up in the courthouse!
Isn't there someone here with some backbone?!
Eliminate Straw Hat Luffy immediately!
How did they do it?
Don't think you can defeat me just
by attacking me in large numbers!
They could say the same about us!
Vice Admiral!
Treinta Fleurs! Clutch!
Yeah...
Prepare to fire cannons.
--Aim at them.
--Yes, sir!
Oh?
Hm? That's...
After stating your unit and marine code
A broadax? How daring.
and showing your picture ID,
you may board the battleship!
Luffy!
So you're Roronoa Zoro?
Okay. Go.
Hey, Paulie! Come back!
What a relief. I thought we were gonna
get eliminated along with the island.
And if I am?
I like it.
I'll defeat you!
You're picking up a transponder snail?!
What're you gonna do with that?!
Fine!
We can find out how the Straw Hats are doing!
What's the matter?!
Luffy's in danger! We have
to at least bring him over!
Just swinging that thing around
powerfully isn't enough to defeat me.
I ate the Rust-Rust Fruit and became a rust man.
Dammit! It's a cannon attack!
Oh, crap...!
Luffy!
Resisting is futile, pirates.
Bro!
You can't defeat me.
It won't work. Because of the distance,
Make one move, and we'll fire
our guns and cannons at you.
Dammit! My Yubashiri...
even if I try to pull him,
I'll drop him into the sea.
I'll turn all your proud swords to rust.
This is bad!
It sure doesn't seem like
they're gonna let us get away.
Luffy!
Three-Sword Style... Oni... Giri!
This is bad. Things are in a terrible state!
Behind us is a harbor and an island on fire.
Interesting...
Straw Hat won, but he can't stand up!
It seems like his life is in danger!
There's no place to escape, either.
I'll test you.
In front of us are guns and cannons...
What?!
Not again! Like I said, instead of
coming to me, go to Zoro! Go to Zoro!
--Straw Hat!
What're you thinking about right now, Paulie?
Ribbit! Ribbit!
Stand up, Straw Hat!
Now you get it, right?
You can't defeat me with swords!
Memories of my past.
Get ahold of yourself, kid!
Good job, Zoro-kun!
Don't say something like that.
Pirate guy!
We can depart anytime!
Or...
I... I can't move my body!
Sogeking! Duck!
Or...?
Luffy! Stand up! Please!
Once Luffy gets here,
we can set sail right away!
The hell that we're headed to now...
Isn't there something you can do, Luffy?!
Nice, Zoro-kun!
Okay.
I rusted your joint. I'll continue
until your entire body is rusted!
Ribbit!
Luffy!
Straw Hat!
Straw Hat! You can do it!
Dammit!
Firebird Star!
Grandma! The Navy's coming here, too!
Straw Hat!
We finished retrieving marines and officials.
That's not good.
Ribbit, ribbit!
To all battleships.
Maintain a distance from the main gate.
Robin, stay here. I'll hold them back!
But, simply put, there are about as
many battleships as there are of us.
Are you okay, Zoro-kun?!
Oh, crap... I'm seriously in trouble...!
What're they trying to do?!
Luffy!
Even if we could set sail, it's virtually
impossible to get through here.
Here I come! Thunder Charge!
Do something, Luffy!
Gum-Gum... Jet Pistol!
This is a report from the
front gate in the northwest.
Straw Hat!
Get ahold of yourself, Straw Hat!
Swing Arm!
We've completed retrieval of
Enies Lobby's marines and officials.
Th-This is...
Straw Hat!
Also, at the front gate,
we identified about fifty pirates,
including the giants, escaping the main island.
Gum-Gum... Jet Pistol!
Again...!
Thunder Ball!
Those guys...!
Who is that?!
--What's this?!
--Clouds?!
I'm not gonna take that a second time!
That's Zambai and the others!
See, I told you! They escaped the island okay!
Hey! Do you wanna get killed?!
This is no time to be spacing out!
Ultimate Radius...
I wasn't worried about them at all!
Just whose voice is this?
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Really, they wouldn't die
even if you killed them!
Six King Gun!
Th-That's right! This is the
same voice from that time...
I did it!
How dare you fight us
with that joke of a weapon?!
The other day, too...
You pirate bitch!
H-He found me!
We have finished eliminating them
with a barrage of cannon fire.
That's quite an unbalanced
combat power you've got.
All are dead.
You should willingly accept it,
Under the circumstances, no one could
possibly survive on the main island.
What's going on?!
if that's the price you pay
for the power you used earlier.
--Straw Hat!
Hence, the number of survivors on
Enies Lobby's main island is zero!
It's obvious! My underlings are...
Life Return. Paper Art. Fighting Form.
Robin...!
I'm part of the Straw Hats, too.
When we fight, we fight together.
No! Not those voices!
I've been hearing it for a while!
This is a report from Battleship 2.
Huh?!
The courthouse and the Tower of Law
in the southeast of the island...
Finger Pistol!
...as well as the underground passage
connected to the bridge...
Gah! There's more?!
Hello! We're hostages!
...have all been destroyed.
The only target left to attack
is the Bridge of Hesitation.
We're weak!
After all, your ridiculous attacks wouldn't...
Below...?
Look below?
Until I defeat you...
I-I got stuck!
...I won't... sink to the ground ever again!
Franky...
This is bad!
I'm not mistaken. I can hear it. What? Below?
Those guys have been...
Hold strong until Luffy comes!
Sorry, but die in that stupid state, Straw Hat!
All right, you guys go straight to
the courthouse and join Straw Hat.
Who's that?!
Finger Pistol! Spots!
We're gonna split into two
and bring the drawbridge down.
What the hell is this?
Go back to normal, body!
Hurry! Hurry! I'm gonna be killed!
Shave!
Galley-La's shipwrights, too...
In the not-so-distant future, you'll regret
that you took in a troublesome woman.
When you see... those guys, tell them...
It's telling us to look below!
What's the matter?
What're you talking about, reindeer?
Gum-Gum...
It seems to me that doping
technique of yours is losing its edge.
In five seconds, fire at Straw Hat
Luffy in the first column!
Yes, we are. I'll never see you guys again.
"You guys're fired."
It's not a matter that people
like you can get involved in.
Oimo... Kashii...!
--Luffy is gonna...!
--Straw Hat!
It's pointless to struggle!
The damage I took earlier is affecting my legs!
How...
You guys won't be able to
get past Enies Lobby after all!
Robin intends to die for us!
Oh? I'm going back...!
I'm going back to normal!
...dare you...
That's just reality!
You're such a... Really, you're such a...
...deceive us?!
Gum-Gum... Jet Axe!
I guess Yokozuna was with them, too.
Iron Body!
Even if this island gets
destroyed in the process...
Are you insane?! Don't think
that you'll be able to survive
Do you wanna come along?
after making the entire world your enemy!
...I'll pursue that woman who
threatens the World Government's plans
Ribbit... Ribbit!
Jump into the sea!
See? My attacks...
I'll pursue that woman to the very
ends of the earth and eliminate her...
to the very ends of the
earth and eliminate her...
Sodom and Gomorrah, too...! They all...
...did a number on you after all.
Four seconds!
...in the name of dark justice!
Into the sea!
I want to live!
We came to take Robin away from all that!
Usopp?!
Robin! Can you drop Luffy into the sea?
...Jet...
--Leave it to me!
--You idiot! Are you trying
to get us to commit suicide?!
Jet Stamp!
He says, "I'll be faithful to
Big Bro Franky for the rest of my life!"
...Gatling!
Getting desperate won't save us!
Six King Gun!
Three!
Is there anything we can do?
We're gonna be saved!
She came to rescue us!
We've got one more friend, right?!
We have to do something...! Or we'll all drown!
His pectoral muscle got hurt by a trench mortar!
Two!
When we still haven't really
gotten Robin-chan back yet...!
Chopper! Did you look below?!
Move over now before he falls!
I did!
No one's gonna be saved
unless you guys move forward!
Is this it? My life...
Is it really okay...
Cien Fleurs!
...was quite fun... Hey!
I haven't lived long enough!
...for people to die so easily like this?
Besides, it wouldn't even be funny
You can't see people on the map.
if the great Usopp, brave warrior
of the sea, died from drowning!
One!
They just erase a small island from the
world map, without a shred of emotion.
Delphinium!
I'm moving! Is Robin doing this?!
I can't hold my breath any longer!
That's what Buster Call is.
I can't breathe...! Everything's going dark!
Into the sea!
What's going on?!
Into the sea...!
Help!
Into the sea!
What happened?!
You'll be fine. Get ahold of yourselves!
I'm not gonna let you die!
Bro! We came to rescue you!
Luffy!
Follow Luffy!
Luffy...!
Bro! Let's go back together!
What?! What's going on?!
Here we go!
The first column is...!
My body is being pulled by something!
Here we go...!
H-Hey... What's that?
Into the sea!
Hurry up! Straw Hat!
The pirates are jumping into the sea!
Hey! Look over there!
Your friends are waiting for you here!
Th-This is a report to all ships.
How stupid! There's no way that they
can survive after jumping into this sea.
This is a report to all ships!
Don't you dare die on us!
Mr. Rob Lucci of CP9 has just...
Did the pirates lose their minds?!
Oh... Am I dreaming?
Has just been defeated...
by pirate Straw Hat Luffy!
I must be...!
Several sailors are drowning in the sea...
Franky...
As their consciousness fades away,
they see an elegant tail fin...
Luffy!
Let's go back, everyone!
When they look up, they see
long hair swaying in the sea...
Luffy...
--I got him!
--Watch out!
She's so beautiful.
Hey! Now's not the time
to be spacing out, Soge...
This is the mermaid legend...
It's like we're seeing a fantasy...
It's over...
Fire!
We'll be okay now.
If I'm dreaming... please don't let me...
We're gonna go back together!
Back to the seas of adventure!
...wake...
I'm gonna go super express!
Make sure you hold your breath tight!
This will be the last time!
Robin!
Until I bring you down, I won't stop it.
Get on the Merry!
Du...
Are you gonna try to use up
all your power and die?
--Du...
I don't know what's gonna happen.
Du... A dugong?!
Merry!
Luffy!
I came to get you!
Second... Gear!
What on earth... is this Buster Call thing?!
So you came... You're such a... You're such a...
Two hundred Captains
from Navy Headquarters?!
I have been alone all this time.
They're all alive!
Just how many strong guys
do they have to send in?!
To think that what Saul said came true...
Hey! Hurry up, Straw Hat!
All I have to do now is beat up
this guy... The pigeon guy!
That proves just how scared they are of us.
Luffy! Into the sea! Jump into the sea!
Friends...
Your friends... Your friends...
are waiting for you here!
Listen up! Hold strong until Luffy comes!
I appreciate them for rescuing me
from the bottom of my heart.
We're gonna go back together, Robin!
We've got one more friend, right?!
We'll all make it through this
and leave this place!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Everyone Makes a Great Escape!
The Road to Victory Is for the Pirates"
"From the Sea, a Friend Arrives!
The Straw Hats Share the Strongest Bond"
"Fists Full of Emotion!
Luffy Unleashes Gatling with All His Might"
"Cannon Fire Sinks the Island!
Franky's Lamentation"
"Wait for Luffy! Mortal Combat
on the Bridge of Hesitation!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!