Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Nami would never kill Usopp!
"The Worst Man in the Eastern Seas!
Fishman Pirate Arlong!"
We're friends!
"Witch of Cocoyashi Village!
Arlong's Female Leader"
Who're friends, Luffy?
You have as horrible
a reputation as ever.
Don't make me laugh.
You're just a pathetic bunch of
people cooperating with each other.
That's fine. I am a pirate!
But Arlong's a reasonable guy.
W-What the hell...
are you guys doing?!
Just a little more until our agreement.
What do you mean?
We're here to get Nami.
Now I see...
No matter what, I'm going
to earn 100 million Berries
Yeah, that'd hit you hard.
and buy this village!
Oh, yeah. Where are Usopp and Johnny?
To think that someone
really showed up for her...
Usopp! T-That's right!
There's no time to be
loafing around here!
"Usopp Dead?! When is Luffy
Going to Make Landfall?"
Friends, huh?
What's this guy saying?
What's wrong?!
The most painful word for her...
That bastard's been caught by Arlong!
We gotta hurry before he's killed!
--He was killed!
--What?!
Let go.
The weather's so great!
So that's how Nami pretended
to kill me and let me escape!
Big Bro Usopp is dead!
I told you, that's mine!
Say what?! Who decided that?!
He was killed!
Is the Grand Line far,
far away that way?!
Go! To Arlong Park!
It looks to me like there's a reason
she's in a fishman pirate group!
I took it myself and put it on my
own plate, so of course it's mine!
By Big Sis Nami!
Or is it maybe this way?!
Please, don't get any more
involved with this village.
Oh. Really? Then you should've said so!
That way?! This way?!
Leave Nami alone.
I'll explain the circumstances.
This is so exciting!
You're annoying. Sit still, will ya?
--I'll pass.
--H-Hey!
I don't care about her past.
Sorry! Sorry!
--Where are you going, Luffy?!
--For a walk.
Hang on, Nami!
And I was saving that for last, too!
"Everyone's Gathered!
Usopp Speaks the Truth About Nami"
But we finally have a cook,
so now we just need to get Nami back
Okay, I'm sorry! You can have this!
Who's he?
You know I can't eat that!
I'm not a dog, you know!
and then we're finally
going into the Grand Line!
Are you serious?!
Nami-san, huh?
"Untold Past! Female Warrior Bellemere!"
Yeah. It's terrible!
She was a witch all along!
Just remembering her beautiful
visage makes me happy!
Quiet!
She's been winning Arlong's favor
How I can't wait to see her again!
Something's down there...
so she could have the treasure buried
in Cocoyashi Village all to herself!
What a shock!
Let go! Let go, I said!
I guess we really did see a
ship fall from the sky, huh?
She'll calmly kill people for it, too!
She's scum, rotten to the core!
Hey, Yosaku. We're almost
to where Nami is, right?
It's big...
Have they still not caught
that Long-nose yet?!
It seems some unordinary humans
have stepped foot on this island.
She had us all fooled the entire--
You guys're soft-minded!
Too soft-minded! Don't you get it?!
You!
Try saying that again! I'll kick your ass!
Who could it be? And why?
Minute by minute, we're heading
right for the infamous Arlong!
A mere, lowly human,
defying our species!
What's that?
Stop, Luffy. This has
nothing to do with Johnny.
Look! Who's that?!
If you don't wanna
believe me, then don't!
A sea monster!
He's not from this island!
But I saw it with my own two eyes!
We're returning to Arlong Park!
She killed Big Bro Usopp--
Big Sis's eyes were glued to
Arlong's picture when she saw it!
Quit spouting nonsense!
Nami would never kill Usopp!
It's a cow! It's huge!
A cow? They don't swim. It's a hippo.
We're friends!
She wasn't her normal self!
Oh? So those are fishmen?
B-But, I...
What's something like this
doing in the East Blue?!
This is a Grand Line creature!
Who're friends, Luffy?
Nami!
Damn! I can't lose 'em!
Big Sis Nami plans to take down Arlong
Why are you here?
Huh? What's this guy doing?
What're you talking about?
You're our friend! We came to get you!
and collect his
20 million-Berry bounty!
W-Where is he?
She may already be inside
his compound as we speak!
--You're a big problem.
--Nami?
Who thinks Usopp-sama is too
important of a person to have die yet?!
--He's after the food!
--What?!
Friends? Don't make me laugh!
Hurry and give it to him!
He'll flip the boat over!
--Well, let's have some food!
--Yeah.
You're just a pathetic bunch of
people cooperating with each other.
Me!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Me! Me! Me! Me!
Gahh!
Damn you! You killed him!
I saw it with my own eyes!
Don't tell me you guys've
never heard of Arlong?!
Fool! What are you thinking?!
Oh, you guys think so, too? I agree!
H-Hey! Wait! You!
How dare... How dare
you kill Big Bro Usopp?!
Arlong? Who's that?
Stay away from my food!
Never heard of him.
Huh? You called?
So what? Why not kill me
as revenge, then?
You did it! You're incredible,
Big Bro Luffy!
W-Who are you?!
What are you doing on this island?!
What?!
What does it matter to you?
W-What?
Looks like you made it mad!
Alright, listen up! I guess I'll just
have to fill you in about everything!
I'll tell you this much.
--Another one, huh?!
--You dumbass!
Y-Yeah. You have a point.
Right now, Arlong wants to kill
Roronoa Zoro and his men.
Special Attack: Egg Star!
Don't beat up someone
who's hungry for no reason!
Arlong is a fishman who used to
rampage throughout the Grand Line!
I'm Luffy. I'm taking a walk.
Because Zoro just had to be stupid.
He's probably hurt or something
and can't catch his own food.
--Rotten eggs!
--I can't breathe!
No matter how monstrously
strong you guys are,
Fishman?
A walk?!
A fishman, huh? I haven't met one yet.
Right?
Have fun!
you're no match for real monsters.
What love...
Say, I hear the mermaids on
Fishman Island in the Grand Line
Howdya like that?! I guess fishmen
aren't all they're cracked up to be!
Here, eat up. No need to hold back.
If you hang around this island,
you will wind up being killed.
are absolutely beautiful!
You! Where are you headed?
Looks like every one of 'em
let Captain Usopp escape!
Heck if I know!
Are fishmen...
Not that it matters to me, though.
...like this?
He seems like a funny guy!
Y-Yikes. I somehow
wound up at a shore!
--That's a masterpiece!
--Can't you guys stay focused?!
Just who is he?
Her cool look is so enchanting, too!
Die, you damn thing!
He walked right by us,
with no fear whatsoever.
Alright, then. I'll explain
from the very beginning.
--I heard his voice over here!
--Let's check it out!
Hi, Nami-san! It's me!
Do you remember me?!
He's a mysterious guy.
Let's set sail together!
What're you doing?!
What happened to that love?!
The reason the Grand Line's called
a pirate graveyard in the first place
Shut up, you!
You're just complicating things!
The bastard just tried to eat me, too.
No one here.
Was it just our imagination?
is because of the three
powers that reign over it.
Say what?! Love is always a hurricane!
The guy's quick to run away,
that's for sure!
Bellemere?
And this person raised you and Nami?
One of which is the
Seven Warlords of the Sea!
Let's look somewhere else!
Hey! Listen when people are talking!
Yeah, that's right.
Where's Usopp?
Here he comes!
He's gonna sink the boat!
How should I start to explain
about Bellemere-san?
Bottom of the ocean.
--That jerk!
--Get back. I'll do it.
Damn it! Cut the crap!
Seven Warlords?
Whew...
Simply put, they're
government-authorized pirates.
I-I don't know!
A swordsman would even
strike a lady, Roronoa Zoro?
What? Why would pirates
get a government's approval?
Collier Shoot!
It's not in your best interest to lie.
What?! You don't even know
what's going on here! Back off!
I fell asleep?
By paying the government a cut
of the loot they take from pirates,
Damn hippo...
Huh? Nojiko?
I guess I'd be irritated too,
coming right off an insulting defeat.
Where could she have gone?
the Seven Warlords
are allowed to exist!
Huh?!
Alright! Back to food!
Hey! Watch that mouth of yours!
In other pirates' eyes, they're
no more than "government dogs,"
Oww...
That was good exercise.
Mind your own business,
you damn bastard!
These guys are crazy...
Huh? What?
but they're strong!
Just a little more, Bellemere-san.
Bros! This is no time for
you two to be going at it!
Thanks for your cheering!
As you can see, I'm perfectly okay!
That's right!
Just a little more,
and everything will return!
If you're going to fight,
could you do it off the island?!
Even Hawk-Eye Mihawk, the guy
Big Bro Zoro lost to, is a Warlord!
Cocoyashi Village,
Don't butt any more into this
land's affairs, you outsiders!
the tangerine orchard,
and even my dream!
Maybe a little too okay?
W-Where am I?
Do you still not get it?
That's awesome!
There's seven of those guys?!
My house.
The one and only reason I got
close to you was for the money!
Yeah...
--You awake?
--W-Who are you?!
The Seven Warlords are awesome!
What's taking so long?!
Now that you're flat broke,
you have no charm whatsoever!
So, one of the Seven Warlords
is Jimbei, a fishman pirate boss.
I'm Nojiko. I grow tangerines here.
It took eight years...
That's right! You thwacked me!
When is Luffy gonna show up?!
You can have your ship back,
so just go find a navigator somewhere
and go into the Grand Line!
And the fishman Arlong is
a pirate right on par with him
Five more minutes
and I'm gonna die of boredom!
Just when I was trying
to save you, too!
Go look for your One Piece or whatever!
Ohh! Oh!
who used to commit atrocity
after atrocity in the Grand Line!
I'm the one who saved you.
Oh! Incredible!
Just get the hell out of here!
You're an eyesore!
All done...
Had you done anything to that fishman,
Not even Hatchan, major octopus
leader of the Arlong Pirates,
All done!
Like this?
there's no question
you would've been killed.
That's just your last picture standing up!
can pull you up!
Goodbye.
This is why I hate outsiders!
You're a super-grade fish!
Arlong has rule over 20 towns
since coming to the East Blue!
Nami...
Dunno who you are, but you're
the gutsiest fish in the East Blue!
But you're a kid from Gosa, right?
Now I just need to check that book...
His strength is
far superior to Don Krieg's!
Surely you know all too well
from firsthand experience
What the... Oh! It was me all along?
that you'll be killed if
you mess with the fishmen.
But why would Nami-san
go to this guy all by herself?
Big Bro Luffy?!
I know!
You're indeed the gutsiest
fish in the East Blue, me.
--I'm going to sleep.
--Sleep?!
I know, but... they killed my daddy!
I told you, she's after
the bounty on his head!
In this situation?! And right
in the middle of the road?!
Wait, does that seem strange?
No, who knows? Maybe Nami-san
is actually a mermaid!
I don't plan on leaving the island,
Oh! Nacchan!
They stole everything,
destroyed our town,
Sure does.
and I'm not interested in
what's happening on the island.
What's wrong?
and killed tons of people!
Especially given how lovely she is!
W-Who are you?!
Nothing! Nothing at all!
They have to pay!
No matter what, they have to pay!
And I'm a little sleepy.
"Nami"
Like this?!
Me? I'm Hatchan! Call me Hachi!
--I'm going to sleep.
--Huh?!
I'll kill you!
So I went to Arlong Park!
But a girl on his side got in the way!
B-Big Bro...
Do you guys even understand
what I've told you?!
You a fishman, too?
Yeah, there's a strong
fishman, right? We get it!
Of course, of course!
I'm a fascinating octopus fishman!
No, you don't get it! You don't
know how strong fishmen are!
She... was like a witch!
From the looks of it, you're a human?
Oh, my!
Y-Yeah.
I hate this! I don't care if I die;
I'm going to avenge my daddy!
A marine? Or maybe a guest?
Damn it, Nami! Not again!
We'll find out when we
get there. Quit worrying.
Fine...
Guest?
Fine, whatever!
Go ahead and die!
Then die.
Anyways, let's have some food.
--Oh? Did it again, Nacchan?
--Let go!
I guess you could say I'm a guest.
Na--
--You just never learn!
--I'm not a cat!
If you're prepared to die,
then go get your revenge!
Yeah! Food!
Arlong-san's not here right now, is he?
Eh? Food?
Nope. Where'd he go?
But know this much.
You idiot!
What do you want?
Apparently, there's a long-nosed
outsider running all over the place.
--Hurry! Hurry!
--What's the big deal?!
How many times do I have to
tell you stealing is wrong?!
Now that me and that witch
at Arlong Park have stopped you,
Meat things with bones in it!
Bleh!
It's the navy! The navy's here!
I want sautéed bean sprouts!
It's not my fault we're poor!
you've escaped death twice now!
Some survivors from Gosa managed
to contact the government!
Alright! Leave it to me!
He locked up his friend here
Cheapskate!
and went to Cocoyashi Village
to get this other guy.
I'll be done in no time!
Leave when you're done with your tea.
The navy's come here to pick us up!
Bellemere!
Meat and bean sprouts...
Hey! Isn't that being
a little harsh on the kid?!
Usopp, huh?
Bellemere! Your no-good
cat's been at it again!
--Having a cook really is great!
--Y-Yeah!
See?
Guess I'll save him for now.
Kid or not, if someone wants to die,
then just let 'em die!
We're saved!
Meat! A jumbo serving of meat!
This Cocoyashi Village...
And bean sprouts for me!
A jumbo serving!
We can finally escape this island!
He doesn't have the guts to live
through hard times anyway!
Whadya want? You're annoying!
--How do I get there?
--Get in.
Say what?!
Oh! Welcome home, Nami!
I know a kid who's staring
fixedly at the distant future
You're a guest.
I'll take you there, swordsman!
I'm back!
So that's the infamous Arlong Park...
Look! This is the umpteenth time!
while she endures a life
more painful than death.
The world's on its last legs if
pirates can settle down so blatantly.
She's even famous in the village now!
That's why I hate people like him
who consider death right off the bat!
So?
Listen, men!
Surely even you've
shoplifted before, Gen-san?
Our mission today is to
successfully extract from the island
This is why she acts this way!
the survivors of the town of Gosa,
I'm back here again...
What... should I do?
I'm just kidding!
which was destroyed
by the Arlong Pirates!
--Alright. You paid for her, right?
--B-Bellemere...
W-What the hell happened?!
My... hometown...
I hate this! I'll endure it!
What should I do?!
But I am left to wonder...
What happened here...
Thanks so much.
I don't have money right now.
Would our brand of justice
allow us to overlook the castle
I'll pay you later...
What about your mom?
...my brothers?!
of this unchecked pirate?!
...with my body.
She's alive...
It would not!
D-Don't be s-saying
things like that!
Roronoa...
Our unit will now annihilate
Arlong and his men!
She's worried about you. Go back to her.
What? What are you trying to say?!
Look at you blush!
Prepare for battle at once!
All right. Here is this
month's amount. Accept it.
Roronoa Zoro...
Okay...
Yes, sir!
Navy Branch ♪77?
What?!
The pirate hunter?!
Did he come to collect my head?!
Arlong-kun.
Yes. That's what it said.
Oh? And why are you laughing?
You're on a completely different level
of intellect than ordinary pirates.
A newcomer.
Someone go there and negotiate
with the head honcho.
You truly know how
to get ahead in the world.
N-No, he didn't come... T-That guy...
If two million isn't enough to keep
them from trying anything funny,
Try that again and
you'll get 100 spankings!
You're actually a nice person!
Even though you have tattoos...
I'm sorry!
--He was Zoro!
--What?!
Likewise!
get rid of 'em!
But I really wanted this book!
Befriending me means you can
milk the East Blue all you want!
Prejudice!
That haramaki guy
we caught was Roronoa...
I don't know anything
about you, you know...
If you wanted it,
why didn't you just tell me?
They're suddenly opening fire!
Oh, right!
For a navy colonel,
you're wise to realize that!
Arlong-san! Look out!
My name is Captain Usopp!
I'm looking for a girl named Nami...
Because you wouldn't
buy it for me anyway...
Thanks as always.
Of course I would!
I caught him, Arlong-san!
Nami?!
We do have some
money stashed away.
You know her?
Now you say that?
W-What in the world?!
But the villagers said the
climate's been so good lately
A good world is one in
which money flows well!
Took you long enough, Choo.
--H-He crunched a cannonball!
--What terrifying jaws and teeth!
What?! Nami's a leader
of the Arlong Pirates?!
that you can get tons of
tangerines from any old field,
Money is good. You can
trust it more than anything.
D-Don't tell me Zoro--
and our tangerines won't sell good
'cause they don't go up in value.
Yep. She's infamous in this area.
Wouldn't you agree?
They can mind their own business!
Well, here we are!
I-Indeed...
Even that little boy said
she seemed like a witch.
I hate humans, but good sports
like you are an exception.
Arlong-san. The negotiations?
You're so dumb, Nami!
I would've stolen it way better!
Even more surprising, that witch
grew up in this very house!
Cocoyashi Village.
Canceled.
Arlong-san should be here.
Well, I should be going...
--Alright! Let's go!
--Time to fight!
I said no stealing!
Great. Thanks.
It'll be a navy bloodbath!
Come drink with us sometime!
Let's have fun!
No problem! Bye, now!
I was just joking!
Me and Nami are adopted sisters.
That hurts!
It's not good for a navy ship on patrol
to be stopped at a pirate island.
Not so fast, guys.
Whoops! I just remembered,
I forgot to ask your name!
There's no need to expend so much
energy just to take out the trash.
I'll kill anyone for you
who tells headquarters.
Huh? Me? What are you
asking my name again for?
But you know,
there's one thing for sure!
So this is...
The maps you draw are
really amazing, Nami!
No, I'll be leaving.
It's Hatchan!
We'll go!
...Nami's house?!
Come back again!
Hey! The colonel's heading back!
Take him to his ship!
What foolish humans they are to pick
a fight with us in these waters.
Me and Nami are both orphans.
First you learned how to draw
sea charts, and now land maps!
Strange guy.
We were brought up in this house.
Right!
Three of our leaders'll
make for a grand fight!
Our foster parent is dead, too,
This is a map of this island, isn't it?!
Get in the octopus pot!
I'll take you there!
but the three of us used to live
happily here in Cocoyashi Village.
That ship won't last even three minutes!
No one would ever think
such a little kid drew this!
Right. Thanks.
Catching this scum isn't
enough to satisfy my hunger!
But you always have such a funny face!
That's odd...
I'm studying navigation too now!
Then... Nami betrayed her own
parent and fellow villagers
It looks just like a rat's!
Commodore! The cannonball
appears to have been a dud!
Y-Yeah, huh?! So you should let me go!
Hey! Hachi! Watch your mouth!
The colonel is a valued guest!
Fire another! This is a
signal of open hostility!
Navigation, too?!
and joined Arlong's group?!
I was just saying hello earlier!
T-That's how we do it in my village!
It is Nami's dream!
We're dealing with fishmen!
Don't let your guard down, men!
Yeah, pretty much. A real witch, huh?
Yeah!
Oh, right! Sorry!
Yes, sir!
I'm gonna use my navigation skills
to travel to all the world's oceans!
No, it's all right.
Damn it! So that's the deal?!
But you are one of Zoro's men.
And then I'm gonna make a
world map of everything I see!
He's been hit!
It's one of Arlong's men!
So she had us fooled the entire time!
Get him! Commence attack!
Stop! Remain calm!
Okay! Here we go!
She was after treasure
from the very start!
Though, it's only natural for famous
bounty hunters to come after me.
So your map of this island is your
first step toward your dream, then?
You damn fishmen. You're creepy as hell.
One of Arlong's men, yes?
Even after she helped
fight to protect my village
I am Commodore Purinpurin
of Navy Branch ♪77.
But you're great as pay dirt!
and smiled so happily aboard our ship!
Yeah!
Don't kill me! I don't have
anything to do with Zoro!
A map of the world, huh?
We are a somewhat
well-known elite naval unit!
Oh? Happily?
Nami! Someday, you will
make your dream come true!
Her?
If you do not wish for death,
I suggest you dutifully surrender--
Enough of your poor lies.
You stood up to Arlong-san, too.
We came here to
bring her back with us,
I just know it!
Doesn't look like you're
going to live either way.
but I guess there's no need for--
Commodore!
--How dare you?!
--Kill him!
H-Hey! As a matter of fact,
Zoro and I are really close!
W-What's this shock?!
Hey, you! Out of the way!
Hey, Bellemere-san.
Don't tell me there's
fishmen under the ship?!
That reminds me, a friend
of ours was unlucky enough
I'm here to kill Arlong!
You haven't been eating meals lately...
So just try and lay a finger on me!
Zoro won't stand by quietly!
to be caught by the fishmen...
Arlong killed my daddy!
I've been eating tangerines,
though. I'm on a diet!
I'm sorry to bother you like this,
Oh? Which means if I kill you,
Zoro will come back?
This is bad... I wonder
how the guy's holding up...
I don't need any meals, either...
Move, or I'll kill you, too!
but we just took the liberty
of removing your ship's rudder.
What're you taking interest in guys for?
N-No, you're wrong!
Kids need to eat right!
Hey!
Well? Now do you see?
--W-What?!
--Commodore! Are you all right?!
Killing me'd be very bad!
If you keep me alive, Zoro'll show up!
You keep lying!
I was only using you guys
from the very start.
You don't have any food because
we don't have any money!
Don't worry.
I didn't hit any vital spots.
Arlong doesn't have time to
bother with little brats like you!
But if you don't keep me alive,
Zoro won't come!
You had some decent skill, and you
were good suckers worth using.
For reals?!
--You're suffering, so that we can...
--Diet!
This is just hypothetical, Commodore,
But how exactly did Zoro...
Now go home!
You shouldn't underestimate
the beautifying power of tangerines!
So you had them completely fooled!
but if one were to move a large reef
directly into a strong current,
...escape from our prison?
Use that to at least keep yourself safe.
What do you mean?
This girl's like a cold-blooded witch--
They're the reason I still have
such lustrous skin at the age of 30!
What I mean is, someone let him escape.
what do you suppose
would happen to the ocean?
What?!
Darn it!
she'll even forget about her
own parent's death for money!
Arlong-san. Does this
sound plausible to you?
But your hands are yellow.
Just shut up and eat!
Just chalk it up to bad luck
that you crossed her and give up.
Perhaps Nami let Zoro infiltrate
this place so he could take your head?
M-Moving a reef?!
That can't possibly be done!
Here you are, Nami! All done!
I see.
Oh! You're back, Nami!
That was a long trip!
A super custom-made
Bellemere brand!
Alright! Right around there, Hachi!
N-Now that you mention it,
Nami has been acting strange lately.
Though it's not like I ever
trusted her to begin with.
Right!
Another hand-me-down from Nojiko?
Well? How was your haul this time?
C-Commodore!
Yeah. She even helped Zoro
when he jumped into the water.
Here we go!
It looks great on you, Nami!
A giant whirlpool has
suddenly appeared ahead!
Couldn't have gone better!
I earned a ton!
Even if she were a homicidal maniac,
I wouldn't be too surprised.
The rudder's not working!
Don't tell me she was working
with Zoro from the very start...
I found so many suckers who are
fooled so easily! As you can see!
What?!
This lion used to be a sunflower!
I told you. We removed the rudder.
In that case, could you get the hell
out of here?! You're an eyesore!
...and tricked us all?!
It can't be helped!
You're two years younger
than me, you know!
This rudderless ship is now headed...
Betrayal is her specialty.
Betrayal is your forte!
Age has nothing to do with it!
I want new clothes too!
I guess.
That's enough of that!
...into the depths of the sea.
Hey! Brothers! Our friend
has returned! Prepare a party!
Mine are old clothes too, you know!
You get my stuff 'cause
you're my baby sister! Blehh!
--It's Nami!
--Nami's back!
Quit discussing stuff based
on a bunch of conjecture!
But I'm not your real sister!
What happened?! Why'd he
suddenly jump into the water?!
We're not related by blood!
Nami...
Is someone pulling
some kinda lame joke?
Nami!
No, it's not like he slipped or anything...
Then he ran away!
No, his arms and legs're tied!
He can't swim like that!
This can't be happening...
It's a suicide!
This is reality.
Bellemere-san!
Leave him be.
There's no way we can escape
from Arlong's control.
So what if you're not
related by blood?!
Watch what you say!
Me, a traitor?
Never say anything
stupid like that again!
I swore I was a member of this group
eight years ago, with this tattoo!
W-Whatever...
You're not our real mother, either!
You'd be better off
without us, wouldn't you?!
W-W-We're finally here! Arlong Park!
Can't believe he'd kill himself...
Sorry to make you work so hard!
Sorry, sorry.
He was terrifyingly good at giving up!
Not at all. We know
everything about these waters,
Nami. It's only natural
for you to be upset.
That way, you could eat,
It's like, damn, value your life more!
from the winds to the
depths. It was a cinch.
buy all the clothes
you want, and be free!
But rest easy.
I don't suspect you one bit.
So this is the hideout
of the fishman Arlong,
With our top skills, we have
no one to fear in these seas!
who came from the Grand Line?!
I wish...
T-That idiot!
I wish someone richer
had adopted me instead!
You and me've known each
other for eight years now!
And let's not forget Nami's sea charts.
Is Nami really here?!
I moved the reef after checking that!
We were just a little on edge is all.
Big Sis Nami was on the Going Merry,
It even tells the flow of
the currents and everything!
Right, Nami?
Those are some excellent
charts, all right!
so let's first see if it's
stopped on this island or not!
The ones we do need to get rid of
are Roronoa Zoro and his group!
If we have Nami draw up charts
of all the world's oceans,
I-Is that so?
G-Good idea!
we'll be the eternal kings of the sea!
H-Hey, Nami! S-Say something!
--He's back up!
--Hey! What's going on, Nami?!
Fine, then! Do whatever!
If you hate this house that much,
then go leave for somewhere else!
Nami!
Nami's definitely vital to have for
the creation of the Arlong Empire!
We're busting in.
What do you think you're doing?!
Stop it, you two!
W-Why are we suddenly doing that?!
Zoro just had to go and do that...
--It's a real shame!
--A shame?
I will leave!
No, what do you think you're doing?!
Are you stupid?!
We haven't even found any clues yet!
He promised to let Nami
and Cocoyashi Village go
Nami!
What's wrong, Nami?
Nami!!
once she saves up 100 million Berries.
We're dealing with
those fishmen, you know!
You're just a small fry who
can't even watch one guy die...
We gotta have a strategy first!
For reals, Arlong-san?!
You seem a little pale.
You're really going to let Nami go?!
Forget that tedious stuff.
Luffy told me to bring her back.
Quit tryin' to act cool!
For reals, for reals?! That's a big waste!
But, as for Long-nose here...
Save me sooner next time, you idiot!
I thought I was gonna die!
It can't be helped.
...not even you can save him now.
I'm gonna do just that,
no matter who we're dealing with!
That's what we agreed
to eight years ago.
Screw you!
Not good...
Not after he's defied Arlong-san.
I'm a man who'd die to keep
my money-related promises.
Mess with me any more
and you will die!
Let's go!
How long...
I wonder.
How long are you going to suspect me?!
That's a lot of bandages you have.
You're too smart, you see.
Hey, Big Bro Zoro!
What on earth are you thinking?!
Didn't have a change of clothes,
so I used these instead.
There it is! I found it!
I'll have the amount
Arlong and I agreed to soon!
It's the Going Merry! It's over there!
Arlong is out to kill us!
Why would I betray you now?!
So Big Sis Nami is here!
So why aren't we running away?!
Agreed amount?!
Now that we know
what Nami's really like,
I know.
Hey, you!
What's the big idea?! Untie me!
Bellemere-san...
there should be no reason
at all to stay on this island!
You agreed eight years ago to buy
Cocoyashi Village from Arlong-san
The three of us are a family!
Hey, Nami.
What should we do with him?
A reason for staying on
this island? There is one.
We're farther east of Arlong Park...
Cocoyashi Village.
I'm sure Nami feels the same way!
for 100 million Berries.
Lock him up! I'll deal with him myself!
He's staying here.
She didn't mean what she said!
But it's strange. Why's the ship
stopped so far from the village?
But I just can't make sense of it.
Arlong-san! Arlong-san!
Don't tell us you're still gonna try
to get her back too, Big Bro Zoro!
You betrayed the villagers
and your parent,
Untie me!
What is it, brother?
and only trust money,
I have nothing to do with it.
You've been hurt so bad
you're nearly dead!
I'm sorry! That guy had a long-nosed
friend with him, but he got away!
He decides who we have as navigator.
You're a strong person, Nojiko.
so why do you care so much
about Cocoyashi Village?
That was real immature of me.
Just take it easy!
Why such a puny little village?
Big Bro...
Could you go bring Nami back for me?
Just leave this all to me!
Actually, I found this... in your room.
What the hell, Usopp?!
You wound up getting spotted anyway?!
I'll have a super delicious
supper ready before you get back!
A-All right! Understood!
I think he might've escaped
into Cocoyashi Village...
Okay!
I am so going to chop him up someday!
It was a short reunion,
but our role as guides ends here!
I'll bring the girl back!
T-That's my...
Cocoyashi Village, huh?
Same for me! I don't wanna
deliberately wind up killed!
Perfect. I have other
business there, too.
You're in high spirits, now that
you know she's not in Arlong Park...
S-Say what?! Usopp's been captured?!
Yeah. Take care.
Guess I'll head out for a bit.
Yeah! They took him to
Arlong Park a little while ago!
Right rudder, full!
Pull the boat up to the Going Merry!
Well, until we meet again!
Stay well, you guys!
Okay, Miss! I'll lower it to this much!
Brave as he was,
that youngster defied Arlong!
You, too!
Right!
Eh? Lower it a little more!
He's surely dead by now!
All right! I hereby title
this brave image of me
Right over here!
Low prices! Low prices!
Hey! Arlong's coming!
about to tread unknown soil,
"Captain Usopp's Grand Adventure"!
Damn.
It wouldn't hurt to buy any of
these fresh fruits lined up here!
What?! What for?! We just
paid our tribute money to him!
Of all times to get caught, it had
to be after I killed some time there!
It's probably about the
weapons of mine they found...
Usopp! Stay alive!
Return to your houses, everyone.
Gen-san...
So, coming here from the outskirts
of the village is "running away"?
Are you alright?!
They're here!
There! There!
That's sure nice and convenient!
Fishmen!
--Full speed ahead!
--Right!
Here. Drink up before it gets cold!
Is this a treasure map?
--Hey.
--Yeah?
Why did you just pass by it?!
It seems to be pointing
to Cocoyashi Village...
Why do you suppose
Nami-san was crying?
Bellemere-san would be
happier if we were gone.
So you're the bastard who
was in possession of weapons...
She was crying?
--Treasure in Cocoyashi Village?!
--Really?!
Did you see that?!
There were fishmen there!
Why do you think that?
Inside her heart.
Yes. That's right...
They're Arlong's crew! They're scary!
Somethin' wrong with that?!
That's my own personal map!
It has nothing to do with you at all!
Having two children
costs lots of money...
Because I've always
enjoyed looking at weapons.
You sure they weren't tears
of grief for killing Usopp?
Don't you snap at me!
And everyone in the village
hates her, because of me...
I guess this whole area is
seriously under Arlong's control!
Oh! What's wrong?
You suddenly look so furious...
Are collections not allowed
under your rule, either?
Yeah, right. Are you serious?
You're old enough to
consider others now, huh?
What now?
No, I can't have that.
Do you honestly believe
Nami-san killed Long-nose?
Alright! We'll just say we
couldn't bring Nami back!
What is this?!
Don't worry.
Weapons breed nothing
but evil thoughts and violence.
She was a famous brat in this
village when she was your age, too.
Untie me, you idiots!
What in the world happened here?!
They're the chief things
that undermine peace.
Bellemere-san was?!
--Never seen that boat before.
--It's suspicious.
It's the work of Roronoa Zoro,
the pirate hunter!
Even now, she's still quite
a brat in the villagers' eyes!
He's huge! That's Arlong?!
H-He's not human!
But where were you, Hachi?!
How shocked the village was
when that brat suddenly said
--Escape!
--Agreed!
When she did that...!
This could've been prevented,
had you been here!
--Nope. Because he's a fishman.
--Yeah...
Hold it, you two!
Of course it could've!
Had I only been here!
she was going to be a marine...
It's for my business!
I control 20 towns and villages.
A marine?!
Bellemere-san was a marine?!
Bye!
This is unforgivable!
As their manager,
I can't afford to have rebellions.
This was my only choice!
Hey! At least untie me!
Yeah.
Meaning you don't know
where Zoro disappeared to?
When she did that,
I destroyed the great port town
of Gosa as an example
Nami stabbed her own hand to
make it look like she stabbed me!
to the other communities!
Well, all I saw was one
slightly suspicious swordsman
The blunder of being
unable to pay tribute money
Huh? It's just him?
Pirates have to pay for
slaughtering innocent people...
Were you banished from
somewhere or somethin'?
is an act of rebellion against us!
If Nami hadn't done that for me,
Arlong would've killed me for sure!
whom I'd never met before...
I-I guess...
Hey! Tribute money?
With those words, she left the village.
I'm gonna kill those guys!
Exactly as it sounds.
It's money that we offer to them.
Ah! So you got these injuries
from being tortured!
What now?! Manly Usopp can't
just turn tail after being saved!
It was him?!
Alright! Let's take him
back to Arlong-san for now!
We buy our lives
every month with money.
You did see him, you idiot!
For now, I gotta hurry and find Zoro!
Forgive us, Zoro! I'll tell Luffy
you were a truly brave man!
Adults and kids...
She says she felt her time
to die had finally come...
So, where did Zoro go?!
If anyone in a village can't
pay the tribute money...
He wanted to see Arlong-san,
so I just took him to Cocoyashi Village!
What an unlucky person!
I'll never forget about you, Big Bro!
Is that... Zoro?!
If there's even just one person...
Oh, well...
It is! Yes!
...the village gets
wiped out just like Gosa.
All right, then!
Let's get on dry land for now!
Nami didn't kill him. Is that
what you're tryin' to say?
Right!
Meaning there's no reason
to rush out in a hurry.
Then that huge town was destroyed
just because of one person?!
Am I wrong?
I wonder.
That's how Arlong governs.
I did make her out to be a small fry
who can't even watch a guy die.
He's looking for me, too.
They're species-obsessed and don't
give a damn about killing people.
He said he was a guest
of yours, you see.
There should be a town
called Gosa up here!
She might've done it out of frustration.
Listen. You lowly humans simply need
to keep paying up without thinking!
Whadya mean, "small fry"?!
And I didn't think you'd be
back so soon, Arlong-san...
What's so small about
Nami-san's chest?!
Is that all you can think--
Zoro, huh?!
I need enormous funds!
Your baby sister?
Which means, if I can just
buy me a little more time...
Your tribute money will
eventually become the cornerstone
He's alive!
No, I think he's dead now...
No. I don't know who she is.
of the Arlong Empire,
which will rule the East Blue!
W-What happened to this town?!
Why are you getting in the way?!
Usopp!
I heard Arlong ravaged it
a few weeks back, but...
Everything's so close to working out!
A-Arlong Empire?!
Did Nami do this to you?!
Sorry. Me and him did that.
They're planning to turn the entire
East Blue into a fishman empire?!
A-All the houses have been flipped over!
You did it!
So close!
You have no idea
how that makes me feel...
L-Luffy! You're here?!
I hear fishmen generally have
ten times the strength of humans!
Yeah. Just got here.
Oh, I came too!
Good to work with you!
Someday I'm gonna kill you!
In short, could this be how strong
people from the Grand Line are?!
--Oh! You're pretty alright after all!
--Shut up!
D-Damn you! You picking a fight?!
Speaking of which,
we heard Nami killed you.
You're getting in the way!
You're the one to blame!
--Eh?!
--That damn Johnny!
And that was you, Nami.
He was talking nonsense after all!
This is what you get
for messing with Arlong!
But how'd even the street get like this?
No... In a way, it's not a lie...
When she saw you, Bellemere
mustered up the will to live again.
Nami! You really disappoint me!
That was the doing
of a monster called Momoo.
But it's actually the opposite!
Nami saved my life!
Even after you stole
our ship and ran off,
Monster?
Hurry and escape.
Before Arlong comes back.
This place even has monsters?
Luffy didn't suspect you one bit!
We brought him from the Grand Line.
Even now, he completely trusts you!
How can you trick someone like
that with such an uncaring look?!
From the Grand Line, huh?
It is a boat! I knew it!
"We"?
The only thing I trust is money.
Those who get fooled are the fools!
On a stormy night like tonight?!
Who on earth could it be?!
You're with that guy who
got banished, aren't you?!
Say what?!
Bye!
Everything was
supposed to go smoothly.
Gen-san!
Get back here!
Escaped by a hair...
The possession of weapons
is a clear sign of rebellion!
You guys are going to make my
eight years of business meaningless.
Doctor! Call the doctor!
Please stay safe, Big Bro Usopp!
To keep any more rebels
like you from showing up,
You really know how to trash a place.
I'm going to wait here for
Yosaku and Big Bro Luffy!
I'm going to kill you right now,
as an example to the other humans!
Bellemere? Is that you, Bellemere?!
So the least I can do is
get rid of you by my own hand!
What's wrong, Nami?
--Bellemere!
--What is this?!
Nothing. I'm just here to rest a little.
As if a fishman can possibly
catch me on dry land!
No way! He'll kill someone
just for having a weapon?!
Seems you've become a lot more
pirate-like since you were last here!
I'm used to this!
Just try and catch up to me!
Breaking glass and furniture
just to rest is a bit much.
--Who are these children?!
--Doctor! They have terrible fevers!
--He has no right...
--H-H-Hey, you!
They've been completely
worn out by the storm!
Get rid of?
What?!
You have no right to do this, Arlong!
W-What the...
You, get rid of me?!
Don't make me laugh!
You have that treasure map open
even though nothing's wrong?
Alright! But we need to tend to
those nasty wounds of yours, too!
I found you, fishman!
I wouldn't underestimate
me if I were you.
You killed my daddy!
And I'm gonna kill you!
Something happened to
make me mad, that's all!
For these past eight years straight,
we've paid you your tribute money!
Just hurry!
Please! Don't let them die!
Save those kids' lives!
Dammit...
Them, huh? Who are they?
Why would we want
to rebel now, of all times?!
If I stay here, I'm dead for sure!
You met them?!
Don't mess with the fishmen!
I beg of you!
Yeah. Some Captain
Something-or-Other.
Take your hands off Gen-san!
Special Attack!
Have you forgotten?!
Everyone here in Gosa
He seemed kind of liar-ish, though.
was slaughtered because just
one villager defied them!
Yeah!
It's not like he used any weapons!
Smoke Star!
I hear you smiled happily when
you were traveling with them.
What did you just say, girl ruffian?!
--Stop this!
--Let Gen-san go!
Bastard used a smoke bomb!
I'm going to be these kids' parent.
That's what I said.
Huh? You look like a fishman,
but you're human. Just barely.
Surround him! Don't let him escape!
I'm saying that the possession of
weapons indicates the will to rebel.
Even though I haven't
seen you like that in years.
You can't!
Now's my chance!
Just barely?!
Don't do it! A punk like you
can't possibly raise children!
Or what? Shall the entire
village be destroyed?
Where are you?! Over there?!
Talk to me! Who are those guys?
This is just like
something you'd think up.
He's coming!
T-Take my advice! Give them
to a government institution!
A fishman!
If just one of you lays a hand on us,
your village will meet its demise.
Nami!
There was a real one, too?
I've already decided!
D-Don't...
We agreed you could tell me
anything, remember?
Get back! I, Captain Usopp,
will protect you!
I'm an adult now, too.
I was even in the navy.
Either way is fine with me!
I can handle one easily enough!
Get inside, everyone!
I think I'm a little
more upstanding now.
If we cause trouble now, the last
eight years will be for nothing!
I'm going to take the responsibility
of raising these kids.
I had planned to forget about them...
It's for my business!
Take this! Special Attack: Lead Star!
If you're going to fight to
the death to defy his rule,
I'm going to raise them
to be wonderful people
who won't lose to the era we live in!
then you should've done so
eight years ago instead!
This was my only choice!
I thought I had erased
them from my mind.
I'm going to live with these kids.
But we all swore to fight
the patient fight! To live!
N-Nami... How could you...
No one ever listens!
Nami and Nojiko gave me life.
Yes! I'm out!
I told you, the fishmen'll
kill us if we mess with them!
Darn it! You win all
by yourself again?!
Die like a good little boy.
Wait, hold on, Luffy!
Why do you have so many cards?!
--Gen-san!
--But...
You girls have a bond that goes
far deeper than a real family's.
I get the feeling having more is better!
What a valuable opinion!
You're a great speaker!
--What is it?!
--There was a long-nosed man!
You idiot!
Learn the rules already!
Yes! Being alive is enjoyable!
Even for puny insects like you!
--Way to go, Nami!
--Way to get revenge!
--Where'd he go?!
--That way!
Alright! Then let's say
the one with the most wins!
Now that's why you're a
leader of the Arlong Pirates!
That way, huh?!
--Alright, it's decided!
--Quit deciding on your own!
--But the more I tried to erase them,
Hurry! We'll carry him to my house!
Nami! I thought you'd be here!
B-Big Sis Nami k-killed Big Bro Usopp!
Gen-san!
N-Nojiko!
the more I remembered...
Bellemere-san is waiting for us!
She's making a yummy supper!
Not all living things are born equal!
Oh, crap! We sprung a leak!
Hurry! Stop it!
Alright! Leave it to me!
--Damn you!
--Stop!
Okay!
That's what you wanted, right?
To die at sea...
I bet it's your favorite!
Omelets with tangerine sauce!
Don't do anything!
Quit thrashing around!
--That looks great!
--Lemme see, lemme see!
Nami. I'm sorry for doubting you.
You're our friend.
Yes!
B-But, Gen-san!
Yay! Omelets!
Friend?
If you die, it's all over!
Don't stop fighting the patient fight!
I have no friends!
How time flies...
The truth is, I once forgot
the fate I bear for a short while...
Even if I die!
Children once on the brink
of death, now so full of life...
There's only one reason
why I joined this group!
That's nice resolve!
Pay close attention, humans!
To buy Cocoyashi Village!
Watching them grow up
is like a joy for all of us!
This is what happens to those who
have even a sliver of evil thoughts!
Keep your part of the bargain!
I'll have the 100 million Berries soon!
Who do you take your friends for?!
Yeah! We won't feel happy until
we see that family of three happy!
Exploding Star!
But of course.
I'd rather cut my belly open and die
Right?!
than break a promise
concerning money.
W-What was that?!
That's the kind of man I am.
Yay! Yay!
Look! Up there!
Glad to hear it, Arlong.
You know the score.
There's someone on the roof!
Pirates, everyone!
Who the hell are you?!
She's one creepy girl.
My name is Captain Usopp,
Brave Warrior of the Sea!
Pirates are coming!
Guess that's good enough.
What a truly great
woman she's become!
Pirates! Everyone hide!
Him!
Momoo! Time to eat! Momoo!
A witch! She's really a witch!
I honestly felt like always being
with them, if it were possible.
T-The world fears me
and calls me Demon King Usopp,
That's strange.
He should be starving by now...
the man from the Netherworld!
If you run away now, I'll forgive you!
--I have 8,000...
--Arlong-san! That's him!
There it is! Arlong Park!
--It's the Arlong Pirates!
--Arlong?!
Where could he have gone?
That can't be!
--The guy who got away earlier!
--Eep.
What are fishmen from
the Grand Line doing here?!
Now I see...
Hey! Don't get tired, cow!
Bring all the tens of
thousands of men you want.
Was the rumor about a split in
the fishman pirate group true?!
Yeah, that'd hit you hard.
Yeah, Big Bro Sanji's kicks
must've really taken their toll!
I'll tear apart every last one!
To think that someone
really showed up for her...
Nami! Nojiko!
Gen-san!
Hey! Not that way!
To the left! That building!
He's not scared, and the
Exploding Star had no effect!
It's dangerous here!
Hide in the back woods!
You're great, Big Bro Sanji!
This is topnotch seasoning!
What has a human...
I want to make dinner for Nami-san
more than I do for you guys.
Friends, huh?
Eh? But...
Go! Now!
...a mere, lowly human... done to me?!
The most painful word for her...
I hope you manage to get
Big Sis Nami to join again!
We will! She's our navigator!
Arlong-san! Wait!
We'll lose another source
of tribute money, after Gosa!
You seem to be in excellent
spirits, pathetic humans!
So that's how Nami pretended
to kill me and let me escape!
She's going to the Grand Line with us!
As of this moment, this village--
Human settlements are easy to destroy,
but our goal is to rule them!
--That's mine!
--You just ate one!
After I've come so far...
no, this island is now
under my control!
It looks to me like there's a reason
she's in a fishman pirate group!
Let me have one, too!
--But it's mine!
--C'mon, just one!
I've endured eight whole
years since that day...
If we lose some,
we can just get some more!
Obviously.
Listen up!
--No! Give it back!
--C'mon! Let me have it!
So, what do we do?
Do we storm Arlong Park?
On this memorable day, you will
all buy your lives from me!
We are the supreme species!
Alright! As of today, this is your room!
H-Hold on! We gotta find out what
the story with Nami is first!
Your desk, your pens...
Now he's destroying the village!
Quit rockin' the damn boat!
It's no use, either way.
100,000 Berries per adult.
50,000 Berries per kid.
Everything you'll need is here!
You're going to make me
spill this fine alcohol!
No matter what you guys do,
Arlong's rule won't come to an end.
Is he--
Those who can't pay... die!
Whoa! I'm gonna die! I'm gonna die!
Nojiko!
I endured it all this time... so I had
no other choice than to do that!
--Who's she?
--Nami's big sister.
Open the gate!
--H-He's still alive! After 'im!
--Crap!
What do we do, Nojiko?
N-Nami-san's older sister?!
No wonder she's so beautiful!
We've brought someone suspicious!
We can't pay that much!
Catch him and kill him!
What do you mean it's no use?
But they might not spot our house!
Hey! Let's get back to Arlong Park!
Please, don't get any more
involved with this village.
You can't see it from the village!
He's seriously about
to destroy the village!
Leave Nami alone.
Yeah!
--I'll explain the circumstances.
--Circumstances?
Do not let him get away!
Who does he take us for?!
I'll ask again.
Just why have you come here?
You mean why she
joined Arlong's group?
How much did we get, brother?
We'll be back another day.
Looks like you're spared for now!
Yes. You'll feel like leaving
the island once you hear it.
Just over 25 million, I'd say.
I told you already-- I'm looking
for a girl! Half-fish bastard!
Excellent!
Alright. Let's hear this
reason or whatever, then.
--It's almost like we're flying!
--Not "like"!
You've got a big mouth
for a lowly human.
--I'll pass.
--H-Hey!
I'm sorry... I caused you all trouble...
Sounds like we'll hafta pay
for our lives every month
We are flying, dumbass!
I don't care about her past.
I'll excuse you this time,
but never say "half-fish" again.
W-We're falling!
at 100,000 Berries
per person from now on!
--Where are you going, Luffy?
--For a walk.
What are you talking about?
You're not at fault here!
100,000?! We can't
make a living that way!
A-A walk?! You're not
gonna listen to this?!
We fishmen are "evolved humans"
--Yeah!
--But who was that youngster earlier?
Endure it for now!
who've gained the ability
to breathe underwater.
No. I'll pass.
We should just be glad no
one in the village has died.
Those fish abilities result
in us being superior to you.
Who's he?
Everyone! It's good to see you again!
Don't mind him.
That's just how he is.
If money is all that's needed,
it's an easy price to pay.
--Nami!
--It's Nacchan!
--It's her!
As proof, we possess numerous
abilities that surpass those of humans!
We'll hear you out.
Landing successful!
I at least hope they'll leave
without noticing Bellemere's house.
Though I don't think
it's gonna change anything.
Get it through your head that
fishmen are the lord of all things!
Yo! Zoro!
Yeah! I'll listen, too!
I wanna know what's
happening on this island!
With the two children, it would
come to 200,000 Berries...
Humans defying fishmen is basically
defying the laws of nature!
What's going on? You never walk
right through the village...
I doubt she has that much saved up.
Me, too! I want to know
everything about Nami-san!
I heard a loud sound...
Alright! Time to go, brothers!
I'm sick of those ridiculous
opinions of yours, Arlong.
And now he's sleeping.
Arlong, huh?
Don't sleep right after you say that!
We made it! We made it!
Don't look so stern, Nami.
W-What the hell... are you guys doing?!
Arlong-san! There's smoke
coming from outside the village!
You may be human,
but you're an exception.
I see. This is why Nami
had such a hard time.
You're a skilled surveyor and prized
member of the Arlong Pirates!
What do you mean?
We're here to get Nami.
There's a navy ship at the shore?!
Just seven million Berries left to go...
You make truly accurate
sea charts for us!
It's Branch ♪16's ship!
Have you still not found her?
Okay!
I have far more smarts than
you guys. It's only natural.
Alright, let's see!
You have as horrible
a reputation as ever.
Maybe Headquarters is taking action
Oh, yeah! And what about
Usopp and Johnny?
Too delicious!
after what happened to Branch ♪77?!
Nothing's quite like Bellemere's
Special Tangerine Sauce!
That's fine. I am a pirate!
Usopp!
Hey! Nami! What does
he mean, "surveyor"?!
T-That's right! There's no time
to be loafing around here!
Nami and Nojiko are gonna
leap out of their seats!
But Arlong's a reasonable guy.
Why are you acting all
friendly-like with this guy?!
I am Colonel Nezumi of Navy Branch ♪16!
The smoke is coming from a house!
What's wrong?!
Money will fix all this, so it's just
a little more until our agreement.
That bastard's been caught by Arlong!
Oh? He's an acquaintance of yours?
Bring me Genzo, the
representative of Cocoyashi Village!
Oh? We almost missed it.
We gotta hurry before he's killed!
Don't be ridiculous.
He was just my prey.
--He was killed!
--What?!
I'm Genzo, Colonel.
Damn!
I swiped a whole load of treasure
from this guy this time around.
Bellemere-san!
No matter what, I'm going
to earn 100 million Berries
You, huh? Lead me to the
house of the girl named Nami.
Let's go! Let's collect our money!
and buy this village!
To think he'd follow me here,
without any idea he'd been tricked...
We're too late...
Nami? But what on earth for?!
Whoa, this is bad! The pirates...
Talk about unbelievably stupid.
...are headed to Bellemere's house!
So these are your true colors, huh?
She tells me to run, but I got
nowhere else to go but here...
You simply need to lead the way.
Big Bro Usopp is dead!
After you hated pirates so much before.
He was killed!
Surprised? It was all an act.
Does this make it clear enough?
Hey! Nojiko and Nami are gone!
Plus I promised Luffy I'd bring her back.
It all goes back to eight years ago...
What?!
By Big Sis Nami!
Ten more minutes for the duck in
the oven. And the stew is boiling.
What's he up to now?
Things're starting to get messy.
T-That's...
This'll be a big blow
to our family budget.
To that day, when we
were still little children...
But I guess I'll splurge, anyway!
Yahoo! So fast! So fast!
She was in this village.
Big Bro Luffy! I see it! Arlong Park!
I'm a pirate, plain and simple!
Me and Nami will never forget
her as long as we live...
Bellemere-san's gonna...
Go! To Arlong Park!
And a leader of the Arlong Pirates!
Am I... a ghost?
Her name was Bellemere.
Bellemere-san's gonna be killed!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Hey! Luffy!
Why're you flying here in a boat?!
Apparently Arlong and the
fishmen rule this village,
Nami would never kill Usopp!
We're friends!
Bellemere! What a beautiful girl's name!
Oh! How cute Nami-san
was as a child!
and no one can oppose them!
How I'd love to meet her!
'Cause I was in a hurry!
Geez, were you even
listening to the story?!
Who're friends?
That's not what I meant!
What the hell are you doing?!
Hey, are Bellemeres yummy?
Eh? Don't tell me
fish cuisine isn't allowed.
N-Nami-san! It's me!
Do you remember?!
Of course I was!
It's not food! It's the person
Nami-san will never forget!
I'm here to get Nami back!
Have you still not found her?
--Why are you here?!
--To get you!
I'd listen to every single
word that's about Nami-san!
I prefer meat with a bone in it!
Sanji! More meat!
About that... it's a long story.
Meaning she could be Nami-san's...
Nami-san's... Nami-san's...!
--Hey! Where's Usopp?!
--Bottom of the ocean.
--Got that?!
--Yes, I'm sorry.
Damn it! Cut the crap!
That reminds me, where's Long-nose?
Wait, why am I apologizing?!
Shut up! I can't sleep, Sanji!
To think she'd team up
with the fishmen...
Shut up! Get the hell out, outsiders!
You're an eyesore!
Is it over? Where's Luffy?
Crap! He's been caught by Arlong!
Wasn't Nami one of us?!
Are you guys even serious
about listening to Nojiko?
He was really sleeping?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Everyone's Gathered!
Usopp Speaks the Truth About Nami"
"Untold Past! Female Warrior Bellemere!"
"Usopp Dead?! When is Luffy
Going to Make Landfall?"
"Witch of Cocoyashi Village!
Arlong's Female Leader"
"Survive! Mother Bellemere
and Nami's Bond!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!