Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Into the sea!
Your father's name is...
Thanks, Merry.
A long time ago, I made the decision
that I'd never again build a ship.
...Monkey D. Dragon. He's a revolutionary!
Usopp?!
We're gonna be saved! She came to rescue us!
Thanks to you, we were able to escape.
What?!
I never thought that you'd come, Merry...
We've got one more friend, right?!
But I wanted to catch up to the
person who was my goal after all.
Hey, guys... What are you so surprised about?
But when I think about it,
you've always protected us.
Chopper! Did you look below?!
There's a power trying to bring down
the World Government directly now.
The next thing I knew, I was
drawing blueprints for a ship.
I did!
I'm so glad that you're our friend.
I'm sorry...
That's the revolutionary army.
Thanks, Merry!
Cien Fleurs!
And Dragon is the man who leads it.
My dream is... to use that treasure tree...
At any rate...
Ah! I guess...
Delphinium!
...you guys sure did pull one
outrageous stunt back there.
...to build one last ship...
A dream ship that crosses any sea!
I wanted to carry you to further places.
...I shouldn't have said anything about it, huh?
To start with, to think that you shot
through the World Government's flag...
I'm moving! Is Robin doing this?!
I'm sorry...
Well... it's not a big deal.
I wanted to continue the
adventure together forever.
Into the sea!
Into the sea...!
Merry!
All we did was take back a friend
who was taken away from us.
Into the sea!
Well, then...
I've already obtained this treasure tree.
...forget what I just said!
But I--
It's us who have to apologize, Merry!
Whaaat?!
I've already got blueprints, too.
I'm going to build this ship now.
Follow Luffy!
I'm not good at steering...
So... when it's completed...
Since you're my grandson, I decided
not to capture you on this island!
Here we go!
...so I ran you into icebergs at times...
"Thank You, Merry!
Snow Falls over the Parting Sea"
Here we go...!
...will you set sail on the ship I've built?!
There was a time I tore the sails, too.
I'm gonna give the Navy that good excuse,
so stay here and rest easy!
Into the sea!
Hey! Hey, hey, hey! Usopp!
The pirates are jumping into the sea!
Zoro and Sanji are stupid,
so they broke all sorts of things!
That can't be an excuse,
so let's tell them that he got away.
How stupid! There's no way that they
can survive after jumping into this sea.
Where are you, Usopp?!
What?
I just came along with these two.
Hey!
Usopp would fix them each time,
but he isn't good at it!
Usopp!
Well, take your time and talk with them.
Oh? He isn't here?
Let's go back, everyone!
What?!
Dammit!
So it's us who have to...
I'm going back!
Usopp! Usopp!
Wake up!
Okay! See ya!
That's too casual!
Usopp!
Be more reluctant to say goodbye, you idiot!
Where are you, Usopp?!
Luffy!
You haven't seen your grandpa in forever!
O-Ouch! That hurt!
But I've been happy.
Hey, he's calling for you.
What do you want me to do?!
All you did was hit me!
Fire!
O-Oh, this isn't good. Without thinking, I...
That hurt?! What're you saying?!
Even so, I still want my grandson
to love me, you moron!
That was a punch! There's no
way that'd work on rubber!
That's enough! Come out already!
Thank you very much...
for taking good care of me.
There's no means to ward off a fist of love!
Ah...
If you don't, I'm gonna beat the crap outta you!
That selfishness... You can
really tell that they're related.
Back to the seas of adventure!
We're gonna beat the crap outta you!
Looks like you've gone on
quite the rampage, huh, Luffy?
Yeah.
Hey, do you know where Usopp is,
Sogeking? I can't find him anywhere!
Ack! G-G-G...
Get on the Merry!
I really have been happy...
"Its Name Is the New World!
The Fate of the Grand Line!"
Grandpa!
D-Don't worry. He went back
ahead of us on a small boat earlier.
What?
Merry!
What?!
...because I had you.
Why?!
But this ship actually belongs to him now...
Anyway, that old man was like a storm.
A-A Navy Vice Admiral is...
"Everyone Makes a Great Escape!
The Road to Victory Is for the Pirates"
Just what is it they need
in order to recognize Usopp?
I was really surprised about Dragon.
"The Strongest Family?
Luffy's Father Revealed!"
So he was special to begin
with because of his lineage.
What're they trying to do?!
Where's Luffy?
Not here, either.
Merry!
There's no way that they'd be
saved after jumping into the sea!
He's out front talking to Coby and his buddy.
There should be power
holders among them, too!
Don't you have to go?
They're your friends, too, right?
What's going on?
That's suicidal!
It does bring back memories...
Hey, hold on a sec...
As we suspected, I can't find
anyone anywhere on this ship.
...but it was Luffy who saved Coby.
What the heck is that?
Luffy!
That's strange.
It's a ship! From its pirate flag,
it's the Straw Hat Pirates' ship!
Nami isn't around either, huh?
I wonder who on earth sailed this ship to us...
I thought she wanted to hear
stories about the marines...
Isn't there something you
How did it sneak in undetected
by all our battleships?
But we definitely heard
that voice calling out to us.
"Monkey D. Garp
'Garp the Fist'
Vice Admiral, Navy Headquarters"
I wonder if she decided to let them talk alone...
need to apologize to me for?!
She went to the pool with
Kokoro-san and the others.
Is that right?
Pool?
Vice Admiral Garp's got a grandson?!
Yes, someone most certainly called to us.
Yeah, to the Galley-La Company's
employee pool that's behind here.
This is the first I've heard of it!
"Two days later"
Like I said all this time...
it was the Merry's voice!
What?! Nami-san's wearing a bathing suit?!
Garp?!
I'll go bring drinks or something!
"Peace Interrupted! A Navy
Vice Admiral with a Fist of Love!"
What?! Really?!
"Garp" is the name of a Navy hero!
Then, you guys also crossed
that mountain, huh?
What?!
That mountain? Oh, no,
we didn't cross Reverse Mountain.
Right, Merry?! Say something!
Luffy! Is he really your grandpa?!
You idiot. There's no way a ship would talk.
I don't know who you are, but thanks for...
Hm? But I saw in a newspaper before
That's right! Don't you dare mess with him!
I kinda felt that way too, though...
that my grandpa's ship
crossed that mystery mountain
and entered the Grand Line.
But there's no way something
like that... could happen, huh?
Oh, that article was a lie.
--Yaay!
--Blue Station...
Hey, Coby! You shouldn't
tell him about it so casually!
What the heck?
--Hurry! Hurry!
--Blue Station, Water Seven.
When I was small, he almost
killed me a bunch of times!
Ah...
All passengers, please make sure not to
forget your belongings when you get off.
But it's okay, since it's Luffy-san.
H-How could it be okay?!
He is a pirate, you know!
--Oof!
Don't worry.
Everything was a mystery to us, but...
Is something wrong, Sanji-kun?
Hmm... Don't just talk to each other.
...for some reason, these words
remained in my heart.
Hmm... Well, Nami-san...
Ah... Let's see... This is top secret,
Now, don't go around giving me a bad name.
The rope ladder was definitely dropped,
but there seems to be no one here.
I don't even know if this person actually
said it or I was imagining things...
but headquarters' battleships can
get through the Calm Belt, so...
What?!
I shoved you into a bottomless pit...
Yaay!
What?! That's not fair!
Merry!
Don't worry.
Forget the money. Just take it.
I wish you good luck!
Of course, it's not 100% reliable, though.
Seriously, learn how to swim, brother!
I threw you into a jungle at night...
I'll carry you guys for a little bit longer.
But how come?
Now, get on board, power holders!
There's a swarm of Sea Kings several
times larger than battleships there.
I attached you to balloons and let them fly...
This may sound stupid, but...
Robin-chan!
...I feel that it might've been
an incarnation of the Merry.
Throw yourself into my arms!
This bites...
I did all those things in order
to make you a strong man!
We had a terrible time there!
To tell you the truth,
at the bottom of the battleships,
You think I'm crazy, don't you?
You don't have to believe me.
How're things over there?
This is the Merry! It's the Merry!
they spread these stones
called Sea Prism Stones.
No good, it's a total mess!
I think I've just discovered where
Luffy's endless vitality comes from...
What about it?
I really love the Merry!
Believe you?
Ah... That is to say...
At any rate, this year's Aqua Laguna
was terribly destructive.
This person looked like a sailor
holding a wooden hammer, right?
...that Sea Prism Stones release
the same energy as the sea itself,
Merry... Merry...
I eventually entrusted you with my
friend and had you train with Ace...
This is far beyond our
ability to repair on our own.
My Merry is alive!
so to the fish in the sea, those ships are...
What...? Why...?
The sea's energy...!
Why... Why are you so...
Do you know?
Hm? That's...
Oh, I see! So even when those
ships pass by on the sea's surface,
Brother...
...but I take my eyes off you,
and look what happens...
If... If I was... If I was more...
Paulie from Dock #1! What's he
doing in a backstreet like this?
You saw a Klabautermann.
the Sea Kings wouldn't notice them.
I trained you to become a strong marine!
K-Klabau...?
Paulie-san!
I can't believe it! This ship
was dropped into the sea!
Klabautermann.
In that case, they don't have
to go through the trouble
Out of our way! You guys
stay away! You're in our way!
I told you over and over that
I wanted to become a pirate!
of passing through Reverse Mountain,
the entrance to the Grand Line.
It's one of the legends known among sailors.
They can just enter as they please.
You got corrupted by "Red Hair"! How foolish!
The more care the ship receives,
the more it appreciates the sailors.
Guys from Dock #3! I'll leave this block to you!
Sh-Shanks saved my life! Don't badmouth him!
Okay!
The Navy's scientists are pretty impressive.
This ship probably wanted to somehow
carry you across to the other shore.
Guys from Dock #5! Take the block next to the
scrap heap island! Start with private houses!
I got some good info.
How dare you talk like that to your grandpa?!
Okay!
Lady! Lady! Aren't you gonna swim?!
You've got your regular work, too!
So work on the backstreets
She was able to encounter a crew
that she wanted to carry so badly
Who on earth sailed the ship here?
Ahhh! I'm sorry!
during your breaks! I want it
all restored within a month!
Hey!
This is terrible! Luffy got captured by the Navy!
We'll talk about it later!
Give us your instructions!
Hey, be quiet, Chimney!
Chances like this don't come often!
Got it!
that she'd borrow a human form to appear...
--That's right.
--Let's get out of here!
Get on it!
Luffy!
Yeah!
Let go of me! Ow, ow, ow...
Hey! What're you doing, Sanji-kun?!
I bet she's been very happy.
Pirate lady! This is boring! This is boring!
Whoa! They're too dependable!
N-Nami-san!
Oh, no! Luffy's combative spirit against
that old man has already been broken!
That's our Galley-La Company!
That was close! I thought I was
gonna be killed by the battleships!
Quiet! I'm eavesdropping right now!
"Remains of Franky House, north shore"
What?! They fell asleep?!
Is that something you want
to broadcast out loud?
Hey, Robin! You saved me! Thank y...
W-Well, what the heck should we do?
Dig into these epoch-making technologies,
and you'll always find Dr. Vegapunk,
a Navy scientist. He's incredible!
I've never been in this kind of situation!
I see...
This sure takes a lot of time to build.
Then, the one...
Yeah, he's really incredible!
Well, our specialty is demolition.
Oh, no. I fell asleep.
...who talked to me then...
Just leave the rest to us!
For example, Straw Hat,
take Devil Fruits, like the one you ate.
So we'll be camping out tonight again, huh?
Hm?!
...was really you, huh?
He's already clarified how
their powers get transmitted.
There, there.
Merry...
Sodom... and Gomorrah.
Wake up, Luffy!
In addition, another one of his big
achievements over the past few years
You two get a good rest, okay?
is creating new tech that allows
an object to eat a Devil Fruit.
Is that how you behave
when you're being scolded?!
Dr. Vegapunk...
Hm?
That reindeer guy said that Gomorrah's
eyes will get better if he keeps resting.
Luffy... and everyone...
I see a ship coming towards us!
I see... There are some
amazing guys out there, huh?
And that's not how you should speak
to your grandpa in the first place!
Wh-What?! Who's that?!
Is that right? That's good news!
Thank you!
Yes, the world is full of incredible people!
Hey, guys. Give me a hand, will you?
It's the Straw Hats!
They're alive!
I don't care anymore. Do as you please.
I realized what a small world
I lived in before I met you.
So you guys're okay!
I need to go pick up a shipment at the station.
A shipment?
The Galley-La Company's ship...
Could it be...?
Yep. It seems like that stuff has arrived.
This is amazing!
Ribbit?
Don't worry about it.
They rushed out in Aqua Laguna and
still made it okay! I can't believe it!
Seriously?!
If you hadn't come out of that
barrel that day, Luffy-san...
So Luffy's grandpa is a marine
at Navy Headquarters?
"Dock #1, shipbuilding island"
They came back from Enies Lobby!
Let us see the pirates
This is getting crazy...
Say stupid stuff like that
after we escape from here.
and let us apologize to them
Ribbit...
Ahoy! Ice pops!
...I bet I would still be buttering up
Alvida and doing chores for her.
for calling them assassins!
What do you mean "stupid stuff,"
you damn moss head?!
You can't! The pirates won't see anyone!
Th-Th-That hurt!
Stupid-berg...
What do you mean, you damn moss head?!
We owe them for saving Iceberg-san's life.
Let us at least thank them!
Do you even know what kind of pirate
"Red Hair" is to start with?!
Shut up! If we die here,
it'll all come to nothing!
Nico Robin...
That's right, you were on Alvida's ship!
That was really funny!
I'm from the Water Seven Newspaper!
Apologize to Robin-chan, you bastard!
Let me have some comments from the
heroes who saved our mayor! Please!
He's right! Apologize to Robin!
To start with, the reason
you were on her ship was...
Shanks?! Are they... Are Shanks
and the others doing okay?!
That's enough!
Just give up! You can't see them now!
Hm? Hey, Chopper...
What a crazy lot.
Let us at least take their pictures, then!
What is it? I don't know anything about that.
You can move now?
--I said no! Are you all deaf?!
--I'll work as a secretary in place of Kalifa-san!
Where are they?!
They took on the World Government...
What?
Doing okay?!
Y-You're right! I'm moving!
Let me do something to help!
Err... Well... Um...
Well, there are countless pirates
nowadays, but out of all of them,
Let us see the pirates!
I can move now! Zoro!
You wanted to go fishing and got
on a pirate ship by mistake, right?
No means no means no!
he's ranked in the top four pirates,
in the same league as Whitebeard.
Apologize to Robin already!
...and they really took everything back.
What the hell?! What a bungler!
Give up yet?
No! No!
These four reign over the second half
of the Grand Line like emperors.
Back then, I was such a coward
that I couldn't even run away.
Now, guys! We're gonna
hurry up and get outta here!
Yeah!
So people call them the Four Emperors.
But because I was on that ship,
I was able to meet you, Luffy-san.
Hey, hey... Give me a break!
Are you guys letting them get away?!
Navy Headquarters and the
Seven Warlords of the Sea
Amazing! They've got
unbelievable superhuman strength!
So it wasn't a mistake after all!
Is this how you want it?
If they're getting away anyway,
might as well just blow up Nico Robin!
have joined together to
fight against these four!
Thank you! That's giants for you!
I was doing chores on that ship
in order to meet you, I bet!
Merry!
But we have to capture her alive!
If we can do something like this
to help, just let us know any time!
If the balance among these
three great powers is lost,
Look! Their ship is...!
Admiral Aokiji asked me to tell you that.
it is said that world peace will fall apart.
That's how large their power is.
Hey, what's going on?!
What happened all of a sudden?!
All ships! Prepare to fire cannons!
Is that how it is?
All of a sudden? Isn't this just natural?
You guys really are great!
A-Admiral Aokiji did?!
Huh? Err...
That's how it is, yep!
Say, king of snipers...
I didn't really get all that,
but it's good to hear he's doing okay.
Okay! Aim at them!
What?
Hm?
It was declared that Merry could no longer sail.
All ships! Prepare to fire cannons!
You've kinda become strong.
Is it okay for you to stay here?
It really brings back memories.
What?
But...!
We were thinking...
I'm being trained every day, so...
I'll leave this hat with you.
The Merry is...!
That was a big lie. I'm not gonna let
them get away. I'm gonna kill them.
Seriously, your grandpa doesn't
know how to go easy on others.
It's dear to me.
If our bosses are still fighting,
we can't set foot on that island.
Now that it's come to this,
I'm gonna kill them all!
Take good care of it!
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Pops! This is bad! Merry is in trouble!
Please do something!
No, Vice Admiral Garp is a wonderful man!
Hey! Hurry up and load the cannonballs!
So we decided to help out
the guys on this island a bit
You guys... This is good timing!
You guys're all shipwrights, right?!
So Spandam is alive.
and then take our time going back to Elbaf.
He took us in when we had
nowhere to go due to an incident.
Come bring it back to me someday!
They're gonna fire at us!
If you like Elbaf, we can take you with us.
I'm begging you! Please do something!
Catch the wind from starboard and head east!
Once you've become a great pirate!
That's our promise, Luffy!
She's our friend who has been
traveling with us all this time!
We can't! We're completely surrounded!
We can train in Navy Headquarters right
now all thanks to Vice Admiral Garp.
And just a bit ago she saved us!
The number of cannons
aiming at us is overwhelming!
I...
So please, pops!
Where I'm going is my own business.
It's impossible that they
would all miss this ship.
Yeah, his grueling training sure is tough...
I'm... leaving the gang!
Fire!
Luffy and "Red Hair" know each other?
Fight a duel with me!
Ahh! They're coming!
Luffy told me that this guy
entrusted the straw hat with him.
I...
Then let her...
"Remains of Galley-La Company headquarters--
Iceberg's residence"
But I didn't realize this guy
was such a famous person.
Hey, are they firing at each other?
None of the other attacks are hitting us, either!
It's tough... but I really appreciate him.
...rest now.
"Temporary headquarters building"
I see... So you burned the blueprints...
Where are you all aiming?!
So, I'll at least become able to
return the favor first, and then...
Th-This way, Zoro-san!
I've already done everything I could.
There's something wrong! It's like
the cannons are aiming themselves!
Dammit! The Navy is already here!
That's for the best.
Don't give me a weird excuse!
No! I'm gonna get promoted
high enough to boss him around!
Please go on ahead!
You made an enemy of
the government too, huh?
Well, really...
Keep clear!
Whoa! Cool, split chin!
We can't! We're gonna collide!
We're sorry that we tried to extort you!
What'd you say?! It's not split!
Well, don't worry about it!
Thanks for showing me the way! Later!
Guess I did.
What's this sound?
So... what are those plans
you've been drawing up?
Seeing the scale of this past Aqua Laguna
It's coming this way! What the hell is going on?!
Hm? What's going on?!
Is someone on the scrap heap island?
must have made the citizens worry
that this island itself might be
swallowed by the sea some time soon.
That's Pirate Hunter Zoro,
a criminal with a bounty on his head.
What's the matter?! What's going on?!
Isn't this... the Straw Hats' ship?
Oh...? That's Luffy's friend.
I still can't get used to...
L-Look over there!
He's quite energetic, huh?
...Kokoro-san looking like that...
What the hell?!
The damage must've been caused by
Aqua Laguna. It's in a terrible state.
Well, if something like that keeps attacking,
Well, you guys, try stopping him.
Pirate lady! Let's play volleyball!
The Gates of Justice started
closing at some point!
Yes, sir!
the island might sink, too.
The currents blocked by the
gates are producing whirlpools
Well, I guess it's beyond just damage...
So what're you gonna do?
and we can't control the rudder!
I'll have the entire island float on the sea.
So that's why our aiming was off the mark!
I want to set sail.
What?!
Don't get swallowed by the currents!
Turn Water Seven into a ship?!
What?! Are you really going back already?
Wh-What the hell is going on?
Kukris, huh? It's not often that you see those.
What was that?
But i-is something like that possible?!
Why don't you have dinner with us? Dinner!
Hiya!
Hiya! Hiya!
Did you forget...?
Properly speaking, we're enemies.
Hey, Zoro, wait! You don't have to fight!
Put out the fire! Hurry up!
I want to set sail one last time!
We witnessed a great man who
made the impossible possible
This is it! Everyone, get out of here!
We can't become close, so...
What the...? You bastard!
for quite some time, didn't we?
Idiots! Why did you close the gates?
What're you morons doing?!
Shave!
Luffy-san, do you know what the
second half of the Grand Line is called?
This technique...
If you're a man... do it resolutely!
The lever to open and close the gates is inside
the third column of the Bridge of Hesitation,
so we couldn't have done anything!
Whoa! This is more than I expected!
Sanji! Don't tell me you did something earlier!
People call the last sea that
lies beyond the Red Line
"If you're a man, do it resolutely," huh?
Yep.
These guys aren't the kind of enemy we
could escape from with just guts, right?
--Sergeant Major!
--Sergeant!
by another name...
Now I remember.
You're right.
The New World.
You guys are no match for them at all!
Bingo!
Hm?
You really are strong.
What am I doing?
--Click.
--Hello?!
I'd expect no less from you!
Oh, is this Bro?
There's no hope left for this ship...
Th-That's amazing, Sanji!
The New World...
Oh, hey, Zambai! What's up?
Are you a genius or what?!
I concede!
Please rejoice, Bro! It's finally here!
Iceberg-san!
We can't go on rejoicing forever.
The whirlpools are a problem for us, too.
What are you doing there?!
Another big wave is coming!
It's just arrived by sea train!
Luffy-san! Zoro-san!
Ahh! That's right!
It's a sea where those who will open
the way to the next era gather.
--We're gonna die!
--Shut up, you guys!
The item that you purchased
for 200 million Berries!
It's been a while. Do you recognize me?
There was no sea that the Merry
couldn't cross with us on board!
The one who comes to conquer this sea
will indeed be the King of the Pirates.
So it's finally arrived...
Who are you?
"Special pirate room with kitchen and bathroom,
temporary headquarters building"
It's me! Coby!
Thank you.
Don't you remember me?
Ohhh...
Coby?
--That's right! We're counting on you, navigator!
--Nami-san! You're so cool!
Just hang on until I can figure out
the trajectory of the whirlpools!
Do you think... even I could join the Navy?
Yep.
Leave it to us!
Luffy-san! Let's meet again there for sure!
I'm coming in, guys!
--Navy?
--Yes! Catching bad guys is my dream!
Granny Kokoro!
Hey! I'm coming in!
Next time I see you, I'll capture you!
And you kids...
It's been my dream ever since I was little!
Do you think I can do it?!
I'll get stronger and stronger,
One-Sword Style... Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
Ribbit! Ribbit?!
and one day... I'll become a...
Luffy-san and I haven't known
each other long, but we are friends!
Ribbit!
...N...
Right?
What?! You want to set sail?!
Dammit! I can't do the Hundred-and-eight
version with just two swords!
Navy Admiral!
Yeah! We're gonna part ways,
but we'll always be friends!
You stay outside.
The sea is still stormy!
You can just take a break, then.
I'll go alone if I have to.
Thank you! I'll never forget
all you've done for me!
What'd you say, you jerk?!
Whoa... Ah... Um...
What?!
H-Hey! They're coming again!
Ribbit, ribbit.
We can't let you go out there all by yourself!
Let's meet again sometime, Coby!
I-I-I'm sorry! I-I got too full of myself!
Looks like everyone's finally woken up, huh?
You guys slept for two days.
Collier Shoot!
--Luffy-san...
--Bye!
I'm watching a miracle right now...
I'm so embarrassed! I wanna crawl under a rug!
You must've been quite exhausted...
of course, it's only natural after everything.
I-I got carried away, since I saw you, and...
All hands, salute!
A miracle of a ship that
has long passed its limits...
Cien Fleurs! Defense!
Oh? The King of the Pirates
is doing pretty good, too, huh?
Coby...
See ya!
You're gonna fight me, right?
Oh... It's not like that.
Then at least get to that level.
It's obvious you'll need to.
What do you mean?
Coby?!
Here! I'm returning these to you!
I've been a shipwright for many years,
Because he doesn't want to collapse
and miss any meals after fights...
I do have a friend Coby...
but the Coby I know was short.
but I've never seen a pirate ship this incredible.
Triple... Flame... Stars!
I-It's an Admiral we're talking about...
Huh?
It's lived a splendid life.
Next time we meet, we'll be stronger!
That's me! The Coby who
was a hopeless crybaby!
...he said he acquired the skill
of eating while sleeping.
More amazing!
I wonder if Zoro and the others are okay.
He's actually sleeping?!
What?! Is that true?!
I wonder...
Amazing! Pirate guy!
--Chopper!
--Hm?
That Coby?
They're fine, so just focus on steering.
What a skillful man!
Let's go back, everyone!
Why...
Why are you in the Grand Line?
Ribbit...
I've still got a ways to go
to become a Navy Officer,
O-Okay.
By the way, the Log for the Log Pose
should be ready in 2-3 days, right?
but when I heard that you were nearby,
I just wanted to see you guys so badly.
Back to the seas of adventure!
Hey, what's going on over here?!
Merry!
As I am right now, it's such a wild dream
What?!
I came to get you.
Even if the Log is ready,
we can't move forward for a while.
that just saying it almost makes me faint...
We owe you two for helping us
"Coby
Sergeant Major, Navy Headquarters"
become who we are now!
Dammit! Why?! Why can't you bring down
that puny little ship with seven battleships?!
"Helmeppo
Sergeant, Navy Headquarters"
Well, I wouldn't go that far, but...
And yet, how can you
have faith in me like that?
The whole 100 million Berries
we saved to buy a new ship,
For various reasons, Vice Admiral Garp
is currently training us at Headquarters.
You useless morons!
Oh? You're still a crybaby, huh, Coby?
our clothes, furniture, and Bellemere-san's
tangerine trees... Everything...
Hey, they're coming your way, Usopp!
Okay! Leave them to me!
Oh, yeah?
I missed one! Sanji, take care of it!
...was swept away by the Aqua Laguna.
Basses Côte!
We can no longer go anywhere.
Ahhh! I'm gonna fight, too!
Okay...
I'm so glad that I was able
to see you two again today!
How gloomy...
You idiot! You can't move, can you?!
We entrusted them all
with a backstreet inn, so...
At any rate, usually people can
only grow so much, you know!
He's right, Luffy. Leave this one to us...
It really is a lot of work
chasing after these people.
Then I wonder if the visitors outside
have something to do with that...
...and take it easy!
I'm so surprised!
Visitors?
Your body was flabby!
--Excuse me...
--Hm?
Actually, we came to deliver these.
We'll get stronger and stronger!
Ahhh! I don't care what you guys say--
Hm?
Sorry for visiting now, when you're
tired after all you went through.
Let's meet again in the New World for sure!
Tangerine trees! I thought
I'd never get them back!
Don't worry about it. It's been
a while. Let's have a party!
I'm gonna fight!
--Let's go!
--Ah, hey!
I'm so glad!
Well, when we were chasing you guys
around as Iceberg-san's assassins,
You guys'd better be prepared!
We'll blow you away in time!
Hold on a sec, you guys!
I'll give a medal to the one who actually
hits them! So hurry up and hit them!
we confiscated everything as
pirates' belongings. Sorry about that.
You haven't noticed me, have you?!
Hey, wait up, you jerk!
All ships! Concentrate all
attacks on their back deck!
All right! Let's see who
makes it to the harbor first!
Who are you?
Not at all! Thank you!
That's enough, Luffy!
It's me! It's me!
Don't be silly! That's not fair!
Fire!
I'm happy for you.
I don't know you. Who are you?
Luffy... didn't you just
create another crazy enemy?
Hey! We're back!
Shut up! I'm your captain!
The answer is...
--We're back.
--Hey, Chopper! And Robin-chan!
Whoa!
Coby is a man who makes
things happen. I know that much.
...Helmeppo. The son of Captain Morgan...
It must've been heavy. Now, give me your hand.
Thank you.
Helmeppo!
I went to check on the
Franky Family guys' injuries.
I'm the man who crucified you and
nearly executed you, Roronoa Zoro!
Also, I didn't take my eyes off of Robin!
Okay! Well done!
Yep!
I told you, I'm not going anywhere.
One...
Huh?!
Two...
It's a promise, okay?!
Three!
Now you remember me, right?
Yes, it's a promise.
Oh, crap! They're bouncing back!
Both of you! Look at this!
The tangerine trees were okay!
Huh?
Hey, hey, that's enough.
We got everything back,
including our money and belongings!
Yeah!
We can now continue our journey!
Well, then... are you guys ready?
That saved us, captain!
It's not nice to be a bully!
All right! I'm so glad!
Just as we'd expect from our captain!
It was good to see that
he seemed to be doing well.
--Yeah.
Hey! Are you guys demons?!
You seem surprisingly well, Roronoa Zoro...
But I wonder if he realizes how the world
sees what happened in Enies Lobby...
Victory!
--Take this! And this!
--Stop! Stop!
Hm?
Yow! Are you guys super?! Everyone...
That specially treated stupid son!
Merry... The seabed is dark and lonesome,
I see it... the road to victory!
In any event, an island directly under
the Government was annihilated...
Chopper, hard aport at 9 o'clock!
...isn't here, but that's okay.
so we'll watch you to the end.
...although I guess the news that they brought
down CP9 probably won't be made public.
Oh...
O-Okay!
It's you...
What is it, Franky, all of a sudden?!
Hey!
Of course, it can't be made public,
since CP9 is a secret organization.
The pirate ship escaped towards the falls!
Listen!
Maybe it was good that Usopp wasn't here.
Oh, yeah... There was a
guy like that. So it's you!
Fire! Fire! What're you doing?!
I've got something important
to discuss with you.
There's no way... that he could bear this.
The truth is, Enies Lobby caught fire
due to the Buster Call in the first place,
I still can't stand these guys, Coby!
Are you all idiots?! Sink that ship already!
What do you think?
It seems that they caught
the flow of the whirlpools!
I disagree.
and yet they claimed that Luffy-san
and the others did all of that.
It can't be helped, Helmeppo-san.
You should accept the past.
They're moving at an incredible speed!
Everyone must someday say farewell.
This is a man's parting.
I'm gonna be useful, too!
Oh, that?
With the entire military force
of Enies Lobby at our disposal...
Not even a single tear should be shed.
Yeah, that.
Go for it, reindeer!
Luffy-san, you and I are now enemies, but...
Go! Speed forth with all your might!
With the power of Buster Call,
as strong as an entire country's military...
Hm?
...are we still... um...
He, too... is prepared.
On an island where wars
happen one after another...
Why... Why in the hell can't we...
Yeah. We're friends.
What is it all of a sudden?
Why...? Why can't we take a single woman...
You just barged in here. If it's a
stupid story, we're not gonna listen.
Shut up! Just listen to my story!
...from a puny little band of pirates?!
No matter if the islanders start a war
where cannonballs fall incessantly,
The Navy should be protecting Justice...
There's no way this is right.
or if everyone dies and the town
also dies and turns to ruins...
Dammit! Dammit! Those bastards!
...this huge tree would continue to stand.
So you just need to become a
big shot and change it, right?
Well then, you guys...!
With the entire military force
of Enies Lobby at our disposal...
Yes, sir!
No matter what happens, this tree will not fall.
Repair this wall.
Yeah, you're right.
With the power of Buster Call,
as strong as an entire country's military...
People once again nestle close to that
tree and create a town... A country.
What?!
That's so selfish!
Seriously, to think that he picked
a fight with the Government
If you were going to have it fixed,
why did you break it in the first place?!
Why... Why in the hell can't we...
Thank you for carrying us
for such a long time, Merry.
in order to get just one crewmate back...
Only a few trees like this exist in the world.
It's cooler to go in that way, isn't it?!
Just how stupid is he?
Why...? Why can't we take a single woman...
Don't break things for reasons like that!
The name given to the strongest of all trees is...
So you're worried about Luffy-san, too, huh?!
Well then, we'll repair it,
so please help us, okay?!
..."Adam," the treasure tree.
No, it's not like that!
I have nothing to do with him.
...from a puny little band of pirates?!
What?!
A tree?
Okay.
I'm just looking on from a distance.
What about the tree?
Hey! What're you two doing slacking off?!
Its wood appears on the
black market on rare occasions.
Snow...
--Ahhh!
--He's here!
I thought your grandpa was a big shot.
It's 1,000 years too early for you to fool
around in a place like this, you idiots!
I wanted it... but it cost almost 200 million.
Well... I don't know much about his job.
No meals for either of you for a week!
So it was impossible for me to buy it.
Y-Yes, sir!
And then, there appeared pirates with
a lot of money--in other words, you guys.
Come to think of it, Luffy...
Whoa...
A caravel!
Every day we'd play
covered in mud until the sun set
I heard that you saw your old man.
Yahoo!
What?! My dad?
You jerk! You'd better not have bought
something like that with our money!
What do you mean by my dad? I have a dad?
Nami-san! Water-water meat barbecue is ready!
Just keep listening!
Now the Going Merry pirate ship is all set!
Okay!
Chief!
It's hard to abandon
those innocent days we spent
Cheers to our new ship and crewmate!
Grandma, that was amazing!
Oh... Then he didn't tell you who he was?
It smells good.
A long time ago, I made the decision
that I'd never again build a ship.
I heard that he saw you off at Loguetown.
Right?!
If I hadn't recognized
the value of your existence,
Even if I'm a dreamer, I'm still me
Here, say "Ahh."
Ugh!
Loguetown...
it would've been practically worthless!
But I wanted to catch up to the
person who was my goal after all.
Err...
Look at this! The Merry
got damaged quite a bit!
Huh?
Yummy!
There's no hope left for you!
So that's the island where Loguetown is!
The next thing I knew, I was
drawing blueprints for a ship.
When navigating a sailboat,
everyone has to participate!
Yummy! Water-water meat barbecue!
So things don't all have to fit
together like a jigsaw puzzle
Learn it appropriately!
That island is where Gold Roger
was born and then executed, right?
--Aw...
--Yes, ma'am.
So you were so unhappy it'd make you cry?
I'm sorry.
Sogeking! When'd you get here?!
My dream is... to use that treasure tree...
What are you doing?!
Okay, guys, keep eating!
Wow, you actually remember!
...to build one last ship...
A dream ship that crosses any sea!
Cannon practice!
Just as someone's "Yes"
could be a "No" to you,
Why are you crying?
The town where the King of the Pirates died...
They sure don't fly good!
Shut up! The smoke is hurting my eyes!
I'm telling you, let me try!
Also known as the city
of the beginning and end...
So how is it, Robin-chan?! You can
tell it was marinated well, right?!
Help!
Yeah, it's delicious.
Awesome! You hit it on your first try!
you'll surely always be free
Help...
Oh, there they are!
Straw Hat! We heard that you woke up!
Whoa...! I really hit it on my first try!
Clutch!
Oh, Franky Family! Come here and eat!
I've already obtained this treasure tree.
I've already got blueprints, too.
Whoa! They're having barbecue!
Even if tomorrow a wind passes
through and breaks the puzzle
I'm going to build this ship now.
Wh-What's going on?
My favorite!
C-Chief!
Whoa! There are so many of you!
So... when it's completed...
Hey, add more meat!
To my several hundred billion
servants around the world! Look!
...will you set sail on the ship I've built?!
--Fight! Fight! Fight!
--All right... it's about time.
Ah! Sodom and Gomorrah!
No one would blame you for that
We'll now super flashily
start the open execution!
Zoro! Hey! That's my seat!
Franky!
Could you do that thing?!
Monkey D. Luffy! You can
no longer move even an inch.
The entrance to the Grand Line
lies ahead of that light.
What?
Got it!
I'm hungry.
Me, too.
Giants! Hey!
In order to find the All Blue!
We had a dream that day
You feel honored, Straw Hat?!
What? What? Th-Then...
Hey, Straw Hat! You woke up?!
You can die in the same place
the King of the Pirates died.
Everyone, be prepared for a shock.
Then... a-are you going to give that ship to us?!
In order to be King of the Pirates!
Oh, Galley-La is here, too, huh?!
Our belief in ourselves
Block their route! The enemy ship
can't get out of the whirlpools!
What're you guys doing around the pool?
That's right. Nothing would make me happier
than for people I like to travel on my ship.
In order to become a master swordsman!
Ahh! Shameless girl! What're you...?!
It'll be rough on the ship... Sorry about that.
In order to draw a world map!
makes us able to cross the wildly surging ocean
This is a pool, mister.
I-In order... to become a
brave warrior of the sea!
Well, that, and it's kinda like you
gave me the money for it, so...
Coup de Vent!
Well... something smells good.
Since you have a big audience, do you
wanna say something before you die?
The Oro Jackson, the ship of Gold Roger,
the only man who completed
Iceberg-san! No! You shouldn't
see this! This woman is a perv!
Th-The pirate ship is flying!
We're going... to the Grand Line!!
We know the pain that
you hold in your heart, so...
the round-the-world journey,
was also built using this treasure tree.
Is this really happening?!
Hey...
They've gone outside of the fleet's range!
We're taking a break from building a ship!
Well, that's okay.
I swear... I'll build an incredible ship!
Whether you wanna say something or not
doesn't matter, since you're gonna die.
That's right! Rejecting a party
would make me less of a man!
Don't underestimate what she's been through!
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
The Merry flew 10,000 meters high in the sky!
You'd better have a seat for me!
I guess it can't be helped, huh?
The entrance to the Grand Line is a mountain!
You'd better!
Special Attack! Super Smoke Star!
Tom-san and you are both craftsmen after all.
I'm the man who'll be King of the Pirates!!
Yow!
A mountain?
We've been waiting for you, Bro!
In the end, we can all surely smile
Here we go! Entrant #1, Sogeking! I'll sing!
It's a smokescreen!
Yeah... Now...
Out of our way!
Now... I can understand the feelings
of Tom-san, who died with pride.
Those bastards...!
All right! Party time!
After them! We bow to nobody in speed!
Not even Zoro can stop me now!
♪ I was born on the island of snipers ♪
We can't! We're caught in the whirlpools!
We made it!
All right!
It's taking everything
we've got just to stay afloat!
This is the end of your captain!!
This is the greatest sea in the world!
--You're a nice guy! We'll take it!
Thank you, Franky!
--Ribbit, ribbit! Ribbit, ribbit...
Damn bastard!
Go!
♪ I never miss my mark ♪
All right! We can travel to the next island!
♪ Lulu lala lu ♪
Fire! Fire!
Oh, I'm so happy! Luffy!
We're gonna get a ship!
Yow! Yow!
If I cut down the execution platform...
♪ Whether it's a mouse's eyeball, lock on!! ♪
Here you go, sis.
Ribbit!
--Please have these!
--Oh, thanks.
Ahhh!
♪ Or even your heart, lock on!! ♪
All right, guys! These are ready!
Zoro! Sanji!
You guys, help us, too!
--Hurry up!
--Usopp!
--This is heavy!
--Nami!
♪ The man who hails
from the island of snipers ♪
Sorry.
I'm... dead.
This is bad. To think that they figured
out our whereabouts this soon...
♪ Lululu, lulu lala... ♪
Yummy!
Whoa! We're flying out of it!
And Luffy's still sleeping!
I have to let them know immediately!
Don't look back! We're going straight ahead!
What?!
Sea...?
It seems that Straw Hat and
the others were able to escape!
Stay there and listen, Nico Robin.
All right! We'll go back, too!
Let me... join your crew.
Crap! I went the opposite way!
Did everyone get on board okay?!
It can't be...
There's no place for me to go or go back to.
Yeah! I put the seriously
injured in the passenger cars!
Aokiji...?
So let me stay on this ship.
Okay! Those who're outside, hang on
tight so that you won't be thrown off!
Oh, I see... Then I guess
we have no choice... Okay.
I'm still alive after all.
Why didn't you run as usual?
I got lucky.
We continue to dream even today
Luffy!
I'm sure you could've escaped
from CP9 alone if you'd wanted to.
Who's this ship's navigator?!
We're flying!
Carrying the feelings you
entrusted with us as well
What?! Sea again?! Dammit!
The Straw Hat gang is running away!
I told you that it's different now.
Awesome! The ship is flying!
Capture them!
Give me a break! Is this island a maze?!
Go after them!
I couldn't just stand by... and let them die.
Luffy's old man was in that town?!
This is terrible. They came
to capture the pirates.
It's a sky island!
They saved Iceberg-san's life!
Wh-What's my dad like?
Jaguar D. Saul, the giant who
fought for Ohara 20 years ago,
The whole thing is over, huh?
We once again cross these
rough seas and fight the pain
Hey, take a good look at that!
I'm curious... about Luffy's father!
Yeah.
I'd heard rumors,
was a close friend of mine.
That battleship belongs to
Vice Admiral Garp from headquarters!
but I never realized that a Buster Call
was such an inhumane thing.
Your father's name is...
Garp, you said?!
Kuzan!
...Monkey D. Dragon. He's a revolutionary!
That's the legendary marine who
cornered Gold Roger many times!
Can you take pride in this attack?
Well, Enies Lobby was eliminated in the end.
So that our promise won't become a lie
Maybe Iceberg-san will take
some measure of relief from that.
Can you still keep your head high?!
Why did such a high-level marine come?
Yeah.
Whoa! You guys, don't come in here!
Aren't the pirates in big trouble?!
You're running out of your devil's luck.
And someday, to you who departed
our ship and live in a different world,
We never would have
made it without your ropes!
On that day, I let you escape
the island according to his wish.
Don't be so sure.
We owe you our lives!
You're...
Shut up! Get off of me, you pervs!
So I'm obligated to watch
the rest of your life to the end.
Enough already...
Why the heck am I here again?
we'll deliver the completed puzzle
You're as innocent as ever.
But after 20 years, you seemed
to have no tree to call home.
You really are innocent.
You two... Enough is...
Dammit! Why's this gotta happen when
I have to let them know right away?!
I judged that I could no longer
ignore a dangerous bomb
Dragon?
Oh, boy! You've got it tough, huh, Paulie?
that bounced around as it was chased.
What?!
Hey, there's an idiot over there.
Oh, my! We'll take good care of you!
Above all things, I thought
that you wanted to die.
Let's do it.
P-Please, I beg you... Get out of here.
Whaaat?!
With this whole thing, I was going
to settle everything regarding Ohara.
T-T-The revolutionary Dragon has a son?!
Hey, pops! We haven't
seen your face around here.
Luffy-san is the son of that Dragon?!
Go! Puffing Tom!
As a matter of course, I couldn't predict
that CP9 would be defeated at all.
Then... Dragon is Vice Admiral Garp's son?!
We want to have a word with you.
Oh, yeah?
What the hell is with his family?!
I've never heard Dragon's full name before!
So you finally found a tree to call home?
I-I didn't realize that you were here.
We'll still pursue them, so...
Hey, guys... What are you so surprised about?
Yes...
P-Please hold on a second, marines!
We can't possibly let it end like this.
Idiot! You don't know the name "Dragon"?!
To maintain our dignity as the Navy--
no, the World Government--
Whether Saul letting you
live was right or wrong...
--Our president is the only one back there.
--Shut up! There've got to be pirates!
Your father is a dangerous man!
N-No, there aren't!
Hey, don't enter without permission!
we'll bring down the Straw Hat Pirates
Will you show me the answer from here on?
and we'll bring in Nico Robin, a criminal
of utmost importance, without fail!
Stop! The Straw Hats are--!
Huh?
Idiot!
I'm sorry...
Therefore, fleet reinforcements
and additional marines are...
That's what I intend to do.
Then, live strongly.
Ribbit...
Don't bother.
But...!
Ohara still lives on.
Hey, Robin...
We used a Buster Call, an attack as
strong as an entire country's military.
I wanted to carry you even further.
How can I explain it...?
When we see the blunder this fleet
made and the current situation
Pirates wouldn't start a fight
with the Government or Navy,
You two, wait here!
of Enies Lobby, the symbol
of law, it's quite obvious.
I'm sorry...
Yes, sir!
I wanted to continue going on
adventures with you forever.
Aokiji!
but there's a power trying to bring down
the World Government directly now.
On this matter, we've been
completely defeated.
Merry!
Hey! Robin! Look at this!
A voice...
That's the revolutionary army.
Is the top of this sheep head here okay?
And Dragon is the man who leads it.
Robin! Look at this!
Yep. That's my seat.
Robin!
But I--
It's us who have to apologize, Merry!
There you go. Be careful not to fall.
Their ideology has now spread in
many countries around the world,
Are you eating meat?!
I'm not good at steering...
Yeah. Thanks, monster granny.
which caused rebellions and
led several kingdoms to fall.
What the hell?!
That's so cool, Luffy!
Who's there?!
...so I ran you into icebergs at times...
The government naturally became angry
You're doing that stupid
stuff again?! Cut it out!
Thanks, Merry.
There was a time I tore the sails, too.
and has been searching everywhere for
their mastermind, Dragon, all this time
Thanks to you, we were able to escape.
You too! You're wearing a shirt over
a bathing suit! That looks stupid!
So you guys are the Straw Hats?!
as the world's most heinous criminal...
I never thought that you'd come, Merry...
Zoro and Sanji are stupid,
so they broke all sorts of things!
--Are you tryin' to be Franky?!
--Don't say that!
I've got some guys who I want
to have meet Monkey D. Luffy.
Hey, that way!
...but he's been considered a mysterious man
whose background was completely unknown.
But when I think about it,
you've always protected us.
I heard that the pirates are having a party!
Usopp would fix them each time,
but he isn't good at it!
Navy!
I'm so glad that you're our friend.
And yet...
And yet?
Thanks, Merry!
Geez... He's as hopeless as ever.
You finally found a tree to call home?
So it's us who have to...
At any rate...
...you guys sure did pull one
outrageous stunt back there.
No one is born into this world to be alone!
To start with, to think that you shot
through the World Government's flag...
What?!
But I've been happy.
Dammit!
Ah! I guess...
Wake up!
Well... it's not a big deal.
Yeah, you're right, Saul.
...I shouldn't have said anything about it, huh?
What?!
Thank you very much... for taking
good care of me all this time.
All we did was take back a friend
who was taken away from us.
Luffy!
O-Ouch! That hurt!
Live together with them.
That hurt?! What're you saying?!
Thanks for helping us save Robin.
That was a punch! There's no
way that'd work on rubber!
I really have been happy...
Well, then...
Well, to me, it was no big deal.
Yes...
There's no means to ward off a fist of love!
...forget what I just said!
Hey! Robin!
Looks like you've gone on
quite the rampage, huh, Luffy?
Anyway...
...because I had you.
...this fight...
Hey! This way! This way!
Ack! G-G-G...
Whaaat?!
...is over...
Grandpa!
Maybe... I'll try it, too.
...and we won!
What?
Yeah! Do it! Do it, Robin!
Yeah!
What?!
Please don't do it, Robin-chan!
Merry!
A-A Navy Vice Admiral is...
Whoa! You don't have to go that far...
His grandpa?!
Are you really going back already?
Hold on a sec!
Merry...
Pardon me, but since I'm on an enemy ship,
I used a bit of intimidation.
Luffy's grandpa is a Navy hero?!
It was quite an ordeal, but we're back.
Merry!
Why don't you have dinner with us? Dinner!
Merry...!
We're enemies. We can't become close, so...
We're back!
Nooo! Sanji! Luffy's in danger!
There's something I want to discuss with you.
The restoration of Water Seven starts now!
Your name is the Going Merry!
Whitebeard...
I'm so glad that I was able
to see you two again today!
Hm... There seems to be a ruckus outside.
Please stop Ace, your second
division commander.
What the hell is with his family?
And you're one of us!
Let's meet again for sure in the New World!
Grandma! The Navy is here!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Strongest Family?
Luffy's Father Revealed!"
"Thank You, Merry!
Snow Falls over the Parting Sea"
"Peace Interrupted! A Navy
Vice Admiral with a Fist of Love"
"Shanks Makes a Move!
The Linchpin to the Reckless Era!"
"Its Name Is the New World!
The Fate of the Grand Line!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!