Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
"I've decided to head to Elbaf!"
Where did the 100 million
Berries we had in here go?
So you finally found a tree to call home?
"What?! Please don't go!"
Oh, that. I gave it to them to buy meat
and booze and stuff for the party.
--What does Gonbe's "Go" mean?
--Hey, pops. Give me that water-water candy.
"I was just kidding. I know how you guys feel."
Here you go, thanks!
No one is born into this world to be alone!
Mister!
"So you're coming back, Usopp?!"
--What does Sanji's "Sa" mean?
--The barbecue last night was the best!
Gave it to them?
Well...
Yeah, you're right, Saul.
"Of course I am, silly!
--Yeah.
--And you have a good eye for food, too!
...we got a good deal with the ship,
so there's no problem, right?
Hey! Robin!
Geez, you guys must like me so much!"
Yeah, I'm a first-class cook, so... See you, then.
Oh, Nami! I'm gonna go out and have fun,
so give me some spending money.
See you later, pops!
What the hell is that idiot doing?
Don't be ridiculous!
See you!
@#$%&!!
You think you can buy a real sword
for that paltry amount of money?!
Maybe... I'll try it, too.
Ah! I see pirate ladies!
You're not getting anything!
Oh, well...
Whoa!
Yeah! Do it! Do it, Robin!
If you're not gonna buy anything, scram!
What?! Whoa!
Please don't do it, Robin-chan!
Geez...
Nami-san!
"A Girl in Search of Her Yagara!
Great Search in the City of Water!"
Please tell us how you two
joined the Straw Hat Pirates!
"Everyone Finally Has A Bounty!
A Pirate Group Worth Over 600 Million!"
At any rate...
--Robin-chan! Mellorine!
--Please tell us everything there is to
know about the beautiful female pirates!
I can't really talk about
personal things like that.
It's like a ghost town here!
Everyone's already there!
What is it?
Yokozuna! I need lumber! Hurry up!
We aren't going to get
much shopping done like this.
Yeah! I know our duty is to ensure the
train leaves safely, but I can't believe
Ribbit, ribbit!
What is it, Aobire?
What type of men do you like?
Bring me some, too!
Ribbit, ribbit!
Let's see...
that we're late for the party
held for the entire town...!
If I remember right, they're...
Nami-san might say that
"Sanji-kun is my type"...!
But... I can't... run anymore!
Was it a dream?
Please go on ahead!
--I wonder what the cook guy's doing...
--Nami-san! I love you, too!
Well, really...
Don't give up!
We're sorry that we tried to extort you!
We have to go to Paulie-san's
party no matter what!
How nice of you, Chopper. Thanks for
treating me to this water-water candy.
How would you two feel about putting
out a swimsuit photo book with us?
Seriously, those two are extraordinary.
Well, don't worry about it!
Thanks for showing me the way! Later!
What? Swimsuit?!
Just as you'd expect from Tom's Workers!
No problem! After all,
she did give me 10,000 Berries.
There's no doubt that it'll be a best seller!
What?! It's Paulie-san's?! I didn't know!
Yeah, we're barely keeping up with them.
I'll use the rest of the money
to buy medical books.
...the brats who showed me the way that time.
Hey, you. You've got some guts!
Of course it is!
It boggles the mind that they
could work at such a crazy pace.
Zoro-san! Zoro-san!
Oh, yeah?
The town is still in the
process of being restored,
Please be our big brother!
Hm?
Oh, I-I'm sorry!
And there isn't even the
slightest fault in their work.
Isn't that Straw Hat?
Huh?!
and yet Straw Hat is holding
a big party at Galley-La!
I'll cost you a fortune.
So how much can you pay?
You're right!
We're not gonna get anywhere by
just sitting here and admiring them.
Hey, everyone! Our town's hero's here!
No matter how you look at it, it's...
Huh?
Let's show them what us
Dock #1 workers are made of!
Are you serious?
--Whoa!
--Yo! Party King!
"Mothers Are Strong!
Zoro's Hectic Household Chores!"
With that girl?!
Sure, since Luffy used most
of that 100 million Berries,
Yeah!
We had fun yesterday!
That's right!
--Thank you!
--Let's do it again!
It's a wedding party!
Yeah! Leave it to me!
we need to earn money through
photo books or whatever else we can.
--I refuse.
--What?! Really?!
After Nami just got done scolding you...
Hold on a sec...
A swimsuit photo book of Nami-san
and Robin-chan would have...
Why do I have to become a
big brother to brats like you?
If that's the case, I can't
just sit around like this!
Yokozuna! Guys! Keep it up!
After all, we're important to them,
since we witnessed that precious moment...
...pics like this...
"Missing Yagara"
Now, now, don't be like that.
...and like this...
Having seen you beat marines,
we've taken quite a liking to you!
This'll do.
Anyway, the way you ate
was really something else.
What's funny?
--Am I wrong?
--You're not wrong!
Hey! What were you guys
just fantasizing about?!
Oh, I'm Michael. Glad to see you again.
Well...
We may even end up having to deliver
a congratulatory speech! Tada!
I was really admiring, Party King!
I just remembered you used to collect junk
I'm Hoichael.
Why don't we pick up where we
left off yesterday at my place today?
Whoa! This guy is the Straw Hats' cook!
and built a bunch of weird
battleships on this scrap heap island.
Around the backstreets,
we brothers are a bit famous for...
Seriously?!
What? Are you sure?
Yes, seriously!
Sanji-kun!
--If that's the case, come to my place!
--That's...
I'll do my best!
You should hear people out!
I'm gonna kill every single one of you
who just had a lewd look on your face!
You didn't like me building weapons, did you...?
Let's do our best!
--He's coming to my place first!
--If I remember correctly,
--No, my place!
--My place!
--he's the pirate who saved Iceberg-san...
Bro, we'll take you wherever you wanna go.
Yep!
Right. On top of that, they were
used to frame Tom-san as a criminal.
Now, let us go, my friend!
My place!
Wanna go buy some meat?
How about vegetables?
--My place!
--If it's him, maybe...!
--I refuse.
--You refuse? Refuse what?
Nami-san. Robin-chan.
Both becoming your big brother
and having you show me the way.
But by looking at this, I can tell...
I drove those damn noisy
flies away, so please rest easy.
Get lost already.
Abi! You left without having breakfast again!
...that your experience building those
battleships wasn't a waste at all.
Oh, yeah, that's right!
Bro, you're looking to buy a sword, right?
Thanks, Sanji-kun. Now we can
do our shopping in peace.
Yow! Entrant #9985, Sogeking!
The sword shop owner turned me down earlier,
since I don't have much money.
Ha! Is that sarcasm?
Maybe you should give up on finding Aobire!
This is my chance for a date. On top of that,
I'll be between two pretty women!
I'll sing about the pride of
the man hidden behind the mask.
I wanted to show Tom-san that
the Moron-ky from back then has...
Then you should go to a secondhand store.
I bet you'll find quite a bargain!
By the way, about today's schedule,
how does this sound?
♪ I was born on the island of snipers! ♪
Abi...
The three of us will rent a pool
Yep! We'll show our big brother
the way to the secondhand store!
With this ship, going to the New
World is no longer a pipe dream.
--Cook guy!
--and have a nice date on the water.
And then we'll go to a nice restaurant.
Yow! Yow!
This time, I'll have him eat at my place!
What?!
I guess it couldn't hurt.
--♪ I never miss my mark! Lulu lala lu! ♪
--Yow, yow, yow, yow!
Even before Tom-san...
I'm hungry!
...you can resolutely stand proud!
But let me just point out that I'm not
agreeing to become your big brother.
No! We'll have a party at my place first!
You just ate some water-water candy!
Iceberg...
Yes, sir, Bro!
--No! He'll come to my place!
--Your place is tiny!
I'm hungry! I'm hungry! I'm hungry!
I never thought those two would
work together to build a ship.
Straw Hat!
Now, make way, make way!
Hm?
Pirate Hunter Zoro-sama coming through!
Okay, then. I'll give you some money,
so you guys buy some food and go home.
Cut that out!
Ow!
I have a favor to ask!
Well...! What the hell are you doing
instead of helping me with work?!
I might go out on a date with them,
so don't be so whiny!
My family's Yagara went missing!
To think that you keep making
unstable stuff like this!
I don't wanna go home yet!
Help me find him... I mean, please!
Shut up! It's none of
your business, Stupid-berg!
Crying won't get you anywhere!
Hm?
Seriously, what's with him?!
You should just kick out an idiot like him!
Don't worry, Chimney.
Hey, that's Abi, the photographer's daughter.
Sanji-kun has a harsh tongue,
but he's very nice to women.
So she's still looking for him?
Well, don't say that. He's a fellow ship builder.
That's right. He isn't someone
who'd overlook a lady in need.
It's been three days since the Aqua Laguna.
Whoa!
His shipbuilding skills are already almost
on par with the craftsmen on the island...
They're skipping school
and wandering about again.
I feel bad, but he's probably gone.
Nami-san... Robin-chan...
Yeah.
They're gonna grow up to be
good-for-nothings. What ungrateful kids...
He was already over 100 years old.
That big wave was too...
...though what he makes is shaky.
Well, at their home,
it's rather the mother that's...
Chimney, have Sanji-kun play
with you to your heart's content.
He's just always honest, that's all.
Don't lump him with the
stupid Yagara you have!
I feel sorry for those kids.
You two will definitely become
world-class shipbuilding engineers someday.
That big wave wouldn't be
enough to take out our Aobire!
Yep!
Well, then...
Oh, no!
--What'd you say?!
--Now, now... Calm down, Abi.
You should be nice to each other.
Seriously... you're the
very example of a burden.
This is far from over!
Guys! Let's all party!
As you say, he might have
survived the Aqua Laguna,
The way things are going,
I guess it can't be helped.
it looks like we'll be able to
finish it sooner than we planned.
So... do you know a place
that serves good food?
So no luck here, either.
but he hasn't been back for
three days now, so he, um...
Iceberg, let me tell you one thing.
This isn't just another pirate ship.
Hey, what're you looking at?!
All right!
Yeah, he's right. You shouldn't
drag Straw Hat into it.
That's rude to Big Bro Zoro!
--Now, let's go.
--Okay!
I know. You've put your heart into--
You're from Water Seven,
too, so you should know
That's not what I'm saying.
Hey, isn't that swordsman who's with them
the story about Yagaras seeking out
their "final nesting village"...
"Sanji's Shock! Mysterious Old Man
and His Super Yummy Cooking!"
The Straw Hats went head-on
one of the pirates who saved Iceberg-san?
against not only Navy Headquarters,
but the World Government.
Ahhh! Shut up! Shut up!
What the heck? I thought he was a hero.
No one has seen that place,
so I'm not gonna believe it!
This is the ship they'll be traveling on.
So he's just a punk? I misjudged him.
And you, the mayor of Water Seven,
took part in building it.
Are you really sure there's a place that
serves good food in a place like this?
Aobire appeared in my dream!
You guys have got quite a reputation.
Yep! Grandma's friend is running it.
The townspeople are clueless.
He asked me to help him!
If that becomes known, you could be in trouble.
"Shanks Makes a Move!
The Linchpin to the Reckless Era"
They can say whatever they
want about us. We don't care.
Granny Kokoro's friend?
Say, Straw Hat! You pirates
love treasure, right?!
Oh, yeah? Good for you, then.
Your dishes taste good, too, but Gramps
Bang-Bang's dishes are tastier!
You do understand that, don't you?
Well then, take care.
Well...
Wh-What do you mean?
Here!
I'll think about it when the time comes.
Are you abandoning your dear little brothers?!
This is all the money I have!
If you find him, I'll give it all to you!
Besides, did you forget what Tom-san said?
Oh, is that right?
Five Elder Stars! Five Elder Stars!
Something terrible has happened!
Like I said, I don't remember
becoming your big brother!
Oh, it's right after we go down those stairs.
Oh? Did you say something?
What's the matter?
Oh? You'll give it to me?
We can't hear anything.
Seriously, that food was awful.
Franky, there's no such thing
as blueprints for a pirate ship.
That's if you find him!
Whoa! What the hell is that?!
The fleet we sent out to the New World
the other day has been defeated...
I can't believe someone
said this place was good.
You shouldn't bother, Straw Hat.
If the sailors who board a ship put up
a skull flag, then it's a pirate ship.
What is it?! What is it?!
I thought I was finally gonna have a
decent meal after getting off the ship...
If you, by any chance, come to step
into their final nesting village...
Also, Red-Haired Shanks and Edward Newgate,
aka Whitebeard, two of the Four Emperors,
If they put up a seagull flag,
then it's a Navy ship.
You, shut up!
Hey, hey...
Scary!
This way!
I don't care what you wanna build,
are finally about to make direct contact!
I don't quite get it, but it is true
that pirates can't just pass up
but a man should be resolutely
proud of the ship he built!
What?!
Hey, Gramps Bang-Bang!
Cook something for me!
treasure that's right in front of them.
All right, I shook them off.
Hey, is this drunk old man really a cook?
Bro!
What?!
I'm hungry! Wake up!
That treasure of yours...
So I...
No, Galley-La has been building ships
based on that creed all this time.
I'll make it all mine.
Oh, leave him alone.
I've got some foodstuffs, so I'll cook for you.
Really?
But to think that...
Bro!
Yeah.
This kitchen is unexpectedly well organized.
It's a deal.
...I'm giving you a hand
towards achieving your dream...
I'm Abi! Nice to meet you!
I'm hungry! I'm hungry!
Even I feel that... I'm not in my right mind.
I'm Luffy.
This is Chopper, our ship's doctor.
He uses a fanatical kitchen knife!
It's not like I asked you to
give me a hand, Stupid-berg.
Bro!
N-Nice to meet you.
It's well taken care of, too.
Bro!
Th-The little raccoon dog spoke!
Let's see...
Bro! Bro! Bro!
Oh, this is it.
Who're you calling a little raccoon dog?!
Bro!
You abandoned your real name
So... what am I supposed to find again?
and your body, too, is like that
of a completely different man.
Whoa...
Weren't you listening?!
Aobire! My family's Yagara!
But you haven't changed at all.
You're just the way you used to be.
Look!
You'll know it's him by the blue fin on his head.
My dream... Huh...
We know this town like the back of our hands.
His fin is blue, so his name is Aobire, huh?
I like it. It's easy to understand.
Give Tom-san back to us!
There's no way you can get away from us.
Shanks?!
Old man! Old man!
All right, then! Leave it to me!
Shut up! Stop mocking me, you brats!
Stop! Sea train!
Sorry, gramps! I'm borrowing your kitchen.
Red Hair wants to see you!
Go! Go!
Good morning, Gramps Bang-Bang!
Yeah... Let him come aboard.
That's harsh, Bro!
Tom-san...
And why are we starting our search here?!
Hey, where'd you learn how
to use that kitchen knife?
Don't call me "Bro"!
I don't wanna build ships anymore!
That brat better have brought good booze.
I can't love ships that hurt
the people I really care about!
Ah, at a restaurant I used
to work at called Baratie.
Why not? This is the best place to
look out over the city, don't you think?
Who the hell are you?
Just what do you think
you're doing, hitting my kids?
"Navy"
But, Tom-san...
Here you go. It's done.
Is it true that the fleet has been defeated?
"My kids"? Then...
All right! Thanks!
...you're my goal after all!
I-I'm scared!
Yeah, it seems like it.
Go back to town already!
What strength! What's with this woman?!
Yummy!
Well, hold on.
So Red Hair and Whitebeard will be in contact?
Oh?
Are you Zeff's apprentice?
That's Zoro.
Hey, Zoro! I'm here!
I'm right here! Can't you hear me?!
Attention!
Oh? Not bad, lad.
What?! You know that damn geezer, gramps?!
Listen up! We don't know
what will happen next!
Hey, it's shaking!
Then... Special Attack! Bam-Bam Tornado!
There's no way he can hear you!
So I want you to come back
and teach me again...
Stand by on maximum alert!
Besides me, that lad Zeff is the only
one who uses that kitchen knife.
We're gonna fall!
Huh?
Yes, sir!
Destination straight ahead! Furl the sails!
"Lad"?! That damn geezer used
to be the captain of a pirate group!
Stop it, Mom! He didn't do anything wrong!
It was all our fault!
Ha! From my perspective, everyone's a lad!
...because I want to...
You guys were misbehaving again?! You idiots!
...build a dream ship someday, too.
That was dangerous!
So, what're you doing in Water Seven?
Ow!
You are dangerous!
A ship that resolutely and proudly traverses
Get your act together!
Were you kicked out of Zeff's restaurant?
even uncharted waves at edges of the earth!
It's not like that. I left there
in order to go to the All Blue.
Sorry about that.
A dream ship like that!
But I guess it's okay, right,
since you became their big brother?
How about this one, Robin?
Captain! Red Hair is here!
That's nice! It looks good on you.
All Blue, you said?
No, I didn't.
Oh?
Red Hair is coming.
Yeah, a legendary sea that's said to
have the world's best foodstuffs...
--Hey! Nami! Robin!
--Not again!
You guys, come out and say hello.
This bites... My body... is on fire.
--Hey!
--Oh...
Greenhorns oughta stay back...
I'm Yoko.
It's a miracle sea.
Oh, that's right. If we ask Robin...
I'm Yuuya.
...unless you wanna get knocked out.
I became a pirate in order to go there.
--I'm Shou.
--I'm Ayako.
So I'm still alive.
Knocked out?! What're you talking about?
I'm Akihiro.
A Yagara with a blue fin on his head, huh?
But I wonder if I'll die like this...
Guys, this is Big Bro Zoro!
Just go to the back and stay there.
Yeah, I get it. You, too, are gonna
tell me that sea is just a legend, right?
Okay. I'll try.
He's our new oldest brother!
Ah!
Oldest brother...? Don't tell me you
want me to be your big brother for real?
Ojos Fleur!
The All Blue does exist.
Come with us. We're behind
with our household chores,
Hey, guys, what's the matter?!
It's a sea that any skilled cook
would dream of visiting at least once.
What's going on?!
since we've had to spend a lot of time
repairing our house after Aqua Laguna.
Oh... I guess it's already too late.
But it's definitely a place one can't
reach with halfhearted determination.
Huh?!
Bro! Bro!
I see no one on board.
--Hey, guys! Say something! Hey!
--Don't make a fuss!
Hey, wait! I didn't agree to this!
Let go of me! Hey!
An abandoned ship, huh?
Many cooks have taken up
the challenge to go there
They've just been knocked
unconscious, that's all.
Robin, did you find him?
Scrap wood... Scrap iron...
but ended up giving up on their dreams
without ever seeing that miracle.
Now, let's go home, kids!
Those who lack the mettle can't even
stay conscious in front of that man.
Yeah!
I'm sorry, but I can't find him.
This place makes me... feel quite at home.
It's a cruel sea.
I see. Thanks anyway.
Good heavens...!
Let's go, Abi.
So it really isn't just a legend?!
I have to do something
about my disabled body first.
As always...
Abi!
Could it possibly be... that you've
been to the All Blue, gramps?!
Later, Robin.
...he's got an incredibly strong Haki...
Okay.
--Nope.
--You haven't?!
Well... anyway, what's up with
that funny looking body of yours?
By the way, what's that?
What I was watching just now
was a picture from my early days!
I was really shocked!
When Mom is out working,
we go pick up scrap wood at the harbor
Thanks to Robin, we now know that
he isn't on the shipbuilding island.
Shut up! Since my whole
body became of no use,
Don't act misleading!
Geez, what a cheeky old man.
while we're babysitting our siblings,
and once we get enough wood,
we go sell it to Galley-La on the weekend.
Pardon me... for the bit of intimidation
I gave off, since I'm on an enemy ship.
I rebuilt my body using iron
scraps and escaped death!
The good news is that it saved us some time.
Hm? I ran out of booze.
We can make quite a bit of
allowance money that way.
Say, Abi. Can I ask you a question?
We never change, huh?
Thank you! That was good!
Whenever I see your face,
the scar that guy gave me throbs.
What is it?
Whenever we meet face to face,
we yell at each other.
Well then, say goodbye to your mom for me.
What is the final nesting village that
the townspeople were talking about?
Are you really leaving?
I still won't forgive you... and you
may feel the same about me, too.
Sorry, but this has nothing to do with me, so...
"Alcohol"
I brought some healing spirits with me.
It is said that when Yagaras realize
their lives are about to end,
This is in return for you letting
me use your cooking tools.
Watch out!
I don't intend to fight.
There's something I want to discuss with you.
Franky... I'm... really...
they leave their groups or their owners
and go to a certain place to die.
Thanks!
Says the man who shows up
throwing his Haki around?
Hey, we're going back now.
--Geez...
--Nice babysitting!
What? I wanna eat more.
That's the final nesting village.
You fool.
Bro!
...glad that... you're alive.
I see...
You guys have been eating too much!
--But...
--But?
Hey, Red Hair! What'd you do that for?
...if humans see this final nesting village...
Well, wait, lad.
As thanks for the booze,
eat my food before you go.
Not bad at all.
If they see it...?
Oh, you're Marco of the first division, right?
Just as I thought, you're good with babies!
Oh, don't worry about it.
...they'll also be taken to the netherworld!
The hell with "I'm glad that you're alive"!
I wanna eat it!
Why don't you join my gang?
Just because I'm alive, he ended up
helping me achieve my dream.
Nooo!
Whoa! He wet himself!
Shut up!
You're still young. Don't be so modest.
It's just a superstition!
There's no need to worry!
Hey, are you okay?
Give him to me.
Old man, what should we...
Lad, say that line after
you see my cooking skill...
You're quite an idiot, too, Iceberg.
Oh, hey, captain! Do you need
a sniper for your pirate group?
Go change his diaper.
Yeah, looks like there won't
be a battle. Leave us alone.
Okay!
H-Hey! What're you doing?!
What are you, a perv?!
See, what did I tell you?
We're gonna wash it. Wear this until it's dried.
Oh, yeah, we've got a good doctor,
so I'll introduce you to...
"Whoa, Luffy! What a coincidence
to see you in a place like this!
This humble, flattering plan isn't that good.
You fixed it yourself?!
I was just taking a stroll...
but, well, this must just be fate.
Wh-What the hell is this?!
Is there something else...?
Oops!
Take care of him, okay?
What can you do? I'll come
back and rejoin the gang!"
Okay, kids! Let's work hard
and clean up the house!
Whoa! I got a bite!
Is this old man serious?
This booze is from the West Blue...
Oof! I'm not gonna let you escape!
This is the cheap stuff, isn't it?
Yeah!
So this is pattern 53.
Having traveled around the world,
I give up.
But not being able to use it
unless they find me is a flaw.
Aobire! Where are you?!
I find nothing's better than the booze
made from the water I grew up with.
He isn't around here.
Let's go check the backstreets, shall we?
Hey, Hoichael. Sorry, but I...
In that case, I should take
some initiative myself.
It's booze from my hometown.
Okay.
Please try it.
Hey, gramps, you don't have to
push yourself. If you like, I can...
Yep! That's what I'll do!
I thought I was a goner.
Don't panic, lad!
Hey, hey... Hey!
H-Huh? Me?
Stop it!
Hey, Luffy!
Sit there quietly and watch!
Hey, Michael! Do something about these...
I found someone who heard Aobire's voice!
Okay, okay, I got it, I'll watch.
Not too bad.
Uh-huh, uh-huh...
Roger, Garp, Sengoku...
Stop!
So on the night of the Aqua Laguna,
you heard someone around here say,
There aren't that many people
left who know about that era.
Hey, hey, his hand's shaking...
"I'm coming to rescue you, so hang in there"?
What? Why are they all looking so serious?
It's been 22 years. That's just natural.
It seems that the Straw Hats
really have become edgy
Hey, he's cutting them in a way
that makes use of his shaking hand.
He says it was definitely
Grandpa Aobire's voice.
and lost their cohesiveness without me.
You sure have worked your way up the ladder.
--Abi!
--Yeah! Thank you, little guy!
Okay, then, for everyone's sake, I'll...!
You were just a young apprentice
on Gol D. Roger's ship.
Pattern 34!
It's incredible that you
understand the Yagara's language!
Hey! Where do I put these...
"Ah-choo! Ah-choo!
Geez, that night breeze is cold!"
Since we were fighting Roger's
gang all the time back then,
Oh, stop it! I'm not a "little guy," you jerk!
you and I got acquainted in an unusual way.
Now that we know that, let's thoroughly
search this area, shall we?!
You're quite a natural at this. Keep it up.
I'd sneeze loudly so that they'd hear me.
There you are, Whitebeard!
Yep, they're coming.
Yeah!
Hm? He's adept for a drunk person.
Now we've found you!
You can't escape anymore!
This is the crucial moment. I definitely
have to act like this is a coincidence.
We're gonna dye that beard of yours blood red!
Go!
"Oh, is that you over there, Usopp?"
Hey, my nose isn't blood red!
Hey, you're gonna fall.
Okay, be good, you guys.
"Well, I just happened to be passing by."
"You shouldn't stay outside, you'll catch cold.
Has that funny Red-nose who was
with you kicked the bucket yet?
Here you go!
Come inside and have something warm."
Yaay!
Hey, lady. I'm going back now.
Give me my shirt back.
"Oh, yeah? Well, I know
exactly how you guys feel.
Oh, Buggy? That brings back memories.
Thank you!
It tickles!
After all, you need me, right?
We parted in Loguetown
What're you talking about?
I'm looking all over for him, and yet, why...
Yummy!
on the day our captain was executed,
and I haven't seen him since.
Let's let bygones be bygones!
Do you even have a place to
go back to besides this house?
He was indeed adept, but...
I'm back!"
Yeah. My friends are waiting for me.
...any way you look at it,
it's just plain old fried rice.
Oh, they're going to bed?
Come with me, Buggy!
How stupid! Friends or family--
which one's more important?
What's the matter, lad?
Aren't you gonna eat it?
I refuse to be your subordinate, you moron!
I'm not your family. I don't
remember you giving birth to me,
I have a policy of eating everything
served to me. So I'll gratefully eat it.
The new ship is coming
together quickly, and I haven't yet...
I heard that he's still a pirate.
and we're not blood-related, either.
Shut up! The hell with blood relationships!
How is it? Is it warm?
I need to somehow rejoin the gang.
Whoa! Watch out! Not that direction, Aobire!
To me, the time seemed to flash by.
Are blood relationships that important?!
All right, now that it's come to this,
I'll come up with more patterns!
This is super damn good!
Many pass down stories about the days when
you and Hawk-Eye used to duel like legends,
Dad, is it true that Aobire can't see?
The way he cooked was nothing special.
No difference in the foodstuffs, either.
We're gonna settle this today for sure.
Yeah, he's an old Yagara who
turned 100 a long time ago.
And yet, why is this flavor so deep?!
but those days seem like yesterday to me.
Get lost.
Bro! I brought some food and drinks!
I came here yesterday and the day before,
but you didn't pay us back, you bitch!
It's damn good!
When someone of your caliber lost
one of his arms in the East Blue,
For you Galley-La guys, too! Take a little break!
I was told that there's no chance
that his sight will come back.
What, was it so good that
it made you shake, lad?
Hm? Who are you?
We brought you cold cola, Bro!
Oh, no...
I feel like I've seen you somewhere before.
Another new family member?
Aobire has been serving our
family very well for generations.
everyone was surprised.
We chilled them good!
Thanks! It was yummy!
--That's right.
--No.
--Which is it?!
S-Something like that.
What enemy did you give your left arm to?
Yaay! I was pretty hungry!
But we can no longer deny
the decline in his strength.
I guess it doesn't matter.
So do you know why it was so good?
Anyway, it's not like you're
Paulie from Galley-La.
We should start preparing ourselves...
Quit dragging your feet
and pay us back, you old hag!
Of course, you brought some
of this stuff, too, right?
No, I don't.
Like I told you before, I already
paid back what I borrowed!
But... I don't know how
best to explain it to Abi.
This...?
It seems you're somewhat
confident in your ability,
Iceberg-san! Franky!
Go ahead and take a break.
You fool. Debts come with interest.
I wasn't gonna take you anyway!
but if you can't figure out something like that,
You guys have been working
without eating or drinking.
That interest also accrued more interest,
You'll never be a pirate!
the All Blue will just be
an unfulfilled dream for you.
so it's now several dozen times more
than the amount you borrowed!
There's no way you can keep on going like that!
I will too!
Yeah, we can take a break later!
That's none of my concern.
Why don't you pay it yourself?!
Someday, I'm gonna gather a crew
every bit as good as yours,
Chimney! Gonbe!
Well... then I'll take you up on that offer.
What'd you say, you damn old hag?!
and I'm gonna find the greatest
treasure in the world,
No! Aobire's coming, too!
Stay here for a bit, will you?
I guess it's not a bad idea for me
to replenish cola and power up.
and I'm gonna be King of
the Pirates! I'll show you!
Sure.
We can't take him to the evacuation facility.
I'm not telling you to suffer all by yourself.
I'm gonna reveal the secret of gramps' flavor!
We do this every year. You should know that.
If you work those brats hard,
you can earn money easily.
I bet it... on a new era.
Replenishment completed! Super... Franky!
No, no!
They're not your real family anyway, right?
--Yeah, he is!
--Yeah!
What'd you say?!
What?!
It's not how he cooks or the foodstuffs he uses.
Fine, as long as you have no regrets.
Franky, what're you going to do
once the ship is completed?
In that case, that's the only decisive factor!
Hm?
Whitebeard...
Our house is in the center of the city.
Come to think of it...
There's no way he'll be swallowed
by the Aqua Laguna, Abi.
I've experienced many battles
and received many scars,
What am I gonna do?
Once you hand the ship over to the Straw Hats,
...they don't look alike at all.
are you going to be satisfied?
Aobire...
but the scar that throbs right now is this one.
Does that mean you've achieved your dream?
That hurt! What're you doing, you old hag?!
You like those guys, right?
Just say that one more time,
and I'll blow your head off!
Aobire!
Get her!
Like I told you so many times,
I wonder if he really was
swallowed by the Aqua Laguna...
I have no intention whatsoever
of leaving this island.
Oh, hey! You're the cook guy in the
Straw Hats. Looking for something?
I see...
Or...
Bro...
Well... I'll let you off the hook for today.
No fish would drown.
Pops! Are these all the condiments you've got?
Guys, let's go!
Now, I'm gonna go back to work!
Yeah. Our product lineup is the best!
This wasn't a wound from an adventure
or one received from Hawk-Eye.
He asked you to help him, right?
Yokozuna, you sit back and relax for a while.
You won't get away with this!
Then you shouldn't give up!
Ribbit.
This isn't it.
--Cool!
--Just as we'd expect from you, bro!
He's right, Abi.
Paulie, it's you guys' turn now.
Good boy. Mom's proud of you.
The one who gave me this scar
was one of your men...
You can cry later.
This isn't it, either.
--"Good boy"...?
--Okay, kids!
Pops! Don't you have other stuff?!
Let's go shopping for dinner, shall we?!
Blackbeard Teach.
Other stuff, huh?
Yeah!
I'm not crying!
Since Water Seven is a city of trade,
Well then, I'll get going now.
our store has all sorts of condiments
from around the world, so...
Ah, I see.
I didn't let my guard down.
When we're so exhausted that we
can't even manage a late-night snack...
All right, then! We know the
area we should be searching.
Hurry up. You're coming, too.
Do you get what I want to say, Whitebeard?
Dammit... Is it a condiment
that gramps mixed himself?
Let's check it one more time.
Those two are the very
definition of inexhaustible.
Hm?
He was quietly waiting for the right moment.
No, it's more fundamental...
Ugh! Dammit! I can't figure it out!
Indeed...
Hang in there, Bro!
He didn't become a
commander or make his name.
What's this?
You got a job for me?
Let's have a party once the ship is completed!
Oh? Sanji-kun!
Ah!
He kept his true self hidden
This is Aobire's...!
That's strange. He didn't notice us.
and stood in the shadow of the
great pirate Whitebeard all this time.
I'm looking forward to it!
Yeah, me too!
Wrong person?
Did it come from there?
Must be--Chimney and Gonbe
weren't with that guy, either.
And now, he's gained power
and started to make his move.
That's an entrance to the
underground waterways!
In the end, he'll aim for the top.
It was a short time, but I had fun with you guys.
Hm? I've come this far?
This is the place!
With his own will...
This area took quite a bit
of damage from Aqua Laguna.
...he'll eventually come
to take even your position.
We're gonna rescue you for sure!
That's Galley-La's restoration team.
I finally met someone worthy
of entrusting with my dream.
Oh? You're one of the Straw Hats!
What do you want me to do?
That's what you came to talk about, right?
Pops, knock the price down a bit more!
Thanks for the food yesterday!
I couldn't be happier.
Who do you think you're dealing with?!
Don't take us lightly!
Hey, guys! Have a little break! Let's have lunch!
As I promised, I'm gonna build an amazing ship!
Please stop Ace!
Knock it off.
Just wait, Straw Hat!
Dammit! However you look at it,
this doesn't make sense.
Okay!
Although he's young, you made him
your second division commander.
Whoa! That's what I've been waiting for!
--Hey! Aobire!
--Say something!
Bro...
Why do I have to do things like this?!
--Where are you?!
--Aobire!
If they see me like this...
--Hey!
--Aobire!
Ace is strong!
Yummy!
I know that much.
Hey, would you like one, too?
--Hey!
You dummy. It's rude to offer a plain
salted rice ball to the Straw Hats' cook.
Shoot!
Of all people, it had to be that damn cook...!
I guess you're right!
So that alley over there is a shortcut? Thanks.
No, I'll have one, too.
Thinking made me hungry.
But that fame and trust
make the matter complicated.
Oh, then don't stop at one.
Eat as many as you want!
What's wrong?
It's still too soon to have those two fight.
H-Hm?
Seriously...
The water is...
Thanks.
Stay away from Blackbeard Teach!
At any rate, you guys astounded us.
We can't go any farther on the Yagara like this.
You outwitted Navy Headquarters.
That's incredible!
That's all I want to ask.
Now that I've come this far...
There's no water ahead of here.
In any case, let's try moving ahead.
Yeah.
Hey, cook guy! What's wrong?! Are you okay?!
You stay here and wait for us, okay?
The old man's laughing?
See you later.
Iceberg! Why don't you take it
easy and get some sleep, too?!
That darn Gramps Bang-Bang!
To think you'd talk to me like that...
That snot-nosed brat sure did grow a pair.
I hope he wasn't so drunk that he
put weird stuff in the rice balls!
Why don't you do that?!
Seriously... I'm exhausted.
Sorry, but I'm feeling super energetic!
His crime was killing one of his crewmates.
What?! Gramps Bang-Bang?!
Seems like you're having a rough time.
That's the worst sin you
can commit on a pirate ship.
What's this? There's a town
underneath the town.
Did that old man make these rice balls?!
Sorry, me too!
Yeah, tell me about it.
How could this be happening to...
What's going on?
They're compliments of that gramps!
If you have complaints, talk to him!
He broke the golden rule.
My dad told me once that they built
new buildings above the old ones
It's you?!
I get it now! I finally get what
the secret of his flavor is!
Once I let them board my ship,
Are you watching this, Tom-san?
they are all my sons,
no matter how foolish they are.
and kept doing that.
--Dammit!
--Robin!
You were called a legendary shipwright.
I appreciate this a damn lot. So, this is it!
Huh? Where did she go?
I see...
Where can my killed son's soul go?
Looks like your skills and spirit were
passed down to your disciples splendidly.
Thanks!
Y-Yeah.
Robin!
It's my responsibility to show that idiot Teach
There.
Hm? What's that light?
that you can't make your way in the
world if you lack a moral code, right?!
Don't worry. I won't tell anyone.
Shhh.
Oh, and... that look suits you.
Gramps!
H-Hey! Abi!
A log has been stored!
I got it, gramps.
I'm sure he's there!
The Log Pose is pointing to the next island!
Oh, it's you.
You got that, you idiot?!
Welcome back, cook guy!
Then, all we need now is the ship!
I'm looking forward to it!
It's 100 years too soon to tell me what to do.
I'll see him soon!
Gramps, the decisive factor of your
flavor isn't some special ingredient.
Yeah. He told us not to come until it's
done because he wants to surprise us.
I'll see Aobire!
I've had enough! I'm going back!
Well, it's actually one of the
most basic ingredients... salt.
Oh? You're going home ahead of us?
Do you guys know where
following that log will take you?
Then I'll give you the key to the house.
Clean the restroom or something.
What's this?!
I heard you're the one who gave those
salted rice balls to the Galley-La guys.
No! I'm not going back to your house!
I'm going back to my friends!
No. Where is it?
It somehow looks like it's
pointing a little downwards.
You didn't?
No one will be able to stop...
Don't speak nonsense!
Hm? Well, it's true. But that's
not the right answer yet.
You're the one who's speaking nonsense!
...this reckless era!
Of course it is. The next island
is a paradise on the seabed...
Don't speak like that to your mother!
The thing is that this salt is
unlike any I've ever used before.
It's nothing to fear!
You're not my mother!
I'm Whitebeard!
Fishman Island!
Shut up, you Broccoli Head!
It's not Broccoli Head! It's Moss Head!
It isn't simply salty like regular salt is.
It has a deep flavor.
Ah, Moss Head...
I-I can't breathe!
I see, Moss Head.
How are you able to get such
a special salt on this island?
Yep, yep.
Right? Hey, no! That's not what I meant!
Help...! Help!
What?! F-F-Fishman Island?!
The answer is...
Well then, bye.
Aobire!
Finally?!
R-Red Hair, that bastard!
What's he doing to the old man?!
...Aqua Laguna.
What?! What's wrong, Sanji?!
Aqua Laguna is a detestable
and hated existence.
Hold on. He's not the type
to pull a stupid stunt.
Fishman Island, huh?
I have mixed feelings about it.
What am I gonna do with my oldest son?
But it brings special seawater
that contains plentiful sea minerals.
Yeah, it reminds us of what
happened in your village.
Michael, Hoichael. Go get him later.
But whatever discussion they
had seems to have fallen apart.
Okay!
Well then, let's go home.
The salt made from that
seawater is a special salt
Look above.
Okay!
But even though they were fishmen,
they were pirates, right?
The clouds have... No, the sky has been split!
that contains plentiful sea minerals.
I'm alive...
Sorry about earlier.
You're exactly right, though you're stupid,
you damn jerk! I'm impressed!
Luffy! Little guy! Are you guys okay?!
That's the answer!
Looks like your bodyguard is gone,
so I'd like to continue our discussion.
Correct! I've lost!
Fishman Island is a famous
place in the Grand Line.
Ahhh...!
Could you come with me for a bit?
Beautiful mermaids draw arcs
over the water and play with fish.
Geez... Give it to me.
But, gramps, in order to make salt,
you need a large amount of seawater.
Hoichael, go get Bro.
I bet they'll take us to that place.
Good!
It's nearly impossible to
collect seawater in that storm.
It's a dream kingdom!
Okay.
Hey!
Wh-What's this place?
Is that right? That's amazing!
Look! I got today's newspaper!
There's gotta be a special way to do it.
Gramps, I'm responsible
for cooking for the gang.
It's talking about Enies Lobby!
S-So it's finally in the news?!
Hey, what's it saying?!
I want to serve the best food
to the crew at all times.
Can't I be allowed to dream?! I'm a pirate!
It's an article that'll determine our fate!
I know it's a special salt.
They do have young ones there!
But please give me some of your salt!
--Well...
--W-Well?
But it's not easy to get to this paradise.
It's not...
Say, lad...
...talking about us at all.
What's the matter, Abi?
I'm concerned about it being on the seabed.
Today is another fine day, isn't it...?
Ahhh!
Luffy... Aobire is here.
Huh? Y-Yeah.
Well, we'll see once we go there.
I knew it! We have no choice
but to leave this island!
I'm not your family. I don't
remember you giving birth to me,
We've been having sunny days
since the Aqua Laguna ebbed.
That's not the problem.
This is the same place that I saw in my dream!
Take a look at the front page.
It's a recent newspaper.
Don't tell me... this is the final nesting village?!
and we're not blood-related, either.
Wait, what?! It's not talking about us?
There's a place I wanna go.
Would you take me there?
Shut up! The hell with blood relationships!
R-Really?!
What's this?
That can't be right! The final
nesting village is a superstition!
--Yeah!
--Not at all?! Is that possible?!
Are blood relationships that important?!
A place you wanna go?
"Fourteen more ships have
disappeared this month."
There's no mistake about it!
Don't talk like Aobire is dead!
All right! I thought we had to
live life on the run! I'm so glad!
Lad, go up to one of the rooftops around here.
Bro!
What does this mean?
That's just a story created to
explain mysteries about the Yagaras!
The Devil's Triangle,
also known as the Florian Triangle.
Bro, there's trouble!
Rooftop?
The debt collector took our mom away!
Gramps, is this place okay?
What?
What's the deal, when the Franky
Family went on such a rampage?
Yeah.
You can't reach paradise without
passing through that area.
Sorry, but it has nothing to do with me.
And that lady can take care of herself.
Oh, it's ready!
Maybe your grandpa spun
the information by saying
Ready? You mean salt?
But this time, he brought a bunch of his buddies
that they were regular people
who got dragged into the incident?
I see only roofs around here.
In that sea, more than 100
ships go missing every year.
and took Michael and my siblings away, too!
Take a closer look.
Good! So you were there!
What?!
This area...
Well, I don't think he'd even think of that.
Aobire! Come here! Let's go home together!
And after they go missing, sometimes
the ships will show up with no crew,
I don't think he would, either.
...gets submerged all the way up
to the rooftops during Aqua Laguna.
And after Aqua Laguna ebbs,
and increasingly, people are seeing
ghost ships with a dead crew on them.
Chopper!
the seawater on the roof
gets completely evaporated.
I bet it's Aokiji who did it.
He's hard to figure out.
He says, "I'm sorry, Abi."
You sure got cocky with me before.
Why are you apologizing?!
I wanted to see you all this time!
At any rate, that's good news.
And then, what's left is this.
Ghosts?! That's scary!
We're pirates, but they're not.
As thanks for that, I brought
some scary guys with me.
If they had to live life on the run
from here on out, I'd feel bad.
I see! The salt of Aqua Laguna!
We can meet skeletons that are alive?!
Don't be scared out of your wits!
We're not mad about
your sudden disappearance.
What kind of imagination do you have?
Hold on a sec... Does that mean...
Instead, they wrote terrible things about us.
Sir! Please come here!
Forget that! Let's go home together!
...that all the roofs around here are like that?!
No! I definitely don't wanna encounter them!
I don't wanna even see them!
According to this, we declared
war on the World Government.
That's right. All the roofs around here
have finished making salt by now.
What?
Such creepy ships!
Even burning down the island
was our doing, it says.
What's he saying?
What happens in that sea?
Er... Yeah...
Take as much as you want.
Looks like our bounties will go up again.
He says he can't do that.
Beats me.
This is more than enough!
Why?!
Those who encounter trouble
never come back, so I don't know.
Whoa!
This is the captain of the
Big Helmet Pirate Gang, Mikazuki-san.
Lad, the salt of Aqua Laguna is
different from the salt from any sea.
D-Do you think I'll get a bounty, too?!
He's got a 36-million-Berry bounty on his head.
"Now I can feel at ease."
Well, it's not impossible...
It's a dark sea with deep fog. So be careful.
There are still unknown seas in the world.
Kids, stay back. Don't do anything, got that?
...but I'm the one who's gonna be in trouble.
Ahem.
The All Blue...
Nooo!
Mikazuki-san has a vicious past.
He tried to walk out of Dock #1
Anyway, it's a dangerous sea
where lots of disasters happen.
"Thanks for everything."
at Galley-La without paying
for the repair of his ship...
"A superstar appears."
No! Don't go!
Make sure you are well
prepared before you set sail.
Whoa, that's quite a bit of salt you collected.
...although he was regrettably
defeated by Galley-La's foremen.
Why are you guys happy about it?!
Are you stupid or what?!
Is that all salt?!
Hence, in order to earn money for the repairs,
Along with the stories about ghost ships--
he's been earnestly working
part-time at our company and...
Our journey has still a long way to go, so...
in other words, wrecked trading
ships and pirate ships--there are...
By the way, gramps, when we got here,
two guys came out complaining.
Well, you guys, think hard...
...legends of treasure ships, right?
...about which is better--hurrying up
and paying so you can survive,
Let's find ghost ships!
Bro, Iceberg is here.
Seriously, that food was awful.
or defying me and becoming prey for my sword.
Leave it to me!
He's here.
What?! I don't want to!
Oh, those guys... It's about time...
Working hard, Franky?
Aobire!
No! Aobire!
I'll give you five seconds to think it over.
--Ribbit!
--Hm? What're you doing here?
If the worry's just about getting lost,
don't worry, as we'll have plenty of food.
Hey, gramps!
We were always together!
Let us have the same food we had earlier.
Well, so what, you don't want
help from the likes of me?
Oh? You wanna fight with me,
the great Mikazuki-sama?
Treasure ships, huh? I wonder
if they have swords, too.
I'm coming with you to the final nesting village!
Well, I thought the food tasted awful at first,
What a fool. As mentioned already,
my bounty is 36 million Berries, and...
Pirate guys!
but now I've got a craving to eat it again.
Ha! Can you keep up with my ship design?
Straw Hat!
Gramps, what's going on?
Bang-Bang Tornado!
I served them herbal medicine food.
Go, Mom!
How about you? Do you still have the
skills after doing demolition for so long?
What brought you guys here?
Sailors can't eat good food on the ship,
so their taste buds don't work well,
Let go of me!
An attack like that won't work on me!
Big Bro Franky asked us to bring you guys!
Show me the blueprints.
but once the herbs' effect kicks in,
food starts tasting good.
Everyone from Tom's Workers is here, huh?
The dream ship has been completed!
Do you know where they took them to?
They always take people to the
same place. We've seen it before.
You guys don't have to build a ship
in a place like this, you know.
I somehow feel spry, too.
They built an incredible ship!
Gramps, please, we're starving here!
Dammit!
I heard that it's a ship for the Straw Hats!
What?! It's already done?!
That was really quick!
Gramps, why do you stay in
Water Seven when you're so skilled?
Is there something we can do to help?!
Five top-notch shipwrights
worked on it day and night!
It's not good if you rush through it all
by yourself and do a sloppy job, so...
Don't take a man with a
36-million bounty lightly!
Well... You guys don't have
to work on the backstreets?
Because I can't get away
from that salt anymore.
Yeah, they did!
All right! Let's head there right away!
Aobire!
I see... but gramps,
when I come here next time,
Yeah!
I told you kids to stay back!
Don't do anything dangerous!
The others said that since they
couldn't come, at least we should go help,
Straw Hat...!
Straw Hat!
I'll tell you the stories about
my experience in the All Blue.
if he was working on a
replacement for that pirate ship.
What're you saying, Mom?! We're a family!
Franky Family...
What is this?!
Oh, yeah? I'll be looking forward to it.
What's a family for if we
don't help each other?!
You guys are all...
What're you guys running that
frantically for? You're out of breath.
Gramps!
What a sassy thing to say, you stupid son.
What a nice story...
Is your stall open, gramps?
It is.
Bro! Over there!
Whoa! You ladies can eat free!
Don't stand in my way, okay?!
To tell you the truth, we came
to ask you a huge favor.
You're so wonderful!
Ladies in Water Seven really are the best!
Guys, teach them a lesson
they won't soon forget.
Did you see the wanted posters?!
All right! We'll show you
the skills of those at Dock #1!
Wanted posters?
Straw Hat, the bounty on
your head has gotten crazy!
Isn't that the real reason, you dirty old man?!
And all the others, too, are wanted in addition!
--What's that?
--A Yagara's voice...?
Cook guy, thanks for today. I had fun!
Huh?! What?!
Me, too?! All right!
Franky's building a ship for us?!
It's me who should be saying thanks.
Thanks to you guys...
Me, too...?!
Me, too?!
Oh, that's right. You were sleeping.
Instead of having me explain,
just take a look at these.
--Huh?
--No, nothing.
All right! I'm glad to hear that!
All seven of you now have
bounties on your heads!
Mom!
Oh, then, he's a nice guy after all!
Well then, we're gonna
go back to Grandma now!
--He's a nice guy! Yep, he's a nice guy!
--I'm looking forward to seeing the new ship!
--He's a nice guy!
--Well then, why don't I go
out shopping while we wait?
Yeah! Be careful!
Straw Hat Luffy, 300-million-Berry bounty.
His heartbeat is weak...
Bro!
You small fry...
So when will that ship be finished?
...but I think he'll be able to pull through.
Hm?
Seventy-two Pound Phoenix!
Looks like the scarf kept him
warm and helped him survive!
All right! It went up!
When he came by yesterday,
he said he needed five days.
Usopp?
Die!
Pirate Hunter Zoro, 120-million-Berry bounty.
So, four more days.
"What, Luffy? Now you're
saying that you want me back?
Th-That's the scarf that I gave to Aobire...
I can't wait!
D-Dammit!
Seriously, what will I do with you guys?
Cat Burglar Nami, 16-million-Berry bounty.
"I'll rescue you now, so hang in there!"
You can't do anything without me.
Oh, no...
That's a strange dance.
So Aobire tried to save him...!
Well, all right, if you're so insistent,
I suppose I could come back."
--Incredible!
--Just as we'd expect from you, bro!
Cotton Candy Lover Chopper,
the gang's pet, 50-Berry bounty.
Do you call that a dance?
Yeah! Amazing!
Yeah, it's best if I can make it
so that they'll ask me to rejoin.
All right! Good job! That's my oldest son!
Fifty...?
Devil's Child Nico Robin,
80-million-Berry bounty.
You're still saying that? Hey, lady. Listen to me.
So this is pattern 23.
That's why he appeared in my dream...
"Oh, hey, Chopper. It's a fine day today.
Let's go fishing or something."
Now, to start with, I...
Where did the 100 million
Berries we had in here go?
Are your friends as good as our family?
Oh, that. I gave it to them to buy meat
and booze and stuff for the party.
"Hey, Luffy! Wanna come along?"
Who's this...?
This one's good, too. Operation
Act Like Nothing Happened... Or...
Yeah, they're like that.
Black Foot Sanji, failed to obtain
a picture, 77-million-Berry bounty.
Then why didn't you tell me sooner?!
Gave it to them? It was our money!
I told you a bunch of times!
"I've decided to head to Elbaf!"
It was our party, wasn't it?
"What?! Please don't go!"
Hey, Sogeking's got a bounty, too.
"I was just kidding. I know how you guys feel."
Fifty...?
Hey! We don't have much left!
W-Well, we sympathize with you, or well...
You're a member of our precious family,
"So you're coming back, Usopp?!"
Yeah, I can imagine! In the end,
everyone in town showed up!
Here!
but, well, if you're gonna run away
from home for a bit, I won't stop you.
I'm sure you wanna say all sorts
of things, but, well... please wait.
That's okay. I couldn't keep my promise, so...
"Of course I am, silly!
"Run away from home"?
It was a real blast!
No...
Geez, you guys must like me so much!"
The favor we're talking about
has something to do with this!
Take care of yourself.
Thank you, Luffy.
Bro, congrats on running away from home!
Please take a look at this!
Franky!
Thanks to you two,
I was able to see Aobire again.
What the hell is that idiot doing?
You should go now before
Mom changes her mind.
Cyborg Franky, 44-million-Berry bounty.
Well...
See you later!
I was very glad!
...we got a good deal with the ship,
so there's no problem, right?
Well then, bye.
Food's ready!
Also...
Oh, no! Bro's got a bounty on his head!
Whoa!
...I was able to grant his last wish...
Bye-bye, bro!
I wanted to get gorgeous furniture for the ship.
Yummy! Today's food is especially yummy!
Oh, no!
--Take care!
--Bro!
I was able to save this baby Yagara, so...
That's right. We somehow
were able to get off the hook,
--Thank you!
--See you again!
What's this?!
Let's go hunt for a bargain.
This is delicious!
Yeah, it is!
I see.
but Bro had no such luck.
Oh, Nami! I'm gonna go out and have fun,
so give me some spending money.
Yep.
Wait a sec!
It really is yummy! Hey, Sanji!
If he stays in Water Seven,
his life will be in danger.
I can't wait!
Then...
@#$%&!!
Hm?
Thanks for always making yummy food!
If he gets caught again, we're not
strong enough to rescue him!
You're not getting anything!
Thanks!
Yes, ma'am!
I've come this far. I should be fine now.
There's more if you want it!
But he probably will try to stay on this
island because he's worried about us.
He'll need lots of food in
order to get strong, so...
Hold it!
Hey, eyebrows! Give me more!
You can get it yourself!
That woman!
--Give me more!
So we got together and discussed it.
He never learns, does he...?
Give me more, too!
He can't run from us.
I'll have some more, too.
Geez, he forgot to change his shirt.
Thank you.
My pleasure!
Straw Hat, please! You can
do it by force if you have to.
What am I gonna do with my oldest son?
Say, do you think that place
was the final nesting village?
Please take Bro out to sea.
He's a pirate's son to start with!
Lad! I'll be waiting to hear
the stories of your journey!
Seriously...!
Wait! I said, wait!
Well, it doesn't really matter.
Whoa!
After all, the world is full of mysteries
that we know nothing about!
Give me a break!
H-Hey, don't pull me, Chimney!
S-Straw Hat!
Alright! Let's go get our new ship!
Boy, why does water-water
candy taste this good?!
Okay, then, everyone!
We're gonna go shopping!
Th-There's trouble! The wanted
posters have been released!
Listen. I have nothing to do
with you guys! Why do I...
Grandma told me about this place.
I'm so looking forward to it!
It's the best, you jerk!
Whoa! So is that it, Luffy?! It's huge!
Whoa! They're finally out?!
If I put it on top of cotton candy and eat it,
I don't know what'll happen to me!
A stall, huh?
Oh, hey, pops! How're you doing?!
Well then, carry the younger ones on your back.
Straw Hat, the bounty on
your head has gotten crazy!
Sure, I can carry two babies on my back...
Hey, that's not the point!
A petty stall like this wouldn't...
S-Straw Hat!
This is incredible!
Hm? Looks like the cook here
is better than I expected.
And the others have bounties, too!
--Hm?
--My... Um...
Franky! Where are you, Franky?!
Are you listening to me?! Hey!
Anyway, take a look at these!
I have a favor to ask!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Mothers Are Strong!
Zoro's Hectic Household Chores!"
"The King of Animals that Overlooks the Sea!
The Dream Ship Magnificently Completed!"
"Sanji's Shock! Mysterious Old Man
and His Super Yummy Cooking!"
"Everyone Finally Has A Bounty!
A Pirate Group Worth Over 600 Million!"
"A Girl in Search of Her Yagara!
Great Search in the City of Water!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!