Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Ah! Zoro! Sanji!
If you really intend to take him with you...
Pirate guys!
I'm sorry!
We've got trouble!
Straw Hat!
Your grandpa is back, Luffy!
...do whatever it takes.
I'm sorry for being bullheaded!
What brought you guys here?
Take him by force!
They're at the opposite seashore.
Live as you please, Luffy.
Big Bro Franky asked us to bring you guys!
I was wrong!
That's the only way to free him!
They're looking for us now!
They're going to attack us!
In the flow of time, as a result of
various circumstances and strong spirits,
What?! Why?! I thought he said
he wasn't gonna capture us.
The dream ship has been completed!
"Goodbye My Dear Underlings!
Franky Departs"
They built an incredible ship!
How would we know?!
Hurry up and get ready to set sail!
people come to question the world they live in!
Luffy...
The day we meet will come at some point.
What?! It's already done?!
That was really quick!
You idiot! Grab my hand already!
Five top-notch shipwrights
worked on it day and night!
I'm giving this back!
The judicial island Enies Lobby is the front door
Yeah, they did!
All right! Let's head there right away!
that leads to the World Government,
a huge organization.
Yeah!
Straw Hat...!
Now, come on board, Franky...
Now that they've caused it to fall,
neither the Navy nor pirates
will leave them alone.
"Wanted Posters Make It Around the World!
Celebration in Their Hometowns
Straw Hat!
Board my ship.
You can say that the Straw Hats
are now known all around the world.
as the Ship Moves Forward!"
Franky Family...
Don't be so cocky!
What're you guys running that
frantically for? You're out of breath.
You guys are total amateurs who
could only manage makeshift repairs!
And so is this wanted poster.
It'd be a pity for such a magnificent ship
not to have a shipwright on board.
Sanji! You're the best!
Put something on!
To tell you the truth, we came
to ask you a huge favor.
You perv!
Isn't this incredible?!
It's the spitting image of him!
How dare you destroy the town again?!
I guess I don't have much choice
but to help you guys out!
Did you see the wanted posters?!
Leave town, you perv!
Wanted posters?
Straw Hat, the bounty on
your head has gotten crazy!
I, Franky, will be the shipwright on your ship!
You good-for-nothing!
Meteor... Fist!
And all the others, too, are wanted in addition!
Give me my swimsuit back, Straw Hat.
Then join us!
"Departing the City of Water!
Usopp Mans Up and Brings Closure to the Duel!"
Me, too?! All right!
He pulled one crazy stunt!
Don't be silly! You think
you can make me join you
Me, too...?!
L-Luffy-san...
Me, too?!
just by stealing my swimsuit?!
Hey, look! It's an article on Straw Hat!
Instead of having me explain,
just take a look at these.
Vice Admiral Garp sure doesn't show
any mercy, even to his own grandson.
Looks like he toppled the Tower of Justice.
All seven of you now have
bounties on your heads!
Vice Admiral Garp!
His bounty is going to skyrocket after that!
Hm?
Yow!
We've found the Straw Hats!
"Navy"
Go, our town's heroes!
They're on the scrap heap island at
the southeast seashore, about to set sail!
Enies Lobby is famous
for Water Seven's sea train.
Straw Hat Luffy, 300-million-Berry bounty.
Don't be taken out by the Navy!
"Nothing should phase men."
Nothing should phase men.
"A man should be resourceful,
even with only the skin on his back."
A man should be resourceful,
even with only the skin on his back.
Hey, rooting for them could get us in trouble!
We're gonna head there right away!
Get on board immediately!
It isn't that far from here...
All right! It went up!
"He should be like a lion that
stands against the waves!"
He should be like a lion that
stands against the waves!
Go, Straw Hats!
This must be a twist of fate.
Yes, sir!
Pirate Hunter Zoro, 120-million-Berry bounty.
Run, run, then keep running!
For them to be within range...
What a pitiable, unfortunate crew.
Bro!
Cat Burglar Nami, 16-million-Berry bounty.
"Navy"
He struck a pose, completely
exposing his private parts!
Oh, no...
Don't look at him!
Vice Admiral Garp! We lightheartedly
parted with Luffy-san and the others.
Cotton Candy Lover Chopper,
the gang's pet, 50-Berry bounty.
He's the worst... He's the worst!
I underestimated him!
What a strong-willed guy he is!
Let's go, Captain!
This is quite embarrassing!
Fifty...?
Devil's Child Nico Robin,
80-million-Berry bounty.
If you wanna complain, talk to Sengoku!
Huh?
Of course we're going!
He's a man among men!
Wh-What the heck? They're furling the sails?
He's the one who chewed me out
and made me come back here!
He's just a total perv!
Come on! Get ready to set sail!
How bossy of him.
I wonder if they gave up.
We're about to get busy!
Who's this...?
That's because you said,
Give up?
If it's okay to get rough
with him, I can help you.
Hey!
"It's my grandson, so..."
on the transponder snail.
Black Foot Sanji, failed to obtained
a picture, 77-million-Berry bounty.
Hold it, Teach!
What?
I doubt Luffy's given up,
but then, just what is he up to?
Shut up! Mind your own
business, you greenhorn.
I've been looking for you.
Come to think of it, Ice pops said that we
had no choice but to take him by force.
What?
Hurry up! Furl the sails!
A-Admiral, what about you?
Is it okay for you to be here?
Hey, Sogeking's got a bounty, too.
Yeah! Furl the sails!
But how?
It's a lot of work going back by bike.
Well, don't worry. I won't do anything.
Fifty...?
Hey! Are you really sure about this, Franky?!
Go back three days before the
world was shocked and amazed
W-Well, we sympathize with you, or, well...
Dos Fleurs...
Huh? Are you asking me if I'm really sure?!
Er... I think that also can be a
problem when facing our enemy.
I'm sure you wanna say all sorts
of things, but, well... please wait.
by the Straw Hat Pirates' wanted posters.
You dummy! Have faith in this ship!
There was an event that
occurred on a certain island.
The favor we're talking about
has something to do with this!
He's right! Have faith in it, you dummy!
Set sail!
Please take a look at this!
You jerk! You dummy!
This is Banaro Island on the Grand Line.
Franky!
What?
Usopp, just a minute ago, you were...
Bro! Take good care of yourself!
Cyborg Franky, 44-million-Berry bounty.
Well, I guess it doesn't matter.
Give me a hand, you bastards!
"The Most Heinous Power!
Blackbeard's Darkness Attacks Ace"
Oh, no! Bro's got a bounty on his head!
Grab!
The Franky Family will live on forever!
Seriously, what the hell are they
thinking at a damn busy time like this?!
Oh, no!
Straw Hats! You guys take care, too!
That's right. We somehow
were able to get off the hook,
Hey, Luffy!
but Bro had no such luck.
Franky, I've furled the sails, as you said to.
Luffy!
What?! Hey, Robin!
If he stays in Water Seven,
his life will be in danger.
Are you really sure you don't have to
wait for one more person, Straw Hat?
You grabbed them! Ouch!
We'd better hurry up, or the
battleship will catch up with us.
Oh, Ace! Commander!
If he gets caught again, we're not
strong enough to rescue him!
--You're gonna crush them, Robin!
--Ow, ow, ow...!
Not quite yet.
Huh?
I did wait. Ever since I heard what Sanji told us,
We still haven't named this ship yet.
But he probably will try to stay on this
island because he's worried about us.
Don't call me "Commander" after all this time.
I tried so that our room at
Galley-La wouldn't be empty.
Name?! At a time like this?!
That word is meant to be
reserved for people you respect.
That's right. You don't wanna depart
in an unnamed ship, do you?
So we got together and discussed it.
Don't mock me.
What the hell?
Oh, so you must be "Fire Fist" Ace.
What? Usopp is coming back?!
Straw Hat, please! You can
do it by force if you have to.
Yeah, that's me. Nice to meet you!
They're gonna come off!
Yeah. He was by himself rehearsing
how he'd rejoin us at the seashore.
Please take Bro out to sea.
He's a pirate's son to start with!
Then, a name like "Something-or-other Lion"?
Okay! I got a name that sounds strong!
They're gonna be plucked off!
I see... you've already become
a great captain in your own right.
Just like tangerines!
The "Bear! Polar Bear! Lion!"
Isn't that right, Captain Marshall D. Teach
of the Blackbeard Pirates?
Straw Hat!
No one would give a ship
a weird name like that!
Really?! So he really wants to come back.
This is how we all feel!
Then, the "Tiger! Wolf! Lion!"
Please consider it!
Then let's go get him right away!
Stop just listing animal names like that!
What is it, some sort of a curse?!
Jeez, Ace! I haven't seen you in ages!
Yeah!
"Squid! Octopus! Chimpanzee!"
He's always gotta do things the hard way.
Now you're not even putting "lion" in it!
You guys didn't have to ask me that.
So what's the deal?
How'd you know I was here?
Hey, Robin! I want him to still
be a man when he joins us!
Well, "lion" is on the right track.
But the Galley-La guys were like...
I decided a long time ago that he's the
only person I'd accept as our shipwright.
Usopp is coming back!
Teach, let's cut the idle talk!
Seriously?!
Don't tear them off!
Hold it, you guys!
A-Are you guys all okay with that?!
It hurts just to watch!
This figurehead looks good.
You should know the rules, having lived
through twice as much as others.
--Who's this...?
--I-I guess...
I won't allow any of us to go get him.
Oh, that's a nice sunflower!
It's not a sunflower, you idiots!
What? Why?
Of course.
What's going on?! Franky's in pain!
Isn't that right?
Looks like you have your answer.
Well, it's just natural that
you guys wouldn't get it right.
Whatever you do, don't assume a
subservient attitude towards him, Luffy.
I... I'm relieved!
What's this gut-wrenching cry?!
It sounds like he's on the verge of death!
But this is a ship that the future
King of the Pirates will board.
Now that we know how they feel,
we'd better get going.
Zoro...
I kinda feel sorry for him...
So you made it with that
hope in mind, right, Franky?
I'm not gonna accept him
until he apologizes first.
Okay, let's go, guys!
Yeah!
That's right. He'll set sail into
a sea filled with savage beasts
...even though he's a perv.
Yeah, I get it.
If you're telling us, pirates, to give up
the treasure right in front of us,
--Zoro! Why?!
--Hey! Who are you to decide...
Where're you guys going?
and rise to the top. So I wanted
a figurehead suitable for that.
But let me say something first!
The scrap heap island is this way!
Shut up!
we can't back off unless
you give us a good reason.
That's a splendid sun!
What do you say, Ace?
Why don't you join my crew?
It's not a sun, you idiot!
No matter what feelings were involved
in Luffy and Usopp's first argument,
Sorry... but we're not going to see him off.
A ship that'll cross a thousand rigorous
oceans cheerfully, just like the sun...
L-Like I said...
Seize the world with me!
Seeing him would make it
hard for us to say goodbye.
or no matter who the right one is...
I've already planned out how
I'm going to rise up in power!
...once a man decides to fight a duel,
...I-I wanna stay on this island!
Mozu! Kiwi!
It's perfect for them!
Whitebeard's reign is over!
I'll become the next Pirate King!
I said it's not a sun, you Stupid-berg!
Tell him that we wish him all the best!
the outcome of the duel decides that argument.
What do you think about this
for the ship's name, Franky?
I-I do appreciate you guys!
In fact, I can't thank you enough!
For starters, I'm gonna kill
Straw Hat Luffy, who is in Water Seven,
The pirate ship...
It's true that the ship
belongs to you, the captain.
I wanna go with you and help you out,
as a gift to the Government!
but there's something I need to do here.
So fight me...
Luffy? What did you just say?
"The King of Animals that Overlooks the Sea!
The Dream Ship Magnificently Completed!"
If I win, I'll take the Merry.
That's why I gave you the ship as a gift!
Oh! You know him?!
...Thousand Sunny!
Monkey D. Luffy!
Besides, I'm not a shipwright
anymore in the first place!
Whoa!
Another reason I can't let you go free!
Fight a duel with me!
That sounds cool!
That's better than the "Dumpling!
Gorilla! Lion!" name I came up with!
So that ship is the last ship I'll ever build!
He's my brother!
You guys are prepared for the
worst regarding Usopp, aren't you?
What?
He lost...
What is this, a word game?!
And naturally, there is no way I'm going to...
It was my long-cherished desire.
...and walked out on us on his own.
That sounds better than
"Boss Lionel" that crossed my mind...
That, indeed, is a dream ship!
Now, listen, you guys. He might be
an idiot, but he's still our captain.
Zoro...
Better than the "Darkness" that I thought of...
Hold it, Franky.
This is how it should be.
...join your crew.
Right.
Better than the "Monsieur
Sunflower" that I thought of...
Damn!
If Usopp can't treat him with
respect when things are critical,
Now, hey, you guys! Just how
long do you have to feel down?
I don't think that ship has become
the dream ship you're referring to yet.
Have you guys lost your marbles?!
we're better off not having him in our gang.
Shut up! Why does mine have to
be the only one that's a drawing?!
A ship that crosses a thousand oceans...
If a captain stops commanding respect,
his gang will fall apart without fail.
How lovely! And so is the sun!
People don't usually start off
with a bounty that large.
A dream ship?
Huh? Just how does this
picture look like me?! Well?!
Wait, you guys! That was
just to start things off.
That's right! Blueprints alone
can't complete that ship!
One of your men could use a lesson in manners!
The one I came up with sounds a lot better!
--How could they think this is me?!
--You look like that, you know.
Fire Gun!
After setting sail, it has to cross many seas
Listen! I don't care if you
want to act happy-go-lucky,
Here's my name for the ship!
Use real words. I don't
understand what you're saying.
--The "New Battle Franky,
Lion Gang Champion"!
--Let's use what Ice pops came up with! I like it!
and overcome many battles and hardships...
but if you, the man who is above me,
ever shows weakness,
I'll be the laughing stock... of all
the ladies throughout the world.
--"Lion Gang Champion"!
--"Thousand Sunny," huh? That's a good name!
...before it reaches the end of the sea.
After doing all those things,
next time, the one leaving the gang will be me!
Flame Commandment!
--I agree!
--Let's get along, Sunny!
I was tricked...
Fire Pillar!
He said he was a reporter from
one of the local magazines.
I guess deciding on the ship's name has
helped us brace ourselves for departure.
What?!
then you can finally call it a dream ship.
Hey, that won't solve anything!
At least he did manage to
get a cute pic of me, but...
I agree.
And when my best ship is completed one day,
I've finally gotten a bounty myself...
It's good that that idiot
now wants to come back.
Hey, Franky, what're you
booing about over there?
I'm a pirate, too! I fought hard like a man!
Auger, Burgess! Keep outta this!
I'll board that ship as a shipwright
Hurry up and shake them off with
the secret weapon or whatever.
But...
You don't stand a chance
against that man. Stay back!
I wanna file a complaint
about my 50-Berry bounty!
in order to witness that fated day.
...if he tries to fudge on this issue
without taking any responsibility,
Yeah, you'd better hurry up.
The battleship is already nearby.
Well, there's always next time.
By that day, the ship will
probably be falling apart,
--Sorry!
--Fire Fist!
Straw Hat! What're you doing?!
All right, fine, stop bugging me!
I won't accept that no matter what!
but I'm sure that it'll be
giving off a magnificent light!
Take a last look at this beautiful
city of water while you can.
If that happens, we'll leave him on this island.
In just a second, this island
is going to be out of sight.
Let's hurry. Bro's waiting for you!
What do you think? Isn't that great, Tom-san?
What?
Hold on, Zoro. It's true that
his actions weren't appropriate,
Yeah, that's great!
Sorry!
--Captain!
--Aw, that burns!
I see. Then...
If you also become a sailor, you'll beat me.
but we can give him a good
talking-to once he comes ba...
Don't forget anything.
Captain!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
We're gonna get the ship
and Franky and set sail!
I wonder if your pirate blood is affecting you.
Luffy, Sanji isn't moving.
I'm burning!
Grandpa!
Is leaving the gang such a trivial matter?!
Ha! Moron-ky, someone like
you can't surpass Tom-san!
Just leave Twirly-brows be.
Huh?! Hey, wait!
No.
And Coby and...
What'd you say?!
Are you pirate ladies and guys already leaving?
Hot, hot, hot, hot!
What're you doing, you Moron-ky?!
But...
Nami-san.
Chimney, Gonbe, thanks for everything.
Ribbit, ribbit.
Unfortunately, this time,
what he's saying is correct.
I was glad I got to see you
after such a long time!
Well, if you're a man, do it resolutely!
Call my name, too!
What, Luffy? I've got more cannonballs left!
There's no way we can trust a man
who'd do such a thing on impulse.
What I wanna do has changed!
Meteor... Fist!
What you wanna do? That's not true.
Wow, hot, hot!
Here is what it boils down to.
"Navy"
This is indeed an incredibly rare case.
If the first words coming from Usopp are
a sincere apology, then we're all good.
Everything you're doing on
this island right now is...
Captain!
Few though they may be,
to think that they all have a bounty...
Damn it! Hot, hot, hot, hot!
Otherwise, there's no place
here for him to come back to.
It's no use!
...atonement.
We're gonna run with all our might now!
Shut up, men! Give me some space!
Furthermore, their bounties
total over 600 million Berries.
We're not little kids playing pirates.
I'll see you guys again someday!
By the way, this "Black Foot" guy...
why isn't there any picture of him?
Luffy-san's cool!
You're still regretting that Tom-san
was taken that day because of you.
How dare you talk cheeky?!
You're nothing but my kid's kid! Luffy!
Yes, sir, well... I am certain
that I took his picture,
Vice Admiral Garp, please calm down a little!
but I was shocked when I
saw the developed picture.
Ice pops! We decided to use the
name you came up with for the ship!
This is the picture.
Do what you want with the Merry.
But Tom-san had already
forgiven you on that day...
This is indeed something
right out of a horror story!
Thanks for the nice name!
We'll get a new ship and
move on to the seas ahead!
Did you take off... the lens cover?
...and tried to guide you.
Everyone! Thanks for everything!
We're taking off!
Ships that would do something like that...
They're no longer my ships!
It sounds like he's saying something.
Eh?
Well then, bye, Usopp...
It's been fun.
We can't even make it out.
Bro!
Seems like pirates can't even
depart without making a racket.
We brought them!
You're right.
Here we go!
We went our separate ways.
This is an astonishing emergency
accelerator made with a huge air cannon
I get it, Ace. You're burning
to kill me, aren't you?
Tom-san... hit Franky for the first time...
We still have several days before the
ship gets completed and we set sail.
taking advantage of the strength
of the treasure tree Adam!
Bro! Where are you?!
It's no surprise. Murdering a
crewmate is a grievous crime.
What'd you do that for?!
Let's just stay here and wait for him.
"Navy"
They're here.
Whoa! There's something huge!
It's true that I killed the
4th division commander Thatch!
"They're no longer my ships," you say?
I waited for him there all this time,
but he didn't come.
Is that it?!
Hey! We're here, Franky! Give us the ship!
You can say anything but that!
A-A massive iron ball!
I didn't have a choice! He got his hands on
the Devil Fruit that I had my sights set on!
That's his answer.
Oh, Ice pops!
What's wrong with saying that?!
I'm regretting it!
So you're here.
Luffy!
Where's Franky?
Straw Hat...
The ship's rule dictated that whoever
found the fruit could eat it, remember?
Unfortunately, he had to go somewhere.
I'm sure... he'll have a fun life, too.
If only those ships didn't exist,
no one would have had to get hurt!
But the ship is completed.
I'll show it to you in place of Franky.
He probably won't quit being a pirate,
so I hope I'll see him some day on the sea!
I memorized what every fruit
in the book looked like,
What the heck is that?
Ahhh! We're gonna die!
No matter what kind of ship it is,
the act of building it...
Yeah.
No way we'll survive that! That's not possible!
so I knew it was the one I'd been
looking for the second I saw it!
This ship is incredible!
When I saw its blueprints,
my eyes opened wide in surprise.
If you underestimate me...
The only reason I spent all those
decades on Whitebeard's ship
...is neither an act of good nor evil!
It can sail any kind of sea!
With this ship, going to the end
of the world isn't a mere dream.
was because I figured that was
the most likely place to find it!
R-Run, Luffy-san! You're gonna get killed!
I don't care what kind of
ships you choose to build,
Hurry up and show it to us!
All right! I'm gonna go back to my friends!
Hurry up!
but even if the ships you built hurt someone,
Franky! Hurry!
Here is Franky's message to you, Straw Hat.
I woulda given up if fortune
hadn't smiled down on me,
We've got a magnificent ship!
They're all waiting for me!
or even if they destroy the world,
...you'll get hurt!
If you're going to be
King of the Pirates someday...
but that fruit fell into my friend's hands!
at least the one who created
them must love them!
The question is, how will I rejoin them naturally?
Well, no matter how they act,
I've got 100 strategies!
So then you killed Thatch and stole it?
Their creator mustn't deny them!
...board this King of Animals ship!
Don't blame the ships!
We're gonna die!
The strong candidate for my first
words has to be these, after all.
A man should be resolutely proud...
of the ships he created!
Coup de Burst!
Well, that's how the ball bounces.
Incredible!
"If you're begging me so
much that you're in tears,
This ability chose me, Ace!
This is...
I suppose I can come back if
you make me Vice Captain."
--What a spectacle!
--Well, well...
That you brought the punks
on the backstreets together...
Whoa! It's huge! It's so cool!
"Thank you, Vice Captain Usopp! Yay!"
It has made me the most
powerful person out there, Ace!
It looks like it has all sorts of things flying out!
That you called yourself a bounty hunter
and protected this island from looters...
"We'll do whatever you tell us, so please
come back." They might say that!
Whoa! He's gonna give this to us?
Look! It's rare, even for a Logia type.
The ship... flew... away.
I see... This is at least twice as big as Merry.
I'm so good!
You did all that to protect this
city of water that Tom-san loved,
What a big fore-and-aft sail! Is this a sloop?
I'm the very example of a man who
turns even his mistakes to good use!
Let me see the kitchen! The kitchen!
Ace, isn't your body made out of fire?
which was your way of atoning...
In this adverse situation, I'll further
endear myself to them and live happily.
What a fine ship!
...though it doesn't appear that way to others.
I wonder what kind of
flower the figurehead is...
--Well, I think it's, of course, the mane of a lion.
--Whoa! The interior is incredible, too!
Okay! I'd better hurry up!
Not bad.
Of course it doesn't.
Mine is darkness!
I'd love to stay, but goodbye,
Water Seven, the City of Water!
That's not why I did what I did at all!
It's a deck with a lawn! It feels good!
Ow, ow, ow...!
Look! It's the same black smoke from earlier.
A slide! Whoa!
Looks like we can do gardening, too.
Cool!
You quit building ships,
which was your favorite thing to do,
Those pirates are still in town.
What a good view it has!
I remember experiencing this feeling before.
and have lived suppressing yourself.
They're still going at it?
If they destroy any more of our village...!
Hey, where's the kitchen?!
Usopp...
Are you going to live like that
for the rest of your life?
That big gaffsail seems
to have a lot of mobility!
Luffy, let's wait a little longer.
We're not in a rush or anything.
Keep away from them!
Our only option is to run!
Even if Tom-san forgives you,
or even if I forgive you,
It's called brigantine.
Merry...
It consumes three barrels of cola,
but it lets us fly one kilometer.
Sloop boats sail as people's
imagination dictates.
Hey, Luffy!
nothing is gonna change, is it...?
There's nothing the Going Merry
could do that this ship can't.
The navigator's skills
determine the sail's usefulness.
Darkness...?
What was that?!
Isn't it about time...
I can hardly wait! I'll do my best!
That's right, Commander Ace. You can't kill me.
It exceeds the Merry in every way.
I'm gonna go check out the ship, too!
But the Merry's brave soul will be
inherited by the Thousand Sunny.
Whoa! My dream fridge! One with a
lock on it! There's a huge oven, too!
Dammit! They found us! It's the Navy!
...for you to forgive yourself, Franky?
It's said that this is the most
evil power in Devil Fruit history.
Grandpa?!
If it breaks down, I'll fix it perfectly!
It's Vice Admiral Garp's battleship!
Thank you, Franky! This ship is awesome!
It's the Logia Devil Fruit, Dark-Dark Fruit.
Bro! Straw Hat! Get out of here!
When it comes to the ship and weapons,
rely on me for anything!
I've become a man made of darkness.
Isn't it about time for you to
start living for your own dream?
Hey, Ice pops. Where's Franky?
We'd like to say thanks.
From today on, this is your ship!
Hey, Luffy! Can you hear me?!
I'll give you a taste of just how powerful it is!
Yeah!
This is Grandpa! This is Grandpa!
If you can hear me, say something!
It seems he has no intention
of seeing you guys again.
Go ahead and try.
What?
Hey, Grandpa! What're you doing?!
Straw Hat...
You said you weren't gonna capture us here!
Are you going to ask him to
join you guys as a shipwright?
What are you doing?! Hurry!
Yeah. How'd you know?
The captain is about to cut loose!
Well, the thing is, a lot
has happened since then.
"Navy"
If we don't hurry away from here,
we'll get caught in the attack!
They sure showed me.
I've decided that he's our shipwright.
Sorry, but I'm gonna send you
to the bottom of the sea!
They escaped.
What the heck?!
What?!
Stand right back up!
He seems to have realized it.
Well, I'm not doing this as an
apology for that or anything,
Then he doesn't want to?
A bag?!
It's the opposite.
but I'll fight your gang all by myself!
That's my grandson!
He's not sure if he can turn you
down if you ask him face to face.
It has what you'll need for your journey, Bro!
Give me a cannonball.
Out of the way, you bastards!
H-Here you go, sir.
That's why he went and hid.
It's the Franky Family!
--Bro!
What's he trying to do?
But, well, his honest wish is...
He wants to set sail with you guys.
Those guys...
That he's entrusting this dream ship that
he's been planning all this time to you
Meteor... Fist!
After all, he didn't come with us.
Bro! Please forgive us for all that
stuff we pulled! We're really sorry!
is proof enough, isn't it?
Whoa! There's an aquarium here!
Of course he wouldn't.
But the king of snipers promised us
Hey, you're right! Amazing!
We're sorry!
that he'd come to Elbaf
some day with his friends.
We're prepared to receive
any kind of punishment!
Franky has come to genuinely like you guys.
I'll look forward to it.
Since we're fools, we racked what
little brains we have thinking about it!
We'll wait patiently.
A giant's life span is 300 years.
Whoa! H-He fired a cannonball
with his bare hand!
But he's imposing a duty upon himself
to stay on this island forever.
The darkness gushing from his body
is crawling across the ground!
We did some good work!
That came flying at us with more
power than the ones fired by cannon!
Just what did you rack what little
brains you have thinking about?!
Yeah. Now, let's go back
to our work place, shall we?
A duty?
It's not like he was just throwing a baseball!
Creepy! It's pitch black, almost like
there is a hole in the ground.
It's a stupid persistence, if you ask me.
How to steal my swimsuit? Well?!
Or do we wanna go get a drink?
All right, I'm in!
It's scary how it feels like it could absorb you.
How to make me a pirate?!
Mind your own business!
My power's been declining lately.
If you really intend to take him with you...
Hurry and get away!
Get as far away as you can!
It's my life! No one can decide it but me!
We're heading back to
the station, Chimney, Gonbe.
We have no choice!
We're getting out of here for now!
Go through the forest!
Run all the way to the beach!
...do whatever it takes.
Or our new ship will be blasted to bits!
Take him by force!
Let's see... How did Bro do things?
How can I, your boss, willingly walk
on the way paved by my underlings?!
Bring 1,000 cannonballs to me!
That's the only way to free him!
Beats me.
Yes, sir!
We were just doing whatever
he told us to do, so...
Hurry!
That's shameful!
Darkness is gravity!
It has the power to pull everything in!
By force?
If your brains are so small, then don't
try to use them in the first place!
We're gonna starve to death like this, huh?
Those guys said the same thing,
too, but is that really okay?
Iceberg!
This isn't good! A whole bunch of those
things are about to come flying at us!
Not even a ray of light can
escape from its infinite gravity!
Well... I knew this would happen.
I-I'm sorry. But...
Meteor Fist Shower!
Wh-What?! What'd you come here for?!
Oh, boy... Against that,
no ship would stand a chance.
...aren't we even allowed to think a little?
If you're worried about work,
I can give you some.
But you're up against me...
and I'm still untouched.
We're deeply indebted to you
for taking in thugs like us.
This is the start of Bro's new life.
We mustn't show tears. Smile!
Come to Galley-La's headquarters
one by one, one per day, every day.
What?! Are you sure, Iceber... I mean, Bro?!
But... they're coming down
on their own. What can I... Ah!
I'm not going after you just yet.
Aren't we even allowed to
think about your happiness?!
You can stay there and
enjoy the view of the town.
New Bro!
Don't call me that.
Now, let's get started, shall we, lads?
Black Hole!
Bro! What are you doing back here?!
Don't think that you can
run from me! Be prepared!
Who's the fool here?
Huh? Why do I need a reason?!
You guys are all...
This is Franky House! It's my house!
Full speed ahead!
We'll take care of the cannonballs!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
But...
Got it!
I'm gonna come right out and say it, Bro!
--B-Bro!
--Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Dammit! Is he really not coming?
You want to go with the Straw Hats, right?!
"An island in the Grand Line"
What's he doing?
Commodore Smoker!
--Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
--H-Hey, Robin!
Huh? Don't be silly!
Thank you for your help, sir!
Go easy on him! Please!
You're gonna make him a woman!
Huh? The bounty on that pirate
I just caught is 50 million?
There's no way I would, is there...?!
Yes, sir!
He's crying!
How ridiculous! What kind of
criteria does the Navy use?!
They're gonna come off!
Look at this! With your skills, you guys
can't even properly build a single house!
He's here!
They're gonna be plucked off!
Geez, the days sure are boring...
Usopp's here!
Smoker-san!
Just like grapes!
We just went to see them...
Ensign Tashigi!
Hey, everyone! Usopp's here!
Ow, grapes!
Have you seen the wanted posters?
The Straw Hats are...
...to ask them to take you out to sea!
Really?
Damn you, Nico Robin!
You're not gonna get away with this!
Who are you talking to?
Yep!
What?
Ah! I-I'm sorry!
You fools! Mind your own business!
Wear your glasses, you idiot.
They're gonna come off!
B-But he had already made up his mind
to ask you to be their shipwright!
They're gonna be plucked off!
Just like apples!
We're marines after all.
Why do I have to become a pirate?
Ah... pples...
Since the Navy is hierarchical in nature,
It doesn't take a genius to see it.
there's a limit to my freedom
so long as I'm only a captain.
We had never seen you building a ship before.
What we need now is higher ranks.
My tears won't stop because of the pain!
After the incident in Enies Lobby,
pirates all around the world
But I thought, "Wow, I never
knew he could look this happy."
Robin!
started acknowledging that
the Straw Hats have the edge.
H-Huh? You aren't doing anything?
I've never seen you having
that much fun before.
The ground is devouring the town!
Yes.
I only did it once, the very first time.
Why? Wh-What's going on?
On my pride, I'm gonna crush
them in the New World!
Bro...
How sly of him to pretend
that he's crying out of pain.
You know the Straw Hats are looking
for a shipwright, don't you...?
Out of my way! Out of my way!
"Sea Restaurant 'Baratie,'
East Blue"
S-Sorry! L-Let me through!
--What?
--Just once?
You ran away on purpose, didn't you...?!
Dark gravity uses its limitless power
to condense objects and crush them!
Hey, nose guy! What're you doing here?!
Dammit! Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
The judicial island Enies Lobby is the front door
Look at this, Bro!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
What?
My wanted poster!
So they put it out, as I thought.
It hurts so bad I can't stop the tears!
that leads to the World Government,
a huge organization.
Wh-What's going on?
You shouldn't stay with us any longer!
Now that they've caused it to fall,
We don't wanna be a hindrance to you!
neither the Navy nor pirates
will leave them alone.
Why are they setting sail
just because the Navy's here?
You can say that the Straw Hats
are now known all around the world.
I just assumed that you were on the ship.
What're you guys doing?! I'm still right here!
And so is this wanted poster.
Is this a nightmare? Our village is...
Why? Why? Why?!
Sanji! You're the best!
When we fought together
even after our argument?!
Isn't this incredible?!
It's the spitting image of him!
Black Foot Sanji with a
77-million bounty used to work here!
Sogeking.
You still haven't found them yet?!
Look at this, Bro!
Hm?
And now I'll show you what
happened to the missing village.
Don't let them get away no matter what!
Look far and wide for them!
Shoot through that flag.
My wanted poster!
So they put it out, as I thought.
We hope you'll come visit us again
here at the sea restaurant Baratie!
Roger.
You shouldn't stay with us any longer!
Behold the shambled mess it has become!
This is my new weapon,
a huge slingshot... named Kabuto!
"'Fusha Village' (Luffy's hometown),
East Blue"
We don't wanna be a hindrance to you!
It hurts! It hurts! I can't stop the tears!
Liberation!
Party time! Let's have a party today!
Have a good look at its power!
Don't talk so cocky! The hell with the Navy!
He's the most successful one in the
East Blue with a 300-million bounty!
Special Attack... Firebird Star!
Bro!
Cheers to our Luffy!
Are you okay?!
I took you all in when you were about
to die like dogs on the backstreets!
How could I be okay?!
--Hm?
--That's...
Snap!
Shut up, you idiots!
That might be true...
I've never seen you around.
What's with you, bikini guy?
Shame on you!
...but...!
You are a sword!
You guys can't even live
without me, and... Whoa!
Cheers!
Someone get me a lawyer!
Don't be so stuck-up on these backstreets.
Stop it!
Seriously... No one's listening to me,
the mayor of the village.
I got his swimsuit off of him!
Swimsuit? Why'd you do that...
Get him!
Our village... has been reduced to rubble...
Ah, wait! I get it!
Luffy seems like he's having a fun life.
He's got such a cute pet, too.
--Good job!
--Pass it around!
Don't tell me you've forgotten.
Don't give it back to him, no matter what!
So these kids are his friends, huh?
Give me my swimsuit back! Hey!
I'm the one who fought outstandingly
as that king of snipers, Sogeking!
"Friends"? They don't look friendly to me!
That's my best swimsuit!
You gave up on me because I disappeared?!
Now do you get it, Ace?
Someone from our village
became a vicious criminal
Scatter! Let's go!
This is the power I've obtained!
Wh... What the hell?!
that made the entire world his enemy!
Wait!
I've never heard of pirates picking
a fight with the World Government!
Fine by me!
Firefly!
How dare you mock us?!
Fiery Doll!
Hey! The stairs are broken! Be careful!
He's coming after us!
Yeah, that's true.
To start with, what is Garp doing,
You'd better know that you can't defeat me,
even if you all gang up on me at once!
What's wrong?! Hey!
Hot, hot, hot, hot!
allowing his own grandson to run
free and commit such a crime?
You're quite strong. You're just
wasting that strength by being a thug.
That burns!
Just one survivor would do!
Deliver his swimsuit to Straw Hat!
Something's wrong with that whole family.
Hey! Guys! No more worries!
--I fully understand how great
the power of darkness is.
--Hot, hot, hot, hot!
Does Dadan know about this?
I'm back for you guys!
Bring it to the scrap heap island!
Cheers!
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
But here's what puzzles me...
Like I said, shut up!
"'Syrup Village' (Usopp's hometown),
East Blue"
--If it's a Logia, these attacks
should go right through you.
--Dang, this is hot! Hot, hot, hot, hot!
Zambai!
Strong Right!
I'm Franky. I've decided to make the
backstreets of Water Seven my turf.
King of snipers... Yes!
There's no mistake about it!
This is Usopp-san!
--Right?
--This nose has to be our captain's!
Nice meeting you!
You jerks...
Give me my swimsuit back!
Y-Yes, sir.
Yes!
People at the village wouldn't believe us!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Stop...!
Sorry! I don't have it!
Well, his bounty is 30 million, so...
I already told you:
Darkness draws everything in,
Bro!
But we thought you'd agree, Kaya-san!
I'm sure I saw you had it! Enough of...
They don't know how incredible our captain is!
including bullets, swords,
punches, fire, and lightning!
I'm feeling great!
Hey, brother! Take this!
Our captain turns all lies into truth!
Unlike the rest of you, I don't get the
option of letting stuff pass through me!
Dammit! A fake-out!
Let's go to one more bar!
Gum-Gum... Balloon!
My body feels far worse pain than the
average person in every way possible!
This mask looks cool!
Run to the southeast!
Hey, you over there with the stylish bikini!
Let's make it using clay!
Oh? Where are you going, Kaya-san?
Let's have a drink together.
But in exchange for accepting that risk,
there is one other thing...
We'll take you to a bar.
I'll go home and continue
studying to become a doctor.
...that I am able to absorb.
I'd better hurry up and
become a full-fledged doctor
Vortex!
Hm? What's this fuss about?
so that I can treat Usopp-san if
he's injured when he comes back.
Wh-What're you doing?!
Let go of us!
Usopp's coming, Luffy! Usopp's coming!
You young girls, don't sponge booze
from others in broad daylight!
The perv is... Franky is going on a rampage!
To be exact, dark gravity has the ability
to draw in a Devil Fruit
power holder's physical body.
I envy Captain.
Protect the ship!
Let's hit him if he makes Kaya-san unhappy.
I know a place that serves good cola!
Not again!
The town will be destroyed!
Yep!
"'Shimotsuki Village' (Zoro's hometown),
East Blue"
Hey! Rejoice! It's me!
Sensei! Sensei!
Gravity?!
Why don't you come with me?
Is it true that the Pirate Hunter Zoro
Bro! Bro!
used to train at this dojo?
Chopper! It's a fine day today! Let's go fishing!
Yes, that's true.
And my body...
But you kids shouldn't look up to him, okay?
He's coming this way!
Well, I guess this is no time for that, huh?!
What?
Why? He's so cool!
Hold it, you bastards!
Teach us how to become pirates, too!
Oh, yeah, I've got good news!
Well? Have you figured it out, Ace?
G-Give me something to eat.
Hey! He's not wearing anything down below!
I didn't teach him how to become a pirate.
Believe it or not, when I'm back,
Are you telling the truth?
Don't play favorites, Sensei!
I don't mind becoming your Vice Captain!
What do you think? Well?!
Bring everyone who has nothing to eat!
--Good grief, what a troublesome alumnus.
--He's amazing! I wanna
be a swordsman like him!
It couldn't be...!
Hey, Luffy! Guys!
I sure was surprised to hear about
the incident on the judicial island,
I know!
but Zoro-kun, I think there's
no doubt in your mind.
You guys're crying with joy over there, right?!
Ah! Ding-don...
Go as nuts as you want!
No matter who you become,
Take the children inside!
Hey, you are, aren't you?!
We're starting the Franky Family!
if you're faithful to your swordsmanship,
that's all that matters.
Don't let them see the perv!
Strong Right!
Yeah!
Luffy! I can't go along with you anymore.
"'Cocoyashi Village' (Nami's hometown),
East Blue"
--It's our start!
Gen-san!
Sorry to cause you trouble until the end.
Here, I brought some tangerines.
--We're the Franky Family!
What, you brought them again, Nojiko?
I told you I'd buy them at the store.
Don't tell me you actually
believed that joke I made!
Well, just take them.
Don't act like we're strangers.
We've been friends for so long!
Yahoo!
I bet it's been a while since someone's
landed a punch on you, eh, Ace?
I think of you like a father to Nami and I, so...
There's no way I'd say
something like that seriously!
Although we said all sorts of things
to each other, we're friends!
I was never consulted.
Franky! Franky! Franky!
What're you doing?
I think that you got it when I grabbed you!
I'll let these little things go!
Hm? Oh, this...
Dammit!
Now, hey!
Franky! Franky! Franky!...
I've been calling the Navy Headquarters
to complain, but I can't get through at all!
You're committing indecent exposure!
You're under arrest!
Say something!
Another thing that my darkness drags in is...
Complain?
...Devil Fruit powers!
That's right!
They can't just release a lewd wanted
poster like this to the entire world!
That means that while I'm touching them,
Devil Fruit power holders
can't use any of their powers!
She'll have more suitors after her
than bounty hunters! Outrageous!
Enough already, you jerks!
Can you... live without me?!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
Logia, Zoan, and Paramythia!
But you like that picture itself, right?
You did blow it up quite a bit.
Against a world of Devil Fruit power holders
who are overconfident in their abilities,
Bro...
D-Deliver... Deliver the swimsuit!
The face of the Water Seven underworld...
Well, let it go, because this
proves that they're keeping...
I've obtained a means of attack
that cannot be defended against!
We'll work together to take
over that role splendidly!
But if you guys ever do anything
to take away Nami's smile...
Luffy! Usopp's talking to us!
So don't worry!
We'll go ahead of him by Yagara and wait!
So I just can't let you catch me, right?
Don't cry, Bro!
Okay! Go!
I can't hear it.
...I will come kill you!
Bro!
I already proved that you can't
escape from my dark gravity!
No matter how far you go,
Zoro!
...the promise they made you, right?
I can't hear anything!
we're your underlings for the rest of our lives!
Vortex!
W-Well, it's true, but...
That's a lie! I know you can hear it!
...that's those pirates' business, not mine.
Bro!
Then, would you have preferred
if she looked rough in the picture?
Ow, ow, ow...
St. Elmo's Fire!
The backstreets... have become a battlefield!
No! That'd be outrageous!
Take this!
"'Sakura Kingdom' (Chopper's hometown),
Grand Line"
I can't stop the tears!
Dammit! My legs...
Stop... joking.
Hurry!
Oh, no... Is this it?
This isn't good.
Hey! Pass it to me! This way!
Luffy!
So that's how it is.
So you really are trying to part with me?
Ah! Zoro! Sanji!
I see... Fine, then.
We've got trouble!
Dr. Kureha.
Damn it! The fire lances...!
Throw it to me!
Your grandpa is back, Luffy!
What did you have me come here for, Dalton?
I'm pretty busy, you know.
Listen, Luffy! It's not like everyone
can live looking ahead like you do!
Straw Hat...!
They're at the opposite seashore.
He messed up some vertebrae!
They're looking for us now!
They're going to attack us!
Straw Hat!
Well, I'm sorry, but I definitely
wanted to show these to you, too.
I can't just leave our wounded friend
here and move on to the seas ahead!
What?! Why?! I thought he said
he wasn't gonna capture us.
His new power is a pain...!
What is it? You wanna know
my secret to staying young?
Cross Fire!
How would we know?!
Hurry up and get ready to set sail!
To start with, Dalton, why don't you live
in the castle like kings normally do?
Go ahead and cut off useless friends
one after another and move on.
Package receipt confirmed!
You bastard!
Whoa!
I can let you use some of the rooms.
Franky! You still haven't
put on your swimsuit yet?!
I've been thinking about this for a while.
Straw Hat!
Well, I like living in this familiar village.
Also, I like rice cooked with chestnuts.
Did you like the ship?!
To be honest,
I've been thinking that I can't keep
up with your monstrous strength.
Yeah!
I'm giving this back!
I've never seen such an incredible ship! Thanks!
Banana Rock...! It's collapsing!
Oh? These are those Straw Hat lads.
What's going on? They can't be humans!
These wanted posters were issued
after the big incident the other day.
You perv! Go away!
You don't need weak friends, right?
--Have some shame!
--You perverted bastard!
Now, come on board, Franky...
Chopper...!
Luffy... you're the man
who'll be king of the pirates.
Forget the village! What is going
to happen... to our whole island?!
Of course it is! In addition to my super design,
I think his bounty amount
is some sort of a mistake.
Board my ship.
I don't care as long as I can see his face.
everything you guys requested was added!
But I don't have to go that high up.
Don't be so cocky!
I see... This is wonderful news.
Did you see the soldier
dock system I invented yet?!
You guys are total amateurs who
could only manage makeshift repairs!
Thinking back, when I was about to sail out,
you guys asked me to join you.
It'd be a pity for such a magnificent ship
not to have a shipwright on board.
No, not yet!
"The sand kingdom 'Alabasta,'
Grand Line"
It's the biggest showpiece! I bet you'll like it!
I had assumed that Devil Fruit power holders
were so preoccupied with their powers
Wh-What?!
He's coming this way!
I guess I don't have much choice
but to help you guys out!
What about the fish tank?!
Nico Robin... Why is Miss All Sunday
a member of Luffy-kun's gang?
that they would be pushovers
once they lost them.
I saw it!
I, Franky, will be the shipwright on your ship!
If you put the fish you catch in the fish tank,
That's all that's tying us together.
But I should have expected one
of Whitebeard's commanders
you can view and enjoy them
through the big tank downstairs!
We don't have to travel together
when we have a difference of opinion!
She surely was a mysterious woman,
All right! We've got a new crew member!
so much so that something about
her stuck in my mind, but...
It's a room that's like an aquarium!
You can have meals there with the others!
If that's what you want...
Yay! All right!
to be a fearsome fighter
in basic combat as well.
If Vivi-sama finds this out,
she'll probably feel very sad.
You can always have fresh fish!
...let me say one last thing. You guys...
I'm looking forward to it!
Oh, that. I already know,
but it doesn't bother me at all.
Bro...!
Where I'm going is my own business.
Don't cry! Don't cry!
I-It doesn't bother you at all? I thought
you'd be more shocked than anyone.
That ship is the ultimate dream ship
to you guys as well as to me!
Now then, today brings us
to another crossroad of fates.
Straw Hat is a man we can trust!
It has nothing to do with you guys anymore.
Even if you stayed close to Luffy-san,
you wouldn't understand what he's thinking.
So why are you...?
I'm...
...leaving the gang.
Give me my swimsuit back!
It's just a waste of time thinking about it,
but you can trust everything they do.
Tom-san... I'm leaving this island.
Chopper!
Yep!
He's the man who'll be King of the Pirates.
Say, teach me how to draw
blueprints for a pirate ship!
He's of quite a different caliber.
I'm sorry!
H-He's coming! Roronoa-san!
Sanji-san! We're counting on you!
How magnanimous! You've grown, Vivi-sama.
Everything is rendered
powerless before darkness!
What's so funny?
Leave it to us!
Even someone as powerful as you.
I'm sorry for being bullheaded!
Hey, why are you crying?
I was wrong!
But this makes me want
your power all the more.
"Land of white soil 'Baltigo,'
Grand Line"
Aren't you going to bed yet, Tom-san?
Get in!
The rebel group took Centaurea in the South Blue.
What're you drawing?
Ace, join my crew!
Mm... It's this island's hope.
Another country has fallen...
Aim at the scrap heap island!
Hope?
What're you guys doing?!
We did it! Now the North Blue's--
I wasn't a good disciple. I always
caused you nothing but trouble, but...
Franky Family's specialty!
This is no cause for rejoicing. This is a war.
Anything Cannon! Fire!
Usopp!
If I yield to power, there's no
point in being born a man.
H-Hey, you guys! Enough with your jokes!
Did you guys hear about the scrap heap island?!
Y-Yes, sir, I'm sorry.
I know I'm being pathetic.
I know I said I was leaving the gang.
Tom's Workers has finished
building the sea train, you say?!
I'll never leave anything to
be regretted later in my life!
What's this?
Thank you for everything!
Oh, it's Straw Hat Luffy.
But... is there any chance
that I can take that back?!
Do you understand, stupid?
He's the guy who actually
defeated Crocodile in Alabasta.
How long can you live like that in this world?
What?! He's flying there before
his swimsuit even gets there!
After the incident in Enies Lobby,
his pirate group is becoming so big
Can I?!
It's a pity, Ace!
Hang on to me, Chopper!
Please!
that the government can no
longer hide their existence.
Huh?
Gum-Gum...
Die in darkness!
The total bounty for the entire group
is 667 million and 50 Berries.
...Rocket!
Please let me...
Flame Commandment...
...stay with you!
I heard that their captain is the
grandson of Garp from the Na...
One more time...
Where are you going?
I'm going to get some air.
...let me join you guys!
Flame Emperor!
Galley-La's foremen...
Wh-What the heck is that?
Live as you please, Luffy.
Is that some sort of a curse?!
You dummy! It's just a perv!
Take good care of Iceberg!
In the flow of time, as a result of
various circumstances and strong spirits...
I've caused you nothing
but trouble, too, Iceberg.
The sun or the darkness--
there'll be only one winner!
--We can see everything!
We can see everything!
--B-Bro...
"'The World's Most Heinous Criminal'
Revolutionist Dragon (Monkey D. Dragon)"
Old hag Kokoro, little one and bunny...
...people come to question the world they live in!
We can see everything!
I'm gonna make Whitebeard the king!
R-Ribbit...
The day we meet will come at some point.
Luffy...
Yokozuna...
You idiot! Grab my hand already!
Well...
Perv!
--Lively townspeople...
--Where're you going?!
What the hell is going on?
You're coming back, aren't you?!
My little sisters...
Sodom... Gomorrah...
Guys!
And... my dear underlings...
Do you have it?
Yeah!
Franky!
Well then, once again...
You're the one who's an idiot!
To Robin and Usopp, who came back to us,
to our new friend, Franky...
You guys are so lame!
Thanks for the ship!
...and to our pirate ship, the Thousand Sunny!
It's the best ship ever!
We'll take good care of it!
--Cheers!
Yeah! I wish you a safe journey!
The "Decisive Battle of Banaro Island"
on the Grand Line...
If you want me to give
this swimsuit back to you,
Everyone's finally on board!
The fight between these two pirates...
then join us!
We're gonna hurry up and get
through this cannonball attack
...will be described as the trigger for a
massive incident that is soon to take place.
I'm stepping out for a bit!
so that we can get on with our adventure, guys!
Let's go! Our next destination is Fishman Island!
Yeah!
Put on your swimsuit.
What?! Usopp's coming back?!
Say, Chopper. We finally have a bounty, too.
We're hitting the sea of adventure!
Blackbeard, is that the power you
gained by killing your comrade?
Those idiots... They know they
can't do anything without me.
Head straight for Fishman Island!
Really?! All right!
Ace, you can't defeat me now.
No, no, no, no! With the New World nearby,
we should exercise caution!
Like I said, I can't accept that!
How cocky of them to say that!
Okay, then! Let's go get him right away!
50...? 50...?
To me, this town is...
Hold it, you guys!
What?
--What?
--I won't allow any of us to go get him.
I've gained the power I need
to fulfill my ambition!
Oh, Sanji! There's a ship.
Nojiko, Gen-san, and everyone
in Cocoyashi Village...
You guys all are...
It's missing both a sail and an ensign.
We're sailing full-speed
toward trouble already?!
I wonder how they'll feel when they see this...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Departing the City of Water!
Usopp Mans Up and Brings Closure to the Duel!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Most Heinous Power!
Blackbeard's Darkness Attacks Ace!"
"The Mysterious Band of Pirates!
Sunny and the Dangerous Trap"
"Goodbye My Dear Underlings!
Franky Departs!"
"Wanted Posters Make It Around the World!
Celebration in Their Hometowns
as the Ship Moves Forward!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!