Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Live as you please, Luffy.
In the flow of time, as a result of
various circumstances and strong spirits,
people come to question the world they live in!
The day we meet will come at some point.
The judicial island Enies Lobby is the front door
that leads to the World Government,
a huge organization.
Now that they've caused it to fall,
neither the Navy nor pirates
will leave them alone.
You can say that the Straw Hats
are now known all around the world.
And so is this wanted poster.
Sanji! You're the best!
Isn't this incredible?!
It's the spitting image of him!
He pulled one crazy stunt!
Hey, look! It's an article on Straw Hat!
Looks like he toppled the Tower of Justice.
His bounty is going to skyrocket after that!
Enies Lobby is famous
for Water Seven's sea train.
It isn't that far from here...
This must be a twist of fate.
For them to be within range...
What a pitiable, unfortunate crew.
Let's go, Captain!
Of course we're going!
Come on! Get ready to set sail!
We're about to get busy!
Hey!
Hold it, Teach!
I've been looking for you.
What?
Go back three days before the
world was shocked and amazed
by the Straw Hat Pirates' wanted posters.
There was an event that
occurred on a certain island.
This is Banaro Island on the Grand Line.
"The Most Heinous Power!
Blackbeard's Darkness Attacks Ace"
Oh, Ace! Commander!
Don't call me "Commander" after all this time.
That word is meant to be
reserved for people you respect.
Don't mock me.
Oh, so you must be "Fire Fist" Ace.
Yeah, that's me. Nice to meet you!
I see... you've already become
a great captain in your own right.
Isn't that right, Captain Marshall D. Teach
of the Blackbeard Pirates?
Jeez, Ace! I haven't seen you in ages!
So what's the deal?
How'd you know I was here?
Teach, let's cut the idle talk!
You should know the rules, having lived
through twice as much as others.
Isn't that right?
Yeah, I get it.
But let me say something first!
What do you say, Ace?
Why don't you join my crew?
Seize the world with me!
I've already planned out how
I'm going to rise up in power!
Whitebeard's reign is over!
I'll become the next Pirate King!
For starters, I'm gonna kill
Straw Hat Luffy, who is in Water Seven,
as a gift to the Government!
Luffy? What did you just say?
Oh! You know him?!
Another reason I can't let you go free!
He's my brother!
What?
And naturally, there is no way I'm going to...
...join your crew.
Damn!
One of your men could use a lesson in manners!
Fire Gun!
Flame Commandment!
Fire Pillar!
Auger, Burgess! Keep outta this!
You don't stand a chance
against that man. Stay back!
--Sorry!
--Fire Fist!
--Captain!
--Aw, that burns!
Captain!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
I'm burning!
Hot, hot, hot, hot!
Wow, hot, hot!
Captain!
Damn it! Hot, hot, hot, hot!
Shut up, men! Give me some space!
I get it, Ace. You're burning
to kill me, aren't you?
It's no surprise. Murdering a
crewmate is a grievous crime.
It's true that I killed the
4th division commander Thatch!
I didn't have a choice! He got his hands on
the Devil Fruit that I had my sights set on!
The ship's rule dictated that whoever
found the fruit could eat it, remember?
I memorized what every fruit
in the book looked like,
so I knew it was the one I'd been
looking for the second I saw it!
The only reason I spent all those
decades on Whitebeard's ship
was because I figured that was
the most likely place to find it!
I woulda given up if fortune
hadn't smiled down on me,
but that fruit fell into my friend's hands!
So then you killed Thatch and stole it?
Well, that's how the ball bounces.
This ability chose me, Ace!
It has made me the most
powerful person out there, Ace!
Look! It's rare, even for a Logia type.
Ace, isn't your body made out of fire?
Mine is darkness!
Look! It's the same black smoke from earlier.
Those pirates are still in town.
They're still going at it?
If they destroy any more of our village...!
Keep away from them!
Our only option is to run!
Darkness...?
That's right, Commander Ace. You can't kill me.
It's said that this is the most
evil power in Devil Fruit history.
It's the Logia Devil Fruit, Dark-Dark Fruit.
I've become a man made of darkness.
I'll give you a taste of just how powerful it is!
Go ahead and try.
What are you doing?! Hurry!
The captain is about to cut loose!
If we don't hurry away from here,
we'll get caught in the attack!
Stand right back up!
The darkness gushing from his body
is crawling across the ground!
Creepy! It's pitch black, almost like
there is a hole in the ground.
It's scary how it feels like it could absorb you.
Hurry and get away!
Get as far away as you can!
Go through the forest!
Run all the way to the beach!
Darkness is gravity!
It has the power to pull everything in!
Not even a ray of light can
escape from its infinite gravity!
But you're up against me...
and I'm still untouched.
I'm not going after you just yet.
You can stay there and
enjoy the view of the town.
Black Hole!
The ground is devouring the town!
Why? Wh-What's going on?
Dark gravity uses its limitless power
to condense objects and crush them!
Is this a nightmare? Our village is...
And now I'll show you what
happened to the missing village.
Behold the shambled mess it has become!
Liberation!
Our village... has been reduced to rubble...
Now do you get it, Ace?
This is the power I've obtained!
Firefly!
Fiery Doll!
Hot, hot, hot, hot!
That burns!
--I fully understand how great
the power of darkness is.
--Hot, hot, hot, hot!
But here's what puzzles me...
--If it's a Logia, these attacks
should go right through you.
--Dang, this is hot! Hot, hot, hot, hot!
I already told you:
Darkness draws everything in,
including bullets, swords,
punches, fire, and lightning!
Unlike the rest of you, I don't get the
option of letting stuff pass through me!
My body feels far worse pain than the
average person in every way possible!
But in exchange for accepting that risk,
there is one other thing...
...that I am able to absorb.
Vortex!
To be exact, dark gravity has the ability
to draw in a Devil Fruit
power holder's physical body.
Gravity?!
And my body...
Well? Have you figured it out, Ace?
It couldn't be...!
I bet it's been a while since someone's
landed a punch on you, eh, Ace?
I think that you got it when I grabbed you!
Another thing that my darkness drags in is...
...Devil Fruit powers!
That means that while I'm touching them,
Devil Fruit power holders
can't use any of their powers!
Logia, Zoan, and Paramythia!
Against a world of Devil Fruit power holders
who are overconfident in their abilities,
I've obtained a means of attack
that cannot be defended against!
So I just can't let you catch me, right?
I already proved that you can't
escape from my dark gravity!
Vortex!
St. Elmo's Fire!
Take this!
Damn it! The fire lances...!
He messed up some vertebrae!
His new power is a pain...!
Cross Fire!
Banana Rock...! It's collapsing!
What's going on? They can't be humans!
Forget the village! What is going
to happen... to our whole island?!
I had assumed that Devil Fruit power holders
were so preoccupied with their powers
that they would be pushovers
once they lost them.
But I should have expected one
of Whitebeard's commanders
to be a fearsome fighter
in basic combat as well.
Now then, today brings us
to another crossroad of fates.
Everything is rendered
powerless before darkness!
Even someone as powerful as you.
But this makes me want
your power all the more.
Ace, join my crew!
If I yield to power, there's no
point in being born a man.
I'll never leave anything to
be regretted later in my life!
Do you understand, stupid?
How long can you live like that in this world?
It's a pity, Ace!
Die in darkness!
Flame Commandment...
Flame Emperor!
The sun or the darkness--
there'll be only one winner!
I'm gonna make Whitebeard the king!
The "Decisive Battle of Banaro Island"
on the Grand Line...
The fight between these two pirates...
...will be described as the trigger for a
massive incident that is soon to take place.
We're hitting the sea of adventure!
Head straight for Fishman Island!
No, no, no, no! With the New World nearby,
we should exercise caution!
Oh, Sanji! There's a ship.
It's missing both a sail and an ensign.
We're sailing full-speed
toward trouble already?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Mysterious Band of Pirates!
Sunny and the Dangerous Trap"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!