How'll we save Luffy?!
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
I left everything this world
has to offer there!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
And so men rushed onto theGrand Line
in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Now, come on board, Franky...
As the Straw Hat Pirates
headed for the New World,
The bounty hunters have left
to hunt the Straw Hat Pirates,
The Straw Hat crew
encountered the Accino Family
On their way to the New World,
the Straw Hat Pirates
Board my ship.
who have fallen for their trap.
in the ice-enclosed ocean, the Arctic Path.
a suspicious ship appeared before them.
were confronted by the
Accino Family bounty hunters.
Don't be so cocky!
Luffy and his crew helped
those aboard the ship, but...
I guess I don't have much choice
but to help you guys out!
Coup de...
We finally found you!
...Burst!
There is someone else I'd like you to see.
I, Franky, will be the shipwright on your ship!
A total bounty of 600 million Berries, eh?
Dearies, now that you've
wandered into the Arctic Path,
I can't wait to see their Jolly Roger!
I-Is that the patient?
Hey! Rejoice!
you'll never get to see
the open ocean ever again.
The Straw Hat Crew dodged the Accino Family
Click.
It's me!
What is it?
Why don't we celebrate early?
and managed to get the Sunny
outside of the Arctic Path once,
Say your prayers!
I have managed to successfully
drive the prey into a tight corner.
Although we said all sorts of things
to each other, we're friends!
May our beloved Papa, Don Accino,
Meanwhile, Luffy and Chopper
tried to return to the Sunny
I'll let these little things go!
only to lose their Jolly Roger,
the embodiment of their pirate souls.
Oh?
My, my.
and the Accino Family's knit
blood relations be blessed!
How appropriate for such a splendid day.
after treating Puzzle's wounds, but...
Stop...
And the flapping Jolly...
How could you call this a "mission"?!
joking.
And here's to our present for Papa--
Count us out!
If that's what you want...
It's gone!
the heads of the Straw Hat Pirates.
We're going to steal this ship
and prepare to strike back.
Our Jolly Roger is gone?
...let me say one last thing.
Cheers!
As things stand now, Vigaro-san
will never be able to rest in peace!
You guys...
The Sunny is gone!
Hey, punks!
"The Dream Sinking in the New World!
The Disillusioned Pirate, Puzzle"
I'm sorry!
You're free toargue amongst yourselves...
In order to escape from
the surrounding icebergs,
The secret behind the
Arctic Path's moving icebergs
...but I don't like the direction
this conversation's going.
they tried to blast free with the Sunny.
I'm sorry for being bullheaded!
were the peculiar Savage Penguins.
I was wrong!
The icebergs moved?!
Coup de...
"Sunny's in a Pinch!
Roar, Secret Super-Speed Mecha"
Usopp!
...Burst!
Are you morons?
Freezing!
It's only natural for icebergs to move.
Water moves!
Perhaps that's not quite what they meant.
D'oh!
Luffy...
Crap!
You idiot!
Now that the Straw Hat Pirates
have been split up,
But the Accino Family implemented
a certain plan to foil their escape.
Right.
Grab my hand already!
They aren't moving because of the currents.
the Accino Family is swooping
in to claim their heads.
Why not get the flag first?
They're moving of their own accord!
N-Now, now.
Of their own accord?
Let's play, Miss!
Don't get worked up, brothers!
Hey, don't give us this crap
first thing in the morning!
Just for the record, we aren't
the least bit suspicious!
What do you think about this
for the ship's name, Franky?
Watch and see!
Your luck bites.
A strange fish?
We're really just a group
of good-natured fishermen.
Sanji-kun, if you please.
The pirate ship...
I am Blend-sama, the second
son in the Accino Family!
Okay!
...Thousand Sunny!
Right, men?
Coup de Burst!
We'll only let your sketchy antics go so far.
Simple fishermen don't offer pirates
booze laced with some anesthetic.
"The Assassins Attack!
The Great Battle on Ice Begins"
It consumes three barrels of cola,
"Desperate Battles for the Straw Hat Crew!
Pinning Their Pirate Souls on the Flag"
but it lets us fly one kilometer.
There's nothing the Going Merry
could do that this ship can't.
"Lovely Land"?
Our Jolly Roger...
Love...?
It's gone missing?
It exceeds the Merry in every way.
When'd that happen?
But the Merry's brave soul will be
That's right!
Wh-Where'd it go?
Now then, it's time you came clean!
Your flag is in Lovely Land!
It's gone!
inherited by the Thousand Sunny.
Gone! Gone! Gone! Gone!
The Accino Family's base of operations
is none other than Lovely Land!
What the heck are you--
Yeah!
W-Wait a sec!
Wh-What the heck?!
If we have a heart-to-heart, I think
we can and can't see eye-to-eye...
Where do you see cuffed pirates smile
as they're handed to the Marines?
Go, my kite, Uo!
Well then, once again...
Once more!
To Robin and Usopp, who came back to us,
Which is it?!
Well, like I said...
to our new friend, Franky...
That's right!
Lovely Land!
...and to our pirate ship, the Thousand Sunny!
H-Hey, guys!
W-Wait!
Whoa!
I don't care about that!
Cheers!
Don't mess with them, Guile!
For chunks of ice, they're bossy punks!
There are only three of them!
Cheers!
I was still in the middle of my explanation.
What's up, Nico Robin?
Let's go!
Let's take this ship by force.
Our next destination is Fishman Island!
It couldn't be...
Huh?
Wait!
Is something over there?
Yeah!
Then we can go back to...
I'm through with taking
orders from those freaks!
Luffy!
Oomph!
B-But they've been so good to us!
Oh, well.
You caught me off guard a second ago--whoa!
Found it!
Jolly Roger, found!
I can't...
Where?!
But that won't happen again.
It's just too heartless!
A bird-like fish has it!
Shut it!
If you won't seize their ship, we will!
Hey, raccoon!
I'm not a raccoon!
I thought so.
What?!
At the very least, don't hurt the lady!
Your captain isn't too bright, is he?
The people we saw earlier
have stolen it from us.
It's no wonder you lost
your precious Jolly Roger!
Right!
You can't hurt her!
What?!
Don't, Vigaro...!
I saw one of them issue that fish an order.
Hey, ex-pirates!
So that's your answer, huh?
It's just a mass of ice.
Get ready for the worst!
Hey!
You're going to see Hell,
all because you covered
But it definitely moved to block our path...
It's nice and straightforward.
It's taking our Jolly Roger back
in the direction we just came from!
for that pathetic excuse of a captain.
Damn it!
Sanji-kun?
The iceberg itself seems normal enough.
There were also those
Marine ships last night.
If you dilly-dally, who knows what
will happen to the flag we stole?
You bastards!
Don't mess with them!
It feels like something is
trying to lure us somewhere.
Papa, are you looking at your
collection by yourself again?
Gum-Gum...
I have no idea who it is,
but they've got guts!
Hey, where do you think you're takin' us?
What?!
Gatling!
Whoa, there.
Yeah.
Isn't it obvious?
Is everyone already here?
We're going back!
Crap!
You were awfully quick.
Let's duke it out!
What?!
I figured I'd let him attack me until
he wore himself out and screwed up...
Don't be stupid!
We're going to get started
on the preparations now.
We just escaped.
But first we have to figure out
who exactly is behind this.
Calm down, Sanji-kun!
I'll make sure that you have
a special birthday, Papa.
We're still missing both Luffy and Chopper!
Oh, sorry!
...but he isn't showing any openings!
A-A few of mycrew mates have short fuses.
Yeah, and Zoro!
In fact, his openings are getting smaller!
At times like this, you should
think before you leap!
It's not like they meant you any harm.
Hey, you!
Quit moving!
Isn't that right?
Hey, I said to quit moving!
Right?
Don't "eheh heh" me!
C'mon!
You have a cute ship!
Freeze!
What are you trying to hide?
Swap out with me, Jiro.
They clearly "meant us harm"!
What was the name?
Go get some sleep.
We can't afford to stay put.
It's the Thousand Sunny.
I'll keep an eye on the captain.
Brrr!
Vigaro...
A Jolly Roger is as important
to a pirate as his own life!
Thousand...?
It's freezing!
Wait...!
Jeez!
You still haven't dealt with them?
We can't allow even one to get stolen!
No, I meant your name.
"The Mysterious Band of Pirates!
Sunny and the Dangerous Trap"
I thought they seemed fishy.
My name?
Puzzle-san?
We know that, but first we
should meet up with Luffy--
Vigaro...!
For fishermen, you didn't seem like
youwere all that great at fishing!
I am Robin.
Vigaro...
I've got another reason!
Nico Robin.
Come on!
Nico Robin?
Vigaro!
Ow...
Right.
We aren't nave enough to fall for that one!
Guys, do you want our captain
to scold us for screwing up?!
Didn't I see you earlier?
What is it?
What happened?
You recognize me?
Minus a certain two, that is!
Puzzle-san...!
Of course!
Puzzle-san is...!
C-Commander Stansen...!
I was surprised when you
showed up so suddenly.
Ow...
We're in trouble!
Ah, this is bliss!
I can't believe you guys!
Now then, you'd better be ready to fight!
Pure bliss!
Puzzle-san...
Say, Lil, do you know where
the rest of the crew is?
Thank goodness!
Nothing beats bathing in a massive
tub that sways on the waves!
Really!
Thank you, Doctor!
In that case, we'll just have to...
No!
The Thousand's crew?
You really are a great physician!
Anything but that!
I don't know!
Retreat!
I couldn't take it!
Whee!
I see...
I-I'm not happy about getting called a
"great physician" or anything, you punk!
This here is my room.
No way!
My pride won't let me endure
a lecture from that moron!
But I know where your flag went!
"What seems to be the problem?"
Dang...
Jiro, what am I doing here?
Wait, darn it!
Just kidding!
Aren't you searching for it?
Those two...!
Don't let them escape!
Yes.
Damn it!
I'm so excited!
Where is it?
Okay!
I'm gonna give your whole crew a watery grave!
Don't you remember, Captain?
I wonder if I'll
get a patient anytime soon.
Let's go!
We were attacked by some really
strong guys in the New World...
Could you tell me?
It's okay.
Leave them be.
I caught something!
Actually, have you seen Chopper?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Looks like I got a cool shark!
Will you...
I can't find him anywhere.
Put it in! Put it in!
play with me?
Crap!
Huh?
Chopper?
Let's put it in the aquarium!
What was that?
Not again.
Will you play with me?
Oh, crud!
Put it in!
Are you gettinga bad feeling about this?
What the hell?!
In ya go!
I'll tell you if you do.
Yay!
How can they move?
Who are those guys?!
Those men must have kidnapped him.
All right, I'll play.
Put out the fire!
They're just ice!
Don't drag your feet!
Really?
It looks like we can't get any further
Please help me!
That seems likely enough.
Yay!
How is an attack like that even possible?!
They dropped in another one.
Tch, the punks!
until we learn the truth
behind these icebergs.
Isn't it a shark?
My big sister hasn't been
playing with me lately.
Hurry and carry the injured!
Well?
Isn't this a nice room?
At any rate, the quickest way to find
out is to board their ship and ask.
Franky!
The room's great,
She's always playing with him.
Yeah?
I'd like to borrow something.
but I can't believe those
idiots tossed in a shark!
She's always with that creepy guy.
Let's hurry.
Great!
Now let's go see it!
The wind is picking up.
Let's check out the aquarium!
This could turn into a storm!
Hey!
With that having been said,what
should we do about these two?
Did a shark come in?
Nice!
It's an awesome one with horns!
This is really nice!
Retreat!
Yes, it did, but you've lost all
of the other fish you caught.
Get us out of here as fast as possible!
Yes, Salchow!
I can't believe them!
The punks!
We're looking truly terrific!
Where did they go?!
What is with these two?
Wake up!
Think about compatibility
before you throw something in!
Ow!
It's not like they're launching an attack!
We still weren't ready... for the New World!
Isn't that a no-brainer?
I, Hockera-sama, will find them first!
They're just circling around us
over and over and over again!
Hey!
Darn it!
It's super cold out here!
This punk's gonna be tonight's dinner!
Eep!
What's gotten into you?
Just you wait and see!
Yeah!
All righty!
And my head hurts.
Sanji, roast it!
It's not like Puzzle the
Phoenix to sound defeated...
Jump and kick!
We'll barbecue that stupid shark!
It hurts bad!
Lan la-lan la-lan!
Wait, you amateur!
I'm not a phoenix!
Arbell, the rink today...
It's still a fresh fish.
I'm just a whippersnapper
that got in over my head.
I should either make sushi or serve it
boiled with a hot and sour miso sauce.
is perfect for... skating on!
Moron!
Listen to me, Puzzle.
I told you not to underestimate them!
We really don't have time for this, Honey!
We've followed you because we believe in you.
Tempura might be nice, too.
Darn him!
Darn it!
I'm starting to get hungry!
You've ruined the plan I devised!
Jump and kick!
We need to hurry and find those pirates!
That's because--
It's no use, Captain!
They're too fast!
Don't be in such a rush, Darling!
You're right, Salchow!
Yeah, I'm terribly sorry...
No matter how hard they try,
there is no escape from the Arctic Path!
I think... we're going to
get... some good skating in!
But seriously, thank you
for this great ship, Franky!
Puzzle, I'll buy some time!
N-Next time, we'll--
They aren't gonna let us
up and leave, are they?
Stansen, bring out the raiding dory!
Indeed, it's impossible!
It's no biggie!
Hey, Sanji!
Oh, forget it!
Yeah?
Nice!
But you still haven't seen
its true power yet.
First Officer!
Don't we need to hurry back to the Sunny?
That expression was nice!
You can pull back.
Hurry!
Sir?
Honey, you're the best!
R-Right!
Oh, jeez!
Wait, Vigaro!
Yeah...
Didn't you hear me?
Its true power?
I'm going with you!
Then do something about these two!
Idiot!
Yeah!
I said that I want you worthless
pieces of trash to keep out of my way.
But it's strange how we haven't found
them despite all of this searching.
This ship's key features are
its "Soldier Dock System."
You can't leave the ship!
You're the captain!
La-la!
But...!
I wonder what rock they're hiding under...
Did I make myself clear?
There are five docks ranging from
Channel 0 to Channel 4 located on the bilge.
Puzzle, I believe in you.
Arbell-chan, that's sexy!
Y-Yes...
You're absolutely right!
So sexy!
You are the man who will
become the King of the Pirates!
Soldier Dock System, Channel 3!
Each dock is rigged to
handle different situations.
Right!
That's right...
You're super easy on the eyes!
Right!
This is just how he is...
Roger!
Hey, Vigaro!
You're super sassy!
...all the time!
Right!
Wait!
All of them will play a unique role
in assisting the Thousand Sunny!
Take care.
Captain, here it comes again!
Darn it!
Hey, punks!
Click.
You're the ones who stole
our flag, aren't you?
Wow!
Men, we have a change of plans.
Then lemme see them in action!
Hey, hold your horses.
Arbell, you're nice even on the rink!
Where did you put that flag?!
We're going with Trap: Sea Gull.
I'll let you see them as they're needed.
Really nice!
Listen to me!
Yessir!
M-Meteors?!
It'd be a shame to show them off all at once.
La la-la la!
I can hardly wait.
Damn those jerks!
Boo! Boo! Boo! Boo!
What is with this couple?
Vigaro!
How dare they trick us like that?!
I bet Papa-san would be tickled pink
That was a great bath!
Shark Submerge III, take off!
if we finished these two off
and brought back their heads.
Chopper...
Even First Officer Vigaro didn't last more
than a few seconds up against them...
Definitely, Salchow!
I'm sure he would be!
I thought it seemed a lot colder
than yesterday, and I was right!
I'd say that was enough for our warm-ups.
But during that brief period of time,
he managed to destroy their rudder.
Hey, you jerk!
O-Our heads?!
Where are you hiding Chopper?
S-So they really are...
I wonder if we've entered
a winter island's currents.
Captain Straw Hat, I hate to do this
after you took such good care of us,
Thanks to him, we were able to escape...
But Kokoro-san never mentioned
anything about this...
It's show time!
Love Throw!
but it's time we parted ways!
That's why everyone who
survived swore an oath!
What?!
H-Hey!
Wait a sec, geezer!
Arbe--
It's snowing?
What do you think you're doing?!
Well?
Yay, it's snowing!
How does it feel inside
my Shark Submerge III?
Crap!
He's going to cut the rope
that's connecting our ships.
We should be like our first officer
and protect the captain with our lives!
Yahoo!
Sweet!
Ain't it super?
What?!
Wait, damn it!
Hey, Zoro!
Damn it!
Sanji-kun, do you copy?
You're spoiling the party!
Gum-Gum...
Once more!
She blew me off...
Love Throw!
Pistol!
This is how you're supposed
to act when it snows:
I read you loud and clear, Nami-san.
The lady is flying into my chest!
You're absolutely right, Jiro!
"Guys, it's snowing!"
So?
I'd be willing to lay down
my life for Puzzle-san.
Have you learned anything yet?
I guess you still didn't know that.
Damn it...!
It looks like we'll have
to dive a bit deeper...
The wind--!
You really aren't that bright!
Dumb-dumb!
Franky, please take us
directly under the icebergs.
D... Damn it...!
Oops!
Nothing ticks me off more than
having them call me names!
Same here!
A power holder?
Let's protect the captain!
Sure thing!
Yeah!
But your powers won't help you!
Let's do it!
I can't believe he sent a lady flying...!
Sounds good.
I'm going to the New World!
Wow!
What a vile thing to do!
What?!
I haven't seen snow in ages.
Huh?
Robin!
I wonder if it'll stick.
What's that?
Way to go!
I hope it does!
What is it, Nami-san?
Did you find something?
But then Stansen-san...
Maybe I should make something
warm for dinner tonight.
It's the guy from earlier...
She's another Devil Fruit power holder?
Please slow down a bit.
Why do you think Vigaro was willing
to sacrifice his life to protect yours?
Yeah.
You're the guy who stole
our Jolly Roger, aren't you?
Salchow-sama, Trap: Sea Gull is set!
Huh?
Stop right there!
Your Jolly Roger got stolen?
Great!
Who coulda done that?
Don't you dare throw your life away!
Then let's get it under way!
What is that...?
You're working for a group
of bounty hunters...?
It's show time!
It wasn't you?
Then let's go!
It's true that they're incredibly strong
We're wasting our time.
Yeah.
I swear, this place is too cold!
and we were a mess after the New World...
W-Wait!
Timeout!
I can understand why we lost,
Don't quit the game!
What's that music?
Y-You were right!
but then they stole our Jolly Roger...
M-My Family stole your flag.
Hey?
They noticed us!
Hey, there's a ship!
our pride as the Phoenix Pirates....
Do you hear that?
What did?
I don't know!
Something seems a bit off.
It's coming from over there!
Where is it?
What?!
How could he...?
What's with the music?
It seems off?
The location?
They're headed straight for us!
How so?
Where, indeed?
What are?!
Stansen-san is a coward!
Just get us outta here!
What gives?
If you don't know, we're leaving!
Something is coming!
Whoa! Whoa!
It doesn't have any sails,
let alone an ensign.
But that's all coming to an end today!
W-W-Wait!
Wh-What's going on, Nami-san?
Crap! Crap! Crap!
Timeout!
It doesn't have any sails?
Don't go!
Puzzle the Phoenix has risen once more!
That means it's just floating there!
Don't go just yet!
What is that?
I actually do know where your flag is.
It's either a ship in distress, or it's a...
Puzzle-san!
Don't push yourself!
What's going on?!
Then where is it?!
Come to think of it,
Go faster!
Er, where was it again?
It's okay.
some pirates play a nasty game
called the "Davy Back Fight."
No way...!
I feel fine now...
I-It's the Marines!
We're gettin' nowhere fast!
What?!
Gather the whole crew up on the deck.
Tch!
Yeah, we know.
Timeout!
They've already sniffed us out.
Why'd they have to show up now?
You don't think...
I didn't know you had projectiles!
they fell victim to that game, do you?
Aye, Captain!
Darn it!
That isn't how real men fight!
This is bad!
Nami-san!
Get us out of here, Nami!
Just a sec!
You shoulda played nice and told me
you packed that stuff from the start!
Some people just came out.
I'm on it!
This is really bad!
The captain has regained consciousness!
Hey, is that true?!
The Straw Hats' ship is on the move.
Fishing?!
It's too cold for this!
They must be in distress.
The day we've been
dying for has finally arrived!
Why don't we give them a bit of a scare?
Please send him flying already!
They look horribly exhausted.
Sure thing!
Do it!
This is the revival of the Phoenix Pirates!
Yessir!
Hey, Captain!
Let the game begin!
Now that damn Stansen will
get what's coming to him!
Yeah, let's go check on them.
If they end up being our enemy,
we'll just send them flying!
D'oh!
If it's my projectiles versus yours,
I'm not gonna lose!
Crap!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
They're firing at us!
Puzzle-san!
Hurry it up, Nami!
They're gonna blow us sky-high!
What was that?
I know, I know!
Found 'em!
Tch!
This defeats the point of my winter outfit!
Sanji-kun!
Let's go.
Aye aye!
Damn it!
Wait for me, Honey!
There aren't any fish out there that'll
bite a hook without bait, are there?
I'm not done yet!
Crap!
Men, I'm sorry to have put you out.
I'm starting to lose visibility.
Light up!
Light up, pronto!
It was nothing!
I thought he was just goofing off,
Don't say that.
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Don't even say that...
Imagining today made it easy!
but I'll never get anywhere if
I can't see where I'm shooting!
It beats doing nothing.
That hurts!
Puzzle-san, I'm glad you're okay!
Hey!
And the cold is starting to numb my movement.
They're in front of us, too!
We've got time to kill,
so let's be patient and wait.
Nami, what now?
I need to finish this fast!
Let's go, Chopper.
Hard left rudder!
Uh-huh.
Aye aye, sir!
Puzzle-san!
It looks like you're struggling!
We must have fallen from up there...
Dance, dance!
Wha--?!
Dr. Chopper!
Luffy-san!
Hey, are you guys all right?!
You're wasting your time if
you can't see your target!
Light up Numbers Six, Seven, and Eight!
Now eat this!
P-Pirates!
Thank you so much.
You can't see me!
Pirates!
No!
They're over here, too?
It was nothing.
What?!
Dang!
I only did what any doctor would do.
M-Make a break for it!
Tsk!
No way!
If it isn't a cute penguin.
I don't have time to play with an idiot!
What's going on?
I'll be sure to pay you back someday!
The rudder doesn't work!
Penguin!
Pen-pen!
And we don't have any sails!
Penguin!
Next time we meet will
be in the New World, huh?
Please show mercy!
Hey, now...
This can't be real!
Y-You found me...?
What's going on?
Yeah!
Youch!
Long time no see.
That's right!
You were also headed for
the New World, weren't you?
What's up?
W-We're surrounded!
Hey, look.
Then that means we'll be
rivals from here on out!
Now, which hand is the coin in?
Nice!
Really nice!
It's a penguin colony!
Dang, both you and your ship are
in sorry shape! You're both a mess!
I can barely wait!
Hmm, give me a second.
What will you do next?
Captain, we need to hop to
it and build up our forces
What should we do, Nami?!
Wh-What should we do?
This one!
so we can return to the New World...
Please figure somethin' out, Nami!
Who are you guys?
What type of question is that?
Hmph!
Captain?
Jeez, you're annoying!
W-We're just humble fishermen.
Our only option is to run!
I'm trying to think!
Say, Lil?
Hey?
Captain?
What?
Nami-san, there is a hole
right through there!
Where is our flag?
Puzzle-san?
Fishermen?
Yeah.
What?
I don't know!
About three days ago, we were
attacked by an unidentified ship.
No way!
For real?!
We...
Please!
Don't leave me!
Damn it!
Won't you tell me?
Don't leave me!
What's with these birds?!
Where?! Where?! Where?!
But I don't know!
Wow!
Someone please tell me!
aren't going back to the New World.
There really is one!
Not only did they steal all
of our valuables and food,
Think we can make it?
Please save me!
Help me!
but they also trashed our sail
and destroyed our rudder.
Let's go!
You got it!
We've been floating out here ever since!
Okay, okay!
So you've got nothing to gain by attacking us.
No...
I'll tell you!
I'll tell you where it is!
Stansen's decision was right.
No worries there!
Really?
Really!
Long story short, all of
you are hungry, right?
Honest!
We're going to continue working
for those bounty hunters.
What's going on?!
Sweet!
We were just about to eat, so come join us.
It won't work!
Now I can get back.
The wind changed directions.
We can't get on course!
All of our flags are in Papa's room.
No way!
What?!
Savage Penguins?
Are you serious?
Why?
Why?!
Your Papa?
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Whoa!
Right!
Yeah!
They're a violent breed of
penguin that inhabits these parts.
He has a whole bunch!
My cook can't turn a blind
eye to guys like you.
I can't take any more of this!
D-Damn it!
His room is covered with Jolly Rogers!
H-Have you lost your mind, Puzzle-san?!
The rudder won't budge!
They're what has been moving the icebergs.
Don't be strangers!
Move it!
Hey, Sanji!
Everyone is willing to fight to
the death, just like Vigaro-san!
It's filled with them?
Awesome!
Jerk!
Today is his birthday, so everyone
came to pick up a birthday present!
Is it ready yet?
What was that for?!
Have you forgotten?
The bounty hunters use them to
round their prey into one area.
We're starving!
We've got a Soldier Dock
System for times like this!
Yeah, it's just about ready,
That's right...
but first...
Was the flag the present?
Vigaro died... all for me.
That is why it's said there is
no escape from these waters.
Chopper!
Channel 0...
Boo!
You've been dying to get some patients.
Bad guess!
Puzzle, I believe in you.
Go tend to them.
Activate!
Got it.
Hey!
S-Sure...
These are the presents.
With its cola-run engine,
it's the Paddle Ship Sunny!
Chopper, we're going back to the Sunny!
You are the man who will
become the King of the Pirates!
This person has a 300-million-Berry bounty.
For starters, let's have
anyone injured come see me!
Y-Yeah!
This one has a 120-million-Berry bounty.
What?!
Is anyone too badly hurt to move?
This one has a 44-million-Berry bounty.
Thank you for everything.
But we have you on our side, Puzzle-san!
Their pet just talked!
Later!
Go!
And then...
H-Hey!
I'm not a pet!
Let him go.
I'm a pirate, too!
It's all the same, no matter where he goes.
We've been waiting this whole time
for the Phoenix to rise from the ashes!
...you have an 80-million-Berry
bounty, right?
I'm worth a whopping 50 Berries! Damn it!
Wh-What's going on?
What happened to Puzzle the Phoenix?!
On the ocean, there is no
defying fate.
Gum-Gum...
Jiro, lend me a hand!
Ouch!
Sit still.
Pistol!
This rocking is going to
split his wounds back open!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Isn't that right?
The Phoenix...
Okay!
Is your flag all that important?
only existed
in the world of fairytales.
Of course it is!
That flag represents our pride!
Yahoo! We got through!
I have no right to go to the New World
when I couldn't protect my crew!
Thanks for having us!
It's more important than anything else!
Awesome!
Later!
It looks like the Marines can't
do a thing to stop us!
Gum-Gum...
Battle Axe!
Of course not!
Careful there!
How could you say that, Captain...?
No one can keep up with us!
That means nothing to a raccoon like you.
I can't accept that...
I suppose these are rookie
pirates who just hit the seas
We're talking pirate talk right now.
Our flag...
with their new ship and stars still in their eyes.
Super!
What about the Jolly Roger
they stole from us?!
What is it?
Shut up!
I am a pirate!
Click.
Hello?
It's me.
The operation is complete.
How do things look over there?
Don't think you'll get off lightly for this!
What's this?
We successfully got the Straw
Hatsto head for the Arctic Path.
We don't need a Jolly Roger anymore.
Oh, hello.
To be honest, we're in the middle
of winning a pirate crew over...
What could a raccoon possibly hope to do?
And here I'm sure you told me he was dead...
Shut up!
They fell for it hook, line, and sinker.
uh, sir.
Whoa!
What a great success!
Hmph!
Aren't you the feisty one?
So what does their
Jolly Roger look like?
They have no hope to escape now, none at all.
Damn it!
Have you lost all sense of pride?!
Uh, it's a skull wearing a straw hat, I believe.
What was that?!
It's an honor to meet you in person,
Puzzle the Phoenix.
Now let's report to Campaccino-sama!
I don't mind if you take me down,
but what will you do about your flag?
Come again.
If you take me out, who will
guide you to Lovely Land?
It's not like you'd go hunting
for bugs out on the ocean.
Hey, Luffy...!
What could they be thinking?
Hey, wait!
Don't make small talk with me!
I'd love to thank you for tending to me,
I'm sorry about that.
Luffy!
but I'm afraid we lost
everything in the New World.
No worries there!
N-Now listen to me carefully!
Those are the Straw Hats,
Those waters...
I'll ask for directions after I whack you!
with a total bounty of
600 million Berries on their heads!
The New World isn't as
forgiving as you think.
Chopper, where are you?!
600 million, sir?!
That's right!
Hey, Chopper!
That's okay.
I'll find out when I get there.
We came to get you!
That voice...
You know what you must do, don't you?
Besides, we're strong!
Let me know if you're here!
It's Luffy.
Yes, all too well...
I'll be right back.
Listen, don't you dare let
them escape before we arrive!
D-Dr. Chopper?!
Hey, where are you?!
We managed...
Chopper!
Click.
Wait!
Don't move!
Don't take another--
600 million Berries on their heads...?
to get away...
That's enough!
What the heck were...
Straw Hat...
those birds?
I suppose a 300-million-Berry bounty
won't go down without a fight...
I'm sorry!
I'm terribly sorry!
Lan la-lan la-lan!
Hey, knock that off...
That's okay.
It'd be safest if I threw in the towel for now
and finished them off at Lovely Land.
Lan la-lan la-lan!
I'll find out when I get there.
Why are you kowtowing to him?!
Shut up!
Besides, we're strong!
I am terribly sorry about
how rude we've been!
All right!
I-It's the couple from earlier...
You win!
I feel bad about tricking you.
Don't take the New World lightly, Puzzle.
Just give me a--
I swear, you certainly are stupid.
Give back my Jolly Roger!
I'm begging you!
Don't worry, Vigaro! I'm a phoenix!
Please forgive us!
None of that matters.
Didn't I warn you that there was no escape?
You bastard!
We just cameto get Chopper back.
Good!
Yahoo!
W-Wait!
This is too good, Mister Eyebrow!
I give!
I surrender!
I see.
Seriously!
Right?
It's an honor to see you once more!
Uh-huh!
I'm raising the white flag!
Then do as you please.
It's so good it's making me cry!
As a sign of our growing closer...
This guy keeps throwing me off.
Are they crying drunks?
Don't get near me!
U-Understood!
Actually, I have your flag right here.
We'll go searchfor your
ship's doctor right now!
Wow!
You ladies sure are cute!
I'll hand it over now...!
Luffy!
Sure are!
Chopper!
Jiro...
You're so cute you're making me cry!
Dang, that was close!
Jeez!
Let's go, Chopper.
So you were here after all.
So it would seem.
Luffy!
But...
C'mon.
Let's hurry on back.
And they were late to notice us!
He's given up on their Jolly Roger.
Oh?
Actually...
Give our Jolly Roger back!
Would you like to fight a round?
Wait!
Don't take off with him!
They aren't pirates anymore.
Ah, crap!
I still need the doctor to stay here!
I see you're halfway decent.
Who're you?
R... Right...
But you're doomed now that we've found you!
Luffy!
If you're dead set on
taking him now, I'll...!
This is the end of the line.
You'll what?
I can't believe you fell for it!
Jiro!
Nice!
There...
Excuse me!
I dare you to come after me
if you want the real flag back!
Don't do it, Jiro!
You sounded so cool, Honey!
Huh?
Put me down!
Didn't you leave to eat?
Don't be crazy!
He'll kill you!
As for you ex-pirates!
Thank you, Darling!
So what if he does?!
What's the matter?
You'd better prepare yourselves!
I'm not afraid to die!
Doctor, please!
Not in front of me!
I'm not like you cowards!
Doctor, after seeing what you can do,
Hey, get away from her!
there is someone else I'd like you to see.
Kissy!
Mr. Ugly!
I'm not gonna lose!
Quit kissing right in front of me!
I don't care how strong he is,
I'm never gonna lose ever again!
Guys, you're so annoying!
Could you follow me aboard our ship right now?
Puzzle-san?
Puzzle!
Let go of me!
What?
Chopper, what the heck is going on here?
I thought I was gonna die!
Luffy,
honestly, I want to stay
here for a while longer.
That was a nightmare!
Luffy!
Goodness!
Love Throw!
Luffy!
Chopper!
I have a patient who is badly hurt.
They'll be fine without us!
I've already finished the operation,
but he's still in critical condition.
What now?!
Guys, take care of the ship!
Show yourself!
Please!
You can count on me!
They're the ones who stole our Jolly Roger.
I want to look after him until
he regains consciousness.
I've finally found ya!
I'm sure of it!
We're going to swerve around to the right!
What?!
You're headed straight
for the New World?!
'Kay!
Who're you?!
That right?
Hard a-starboard!
Okay.
No one will think any less of you!
You've incurred the wrath of the almighty
Usopp-sama, you stupid doting couple!
Hard a-starboard!
In that case, we can wait.
Turn around now!
I'm Hockera, the third
boy in the Accino Family!
It's hell over there.
What?
You're going to be my presents to Papa!
Special Attack: Flame Star!
Have you been there?
Presents to Papa?
N-No...
Uh, we've only heard rumors...
What're you talking about?
Bull's eye!
Doctor, thank you for
what you said back there.
Bad move!
Turn us around!
Arbell!
Supposedly it's a horrible place!
To the left!
Take this!
Arbell!
Jiro, I don't know much about you guys.
Stupid!
Oh, Arbell!
This is what happens to the fools
who damage a pirate's pride!
Arbell!
I don't care what the rumors claim.
And it looks like you can't
disclose what's going on.
I'm gonna put you on ice!
I'll find out for myself if it's
like hell when I get there.
But don't you worry.
I may be a pirate, but I'm also a doctor.
Franky!
Stop!
How dare you hurt my partner?!
If I see someone in pain,
The icebergs are gathering together.
it doesn't matter who he is,
We were really in the groove!
I'd give my life to treat him!
Bring it on!
What was that?
Hey, Sanji!
Where do you think you're taking us?!
If you're looking for a
playmate, I'm game, kiddo!
Damn it!
We're also a band of pirates.
Oh, sorry about that!
The rudder's not responding.
I'm gonna break your nose!
No, look over there!
It looks like you've been
looking after my men for me!
You guys are pirates?
I'm sorry!
Please let show you my gratitude!
Yeah...
I'm their commander.
L-Luffy!
And this man is the captain of
our pirate band, the Phoenix Pirates.
The name's Stansen.
Luffy fell into the ocean!
When the waterways got blocked,
it created those whirlpools.
Was it all for their Jolly Roger...?
Why would he do that if he couldn't swim...?
What is with these waters?!
He's Puzzle-san the Phoenix.
It's my best brew,
which I had specially ordered!
Luffy!
No, you don't!
Phoenix...?
Please help yourselves.
Let's play, Miss!
Yeah?
Yeah.
Doctor, you can't swim either!
No matter how dangerous the situation got,
Th-That's...!
Now that you mention it...!
no matter how severely he got injured,
Who are you?
I wanna turn that into
shaved ice and gobble it up!
I am Lil.
he always stood back up!
So?
He was just like a phoenix...
Shaved ice?!
Will you play with me?
S-Stupid!
Captain!
It's huge!
How are we supposed to set
sail without the Jolly Roger?
I burnt him to a crisp!
Looks good!
Do you think the Sunny is okay?
Everyone, go look for it!
Wh-What?!
Do you really have a patient down here?
This isn't the time for that!
Sure!
I didn't feel a thing!
There's nothing to worry
about with them around.
I'll be back in just a sec!
You can't kill me with that toy.
By the way, do you know which
direction I'm supposed to be rowing?
Gum-Gum...
Are you a monster?!
Gatling!
Yeah!
Nope!
Hey, it's about time you put that back.
I'm a phoenix!
We were the ones in a bind!
They're in an uproar, claiming that
the Jolly Roger "went missing."
Whoa, there.
Where does
he think he's taking me?
Me and the guys...
Yeah!
I'm going to become the King of the
Pirates under this Jolly Roger!
We all felt that he was going
to become the King of the Pirates.
He's a Devil Fruit power holder?
It's pushing us back where we came from!
And...
Whoa! Whoa!
I'm tired of hearing that,
but I have to agree.
What?!
It's a waste of time.
But things were different over there!
What gives?!
Battle Axe!
That's what makes you the captain!
The New World was on
a completely different level.
It looks like you live up to your
reputation as the "Phoenix."
I don't think anyone can defeat us!
You went to the New World?
Yeah,
But I'm afraid you'll be
stripped of that title today.
but we didn't stand a chance.
P-Please wait!
They didn't even take Puzzle-san seriously.
Y-You must be mistaken!
This isn't our captain.
We managed to escape somehow.
My shaved ice...!
They truly were on a completely
different level...
I-Is that the patient?
This is just a worthless
crewmate who got injured.
Yeah.
The Sunny is gone!
Our captain died a long time--
But...
His entire body is seriously injured.
This is the Arctic Path.
But I still believe that Puzzle-san will
rise back up, just like a phoenix!
Any ship that wanders in never
sees the open ocean again.
It's been days since the
last time he was conscious...
How dare you bastards try to trick us?!
Please, Doctor!
You've got to help him get better!
I should teach you a lesson!
There is no mistaking him!
What the heck?!
Damn it!
This is horrible!
That's Puzzle the Phoenix,
with a bounty of 100 million Berries.
I-It's the Phoenix's Jolly Roger!
His wounds are festering!
I can't take it anymore!
Curse that jerk Stansen!
Why did you let him get this bad?!
Wasn't he supposed to be dead?
Shhh!
Dang, that was pathetic!
Stansen!
Quit leaving "Commander" out
when you say his name!
We've been had!
It's not like I had a choice...
What's going on?
That Stansen guy tricked us.
If you're gonna run from a fight,
you should give up being pirates!
What made that noise?
He'll whack us again if he hears you.
It's not safe to move him!
Oh, Stansen!
Straw Hat Luffy,
a 300-million-Berry bounty, is with him,
Hmph!
Are you okay?
I'm going to begin the
operation right now.
Like I care!
Don't be so harsh.
I've just abouthad it with
that freaking coward.
bringing them to a total
of 400 million Berries.
It just goes to show how powerful
this Jolly Roger has grown.
Well?
This is turning into something else!
Come out and say it!
Let's hurry and inform Blend-sama!
Yeah!
Fess up that the useless man
over there is your captain.
Don't you feel the same way?
This has a unique flavor.
Guile's right!
Puzzle the Phoenix is still alive?
How can you stand things the way they are?
So you had booze, even though
you didn't have anything to eat!
How dare the fallen pirates
deceive the Accino Family?!
Seriously!
Pretty much!
How long must we endure this humiliation?
But, wow, this is good!
They've got some nerve!
It's like finding a port in a storm!
First they stole our Jolly Roger,
Siblings, we can add another present
to the list for our beloved Papa!
Puzzle, I believe in you.
and then they made us their lackeys!
We really ought to do more to thank you!
I'm going to check on it right quick.
You are the man who will
become the King of the Pirates!
Don't sweat it!
You may handle things here!
That isn't an option!
Jerk!
Hey, Vigaro!
How dare you take advantage of the
confusion to grab onto Nami-san?!
You really must drop by our port
Wait!
so we can thank you properly.
What were you thinking?!
Why are you using the paddle wheel?
"Drop by our port"?
I'd rather die than join the likes of them!
Franky, where have you been?
Luffy!
In other words, you want us
to take you there, right?
I was fully charging the cola
barrels in the energy room.
Thank goodness!
Luffy-san...
Moron!
You caught on?
Luffy!
Good guess!
Why do you think Vigaro was willing to
sacrifice his life to protect yours?
I'm so glad you're okay!
If my guess is right, there will definitely
come a time when we need them.
Captain, what are you doing?
You're one funny man!
Let that creep have it!
It's great!
All right, we'll take ya.
At any rate, if we're ever going
to get out of these crazy waters...
Go on, Captain!
I'm so happy!
Really?!
I appreciate it!
Don't you dare throw your life away!
Wait, Luffy!
What about Fishman Island?
...first we've got to unravel the
puzzle behind the moving icebergs!
That brat just let the cat out of the bag!
If we visit any of the other islands,
it'll change our log's course.
We believe that once the
captain has recovered,
You're the captain of this ship.
There has to be some sort of trick.
we'll steal our Jolly Roger back and
return to our pirate ways.
Won't it be fine if we leave
as soon as we drop them off?
In other words, you have
a 100-million Berry bounty!
That doesn't mean squat to us!
C'mon! What's the big deal?
It doesn't?!
But I bet Stansen's plans are different.
They're in need of help!
It'd be a cinch for us
to get out of this place!
Although it still stands to be
proven whether you're a man worthy
Man, I'm glad you have such
an understanding captain!
How are they different?
Well, I'm counting on you to get us there!
When you get down to it, he's just
a coward who's afraid to die.
of such a bounty.
It's obvious by the way
he treats those hunters!
Oh, yeah!
Captain...!
Captain!
Oh, yes!
Our defeat in the New World must
have shaken him to the core.
What happened to Straw Hat?
He was supposed to be here.
Here you are.
Are you also hiding him somewhere?
For now, all we can do is pray
for the captain's recovery and wait.
Well?
Out with it!
You still haven't caught them?
How is the Straw Hats' flag coming?
But if anything should
happen to the captain...
Stansen!
It should be here soon, Papa.
We finally found you!
Captain, why?
You know, they say that the people
you travel with make the journey.
Please calm down.
Huh?
I am calm!
Dearies, now that you've
wandered into the Arctic Path,
Go back to the way you used to be!
...he's obviously going to
continue working as a hunter
Really?
So I'd say we're due for another "cheers"!
I'm glad to hear it.
Please!
to prolong his own sorry life!
Well, they say that you enjoy things more
if you have to wait for them, Papa.
Come back to us!
you'll never get to see
the open ocean ever again.
Yeah, sounds good!
But not me!
Cheers!
Say your prayers!
If it means giving up being a pirate,
Damn it...!
Hey!
Huh?
I have to agree!
I'd rather defy him and
challenge the hunters to a fight
We came back.
Did someone pass by just now?
You have a hilarious captain.
Don't you?
as a member of the Phoenix Pirates!
No, I didn't notice anyone.
Incoming!
Don't you?
We always see eye-to-eye, don't we?
How is he, Doctor?
What's that?
If the time comes, I'll join you!
Have you had too much to drink?
Naturally!
I've done everything I can.
I don't know...
How about you?
I joined this band out
of respect for Captain Puzzle.
Now all we can do now is wait.
They're stifling.
That beautiful lady is
with such a hideous man!
Sorry!
Thank you, Doctor!
At any rate, hurry up with the flag!
Could you give us a lift after all?
Yeah!
We can't let our guard down.
Uh-huh.
No matter what happens to the captain,
I'll see how it's coming along.
S-Straw Hat?!
we can't do anything that
would hurt his name!
He isn't over the worst of it yet.
Hey, you there!
I challenge you to a duel right here--
Didn't you return to your own ship?
Hey!
Yes?
That's true...
Also check on Straw Hat.
Ow...
I'm afraid we don't have
time to play with you.
I'm sure Vigaro-san wouldn't want to
see us like this from the other side!
Certainly, Papa.
An iceberg forced us back.
And I didn't know which way to go!
Yeah.
It's about time we took our leave.
All right!
It sounds like everyone is
prepared for the worst.
D-Didn't they think of that before they left?
You sure are dense!
We were just telling you
that there is no escape!
Tonight will be a critical
turning point for all of us...
Dunno...
None at all!
If anything happens to the
captain, you know what to do.
That hurt...
In other words, it's impossible!
Where am I?
Whoa!
Nice!
That expression was nice!
True, it must be terribly difficult to find
Wasn't it?
a pirate ship that has lost its mark.
We always see eye-to-eye, don't we?
Eh, Captain Straw Hat?
The best part of a game is the brawl!
What should we do?
Isn't it obvious?
But today is my lucky day!
Do it, Franky!
A brawl?
We've got to do it!
Got it!
To think I ran into two
wanted men at the same time!
I'm good at those, too.
Here I go!
I'm not excited about this...
Wow!
Coup de Vent!
Everywhere you look, there are icebergs.
You mean three.
They were such considerate guys, you know?
And who are you?
What is it?
True enough!
Your luck bites.
Something feels off...
And the girls were cute.
Coup de...
I am Blend-sama, the second
son in the Accino Family!
Because of these icebergs,
How could you say that?!
it almost feels like the ship
is following a path of its own...
We don't have a choice in the matter!
Hey, geezer!
He's right!
Game set...!
If we lay claim to this amazing ship, I bet we could take them on!
What happened to you?
...Burst!
What was that?!
Listen to me!
Dang, talk about dangerous!
Not happening!
You see, that flag of yours has been
added to our family's collection.
Super!
Oh?
We are going to hand this ship over to them.
Sanji-kun, look ahead!
What--?
And right when I ran outta cola!
Crap!
We are merely going to carry out
whatever missions they assign to us.
Hard aport!
Your collection?
What's with this place?
We stole your pirate flag of
a skull wearing a straw hat.
It's too cold!
How could you call this a "mission"?!
It's kinda cramped in here, huh?
Wh-What type of ship is that?!
Damn it!
Count us out!
Sorry.
We're going to steal this ship
and prepare to strike back.
Nice!
That's really nice!
What about a flag...?
I kept you waiting, didn't I?
Phew, that was close!
I wanted to lend you a hand
and tried pressing some buttons,
As things stand now, Vigaro will
never be able to rest in peace!
Th-They stole our Jolly Roger, too.
What's the matter, Salchow?
What was with that iceberg?
It came out of nowhere!
Hey, punks!
but nothing would turn on and it's cold...
The ship...
You're free to argue
amongst yourselves...
is f-flying away in the sky!
What's going on?
I don't know if it's your symbol or
your cymbal, but you're not all that great
Do you expect me to believe that nonsense?
What's wrong with it?
...but I don't like the direction
this conversation's going.
There is something weird about these icebergs!
Jeez!
if you've got something that easy
to steal out on display, Straw Hat.
But...!
Hand that over!
That pounding won't stop and
the temperature keeps dropping!
It looks like they're moving on their own.
Brother, he's telling you the truth.
W-Weren't you sound asleep?!
The ship is flying away
right before my very eyes.
This isn't funny!
The smell of anesthesia was so
strong that I couldn't fall asleep.
What?
Pounding?
You see, those new recruits screwed up!
Uh-huh!
Papa, we've run into some trouble!
You ruined my cuisine with that nasty drug!
Oh, but I was sure to chase our
prey into the usual area, Brother!
It couldn't be...!
It isn't your place to call me that.
You better be prepared to
pay for what you've done.
Why not get the flag first?
Well, we may only be
brothers-in-law, but we are still--
Hey, if you know how to
pick a fight with a pirate,
Way to go, Papa!
Really, Campaccino!
That's a splendid idea.
I can't believe you're teasing my honey again!
then you're prepared to face one, right?
The three of them can
handle this on their own...
Salchow, you didn't fail to finish
off that big fish, did you?
He said to get the flag first, my darling.
I caught them alive!
Sure thing, my honey!
Never let your guard down!
Where is our Jolly Roger?!
But, but, I didn't let them get away!
Your Jolly Roger should be
in Lovely Land by now.
I did everything I could!
Hey, Lil-chan!
Okay, Honey?
If you want it back, I dare you to go get it.
Could you summon
that one critter for us?
Really!
Click.
Don't expect me to pamper you!
No!
Huh?
Eh?!
What was that?
Er, um, I'm sorry, but you can't just--
But I'm so cold without you that
I'm afraid I'll freeze, Arbell!
Lovely Land?
Happy birthday!
Uh-huh.
Two?
Lil-chan, you'd be doing it
as a favor for me, too.
Oh, is that right?
Oh, you're so silly!
Uh-huh.
Okay.
Plus it was an order from our beloved Papa.
You got it.
The party is on hold.
We're going to have to personally
hunt down that prey.
It's freezing!
Click.
What is it?
I have managed to successfully
drive the prey into a tight corner.
Go, my kite, Uo!
The timing couldn't be better!
We can work together as siblings to
catchthem as our birthday present for Papa!
Oh?
Some rookies are currently
onboard their ship right now.
Just wait until you see
what we bring in, Papa!
Them?
They've proven surprisingly useful.
What... is that?
Hey, Arbell!
Sir, if I may be so bold,
it's still too soon to say.
Go, my kites, Uo!
Let's go together.
I can't, Lil!
You know that.
After all, they have hooked a rather large fish.
I'm paired with my darling!
A strange fish?
Now then, let's resume our game.
I hate that man.
A large fish?
What happened?
Yes, sir!
Monkey D. Luffy and his
Straw Hat Pirates.
My third oldest brother
caught two of the bounties.
A total bounty of 600 million Berries, eh?
Their total bounty comes to 660 million Berries!
I can't wait to see their Jolly Roger!
It was her and him.
C'mon, c'mon!
Hurry!
My, my.
Why don't we celebrate early?
Let's play!
At long last, we can finally relax!
How appropriate
for such a splendid day.
R-Right.
May our beloved Papa, Don Accino,
Why don't we play some more at your house?
Indeed!
The ocean really is great!
It certainly is!
Blue skies and white clouds!
Well, I'm counting on you.
and the Accino Family's knitblood
relations be blessed!
Huh?
You'll come to my house to play?
The shining sun and the flapping Jolly...
Sir! You can leave this to me!
Will you invite me over?
And here's to our present for Papa--
Sure!
But honestly, you know, this really--
Click.
It's gone!
the heads of the Straw Hat Pirates.
Our Jolly Roger is gone?
Cheers!
I expect this to turn into quite the party.
And Zoro appears to be missing, too...
Damn it!
Now head on out, my
beloved sons and daughters!
I can't believe they got lost again!
It's time for the hunt to begin.
Are they stupid?!
You jerk!
Brrr!
Isn't it troublesome when
you have unexpected guests?
Wh-What's going on?!
Look out!
It's freezing!
Your "Boho boho" is getting old!
Sanji-kun, hard aport!
Why are there two of the same guy?
Not only are the icebergs
cold, but they keep moving!
I can deal with guests!
Give our Jolly Roger back!
You've got it, Nami-san!
Wow!
Is he a Devil Fruit power holder?!
What is with these waters?
Hey, aren't we completely
surrounded by Navy ships?
That flag--our Jolly Roger--
represents our pride as pirates!
It goes from one thing to the next!
I bet the others are taking it easy,
drinking tea on the ship.
It's a clone technique!
It feels like they're luring us somewhere...
That's so cool!
We can't let you keep it!
Hey, Chopper!
You seem somewhat happy.
Let's give it a try.
Wait, damn it!
Look out!
Sure!
Hard a-starboard!
I'll show you this ship's super powers!
Luffy, watch out!
I've got no objections!
The rudder's frozen!
You're gonna fall!
But how do we do it?
What's that gaudy building?
Are Luffy and Chopper ready yet?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Stifling to the Max!
The Twins' Magnetic Power Looms"
"The Dream Sinking in the New World!
The Disillusioned Pirate, Puzzle"
"The Assassins Attack!
The Great Battle on Ice Begins"
"Sunny's in a Pinch!
Roar, Secret Super-Speed Mecha"
"Desperate Battles for the Straw Hat Crew!
Pinning Their Pirate Souls on the Flag"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!