Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
As the Straw Hat Pirates
headed for the New World,
a suspicious ship appeared before them.
Luffy and his crew helped
those aboard the ship, but...
There is someone else I'd like you to see.
I-Is that the patient?
Click.
What is it?
I have managed to successfully
drive the prey into a tight corner.
Oh?
My, my.
How appropriate for such a splendid day.
How could you call this a "mission"?!
Count us out!
We're going to steal this ship
and prepare to strike back.
As things stand now, Vigaro-san
will never be able to rest in peace!
Hey, punks!
You're free toargue amongst yourselves...
...but I don't like the direction
this conversation's going.
"Sunny's in a Pinch!
Roar, Secret Super-Speed Mecha"
N-Now, now.
Don't get worked up, brothers!
Just for the record, we aren't
the least bit suspicious!
We're really just a group
of good-natured fishermen.
Right, men?
We'll only let your sketchy antics go so far.
Simple fishermen don't offer pirates
booze laced with some anesthetic.
Now then, it's time you came clean!
What the heck are you--
W-Wait a sec!
If we have a heart-to-heart, I think
we can and can't see eye-to-eye...
Which is it?!
Well, like I said...
H-Hey, guys!
W-Wait!
Don't mess with them, Guile!
There are only three of them!
Let's take this ship by force.
Yeah!
Then we can go back to...
I'm through with taking
orders from those freaks!
B-But they've been so good to us!
I can't...
It's just too heartless!
Shut it!
If you won't seize their ship, we will!
At the very least, don't hurt the lady!
Right!
You can't hurt her!
So that's your answer, huh?
It's nice and straightforward.
You bastards!
Don't mess with them!
What?!
Whoa, there.
Oh, sorry!
A-A few of mycrew mates have short fuses.
It's not like they meant you any harm.
Isn't that right?
Right?
Don't "eheh heh" me!
What are you trying to hide?
They clearly "meant us harm"!
Brrr!
It's freezing!
Jeez!
You still haven't dealt with them?
I thought they seemed fishy.
For fishermen, you didn't seem like
youwere all that great at fishing!
Come on!
We aren't naïve enough to fall for that one!
Minus a certain two, that is!
C-Commander Stansen...!
We're in trouble!
Now then, you'd better be ready to fight!
In that case, we'll just have to...
Retreat!
No way!
Wait, darn it!
Don't let them escape!
Damn it!
I'm gonna give your whole crew a watery grave!
It's okay.
Leave them be.
Actually, have you seen Chopper?
I can't find him anywhere.
Chopper?
Oh, crud!
Are you gettinga bad feeling about this?
Those men must have kidnapped him.
That seems likely enough.
Tch, the punks!
At any rate, the quickest way to find
out is to board their ship and ask.
Let's hurry.
The wind is picking up.
This could turn into a storm!
With that having been said,what
should we do about these two?
I can't believe them!
Wake up!
Ow!
Hey!
It's super cold out here!
Eep!
Yeah!
And my head hurts.
It hurts bad!
Moron!
I told you not to underestimate them!
Darn it!
You've ruined the plan I devised!
Yeah, I'm terribly sorry...
N-Next time, we'll--
Oh, forget it!
You can pull back.
Sir?
Oh, jeez!
Didn't you hear me?
I said that I want you worthless
pieces of trash to keep out of my way.
Did I make myself clear?
Y-Yes...
You're absolutely right!
Right!
Roger!
Take care.
Click.
Men, we have a change of plans.
We're going with Trap: Sea Gull.
Yessir!
Damn those jerks!
How dare they trick us like that?!
Chopper...
Hey, you jerk!
Where are you hiding Chopper?
Captain Straw Hat, I hate to do this
after you took such good care of us,
but it's time we parted ways!
What?!
H-Hey!
Wait a sec, geezer!
What do you think you're doing?!
Crap!
He's going to cut the rope
that's connecting our ships.
What?!
Wait, damn it!
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
The wind--!
Oops!
A power holder?
But your powers won't help you!
What?!
Robin!
Way to go!
She's another Devil Fruit power holder?
Salchow-sama, Trap: Sea Gull is set!
Great!
Then let's get it under way!
It's show time!
What's that music?
Hey?
Do you hear that?
It's coming from over there!
What's with the music?
Something is coming!
What is that?
No way...!
I-It's the Marines!
What?!
Tch!
They've already sniffed us out.
Why'd they have to show up now?
This is bad!
Get us out of here, Nami!
I'm on it!
This is really bad!
The Straw Hats' ship is on the move.
Why don't we give them a bit of a scare?
Do it!
Yessir!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
They're firing at us!
Hurry it up, Nami!
They're gonna blow us sky-high!
I know, I know!
Sanji-kun!
Aye aye!
I'm not done yet!
Light up!
Light up, pronto!
Hey!
They're in front of us, too!
Nami, what now?
Hard left rudder!
Aye aye, sir!
Dance, dance!
Light up Numbers Six, Seven, and Eight!
No!
They're over here, too?
No way!
What's going on?
Hey, now...
This can't be real!
What's going on?
W-We're surrounded!
Nice!
Really nice!
What will you do next?
What should we do, Nami?!
Please figure somethin' out, Nami!
Jeez, you're annoying!
I'm trying to think!
Nami-san, there is a hole
right through there!
What?
No way!
For real?!
Don't leave me!
Where?! Where?! Where?!
Wow!
There really is one!
Think we can make it?
Let's go!
You got it!
What's going on?!
It won't work!
The wind changed directions.
We can't get on course!
Whoa!
I can't take any more of this!
D-Damn it!
The rudder won't budge!
Move it!
Jerk!
What was that for?!
Have you forgotten?
We've got a Soldier Dock
System for times like this!
Channel 0...
Activate!
With its cola-run engine,
it's the Paddle Ship Sunny!
Go!
Wh-What's going on?
Jiro, lend me a hand!
This rocking is going to
split his wounds back open!
Okay!
Yahoo! We got through!
Awesome!
It looks like the Marines can't
do a thing to stop us!
Of course not!
No one can keep up with us!
Super!
The operation is complete.
We successfully got the Straw
Hatsto head for the Arctic Path.
They fell for it hook, line, and sinker.
What a great success!
They have no hope to escape now, none at all.
Now let's report to Campaccino-sama!
Chopper, where are you?!
Hey, Chopper!
We came to get you!
That voice...
Let me know if you're here!
It's Luffy.
I'll be right back.
D-Dr. Chopper?!
Hey, where are you?!
Chopper!
Wait!
Don't move!
Don't take another--
That's enough!
Straw Hat...
I'm sorry!
I'm terribly sorry!
Hey, knock that off...
Why are you kowtowing to him?!
Shut up!
I am terribly sorry about
how rude we've been!
I feel bad about tricking you.
I'm begging you!
Please forgive us!
None of that matters.
We just cameto get Chopper back.
Right?
Uh-huh!
This guy keeps throwing me off.
U-Understood!
We'll go searchfor your
ship's doctor right now!
Luffy!
Chopper!
Jeez!
So you were here after all.
C'mon.
Let's hurry on back.
Actually...
Wait!
Don't take off with him!
I still need the doctor to stay here!
Who're you?
If you're dead set on
taking him now, I'll...!
You'll what?
Jiro!
Don't do it, Jiro!
Put me down!
Don't be crazy!
He'll kill you!
So what if he does?!
I'm not afraid to die!
I'm not like you cowards!
I'm not gonna lose!
I don't care how strong he is,
I'm never gonna lose ever again!
Let go of me!
Chopper, what the heck is going on here?
Luffy,
honestly, I want to stay
here for a while longer.
I have a patient who is badly hurt.
I've already finished the operation,
but he's still in critical condition.
Please!
I want to look after him until
he regains consciousness.
That right?
Okay.
In that case, we can wait.
Doctor, thank you for
what you said back there.
Jiro, I don't know much about you guys.
And it looks like you can't
disclose what's going on.
But don't you worry.
I may be a pirate, but I'm also a doctor.
If I see someone in pain,
it doesn't matter who he is,
I'd give my life to treat him!
We're also a band of pirates.
You guys are pirates?
Yeah...
And this man is the captain of
our pirate band, the Phoenix Pirates.
He's Puzzle-san the Phoenix.
Phoenix...?
Yeah.
No matter how dangerous the situation got,
no matter how severely he got injured,
he always stood back up!
He was just like a phoenix...
Captain!
I burnt him to a crisp!
Wh-What?!
I didn't feel a thing!
You can't kill me with that toy.
Are you a monster?!
I'm a phoenix!
Me and the guys...
We all felt that he was going
to become the King of the Pirates.
But things were different over there!
The New World was on
a completely different level.
You went to the New World?
Yeah,
but we didn't stand a chance.
They didn't even take Puzzle-san seriously.
We managed to escape somehow.
They truly were on a completely
different level...
But...
But I still believe that Puzzle-san will
rise back up, just like a phoenix!
Damn it!
I can't take it anymore!
Curse that jerk Stansen!
Shhh!
Quit leaving "Commander" out
when you say his name!
He'll whack us again if he hears you.
Hmph!
Like I care!
I've just abouthad it with
that freaking coward.
Don't you feel the same way?
Guile's right!
How can you stand things the way they are?
Seriously!
How long must we endure this humiliation?
First they stole our Jolly Roger,
and then they made us their lackeys!
What were you thinking?!
I'd rather die than join the likes of them!
Moron!
Why do you think Vigaro was willing to
sacrifice his life to protect yours?
Don't you dare throw your life away!
We believe that once the
captain has recovered,
we'll steal our Jolly Roger back and
return to our pirate ways.
But I bet Stansen's plans are different.
How are they different?
When you get down to it, he's just
a coward who's afraid to die.
It's obvious by the way
he treats those hunters!
Our defeat in the New World must
have shaken him to the core.
For now, all we can do is pray
for the captain's recovery and wait.
But if anything should
happen to the captain...
...he's obviously going to
continue working as a hunter
to prolong his own sorry life!
But not me!
If it means giving up being a pirate,
I'd rather defy him and
challenge the hunters to a fight
as a member of the Phoenix Pirates!
If the time comes, I'll join you!
Naturally!
How about you?
I joined this band out
of respect for Captain Puzzle.
Yeah!
No matter what happens to the captain,
we can't do anything that
would hurt his name!
That's true...
I'm sure Vigaro-san wouldn't want to
see us like this from the other side!
All right!
It sounds like everyone is
prepared for the worst.
Tonight will be a critical
turning point for all of us...
If anything happens to the
captain, you know what to do.
Wow!
Everywhere you look, there are icebergs.
What is it?
Something feels off...
Because of these icebergs,
it almost feels like the ship
is following a path of its own...
What was that?!
Dang, talk about dangerous!
Sanji-kun, look ahead!
What--?
Crap!
Hard aport!
Damn it!
Phew, that was close!
What was with that iceberg?
It came out of nowhere!
What's going on?
There is something weird about these icebergs!
It looks like they're moving on their own.
What?
You see, those new recruits screwed up!
Oh, but I was sure to chase our
prey into the usual area, Brother!
It isn't your place to call me that.
Well, we may only be
brothers-in-law, but we are still--
Really, Campaccino!
I can't believe you're teasing my honey again!
Salchow, you didn't fail to finish
off that big fish, did you?
But, but, I didn't let them get away!
I did everything I could!
Okay, Honey?
Really!
Don't expect me to pamper you!
But I'm so cold without you that
I'm afraid I'll freeze, Arbell!
Oh, you're so silly!
The party is on hold.
We're going to have to personally
hunt down that prey.
The timing couldn't be better!
We can work together as siblings to
catchthem as our birthday present for Papa!
Just wait until you see
what we bring in, Papa!
Hey, Arbell!
Let's go together.
I can't, Lil!
You know that.
I'm paired with my darling!
I hate that man.
A total bounty of 600 million Berries, eh?
I can't wait to see their Jolly Roger!
Why don't we celebrate early?
May our beloved Papa, Don Accino,
and the Accino Family's knitblood
relations be blessed!
And here's to our present for Papa--
the heads of the Straw Hat Pirates.
Cheers!
Now head on out, my
beloved sons and daughters!
It's time for the hunt to begin.
Look out!
Sanji-kun, hard aport!
You've got it, Nami-san!
What is with these waters?
It goes from one thing to the next!
It feels like they're luring us somewhere...
Look out!
Hard a-starboard!
The rudder's frozen!
Are Luffy and Chopper ready yet?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Dream Sinking in the New World!
The Disillusioned Pirate, Puzzle"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!