Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
I left everything this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
The words "given up" sound so lame...
Hot-Hot powers, to the max!
Here's the thing about phoenixes:
The Arctic Path is enshrouded by ice.
No matter the hardship,
they always rise back up!
They don't suit you, Captain!
Maximum Heat Level: 10,000 Degrees!
Their total bounty exceeds 600 million Berries.
You're the man who's supposed
to become the King of the Pirates!
After getting split up,
the Straw Hat Crew are attacked
And they're reborn even stronger than before!
This Jolly Roger belongs to the Straw Hat Crew.
by a group of bounty hunters
known as the Accino Family.
You can still heat up?
What do you think with your
120 million bounty, Roronoa Zoro?
The idiot...! All for me, everyone is...
"We'll Be Waiting in the New World!
Parting with the Courageous Pirates"
I...
It's show time!
Love Throw!
The lady is flying into my chest!
Sorry, men! I was a foolish
captain who couldn't live up
How the hell did you get that Jolly Roger?!
"A Mansion in Chaos! An Enraged Don
and an Imprisoned Crew"
"The Phoenix Returns! The Dream
Sworn to Friends on a Jolly Roger"
to the trust my precious friend placed in me.
But... But I wanna let...
Today is his birthday, so everyone
came to pick up a birthday present!
I'm hot! Hot! Hot!!
...Vigaro see it once more!
Luffy...
He has to see our flag flying
above the ocean where he's at rest!
Was the flag the present?
Luffy!
Boo! Bad guess!
What on earth...?
These are the presents.
Hey! Give back my flag!
You have a 80-million-Berry bounty, right?
Wh-What's going on?!
That was close! But I'm not
about to fall into the ocean!
Hurry! We've gotta get our flag back!
It looks like Luffy is here.
Luffy and the men on Puzzle's ship
He's come for our Jolly Roger.
You can count on me! It was around this floor!
catch the second oldest son
in the Accino Family, Blend.
That's right! We're finished!
How far can you run?
Sweet!
Ah, crap!
No! We can still make it!
"Around" this floor?
That doesn't bode well...
Indeed. I don't know how
Luffy learned about the flag,
Wh-Wha--?!
You may have a 300-million-Berry bounty,
but you're nothing before us!
Luffy!
Straw Hat!
but it's not as though he
witnessed it getting stolen.
Huh? Where is this?
I've had enough of your yapping!
Give back our Jolly Roger!
Yep! Which means we've still got a chance!
Unforgivable! I'll melt
the likes of you in a flash!
I know where the Jolly Roger is.
I'm willing to lead the way.
Which room is it in, Zoro?
Sultry Hot Night!
You can leave it to me.
If you can defeat us brothers...
Don't rush me.
Sweet!
How could I not?! Luffy's on his way!
Luffy!
Way to go, Robin!
...we'll take you to that flag.
As for you ex-pirates!
You'd better prepare yourselves!
You're far more reliable
than that lame moss head.
What?!
It's this one!
Jerks!
Put 'em up, you sauna freak!
I nearly fell!
Promise to become my big sister.
Puzzle-san?
Puzzle!
Yow, hot! Hot, hot, hot!
Having a hard time fighting on the ice?
--He's this way!
--Got it!
Do and I'll save you.
It's just as tricky for you!
You still haven't caught them?
How is the Straw Hat's flag coming?
I wouldn't be so sure.
Gum-Gum Pistol!
It should be here soon, Papa.
Please calm down.
The Arctic Path falls under
the Accino Family's territory.
You've made a fool of the Accino Family!
--That way!
--Got it!
Rocket!
When we're in unison, no one here
stands a chance against us!
Where am I?
So you're the one who stole
our Jolly Roger, Naked Balloon!
Meanwhile, Nami and Franky got caught
by the Accino Family's third son, Hockera.
Furthermore, we have the power
of magnetism that strongly unites us!
What?!
Oh! They found some high-end flour.
Hmph! So what if I did, whippersnapper?
Second Gear!
It figures!
Monkey D. Luffy, you're doomed
to succumb to our brotherly love!
Gum-Gum...
Maybe it was the next floor up.
Damn it!
...Jet Pistol!
I can't trust you!
I'm gonna kick your butt right
quick and get our flag back!
Nose Jet!
I've heard enough of your boasting.
Just come at me already!
If you don't remember, come out and say so!
See anything to point us in the right direction?
I'll break your nose!
"The Super Hot-Hot Final Battle!
Luffy vs. the Scorching Hot Don"
I'll kick your butts in no time flat!
At this rate, it'll be dark before we find it.
Scary!
What a brat!
I know! We've gotta find the flag
and fast! If Luffy finds out about this...
Usopp, how dare you harm a lady?!
Hot-Hot Head!
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
Hey! Give back my flag!
Hey! Are you turning against me?!
How dare you hurt my sweet honey, Arbell?!
L-Luffy!
Wow! So you're a Devil
Fruit power holder, huh?
Wait!
Monkey D. Luffy, we siblings...
Hey, Arbell-chan!
It truly has been a long time
since I personally hunted a pirate.
Take this, you punk!
Welcome to Lovely Land.
Ow, hot...
...will be taking your head!
Huh?
I never expected the 300-million
bounty to come on his own.
You should be honored, Straw Hat!
Eat this! Flame Star!
Straw Hat!
I'm amazed you were able to dodge that!
Huh? This is Lovely Land?
Don Accino...
Whoa! Move!
So he's the head of that
family of bounty hunters, huh?
Die!
Let's get him in one go,
Big Brother Campaccino!
Sure is!
It's a weird house.
Papa is growing anxious.
Youch, that smarts! I whacked my head!
What type of powers did he
get from the Hot-Hot Fruit...?
H-He's here!
Naked Balloon!
It's the end of--
It's his fault that the temperature
has been going up and down!
It's Luffy! W-We're doomed!
Steam Iron!
The great Usopp-sama
Headbutt worked! Just as planned!
You really are in perfect unison!
You're going to kick my butt?
10,000-Degree Press!
Don't laugh!
We've hit the worst-case scenario!
Thinking back, I've met countless
pirates who've made that same claim.
Arbell-chan, are you all right?
This really stinks...
Gum-Gum...
I should have expected as much
from a 300-million-Berry bounty.
Tsk!
...Jet Gatling!
Salchow...
Hey! Where are you going?
You really did a number on us!
Isn't it obvious?
Nah, I haven't done anything yet.
Are you stupid or what?
Who're you?!
I'll use sheer willpower to get
the Jolly Roger back if I have to!
Do you know what happened to them?
--Each and every one...
--Gum-Gum...
Go wander these halls forever!
Jet Whip!
You should let me finish talking!
The pirate scum...!
Shut up, you stupid cook!
"Stifling to the Max!
The Twins' Magnetic Power Looms"
How dare he mock us?!
...Pistol!
Curse you!
Die!
Robin!
Hot! Hot!
Robin-chan!
I'm freezing!
I can melt... anything I touch.
I've been searching for you.
I heard you're the one
who saved me. Thank you!
You're such a naughty girl, sending us
a care package with cola inside!
That's my Robin-chan!
But isn't it strange?
Only you got the red carpet!
How do you feel? Does it hurt?
It seems okay.
Wha--?!
Ow, ow, ow!
Still think you can win?
How'd you pull that off?
Gum-Gum...
Hey! You've got some nerve,
making us serve you!
It looks like Luffy is here.
What gives?
He's come for our Jolly Roger.
...Battle Axe!
Lava! I had a feeling this island was...
Oh, yeah! That guy--
How dare you underestimate
the Phoenix Pirates?!
That's right! We're finished!
It burns!
Say your prayers!
No! We can still make it!
Are you sure about this?
My siblings won't keep quiet
No way! That's impossible!
Luffy's attacks aren't working!
This is Luffy we're talking about!
if something happens to me.
He hasn't even touched the guy!
We can still weasel our way through this.
Bastard!
--Got it!
--You've got a point!
Jerk! How dare you get rough
with my Shark Submerge?!
Shut up! We're done taking garbage from you!
Gum-Gum Gatling!
Yep. Whoa, wait!
Indeed. I don't know how
Luffy learned about the flag,
I'm gonna make you pay
for that, you hockey freak!
You still don't get it, do you?
You've got spunk, brat!
The water feels nice...
Actually, I wish it were warmer.
You're a...! You're nothing more than a...!
but it's not as though he
witnessed it getting stolen.
It's only a matter of time before you turn to ice!
Yep! Which means we've still got a chance!
Stop right there!
--He's hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
--Luffy!
Keep the bravado up while you can!
Puzzle-san?
I know where the Jolly Roger is.
Don't get the wrong idea. I didn't
capture him so we could get payback.
Punk!
You can't lay so much as a finger on me.
This sucks! Where the heck are we?!
You can leave it to me.
Doctor...
Sweet!
Tch! Hey, Robin. Think you could
work something out with your powers?
Way to go, Robin!
Huh?
Hey!
Damn it!
You're far more reliable
than that lame moss head.
Sanji-kun! Usopp!
He's too hot to punch!
I want to... cut a deal with you.
Please save us!
I can't tell which flag is ours.
Sheesh, damn that...!
Nami-san, I'm sorry.
I let my guard down just a bit.
Lookie! Slip, slip, slip away!
Damn it! We're screwed!
We're counting on you, Robin!
A deal?
Wh-What?!
We've hit the end of the line.
Yeah. I want you to let them off the hook.
Hey, are you okay?
Now, then...!
I can even do stuff like this!
Huh? Up there... What's that?
Yeah, thanks. You're a lifesaver.
In exchange...
Guys, I want you to hear me out. Listen up.
Now we're down to four bounties left.
My entire body is suspended
by the tiny bit of steam
In exchange, you can have my head.
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
Wh-What is it? What's up?
I just knew you were bounty hunters!
emitted from the ice melted
by the soles of my feet.
What?!
P-Puzzle-san, you're...?!
But, dang, this place is freezing!
A bird...?
How could you say that?!
Awesome! That's so neat!
This was carved from layers of ice that
have been forming for hundreds of years.
Magnetic Love Bazooka!
This is great! You're quite the captain!
It quickly freezes anything that is inside.
You could say it's a natural freezer.
And Lovely Cross Attack!
If you do that, what'll happen
to the Phoenix Pirates?!
What's he doing?
Yay!
Slippity-slip!
Make sense?
Jiro...
Arbell, that comparison was really great!
It was super easy to understand!
The captain has made up his mind.
Wh-What is this?!
Plus Hunter of Love Kick!
But...!
Jiro!
Slip around like fools!
I-Isn't this...?!
I can't wait to see whether
we'll catch the other four first
I...
Check it out!
or you'll freeze first!
With our forces combined,
no one stands a chance against us.
This is it!
Heh heh!
How dare you bastards try to trick us?!
I should teach you a lesson!
It's our Jolly Roger!
Thank goodness!
I was so worried--sheesh!
--Wahoo!
--Screech!
Isn't this great, Doctor?
By now, my children should
have taken out your crewmates.
The magnetic power that binds us...
Jiro!
Stansen!
...is love!
Yeah, I'm so happy!
Your Hot-Hot ability isn't all that bad after all!
People call us the Hunters of Love!
Yay! Hurray!
It's a pity! I hate to slice apart
the guy who treated me to a drink!
Dammit! Your clone technique
really comes in handy.
Hip-hip-hurray! Hurray!
Just what I should have expected
from a 300-million Berry bounty.
Captain, what are you doing?
Let that creep have it!
You're pretty good!
You, slice me apart? Are you up to the task?
We told you, we're twins!
Go on, Captain!
Good at what?!
How'd you learn that ability?
But...
Listen to us!
...the real fight has just begun!
Love Attack!
Wh-What's that?
Captain, why? Go back to
the way you used to be!
Hot Makeup!
You're a Devil Fruit power holder?!
Gum-Gum...
What the--?!
Please! Come back to us!
I can melt anything I touch!
I can't see a thing! What's he up to?
Magnetic Love Bazooka and...
Thank you.
Damn it...!
Hot-Fried Tofu!
I could do this to your splendid
sword in mere seconds!
...Lovely Double Attack!
We aren't pirates anymore!
Uh-huh!
Robin-chan, let's go!
Our flags are somewhere inside that house...!
Puzzle-san...!
I gained this ability from my Hot-Hot Fruit!
We don't need to stick around
now that we've got our Jolly Roger!
If my brothers have brotherly love,
You've got a clever captain.
--Right!
--All righty! To the Sunny!
Jiro, let's go!
Very well. I'll spare your whole
crew in exchange for your head!
then we're tightly bound
together with matrimonial love!
Huh? But...
Yeah!
Luffy'll be fine!
In other words, I just can't touch you, right?
We sure are, Arbell!
All right!
No! I... I'm a member of the Phoenix Pirates!
Men, don't back down!
Kissy!
Wait!
Huh?
Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
Put your backs into it!
Hey!
What's with these guys?
Uh...
It's hard to believe you were
licking those bounty hunters' boots!
Luffy, are you all right?
I love children.
I'm gonna take this jerk down!
It's not like I'm hungry or anything.
Jiro, stop. It's all over...
Which is the real Commander Stansen?!
However...
Doctor, here he comes!
...I only love my children!
Kid, I dare you to so much as touch me!
What?!
Beats me!
That burns!
Don't think you can escape, 50-Berry Pet!
But this is the commander we all know.
I'll get back at you and all of your crewmates!
Chopper!
Dammit, you guys! Quit your yakking and pull!
Damn it!
Hey, Naked Balloon!
Don't throw a hissy fit. I'll play with you now.
The captain and Jiro are risking their
lives to get our Jolly Roger back!
Bastard! Are you trying to
hurt my beloved collection?!
Straw Hat...?
Huh?
Weren't you listening, punk?
Hurt me and they'll all pay the--
Protect our ship as if your lives depended on it!
Ready for the finishing move?
I'm putting you on ice!
Don't you dare let go!
Give back my flag.
Steam...
I was born and raised on a winter island!
Be proud of who you are!
Luffy...
...Iron!
Your flag?! Take a look around you.
We're the Phoenix Pirates!
This doesn't bug me in the least!
Now isn't the time!
L-Luffy!
Okay! You may be hunky dory, but it seems
to be taking a heavy toll on that brat!
This has nothing to do with them.
Give back my Jolly Roger right now!
Yeah!
Wh-What was that?!
Damn it! We can't afford to let
Papa's temper grow any hotter!
I-I don't have it right this second, so I can't!
Jiro!
Papa is going to claim
Straw Hat's head, anyway.
Troisième Haché!
Then take me to it!
At the very least, I need to
take out this 100-Berry-bounty,
Strong... Hammer!
C-Calm down! Someone is on
his way for me as we speak.
so I can lift his spirits
back up as much as possible!
Sorry, but I can't hand my head
over to a lowly bounty hunter!
Exploding Star! Exploding Star Star!
Your flag is in the Arctic Path's last stop,
Ouch!
Usopp Hammer! Usopp Rubberband of Doom!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
my family's base of operations, Lovely Land!
Exploding Star! Pound!
Youch, that hurt!
Darn it, Straw Hat! Keep outta this!
--Sweet!
--Yay!
--Exploding Star! Exploding Star Star!
--You're wasting your time.
But you're finished once you reach Lovely Land!
Take that!
We did it!
There is no way out. Give it up.
Huh? Did I hit you? Sorry, my bad.
I'll send the whole lot of you to the
afterlife before you ever see that flag!
Okay, men! Let's take the ship back.
--Hammer! Exploding Star! Pound!
--It looks like that is the only way out.
Don't play dumb!
Roger!
I'm not playing any games.
Isn't the flag here yet?
Why those--! It's horrible! The penguins
are headed for Straw Hat's ship!
--Exploding Star! Exploding Star!
--Franky!
Chopper and Jiro are strong enough
that they don't need my help!
Puzzle, you may think you're
fighting on par with me,
Campaccino!
Papa, Lil's kite is currently flying it over!
It will be here any second now!
What?!
Dammit! I wasn't even able to dent it!
Those little...!
Luffy...
but the tables are about to turn.
I guess I'll call it a day.
Doctor!
And what happened to my birthday party?
Hey!
I'm going to stand and fight.
What's up?
It will resume as soon as everyone returns.
C'mon! Do "that."
I'm going to fight on my own
and reclaim our Jolly Roger!
Campaccino, how long must I wait?!
What now? They're coming back!
Sure! I should have enough for one last blast.
Well said, Jiro!
I'm frozen to the bone!
P-Papa, don't get so upset!
Cold!
What're you talking about?
Men, is this the best the
Phoenix Pirates can do?
You're just a measly
50-Berry reindeer and a brat!
Let's go, guys! Everyone ready?!
Yo, penguins! Long time no see.
I can't help it!
Yeah!
1.0 Cola Cannon!
Rumble...
Coup de Boo!
This time, you get to face me.
Now then, it's about time I took your head.
We're almost to my house.
Go!
This person and this person are also
What's that...?
Dammit! I'm outta cola!
No, you got us far enough!
headed over to your house, right?
Guard Point!
That hurt, dammit!
Yup!
Wh-What the heck?
My big brother, Hockera, is taking them!
Y-You didn't take any damage?
Here I go!
It's hot!
Damn it!
There is nowhere left for you to run.
I was burning hot at first, but luckily
the ice cooled me right off!
I see...
Doctor...
Soon that block of ice will sink into the lava.
You're incredible!
Is that right? This time I'll melt
your entire body in a flash...
Papa is going to love this!
Don't underestimate us!
Hah! I just have to kick your
butt before that happens.
Hurry and freeze over!
Hey! Can't you do something about the cold?
Sounds simple enough!
...so I don't have to endure any
more of your insolent garbage!
Guard Point is a fur-strengthening form!
Everything you say burns me up!
I could have if I'd known we'd
get turned into popsicles!
Heat Level Up: 3,000 Degrees!
Click.
I could barely even feel that attack!
I-It's horrible, Arbell-sama!
D-Don Accino-sama is...!
Hot-Hot...
Damn it! I'm gonna freeze you alive!
I know! Wanna try melting the ice
from the inside with my Fresh Fire?
That's an impressive amount of smoke!
I won't let you!
Understood. I'm on my way!
Luffy...!
This isn't smoke!
Don't even! What if you started a fire in here?!
I just can't touch you, right?
...Net Surfing!
Stay there and wait for the others to show up!
Then what do you suggest?
Multi-shot Ice Puck!
Wh-What?!
I want you to come up with
something that isn't dangerous!
Luffy!
Hurry it up, Darling!
Take that and that and that!
You're one picky chick!
C-C-Crap!
Coming, Honey!
You're not picky enough!
Oomph!
Hey, we're seriously gonna
freeze if we stay here!
I won't let you escape!
Dang, this doting couple is annoying!
Hot Omelet Shot!
Gum-Gum...
Arbell-chan, what do you see in that monkey?
Papa-san!
What the heck?!
Papa!
...Bazooka!
They really pulled a number
on us earlier, Arbell!
Gah! Stop that!
Yeah!
I'm melting!
--This isn't good!
--It's like a sauna in here!
What the blazes are you?!
Salchow, now that it's come to this,
let's show them our ultimate move!
Uh... Huh?
Yay! He went flying!
Honey, what should we do?
We can't let Papa's mood
get any worse! Put on a smile!
I'm not melting?
Amazing!
Hey! They're about to do something.
What's going on?
Luffy!
We don't have time to be rejoicing!
Nami!
All right! I'd better show
Arbell-chan how cool I am.
What's the matter, Papa?
Looks like my Cool Ball made it in time.
At this rate, Luffy will go after
the Jolly Roger in no time!
You brats!
But it won't last for long!
Didn't you make sure to gather
up my birthday presents?!
Luffy, finish this fight fast!
Crap! Crap! He'll find out that
they stole our flag for real!
Yep. Thanks for your help, Nami!
Oh, crud! This looks bad!
We did it, Doctor!
What's holding Robin up?
They're spinning around a lot more than usual.
You don't know when to give up...
Yeah! You were a big help, Jiro.
Listen to me, Papa! We've gathered them--gah!
I will save Arbell-chan from that ugly man!
Of course not! I'm gonna kick
your butt and go to the New World.
Curse you, Straw Hat!
R-Roronoa Zoro?!
Okay! We'll go with that plan!
What's he doing here?
You're up!
D-D-Damn it! N-Now that it's come to this...!
We're looking really great! Arbell, here we go!
All of you pirates are nothing
but a bunch of idiots!
I won't forgive you, bastard!
Right, Salchow!
Don't ignore us!
You go on about the "New World"
and that "King of the Pirates" nonsense.
Death Spiral High Jump Ultra Love Throw!
Two-Sword Style!
As soon as you lose the ability to manipulate
that vexing chain, you're finished!
--Uh, if I remember right...
--Hawk...
You dream about things that'll never happen!
What's that?
...Wave?!
Whoops!
As a result, our business is flourishing!
These penguins plan on freezing us.
I-I'm sorry, Papa!
I tell you, it's easy for bounty
hunters to earn a fortune--
Youch!
We made a mistake that
allowed one to slip through.
Then they'll come in for
the kill once we can't move.
Damn it! I can't dig my heels
into the ground without slipping!
it's the ultimate business!
--Damn it!
--The beasts!
Sanji, I'm not confident I'll survive
if I get hit by that again.
P-Papa-san, don't worry! We'll be sure
to do a perfect job rounding up the rest!
Men, fall into a close formation
so we can share body heat!
Savage Penguins?
I swear, you always make such
a big deal out of everything!
And it's all thanks to idiots who're
willing to throw their lives away
This is clearly a fatal injury! Isn't it obvious?!
And you got a new flag
to add to your collection!
for a meaningless scrap of
cloth called a "Jolly Roger."
See? So cheer up!
Th-This is so wrong!
Even amongst the nasty Savage Penguins,
this colony is especially ravenous.
And my brothers-in-law will hunt
down the remaining members!
Salchow, we're the best!
I'm working up a nasty sweat!
We're looking really great, Arbell!
Let's give it another go!
Moron! It's not like I want to do this!
Okay, Papa?
Shut up!
Yeah!
Usopp.
He's right! All they keep
saying is, "I'm hungry!"
What was that? You say something?
Men, do you feel nice and warm?
It's time we hit them with
a combo attack of our own.
It's not working. We can't
soothe his temper on our own.
What is it? Did you come up with a sweet idea?!
Wait. Doctor, you can speak Penguin?
That's awesome!
I'd rather fight than keep this up!
Don't... say another word.
Help us, Brother!
I'm with him, Commander Stansen!
Hey! What's with this situation?!
That's the spirit! Let's go!
Prepare yourself, Naked Balloon!
Stupid! I'm not happy about getting
complimented over something like that!
Now I won't slip!
"Prepare yourself," huh?
Damn it! You're tougher than
I expected, Clone Technique Guy!
My three minutes are up!
Ow, ow, ow! Ow, ow! That hurts!
Jiro!
You're better than most at
putting up the tough-guy act.
We told you, we're twins!
Listen to what people tell you!
Puzzle, prepare to die!
Collier Frit!
Jiro! Come back! Hurry!
You're the one going down!
Nice!
Now then, Papa is waiting for us.
We need to wrap this up.
But look at your surroundings!
No! I'm not going back until I reclaim our flag!
You might as well be in the burning pit of Hell!
Arbell-chan...
Wha--?!
Did I earn a high score for artistry this time?
For me, this feels like a cool breeze.
The 100-million-Berry bounty's here.
Where is our flag?!
Shut up, you wanted man!
But for you, it must feel like you're
being cooked alive in a boiling pot!
Get off of me already!
Let's go!
Blend!
Salchow! Hang in there, Salchow!
Big Brother Campaccino!
He's pitting us against penguins?!
He's mocking us!
Yeah!
It's no big deal.
What?
Ar-Arbell...
You aren't the least bit hot!
Don't let your guard down!
Damn it!
Have you learned your lesson?
Your measly attacks will never work on us!
Monkey D. Luffy!
You're the first man to ever bring me
to my hands and knees, Straw Hat.
Jiro...
There is no way someone frozen over
like you could compete with my fire!
All he's got is a stick... He's being reckless!
Your head is ours!
Yeah? You've still got some fight left in you?
Ar-Arbell-chan...
What?
Sanji, how long are you gonna lay there? Get up!
Isn't he the spitting image of
how you were back in the day?
And you're also the first
to have truly made me mad!
If you're gonna give up, now is your chance.
Have you lost it? You think
you're hotter than me?
And despite that, Vigaro never once barked
a word of protest against your orders.
I still haven't hit you with
a full 10% of my power.
Gum-Gum...
Heat Level Up: 5,500 Degrees!
Open your eyes! Who could surpass the
heat emitted by my boiling hot body?
...Gatling!
Hot Omelet Shots!
Did you think we were randomly
skating on top of the ice?
Hey, Vigaro! Why aren't you stopping him?
Don Accino...!
Eh? Huh? What? What do you mean by that?
--Hey!
--Huh?
Straw Hat!
The pirates we've fought are nothing
compared to the guys on that ocean.
Quit arguing with me--bring it on!
This is what we mean!
Robin-chan still hasn't given the sign,
I'm gonna send you flying!
which means we're stuck
reclaiming the flag ourselves!
The captain is being too reckless!
Click.
Sure does! We've gotta beat Luffy to it!
I don't plan on stopping Puzzle.
What is it?
What did you say?! That's bull!
Yeah. Yeah...
What?!
I'll keep an eye on Luffy.
I'm the 10,000-Degree Man!
Stansen, when we set sail
as the Phoenix Pirates,
That's it for our strategy meeting!
--All right.
--Click.
C-C-Cold!
We're all set!
What of it?!
Are you okay, Jiro?
Hey, you! Don't run from me!
didn't we decide to push forward,
no matter how strong the foe?
My blood is boiling... at a million degrees!
Surrender now!
Captain!
Sorry for making you worry about me.
You've escaped death
for now, Monkey D. Luffy.
What?!
Let us catch you and we'd be willing
to save you. If you don't hurry...
I wasn't worried any!
--But...
--And we're talking about the only
man I've ever considered my captain...
What?
We'll finish you off later.
Gum-Gum...!
That aside, we've gotta get our flag back!
Big Brother, what's the matter?
Wh-What're those?
Bring it on! Take me down...
Puzzle.
It sounds like Papa has gotten
even worse! We have to hurry back.
Yeah! We're going to reclaim our--
the Phoenix Pirates'--pride!
Ouch!
You'll die from hypothermia
if you don't surrender soon.
...if you can!
I wouldn't regret dying if it were
to help him realize his ambitions.
Wait, you two! Don't run away!
--Uh-huh!
--Let's go!
Sh-Sh-Shuddup! Hey, Sanji! Wake up!
...Million-Degree Bazooka!
Captain, it's horrible! Our ship pulled
away from the shore all on its own!
Ushopp, I'm sharting to get sweepy...
Here's the thing about phoenixes:
No matter the hardship,
they always rise back up!
Stupid! That's really bad!
Watch out! Your hands are going to melt.
You jerks!
I'm sweepy...
What?!
And they're reborn even stronger than before!
Give back our Jolly Roger!
Not hot! It's not hot!
Please leave the ship to us!
Captain, you go with Jiro!
Fine! Fine! Just save us!
It's not hot! It's not hot!
That's the type of man I've
placed my trust in with Puzzle!
I'm counting on you, Stansen!
What?! That's impossible!
Let's go, Jiro!
Uh-huh!
Look, Salchow! I caught something!
So did I, Arbell!
Puzzle, I believe in you.
Go flying!
D-Damn it...!
Kissy-poo!
You are the man who will
become the King of the Pirates!
Stop it! You'll die if you go to sleep!
Wake up, Usopp! Usopp!
You're one slippery brat!
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
But you're done for, Straw Hat!
Don't wake me up, Nami.
I'm in the middle of a pretty dream...
Beat it!
Take this! Hot-Hot Gatling!
Hey, when is he gonna get here?
What?! That's my move!
There's so many birdies and butterflies...
No way!
Click.
Merry, you've come for me, haven't you?
H-He's fast!
But your shots are moving
at the same speed as earlier!
I...
What's that?
Hey, kiddo! I've got a portable
transponder snail in my butt pocket.
Wake up!
S-Stupid! Hurry and run for it, Luffy!
This is our flag!
Could you get it?
Flag... Our flag...
Are you trying to kill me?!
Someday I'm going to become
the King of the Pirates.
Blend, what's keeping you? You're late!
Luffy!
Papa is angry. Hurry back home.
We can make it to the New World!
Where the heck is this?
Zoro?!
Hey! Can you hear me, Blend?
Where the hell have you guys been?
That startled me!
Answer me!
That's what we should be asking you!
The Phoenix Pirates have Blend!
I don't care about your bounty anymore.
More importantly, I saw our flag upstairs.
Sorry, men! I was a foolish
captain who couldn't live up
If you mess with us, he's dead!
I'm going to melt you into nothing but steam!
Guys, you didn't...
Doesn't 300-million-Berry
steam sound luxurious?
Jiro, you...!
So it really is here, huh?
to the trust my precious friend placed in me.
What's this?
Whoa! What the heck?!
Well, Straw Hat?
We've gotta get it back before Luffy notices!
But... But I wanna let...
What's goin' on?
Damn it! You can't even protect a
single flag, you lame excuse for a cook?
I'm not a sauna, Naked Balloon!
Ah! Over there!
I take back what I said!
...Vigaro see it once more!
What?!
--Luffy?!
--What's he doing down there?
Big Brother is coming.
He has to see our flag flying
above the ocean where he's at rest!
Your brother?
Hey! Luffy! We got the Jolly Roger--
Back at you! How dare you come back
empty-handed, you shitty swordsman?!
You've taken your tough act too far!
Captain!
You've just bought everyone
tickets to the afterlife!
No!
--Jerk, take this!
--Hey, watch where you fling that sword!
Huh? Oh, it's the guys...
Hey! This is no time for fighting!
Hey, guys! What're you doing over there?
It looks like everyone is doing well.
Crap! He found us!
Evaporate off the face of the planet, Straw Hat!
Huh?
Robin!
Wh-What now?
Jiro, let's go! We're getting our flag back.
Guys!
Robin-chan!
Captain...!
--Moron.
--What?!
Robin, save me!
Aye aye, sir!
The ship! Hurry back to the ship!
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
That burns!
Please! Pull us up!
Got it!
It's all your fault.
Hurry!
Really, Miss, you're supposed
to go down there with them.
What do you mean we're going to the afterlife?!
Because of you, my darling
daughter and sons were...!
Huh? Those guys...
Hey, wait! What about the flag?
Wha--?!
I'll never forgive you!
But see, you're special, Big Sister Robin!
Hey!
I-I won't tolerate any funny business.
I'll ask Papa to spare you.
Everyone, remember!
Pretend this never happened.
Why, you...!
Hey, dude! Why'd you start glowing?
And Papa does anything I ask!
--Hey, wait up!
--Gah, he's coming!
Wow! What's he doing?
Hey! I said to wait up!
The temperature keeps climbing up!
My!
What about the flag?! The flag!
Just wait and see!
So let's go to the birthday party.
Is his Hot-Hot Fruit to blame?
Can't hear him! Can't hear him!
There's a birthday party?
There might be more to it than that...
Yup! It's for Papa!
We have a whole bunch of food!
Hey, guys! Hurry!
Straw Hat! We'll deal with these scumballs!
C'mon! Say goodbye to everyone.
Wait!
Crap! He's coming!
What should we do?
Yeah? Then please do!
--Robin!
--Hey!
Sanji-kun! Zoro!
Darling!
Roger! Let's do it.
--Hurry and rescue us!
--C'mon! Hurry and save us! Robin!
--Robin-chan! Darling!
Hey!
What is that?
Huh?
Fly!
Hey! Robin-chan! Come on!
That hurt!
--Hey, guys!
--You damn doting couple!
Huh? When'd you break free?
--Here I go, Usopp.
--What?!
Well, shall we head on up?
You'd better land on the ship.
He's really fast!
Really?
That can't be right!
Wait just a darn second!
Yeah, you! I'm talking to you,
the stupid doting couple!
Pound Phoenix!
Let's go! Let's go!
You sent me flying!
Huh? Sanji, Franky's missing!
--Franky!
--You can count on me!
I'll lead the way.
What's going on?
Did you use a clone technique?
Constantly letching over a
lady is outright pathetic...
Where the heck did he go?
Coup de Boo!
How dare you capture my darling little brother?
...you stinking hound of a man!
Hey! Why'd you leave us?
Don't worry about him!
I'm sure he has plans of his own.
What's with those two, Darling?
It smells like cola!
Wait, Robin!
They're simmering with jealousy.
What?!
Please don't abandon me!
Little Brother!
What are you guys doing?!
--Talk about idiots!
--Aren't they stupid?
This must be the Savage Penguins' doing!
Big Brother!
Didn't they steal the Jolly Roger?
We've gotta hurry and get it back!
Chopper!
Kissy!
Dammit! They trashed our raiding dory,
so we can't go after them!
Hey, you jerk!
Huh? The Jolly Roger?
What are you talking about?
--I won't forgive you!
--Sanji!
It's been a while, but...
Jerks! You let our precious Jolly Roger--
...let's show them our combination plays!
You musta been having a nightmare? Right?
Are they retaliating for how
we took out their friends?
Where'd you go, you hockey freak?!
Just how messed up are these penguins?!
Awesome! How did you do that just now?!
Huh? Y-Yeah!
I'm back!
Come back like a normal person!
Right here!
The captain and Jiro will
definitely get our Jolly Roger!
Luffy, look over there.
We have the ability to manipulate magnetism!
Are you trying to destroy our ship?!
Don't expect a repeat of last time!
What?
My bad.
Let's go! C'mon!
I couldn't bear to face them if they came back
We can pull ourselves together or apart at will!
Let's go! C'mon! C'mon! C'mon!
and there wasn't a ship
on which to hoist the flag!
And the magnetic powers that link us
--Get your butt in gear, Usopp!
--Coming!
Huh? We've still got both of them.
La la-la la!
What's the matter?
Isn't it a bit warm?
Did that clone technique guy lie to me?
Jerk! Wait for me!
can instantly separate us by the
distance of our measurable feelings.
Huh? It couldn't be...
Commander Stansen!
Say your prayers!
Guys, sorry I ever doubted you.
Hold up, you stupid doting couple!
I knew it!
Hey, Usopp! Our Jolly Roger--
Papa's angry!
Such is our...
Don't sweat it, don't sweat it.
Luffy! We have to defeat all of
these guys before we can go inside!
Let's call it off. It's best to stay away
from Papa when he gets like that.
Phew, that was a close one.
Please, Big Sister Robin!
...brotherly love!
Hey! Did you eat a Devil Fruit?
Why is that, Usopp?
W-We make it in time?
Really?
At this rate, he'll melt everyone around here!
Stay here with me forever!
Well, you see...
Why are we drawn to each other?
We did it!
Listen up! Gloss over Luffy's
questions about the flag
Promise that you won't go anywhere.
Because we are...
C'mon! Let's go play in my room.
You were great, Jiro!
...twins!
I can't do that, Lil.
until Robin gets it back! Understood?
Then let's take those snacks and drinks with us.
Wow! Twins are awesome!
You're a man among men!
Why not?
Roger!
--Robin-chan!
--Robin!
No, there is definitely
something fishy about them!
Jiro!
Uh, w-well...
I'm impressed that you managed
to get the Jolly Roger back.
Why won't you do as I say?
Blend, which one is our prey for today?
They're so warm, I doubt they'll be very yummy.
I am very proud of you.
There is a spell cast on that door
For starters, that guy is Puzzle the Phoenix.
He has a 100-million-Berry bounty.
so that it won't open until we
defeat all five baddies here!
That's all right. Also, I'd like
to ask a favor of you.
Is that kid controlling the plant?
Thank you.
In that case, I'll give her a good spanking!
--A spell?
--Y-Yeah.
And that is Straw Hat Luffy
with a 300-million-Berry bounty.
You are strictly prohibited from
raising your hand against a lady.
Captain!
Really? So that's the deal.
Punks, you've got a delivery.
You have a broad definition of the term...
I'll kick their butts!
Oh, so that's him.
It's from Little Lady Lil's friend, Robin-sama.
Unhand Robin-chan, you stinking flower!
Captain...?
And that's his cotton-candy-loving pet,
Chopper. He's worth 50 Berries.
Jiro, I want you to hoist the Jolly Roger!
From Robin?
Here I come!
A delivery...?
Fifty?!
What is with that 50-Berry bounty?
The Phoenix Pirates are setting sail!
Why, you--! Take this!
Big Sister Robin, what were you up to?
What indeed, Big Brother?
Robin-chan, I always believed in you!
Are your friends all that important to you?
Don't say that! 50 Berries says a whole lot!
Okay, Captain!
Pretending to be an adventurer all by yourself?
Yes. I want to get our flag back.
No. I wanted to go see your Papa's room.
Whatever. Moving on.
Hey! Here's some cola, Franky!
Let's get ready, guys!
Do you think you can
escape our combination plays?
The Straw Hat Crew's flag?
Yeah!
Sweet! You can leave the rest to me!
Hey!
Really? You wanted to see Papa?
Pull us out of here!
Papa enjoys collecting a bunch of Jolly Rogers,
--You got it!
--Yeah!
Let's beat it!
You can get to Papa's room
through this greenhouse.
but I don't care about those scraps of cloth...
It's a shortcut, plus it's fun!
Straw Hat!
Indeed, they may be nothing
more than scraps of cloth.
Look over here!
Super! Cola replenished!
Don't, Luffy! Behind you!
Big Sister Robin, don't you like flowers?
Behind me?
But to us pirates, our flag is
more important than life itself.
Repulsion!
Yes.
Big Sister Arbell loved this room, too!
Here I go! Coup de...
It's something we can't lose, no matter what!
We'd always go on walks here together...
Did he fall into the ocean?
Stansen, sure enough, your decision was right.
But then she got married to that gross creep...
...Vent!
He was nothing before us brothers!
Luffy!
I put you through a lot
while the "captain was gone."
Gum-Gum...
Coup de Boo!
...Rocket!
Are they really all that important...?
Hey, let's play that game!
Big Brother!
We wasted a bunch of time down there,
so let's get going, guys!
Luffy!
You know? The one where I guess
which hand the coin is in.
Awesome!
Oh, no! Papa...!
Yeah!
Let's play! Let's play!
He's really angry!
Lil...
Straw Hat...
S-S-Save--!
Let's go, Chopper!
Why did you lie to me?
Are you watching, Vigaro?
Done already?
Yeah!
I'm only saying this for your own good!
You'll get indigestion if you eat him!
Please take me with you.
I swear we won't let your death be in vain!
I suspect this greenhouse doesn't
lead to your Papa's room.
Campaccino!
I'm begging you!
What was that?
Jiro...
Men, let's hit the ocean!
Forget it!
Am I right?
Yeah!
Is someone in here?
--Lil!
--Special Attack! Exploding Star!
Stay here, Jiro.
Big Sister Robin, you lied to me, too.
How long are you going to keep me waiting?
--Don't go!
--Captain...
What happened to my birthday party?
Where's the flag?
You promised to play with me,
There's no need to go.
Dang, it's hot in here! What's with this room?
I'm no longer...
but you plan on leaving
with your friends, don't you?
Hey! What the heck's going on?
It's okay! If we could raise
our Jolly Roger again,
Who're you?
But there is no way you'll
ever escape from this place.
It's that Hot-Hot man's fault.
What's this? You aren't Campaccino!
I'm sure you'd return to your old self!
Lil!
He stirred up the magma
in the underwater volcano.
So I'm going to bring it back!
You're okay now.
I have a special bottle I've been saving...
Would you like to join me?
I'm sorry.
Let's hurry! It's only a matter of
time before the volcano erupts.
Don't be foolish!
Big Sister Robin...!
What? Sure...
I have already given up...
If anything were to happen to you,
your big sister and brothers would be sad.
Got it! Pull out to sea ASAP!
Hey, just make yourself at home!
What is this?!
Thanks!
Yeah!
You're their cute, precious little sister!
Promise to become my big sister.
The words "given up" sound so lame...
The Family was sweet enough
to throw me a birthday party,
Isn't that right?
Do and I'll save you.
You aren't alone.
but then they took off mid-party
and haven't come back!
They don't suit you, Captain!
Hold your family dear!
You're the man who's supposed
to become the King of the Pirates!
Damn that ugly man!
Yeah? Talk about a coincidence!
My friends vanished before I knew it.
I'm still looking for them.
I won't fall for the same trick twice.
Oh, really?
Puzzle, I believe in you.
You too, eh?
Arbell-chan, you're so hot!
Oh, thanks!
You instantly fell for the exact same trick!
You are the man who will
become the King of the Pirates!
Who knows where they went
or what they're doing?!
The island vanished...
Are we on top of a...?
Seriously! Where'd they decide to go goof off?
Here I go!
Second... Gear!
Phew, that was a close call!
Now that I think about it, you can
handle him on your own, huh?
I'm still puny and a total weakling,
but just you wait!
You're going to the New World?
Gum-Gum...
You bet!
...Bell!
Multi-shot!
Fresh Fire!
Yeah. After I get our Jolly Roger back.
I'll steal it back and--
Doctor!
Lil...
Foul...
--Wha--?!
--Eh?!
You'll never get there. Your destination
was set in stone a long time ago!
I'm fine!
Hey, you! I heard what happened!
Guys, if you don't give back our flag,
I'm gonna kick your butts for real!
Gum-Gum...
You returned a piece of Papa-san's
collection to the Straw Hats!
Why'd you whack him, Luffy?!
...Gatling!
Blend, Papa is getting hot with rage!
We need to finish this up fast.
What the heck were--
Don't exclude me from the conversation!
Shut up for a second!
Are you a cold-hearted brute?!
I've already decided that's where I'm headed.
He's a Devil Fruit power holder!
That hurt! What was that for?!
Okay...
I'm definitely going there after I kick your butt!
Gum-Gum Bazooka!
Only someone who has fought till the
very end may use the words "given up."
If we can drop him in the ocean, he's finished!
Lil...
Gum-Gum...
You can't use them!
I'm sorry.
Listen to me!
...Gatling!
Big Sister?
...Jet Pistol!
There is no way a guy like this could
become the King of the Pirates!
Leap!
It's refreshing when my moves hit home!
I've made you feel lonesome, haven't I?
Fusion!
I'm the one who'll become
the King of the Pirates!
Let's apologize to Papa
about the flags together.
The door's open...
Don't be stupid!
Blend!
I'm sure he'll understand.
After all, we're family!
I've already decided that Puzzle-san
is going to become the King!
You're finished, Campaccino!
Luffy!
You siblings use magnetism as your weapon.
I don't care what you say!
Arbell...!
Captain!
I won't give up on my dream!
Found it!
It's no good! He's too far!
Lil...
You can't use that power if you're apart!
There is no way I'm gonna fall in!
--La la-la la! La la-la la!
--Nice! That's nice, Arbell!
That isn't my only power.
Magnetic Repulsion!
Hey!
--La la-la la! La la-la la!...
--The way you care for your sister is really great!
What?!
Hot!
Phew, that was close!
St-Straw... Straw Hat...!
--Love Swing!
--I'll catch you!
Jiro, you aren't weak at all!
Straw Hat!
Zoro!
Papa, thanks for waiting! It's a bit late, but...
You've got an inner strength!
You cannot hope to escape from us!
Are you stupid?!
Zoro...!
What's that moron Sanji thinking?!
I won't let go, even if it kills me!
On a one, two...
You really are persistent!
Luffy-san...
Usopp, the door opened!
This is our pride as pirates!
Happy birthday, Papa!
Ah, got it!
Gum-Gum... Twin Pistol!
C'mon! Let's go get our flags back, Jiro!
Repulsion!
Jiro!
Straw... Straw... Straw...
Crap! Now what'll we do?!
Yeah!
I'll never forgive them for
stealing our Jolly Rogers!
Straw Hat!!
What are you guys doing?!
Don't do it!
Whoo, Nami-san!
You don't stand a chance against them!
I'm on my way, Luffy!
C-Captain... I...
Sanji-kun, you deal with that man!
Don't go.
Papa!
Wh-What was that?
You did great, Jiro!
I'm not going to die.
I'm going to move forward.
Leave him to me!
Where is Big Brother Campaccino
at a time like this?!
I'll take down this woman.
Thunder Charge!
Jiro, look out!
After all, I'm a pirate!
Straw Hat!
My, what a thing to say!
What's your basis to support that claim?
By the Accino Family name,
I swear I won't let you escape!
"Basis"? We're running short on time!
Jiro!
Surprisingly Hot Nose Jet!
You're being a pest, Clone Technique Guy!
Thunder Ball!
The idiot...! All for me, everyone is...
I will avenge Papa! Prepare yourself!
Luffy's going to catch on! Thunderbolt Tempo!
Chopper!
Are you all right?
Campaccino!
Guys! I... I made sure to get it! Look!
Captain...!
What?! Puzzle?!
Hey, take the ship back! Please go after Luffy!
Honey!
We can't do that!
So we made it in time.
Didn't you hear her? We're short on time.
Your opponent is supposed to be me!
We did it, Nami-san! Now Luffy
won't make fun of--whoa, wait!
You can't tell a ship where
to go here in the Arctic Path.
Basses Côte!
Captain Puzzle...
Straw Hat, he's my prey! Keep your hands off!
Luffy...
Whoa! What's with that flag?!
Longe!
Tendron!
Flanchet! Quasi! Jarret!
--Eh? What?
--You can go on ahead!
We should just ignore anyone
who doesn't come back!
Men, we're going after Jiro!
Curly Cook's merciless, isn't he?
We'll deal with you in the New World.
What the heck?!
Ignore him. He's stupid that way.
Knowing them, I bet they're having fun
slipping and sliding on the ice. Sheesh!
Why'd it turn out like this?
Wait for us to finish you off there!
R-Right...
Sure! Bring it on!
It looks like we get to start over from scratch...
Hey, Nami! Aren't we in trouble
if Zoro is leading the way?
Wh-What's with him?!
You... greenhorn!
Shut your trap!
Let's go!
Well? What do you think?
That collection is my pride and joy.
Didn't Robin, Sanji-kun,
and the others make it in time?
Yeah!
I'm sure we'll turn this into a
party you'll never forget, okay?
I hope ours isn't amongst those...!
Your collection?
Jiro!
Right! They're the flags of all
the pirates I've hunted down.
So cheer up, Papa!
Luffy, why aren't we going to help them?
Impressive, isn't it?
They're going to get killed!
Chopper, take a closer look.
Do-Don Accino!
You've got a disgusting hobby.
Hey, don't be so harsh!
He's... naked!
Does anyone there look like he needs rescuing?
Give our Jolly Roger back!
That's the issue?
Huh?
Straw Hat, how dare you beat up
my darling sons and daughter?!
Oh, it's here! It's here!
What was that?
I'm sure you'll understand
once you feast your eyes on this.
Hey, don't drag your feet! Luffy's on his way!
My beloved family...
At any rate, let's hurry!
My Lovely Land...
Their total bounty exceeds 600 million Berries.
You've made a fool of the Accino Family!
Guys...
And now my prized collection!
This Jolly Roger belongs to the Straw Hat Crew.
Hey, you guys! Don't just sit and
watch us! Hurry and get going!
I swear, I will personally take you out!
So you're the one who stole
our Jolly Roger, Naked Balloon!
What do you think with your
120 million bounty, Roronoa Zoro?
Doctor, let's meet up in the New World!
Hot-Hot powers, to the max!
Hmph! So what if I did, whippersnapper?
Bastard...!
Yeah! That's a promise!
See? I told you he'd come, Papa!
How the hell did you get that Jolly Roger?!
Maximum Heat Level: 10,000 Degrees!
Okay! Sunny, full speed ahead!
It's just a matter of time before we capture him.
I'm gonna kick your butt right
quick and get our flag back!
Wouldn't you agree it's
a rather nice Jolly Roger?
I'm sorry I got mad at you.
Let's go! To the New World!
You can still heat up?
Yeah!
Jeez, it's cold!
What the heck are those two up to?!
The ice is melting right and left!
Naked Balloon, quit saying,
"Bushuuu, bushuuu!"
Hey, guys! How're you doing?!
Hey, you damn moss head!
So you're gonna lock us in here, huh?
I'm Chopper Man!
I only followed you since you claimed
to know where the Jolly Roger was!
I don't really know if it's been a while or not,
All of the walls are made outta ice!
It looks like they're going all out.
Luffy, be careful! It looks
like he can still grow hotter!
Back off! Be quiet for a second!
And it's so cold that I'm starting to get sleepy...
but next week's One Piece is my special!
But I'm starting to get
concerned about our Log Pose.
It's probably this way.
I've gotta hurry and defeat him
so we can get our Jolly Roger back.
Why the heck do we have to follow this jerk?
Don't fall asleep!
They're unbelievable! I guess I'll go
pick them up in my super ship right quick!
You'll definitely have a good dream!
Oh, right. Nami, what on earth were--
If you do, you'll turn into an ice cube!
Crap! Guys, hurry!
Here we go! Killer Cute Spark!
We're here! This is it!
Where did Robin and Zoro go?!
I'm sure of it...
We really gotta beat Luffy to the flag!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Go, Chopper Man!
Protect the TV Station on the Beach"
"The Phoenix Returns! The Dream
Sworn to Friends on a Jolly Roger"
"A Mansion in Chaos! An Enraged
Don and an Imprisoned Crew"
"We'll Be Waiting in the New World!
Parting with the Courageous Pirates"
"The Super Hot-Hot Final Battle!
Luffy vs. the Scorching Hot Don"
I'm gonna be... a huge robot?!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!