Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
The words "given up" sound so lame...
They don't suit you, Captain!
You're the man who's supposed
to become the King of the Pirates!
The idiot...! All for me, everyone is...
"The Phoenix Returns! The Dream
Sworn to Friends on a Jolly Roger"
Hurry! We've gotta get our flag back!
You can count on me! It was around this floor!
Sweet!
"Around" this floor?
That doesn't bode well...
Huh? Where is this?
Which room is it in, Zoro?
Don't rush me.
How could I not?! Luffy's on his way!
It's this one!
Put 'em up, you sauna freak!
--He's this way!
--Got it!
--That way!
Oh! They found some high-end flour.
It figures!
Maybe it was the next floor up.
I can't trust you!
If you don't remember, come out and say so!
See anything to point us in the right direction?
At this rate, it'll be dark before we find it.
I know! We've gotta find the flag
and fast! If Luffy finds out about this...
Hey! Give back my flag!
L-Luffy!
Welcome to Lovely Land.
I never expected the 300-million
bounty to come on his own.
Huh? This is Lovely Land?
Sure is!
It's a weird house.
H-He's here!
It's Luffy! W-We're doomed!
We've hit the worst-case scenario!
This really stinks...
Tsk!
Hey! Where are you going?
Isn't it obvious?
I'll use sheer willpower to get
the Jolly Roger back if I have to!
Go wander these halls forever!
Shut up, you stupid cook!
Robin!
Robin-chan!
I've been searching for you.
You're such a naughty girl, sending us
a care package with cola inside!
That's my Robin-chan!
But isn't it strange?
Only you got the red carpet!
How'd you pull that off?
It looks like Luffy is here.
He's come for our Jolly Roger.
That's right! We're finished!
No! We can still make it!
This is Luffy we're talking about!
We can still weasel our way through this.
--Got it!
--You've got a point!
Yep. Whoa, wait!
Indeed. I don't know how
Luffy learned about the flag,
but it's not as though he
witnessed it getting stolen.
Yep! Which means we've still got a chance!
I know where the Jolly Roger is.
You can leave it to me.
Sweet!
Way to go, Robin!
You're far more reliable
than that lame moss head.
Sheesh, damn that...!
We're counting on you, Robin!
Now, then...!
Guys, I want you to hear me out. Listen up.
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
Magnetic Love Bazooka!
And Lovely Cross Attack!
Plus Hunter of Love Kick!
With our forces combined,
no one stands a chance against us.
The magnetic power that binds us...
...is love!
People call us the Hunters of Love!
Dammit! Your clone technique
really comes in handy.
We told you, we're twins!
How'd you learn that ability?
Listen to us!
Love Attack!
Gum-Gum...
Magnetic Love Bazooka and...
...Lovely Double Attack!
If my brothers have brotherly love,
then we're tightly bound
together with matrimonial love!
We sure are, Arbell!
Kissy!
Huh?
What's with these guys?
Luffy, are you all right?
It's not like I'm hungry or anything.
Doctor, here he comes!
Don't think you can escape, 50-Berry Pet!
I'm putting you on ice!
I was born and raised on a winter island!
This doesn't bug me in the least!
Okay! You may be hunky dory, but it seems
to be taking a heavy toll on that brat!
Jiro!
Ouch!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Youch, that hurt!
Darn it, Straw Hat! Keep outta this!
Huh? Did I hit you? Sorry, my bad.
Don't play dumb!
I'm not playing any games.
Chopper and Jiro are strong enough
that they don't need my help!
What?!
Luffy...
Doctor!
I'm going to stand and fight.
I'm going to fight on my own
and reclaim our Jolly Roger!
Well said, Jiro!
What're you talking about?
You're just a measly
50-Berry reindeer and a brat!
Rumble...
What's that...?
Guard Point!
Wh-What the heck?
Here I go!
Doctor...
You're incredible!
Guard Point is a fur-strengthening form!
I could barely even feel that attack!
Damn it! I'm gonna freeze you alive!
I won't let you!
Multi-shot Ice Puck!
Take that and that and that!
Oomph!
What the heck?!
Gah! Stop that!
What the blazes are you?!
We did it, Doctor!
Yeah! You were a big help, Jiro.
D-D-Damn it! N-Now that it's come to this...!
What's that?
Savage Penguins?
Even amongst the nasty Savage Penguins,
this colony is especially ravenous.
He's right! All they keep
saying is, "I'm hungry!"
Wait. Doctor, you can speak Penguin?
That's awesome!
Stupid! I'm not happy about getting
complimented over something like that!
My three minutes are up!
Jiro!
Jiro! Come back! Hurry!
No! I'm not going back until I reclaim our flag!
The 100-million-Berry bounty's here.
He's pitting us against penguins?!
He's mocking us!
Don't let your guard down!
Jiro...
All he's got is a stick... He's being reckless!
Isn't he the spitting image of
how you were back in the day?
And despite that, Vigaro never once barked
a word of protest against your orders.
Hey, Vigaro! Why aren't you stopping him?
The pirates we've fought are nothing
compared to the guys on that ocean.
The captain is being too reckless!
I don't plan on stopping Puzzle.
What?!
Stansen, when we set sail
as the Phoenix Pirates,
didn't we decide to push forward,
no matter how strong the foe?
--But...
--And we're talking about the only
man I've ever considered my captain...
Puzzle.
I wouldn't regret dying if it were
to help him realize his ambitions.
Here's the thing about phoenixes:
No matter the hardship,
they always rise back up!
And they're reborn even stronger than before!
That's the type of man I've
placed my trust in with Puzzle!
Puzzle, I believe in you.
You are the man who will
become the King of the Pirates!
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
Beat it!
I...
This is our flag!
Someday I'm going to become
the King of the Pirates.
We can make it to the New World!
Sorry, men! I was a foolish
captain who couldn't live up
to the trust my precious friend placed in me.
But... But I wanna let...
...Vigaro see it once more!
He has to see our flag flying
above the ocean where he's at rest!
Captain!
Jiro, let's go! We're getting our flag back.
Captain...!
Aye aye, sir!
Why, you...!
Straw Hat! We'll deal with these scumballs!
Yeah? Then please do!
Hey!
--Hey, guys!
--You damn doting couple!
Yeah, you! I'm talking to you,
the stupid doting couple!
Constantly letching over a
lady is outright pathetic...
...you stinking hound of a man!
What's with those two, Darling?
They're simmering with jealousy.
--Talk about idiots!
--Aren't they stupid?
Kissy!
Hey, you jerk!
--I won't forgive you!
--Sanji!
Jerks! You let our precious Jolly Roger--
Where'd you go, you hockey freak?!
Right here!
Don't expect a repeat of last time!
Let's go! C'mon!
Let's go! C'mon! C'mon! C'mon!
--Get your butt in gear, Usopp!
--Coming!
La la-la la!
Jerk! Wait for me!
Say your prayers!
Hold up, you stupid doting couple!
Hey, Usopp! Our Jolly Roger--
Luffy! We have to defeat all of
these guys before we can go inside!
Why is that, Usopp?
Well, you see...
Listen up! Gloss over Luffy's
questions about the flag
until Robin gets it back! Understood?
Roger!
Uh, w-well...
There is a spell cast on that door
so that it won't open until we
defeat all five baddies here!
--A spell?
--Y-Yeah.
Really? So that's the deal.
I'll kick their butts!
Big Sister Robin, what were you up to?
Pretending to be an adventurer all by yourself?
No. I wanted to go see your Papa's room.
Really? You wanted to see Papa?
You can get to Papa's room
through this greenhouse.
It's a shortcut, plus it's fun!
Big Sister Robin, don't you like flowers?
Yes.
Big Sister Arbell loved this room, too!
We'd always go on walks here together...
But then she got married to that gross creep...
Hey, let's play that game!
You know? The one where I guess
which hand the coin is in.
Let's play! Let's play!
Lil...
Why did you lie to me?
I suspect this greenhouse doesn't
lead to your Papa's room.
Am I right?
Big Sister Robin, you lied to me, too.
You promised to play with me,
but you plan on leaving
with your friends, don't you?
But there is no way you'll
ever escape from this place.
I'm sorry.
What is this?!
Promise to become my big sister.
Do and I'll save you.
Damn that ugly man!
I won't fall for the same trick twice.
Oh, really?
Arbell-chan, you're so hot!
You instantly fell for the exact same trick!
Here I go!
Now that I think about it, you can
handle him on your own, huh?
You bet!
Multi-shot!
Fresh Fire!
Foul...
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Gum-Gum Bazooka!
It's refreshing when my moves hit home!
The door's open...
Blend!
You're finished, Campaccino!
You siblings use magnetism as your weapon.
You can't use that power if you're apart!
That isn't my only power.
What?!
--Love Swing!
--I'll catch you!
Are you stupid?!
What's that moron Sanji thinking?!
Usopp, the door opened!
Ah, got it!
Crap! Now what'll we do?!
What are you guys doing?!
Whoo, Nami-san!
Sanji-kun, you deal with that man!
Leave him to me!
I'll take down this woman.
Thunder Charge!
My, what a thing to say!
What's your basis to support that claim?
"Basis"? We're running short on time!
Thunder Ball!
Luffy's going to catch on! Thunderbolt Tempo!
Honey!
Didn't you hear her? We're short on time.
Basses Côte!
Longe!
Tendron!
Flanchet! Quasi! Jarret!
Curly Cook's merciless, isn't he?
Ignore him. He's stupid that way.
Wh-What's with him?!
Do-Don Accino!
He's... naked!
That's the issue?
Straw Hat, how dare you beat up
my darling sons and daughter?!
You've made a fool of the Accino Family!
So you're the one who stole
our Jolly Roger, Naked Balloon!
Hmph! So what if I did, whippersnapper?
I'm gonna kick your butt right
quick and get our flag back!
Naked Balloon, quit saying,
"Bushuuu, bushuuu!"
Luffy, be careful! It looks
like he can still grow hotter!
I've gotta hurry and defeat him
so we can get our Jolly Roger back.
Oh, right. Nami, what on earth were--
Crap! Guys, hurry!
We really gotta beat Luffy to the flag!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Super Hot-Hot Final Battle!
Luffy vs. the Scorching Hot Don"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!