Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
He flies around using his Chopper cape
and fights for world peace!
The name of our hero is...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
...Chopper Man!
The words he uttered just before his death
"Go, Chopper Man!
Protect the TV Station on the Beach"
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
I don't want to hear about no Chopper Man!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
He interferes with each and every
attempt I make to conquer the world!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
"Evil Incarnate--Dr. Usodaba"
This is Dr. Usodaba, evil incarnate!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Leading the evil Usodaba Gang,
he's a fearsome scientist who
schemes to take over the world!
As night falls upon the
forest around these parts,
Okay! The Great Usopp
will be the first to jump off!
Hi! Hello, everyone! Good day to you.
It isn't night yet, but with this thick fog,
Your less-than-stellar
performance is also to blame.
--Yay!
--Lookie!
Don't be stupid! And what the heck is he?!
it becomes so perilous it hardly
seems like it belongs to this world.
Wow! That was awesome!
it's creepy how dark it is.
Quit lazing about!
Yep! Don't let your guard down.
My, my! They're harsh!
Hey, me next!
Huh?
From the looks of it, we're already
caught in the infamous...
"Naughty Monster--Sanjiropus"
All right, go for it!
If you please, feel free to take
my carriage to the mansion.
This is the naughty monster, Sanjiropus.
Goodness, aren't you a lovely lady?
May I please see your panties?
Almost there!
He insists that he isn't naughty,
but he's always thinking about naughty stuff.
...Florian Triangle!
Stop that, Harassment Skeleton!
There's a mansion?
And here... I go!
Indeed, there is. You're welcome
to visit Dr. Hogback's mansion.
Hey, Luffy! What's up with this guy?
I'm not naughty.
These seas are haunted!
Isn't he funny? I had him join our crew.
Don't lie!
What?!
No, you didn't! I won't allow it!
"Rice Ball Monster--Zorokiller"
Yo ho ho ho
You did it!
What? What is it?
This is the rice ball monster, Zorokiller!
Now, don't get so worked up.
What's the big deal, Chopper?
Ow!
Hogback...
"Absolutely No Entry"
Come on inside! Let's have dinner.
He loves rice balls!
Huh...?
He can't stand people who
don't carry rice balls on them.
That's not for you to decide!
--One appeared!
-- Yo ho ho ho
I can't stand you.
Damn it! I thought I was doing her a favor!
"The Man Called a Genius!
Hogback Makes His Appearance!"
It's a ghost ship!
You're funny!
Guys, try to make yourselves
useful every now and then!
The Revive-Revive Fruit?
--Tea!
--Okay, coming up!
We're on our way...
The Revive-Revive Fruit lets you...
Wh-What in the...? You didn't!
Why am I serving tea?!
...come back to life.
What're you doing in here?
"Matsuhachi"
Serve your boss tea!
In other words, I'm a revived human.
...to deliver Bink's booze
Didn't see the writing that said to keep out?
I guess you can take a peek,
It guarantees the mysterious
power of a second shot at life.
but I had planned on surprising
everyone all at once.
I just realized something.
I bet he's the treasure's guardian!
Let's go look for him.
My organization is understaffed.
A revived human!
Don't tell the others about it yet.
I want higher-level subordinates
who will treat me with respect...
N-Now that I take a closer look,
you don't have a shadow!
Whatcha think? Feeling especially surprised?
H-Huh?
It had a lackluster design,
not to mention boring features.
You're right! What are you, really?
Amateur Sing Off!
No!
So I spruced it up a bit!
Anyone interested in trying
their luck, please enter!
But I've never seen its power source before.
You gave me quite a start!
I have spent far too many
years drifting on these seas
Where'd you get it?
How many decades have passed
since I saw people in the flesh?
This is it! I could use this!
Don't remodel stuff without permission!
Putting that aside...
to tell my story in one sitting.
What did you use as the motif?!
"Giant Luffybomber"
Meanwhile, here at
Chopper Man's secret base...!
No!
...join my crew!
C-Can't you tell? It's a white hobby horse...
Yeah, okay.
Hey! What is it? What's wrong?
This is a hardcore waver
equipped with a Jet Dial!
Hey!
Have at me.
G... G-G-G...
What's keeping you? Have at me! Come on!
Ghost!
And you had the nerve to
turn it into a hobby horse?!
Gah! Something's there!
"Pretty Assistant--Namifia"
This is Namifia, a pretty assistant!
Do you think I'm a kid?!
Evil be gone! Evil be gone!
"The Joy of Seeing People!
The Gentleman Skeleton's True Identity!"
Hey... The fog kept me from
getting a good look at the horses,
Uh, no...
I'm scared! It's a ghost!
Namifia efficiently manages
Chopper Man's missions.
Awesome!
but didn't they seem a bit strange?
It's running away!
It's done!
I know they won't complain
about the design now!
Uh, you must be imagining things!
Now bring it on!
Wh-What's causing that tremor?!
Aw, jeez! Please, someone call!
We're in the red this month!
This is my trump card.
I-It couldn't be!
Really...? I hope that's all it is.
Hi! Hello, everyone! Good day to you.
"Plunging into the Devil's Sea!
The Mysterious Skeleton Floating in the Fog!"
I shall be imposing upon
you here on your vessel!
It's no use... Guess we'll have
to cut our grocery budget.
Anyway, you're a lifesaver!
Thanks for saving our hides!
I am the dead and skeletonized Brook.
It's a pleasure to meet you!
It was nothing! Please, have a drink.
"Evil Be Gone"
Yay! Luffy's next!
You're a polar bear?
Don't be stupid! And what the heck is he?!
What's going on?
I'm a panda.
Go!
"Evil Be Gone"
So how'd an island get there?
This forest is filled with unusual animals,
My, my! They're harsh!
Huh?
making it dangerous to simply walk around.
Wow! That's a new record!
Hey, Namifia! I'm out of potachi!
Yeah, I was surprised! I thought
Cerberus was an imaginary animal.
It's a skeleton!
Go buy me some more!
Nami-san! Robin-chan! Sorry for the wait.
That terrifying beast must
be a mutant or something!
"Champion of Justice--Chopper Man"
Goodness, aren't you a lovely lady?
May I please see your panties?
This is Chopper Man, the champion of justice!
I know! This time let's jump off together!
--Okay!
--Hey, guys!
I was afraid we were gonna be stuck
in that tree when you found us.
He is our hero,
protecting peace around the world!
Stop that, Harassment Skeleton!
--Almost ready...!
--If you're goofing off,
The mansion is the best place
to wait for your friends.
could you grab those octopi you
threw in the aquarium yesterday?
Armed... and... ready!
Ow, ow...
This is the ghost island
that wanders the seas...
It stands out and it's safe.
Octopi?
"Evil Be Gone"
That hurt! Why did you do that, Namifia?
Tada!
Yeah.
Plus...
We're having octopus rice
and octopus shabu.
You're fully decked out in anti-evil stuff!
This is no time to be laughing
at a TV show, Chopper Man.
...I'll get to meet Dr. Hogback!
...Thriller Bark!
I'll boil tomatoes to soft
perfection for a sauce
S-Stupid skeleton! B-Beat it already!
Is he all that famous?
Earth isn't in the least bit of peril today!
and make some colorful salpicon!
There isn't a single doctor
who doesn't know his name!
I figured I'd use all the
octopi in tonight's dinner.
Isn't that a good thing?!
Evil be gone! Evil be gone!
He's a famous surgeon.
Thriller Bark...
No, it's not! We're out of the job if
people don't call asking for your help!
With his miraculous operations, he's saved
as many people as there are stars!
H-Hey...
Wow, it's working! Usopp, that's amazing!
Sounds good! Sanji, add fried
octopus to the menu!
"Evil Be Gone"
You know it! This is my full
"Anti-Evil Spirit Arsenal."
He has obtained status, honor,
and everything you could get as a doctor!
All you talk about is business!
But isn't peace on Earth more important?
"One Unnatural Phenomenon After the Next!
Disembarking on Thriller Bark!"
Make a hundred!
Fine, you got it.
An evil spirit?! Where? Where is it?
He's earned the respect of
doctors around the world!
Starting tomorrow,
you're grounded from eating potachi.
So go get 'em!
Wait a sec! This isn't
showing up on the Log Pose.
All right!
--It's you!
--What?!
I'm sorry.
--Koala--!
--Now for our next item on the news.
That's hardly surprising. This island
came clear from the West Blue.
But then he suddenly vanished one day.
Damn it! There's no way a skeleton
can walk, talk, and grow an afro!
They're certainly lively.
Oh, perfect timing! I
have one for you, Robin.
I wonder if there is any juicy bad news.
This is a dream! It has to be a dream!
The West Blue?!
Some say he went missing,
while others say he was abducted.
--Thank you.
--Hurry! --Octopus!
Like a monster appeared!
Or a robot is going berserk!
Yeah...
Really?!
Octopus! Octopus! Octopus!
It threw the medical world
into an uproar for a while,
Phew! It's just a dream...
Hey, where are you going?!
Hey! Give the remote back.
Heave-ho!
but in the end, no one could find any leads.
--Forget it.
--I wanna watch those comedians!
Goodness, this is truly my lucky day!
I'll get them!
Hello? Please wake up.
Now he's on the verge of becoming a legend.
Good morning.
No!
Not only have I run into people, but my
heartfelt dream has also come true!
Shuddup!
Darn it! They keep getting away!
I can't catch any.
You meant that Dr. Hogback, right?
Hey, Luffy! What's up with this guy?
All of you in front of your TV sets,
how are you doing?
Indeed! The doctor is
still conducting research
Isn't he funny? I had him join our crew.
All righty! Now it's my turn.
Usodaba!
No, you didn't! I won't allow it!
No, wait! If they pull you into the water,
My organization, the Usodaba Gang,
has taken over this TV station!
that goes beyond the
boundary of human knowledge.
He's so agile!
Do you know why you went with him?!
you Devil Fruit power holders will drown!
Indeed! I became light on my feet
after I died and turned to bones!
Great! There's a crisis!
Would it be okay if I
asked for his autograph?
It was to keep Luffy from
doing anything crazy!
Leave this to me.
What's he doing on TV?
Please break through the gate towering
over you and escape with all due haste!
If that's all you want,
I'm sure that would be fine.
We're ashamed of ourselves...
There is but one reason why
we came to this TV station!
Now, don't get so worked up.
Usopp?!
No matter what, do not
drop anchor by the shore!
I have a declaration for all
those currently tuned in!
No way!
Come on inside! Let's have dinner.
It made me so very happy to meet you today!
This forest... even has lions!
Damn! Where'd they wander off to?!
In order to conquer the world,
my Usodaba Gang...
That's not for you to decide!
Found them!
...is currently recruiting people
who would like to join our ranks!
I will never forget that scrumptious meal!
The darn things are clinging onto each other!
You're funny!
But...
Well, take care! May we have the
fortune to meet on other waters!
What?
No!
Join now, and no entry fees!
Prepare to meet your maker, octies!
Honestly, you have a splendid
dining room! And that kitchen!
Hey! Wait, Brook!
No annual conference fees!
Isn't he a power holder?
And that's not all!
In the end, you're no match
for the Great Usopp!
What's your problem?! Don't freak me out!
Why on earth did he jump into the water?!
I will present the most
extraordinary of our applicants
This is all so wonderful!
with my organization's secret treasure.
What was it?!
Isn't it?
J-Just now, I saw a l-lion outside!
It's fast! It's strong!
He's running on the water!
You bet it is! It was made
by someone as super as me!
Wow! Awesome!
But it's a model, so you can't ride in it.
Man, you've got a pretty keen eye.
We'll present the Air Force C Mach 2!
I-It looked like this.
There's one!
I don't buy that!
Hey! Don't get all chummy with him, Franky.
Two and three!
A-At any rate, Luffy, let's take his advice.
Then take a look for yourself!
But I can't wait to eat!
Four, five, six...
I had to stand in line for a week to get this.
Go on!
I have no idea what's going on, but this
island is clearly nothing but trouble!
I really don't want to part with it,
I haven't had a decent meal in decades.
Prey... Fresh prey...
but I'm woefully giving this away!
Huh? Did you say something?
Prey! Fresh prey!
I've had to endure terrible agony every day
It's the Air Force C Mach 2
Limited Edition Version?!
He's dying to go!
as the skin on my belly caved
in until it touched my back!
Now, you in front of the TV!
Join the Usodaba Gang right this instant!
What's the deal with this Ghost Island?
Hey, where'd that ghost go?
But since I'm a skeleton, I don't
have any skin on my belly or back!
This is bad! Chopper Man, it's time for action!
Is it still on board?
Darn octopi don't know when to give up!
Right!
No, it flew back toward the island.
You know what your mission is, right?
Of course I do!
That's probably where it resides.
I'm going to join the Usodaba Gang!
It's a skull joke!
Hey, about that large tremor
we felt a minute ago...
You don't know after all!
Usopp!
A skull joke!
Well, that's no good!
Air Force C Mach 2 Limited Edition Version!
If that mouth-like gate
caused it when it shut,
As a gentleman, I adore the laid-back
time spent while waiting for my meal.
Curse you!
Weird stuff's out there!
Super weird stuff's out there!
I am extremely worried...
I think that it essentially devoured us.
Get off me!
That's right!
--We've got the Giant Luffybomber!
--Bomber!
So it ate us?
--Dinner, yay! Dinner! C'mon, baby!
--Food! Food! Food! Food!
It's hard to see through the fog,
What's going on? The
water turned pitch black!
Stop right here! Stop the
carriage, Hildon-san!
If I used that...!
but the fence extending from the gate
appears to encompass the island.
"Giant Luffybomber"
It's gone!
Why are you so worked up?
Are you having hallucinations?
Chef! For my drink, I'll take milk.
Hey! Are you okay down there?
Oh, yeah... I sold it just the other day...
Usopp's in trouble!
The octopi latched onto him!
Shut up! Wait quietly!
In other words, our ship is currently trapped
That wasn't a hallucination!
I'm sure they were out there!
Before I forget, Kroobuckle...
What?!
inside a fence that surrounds the island.
This forest is way too messed up!
No, I'm Brook.
I suppose. This forest is a little strange.
I get it! So that's why the skeleton
told us to escape ASAP!
Um, actually, you'll have to forgive me,
but I still don't know your name...
Usopp, grab on!
What do you think, Robiflowern?
The combination of thick fog and fear
can induce hallucinations in some.
Wasn't I overflowing with
charisma when I was on TV?
Usopp!
Me? I'm Luffy.
Does that mean someone is making
this island "wander" the seas?
Yeah, well, more or less...
So before I forget, what exactly are you?
Are you okay?!
Huh? That was a hallucination?
What's the point?
Just how little do you
know about each other?!
Usopp!
"Flower Monster--Robiflowern"
What a relief!
If the island is moving,
we're still in the middle of the ocean.
This is the flower monster, Robiflowern.
All right, it's ready!
Really, now? A hallucination?
We can't drop the anchor here...
She's an evil woman
Let go, you little--
Nah, it was too vivid for that!
who's been defeated by Chopper Man's
killer "Cute Spark" time after time.
Whoa, there! Why do I get the
feeling you wanna stay here?!
You little twerp!
Help yourselves. We can
kick the skeleton out later.
Gulp, gulp, gulp!
It's no good! The water's so
dark I can't see where he is!
Hildon-san! Sorry, but could
you take us back to the shore?
We've gotta leave now!
We're gonna get cursed!
Do you guys see me in a
somewhat better light now?
For now, enjoy the meal!
I used up all the octopi.
Listen, guys. I've come down with
Fear-of-unknown-islands-osis!
Even if it's dangerous, we'll manage somehow.
Looks good!
--Huh?
--Don't laze around during our strategy meeting!
Hey, Brook! Eat all you want!
Same! I've caught the same bug.
What?!
If I know where they are, I can...
--Tea!
--Okay, coming up!
Sanji's an awesome cook!
Okay! Let's take her up to the shore!
But then I won't get to meet Dr. Hogback!
Gum-Gum... Gatling!
Do you have Set-for-Adventure-osis?!
I did it again!
But... my heart feels full
instead of my stomach...
I wanna meet him!
"Matsuhachi"
Serve your boss tea!
Think that over! Luffy, open up your eyes!
Yeah, yeah, I get how you feel!
But this is when we've gotta listen to
our special Something's Fishy Sensors!
See that creepy building?!
It's a real haunted mansion!
It's okay. If this plan is a success,
You're...
Miss, you seem to have gotten a bit more.
Are you willing to die to meet that doctor?
high-level subordinates will flock to me...
He's alive!
You're taking malicious
spirits way too lightly.
Would you mind if we swapped plates?
What a relief.
Or will you skip meeting him
so we can leave this island alive?
Usodaba-sama, you're wonderful!
Your punches nearly killed me!
There's extra, so eat your own!
Which will it be?!
Usodaba-sama, you're a genius!
All this over some measly octopi.
Of course I don't want to die! Or get scared!
What're you talking about?
I'm being super careful!
Usodaba-sama, have some tea!
You're the one who said to go get them!
Aw dese octopuses were awive in da
aquaweeam undil naw too wong ago!
Is that right? I shall
go inform the coachmen.
I'm gonna catch that ghost
and keep it as a pet.
But hijacking the airwaves was a good idea...
What were they doing?
...for you, anyway, Usodaba-sama.
You're totally underestimating it!
They were alive until just
recently in the aquarium?
Everyone, please wait here.
And above all else, we have to
bring back our dear crewmate.
That was one word too many, Robiflowern.
Your ship has its own aquarium?
Hey, something's floating on the water.
Sanji, my pirate lunch!
My plans are always perfect!
Stop the carriage!
You bether beweeb it! Fwanky made
dis swip and it hash evewyding!
Crewmate...? Hey, I'm
against you on that one!
What? What?
Huh? Where is it?
If I get it across on TV that my
Usodaba Gang is strong and cool,
Is that it?
I'd be too scared to sleep at night
if we had a skeleton for a crewmate!
"Offering of Treasure to the Sea God"
A barrel?
It truly is an amazing ship!
I've never seen one like it before.
I bet people wanting to join
will come flocking in droves!
Doesn't it say "treasure" on it?
I got your lunchbox.
Luffy! Franky! You'd better
be sure to protect Robin-chan!
Wanna deck it ow wader?
When that happens,
world domination will be as easy as pie!
"Treasure"
You're right! Maybe a treasure
ship accidentally dropped it!
I'm sorry, Chopper! I know
you're passing up a huge chance.
Yes, I'd love to take a tour!
There's nothin' like exploring
an uncharted island, is there?
It can't be helped! I'm still green,
since I can't act on my own like Luffy.
"Offering of Treasure to the Sea God"
And then those two will get the boot.
Treasure?!
How could he understand that?
Hey, Luffy! Let's pull the thing up already!
But what type of show will you put on?
It rocks! Yay! Show it off! C'mon!
You've gotta be kidding!
You're going with them, Robin?
Okay!
I'm glad you asked!
I simply love the thrill.
"10 Minutes Later..."
Eat quietly!
Treasure! Treasure!
A treasure of silver and gold!
All right! So, guys, we're gonna
take a small boat to disembark,
The Revive-Revive Fruit?
I figured a Devil Fruit was behind this.
"Shhh..."
Pieces nice and big! Nice and--
First, we'll start with my enchanting voice.
Indeed, it is.
Nope!
but I've still got a special
surprise I haven't shown you yet!
How long is he going to keep us waiting?
"Super Star"
To be honest, I have already
died once, decades ago.
That contains booze and rations.
He still isn't back yet...
It's Soldier Dock System, Channel 2!
How would you know if
you haven't looked inside?
Wipe your face first! How'd you
manage to get food all over yourself?
Sorry for the wait!
Doesn't the banner say,
"Offering of Treasure to the Sea God"?
That's strange. We're just
going back the way we...
Two?
Just leave this to me!
You heard me!
I'll make all of the women in front
of the TV swoon with my charms.
"Offering of Treasure to the Sea God"
This system uses a total of five channels.
It's called a "drifting barrel."
The Revive-Revive Fruit lets you...
It means someone made an
offering to the god of the sea
0 comes up twice.
What?! No one's there!
1...
Please watch, Robiflowern-chan!
...come back to life.
in hopes of a safe voyage.
2...
In other words, I'm a revived human.
S-Sure...
Even the horses are gone!
3...
It's not my fault if you have to start sharing me.
"Offering of Treasure"
means it's a gift to the god.
They abandoned us in a graveyard!
4!
Each dock has its own unique function.
It guarantees the mysterious
power of a second shot at life.
That bites! So we can't do anything with it?
I wonder if this is a good idea.
They what?! Why?!
Just a sec!
It's fine. Let him perform,
Robiflowern. He's the opening act.
You've already revealed the paddle
wheel in 0 and the contents in 1 and 3.
A revived human!
Hey! Since we picked it up,
let's drink the booze!
Eh?! They abandoned us?!
So it gave you the power to come
back to life once after dying?
Sure they aren't going potty?
Stupid! The god'll get angry at you!
Go wait in the Call Center for incoming
calls from people wanting to join!
But as I recall, you said
2 and 4 were still empty.
Hildon! Hey!
You can drink it as long as you pray first.
Yeah, that's right.
Where'd you go?!
Oh, excuse me.
I don't pray to any gods.
Very well.
'Cause I was savin' them
for a special occasion!
And a long time ago,
I was a pirate just like you!
I've heard that booze is extra good
after it's been floating on the waves.
I see it! I can see it!
Anyone steering clear of the island
should give it a quick spin!
The Call Center will be abuzz
Then we've gotta try it out!
You're a fellow pirate?
with interested viewers
from across the country!
That's right. Oh, pardon me.
Sweet! Let's have a toast!
"Cooking for 30 Hours with Sanjiropus"
Cooking for 30 Hours with Sanjiropus!
It's custom to refill the barrel with
fresh offerings after you've emptied it.
I wish I could beat some manners into you.
Huh?
Soldier Dock System, Channel 2!
Hello! I'm the cooking
monster of love, Sanjiropus!
--Yeah?
--Let's open it! Hurry up and open it!
Set out!
What is it? What's gonna pop out?
Long, long ago, my crewmates and I
Hey, God! I'm taking your snacks. Heh, heh!
Today I'd like to introduce
you to a super-easy recipe
that uses leftovers in your fridge.
Of all the places, why'd they
have to choose a graveyard?
sailed into the Devil's Sea
on the ship you saw earlier.
What's so great about "God"?
Almost like magic, I'm able to
transform any old leftovers...
With its steam engine, this paddle
steamer that sits four is the Mini-Merry!
Didn't a certain someone beat the
crap out of that God on Sky Island?
Stop it! Jeez, I'm so scared!
However, we had the misfortune of running
into some terribly powerful pirates.
You don't have to remind me where we are!
...into dishes like this within three minutes.
It's Merry!
Okay, I'm done praying.
Merry came back as a boat!
What's going to happen to us now?
What?! From those ingredients?!
It's small, but now we can ride Merry again!
Chopper...
Now for the key point!
Cool, it opened!
Our entire crew was
annihilated in the battle.
What?!
For the remaining 29 hours and 57 minutes,
I will gaze at no one but you...
Something flew out!
Beep! Beep!
Naturally, I died with them.
What's that?
Stare...
Red light...?
When I was alive, the Revive-Revive's
only power was that I couldn't swim.
What was that? What does it mean?
Sweet! I'm getting the hang of it.
But on that day, the Fruit's
power finally took effect!
The booze flew out, flashed, and vanished.
N-N-No way...
It was a flare.
My soul returned from the Underworld!
A flare?
Don't you mean the Sea God's curse?
Stare...
H-Hey! Th-That looks bad!
I hope someone did that as a
simple prank, but just maybe...
We'll be fine! You can count on me.
What are you doing?! The food got cold!
Z-Zombies!
Just maybe?
That's the problem?
Someone may come after our ship.
It can't be helped.
No!!
We really do need my enchanting--
My soul should have quickly returned
to my body, thus reviving me!
S-So that was a trap?!
Something-or-Other Giri!
Outta the way!
I'll prove that I'm the strongest.
Now shut up and watch.
But I died on the Devil's Sea and as
you can see, it is dreadfully foggy.
"By opening the barrel, we just informed
someone of our location!" Like that?
I had no idea he was hiding
such a wonderful present...
"Rice Ball Samurai"
Chopper, check the perimeter!
So I got lost!
Thank you, Franky!
What?
--I'm on it!
--More bounty hunters might come down on us!
I'll be more than happy to go shopping
for supplies in a boat like that!
No!
My soul wandered through
the fog for an entire year.
Let's have fun and play, Missy!
No!
I don't see anyone anywhere!
Yahoo! Gimme a turn! I want a turn now!
Save me!
Screaming won't get ya anywhere.
Same here!
Stop right there!
No! That hurts! It hurts!
Yeah, I don't see anyone...
You took "considerate" to a new level.
I finally managed to find my body!
But this air pressure...
And the clouds are moving quickly.
Usopp!
Hey! Hold your horses, Straw Hat.
Please help me!
Who're you?!
We'll get to ride it in just a minute.
But by then, it had already turned
into a pearly white skeleton!
Everyone, take your stations!
We're escaping to the south-southeast!
Who cares? Get him!
Let them have a bit of fun!
Usopp!
A huge storm will be here in five minutes!
Is this everything, Franky?
Lost by a hair...
I don't see a storm, but if that's
what she says, I bet it'll suddenly hit!
Yeah. Including the 1 and 3
I've already shown you, this is it!
No!!
I was so surprised that my eyes
nearly popped out of my head.
Ow, ow, ow...
Nami, where should I take us?
Not that I have any eyeballs!
Channel 0: Support Paddles!
Head straight for 2 o'clock!
The carriage is gonna fall over!
They're insanely strong!
P-P-Please spare me!
Channel 1: The one-man waver,
White Hobby Horse!
What a moron! You're just like Zoro.
Th-There...
Bastard, do you have any rice balls?
Watch it!
Channel 3: The three-man recon
submarine, Shark Submerge III.
And that's how you became a talking skeleton?
It's scary how the Devil's Fruit
still brought you back
What?!
And Channel 2: The four-man
errand boat, Mini-Merry!
even though you're just a skeleton...
Make sure you have some from now on!
Um, excuse me!
Damn! It started to rain
right after her warning!
But now that the Fruit has done its job,
I've been bit!
At the moment, this is everything
the Soldier Dock System has to offer.
Damn it! He bit me!
isn't it just stealing your ability to swim?
--Now I'm gonna turn into a zombie!
--Usopp!
That's practically a curse!
"Fin"
Consider them soldiers meant to
assist the Thousand Sunny's voyage.
And skeletons normally
don't have hair, do they?
I'm on my way!
Now we've got lightning!
That didn't make sense!
Damn it! At this rate, my plan will be in ruins!
Who ever heard of a skeleton with an afro?
I really love the way you think!
I had strong roots.
Hey! Please let me join.
Franky, you rock! You rock! You rock!
I don't really care.
Oh, someone finally came!
No, don't bite me! Stop that!
Crap! We're getting hit by head winds!
--Hiya!
--It's you!
So you aren't a ghost?
You're actually a human?
--You rock! You rock! You rock! You rock!
--Yeah! I'm the ultimate man again this week!
Please save me!
Please let me join your gang. I want the model.
They're going to push us back!
No, you aren't quite human anymore...
Super!
Air Force C Mach 2 Limited Edition Version!
Anyway, you aren't a ghost, right?
Nami-san?!
In your dreams! I'd never give my
beloved collection to you, my enemy...
Right! I hate ghosts!
Let go of Usopp!
Nami-san! What is it?!
I'll start screaming if I see one.
What happened?!
You bastards!
Wait a second.
Hey! Is this ship really
that big of a pushover?
You hate ghosts? Have you ever
taken a look in the mirror?
Come on! Please!
What're they up to?
Shall I throw him out?
Oh, yeah!
I can't see squat through this fog!
No! Please put that mirror away!
No, wait.
Guys, take in the sails!
Hey, you!
We're bringing out the paddle!
Do you want this?
I'm sorry!
What's wrong?
Oh, that?
But her scream came from the island.
Wh-Whoa! T-Time out!
I want it! I want it!
Here, you dropped this.
Then it's yours.
W-Why...
Oh, thanks.
Guys, lemme ride the Mini-Merry already!
Really? Yay!
I love how cool it is! Do it!
Why doesn't the mirror show your reflection?!
In exchange, fight me and lose in a
pro-wrestling program that I planned out!
Jerk! You should be worried about Nami-san!
Hey, save me! They're about to bite me!
Nami!
And you should be worried about
the other two on top of her!
Crap! Let go of me! Stay back!
That's my condition.
He's a vampire!
Are you all set?
Huh? I have to lose?
Zombies are weak against...
The main sail is set, Nami-san!
I wonder if that scream means
a ghost killed them with a curse.
I hate losing...
Really?! That's awesome!
Special Attack! Flame Star!
I took in the foremast!
You're only pretending to lose.
Franky, we're ready!
Stop that! Don't jinx them!
N-Now that I take a closer look,
you don't have a shadow!
Don't you want the Air Force C
Mach 2 Limited Edition Version?
Great!
--Fire!
--That's rottin' bad!
Soldier Dock System, Channel 0!
You're right! What are you, really?
That worked better than I could have hoped!
That was dangerous, you pyro punk!
What was that?!
What if I actually caught on fire,
you stupid jerk?!
I'm only pretending, right? It's a deal!
With its cola-powered engine,
it's the Paddle Ship Sunny!
No one has touched the anchor!
Great! Take him to the dressing room!
Rotten scum!
It's too new for the
gears to be coming loose.
That ticked off the zombies.
Don't soothe yourself!
--Dabada!
--Yay! I'm going to be on TV!
We're freaking out! And it's your fault!
You'd better hurry, Nami!
Go!
This is our chance to escape!
At any rate, raise it back up!
R-Right!
Usodaba-sama?
It's going to throw the ship off balance!
I have spent far too many
years drifting on these seas
Plow forward!
If I defeat Chopper Man in
a fight in front of the cameras,
At this point, the mansion's the
closest place to run to for safety.
What? Did someone touch that?
to tell my story in one sitting.
Yeah, let's go there.
no one will question whether my
organization--no, I am the strongest!
No, no one went near there.
That was scary!
The story behind why I am a skeleton
We'll be okay! They can't catch up
and the story behind why I lack a
shadow are completely unrelated.
Makes sense!
if we run like mad for the mansion
once we're outta the graveyard!
Just you watch!
The main event is about to begin.
Zombies can only walk at a
snail's pace and groan at you.
To be continued.
Tell us now!
"At a snail's pace"?
"At a snail's pace"? "At a snail's pace"?
A certain man stole my
shadow a few years ago.
"At a snail's pace"?!
It was stolen?
Wait for us!
H-Huh?
We survived!
They're fast!
Your shadow?
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Yeah. It's nice that we pulled through,
but what's with this sea?
After seeing you move and talk,
nothing could surprise me.
Luffy! What the hell are you doing?!
Everyone around the country,
thank you for waiting!
It isn't night yet, but with this thick fog,
This isn't the time for games!
But does that sorta thing actually happen?
No, vit ishn't me! I'm vot doin' vis!
No! No! No--er, huh? Huh?
Today's main event is
Usodaba versus Chopper Man!
Yes, it does.
it's creepy how dark it is.
And having lost my shadow, I am no
longer able to exist in the world of light.
Just a sec... Time out!
Do you think we stumbled into that one sea?
We're broadcasting live from a special ring
in the globe-shaped observation deck.
I'm not ready for this!
"Wind"
Zero stamina!
I will be the ring announcer, Shorts.
But aren't you alive?
Look out, Straw Hat!
What? We're drawing up on Fishman Island?
Hurry, Usopp!
No, I cannot live under the light of the sun.
Y-Yeah!
We have invited Minoru Kazeno-san
to be our commentator.
Nope! First we have to cross haunted waters.
It's a pleasure!
Hey, punk! What was that about?!
--Usodaba!
--We already have a pumped-up
Usodaba in the ring.
Yep! Don't let your guard down.
Hey, I'm sorry. My sword sprang out...
I'm only alive now because I avoid the
sunlight here on these foggy waters.
From the looks of it, we're already
caught in the infamous...
Everyone across the nation!
Before today's match,
That's strange...
What would happen if you
were hit by the sunlight?
I'd like to present you with
one of my wonderful songs.
Looks like we're not the
only ones on the deck.
...Florian Triangle!
If I was directly hit by sunlight, my body...
Music--
Oh! At last, Chopper Man
has entered the stadium!
These are mysterious waters where
everything disappears without explanation.
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
...would be obliterated!
Yay! Namifia, are you watching?
I-It's h-ha-haunted...
The waves are carrying the ship away!
Chopper Man!
What's keeping you, Gah?!
With his cape glistening in the blue sky
Don't call me "Gah," punk!
All that cheering doesn't
make me happy or anything!
These seas are haunted!
So we've got company, huh?
The rudder won't budge!
What the hell?! And you all knew about this?!
If we used the paddle,
we could fight the waves, but...
It's him! He's coming this way
Uh, guys...
"Wind"
As expected, the crowd is
going wild for Chopper Man!
You never bothered to fill me in!
I was planning on going to the island anyway.
Working to defend the...
Why don't we go with the flow?
Zoro...
Enjoy letting it get to your
head while you still can!
Jerk! You've totally forgotten
about Nami-san, haven't you?
Today is the day I'm going to pulverize you.
Granny Kokoro gave us the heads up.
If I was directly hit by sunlight,
my body would be obliterated!
What's that?
There's a living skeleton!
Usodaba Lock!
A-A l-living skeleton?
Ow, ow. That hurts!
A spider web on the water?
You're taking this too far.
Keep quiet and let me beat you!
Don't you want that?
Obliterated?!
Only in your imagination.
Don't scare him more than he already is.
"That"?
Right...
At this rate, we're going to
ram right into the spider web.
The Air Force C Mach 2 Limited Edition Version!
Listen, Usopp.
Hey, we need the paddle! Release the paddle!
In this sea, over 100 ships
mysteriously vanish every year.
Don't. It's too late for that.
Well, Usodaba got the first strike, Kazeno-san.
"Wind"
Was it a ghost after all?
Or was it some sorta psychic?
And to top it off, I've heard ghost ships
carrying the dead wander these waters.
I could feel someone touching me.
Chopper Man isn't exhibiting his usual power.
I think I heard the sound of a
beast growling just a second ago.
I wonder what's wrong...
Damn it! It didn't harm the ship,
but now we're stuck here!
It really is a one-sided fight.
No! You shoulda warned me about this sooner!
A beast?
Hiya!
Ow, ow, ow!
Anyway, I'm worried about
Nami-san and the others.
What good would it have done?
I'll let you deal with the ship!
Take this!
And why is this spider
web so freakishly big?!
I-I coulda prepared! I've gotta
cover myself in anti-evil stuff!
What're you gonna do?
I'm gonna swim to the island
and save those three.
Thrum!
Usopp, please let me borrow some!
Wha--?!
No one could have expected
the match to turn out like this!
"Wind"
Usodaba is overwhelmingly powerful.
They... aren't chasing us anymore, are they?
What?! That was lame!
Yo ho ho ho
He's good.
What's with this island?! It's oozing
with stuff that shouldn't exist!
Dang, Chopper Man's weak!
Wow! Sanji's floating back up.
Where's that voice coming from?!
What a letdown.
How's he doing that?
In comparison, Usodaba is putting
up a surprisingly good fight.
Guys, if I turn into a zombie,
finish me off in a single blow!
Whoa!
Yo ho ho ho
Usodaba! Usodaba!
Gah!
Where'd you come up with that?
You said, "Gah!"
Usodaba!
It was in the Illustrated Zombie Guide
I read in Sunny's library!
Usodaba! Usodaba!...
Shut up! Why don't you give it a try?!
Yo ho ho ho
For a scaredy-cat, you read
way too many of those books.
So it doesn't want us to leave the ship, huh?
It looks like Usodaba's popularity
is suddenly skyrocketing!
I don't see what it's after.
If it wanted to kill us, we're wide open.
I have witnessed someone who lost his shadow
Uh, testing, testing.
-- Yo ho ho ho
--One appeared!
Well, we're here. Right now,
I just want a glass of water!
Hello? Is this the reporter, Sanjiropus-san?
disappear under the light of the sun.
What's wrong, Robin-chan?
It's a ghost ship!
The Call Center is getting
flooded with people saying,
"Call Center"
Something has caught me!
It was truly terrifying!
A hair-raising sight to behold!
I get to meet him after all. I can't wait!
"I want to join the Usodaba Gang."
How dare you have your way with her?!
Yo ho ho ho
I don't think anyone in his right mind
would live on this island.
At last!
And here I'm a skeleton!
At last, my time has come!
Your shadow appears on the ground
when you stand in the light.
Hey, can we stop now? I want
to take the model and go home.
I'd bet on it!
Yo ho ho ho
It really does sound like a beast!
Since I lack a shadow,
my body cannot reflect light.
Hang in there for just a bit longer!
Excuse me! Is this Dr. Hogback's mansion?
I'm about to wind this up.
Yo ho ho ho
Wh-What's going on?!
That's why I cannot be seen
in mirrors or pictures.
I'm seriously going to crush you.
Look!
Oh, no! Usodaba has climbed onto the top rope!
Waves are doin' that! Unnatural waves
are forming inside the fence!
We're traveling pira--sailors!
In other words, the light
rejects my very existence!
Yo ho ho ho
Chopper Man is in serious trouble!
We got lost and could use some help!
And my crewmates are all dead!
"Wind"
Will tonight be the birth of a new, dark hero?
Please let us stay here!
Your life sucks!
This will finish him off.
They're carrying the ship!
What's with that song?!
Even so, I've scraped by!
Is anyone here?
Robin-chan, where is he?
It's an evil spirit's sailor song!
Scraped down to the bone!
We're in the clear. He seems to have left.
What's with this mansion?
A tunnel runs through the center of it!
I am the dead and skeletonized
Brook. It's a pleasure!
Don't listen! Plug your ears!
Hey, Gah! Raise the anchor!
It'll curse you!
We can't sail like this.
Why are you so cheerful?
But first, I'd like to sing a song!
I can see a courtyard on the other side.
Who're you calling "Gah"?!
Pretend you can't hear it if
a ghost tries to talk to you!
Excuse me!
Usopp! Chopper! Answer me!
It'll drag you into the sea if you respond!
"Evil Be Gone"
H-Hey! What's wrong? You okay?
My Air Force C Mach 2 Limited Edition Version!
Crap! The current's pulling us
away from Nami-san.
Evil spirits wanna drag you down with them!
Maybe no one's home.
Is it all right?
Hey, Franky! Use one of the ship's
secret weapons to get us outta this!
That would stink! We'll have to
face zombies if we turn back.
No!
Phew! It's still fixable.
Today is truly a wonderful day! I met people!
Sure thing! I've got a Peek-a-Boo Vinyl Pool.
Yo ho ho ho
Thank goodness...!
Look! A light in the back turned on.
Thank goodness!
Sounds fun! Wait...
Is someone aboard that ship...?
Is it today or tomorrow?
Gimme.
It's not just a light, it's
a spotlight for this well.
"Evil Be Gone"
Are you a moron?!
On these dark, foggy seas, I can't tell
when one day moves to the next...
--No way.
--Eh?
Wasn't that the deal?
If he's our foe, we'll take him out.
That deal? I never intended
to go through with that!
Something... is up there.
"Evil Be Gone"
Wh-What now?!
Dumb deer!
Wh-What...?
Right now, I'm more popular than you!
Welcome!
It's all going according to plan!
But I worked so hard...
One, two, three!
Go on, everyone!
Let's hear you call for Usodaba!
What?! What gives?!
We're on our way...
Ouch, ow, ow, ow...
Four, five!
Not yet!
--Dabada!
--This match isn't over yet!
That woman's throwing plates!
No wonder that hurt...
Six, seven!
We fell all the way from up there, guys.
Hmph! You're being a poor loser.
...to deliver Bink's booze
Doesn't it seem like she's goin' after me?!
All of my crewmates passed away...
Killer move!
Yes, I am! I cannot invite
you into the mansion.
Cute Spark.
I was all alone on a large ship
with a broken rudder...
Where are we?
Ah, this is...
We're already on Ghost Island.
Those two may step inside.
Cute Spark!
Yo ho ho ho...
Ghost?!
I merely rocked on the water
as I drifted for several decades.
--Cute, cute, cute!
--Allow me to explain!
Huh? Why?
Hey! Cut that out!
--Cute... Spark!
--Chopper Man can melt the heart
You may get lost!
It makes me even more scared!
--Cute, cute, cute! Cute! Cute?
--of anyone who sees his killer "Cute Spark."
Eight, nine!
I was really lonely!
Why me?!
But how in the world did we get down here?
Cute!
That's enough! Hold your hand!
I was lonely! And scared!
Vroom, vroom! Vroom, vroom, vroom! Cute?
Did you see that just now?
A skeleton was singing!
We got too excited over
Mini-Merry and ran ashore.
What was that?!
I can't take any more scary stuff!
"Evil Be Gone"
I wanted to die!
S-Stupid! Skeletons don't sing.
He's totally aware of how cute he is!
I got a bit overconfident, let it rip
and rammed into the wall.
You're just hearing things!
But I'm glad I've lived such a long life.
I won't lose! I won't lose to you!
That's when all three of us got sent flying.
Yep, yep!
Chopper Man! Chopper Man!
Someone's coming out.
But didn't you hear him?
People are joy!
I think we can make this
one exception, Cindry-chan.
C'mon! Let's go! Like right now!
I see you as "joy"!
--Chopper Man! Chopper Man!...
--Wh-What's this?
Within seconds, we were at
the bottom of this trench.
There really is a living skeleton! Sweet!
I'm sorry if she startled you guys.
D'aw, Chopper Man is so adorable!
I'm 100% at fault, but you'll
forgive me 'cause I'm cute!
If only my tears hadn't gone dry,
so I could shed tears of joy!
A long time ago, this woman was
engaged to her wealthy master.
Go away, Usodaba!
Hold your horses!
"Wind"
The stadium has flipped 180 degrees.
Chopper Man is the crowd favorite!
Not so fast, Luffy.
I'm seriously gonna whack you!
You invited me to join your crew, didn't you?
"I'm sorry."
To test his love, she broke
all of his prized plates.
For one thing, isn't it weird
how all this fog appeared
Let's share some of the
feedback we've received.
That made me truly happy! Thank you!
Go on. We're going to draw to see
who goes aboard that ship with Luffy.
He tossed her out, and her
tragic past has made her
when we entered the island?
"Call Center"
Uh... "Chopper Man, good luck!
Don't let Usodabo beat you."
But I'm afraid I must turn your offer down.
develop an aversion to plates.
Maybe it's a trap to deal with adversaries?
What?!
She's my servant, Cindry-chan!
I'm Usodaba!
Eh?! Why?!
Why?! Send whoever actually wants to go!
We should consider ourselves lucky
this wasn't lined with bamboo spears.
Okay, I really don't care.
"Don't lose to Long-nose."
As I just explained, my
shadow has been stolen.
At least say my name!
And I've failed to introduce myself.
I am the world-renowned Dr. Hogback!
Right! That's what we should do!
At any rate, everyone's really excited over here!
You're right! We're okay because
we landed on these skeletons!
Do that!
I cannot live under the sun.
Whose side are you on?!
Are you sure you're okay with that?
Uh-huh.
Also known as a genius!
--Damn it!
--Chopper Man, let me tag in!
I'm currently protected by the fog that
I said cut that out!
--Ten!
--Usopp!
Okay, let's go!
Become the wind.
blocks the sunlight here in the Devil's Sea.
Hey, hey, hey! Cindry-chan,
I said you could stop!
Hey! Why are you tagging in?!
Yay!
But we've barely set foot on the island.
But if I left with you, it would be a matter
I hate this...
Luffy and the others will
come for us if we sit tight.
Please let me draw!
It makes me look bad
when you don't listen to me.
of time before my body was obliterated.
I won't forgive you for bullying Chopper Man!
But I'm scared of being below sea level.
Whoa, Zoro-kun! Wait, wait!
I will stay here and wait
Uh oh! Minoru Kazeno
suddenly entered the fight!
Crap!
for the miraculous day
when I reclaim my shadow!
Does everyone except the
three of us plan on going?
Fair enough. It's dangerous and hard to find.
I'll draw! I'll draw! I'll take my chances!
At the very least, why don't we wait
for help on the shore at ground level?
I'll just have to pull out my ultimate weapon!
Click.
Don't act like such a stranger!
I can go by myself, you know!
I wish plates would disappear
from the face of the earth!
If you need your shadow,
I'll take it back for you!
What's that?
So, like, which way takes us up?
If we don't hurry, the ship's going to leave.
Hey, look outside!
I understand! I understand completely!
Didn't you say someone stole it?
Who was it? Where is he?
That isn't an option.
Cyber!
But I was in the middle of a conversation!
"Giant Robot--Frangashan"
Just draw your sticks already.
This is the giant robot, Frangashan!
Chopper, is he the guy
you were talking about?
You're a really great guy...
Two people will go with him.
D-Dr. Hogback in the flesh!
This is Dr. Usodaba's latest secret weapon.
It'll be their job to make sure
he doesn't do anything stupid.
What is that? A dog?
I'm surprised! However, I cannot tell you.
He doesn't seem too bright.
Its true strength is unknown!
Watch it, Nami!
Go, Frangashan! Destroy everything!
I could not ask you to die
for me when we've just met!
That's no dog.
You may talk inside.
Today, I will make an exception.
Th-Then what is it?
Okay!
Meaning the foe's too strong?
Leave this to me!
H-Huh? C-Could that be C-Cer...
All three of you may enter.
Why'd it have to be me?
Flick.
It wouldn't kill you!
At least give us a name.
Come in!
See? I really am the strongest!
R-Right, right! Come inside my mansion.
I wanna go back...
Cerberus?!
No, my lips are sealed.
Nami, you ready yet? Hurry on up!
I don't get why I wasn't welcome,
but should we take them up on the offer?
Gotcha!
Honestly, I don't know where he is.
Gah! That's--!
No, no, no, no!
It's Cerberus!
I said I was cool with going by myself...
Sure. Beats the zombies outside.
I don't even know if I'll see him again
before my second life comes to an end.
Forget it! What if you did something
stupid that got our whole ship cursed?
"Giant Robot--Luffybomber"
Wh-What's Cerberus?!
This is the giant robot, Luffybomber!
I-I-I'm p-pretty sure it's
the watchdog of Hell!
But if our paths should ever cross,
I have decided to fight him!
It's a giant robot that's 50 meters tall.
I'm still...
Does that really exist?!
My luck bites!
Personality: It does its own thing!
Sure does! It's right behind us!
I'm still outside...
Nami-san, never fear!
I'll protect you, Nami-san!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I came to save you. It came at a high price.
Does that mean we're in Hell?!
Putting that aside...
No, I don't wanna know!
It's a pleasure to welcome you to my mansion.
But my, you sure are grungy!
...let's sing!
I expect you to pay me back!
How are you supposed to protect me...?
Namifia!
Nami, weren't you eager
to find a treasure ship?
Damn it! Frangashan, do something!
Just run! It'll eat us if we stop!
What brings you here?
There's no way this is a treasure ship!
Bring it on!
A whole bunch of things, but for starters--
Didn't you see that skeleton move around?!
I'll explain everything in detail later.
I bet he's the treasure's guardian!
Let's go look for him.
Zombies attacked us in the graveyard,
so we ran here for cover.
Instruments are my pride and joy.
I was a musician on my pirate ship.
Here I go!
Zombies, eh?
Really?! You're a musician?
There was a whole bunch of stuff
that made us doubt our eyes.
Hey, here he comes!
Please! Join my crew, moron!
Yeah!
What's the deal with this island?
Go, Frangashan! Huh?
Since you live here,
you've gotta know something!
Let's enjoy a fun sailor song!
What's wrong, Chopper?
H-Huh?
Chopper, what are you looking at?
S-Stupid! Stop that!
I see. So they attacked you, huh?
"Yip"?
What are you going to do?
I'm glad you made it here
in one piece. That's a relief!
Upsy daisy.
It lifted up the globe!
Hey, now that I take a closer look,
isn't one of them a fox?
Hey! There are a bunch of people in here!
To answer your question:
I don't know what they are,
which is why I live here.
No!
Wow, everyone was quick to flee.
Look! That hurt its feelings.
So you're conducting research on the zombies?
No!
Here I go!
Hey! What is it? What's wrong?
Must be a sore spot.
Yeah.
G... G-G-G...
Evil be gone! Evil be gone!
We ticked it off!
Indeed, I am!
Ghost!
People are terrified when they hear "zombie."
Luffy, rest in peace!
Gah! Something's there!
Evil be gone! Evil be gone!
But what if I rephrase it
to "resurrecting the dead"?
Now it's saying, "Pow!"
You're pretty good...
I'm scared! It's a ghost!
We must have hit a real sore spot!
Huh?
Hasn't that been all mankind's eternal dream?
Awesome!
Sweet!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
It's running away!
I'm falling!
Look! There is a staircase!
Everyone has a special someone or two
they'd like to see return from the dead.
That will take us to the ground level!
Good day to you!
Wh-What's causing that tremor?!
Thank goodness!
Huh?
I-It couldn't be!
Stupid! Let go! No, don't let go!
But toying with human mortality is
unorthodox medicine that disrespects God!
Sorry for earlier! Our eyes locked, but I
wasn't able to give a proper greeting.
Take this! Feel my wrath
for not giving me that model!
How horrible!
This ship was already under observation.
Chopper Violence!
You gave me quite a start!
That's why I slipped away
from the public eye--
How many decades have passed
since I saw people in the flesh?
Come look! They've blocked
the path in front of you.
so I could continue my
research on this island in secret!
Every ship I run across seems
to be a ghost ship! It's dreadful!
Gah, it's persistent!
Cheers for a good day at work!
S-So that's the story!
This is what caused that tremor!
We hit a really sore spot!
But I'm sure tons of people
around the world
Come along! Feel free to come right inside.
Oomph.
What is that?
A word, please!
would be thrilled if your
research is a success!
Smoke Star!
H-Hey, did a sea monster gobble us up?
Why don't we enjoy a nice,
leisurely conversation?
Man! That applause doesn't
make me happy or anything.
Look! He's talking!
I'll be rooting for you, Dr. Hogback!
What's going on?
The skeleton has an afro and he's talking!
You're rather open-minded!
Thank you, Dr. Chopper.
In the end, this just boosted his popularity.
I can't believe it...
This is the back of the gate.
My, my!
What?!
The gate...?
Damn it! I'll get you for this!
Sh-Shucks, Doctor! I'm not happy because
you thanked me or anything, you jerk!
Which means...
What a truly elegant lady! You're beautiful!
Let's look out the aft!
This one really put us in the red, but...
N-No, hardly!
May I have your autograph?
Why, certainly!
He certainly is beloved!
My eyes follow the beautiful ladies.
"To Dr. Chopper..."
To Dr. Chopper...
What's going on?
That's it!
But I'm a skeleton, so I don't have eyes!
Could you show me your lab later?
Hello. This is the office for
the Chopper Man Fan Club!
By any chance, did you pick up a
drifting barrel while out at sea?
By all means, steer clear of my laboratory!
Oomph!
You'd like to know where
to submit the entrance fee?
--Just one moment please.
--There!
Amazing! We're making a fortune!
"Offering of Treasure to the Sea God"
Something's floating on the water.
"Treasure"
You're right! Maybe a treasure
ship accidentally dropped it!
Hey, how many of these do I
have to sign before I can stop?
Hey, Cindry-chan! Put the flan on plates!
It's a dog that doesn't have
a sense of smell?
You have to sign all of those today.
May I see your panties?
Cool, it opened!
It's gone!
Couldn't you at least do that for me?
In exchange, I'll buy you that model
plane if you get them all done today.
No way!
What should we do?
I wish plates would disappear
from the face of the earth!
It looks like we ran pretty
deep into the forest.
My, my! You're harsh!
Really?! I'll do my best!
What's that?
With that wandering around, we can't
wait somewhere that would stand out!
Guys, I wash the heck out of the
tablecloth for times just like this,
That made my bones rattle,
especially since I'm a skeleton!
--In a sense, the assistant Namifia
was the strongest of them all.
--There! There! There! There!...
We found one.
Shut up!
so feel free to eat away!
Certainly not!
I knew it! That was a trap.
Yes, hello?
Don't mind if we do!
--Go! Don't lose, Chopper Man!
--There! There! There!
How did a skeleton get a bump on his head?
They've been after your ship ever since then.
You can still use your spoons!
There! There!
Who're you?!
Say, do you poop?
I am called Hildon.
What do you mean by that?
It's yummy and sweet!
I was afraid you might be in trouble
when I saw the feral dog chasing you,
I've drawn you a bath.
Our ship has been here this whole time...
There are a boatload of questions
that should come before that!
You're a filthy lot, so go hop in.
so I snuck up from behind.
Well, next we're entering haunted waters!
Don't sneak up!
Hey, Pops. He doesn't mean anything to me,
Granny Kokoro warned us, but I wonder
what type of ghosts are there.
but did a weird skeleton
drop by before we arrived?
Indeed, I wonder what type of ghosts are there!
Yes, I poop.
Yeah! I'm really looking forward to this.
Don't take so long to answer
his question! And who cares?!
As night falls upon the
forest around these parts,
A-A skeleton?
Say, who're you?
Yeah. He's tall with an afro
and he's oddly cheerful.
For starters, why are you alive and
talking when you're nothing but bones?
On the next episode of One Piece!
it becomes so perilous it hardly
seems like it belongs of this world.
"Plunging into the Devil's Sea!
The Mysterious Skeleton Floating in the Fog"
What the heck are you?
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
So how'd an island get there?
What are you doing here?
What happened on this ship?
This is the ghost island
that wanders the seas...
Of course, the fact that he's a talking,
walking skeleton makes him odd enough.
What's the story behind this sea?!
...Thriller Bark!
Answer all of my questions!
Wait.
Do you know anything about him?
If you please, feel free to take
my carriage to the mansion.
Putting that aside...
...join my crew!
There's a mansion?
Indeed, there is. You're welcome
to visit Dr. Hogback's mansion.
Yeah, okay.
N-No, I don't...
What?!
What? What is it?
Really? Then forget it.
What's the big deal, Chopper?
Thriller Bark...
Hogback...
Hey!
Could it be him? Nah, it couldn't be...
Huh...?
Who's that?
Where the heck did that skeleton go?
H-Hey, shouldn't you slow down, Nami?
I never thought I'd get to meet
Dr. Hogback in my wildest dreams!
Nami, why do I have to
stand watch while you bathe?
Hello, everyone! Good day to you.
I'm so touched!
I am the dead and skeletonized Brook.
Don't look!
Who's this Hogback guy?
Don't underestimate my navigation technique!
I'm gonna let her rip!
Listen! We're leaving as soon as night falls.
Who the heck is this, Luffy?
He's saved as many people
as there are stars in the sky!
Whoa, how could you say that?!
There are zombies outside!
Isn't he funny? I added him to our crew.
N-Nami, I don't think there's
any water over there!
Listen to yourself! Do you seriously
think the mansion is safe?
Chopper! Hey, did you hear me?
No, you did not!
Really, don't get so worked up.
Let's have dinner.
I mean, he's a legend!
Of course there--what?!
Maybe I should get his autograph.
Huh? Y-You don't mean...
That's not for you to decide!
Answer my question already!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"One Unnatural Phenomenon After the Next!
Disembarking on Thriller Bark!"
"The Joy of Seeing People!
The Gentleman Skeleton's True Identity!"
"Nami's in a Major Pinch! The Zombie
Mansion and the Invisible Man!"
"The Man Called a Genius!
Hogback Makes His Appearance!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!