Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
He flies around using his Chopper cape
and fights for world peace!
The name of our hero is...
...Chopper Man!
"Go, Chopper Man!
Protect the TV Station on the Beach"
I don't want to hear about no Chopper Man!
He interferes with each and every
attempt I make to conquer the world!
"Evil Incarnate--Dr. Usodaba"
This is Dr. Usodaba, evil incarnate!
Leading the evil Usodaba Gang,
he's a fearsome scientist who
schemes to take over the world!
Your less-than-stellar
performance is also to blame.
Quit lazing about!
Huh?
"Naughty Monster--Sanjiropus"
This is the naughty monster, Sanjiropus.
He insists that he isn't naughty,
but he's always thinking about naughty stuff.
I'm not naughty.
Don't lie!
"Rice Ball Monster--Zorokiller"
This is the rice ball monster, Zorokiller!
He loves rice balls!
He can't stand people who
don't carry rice balls on them.
I can't stand you.
Guys, try to make yourselves
useful every now and then!
--Tea!
--Okay, coming up!
Why am I serving tea?!
"Matsuhachi"
Serve your boss tea!
I just realized something.
My organization is understaffed.
I want higher-level subordinates
who will treat me with respect...
Amateur Sing Off!
Anyone interested in trying
their luck, please enter!
This is it! I could use this!
"Giant Luffybomber"
Meanwhile, here at
Chopper Man's secret base...!
Have at me.
What's keeping you? Have at me! Come on!
"Pretty Assistant--Namifia"
This is Namifia, a pretty assistant!
Namifia efficiently manages
Chopper Man's missions.
Now bring it on!
Aw, jeez! Please, someone call!
We're in the red this month!
It's no use... Guess we'll have
to cut our grocery budget.
You're a polar bear?
I'm a panda.
Huh?
Hey, Namifia! I'm out of potachi!
Go buy me some more!
"Champion of Justice--Chopper Man"
This is Chopper Man, the champion of justice!
He is our hero,
protecting peace around the world!
Ow, ow...
That hurt! Why did you do that, Namifia?
This is no time to be laughing
at a TV show, Chopper Man.
Earth isn't in the least bit of peril today!
Isn't that a good thing?!
No, it's not! We're out of the job if
people don't call asking for your help!
All you talk about is business!
But isn't peace on Earth more important?
Starting tomorrow,
you're grounded from eating potachi.
I'm sorry.
--Koala--!
--Now for our next item on the news.
I wonder if there is any juicy bad news.
Like a monster appeared!
Or a robot is going berserk!
Hey! Give the remote back.
--Forget it.
--I wanna watch those comedians!
No!
All of you in front of your TV sets,
how are you doing?
Usodaba!
My organization, the Usodaba Gang,
has taken over this TV station!
Great! There's a crisis!
What's he doing on TV?
There is but one reason why
we came to this TV station!
I have a declaration for all
those currently tuned in!
In order to conquer the world,
my Usodaba Gang...
...is currently recruiting people
who would like to join our ranks!
What?
Join now, and no entry fees!
No annual conference fees!
And that's not all!
I will present the most
extraordinary of our applicants
with my organization's secret treasure.
It's fast! It's strong!
But it's a model, so you can't ride in it.
We'll present the Air Force C Mach 2!
I had to stand in line for a week to get this.
I really don't want to part with it,
but I'm woefully giving this away!
It's the Air Force C Mach 2
Limited Edition Version?!
Now, you in front of the TV!
Join the Usodaba Gang right this instant!
This is bad! Chopper Man, it's time for action!
Right!
You know what your mission is, right?
Of course I do!
I'm going to join the Usodaba Gang!
You don't know after all!
Air Force C Mach 2 Limited Edition Version!
I am extremely worried...
That's right!
--We've got the Giant Luffybomber!
--Bomber!
If I used that...!
"Giant Luffybomber"
It's gone!
Oh, yeah... I sold it just the other day...
What do you think, Robiflowern?
Wasn't I overflowing with
charisma when I was on TV?
Yeah, well, more or less...
"Flower Monster--Robiflowern"
This is the flower monster, Robiflowern.
She's an evil woman
who's been defeated by Chopper Man's
killer "Cute Spark" time after time.
Do you guys see me in a
somewhat better light now?
--Huh?
--Don't laze around during our strategy meeting!
--Tea!
--Okay, coming up!
I did it again!
"Matsuhachi"
Serve your boss tea!
It's okay. If this plan is a success,
high-level subordinates will flock to me...
Usodaba-sama, you're wonderful!
Usodaba-sama, you're a genius!
Usodaba-sama, have some tea!
But hijacking the airwaves was a good idea...
...for you, anyway, Usodaba-sama.
That was one word too many, Robiflowern.
My plans are always perfect!
If I get it across on TV that my
Usodaba Gang is strong and cool,
I bet people wanting to join
will come flocking in droves!
When that happens,
world domination will be as easy as pie!
And then those two will get the boot.
But what type of show will you put on?
I'm glad you asked!
First, we'll start with my enchanting voice.
"Super Star"
Sorry for the wait!
Just leave this to me!
I'll make all of the women in front
of the TV swoon with my charms.
Please watch, Robiflowern-chan!
S-Sure...
It's not my fault if you have to start sharing me.
I wonder if this is a good idea.
It's fine. Let him perform,
Robiflowern. He's the opening act.
Go wait in the Call Center for incoming
calls from people wanting to join!
Very well.
I see it! I can see it!
The Call Center will be abuzz
with interested viewers
from across the country!
"Cooking for 30 Hours with Sanjiropus"
Cooking for 30 Hours with Sanjiropus!
Huh?
Hello! I'm the cooking
monster of love, Sanjiropus!
Today I'd like to introduce
you to a super-easy recipe
that uses leftovers in your fridge.
Almost like magic, I'm able to
transform any old leftovers...
...into dishes like this within three minutes.
What?! From those ingredients?!
Now for the key point!
For the remaining 29 hours and 57 minutes,
I will gaze at no one but you...
Stare...
What are you doing?! The food got cold!
That's the problem?
It can't be helped.
We really do need my enchanting--
Something-or-Other Giri!
Outta the way!
I'll prove that I'm the strongest.
Now shut up and watch.
"Rice Ball Samurai"
What?
No!
Let's have fun and play, Missy!
Save me!
Screaming won't get ya anywhere.
Stop right there!
Who're you?!
Who cares? Get him!
Lost by a hair...
Ow, ow, ow...
P-P-Please spare me!
Bastard, do you have any rice balls?
What?!
Make sure you have some from now on!
Um, excuse me!
"Fin"
That didn't make sense!
Damn it! At this rate, my plan will be in ruins!
Hey! Please let me join.
Oh, someone finally came!
--Hiya!
--It's you!
Please let me join your gang. I want the model.
Air Force C Mach 2 Limited Edition Version!
In your dreams! I'd never give my
beloved collection to you, my enemy...
Wait a second.
Come on! Please!
Shall I throw him out?
No, wait.
Hey, you!
Do you want this?
I want it! I want it!
Then it's yours.
Really? Yay!
In exchange, fight me and lose in a
pro-wrestling program that I planned out!
That's my condition.
Huh? I have to lose?
I hate losing...
You're only pretending to lose.
Don't you want the Air Force C
Mach 2 Limited Edition Version?
I'm only pretending, right? It's a deal!
Great! Take him to the dressing room!
--Dabada!
--Yay! I'm going to be on TV!
Usodaba-sama?
If I defeat Chopper Man in
a fight in front of the cameras,
no one will question whether my
organization--no, I am the strongest!
Makes sense!
Just you watch!
The main event is about to begin.
Everyone around the country,
thank you for waiting!
Today's main event is
Usodaba versus Chopper Man!
We're broadcasting live from a special ring
in the globe-shaped observation deck.
"Wind"
I will be the ring announcer, Shorts.
We have invited Minoru Kazeno-san
to be our commentator.
It's a pleasure!
--Usodaba!
--We already have a pumped-up
Usodaba in the ring.
Everyone across the nation!
Before today's match,
I'd like to present you with
one of my wonderful songs.
Music--
Oh! At last, Chopper Man
has entered the stadium!
Yay! Namifia, are you watching?
Chopper Man!
With his cape glistening in the blue sky
All that cheering doesn't
make me happy or anything!
It's him! He's coming this way
Uh, guys...
"Wind"
As expected, the crowd is
going wild for Chopper Man!
Working to defend the...
Enjoy letting it get to your
head while you still can!
Today is the day I'm going to pulverize you.
Usodaba Lock!
Ow, ow. That hurts!
You're taking this too far.
Keep quiet and let me beat you!
Don't you want that?
"That"?
The Air Force C Mach 2 Limited Edition Version!
Well, Usodaba got the first strike, Kazeno-san.
"Wind"
Chopper Man isn't exhibiting his usual power.
I wonder what's wrong...
It really is a one-sided fight.
Hiya!
Ow, ow, ow!
Take this!
Thrum!
No one could have expected
the match to turn out like this!
"Wind"
Usodaba is overwhelmingly powerful.
He's good.
Dang, Chopper Man's weak!
What a letdown.
In comparison, Usodaba is putting
up a surprisingly good fight.
Usodaba! Usodaba!
Usodaba!
Usodaba! Usodaba!...
It looks like Usodaba's popularity
is suddenly skyrocketing!
Uh, testing, testing.
Hello? Is this the reporter, Sanjiropus-san?
The Call Center is getting
flooded with people saying,
"Call Center"
"I want to join the Usodaba Gang."
At last!
At last, my time has come!
Hey, can we stop now? I want
to take the model and go home.
Hang in there for just a bit longer!
I'm about to wind this up.
I'm seriously going to crush you.
Oh, no! Usodaba has climbed onto the top rope!
Chopper Man is in serious trouble!
"Wind"
Will tonight be the birth of a new, dark hero?
This will finish him off.
But first, I'd like to sing a song!
My Air Force C Mach 2 Limited Edition Version!
Is it all right?
Phew! It's still fixable.
Thank goodness...!
Thank goodness!
Gimme.
--No way.
--Eh?
Wasn't that the deal?
That deal? I never intended
to go through with that!
Dumb deer!
Wh-What...?
Right now, I'm more popular than you!
It's all going according to plan!
But I worked so hard...
Go on, everyone!
Let's hear you call for Usodaba!
Not yet!
--Dabada!
--This match isn't over yet!
Hmph! You're being a poor loser.
Killer move!
Cute Spark.
Ah, this is...
Cute Spark!
--Cute, cute, cute!
--Allow me to explain!
--Cute... Spark!
--Chopper Man can melt the heart
--Cute, cute, cute! Cute! Cute?
--of anyone who sees his killer "Cute Spark."
Cute!
Vroom, vroom! Vroom, vroom, vroom! Cute?
He's totally aware of how cute he is!
I won't lose! I won't lose to you!
Chopper Man! Chopper Man!
--Chopper Man! Chopper Man!...
--Wh-What's this?
D'aw, Chopper Man is so adorable!
Go away, Usodaba!
"Wind"
The stadium has flipped 180 degrees.
Chopper Man is the crowd favorite!
Let's share some of the
feedback we've received.
"Call Center"
Uh... "Chopper Man, good luck!
Don't let Usodabo beat you."
I'm Usodaba!
"Don't lose to Long-nose."
At least say my name!
At any rate, everyone's really excited over here!
Whose side are you on?!
--Damn it!
--Chopper Man, let me tag in!
Become the wind.
Hey! Why are you tagging in?!
I won't forgive you for bullying Chopper Man!
Uh oh! Minoru Kazeno
suddenly entered the fight!
I'll just have to pull out my ultimate weapon!
Click.
What's that?
Hey, look outside!
Cyber!
"Giant Robot--Frangashan"
This is the giant robot, Frangashan!
This is Dr. Usodaba's latest secret weapon.
Its true strength is unknown!
Go, Frangashan! Destroy everything!
Okay!
Leave this to me!
Flick.
See? I really am the strongest!
Gotcha!
Gah! That's--!
"Giant Robot--Luffybomber"
This is the giant robot, Luffybomber!
It's a giant robot that's 50 meters tall.
Personality: It does its own thing!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I came to save you. It came at a high price.
I expect you to pay me back!
Namifia!
Damn it! Frangashan, do something!
Bring it on!
Here I go!
Hey, here he comes!
Yeah!
Go, Frangashan! Huh?
S-Stupid! Stop that!
What are you going to do?
Upsy daisy.
It lifted up the globe!
Hey! There are a bunch of people in here!
Wow, everyone was quick to flee.
Here I go!
You're pretty good...
Sweet!
I'm falling!
Huh?
Stupid! Let go! No, don't let go!
Take this! Feel my wrath
for not giving me that model!
Chopper Violence!
Cheers for a good day at work!
Oomph.
A word, please!
Man! That applause doesn't
make me happy or anything.
In the end, this just boosted his popularity.
Damn it! I'll get you for this!
This one really put us in the red, but...
He certainly is beloved!
That's it!
Hello. This is the office for
the Chopper Man Fan Club!
Oomph!
You'd like to know where
to submit the entrance fee?
--Just one moment please.
--There!
Amazing! We're making a fortune!
Hey, how many of these do I
have to sign before I can stop?
You have to sign all of those today.
In exchange, I'll buy you that model
plane if you get them all done today.
Really?! I'll do my best!
--In a sense, the assistant Namifia
was the strongest of them all.
--There! There! There! There!...
Yes, hello?
--Go! Don't lose, Chopper Man!
--There! There! There!
There! There!
Well, next we're entering haunted waters!
Granny Kokoro warned us, but I wonder
what type of ghosts are there.
Indeed, I wonder what type of ghosts are there!
Yeah! I'm really looking forward to this.
Say, who're you?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Plunging into the Devil's Sea!
The Mysterious Skeleton Floating in the Fog"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!