Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Hi! Hello, everyone! Good day to you.
Don't be stupid! And what the heck is he?!
My, my! They're harsh!
Goodness, aren't you a lovely lady?
May I please see your panties?
Stop that, Harassment Skeleton!
Hey, Luffy! What's up with this guy?
Isn't he funny? I had him join our crew.
No, you didn't! I won't allow it!
Now, don't get so worked up.
Come on inside! Let's have dinner.
That's not for you to decide!
You're funny!
The Revive-Revive Fruit?
The Revive-Revive Fruit lets you...
...come back to life.
In other words, I'm a revived human.
It guarantees the mysterious
power of a second shot at life.
A revived human!
N-Now that I take a closer look,
you don't have a shadow!
You're right! What are you, really?
I have spent far too many
years drifting on these seas
to tell my story in one sitting.
No!
Hey! What is it? What's wrong?
G... G-G-G...
Ghost!
Gah! Something's there!
Evil be gone! Evil be gone!
I'm scared! It's a ghost!
Awesome!
It's running away!
Wh-What's causing that tremor?!
I-It couldn't be!
"Evil Be Gone"
What's going on?
So how'd an island get there?
This is the ghost island
that wanders the seas...
...Thriller Bark!
Thriller Bark...
"One Unnatural Phenomenon After the Next!
Disembarking on Thriller Bark!"
Wait a sec! This isn't
showing up on the Log Pose.
That's hardly surprising. This island
came clear from the West Blue.
The West Blue?!
Yeah...
Hey, where are you going?!
Goodness, this is truly my lucky day!
Not only have I run into people, but my
heartfelt dream has also come true!
He's so agile!
Indeed! I became light on my feet
after I died and turned to bones!
Please break through the gate towering
over you and escape with all due haste!
No matter what, do not
drop anchor by the shore!
It made me so very happy to meet you today!
I will never forget that scrumptious meal!
Well, take care! May we have the
fortune to meet on other waters!
Hey! Wait, Brook!
Isn't he a power holder?
Why on earth did he jump into the water?!
He's running on the water!
Wow! Awesome!
A-At any rate, Luffy, let's take his advice.
I have no idea what's going on, but this
island is clearly nothing but trouble!
Huh? Did you say something?
He's dying to go!
What's the deal with this Ghost Island?
Hey, where'd that ghost go?
Is it still on board?
No, it flew back toward the island.
That's probably where it resides.
Hey, about that large tremor
we felt a minute ago...
If that mouth-like gate
caused it when it shut,
I think that it essentially devoured us.
So it ate us?
It's hard to see through the fog,
but the fence extending from the gate
appears to encompass the island.
In other words, our ship is currently trapped
inside a fence that surrounds the island.
I get it! So that's why the skeleton
told us to escape ASAP!
Does that mean someone is making
this island "wander" the seas?
What's the point?
If the island is moving,
we're still in the middle of the ocean.
We can't drop the anchor here...
Whoa, there! Why do I get the
feeling you wanna stay here?!
We've gotta leave now!
We're gonna get cursed!
Listen, guys. I've come down with
Fear-of-unknown-islands-osis!
Same! I've caught the same bug.
Okay! Let's take her up to the shore!
Do you have Set-for-Adventure-osis?!
Think that over! Luffy, open up your eyes!
See that creepy building?!
It's a real haunted mansion!
You're taking malicious
spirits way too lightly.
What're you talking about?
I'm being super careful!
I'm gonna catch that ghost
and keep it as a pet.
You're totally underestimating it!
And above all else, we have to
bring back our dear crewmate.
Sanji, my pirate lunch!
Crewmate...? Hey, I'm
against you on that one!
I'd be too scared to sleep at night
if we had a skeleton for a crewmate!
I got your lunchbox.
Luffy! Franky! You'd better
be sure to protect Robin-chan!
There's nothin' like exploring
an uncharted island, is there?
You've gotta be kidding!
You're going with them, Robin?
I simply love the thrill.
All right! So, guys, we're gonna
take a small boat to disembark,
but I've still got a special
surprise I haven't shown you yet!
It's Soldier Dock System, Channel 2!
Two?
You heard me!
This system uses a total of five channels.
0 comes up twice.
1...
2...
3...
4!
Each dock has its own unique function.
Just a sec!
You've already revealed the paddle
wheel in 0 and the contents in 1 and 3.
But as I recall, you said
2 and 4 were still empty.
'Cause I was savin' them
for a special occasion!
Anyone steering clear of the island
should give it a quick spin!
Soldier Dock System, Channel 2!
Set out!
What is it? What's gonna pop out?
With its steam engine, this paddle
steamer that sits four is the Mini-Merry!
It's Merry!
Merry came back as a boat!
It's small, but now we can ride Merry again!
Sweet! I'm getting the hang of it.
H-Hey! Th-That looks bad!
We'll be fine! You can count on me.
I had no idea he was hiding
such a wonderful present...
Thank you, Franky!
I'll be more than happy to go shopping
for supplies in a boat like that!
Yahoo! Gimme a turn! I want a turn now!
You took "considerate" to a new level.
Hey! Hold your horses, Straw Hat.
We'll get to ride it in just a minute.
Let them have a bit of fun!
Is this everything, Franky?
Yeah. Including the 1 and 3
I've already shown you, this is it!
Channel 0: Support Paddles!
Channel 1: The one-man waver,
White Hobby Horse!
Channel 3: The three-man recon
submarine, Shark Submerge III.
And Channel 2: The four-man
errand boat, Mini-Merry!
At the moment, this is everything
the Soldier Dock System has to offer.
Consider them soldiers meant to
assist the Thousand Sunny's voyage.
I really love the way you think!
Franky, you rock! You rock! You rock!
--You rock! You rock! You rock! You rock!
--Yeah! I'm the ultimate man again this week!
Super!
Nami-san?!
Nami-san! What is it?!
What happened?!
What're they up to?
I can't see squat through this fog!
But her scream came from the island.
Guys, lemme ride the Mini-Merry already!
Jerk! You should be worried about Nami-san!
And you should be worried about
the other two on top of her!
I wonder if that scream means
a ghost killed them with a curse.
Stop that! Don't jinx them!
What was that?!
No one has touched the anchor!
It's too new for the
gears to be coming loose.
At any rate, raise it back up!
It's going to throw the ship off balance!
What? Did someone touch that?
No, no one went near there.
H-Huh?
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Luffy! What the hell are you doing?!
This isn't the time for games!
No, vit ishn't me! I'm vot doin' vis!
Look out, Straw Hat!
Hey, punk! What was that about?!
Hey, I'm sorry. My sword sprang out...
That's strange...
Looks like we're not the
only ones on the deck.
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
So we've got company, huh?
Was it a ghost after all?
Or was it some sorta psychic?
I could feel someone touching me.
I think I heard the sound of a
beast growling just a second ago.
A beast?
Anyway, I'm worried about
Nami-san and the others.
I'll let you deal with the ship!
What're you gonna do?
I'm gonna swim to the island
and save those three.
Wha--?!
What?! That was lame!
Wow! Sanji's floating back up.
How's he doing that?
Whoa!
Gah!
You said, "Gah!"
Shut up! Why don't you give it a try?!
So it doesn't want us to leave the ship, huh?
I don't see what it's after.
If it wanted to kill us, we're wide open.
What's wrong, Robin-chan?
Something has caught me!
How dare you have your way with her?!
It really does sound like a beast!
Wh-What's going on?!
Look!
Waves are doin' that! Unnatural waves
are forming inside the fence!
They're carrying the ship!
Robin-chan, where is he?
We're in the clear. He seems to have left.
Hey, Gah! Raise the anchor!
We can't sail like this.
Who're you calling "Gah"?!
Usopp! Chopper! Answer me!
Crap! The current's pulling us
away from Nami-san.
Hey, Franky! Use one of the ship's
secret weapons to get us outta this!
Sure thing! I've got a Peek-a-Boo Vinyl Pool.
Sounds fun! Wait...
Are you a moron?!
Ouch, ow, ow, ow...
No wonder that hurt...
We fell all the way from up there, guys.
Where are we?
We're already on Ghost Island.
Ghost?!
Hey! Cut that out!
It makes me even more scared!
But how in the world did we get down here?
We got too excited over
Mini-Merry and ran ashore.
I got a bit overconfident, let it rip
and rammed into the wall.
That's when all three of us got sent flying.
Within seconds, we were at
the bottom of this trench.
I'm 100% at fault, but you'll
forgive me 'cause I'm cute!
I'm seriously gonna whack you!
"I'm sorry."
For one thing, isn't it weird
how all this fog appeared
when we entered the island?
Maybe it's a trap to deal with adversaries?
We should consider ourselves lucky
this wasn't lined with bamboo spears.
You're right! We're okay because
we landed on these skeletons!
Uh-huh.
I said cut that out!
But we've barely set foot on the island.
Luffy and the others will
come for us if we sit tight.
But I'm scared of being below sea level.
Fair enough. It's dangerous and hard to find.
At the very least, why don't we wait
for help on the shore at ground level?
So, like, which way takes us up?
What is that? A dog?
That's no dog.
Th-Then what is it?
H-Huh? C-Could that be C-Cer...
Cerberus?!
It's Cerberus!
Wh-What's Cerberus?!
I-I-I'm p-pretty sure it's
the watchdog of Hell!
Does that really exist?!
Sure does! It's right behind us!
Does that mean we're in Hell?!
No, I don't wanna know!
Just run! It'll eat us if we stop!
What's wrong, Chopper?
Chopper, what are you looking at?
"Yip"?
Hey, now that I take a closer look,
isn't one of them a fox?
Look! That hurt its feelings.
Must be a sore spot.
Yeah.
We ticked it off!
Now it's saying, "Pow!"
We must have hit a real sore spot!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Look! There is a staircase!
That will take us to the ground level!
Thank goodness!
Gah, it's persistent!
We hit a really sore spot!
Smoke Star!
It's a dog that doesn't have
a sense of smell?
It's gone!
What should we do?
It looks like we ran pretty
deep into the forest.
With that wandering around, we can't
wait somewhere that would stand out!
Certainly not!
Who're you?!
I am called Hildon.
I was afraid you might be in trouble
when I saw the feral dog chasing you,
so I snuck up from behind.
Don't sneak up!
As night falls upon the
forest around these parts,
it becomes so perilous it hardly
seems like it belongs of this world.
If you please, feel free to take
my carriage to the mansion.
There's a mansion?
Indeed, there is. You're welcome
to visit Dr. Hogback's mansion.
What?!
What? What is it?
What's the big deal, Chopper?
Hogback...
Huh...?
Who's that?
I never thought I'd get to meet
Dr. Hogback in my wildest dreams!
I'm so touched!
Who's this Hogback guy?
He's saved as many people
as there are stars in the sky!
Chopper! Hey, did you hear me?
I mean, he's a legend!
Maybe I should get his autograph.
Answer my question already!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Man Called a Genius!
Hogback Makes His Appearance!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!