Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
My eyes follow the beautiful ladies.
People are terrified when they hear "zombie."
But what if I rephrase it
to "resurrecting the dead"?
But I'm a mummy, so I don't have eyes!
I saw what you just did!
You're terribly strong, aren't you?
That's Hogback's laugh.
Hasn't that been all mankind's eternal dream?
Anyway, we should try to stay put!
May I see your panties?
What is this room?
Everyone has a special someone or two
they'd like to see return from the dead.
Luffy and the others are sure
to come save us. You hear me?
No way!
There is a man I would like you to defeat.
His laboratory!
I'm with him! I don't wanna go outside again!
This exchange...!
If I get my shadow back,
I'll do anything I can to thank you!
He repeated him word for word...
But toying with human mortality is
unorthodox medicine that disrespects God!
I'm not going back in the forest or graveyard!
Your shadow?
It's almost done!
So what? Are you another
person who lost his shadow?
Wha--?
That's why I slipped away
from the public eye--
Why, you--!
What a glorious mario!
There is nowhere to run!
You're just like Brook.
so I could continue my
research on this island in secret!
So who the heck stole it?
Someone's here?!
Hey, Nami? Is there a problem?
S-So that's the story!
Behold, Cindry-chan!
The work of a genius... is truly art!
Who is on this island?
They're in the way...
The man's name is Moria.
He is truly terrifying.
But I'm sure tons of people
around the world would be thrilled
He's clearly trying to
turn that into a zombie.
if your research is a success!
Moria?
Huh?
By any chance...
I'll be rooting for you, Dr. Hogback!
Caught ya!
Hogback revived all of
the zombies on the island.
Please let me go!
Are you referring to Gecko Moria?
You're rather open-minded!
Thank you, Dr. Chopper.
Yeah, that's him. That's the Moria I meant.
Guys, why don't you join my pirate--
That's the only possible explanation!
Cut that out!
What?!
Cindry-san, would you be so kind
as to open yonder passage?
"Evil Be Gone"
Sh-Shucks, Doctor! I'm not happy because
you thanked me or anything, you jerk!
Hey, Absalom!
Robin, do you know him?
I was searching for my bride, Hogback.
Gecko Moria is one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea.
Also, I would like a midnight snack.
Good day to you!
Wh-What gives? I thought
he was going to attack us.
If you're curious about
what's inside, you should go in.
May I have your autograph?
That woman tickles my fancy.
Why, certainly!
That scared me. What's he up to?
I'm going to make her mine!
"To Dr. Chopper..."
To Dr. Chopper...
"Yo ho ho"?!
I-It doesn't matter!
C'mon, let's make a break for it!
B-Brook...?!
Could you show me your lab later?
"Evil Be Gone"
The door is wide open!
--You're right!
--Y-Yeah!
By all means, steer clear of my laboratory!
Infidels!
A severely injured old man?
He found us!
You're trembling. How adorable!
He's obviously a zombie!
Three-Pace Hum... Notch Slash!
I made it perfectly clear to
keep your noses out of my lab!
How dare you make fun of zombies?!
You're so cute...
"Nami's in a Major Pinch! The Zombie
Mansion and the Invisible Man!"
Don't underestimate us!
I-I-I didn't see a thing!
I won't let you leave, children!
N-Neither did I!
They must have done
something during the fray.
Are zombies supposed to be this full of life?
Uh-huh! I didn't see anything either.
Chopper! Nami! Head for the door!
Honest?
We're leaving the mansion!
Teach them just how
dangerous zombies can be!
We've lost a valuable man.
C-Cross my heart! I swear I didn't
see a zombie in the works!
Cool it!
What, you wanna fight?
Yeah, but... He's right. Sanji'll be okay.
What's keeping you, Nami?!
No!
We can teach you a thing or two
about how dangerous we are!
Man, Nami! I wish you could
take a bath by yourself!
Don't say that!
D-Don't tell me...
Go! Go!
It won't open! We're trapped in here!
Seriously! I wanted to talk
with Dr. Hogback some more.
Well, it's all good.
Go and learn just how
terrifying our master truly is!
What?!
It doesn't matter what secrets
you uncover. It's too late anyway.
Shut your traps and come with me!
Now you've made me mad!
600 Million Berry Jackpot!
Our real boss is one of the Seven
Warlords of the Sea, Gecko Mori--
Yes, ma'am!
--I won't let you escape!
--Now come on back!
We round up the unsuspecting guests
who wander onto this island.
"His Name is Moria! The Great
Shadow-Seizing Pirate's Trap!"
Ah! I can't say his name!
It's too terrifying!
Then the night raid begins!
No!
Merely saying his name
sends chills down my spine!
Now then, my Soldier Zombie Corps!
So... what were you guys doing here?
Your missing crewmates
won't come back unscathed...
The General Zombies will
take those pirates down!
Well... We are zombies,
so we were kinda buried...
You'll lose one pal after the next...!
"The Zombie's Secret!
Hogback's Nightmarish Laboratory!"
I wanna take a peek...
And we were kinda rotting...
You will regret coming here!
What?! You do?! For real?!
Are you ready, zombies?
Right, right. I was rotting.
Before the Seven Warlord's Gecko--
Yeah, so was I.
Yeah!
I'm not interested in a naked human woman,
no, before my master's true power,
Duck!
Are you trying to be funny?
but I wish I could peek
inside Dr. Hogback's lab...
This is the land of the
deceased, Thriller Bark!
all of you will taste fear!
No, no! Not by any means!
We're sorry! Honest!
I don't wanna see it! I'm too scared!
You sure love to ramble on and on!
That right? Then I have a question for you.
That was close!
Gosh darn it, Nami! Why do we have
to stand guard while you clean up?
May you have unpleasant nightmares!
Let's leave this room for now!
Try another room!
Then pass this message on to that jerk Moria!
Did a man with a long nose,
a woman with orange hair,
We won't let you escape!
Don't bathe if you're scared!
No!
and a raccoon dog that resembles
a reindeer pass through here?
I'm amazed you don't care
that zombies touched you!
"If anything happens to my crew...
"Evil Be Gone"
Huh?! Uh, y-yeah... Yes, yes, and yes.
Well, shall we go?
Nasty!
No! No, no! Let go!
We're just gonna get dirty again. Right?
...I'll send you and this
entire island flying!"
It's a haunted mansion!
Maybe I saw them, maybe I didn't...
Right!
We're leaving as soon as night falls.
What?!
But our lips are sealed!
Wait!
"Feast of the Zombie Song! The Night
Raid's Bell is the Sound of Darkness!"
Whoa, there! Are you crazy, moron?!
We aren't allowed to share information
on that topic with outsiders.
Awaken, General Zombies!
We're in a fireplace!
No!
Here.
Arise, ancient warriors!
It's the rule.
He said we could spend the night!
Right, right!
We're doomed! There's nowhere left to run!
Yeah?
Can't you see what'll happen if we
leave in the middle of the night?!
It's the rule! It's the rule!
It's the rule! It's the rule!...
No!!
Anyway, we should try to stay put!
Luffy and the others are sure
to come save us. You hear me?
So you absolutely refuse to talk, huh?
I'm with him! I don't wanna go outside again!
All three of them passed through!
I'm not going back in
the forest or graveyard!
They squealed like pigs!
It's the same whether
we're inside or outside.
Where is this?
That was fast...
Hey, they vanished!
They disappeared in the fireplace!
Have you paid close
attention to this mansion?
They're my crewmates.
You didn't go after them, did you?
Crap! The entrance to the secret
passage must have opened!
Now go, my courageous General Zombies!
Y-You don't mean...
Now they'll make their way
to Hogback-sama's laboratory!
Huh?!
Th-They're your crewmates?
Yep! If my gut feeling was right,
After them!
I-I didn't attack them! Right?
the halls and rooms were
filled with people's auras.
"A Bunch of Animals?
Perona's Wonder Garden!"
Y-Yeah. S-Same goes for me.
This mansion is already teeming with zombies.
I didn't attack them!
We didn't attack them! We didn't
attack them! We didn't attack them!
What was that crap about
zombie research, Hogback?!
I don't care what part of
the mansion they enter!
Wh-Where were they?!
Instead of investigating them,
Hunt them down and haul them in!
And if they're inside, that makes Hogback
the most suspicious person here.
It's no use! They're pushing
against the door on the other side.
you're the one calling the
dead back from the grave!
They're nothing before you, General Zombies!
You'd better tell me the truth.
H-Hey, Nami! Don't blurt that out!
He's lying to us...
H-Hey, Usopp! Put some muscle into it!
He attacked them!
There is no way he could live in this
zombie-filled mansion or on this island
Hey! Don't drag your feet, Captain John.
What?! Hey, you don't sell friends out!
if he wasn't connected to
those zombies in some way!
You're crushing the name
you made notorious in life!
You nibbled on him a bit, remember?
No!
You're free to suspect anything you like now,
Yeah, yeah. I'm goin'.
We all attacked them together.
but what makes you think that?
Wh-What do you think, Chopper?
If her speculation is right...
No!!
Sheesh! He's such a scallywag.
Stupid! Don't tell him that!
Ab-sama, marry me!
She's wrong! Dr. Hogback would
never do anything like that!
I found a newspaper article
about that woman's death!
Lola! Sow, hurry off to battle!
I'm your commanding officer!
Victoria Cindry, you died
a good ten years ago!
At any rate, let's play ignorant.
Once it's night, we'll make our break.
Then marry me.
No matter where they go, this mansion is
stuffed with fellow "Surprise Zombies."
Why should I?!
Fiends! Did you go inside that room?!
You're a rather clever woman.
Answer me!
Huh? What was that?
W-Wait, Lola! What are you doing?
Usopp? Chopper? Did you say something?
Not only did you check out my lab,
but also that room...
Sow! Are you ignoring a direct order
from Absalom of the Grave?!
Huh? We didn't say anything.
I'll listen if you marry me!
Cindry-chan! Samurai Ryuma!
Ah, I just farted!
Don't be stupid! I'm human!
I'm going to marry a human woman!
Usopp, that stinks!
Send them to the World of Shadows forthwith!
Th-This is nuts!
Gyah!
I'm Uso-P.U.!
Nami and the other two
apparently raced for that mansion.
No!
The hallways are out!
So are places with paintings!
"Evil Be Gone"
Come on, Lola! Just think for a second.
W-Wait a second!
I'm glad they're okay!
Why, you--!
But they didn't know anything about Brook.
Send them to the World of Shadows,
never to bask in the light again!
You're not only a warthog,
you're also a zombie!
We need to find a room somewhere!
Do we really need him? Forget that weirdo!
The night raid has already begun.
You're dead and rotting!
That room!
Yeah, really.
"Evil Be Gone"
What's going on?!
I don't see anyone!
Cut that out!
Yikes, what a terrifying stunt!
Did you see...
A beast...?
That's a marriage registration form!
You're weaker than the woman
on the ship--more my type.
...all you care to of the laboratory?
Stop trying to make us an
officially married couple!
Aw, I just love your wild mouth!
But man, those were some spineless zombies!
Someone's here?!
Usopp! Cho--
Absalom, give me your finger! I love you!
Yeah! That didn't even count as a warm-up!
More paintings!
Woman, be my blushing bride!
"Dragon"
A-Are those photos?
Screw that!
But don't let your guard down.
I'll never spend the rest of
my life with a dead animal!
Hey, Nami? Is there a problem?
What a relief!
We have no idea what could be
lurking around the next corner.
Did Usopp's fart stink up the bathroom?
These aren't zombies, are they?
Bride Fu! Vow Kiss!
Aren't these... of that one lady?
My, my...
What's this? Starting to
chicken out, Swordswuss?
Smooch! Smooch! Smooth! Smooch!
Upon closer inspection,
I see that you are a truly elegant lady.
Cindry-chan, the lady who hates plates...
Smooch! Smooch!
Shut up, you stupid cook!
Thank you very much!
Wife Fu! Vow Hug!
You're beautiful!
You just thanked her!
Don't lump me together with you!
Huh?! N-No, hardly!
I love you to death!
What was that, Disoriented Moss Head?!
They're in the way...
My eyes follow the beautiful ladies.
Stupid! Help me...!
B-But you died a long time ago!
Wanna fight, Curly Eyebrow?!
What is with this room?
But I'm a mummy, so I don't have eyes!
P-Please hold up!
Take that!
Even if I'm a rotting zombie,
my love for you will never die!
Usopp! Chopper! Help me!
May I see your panties?
"Evil Be Gone"
Someone's in here!
Marry me!
Huh?!
No way!
But like I said, I--
I saw what you just did!
You're terribly strong, aren't you?
Now that I really look at her, the servant
Cindry-chan is quite pretty, isn't she?
This exchange...!
This finger is mine!
My eyes follow the beautiful ladies.
She's right! I'm picking up an odor!
So do you think this is her room?
"Evil Be Gone"
Huh? Uh, sorry!
But I'm a skeleton, so I don't have eyes!
I don't mean your fart!
It smells like a person.
Could you please hear me out?
I'm not about to let you
escape, bastard! I love you!
But would she hang a bunch of
photos of herself in her own room?
Hurry! He's escaping out the window!
May I see your panties?
A severely injured old man?
Why did the window suddenly open?
We've told you before, that's a zombie!
What the heck is escaping?!
Bride Fu! Vow of My Love Attack!
No way!
Her face and body were covered in stitches.
Special Attack! Exploding Star!
He repeated him word for word...
No, I'm a severely injured old man.
Give it up!
That's confusing! Just pass
yourself off as a zombie!
Hiya!
I don't see any on her in these photos, do you?
It couldn't be...
So what did you wanna discuss?
Has that bastard... done it again...?
He's on a completely different level
from the other zombies you've seen!
Wait, Lola! Listen carefully, sow!
There is a man I would like you to defeat.
Wh-What should I do? Fire another one?
I have already... picked out the
woman who is soon to be my bride!
But I doubt they're of someone else,
so are they old photos?
No, he's gone now.
With his special body,
he is a General Zombie.
I'm sure you could take him down!
He has created countless victims,
I can't smell him anymore.
She seems strong-willed,
but also has a sense of grace.
This man hails from Wano
Kingdom in the New World!
She's a frail, human woman!
I wonder if we'll make it out of here...
all of whom could be saved
if you defeated him!
Nami, are you okay?!
It'll fall through like always.
If I get my shadow back,
I'll do anything I can to thank you!
No one knows if it's true or not,
but it's said this legendary samurai
Look at this, fool! She is one of the
pirates who disembarked on this island.
He overheard our entire conversation...
Your shadow?
Listen to this!
So what? Are you another
person who lost his shadow?
She is beautiful! This one
is worthy to be my bride!
cut down a dragon soaring through the sky!
"Victoria Cindry."
H-Hey, Nami, what was that all about?
I'm really confused here...
I won't let that happen! That woman...
Your shadow...?
Apparently she was a famous stage actress.
It's true!
...is going down!
Gramps, you don't have a shadow!
He was here the whole time.
Crap! Crap!!
Look! All of these are articles on her.
Don't kill her! Hold up, Lola!
Stay back!
You're just like Brook.
He was an invisible man.
So who the heck stole it?
Huh? A stage actress?
It's no use. It doesn't matter
if we kick or whack it.
There is nowhere to run!
But didn't the doc say she used
to be a servant somewhere?
Who is on this island?
This massive spider web is here to stay.
She got the boot after she broke some plates...
That old zombie wannabe said that
Gecko Moria's had his eyes on us
I don't like this.
Going by this, that doesn't seem very likely...
ever since we were invited to this island.
There is no point in staying here.
We should make looking for Nami-san
our top priority. Let's head on out!
Perhaps the curly cook's disappearance
has something to do with Moria.
She was originally born into nobility.
Hey, Zoro! Come on, Zoro!
And she was popular since she was little...
That stupid cook! He had it coming.
Not only did that skeleton's ghost ship
and Sunny get caught in the web,
What's wrong?
But I never expected to run into
one of the Seven Warlords here.
M-Moria...
She fell from the stage...
Cindry-san, would you be so kind
as to open yonder passage?
Why would a pirate want
to steal people's shadows?
it also snared the Mini-Merry that
Usopp and the others were riding.
Ten years ago, there was
an accident and she died!
The man's name is Moria.
He is truly terrifying.
I would love to know!
Also, I would like a midnight snack.
I-I don't know anything!
Moria?
And it almost feels contrived
how the island entrance
Wh-What gives? I thought
he was going to attack us.
I promised that geezer I'd kick Moria's butt,
By any chance...
Wh-Wh-What're you talking about?!
She was clearly alive!
is right in front of us,
like it's inviting us in.
but that'll have to go on hold.
Are you referring to Gecko Moria?
That scared me. What's he up to?
She wasn't dead!
Yeah, that's him. That's the Moria I meant.
Sheesh! I can practically see
the ghosts inside waving us in.
I-It doesn't matter!
C'mon, let's make a break for it!
But if that obituary is legitimate,
Your missing friends are
already screwed anyway!
Robin, do you know him?
What are you griping about, Zoro?
C'mon, you're joining us!
The door is wide open!
that means she died and came back to life!
--You're right!
--Y-Yeah!
I know his name well.
In fact, you're in no position
to be worrying about others!
That man's bounty used to
surpass even yours, Luffy.
Do you want to fall for
that stupidly obvious trap
Hurry!
Not anymore...
This island is filled with real zombies!
and have those idiots
treat you like a moron?!
Quit oinking and lead the way,
you stupid piggy!
It used to? So that means...
Why not? There's nothing
to do if we stay here!
We saw deceased that truly were resurrected!
Right... Gecko Moria
Oink!
Splendid!
Now let's go!
is one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
I'll share my lunch with you!
When a person has been slashed by a master,
the master can casually walk three paces
Sheesh! Well, I guess it might be fun
to see what those idiots look like.
while humming before the person notices.
One of the Seven Warlords?!
What's wrong?
No!
Are you sure, Robin?
Nothing. It must be my imagination.
Yes... Gecko Moria is a man
shrouded in mystery.
Three-Pace Hum... Notch Slash!
But what is that man doing
in a place like this?
All right! Let's move out!
You took forever, Moss Head!
I'm afraid I don't know. But there
are more than a few victims
Shut it!
Talk about messed up...
Hey, Kumacy! Kumacy!
This place gets creepier by the second!
left to wander this forest
after he stole their shadows.
Why does it go right into a staircase down?!
I wish I didn't know the truth!
The Risky Brothers are
carrying the casket over.
There are other people here?
This is the entrance, so there's
no point thinking about it.
Yeah. You would be wise to remember
Get it from them and take the
casket to Master's dance hall.
What is it?!
that Moria has had his eye on you
ever since he invited you here.
Oh, the ground is covered in bones!
Got that?
Did you get that or not?!
Look at those, Usopp!
He invited us...?
--Ye...
--Don't answer! You're so not cute!
Aren't they treasure chests?
"Offering of Treasure to the Sea God"
You were quick to adapt!
I'll be directing the Treasure
Retrieval Party on the ship,
Oh, Usopp! Open it!
Hmm. Cerberus, huh?
Open up that chest!
So that's the deal?
so come get me if anything happens.
Do you understand?
He would have been safer in Hell.
Uh, okay...
My, how cute!
Hey, isn't he lookin' for a fight?
Sorry! This isn't where we store the treasure!
Those who stayed must creep around
the forest in fear of the zombies.
That's right! You're cute
as long as you're quiet!
Excuse me! I'm coming in!
He doesn't know his place.
Think he's yummy?
It's a jack-in-the-box!
Take care...
Give 'em more time!
Punk! You just whispered something!
Those who took to the sea must
spend their lives in fear of the sun.
Huh? The door's locked.
Either way, it hardly feels
like we're even alive anymore.
Ah! It opened right up!
You've come out!
Woof!
At the very least, I wish that
just once--once is all I ask for--
You call that "opening right up"?
Woof, woof! Woof! Woof, woof, woof!
Zombie Paintings!
Woof, woof, woof, woof! Woof, woof, woof!
Delivery! Delivery for Master!
Hey, cool it...
Gecko Moria! Come on out already!
I could walk under the light of the sun!
Chirp, chirp, chirp!
"This isn't where we store the treasure."
Look. He's ready to fight.
I'm sure that's what the
Jack-in-the-Box Zombie said!
Oh, no! Now we've really done it!
Actually, he's found his
courage after getting cornered.
What do you think they use this room for?
Oh, no! We tripped! There goes
our delivery to Master...!
No!
Doesn't look like anyone's home.
So it would seem.
Then I'll--
Nah, wait.
Hey! Anyone around?
The casket popped open!
Oh, Bodyguard!
Let's try to tame him.
Huh? Where is this?
Gecko Moria!
I see some people have
gotten lost in the mansion.
What?!
He's up! Crap! Hurry and whack him!
Whack him to death!
Stupid! He may be a dog, but he's
basically the boss of all dogs.
Oh, it's you!
This is such a huge mansion...
Shouldn't there be at least one servant?
We can't kill him.
Not a problem! I shall catch them for you.
Then beat him within an inch of his life!
But a dog is still a dog.
Yeah, good dog. Good dog.
Jerks!
Why does it look like there
was a skirmish in here?
Paw!
And here you just warned him!
I hope nothing happened to Nami-san...
That's your story? Dude, that sounds killer!
Usopp! Nami!
Hey, hang in there! Wake up!
All right! I'll help ya out!
There, there. You're a good dog.
Don't worry about a thing, stupid!
You idiot, I'm not crying!
There, there. Good dog. That's right.
Now let go nice and slow.
Ow, ow, ow...
You've got some guts, coming when
you know our master's name!
Huh? But didn't... that samurai attack us...?
You're way too easy to read.
Slowly now. You're such a good doggie.
Don't be so quick to take on
someone else's problems.
Darn mutt!
Huh? A piggy is growing out of the wall?
You heard him!
Down!
Did he hit us with the
blunt side of his sword?
There's still more in store for you!
So like I said, stop jumping at the
chance to recruit these weirdoes!
No, not quite...
Hey, geezer! Only ladies can
use tears to win people over!
It looks like it must have rained a bit.
Show our guests a warm welcome!
But don't those injuries look horrible?
The ground is wet. Where is this?
As it is, we've already got
a raccoon dog and a robot!
You can't make my heart throb!
I'm amazed he's even alive.
I'm not sure, but those
squirrels were carrying us.
That's just so...
Hey, I'm not a robot! I'm a cyborg, moron!
Before that, I think that
fox thrown in the mix
But, hey, I was searching
for the shadow thief.
makes it one messed-up animal...
It's obvious you aren't human anymore!
That's a freaking casket!
At the core, I'm human!
Crap! All three of them are up now.
Oh, jeez! Are these supposed to be zombies?
We found such a fun animal
as soon as we arrived.
At the core, you're a pervert!
Not good! Let's call for backup.
If he's after us, we're gonna
have to kick his butt anyway.
Eh? Oh, well, as long as you understand...
I can't wait to see what
this island has in store!
I think you can find just about any
creature imaginable on this island.
Hey, that wasn't a compliment!
So wouldn't we wind up
helping you on the side?
You look blue, Cerberus-san.
I wonder what will be next!
This looks like it's in
the back of the mansion.
Get it?
Hey, don't show the defeated any sympathy.
I'm happy to hear you say that!
This is a blast!
Hogback's lab was on that top floor,
It'll hurt his pride.
Where the hell...
Even if we're on the side,
it still gives us hope!
Nami-san!
...did you hide Nami-san?!
so they carried us a pretty good distance.
We're counting on you, Mister!
Hey! Where are you, Nami-san?!
Best of luck!
H-Hey, look behind you!
Kick Moria's stinky butt!
It's improper for a lady to
open her mouth gaping wide.
There is a sturdier building
on the opposite side.
What the heck?! The other victims
were listening in on us?!
--Nami-san!
--So the outside of the trench
leads to a forest, huh?
And here you're so pretty.
Huh? Really?
Didn't we run into a treeman
and a unicorn earlier?
This place is like a maze!
Yeah! Excuse us for not making
your heart throb, Curly Eyebrow!
But not when you leave the painting.
What's that?
"Evil Be Gone"
Hey, Nami-san!
Twist!
What about them?
Shut up! Leave me alone!
Do you remember seeing
a huge building behind the mansion?
All of the bizarre animals in this
forest seem to share these traits:
Now for you.
Nami-san!
Usopp! Chopper!
Bandages, stitches and numbers
tattooed onto their bodies.
Between the weird layout and this fog,
my sense of distance is fried!
You snapped my spearhead!
What are you made out of? Iron?!
I figured out what this
area is supposed to be.
Numbers? Yeah, he is numbered, isn't he?
What is it? What's the deal with this place?
Who's there?!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop it!
What the heck are you guys?!
There is also the possibility
that we're walking in circles.
Does that mean someone is overseeing them?
This is the breezeway that connects
the mansion to that building.
Weren't those weaklings
supposed to be your crewmates?
Yes, that's what I would assume.
Yes!
Nami-san!
A breezeway? It's way too big for that!
"Evil Be Gone"
Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive!
Maybe we should have left
Moss Head behind after all...
Two-Sword Style... Nigiri!
They've practically stuffed a forest in here.
--Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive!
--Huh? I hear something.
Are you pinning the blame on me?! Well?!
Well, it'd make for one weird forest.
"Evil Be Gone"
Nigiri? Like sushi? Sounds yummy!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive!...
But for them to have carried us
here while we were out cold,
Flash!
What are you doing here?!
It was nasty!
"Evil Be Gone"
What was with that "yo ho ho"?!
Was that Brook just now?
isn't it safe to assume they
were taking us to that building?
But he wasn't a skeleton!
He had skin and muscle.
Huh?
This island really is fun!
There's a ghost!
If they succeeded, they might
have turned us into zombies.
A-An elderly tree and a
unicorn are sharing a drink!
Darn it! You're one fast bastard!
Plus he was wearing sandals
and carrying a katana.
How dare they blow me off?!
I'm glad I came to! Let's run for it!
You're right! He was wearing
a completely different outfit.
Yeah! Let's blow this popsicle stand.
What's that mean?
--Save me!
--Wait!
Hold your horses.
"Evil Be Gone"
This isn't adding up.
Wait! Wait, dammit!
Infidels!
We've been terrified right and left,
screamed our heads off and run like mad...
He found us!
--Gum-Gum Butterfly Net!
--Strong Right!
Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive!...
--All for free?
--What are you going on about?!
What did you see?
I'm getting a strong reading on
my Something's Fishy Sensor!
There's a ghost!
I made it perfectly clear to
keep your noses out of my lab!
Caught ya!
Please let me go!
Don't say anything! Let's just
make a break for it, Nami!
I-I-I didn't see a thing!
Right! You heard him!
--Back in that room,
--Let's run for it!
Oh, dearie me!
N-Neither did I!
--I'm pretty sure that zombie said...
--Let's get out of here, Nami!
They're multiplying as they dance! Awesome!
We coulda been friends
if you didn't get in our way!
Hey, Luffy! What are you
going to do with that?
Uh-huh! I didn't see anything either.
He wouldn't...
Sorry! This isn't where
we store the treasure!
Guys, why don't you join my pirate--
Honest?
Gum-Gum...
C-Cross my heart! I swear I didn't
see a zombie in the works!
That's one creepy cheer.
Cut that out!
Don't get any crazy ideas!
We're running for it!
...Bazooka!
I'll catch them and keep them as pets!
Don't say that!
Let's get out of here, Nami!
You're so stupid!
I know, sheesh! I'm scared, too.
B-Bear Rug!
Well, it's all good.
But your eyes look funny!
They're spirits through and through!
It doesn't matter what secrets
you uncover. It's too late anyway.
Then which way would you like to run?
Forward? Backwards?
All righty!
Fresh Fire!
That was a close call.
That's a toughie...
In a couple of minutes...
Hey, Absalom! You're here, aren't you?
I don't wanna go back to the mansion
and run into that samurai again.
...the "night raid" will begin!
What was all that ruckus about?
But if we push forward, I bet there
are even scarier people lying in wait.
Were you in the bath again, you pervert?
Shoot! It didn't work.
There! That's the last of them.
"Night raid"?
No, we're not done yet.
I was searching for my bride, Hogback.
That was an epic fail.
I'm such a loser this week.
We round up the unsuspecting guests
who wander onto this island.
There's still one up there.
Eh? What are those
adorable animals? Penguins?
Nothing I do works out.
I'm not sure I can live like this...
Then the night raid begins!
That woman tickles my fancy.
Number 1!
I'm going to make her mine!
2!
I can hear the whole world booing me!
3!
Ew...
Are you really that bummed out?!
Just so you know, she is a wanted woman.
Hello! We're the...
You can't have her.
Okay! I've got the punk!
...Penguin Zombie Duo!
What did you say?!
Oops, I goofed up.
Trio! We're a trio! I'm a new member.
There are six of them this time.
If I could be reborn, I'd like to be a clam.
Like I care about what's
going on with your members!
One of them is worth over 100 million.
And the guys standing behind you are...
The captain is worth 300 million.
I suck! I wish there was a
hole for me to crawl into!
300 million?!
--Behind us?
--...our friends, the Wild Zombies!
What the heck are you two doing?!
Don't take those numbers so lightly, Perona.
Welcome to Perona-sama's Wonder Garden!
If the government put 300 million
on his head, he's no ordinary pirate.
If you understand that much,
dedicate all of your energy to
capturing your prey, Absalom.
Do you think that perhaps touching
those ghosts weakened their will?
There is a disturbing number
of super freaky critters!
That's absurd!
We're going to be busy tonight.
Those two are pathetic! They're at
the mercy of those weird ghosts
because they aren't calm
and collected most of the time.
Perfect! Now carry them away.
They just had to rebury the zombies
right before the night raid!
I'm sorry I was ever born.
That's enough!
Sheesh...
There's no such thing as an invisible man!
It looks like you were right, Robin-chan.
But I'm sure he was back there!
Go! Beat the living daylights out of them!
Not if he doesn't exist!
It was a hallucination or illusion!
Not only do they lack physical bodies,
You scared yourself into
thinking you saw the impossible!
but they also break your
will if you touch them.
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
You couldn't feel something
even if it was itchy, hot, or painful!
Chopper!
What are you talking about, Usopp?!
Nami! Usopp! I'll hold them back.
They would make for formidable foes.
Didn't you see how somebody
was pinning me down?!
No matter where we go,
weird zombies are bound to show up!
You're all dead!
Definitely.
Uh, er, well...
Right...
And these guys are animals!
I bet they're faster runners than us!
What a fascinating island!
Nope, I didn't see that!
Yes, you did!
Gah, you're leading the witness!
Now get up, Soldier Zombies!
You're trying to make me admit that I saw
you naked so you can charge me for it!
What?! How greedy do you think I am?!
The punk! He may look like
a human, but he's an animal.
Gah! Those ghosts are gonna
pay the next time they pop up!
Although I'm still charging.
You are?!
Right! I'm a reindeer.
Anyway, I refuse to believe anything I
see on this island! Including you naked!
No matter how many times you're defeated,
you can rise and attack again!
I don't want them as pets!
So you're a Zoan-type power holder?
That is what makes zombies truly terrifying!
We're fellow animals here!
They must have a weakness! I'll wipe them out!
You just imagined the invisible man!
If you quietly do as we ask,
we won't get rough with you.
The ghosts are just weird birds!
Yeah!
The zombies are just a unique tribe:
The Hollow Earth People!
We aren't "fellow animals"!
What a pain...
You put on quite the show!
Shuddup!
Really? Then we won't hold back.
They're what?
Hey, get your act together!
Sure, we met a skeleton that had died
and come back because of a Devil Fruit!
"Man, I'm sorry! Sorry I was ever born!"
Give me a break, zombies!
Nami, you should go hide!
We did, but that was truly
the exception to the rule!
I dare you to say who I am!
Why, you...!
O-Okay!
Beat it! Ouch!
Uh... Umm... Those three are
sound asleep in their bedrooms.
You're our leader!
Two people can't possess the same power!
You're our leader, Absalom!
And there is no stinkin' way
the dead can come back to life!
Leader! Leader! Leader! Leader!
Ain't it great? They're safe and sound!
Wh-What? You wanna fight?
Right, Chopper?
Like hell they are!
Dumb zebra-like kangaroo!
Or are you a kangaroo-like zebra...?
It's the honest truth!
Don't you agree with me?
It looks like we can put the numbered
patchwork creatures into one category,
Leader! Leader! Leader! Leader!...
All you have to do is check and see!
Isn't it natural to assume they
were something along those lines?
Not that it matters!
Just go up those stairs and down the hall!
but those ghosts were a
completely different life form.
Well, from a medical perspective,
all of this has been impossible.
Didn't one of them appear on our ship?
Hey, wait a second here.
I-I should warn you about something!
I think your logic makes more sense.
The way they occasionally show up,
it's like they're keeping tabs on us.
I'm the invincible reigning champion
But Dr. Hogback has abandoned his
life of glory to delve into his research.
The curly cook is gone.
of 50 World Pirate Boxing
Tournaments straight!
The question is: Who is controlling them?
Huh? He was here a second ago.
Just maybe, miracles of that scale
have been happening on this island!
Where did Sanji wander off to?
Behold! I don't have a single opening!
You can attack from any direction you want!
Hey, a-are you serious...?
Eat my Elusive Right!
Aren't you putting a bit
too much faith in that man?
Hey, don't laugh! They'll hear you.
Dr. Hogback is a truly
wonderful man! I respect him!
Peeping Tom!
Wow, it's a big cemetery!
Y-You're pretty good, aren't ya?
They must have done
something during the fray.
You're the one being rude!
It's got character!
Erotic Leader! Erosalom! Erosalom! Eros!
Don't accuse the doctor of conspiring with
zombies if you can't back up your claim!
Hey, let's eat here!
We've lost a valuable man.
Stupid! It'll ruin the food if we eat here!
Cool it!
Even if I can't, everything is
pointing in that direction!
--Pervert! Pervert! Pervert!...
--Shut up!
Yeah, but... He's right. Sanji'll be okay.
Your game of hide-and-seek is over!
No, we're eating here!
Nothing has ever once ruined a meal!
Don't underestimate a dog's sense of smell.
The doctor is the Zombie King!
But time may be of the essence
Dogs shouldn't talk!
Knock it off, you two!
You're freaking me out!
Only you think that!
for the other three in this zombie mansion.
Besides, we're in a hurry.
No!
Anyway, let me talk to the doctor.
Is that acceptable, Nami?
Don't get cocky just because
you're a little strong, punks!
Eek, here he comes!
Oh, crap!
What?
I hope Luffy and the guys save us soon...
Deep inside, you're terrified after
one of your friends went missing!
Serves ya right!
At any rate, we'll have to go by
our intuition from here on out...
Sweet! That was a smart play!
It's true that I'm only
basing this on my intuition,
Here!
Hey, losers! You're really scared witless!
but everything about this place is creepy...
I doubt these zombies will tell us
the truth if we threaten them.
W-W-Welcome back, Perona-sama... in bulk!
I'm not goin' back down! Are you stupid?!
Shoot!
I'm sorry!
Then let's take this pig as our tour guide.
Gah! Don't talk, Kumacy!
No!
Why must you have such a deep voice
when you're so cute?! It's annoying!
What?!
A severely injured old man?
He's obviously a zombie!
How dare you make fun of zombies?!
Usopp? Chopper?
I-I'm sorry.
Don't underestimate us!
Go! Go!
What is it, Nami?
H-Hey, you!
Isn't that the room we were in earlier?
Go and learn just how
terrifying our master truly is!
Yeah... Whoa! Why is it pitch black?!
If you aren't cute, you have
no right to serve me!
What?!
Our real boss is one of the Seven
Warlords of the Sea, Gecko Mori--
Are zombies supposed to be this full of life?
C-Cindry-chan...?
Teach them just how
dangerous zombies can be!
Ah! I can't say his name!
It's too terrifying!
Doctor, where did you go?
Merely saying his name
sends chills down my spine!
I enjoyed the bath!
Hurry! Hurry!
Your missing crewmates
won't come back unscathed...
It's starting! It's starting!
It's time for the night raid!
You'll lose one pal after the next...!
It's almost midnight!
Ex-Excuse me!
What, you wanna fight?
Master!
Moria-sama!
We can teach you a thing or two
about how dangerous we are!
--Over here!
--Whoa, whoa, whoa!
You will regret coming here!
Time to wake up!
Yay!
Before the Seven Warlord's Gecko--
--Yay!
--Yay...!
no, before my master's true power,
H-Hey! I'm falling!
Nin, do it!
all of you will taste fear!
D-Doctor!
Okay, sure thing!
Gosh darn, that was close!
You sure love to ramble on and on!
Hey! I dare you to come over here if you can!
Then pass this message on to that jerk Moria!
Those two have already
turned in for the night.
Master!
Neener-neener, boo-boo!
You can kiss my shiny little hiney!
I was having a nightmare!
Hildon?!
Eat fart!
How dreadfully wonderful, Master!
600 Million Berry Jackpot!
You jerk! How dare you
abandon us in that graveyard?!
"If anything happens to my crew...
It's been roughly four days
since our last night raid.
My humblest apologies.
...I'll send you and this
entire island flying!"
I left to attend some errands with the horses.
The moment I took my eyes off them--
You've been asleep that
entire time, Moria-sama.
You're a bag of lies!
Everyone on this island
is in cahoots with each other, right?!
As such, we have prepared
four days' worth of food for you.
Anyway, it won't kill
Sanji to fend for himself.
P-Please don't make such vile accusations!
Stay back! Stay back!
We have some impressive prey this time!
C'mon, let's go!
Fwoosh!
After toppling Enies Lobby,
they've become a hot topic!
Waah! It's persistent!
I've got it!
They're Straw Hat Luffy and his gang!
Come right this way.
I'll show you to your rooms.
Hey! You're seriously taking me with you?!
I'm sure you will find
use for them, Moria-sama.
Take this!
You're at it again, trying to
"show us" somewhere!
Say something!
Whatcha think? Did you see how the
great Usopp-sama is a master sniper?
I wonder if that's the real
entrance to the underworld.
Thanks for the offer, but we must be off now!
Rain?
That's Hogback's laugh.
What?! Wait a sec! Let me talk
to the doctor a bit more!
It's coming down pretty heavy.
All right! Let's run for the mansion.
Wait! Wait!
She has spurned you, Hildon.
Dear Master,
Just a sec!
What is this room?
it looks like some fearsome
people have entered the mansion.
Wh-Who's there?! I don't see anyone...
I can see somethin' huge behind the mansion.
His laboratory!
Keep out of this! I'll be sure
to take them to their rooms.
They surprised all of the Surprise Zombies.
It's like some kinda massive mark.
Damn it! As things stand,
there are just too many of them.
A mark?
It's almost done!
Why don't we drop this charade?
The fog has cleared up a bit, hasn't it?
They are already starting to grow suspicious.
What is that? A flag?
What a glorious mario!
No! Isn't that a sail?
Before we slip up and give
them a chance to escape...
Behold, Cindry-chan!
The work of a genius... is truly art!
Wh-Why...
Usopp! Nami!
A sail?!
Chopper!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
...is the picture...
It sure is!
Hey, Nami! What were you...
...t-t-ta...?!
I hope you fail right before completion.
You're still following us?!
How could you say that, Cindry-chan?!
Usopp, fire!
What did you mean?
Fire?!
Just as that man said, it's a sail.
We need fire! These are also zombies.
I swear, I'm taken aback each time
you fling such cruel words at me!
Hey, save me! They're about to bite me!
But it's so large that you
can't see the whole thing.
I made dinner.
Nami!
You're trembling. How adorable!
Oh, is that right? What are we having tonight?
Surround the mansion
Crap! Let go of me! Stay back!
Thriller Bark is carrying an entire village,
Spaghetti soup.
Zombies are weak against...
Let's Fiesta Night!
You're so cute...
Special Attack! Flame Star!
making it the largest
pirate ship in the world!
We won't let a single pirate...
The soup is vanishing right
before my eyes, Cindry-chan!
I won't let you leave, children!
It's a pirate ship that
hauls around a village?!
--Fire!
--That's rottin' bad!
I wish plates would cease to exist.
No!
...get away
Everybody, Zombie Night!
(Fuuwa! Fuuwa!)
Yeah, I get that!
It's the largest in the world...
That worked better than I could have hoped!
Ch-Chopper!
But if that's how you feel,
why must you choose such bold dishes?
Round and round and turn and die
(Fuuwa! Fuuwa!)
Awesome!
A zombie popped outta the picture!
Take this, you darn bear rug!
Save me!
Makes sense. "Bark" is definitely a word
used to define a type of sailing ship.
Everybody, Zombie Night!
(Fuuwa! Fuuwa!)
Aren't there plenty of other
things you could make instead?
Chopper!
--Cindry-chan is also in there...
--Let's see! There's fried soba noodles!
Round and round and turn and die
(Fuuwa! Fuuwa!)
Crap! It's a candle!
Or even fried udon noodles!
That's right! You get him, Nami!
Zombie Night!
But I never thought I'd see a
ship carry an entire village...
See? There's also fried pork cutlet!
It's hot! It's rottin' hot!
Help me out!
Everybody, Zombie Night!
(Fuuwa! Fuuwa!)
I wonder if she's really the lady
who died in that accident...
You can do it, Nami!
Fire! It's terrifying!
Round and round and turn and die
(Fuuwa! Fuuwa!)
You can see how the main mast
connects to the back of the mansion.
Put it out!
Crap! He climbed up the chandelier!
That is where you will find Gecko Moria.
Everybody, Zombie Night!
(Fuuwa! Fuuwa!)
Someone knock him back down!
Round and round and turn and die
(Fuuwa! Fuuwa!)
Eat this!
Darn you!
I can't believe it...
Everybody, Zombie Night!
(Fuuwa! Fuuwa!)
I'm Oinkchuck-sama, the head hog
of the zombies in this room!
That's right! I had that ace up my sleeve!
I'm sick of these soupy dishes!
Round and round and turn and die
(Fuuwa! Fuuwa!)
What about your spaghetti soup?
Special Attack! Flame Star!
You'll be dead before you get so
much as a single foot out the door!
I-I-I'll eat it...!
Zombie Night!
And how about one more?
I'll eat that! I'd like some!
Th-The wall mount... talked!
Now then, my Soldier Zombie Corps!
What's on top of the table?
The General Zombies will
take those pirates down!
Usopp!
It's probably a human corpse.
N-Nami, did you see that?!
The wall mount was talking!
Chopper, look out! Behind you!
Based on his complexion, he's no longer alive.
The wall mount--!
He's numbered, just like the
zombies in the graveyard!
Usopp! Chopper!
No matter how many times they defeat you,
Ow, ow, ow...
You're in danger as well.
He said that it's almost done.
Who was the jerk that
stabbed me in the back?!
stand back up and renew your attack!
Drive them into a corner with
your terrifying immortality!
That settles it!
He's clearly trying to turn that into a zombie.
It's just like Nami said!
This mansion is teeming with zombies!
Hogback revived all of
the zombies on the island.
That's the only possible explanation!
Usopp!
Don't hurt her!
But medicine can only save
people before they die.
Punk!
Bastard! Why'd you attack an ally?
He can make the corpse as strong as he wants,
It's time! All of our prey have
entered the mansion grounds!
Take this, you darn bear rug!
but it won't bring the person back to life!
That woman is the enemy!
You're supposed to kick her butt!
We'll never figure this one out!
Crap! It's a candle!
You may fight to your heart's
content for this one night!
If we spy on him, we'll learn the
secret to how he revives people!
It's hot! It's rottin' hot!
I don't know who this lady is,
Awaken, General Zombies!
Fire! It's terrifying!
but even if it means
defying the master's orders
Put it out!
Crap! He climbed up the chandelier!
Someone knock him back down!
or sacrificing myself, I won't kick a woman!
Well, the clock has struck midnight.
I know what you're weak against!
If you have a problem with that, you can
take it up with me, stinky zombies!
It's time for us to go all out.
Arise, ancient warriors!
I've got enough for everyone! Take this!
Don't count on escaping us, foolish pirates!
Eat this!
Darn you!
And you! And you!
Are you ready, zombies?
Yeah!
Good day to you!
Chopper! Nami! Head for the door!
If you're curious about
what's inside, you should go in.
Huh?
We're leaving the mansion!
--Yeah!
--I'm leaving! I've had it!
Hey! What happened?!
"Yo ho ho"?!
This is the land of the
deceased, Thriller Bark!
B-Brook...?!
The pirates...
Hurry and open the door! I don't
wanna spend another minute here!
Hey, Oinker! Did you pull another
fast one on us? Out with it!
The Straw Hats
are a small crew of eight.
Haven't I been telling
you that I'm in the dark?
What's keeping you, Nami?!
Wipe them out and present
them to our master!
May you have unpleasant nightmares!
No!
Don't laugh! It gives the
impression that you're lying.
D-Don't tell me...
It won't open! We're trapped in here!
How strange. I wonder if he was
strangled so he couldn't utter a sound.
What?!
Now you've made me mad!
Why were your circuits
wired to be so ominous?!
I won't let you escape!
This is so weird! Now Zoro's missing.
Now come on back!
Now go, my courageous General Zombies!
Well, shall we go?
No!
It's a haunted mansion!
Hey, Chopper! According to the newspaper,
aren't a bunch of zoos popping up?
Chopper, I don't really wanna know,
but what's on that operating table...?
What's goin' on?! People keep
vanishin' one after the next!
I never expected that man to be here!
It has finally begun, Absalom!
Hey, Robin! Do you know him?
I've always been against
throwing animals in cages!
First one person vanishes,
then a second, a third and a fourth...!
Do you really want to know?
Right! It's time for the night raid!
This man's bounty, Luffy,
used to surpass yours!
You had to ask? So it's what I think it is?
Does that mean we're next?
This is a reindeer talking here!
The night raid!
I'm against cages, too!
Caging animals is barbaric! But still...
And then no one was left.
Go on a rampage, General Zombies!
Are you ready? I'm going to tell you now.
It used to...?
G-G-Give me a sec! I'm not ready for this!
No one was left.
So he must be the man pulling the strings...
I'll make an exception today...
The stuff you say is freakin' ominous!
--That's--
--I'm scared!
A-A night raid!
Please put the animal zombies in cages!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Vanishing Straw Hat Crew!
A Mysterious Swordsman Appears!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"His Name Is Moria! The Great
Shadow-Seizing Pirate's Trap!"
"Feast of the Zombie Song! The Night
Raid's Bell is the Sound of Darkness!"
"The Zombie's Secret!
Hogback's Nightmarish Laboratory!"
"A Bunch of Animals?
Perona's Wonder Garden!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!