Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
My eyes follow the beautiful ladies.
But I'm a mummy, so I don't have eyes!
May I see your panties?
No way!
This exchange...!
He repeated him word for word...
There is nowhere to run!
Cindry-san, would you be so kind
as to open yonder passage?
Also, I would like a midnight snack.
Wh-What gives? I thought
he was going to attack us.
That scared me. What's he up to?
I-It doesn't matter!
C'mon, let's make a break for it!
The door is wide open!
--You're right!
--Y-Yeah!
Three-Pace Hum... Notch Slash!
They must have done
something during the fray.
We've lost a valuable man.
Cool it!
Yeah, but... He's right. Sanji'll be okay.
Go! Go!
Go and learn just how
terrifying our master truly is!
Our real boss is one of the Seven
Warlords of the Sea, Gecko Mori--
Ah! I can't say his name!
It's too terrifying!
Merely saying his name
sends chills down my spine!
Your missing crewmates
won't come back unscathed...
You'll lose one pal after the next...!
You will regret coming here!
Before the Seven Warlord's Gecko--
no, before my master's true power,
all of you will taste fear!
You sure love to ramble on and on!
Then pass this message on to that jerk Moria!
"If anything happens to my crew...
...I'll send you and this
entire island flying!"
Awaken, General Zombies!
Arise, ancient warriors!
Now go, my courageous General Zombies!
"A Bunch of Animals?
Perona's Wonder Garden!"
I don't care what part of
the mansion they enter!
Hunt them down and haul them in!
They're nothing before you, General Zombies!
Hey! Don't drag your feet, Captain John.
You're crushing the name
you made notorious in life!
Yeah, yeah. I'm goin'.
Sheesh! He's such a scallywag.
Ab-sama, marry me!
Lola! Sow, hurry off to battle!
I'm your commanding officer!
Then marry me.
Why should I?!
W-Wait, Lola! What are you doing?
Sow! Are you ignoring a direct order
from Absalom of the Grave?!
I'll listen if you marry me!
Don't be stupid! I'm human!
I'm going to marry a human woman!
Come on, Lola! Just think for a second.
You're not only a warthog,
you're also a zombie!
You're dead and rotting!
Cut that out!
Yikes, what a terrifying stunt!
That's a marriage registration form!
Stop trying to make us an
officially married couple!
Aw, I just love your wild mouth!
Absalom, give me your finger! I love you!
Screw that!
I'll never spend the rest of
my life with a dead animal!
Bride Fu! Vow Kiss!
Smooch! Smooch! Smooth! Smooch!
Smooch! Smooch!
Wife Fu! Vow Hug!
I love you to death!
B-But you died a long time ago!
Even if I'm a rotting zombie,
my love for you will never die!
Marry me!
But like I said, I--
This finger is mine!
I'm not about to let you
escape, bastard! I love you!
Bride Fu! Vow of My Love Attack!
Give it up!
Hiya!
Wait, Lola! Listen carefully, sow!
I have already... picked out the
woman who is soon to be my bride!
She seems strong-willed,
but also has a sense of grace.
She's a frail, human woman!
It'll fall through like always.
Look at this, fool! She is one of the
pirates who disembarked on this island.
She is beautiful! This one
is worthy to be my bride!
I won't let that happen! That woman...
...is going down!
Don't kill her! Hold up, Lola!
That old zombie wannabe said that
Gecko Moria's had his eyes on us
ever since we were invited to this island.
Perhaps the curly cook's disappearance
has something to do with Moria.
That stupid cook! He had it coming.
But I never expected to run into
one of the Seven Warlords here.
Why would a pirate want
to steal people's shadows?
I would love to know!
I-I don't know anything!
I promised that geezer I'd kick Moria's butt,
but that'll have to go on hold.
Your missing friends are
already screwed anyway!
In fact, you're in no position
to be worrying about others!
Not anymore...
Quit oinking and lead the way,
you stupid piggy!
Oink!
What's wrong?
Nothing. It must be my imagination.
Hey, Kumacy! Kumacy!
The Risky Brothers are
carrying the casket over.
Get it from them and take the
casket to Master's dance hall.
Got that?
Did you get that or not?!
--Ye...
--Don't answer! You're so not cute!
I'll be directing the Treasure
Retrieval Party on the ship,
so come get me if anything happens.
Do you understand?
That's right! You're cute
as long as you're quiet!
Take care...
Punk! You just whispered something!
Delivery! Delivery for Master!
Chirp, chirp, chirp!
Oh, no! Now we've really done it!
Oh, no! We tripped! There goes
our delivery to Master...!
The casket popped open!
Huh? Where is this?
He's up! Crap! Hurry and whack him!
Whack him to death!
We can't kill him.
Then beat him within an inch of his life!
Jerks!
Usopp! Nami!
Hey, hang in there! Wake up!
Ow, ow, ow...
Huh? But didn't... that samurai attack us...?
Did he hit us with the
blunt side of his sword?
It looks like it must have rained a bit.
The ground is wet. Where is this?
I'm not sure, but those
squirrels were carrying us.
That's a freaking casket!
Crap! All three of them are up now.
Not good! Let's call for backup.
This looks like it's in
the back of the mansion.
Hogback's lab was on that top floor,
so they carried us a pretty good distance.
H-Hey, look behind you!
There is a sturdier building
on the opposite side.
What's that?
"Evil Be Gone"
Do you remember seeing
a huge building behind the mansion?
Usopp! Chopper!
I figured out what this
area is supposed to be.
What is it? What's the deal with this place?
This is the breezeway that connects
the mansion to that building.
A breezeway? It's way too big for that!
"Evil Be Gone"
They've practically stuffed a forest in here.
Well, it'd make for one weird forest.
But for them to have carried us
here while we were out cold,
isn't it safe to assume they
were taking us to that building?
If they succeeded, they might
have turned us into zombies.
I'm glad I came to! Let's run for it!
Yeah! Let's blow this popsicle stand.
Hold your horses.
"Evil Be Gone"
This isn't adding up.
We've been terrified right and left,
screamed our heads off and run like mad...
--All for free?
--What are you going on about?!
I'm getting a strong reading on
my Something's Fishy Sensor!
Don't say anything! Let's just
make a break for it, Nami!
Right! You heard him!
--Back in that room,
--Let's run for it!
--I'm pretty sure that zombie said...
--Let's get out of here, Nami!
Sorry! This isn't where
we store the treasure!
Don't get any crazy ideas!
We're running for it!
Let's get out of here, Nami!
You're so stupid!
I know, sheesh! I'm scared, too.
But your eyes look funny!
Then which way would you like to run?
Forward? Backwards?
That's a toughie...
I don't wanna go back to the mansion
and run into that samurai again.
But if we push forward, I bet there
are even scarier people lying in wait.
Eh? What are those
adorable animals? Penguins?
Number 1!
2!
3!
Ew...
Hello! We're the...
...Penguin Zombie Duo!
Oops, I goofed up.
Trio! We're a trio! I'm a new member.
Like I care about what's
going on with your members!
And the guys standing behind you are...
--Behind us?
--...our friends, the Wild Zombies!
Welcome to Perona-sama's Wonder Garden!
There is a disturbing number
of super freaky critters!
Go! Beat the living daylights out of them!
Chopper!
Nami! Usopp! I'll hold them back.
No matter where we go,
weird zombies are bound to show up!
And these guys are animals!
I bet they're faster runners than us!
The punk! He may look like
a human, but he's an animal.
Right! I'm a reindeer.
So you're a Zoan-type power holder?
We're fellow animals here!
If you quietly do as we ask,
we won't get rough with you.
We aren't "fellow animals"!
Really? Then we won't hold back.
Nami, you should go hide!
O-Okay!
Beat it! Ouch!
Wh-What? You wanna fight?
Dumb zebra-like kangaroo!
Or are you a kangaroo-like zebra...?
Not that it matters!
I-I should warn you about something!
I'm the invincible reigning champion
of 50 World Pirate Boxing
Tournaments straight!
Behold! I don't have a single opening!
You can attack from any direction you want!
Eat my Elusive Right!
Y-You're pretty good, aren't ya?
Your game of hide-and-seek is over!
Don't underestimate a dog's sense of smell.
Dogs shouldn't talk!
No!
Eek, here he comes!
Oh, crap!
Sweet! That was a smart play!
Shoot!
I'm sorry!
No!
--Over here!
--Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Yay!
--Yay!
--Yay...!
H-Hey! I'm falling!
Gosh darn, that was close!
Hey! I dare you to come over here if you can!
Neener-neener, boo-boo!
You can kiss my shiny little hiney!
Eat fart!
Stay back! Stay back!
Fwoosh!
Waah! It's persistent!
I've got it!
Take this!
Whatcha think? Did you see how the
great Usopp-sama is a master sniper?
Wait! Wait!
Damn it! As things stand,
there are just too many of them.
Usopp! Nami!
Chopper!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Hey, Nami! What were you...
Usopp, fire!
Fire?!
We need fire! These are also zombies.
Hey, save me! They're about to bite me!
Nami!
Crap! Let go of me! Stay back!
Zombies are weak against...
Special Attack! Flame Star!
--Fire!
--That's rottin' bad!
That worked better than I could have hoped!
Take this, you darn bear rug!
Crap! It's a candle!
It's hot! It's rottin' hot!
Fire! It's terrifying!
Put it out!
Crap! He climbed up the chandelier!
Someone knock him back down!
Eat this!
Darn you!
That's right! I had that ace up my sleeve!
Special Attack! Flame Star!
And how about one more?
Usopp!
Chopper, look out! Behind you!
Usopp! Chopper!
You're in danger as well.
Don't hurt her!
Bastard! Why'd you attack an ally?
That woman is the enemy!
You're supposed to kick her butt!
I don't know who this lady is,
but even if it means
defying the master's orders
or sacrificing myself, I won't kick a woman!
If you have a problem with that, you can
take it up with me, stinky zombies!
Huh?
Hey! What happened?!
Hey, Oinker! Did you pull another
fast one on us? Out with it!
Haven't I been telling
you that I'm in the dark?
Don't laugh! It gives the
impression that you're lying.
How strange. I wonder if he was
strangled so he couldn't utter a sound.
Why were your circuits
wired to be so ominous?!
This is so weird! Now Zoro's missing.
What's goin' on?! People keep
vanishin' one after the next!
First one person vanishes,
then a second, a third and a fourth...!
Does that mean we're next?
And then no one was left.
No one was left.
The stuff you say is freakin' ominous!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Vanishing Straw Hat Crew!
A Mysterious Swordsman Appears!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!