Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
With his special body,
he is a General Zombie.
Perona-sama!
I won't go easy on anyone
who tries to harm the lady!
Hey, Kumacy! Kumacy!
Moria-sama is summoning the Three Phantoms.
This man hails from Wano
Kingdom in the New World!
The Risky Brothers are
carrying the casket over.
The master beckons? Whatever for?
Get it from them and take the
casket to Master's dance hall.
Hit him with the light!
What's going on here?
I've heard that Straw Hat
Luffy has been captured!
Isn't that dog-penguin hybrid our enemy?
What the heck are you doing?!
Got that?
He wants to make a show
out of reanimating No. 900!
Did you get that or not?!
Jerk, I'll get you for this!
Wh-What gives? I thought
he was going to attack us.
The fighting style he just used...
Absalom!
--Ye...
--Don't answer! You're so not cute!
I-It doesn't matter!
C'mon, let's make a break for it!
What are you doing here? This is my room.
He couldn't be...
I'll be directing the Treasure
Retrieval Party on the ship,
Welcome back, Perona-sama.
Bastard!
The door is wide open!
Rookie, you're stepping way out of line!
--You're right!
--Y-Yeah!
Zip it, Kumacy! How many times
must I tell you not to talk?!
That woman is the enemy!
so come get me if anything happens.
Do you understand?
What is wrong with you?!
Three-Pace Hum... Notch Slash!
I see you're as harsh on Kumacy as ever.
I will beat table manners into anyone
uncouth enough to harm a lady...
That's right! You're cute
as long as you're quiet!
You're beary harsh.
More importantly, have you heard?
The master is summoning us.
Take care...
Punk! You just whispered something!
What is that?! My shadow?
They still haven't found us,
if you can believe that.
...you damn zombies!
That hurt, you bastard! Lemme out, dammit!
That old zombie wannabe said that
Gecko Moria's had his eyes on us
I'm sure of it! That dog-penguin is...
It's a miracle!
Why did we hide here in the first place?
--What was that?
--Bastard, lemme out! I mean it!
ever since we were invited to this island.
I'll let you have it if ya don't let me out!
Hey, don't do it!
We didn't have much choice!
--A casket?!
--Open the lid!
Dang, they're persistent!
Perhaps the curly cook's disappearance
has something to do with Moria.
Who knew Beast Man was
gonna catch up so soon?
That voice...!
What's he doing?! Sheesh!
And I didn't realize this was a zombie!
Did that idiot get caught?
That stupid cook! He had it coming.
Gum-Gum...
Straw Hat!
Let's look for a chance to make
a break for it. Sound good?
...Gatling!
Now then, we'll hold the
wedding ceremony right away.
But I never expected to run into
one of the Seven Warlords here.
Absalom-sama!
I've already dealt with the preparations.
So this is where you went!
I have something that I'd like to tell you.
One-Sword Style...
Why would a pirate want
to steal people's shadows?
Put me down! It was you, wasn't it?
What is it?
You're the invisible man
who was in the bathroom!
It looks like we have one more
intruder on top of the pirates.
...Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
I would love to know!
I've obtained 300 million
Berries' worth of might!
My name is Absalom.
I-I don't know anything!
An intruder?
It is the name of your future husband.
Now I can complete the greatest
Special Zombie in history!
It's the Humming Swordsman!
I promised that geezer I'd kick Moria's butt,
You'd best remember it!
What?!
but that'll have to go on hold.
I haven't been babying my skin
every day for a perverted beast!
That move... Zoro?!
Weapons Left!
Your missing friends are
already screwed anyway!
Hey, Zoro! What was that for?!
"The Warrior Known as the 'Devil'!!
The Moment of Oars' Revival!"
That was dangerous!
In fact, you're in no position
to be worrying about others!
We're getting out of this forest.
Not anymore...
Nico Robin!
I won't let you escape!
Quit oinking and lead the way,
you stupid piggy!
They've never failed to catch
our prey, not even once!
Monkey, monkey!
Usopp!
Chopper, look out! Behind you!
We hung out quietly in the ceiling
and snatched your friends up.
Immortal zombies are blocking the
paths in front of you and behind you.
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame!
Usopp! Chopper!
Now say your prayers!
You're in danger as well.
Now we'll take you to the same
place we took your friends!
Hey, wait! What're you doing?!
That hurt, you bastard! Lemme out, dammit!
Coup de...
Brace yourselves!
--What was that?
--Bastard, lemme out! I mean it!
...Vent!
Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho...
I'll let you have it if ya don't
let me out! Open the lid!
You've demolished the breezeway!
Now Straw Hat Luffy belongs to me!
--A casket?!
--Lemme out, bastard! I want out!
Cien Fleurs!
At last! I've finally obtained
the ultimate subordinate!
Open the lid right this second!
Lemme out right now! C'mon!
Who is it?! Who's singing that song?!
Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho
Don't hurt her!
Wing!
That voice...!
What's he doing?! Sheesh!
Bastard! Why'd you attack an ally?
Did that idiot get caught?
All of them fell into the courtyard.
Straw Hat!
That woman is the enemy!
You're supposed to kick her butt!
Goodness, I see everyone really
did disembark onto this island.
I doubt that finished them off...
I won't let you go after him!
I don't know who this lady is,
L-Luffy...!
How did you get up here?
What just happened? Did you see that?
but even if it means
defying the master's orders
I jumped.
What is that?
I'm light!
Hey, hey! Monkey, monkey, monkey!
That's his shadow! He cut off Luffy's shadow...
Seeing as you're here, I suppose
you've left me with no other choice.
or sacrificing myself,
This bag of bones goes...
I won't kick a woman!
I shall tell you everything
about this island.
Hey, Oinker! Did you pull another
fast one on us? Out with it!
His shadow...? Didn't that skeleton,
Brook, mention something like that?
Ka-bone!
I'm the spider monkey that you were
talking about back at the harbor!
Hey! Who the hell are you?!
Haven't I been telling
you that I'm in the dark?
You aren't a zombie, are you?
He stole Luffy's shadow?
Is he the one who took Brook's?
I bet you're with these pirates!
It's a giant spider!
Don't laugh! It gives the
impression that you're lying.
This ain't an arachnid
anymore! It's a monster!
Hey, Skeleton!
"Appearing from the Sky!
That Man Is the Humming Swordsman!"
Yes, yes. Not to worry.
I can't believe it... How did he do that?
How strange. I wonder if he was
strangled so he couldn't utter a sound.
Lemme out, you jerk! Lemme out, dummy!
Open the--
The fight is already over.
And there goes another one!
Why were your circuits
wired to be so ominous?!
Shit! There goes the casket!
Huh?
Hey, Kumacy! You were mumbling
something again, weren't you?
Three-Pace Hum...
This is so weird! Now Zoro's missing.
What are you gonna do to him?!
Didn't I tell you to zip it?
Don't you worry!
...Notch Slash!
Whoa, stop! You can't do this!
You'll get to personally experience
what is about to happen to him.
"The Vanishing Straw Hat Crew!
A Mysterious Swordsman Appears!"
Don't kill her! She's my friend!
Get it through your head!
I'm tired of repeating myself!
Darn boar! Stupid sow! Stop!
I'd be more worried about
myself if I were you!
"Luffy's Emergency Situation!
The Ultimate Shadow's Destination!"
You're not cute when you talk, so don't talk!!
Hightail it, Nami!
You're trapped with me in front
and the armored warriors in the rear!
Wait, you vile Cat Burglar!
You're too harsh on Kumacy.
You're beary harsh.
With this, your crew is finished!
No!
Damn it!
--I'm going to take Absalom to be my husband!
--Stop, dammit!
I wonder what happened.
This is so strange.
--Get off of me!
--No!
"Chivalry Remains! The Traitorous
Zombie Protects Nami!"
Now say your prayers!
The fight's not over!
Swords don't work on zombies!
He's gonna pop back up!
Where the heck did those two wander off to?
H-
Why are you goofing off, punk?
Perhaps the ghosts were behind this.
Hold your horses!
Curse you...!
I...
"Shut up" means "be quiet"!
I...!
Wait a sec...
I'm actually a man!
I hope they haven't been executed.
I've seen you somewhere before!
If you have time to think
up all these creepy ideas,
This shadow will bring me one step closer
figure out how to save them instead!
Not to worry! I've already dealt with that.
to becoming the King of the Pirates, Hogback!
Hey! What's gotten into you, rookie?
How?
Whoa, there.
I-Is that true?
Even zombies have weaknesses!
I thought it was impossible for a
zombie to defy the master's orders!
It's been a decade since we first met.
S-Sure is! I just cross-dress for fun!
I put all of my prowess into creating
No. 900 for a day such as this!
Gimme a break!
Why is he able to pull it off?
Besides... I think you and Beast Man
would make an awesome couple!
With that shadow in it,
I'm certain it'll become the
most powerful zombie in history!
He's as strong as a General to boot!
I was totally shipping you!
It will be a great asset!
--Really?
--Really! Gimme a break!
You cannot use logic to measure this power.
What's that?!
The day I become the world's
"King of the Grave" is close at hand!
Where'd they go?
It is the power to make the
impossible become possible!
It's the zombie's "soul."
I can't believe Zoro and Sanji!
The hurricane that blasts
everything in its path is known as...
His soul?! But I can see it leaving his body!
Jerk! Don't goof off at a time like this!
No one has ever encouraged me to
pursue my feelings for him before...
I can practically see the day I turn
the cute critters of the world
C-Captain!
...love.
Hey! Isn't it every man's dream to don
a random suit of armor lying around?
It's high time you returned...
into zombies and make them
serve me in my dream kingdom.
...to your rightful master!
You're the first person to offer
such kind words of support.
Sure enough, that "dog penguin"
is spouting out a bunch of nonsense.
Damn! It's every man's dream?
That's a solid argument!
Right! You can command absolute loyalty
from the shadow of the nastiest bastard!
He sounds just like Sanji-kun.
Has that steel body made your
heart forget the spirit of wonder?
I... I...!
You're right!
The world will transform into a
land filled with obedient zombies.
Hey, Dogguin! Do you know Sanji?
Raise your head, my friend.
Cut me some slack! I never meant
to turn my heart to steel!
See, we're Sanji's best
buds! Could ya lend us--
If I'd had a subordinate as powerful as this,
This is what you call "friendship."
Shut the heck up, you stinking pirates!
that idiot Kaido never would have
defeated me in the New World.
I am Namizo. Please call me "Nami."
Yay! Sing!
"Evil Be Gone"
Scary!
Friendship...? Nami!
So he really is our enemy after all!
Ever since I lost something important,
a draft has blown through my heart.
Let's wake him up!
Gyoro! Nin! Bao!
Captain Tararan!
You tamed her!
Please listen to "The Cyborg
Traveler's Steel Sentiment."
Yes, Master!
Wh-What's that?
Captain! He took out the captain!
Open the door to the special freezer!
You know, like, I'm always trying
to catch him when his guard is down
Something is headed this way.
Do they understand the situation they're in?
Captain!
Right away, Master!
What now?!
Hey!
so I can get a fingerprint
on the marriage certificate.
He isn't budging an inch...
Wait, Lola!
This opens up to a large hall.
But his guard is never down!
Really?
What did you do?!
Wait for me, No. 900.
He even manages to avoid touching the paper
Huh? A boar?
when I play dirty and hold him in an armlock!
I purified him.
I'm bringing the ultimate shadow down to you,
Wait, dammit! Lola!
You what?
Really, Lola! You're
going about it all wrong.
Look! He's definitely the
"Humming Swordsman"!
so be quick about making
me King of the Pirates!
You're leaving too much room to chance.
Catch me if you can!
Five years ago, he wreaked
havoc on Thriller Bark.
Eh?! Eh?! What do you mean?
Don't be stupid! You're going to stop!
The thing is, he's resisting
because he's conscious.
Could this be...?
We've gotta tell the master!
Nothing in the world could make me stop!
Spider Mouse!
Robin! Where are Usopp and the others?
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Sir!
You should wait until he's sound asleep.
Toss Straw Hat Luffy's body onto the ship.
That's what I'll make you think, and then...
I don't know. In fact...
Attack him in his sleep?!
Don't forget to remove the spider silk.
We can't have him dying on us.
Is that okay?! Won't it make me a bad person?
What?!
That spider web is strong
against physical attacks,
...this hall leads directly outside.
Lola, aren't you a zombie?
--Roger!
--One moment! I need to make a report!
What's with this room?
I forgot about that! What
a rotten blind spot!
but weak against fire.
Bride Fu! Princess Carry Vow!
What?
It looks just like an arena.
What is it?
If he isn't asleep, you can knock
him out and that'll work just as well!
Captain Tararan, the spider monkey,
was just defeated!
What the heck?!
If only it were that forgiving!
Hey, Namizo!
You're right! It melts right off!
You oughta say your prayers!
You'll never make it outta this room.
Weren't you gonna escape?
Wh-What was that?
He was defeated?
By the way, Lola, I forgot
something in the treasure room...
It's not as though the foe removed his shadow.
They got Straw Hat and the others.
But that's exactly what happened!
Ab-sama! Accept my burning love!
Y'know, you seem mighty
knowledgeable about this island...
I'd like to go back and get it,
but I can't recall how to get there.
Could you tell me?
I am, but I don't know where to begin.
He lost his shadow?!
You're such a klutz! Sure, I'll tell you.
R-Right!
H-Hey! Wait, Lola! Knock that off!
Wha--?!
The closest way there is
through Perona-sama's room.
Absalom, there is only one
man who could do that...!
If they've been caught,
we're probably too late.
--How many times must I
spell it out for you?
Franky!
Look, see that? Notice the
room with the tiny veranda?
I'm marrying that woman!
She seriously turns her
misfortune into fortune.
The Humming Swordsman!
What?! It's too late?!
What was that? I couldn't hear you!
If you keep going straight this way,
It sounds like Hildon's report
was accurate after all.
you'll hit a staircase.
Nami's a guy?
P-Please don't yell at me!
Who are you?!
That will take you to Perona-sama's room.
I love you!
What a disaster!
No wonder I thought
she seemed so masculine.
It makes me jump under my skin!
It looks like the Humming Swordsman
is removing shadows wherever he goes.
From there, you'll head inside...
Liar! There is no way you couldn't
hear me when we're this close!
We've already suffered heavy losses
before anyone realized he was here.
But I'm a skeleton, so I don't have any skin!
Wow! Moving armor!
Really, you can be so shy!
At this rate, we're going to relive
the nightmare of five years ago!
Listen to me!
It's my skull humor!
I'm sure it's a zombie.
Give up already!
It's moving with spears piercing though it.
I love you! I love you! I love you!
I love you! I love you!...
Hey, Nami! He's closing in on us!
Don't bother. He's already dead.
You'll never get me!
Really? Lola, this is your chance to attack!
Zombies shouldn't get all
geared up and spook people!
--I won't let that hit me!
--Uh, are they fighting...?
Anyway, please put the
joking aside and hear me out.
What?! We have to go back to the ship?
I'll never see him again,
so don't worry about me!
Beats me...
You mean Sunny?
Don't bother! He's already dead.
Good luck! You two make the best couple!
Right. The worst they'll do
to your captured crewmates
As I already told you,
without a working rudder,
--You're being pigheaded.
--Stuff it!
I'll do my best!
Then marry me.
I spent decades wandering these seas alone.
Thank you, Nami!
is steal their shadows!
That makes no sense!
I'm bursting with courage!
Snatch a Kiss with Love!
But it's not as though that's fatal.
Even if I wanted to escape
from the Devil's Sea,
It's high time you gave it a rest!
Strong Right!
Just look at me! I'm a prime example.
I was at the mercy of the tide
because of my broken rudder.
Oh, my!
Absalom!
Now let's go back to about five years ago.
Oh, I actually did die!
Lola!
But that's a different story!
Much like you and your crewmates,
I was "invited" to Thriller Bark.
Guys, now's our chance!
When ya get down to it, it's not
like losing your shadow'll kill you.
In the end, the boar didn't hurt us any.
What?!
I found you, wretched Cat Burglar!
Nami, you're amazing!
Desperate to leave the Florian Triangle,
Precisely! But the thing is,
everyone falls unconscious
Couldn't you tell how nice and honest
she was after we sat down and talked?
I walked around this island in hopes
when their shadow is snatched away.
Nami!
There is something very wrong with your eyes!
of finding the parts I
needed to fix my rudder.
Crap!
They won't awaken for two days.
Who?! Me?!
The wall--!
The stronger the person,
the sooner he is put on a ship
W-W-Wait just one second!
I haven't stolen anything yet.
I wonder if anything is down here... Nope.
and kicked out of Thriller Bark.
Save it!
What is that?! Crap! Crap! Crap! Crap!
Why do you think they'd do that?
I won't let you take Ab-sama!
Master!
Scary! Help me!
To prevent the victims from returning
to the island to recover their shadows?
Your swordplay can get a taste of my...
--Nami!
--Look out!
Freaky! I hate ghosts!
We did it, Master!
Weapons Left!
Bingo!
Then why don't they kill us
when we're out cold?
Cut the crap, you freaks!
And who's this "Master"?!
All I found were monsters and zombies.
Lemme outta here right now!
They can't.
Don't lay a hand on this lady!
Lemme out, dammit!
In the end, they caught me and
brought me here to this building.
This is important, so pay attention!
You were a pain in the butt!
Inside, I saw...
Who are you?!
For starters, even if you separate
a person from his shadow,
How dare you get in my way?!
H-Hey, let go! Knock that off!
...a martial arts dancer who
they caught before me...
H-Hey!
they are still of one mind and body.
--Look out!
--Dogguin!
If the human dies, the shadow will disappear.
...and a type of corpse covered
in stitches called a "mario."
What is he?
Jerks, you'd better be ready for a fight!
That means the zombie will die then as well.
'Cause I'm gonna let you have it!
A ghastly giant appeared before them!
Sheesh! Who the heck are these guys?!
That wouldn't serve the enemy's needs!
Dogguin!
It was incredible!
Are you okay?
Hence they always keep the human body alive.
"Evil Be Gone"
Why didn't you attack her?
So even if your friends lose their shadows,
What?!
He peeled the man's shadow off the ground...
...and snip, snip!
I won't kick a woman...
Wha--?!
I promise they will get sent
back to your ship alive!
He cut the man's shadow off?
I questioned my eyes!
...even if it kills me!
Not
Whoa! He took down Franky!
Impressive!
The worst case scenario would be for
the two of you to fall victim as well!
that I have any eyes.
I don't believe it!
You're willing to consider this beast
a woman? You're brilliant, man!
Excuse me?!
Doesn't this ship have a
single treasure chest?!
You're asking for a knuckle sandwich!
No! Usopp! Chopper!
It would mean that all of you are doomed
to wander the ocean without your shadows!
There are boxes, but they are all empty...
Feel free to let him have it.
I'll be taking my bride.
There is also a tiny bit of money...
Eh?! Nami's flying? That's awesome!
Awaken your friends while
there is still time to act!
Unbelievable! We're hardly getting
anything out of the two ships.
No, you morons! I'm being kidnapped!
I'm not gonna lose!
This is the only chance you get to look
for a way to recover their shadows.
What? By whom?
Does this ship really belong to
the man who defeated Crocodile?
Not to some corpse!
H-Hey, wait!
Shortly thereafter, I suffered the same fate.
Now then, we'll hold the
wedding ceremony right away.
Did you understand all of that?
Oh, well. Go ahead and pilfer their
ridiculously large supply of food.
I've already dealt with the preparations.
The man who lost his shadow
collapsed on the spot.
I see. Everything sounds logical enough.
Put me down! It was you, wasn't it?
--Yes, ma'am!
--Perona-sama!
You're the invisible man
who was in the bathroom!
His severed shadow was stuffed
into the inanimate mario.
Hildon...
Here, guys, take this.
So there really was an invisible man?
Moria-sama is summoning the Three Phantoms.
Nami!
Now what do you think happened?
He's getting up again.
The master beckons? Whatever for?
What is it?
This is getting nowhere fast.
The zombies' weakness!
I've heard that Straw Hat Luffy
has been captured!
The "mario" corpse got
up and started to move!
He's completely different from
the other zombies we've faced.
I knew it! It was you back there!
You saw how effective it was in my
battle against this spider monkey!
He wants to make a show
out of reanimating No. 900!
I had to appraise your wares.
No. 900?! Is he serious?!
How's that work?
Let that be a lesson to you!
Shadows are our "second souls" that are
always with us, moving as we dictate.
You are worthy to become my bride!
This is what makes zombies truly terrifying!
He managed to get really far away!
My name is Absalom.
Even if we take some damage, it doesn't hurt!
Who're you? You're stinking huge!
That is true of your shadows as well.
What's that?!
It is the name of your future husband.
All of the armed General Zombies
It's the zombie's "soul."
Hey, punk! Careful how
you speak to the master!
Normally, these "souls" always stay with you,
You'd best remember it!
were robust warriors who made names
following your every moment from
the moment you're born until you die.
His soul?! But I can see it leaving his body!
So you are Straw Hat Luffy?
for themselves when they were alive.
C-Captain!
There is a giant of a man who captures
them and makes them do his bidding!
Don't try to sound so macho
after you looked me up and down!
One was a kingdom's Captain of the Guard
It's high time you returned...
while another was a heinous criminal.
There is a legendary samurai,
a pirate, and a gunslinger!
I haven't been babying my skin
every day for a perverted beast!
...to your rightful master!
He is one of the Seven Warlords
of the Sea, Gecko Moria!
These monsters are as good as immortal!
I'm glad to see that you're doing well.
You losers don't stand a chance.
He has eaten the Shadow-Shadow Fruit!
Thunder Charge!
A Devil Fruit, huh?
None of your pals are okay!
How do ya like that?!
Is he the one who stole your shadow?
Is it you?
Are you that moron, Moria?
You bastard!
A certain man stole my
shadow a few years ago.
Wall Zombie!
What a thing to say!
On it!
You have quite a bit of spunk
in you. Quite a bit, indeed.
Your shadow?
Gah! They blocked the path!
This is their weakness? What exactly is it?
Nami!
Does that sorta thing actually happen?
Yes, it does.
I should have expected as much from
someone with a 300 million Berry bounty.
The path behind us is not the
only one that has been cut off.
It's salt.
Thank goodness! Now start running!
And having lost my shadow, I am no
longer able to exist in the world of light.
I imagine you will make an excellent
subordinate in just a moment.
Salt?! If we gotta purify
the things to take 'em out,
We're getting out of this forest.
A subordinate?! Screw that!
Who do you think you are?!
are they some kinda curse?
I cannot live under the light of the sun.
What gives? He isn't blacking out!
Well, I suppose they are in a way.
Who...? "Who do you think you are," eh?
The zombies were originally
animated thanks to a Devil Fruit.
Going by the looks of it,
he clearly isn't a small fry!
What would happen if you
were hit by the sunlight?
Hurry!
Salt holds the power of the ocean.
If I was directly hit by sunlight, my body...
I am the future King of the Pirates!
Based off of my experience,
So just as a power holder
grows limp in the ocean,
Wh-What could the shock
coursing through my body mean?
I'd say these guys are definitely
more than we bargained for.
the salt breaks the fusion
between a fake soul and a body.
...would be obliterated!
There is a whole bunch of armor!
It feels as though I was
suddenly struck by lightning...
Makes sense! So that monkey spewed out
the shadow that was inside of him, right?
I went nuts against one
and it hardly did a thing.
As long as he has a corpse, he can use
a shadow to turn it into a zombie.
Could this be...
We're just gonna burn through energy
if we take all of these guys on.
That never would have occurred to me.
The real problem is that his cohort
is the genius surgeon, Dr. Hogback.
...love?!
Ab-sama! Absalom, you jerk!
Come out and marry me!
To reiterate, please stuff salt into
a zombie's mouth to defeat it!
Yeah, I guess you have a point.
It's not like this is the last battle.
I won't let you escape!
He can reconstruct the body,
making it stronger than before!
If we make it out of this hall,
we should enter the inner courtyard.
That's the trick! Even for this
bag of bones, that's a snap!
You vanished and fled again, didn't you?!
H-Hey, this is no time to be spacing out!
--Snap! Snap! Snap!
--But Brook...
Sometimes he uses his medical
expertise to revive the flesh
Great! Then let's meet up in the courtyard!
Our job was to catch those three!
Why are you so knowledgeable
about the zombies and this island?
of legendary warriors from around the world.
That's right! If we fumble this,
Perona-sama will punish us!
I don't want anyone else
going missing, so be careful!
And he has a tremendous collection of mario
currently preserved in his lab freezer.
Right.
Right, she sure will!
That has to do with when I lost
my shadow five years ago...
"Evil Be Gone"
We shouldn't be standing here!
Charge!
--Did we lose him?
--Probably.
Crap! That lady is in trouble!
Let's go!
Naturally, they sent me back out to drift at sea.
I'm sure Lola...
Dr. Hogback...
Yeah!
But why do I want to protect her anyway?
Fortunately, I was able to
turn back by the time I awoke.
I didn't realize the renowned
doctor has been here
Lola!
He's coming!
assisting a pirate ever
since he went missing.
He's headed straight this way!
Over here!
Where the heck did she go?
And my body won't move...!
So those zombies are reanimated corpses,
This body is too weak!
but it's not like he actually
revived the dead, huh?
Hurry and catch all three of them!
Hurry! Get in here.
Exactly!
What is this?
Beats me, but we've gotta
focus on hiding for now!
The shadow provides their
personality and fighting abilities.
Lola!
And thus I returned to the island and fought.
Wait, Wild Zombies!
Ab-sama!
Don't touch that woman!
Kissy! Kissy! Kissy!
The power of their body depends on
the physical ability of their mario.
Kissy! Kissy-po-po-po! Kissy-po!
Shut up, Erosalom!
What was that...?
I faced the zombie who holds my shadow!
The master ordered us to serve
as Perona-sama's subordinates!
If you combine a strong body
with a strong shadow,
Knock it off, Lola!
Please give up on me!
it will create an even stronger zombie!
We don't fall under your jurisdiction!
That's strange... This is the
only way they could have gone.
--Beat it!
--Yeah, you heard him!
Didn't I tell you that I'm
going to marry this woman?
But in the end, I lost miserably.
Shut up! Keep your nose outta this.
That is why Moria is eager to get
his hands on wanted men's shadows!
I told you to wait!
I fled for fear of my life.
No matter what...
I getcha! No wonder he came after us.
Ab-sama, you belong to me and only me!
No matter what, I did not want to die!
I am fully aware that you
fall under Perona's domain.
Hey, Kumacy!
So that's the deal with Thriller Bark.
I won't show any mercy, Cat Burglar!
I am the sole survivor from my ship!
Erosalom--er, Absalom-sama,
there is trouble afoot!
Moria's favorite aspect about
zombies could be their obedience.
Stop it, Lola!
However, you should also know
better than to incur my wrath!
Stop, that can wait. My business comes first.
I'll crush the life outta her!
Someday I must pull out of the Devil's Sea
Generally, it's a challenge to
keep powerful warriors in line.
Don't!
Did three pirates come this way?
and carry out the promise I made to my friends!
Right, but our shadows possess
the same abilities as us.
I will only take so many snide remarks!
I won't go easy on anyone
who tries to harm the lady!
Actually, about that--
So I ran for my life!
Absalom!
Do you understand?!
What are you doing here? This is my room.
Once he has our shadows,
he can toss us troublemakers out.
But ultimately, extending my
life did not resolve anything.
Perona...
The powerful are quickly returned to
the sea while they're still unconscious.
Welcome back, Perona-sama.
So I am done running!
Zip it, Kumacy! How many times
must I tell you not to talk?!
Who are you?
In that case, they're in trouble!
I won't let you go after that lady.
I know, but I have something important--
What's going on here?
Until I defeat that man and recover my--
I wouldn't worry yet.
Isn't that dog-penguin hybrid our enemy?
Shut up! I don't wanna hear your voice!
What was that?
We still have time.
I see you're as harsh on Kumacy as ever.
The fighting style he just used...
H-Hey, rookie! Bite your tongue.
I will tell you the best way to handle this.
You're beary harsh.
Don't make Absalom angry!
Please believe me and do as I instruct.
Butt out of it. He's my subordinate.
He couldn't be...
More importantly, have you heard?
The master is summoning us.
What?! You want us to believe you?!
Bastard!
Rookie, you're stepping way out of line!
That woman is the enemy!
Good sir, I'm shocked to the skull!
Has there been some sort of incident?
C-Crap!
What is wrong with you?!
Well, I suppose you could say that.
H-Here it comes!
He's going to reanimate No. 900.
Actually, I haven't bickered like
this in decades, so I'm eating it up!
I will beat table manners into anyone
uncouth enough to harm a lady...
No. 900?!
Does that mean the
300 million Berry bounty has been caught?
Well, you'll have to pardon me.
They still haven't found us,
if you can believe that.
I'm in a hurry. Take care!
...you damn zombies!
It's a miracle!
Why did we hide here in the first place?
We'll hear you out, so get talking!
I'm sure of it! That dog-penguin is...
Stop right there!
We didn't have much choice!
Certainly!
Who knew Beast Man was
gonna catch up so soon?
Master!
On top of everything you've told us,
answer this one question before you go.
I warned you not to make me angry!
And I didn't realize this was a zombie!
Moria-sama!
Let's look for a chance to make
a break for it. Sound good?
The Three Phantoms have gathered together!
Absalom-sama!
So this is where you went!
I have something I'd like to tell you.
That was quick! Enter!
Please come in.
What is it?
It looks like we have one more
intruder on top of the pirates.
This ship belongs to Straw Hat, the man
who defeated Crocodile, and his crew...
An intruder?
It's the Humming Swordsman!
I can't wait to see what type of
treasure they're lugging around!
What?!
The Humming...!
Grah, the Humming Swordsman!
Oh, you're here!
Hey! Lemme outta here!
Damn it! He's the only person to have
figured out my zombies' weakness!
Someone... just fell from the sky.
Isn't anyone around?
Turn me into the King of the Pirates!
At least gimme a response, dammit!
We're on it!
Huh? Huh? How did he figure
it out in the first place?
Wait, Cat Burglar!
You can't become the King of the Pirates!
Hey, what just came hurtling down?!
It's so dark I can't see a thing!
What is she doing?
Hey, Nami! Doesn't it seem
like everyone's after you?
And how did he come back--
It couldn't be...
Where the heck am I?
The future King of the Pirates...
Hey, Cindry-chan! Why do you
keep standing in front of me?!
Well, actually, I have a
pretty good idea who it is...
Seriously! What's up with that?
...is me!
Sheesh!
Humming Swordsman...
Who're you?!
Hey! Put me down! What're you doing?!
So, like, I've got an idea.
I've heard about him, but what is he like?
Who the hell are you?
Wh-Why don't we split up?
Perona! Don't you know what he looks like?
Answer me!
That would explain how he
slipped through your recon.
I'm not a decoy, you heartless brute!
What's with this light?
Hey! What're you doing?
No!
Hey! Untie this rope, you oversized shallot!
So it would seem.
Wait up, dammit!
Boars are scary!
Wh... What?!
Give Usopp, Nami, Chopper,
Sanji, and Zoro back!
Master, the seed of trouble
has returned to our island.
Like anyone is gonna wait for you!
Where'd you hide them, shallot head?!
That's none of my concern, simpleton!
Where the heck did that doof fall from?
N-Nami?!
This one has lot of fight in him.
Wait! Don't abandon me!
You can deal with him!
Wait!
So this is Straw Hat Luffy, eh?
H-Hey!
I have a hard time believing this is the man
Here she comes!
who picked a fight with the World Government.
No!
Tch! This bites! Guess
we'd better go save him.
Why is he wearing General Zombie armor?
Strong Right!
Wha--?!
Gah! I'm finished!
Don't you get it? This is every guy's dream!
It's game over. Farewell, everyone.
Sorry for the wait!
You got captured, so don't
lecture me about dreams!
Don't get a big head!
Now then, let's go to the freezer!
Please scatter my ashes in the East Blue...
Hey, Straw Hat Luffy! You've made
a pretty big name for yourself,
It's freezing!
but you're only our third catch so far.
Hey, hey!
Sir...! The present condition is such...
I won't forgive you!
Treinta Fleurs!
We've got Pirate Hunter Zoro and some
blond guy who didn't have a wanted poster.
Despite that bizarre interruption,
you can't escape from me!
Stupid! You should have mentioned that first!
Huh? What just happened?
I can always make more footing if I have to!
If that's the case, he should
buy us plenty of time.
Huh? Sanji's the only blond in my crew...
Move it!
We survived?
Sir!
Monkey, monkey!
Come report to me if there
are any other problems.
She doesn't care about
anyone other than Nami?
We'll have to deal with
this headache first, huh?
Now go toss Straw Hat out!
Phew! That's a load off...
Roger!
What?! Hey, it sounds like
they caught Zoro and Sanji.
Great! Now's my chance!
Ready, go! Heave, ho! Heave, ho! Heave, ho!
Buy me a bit of time.
Shoot! Nami!
Heave, ho! Heave, ho! Heave, ho!
Heave, ho! Heave, ho!
What are you going to do?
No way! And they even have Luffy.
Ooh! Those pillars are just what I needed.
--Luffy!
--Stupid! Don't pop out!
Wh-Why did the three monsters
have to be the first to get caught?
I'm gonna whip up a weapon right quick.
He won't die just because they took his shadow!
How dare you act like I'm no big deal?!
Remember Brook!
I have no idea who these guys are,
but they're definitely bad news!
Uh huh...
Don't treat me like a small fry!
We've gotta stop her, Chopper!
Kumacy, hurry it up!
--Yeah!
--Hi-yo!
Gosh darn it! Zombies shouldn't
be givin' us a hard time!
By the way, what happened
to that trio, Perona?
Coming!
Spider's...
...Sticky Net!
We can't leave now! Let's bide our time.
I recall handing them over
to the Risky Brothers.
He has spinnerets on his hands!
They're going to do something
with Luffy's shadow.
Give Absalom back!
Seis Fleurs!
But Kumacy never got them.
We gotta find out what!
What is your problem?!
We can worry about recovering it later!
You sure they didn't
escape on their way over?
Clutch!
Bingo!
Slap!
Nami!
They're talking about us.
Man, you're one nasty...!
Something touched my eye!
Oh, shoot! I got sticky net in my eyes.
Get away from her!
The casket popped open!
Run for it, Nami!
That duo is long gone.
Don't get in our way.
Thanks, Nico Robin! I'm
ready and raring to go!
Where did they go?
Huh?
Wait, fiend!
Jerks!
I never expected them to defeat Tararan!
Get back!
Damn it! Stop!
What is that?
Nothing much! I just thrust the steel
nunchakus I had on hand into some pillars.
Whoa, there!
Oh, here's the spot!
Usopp! Nami!
Hey, hang in there! Wake up!
Jeez! Did you get lost, Jigoro?
Off my back! Now where are my foes?!
Ya need a big weapon when
dealin' with a monster like this!
Let me face them now! Give me enemies!
Shush! Dude, don't say a thing!
--Actually--
--I keep telling you to keep that mouth shut!
Heavy Nunchaku!
You're too harsh on Kumacy.
You're beary harsh.
Franky...
What is it, punk? I'm not crying, you dummy!
By any chance, did they also...
It looks like they won't let us
walk through without a fight.
But the trio that includes my bride caused
Lemme out, bastard! I want out, dammit!
Why is he so powerful?
Isn't he supposed to be human?
Don't look at me!
Damn it!
quite the commotion in your courtyard.
No matter how many times I
take them down, they get right back up!
Lemme out!
What compelled you... to ask him that?
...get sucked into that wall like
what just happened to Straw Hat?
Hey, wait a second...
Shut up! I can ask whatever I want!
Dang, they're persistent!
Now that I think about
it... Hogback, you pig!
Monkey, monkey!
This means you've raised your
hand against my future bride!
Gosh darn it! I freaking love that skeleton!
Gum-Gum...
Yep! You guessed right.
You'll never find a better guy!
...Gatling!
I warned you not to touch her!
Darn it all!
You'll never get married.
And you will share their
fate in just a moment.
Say what?! Cindry!
You sure won't.
Immortal zombies are blocking the
paths in front of you and behind you.
One-Sword Style...
Now, now, Cindry-chan!
You're only adding fuel to the fire!
Stop--
Now say your prayers!
And why are you standing in front of me?
...Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
I'm not sure if you're a stupid
spider or a stupid monkey,
You won't get married, either.
Tararan is in trouble!
but aren't you responsible
for the massive web
You're killing me! That
was a nasty stray bullet!
Who are those guys?
that got all over Sunny at
the entrance to the island?
At any rate, we need to hurry up there!
That move... Zoro?!
What are they going to do with
Luffy now that they've caught him?
S-Stop!
And what's happened to Sanji and Zoro?
Youve been keeping tabs on us;
you were out to get us from the beginning.
Give it a rest, jerk!
Hey, Zoro! What was that for?!
We're in pretty deep doo-doo ourselves!
Spider's Sticky Net!
That was dangerous!
But there is no way Luffy's
gonna stay in that cage!
Yep! Don't underestimate the
power of our information network!
What?!
We knew exactly what you were up to
thanks to Perona-sama's Ghost Network!
Jerk!
You're lost without your trusty weapon!
Good, good! Keep nice and quiet.
You were asking for that!
No matter what anyone says,
my mind is made up!
Do your large ears also play a
part in collecting information?
That woman will be my blushing bride!
Weapons Left!
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame!
You will never get married.
They look like they have exceptional hearing.
Shut up!
Come on, Cindry-chan!
Why don't you just ignore Absalom?
But I am covered in scars.
Eh? What was that? What did you just say?
Who're you? Are you actually Zoro?
Don't expect to get married... ever!
They're for show!
My name is Jigoro!
That's two stray bullets in a row!
Jigoro? What, so you aren't Zoro?
Franky...
Yeah, I know.
She said I'll never get married!
They really are scary!
How come you were able to use Zoro's attack?
Hey, hey!
Th-The Humming Swordsman... is terrifying!
This situation bites. This is what
it means to be "up against a wall."
I've had enough of your yapping, pirate!
Cut it out! Knock it off!
I can't stand all your fussing!
Nico Robin!
What are those things?
If those pirates got away,
you can deal with it later!
You're my foe, aren't you?
This calls for quick thinking...
Mouse, mouse! Mouse, mouse!
I was so scared...
I'm gonna slice you in half!
Want me to handle it?
I had you gather so we could celebrate
I'm sorry. I let my guard down.
But I won't give up!
You really sound just like Zoro!
Be my guest.
the commemorative creation
of a powerful ally!
I'll try to keep up.
I didn't realize there were more spiders.
You're practically identical!
That's mighty reassuring!
What's up?
Well, here I go!
I will never, ever give up!
C-Crap!
Hey, wait! What're you doing?!
He's insane!
Coup de...
Master, the pirate chewed
through the cage and is escaping!
Never!
That was close! Take this!
...Vent!
Moron! Monkey, monkey!
He chewed...
...through the cage?!
Why did you capture me?!
What?!
It's impossible for you to notice those guys.
You've demolished the breezeway!
--Luffy!
--Sweet!
They're my subordinates, the Spider Mice.
Damn it! There's no end to them!
There are a whopping five
hundred of them in Thriller Bark!
He's going to prove dependable!
And there you have it.
Franky!
Don't, Absalom! We're indoors.
They've never failed to catch
our prey, not even once!
Grab on!
You're rather violent.
I'll stop him.
You can't catch me, dummy!
They strike from the darkness
or from their enemy's blind spot
Negative Hollow!
to catch him unawares!
Hogback-sama has modified our silk
so that no human could ever break it!
Those are...!
Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive!...
Dang! They're really persistent!
We hung out quietly in the ceiling
and snatched your friends up.
Cien Fleurs!
They're multiplying as they dance! Awesome!
I've got the perfect thing for zombies!
I'll catch them and keep them as pets!
Fresh Fire!
I will recover my shadow!
Wing!
It doesn't matter how strong the person is--
we don't give him a chance to resist!
Fresh Fire!
What?!
By the time he realizes what
has happened, it's already too late!
Prepare the buckets!
Shoot! It didn't work.
What?!
Dude, you can fly?!
Now we'll take you to the same
place we took your friends!
Yes...
That was an epic fail.
I'm such a loser this week.
I can't wait!
For about five seconds.
Crap!
Brace yourselves!
That's not long!
When I saw his corpse in the Land of Ice,
my body wouldn't stop trembling.
I can hear the whole world booing me!
But it's long enough.
Once Fleurs!
Strong Right!
Okay! I've got the punk!
It's breathtaking when you
think that this terrifying beast
Slam!
Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho...
Sweet! I latched on.
used to terrorize the seas 500 years ago!
If I could be reborn, I'd like to be a clam.
If we can make it to that entrance,
we'll be able to go after Straw Hat!
--Cold!
--When he conquered a nation, he'd carry
the entire island back to his domain.
I suck!
Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho
I'm sorry. I can't keep this up...
It's said he created a kingdom of thugs.
That won't work on me a second time!
Reel back in, arm!
I was so close to the famous giant
known as the legendary "Continent Puller."
Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho...
I hope we make it in time!
Where's Luffy?
I-I'm freezing!
It looks like he's still back there!
What?!
Where the heck are they going?
Even if we go back, I can't tell
where that idiot is with him in armor!
Yo ho ho ho
If I could be reborn,
I'd like to be a sea cucumber...
Beats me, but I think they said
something about a special freezer...
-- Yo ho ho ho
--Huh? What's that?
Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive!
Damn it! He better not
have gone missing on us!
That explains it!
We're on our way
The Land of Ice? A corpse?
But we can't stay here and wait for him.
to deliver Bink's booze
To fall from the King of the
Pirates to a sea cucumber...
I never dreamed I'd get to see
that legend with my own two eyes!
The zombies are hot on our heels.
Sail leisurely with the sea breeze
Hey! Straw Hat!
This is a zombie creator's--
Brutal!
Sail with the waves
Hey, Cindry-chan! Why are
you walking in front of me?
The setting sun romps about
on the other side of the tide
All of them fell into the courtyard.
Yet another legend shall come back to life!
Damn it! Let go of me!
That hurt, you bastard! Lemme out, dammit!
I doubt that finished them off...
--What was that?
--Bastard, lemme out! I mean it!
Hit him with the light!
I'll let you have it if ya don't
let me out! Open the lid!
...but we won't have to
worry about them for a while.
A ring of birds in the sky sing
What the heck are you doing?!
That worked out nicely.
Jerk, I'll get you for this!
--A casket?!
--Lemme out, bastard! I want out!
Open the lid right this second!
Lemme out right now! C'mon!
Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho...
Long time no see, No. 900.
Man, you're horrible!
How dare you step on me?!
--That voice...!
--When I say I want out, I mean it!
It's Luffy!
-- Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho
--Who is it?! Who's singing that song?!
Who do you think you are?!
Are you tellin' me Straw Hat is in that?!
We can't go back this way.
--Let's go after him, Nico Robin!
--Yeah!
Hey, you! I know you can hear me!
What's he doing?! Sheesh!
Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho...
Don't blow me off! Hey!
Did that idiot get caught?
Straw Hat!
What is it?
Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho
I won't let you go after him!
What is that?! My shadow?
Tch! They sure are tough.
Hey, hey! Monkey, monkey, monkey!
Goodness, I see everyone really
did disembark onto this island.
Curse you! I'll get you scumballs for this!
How did you get up here?
I jumped.
I'm the spider monkey that you were
talking about back at the harbor!
I'm light!
I'm a spider! I can climb
right back up there!
Seeing as you're here, I suppose
you've left me with no other choice.
It's a giant spider!
This ain't an arachnid
anymore! It's a monster!
I shall tell you everything
about this island.
You'd better prepare yourselves!
Hey! Who the hell are you?!
Lemme out, you jerk! Lemme out, dummy!
You aren't a zombie, are you?
Open the--
Now, it's time for him to awaken!
I bet you're with these pirates!
And there goes another one!
Hey, don't do it!
Shit! There goes the casket!
Hey, Skeleton!
He is the only berserker to have
gone down in history as a "Devil."
Yes, yes. Not to worry.
What are you gonna do to him?!
Huh?
The fight is already over.
Don't you worry!
Something's falling?
You'll get to personally experience
what is about to happen to him.
Huh?
Oars!
I'd be more worried about
myself if I were you!
No, someone's raining down on us!
Three-Pace Hum...
I've obtained 300 million
Berries' worth of might!
...Notch Slash!
Now I can complete the greatest
Special Zombie in history!
What is that?
You're trapped with me in front
and the armored warriors in the rear!
This bag of bones goes...
With this, your crew is finished!
Ka-bone!
Luffy!
Knock it off, you oversized shallot!
What's going on? They put
Luffy's shadow in that giant!
Hey, you're one insolent Wild Zombie!
Hey, hey, hey! Who just flew in from the sky?
I'll get you for this, jerks!
This is the moment of the
century, Cindry-chan!
Out of my way!
Wait. Look at his outfit.
We've finally uncovered the
secret behind the zombies.
When I saw his corpse in the Land of Ice,
my body wouldn't stop trembling.
The small island is unable to
escape the whirling storm of love!
Oh, I see! That cane!
Put some light on him!
Ouch! Let go! What's your problem?
Let go of me, dammit!
Cindry-chan, that's my line!
Right! And that hair...!
Nami, what's wrong?
What's happening? My shadow is...? Stop it!
That's right! This is a Love Hurricane!
I was so close to the famous giant known
as the legendary "Continent Puller."
It's that invisible man again!
Well, I have a good idea who it is now.
I've had enough of your nonsense!
Get out of my way!
Nami, you're... vanishing!
That's mine, too!
And from the sky! In-cane-ceivable!
I've gained a 300 million Berry bounty's
worth of power to add to my forces!
I'm gonna be King of the--
I won't let you pursue that lady!
That's a far cry from your line!
Wh-Why...?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Appearing from the Sky!
That Man Is the Humming Swordsman!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Chivalry Remains! The Traitorous
Zombie Protects Nami!"
"Awakening After 500 Years!!
Oars Opens His Eyes!!"
"The Warrior Known as the 'Devil'!!
The Moment of Oars' Revival!"
"Luffy's Emergency Situation!
The Ultimate Shadow's Destination!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!