Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
You are going to disgrace yourself by crying,
Let's get this underway!
We swore to reunite with my crewmate
off some capes. His name is...
"Anything but my afro! Anything but my afro!"
This shadow will bring me one step closer
...Laboon!
as you beg me to spare your life,
just like last time.
to becoming the King of the Pirates, Hogback!
No, that's not how it will go down!
Laboon...
Be still, Straw Hat Luffy's shadow!
They were merciless.
It's been a decade since we first met.
Wha--? M-M-Marriage?!
Seriously?
I put all of my prowess into creating
No. 900 for a day such as this!
I am your new master.
Don't be stupid! I won't let that happen!
It's him...
With that shadow in it,
He's got guts to marry Nami...
I'm about to provide you with a voice and body
I'm certain it'll become the
most powerful zombie in history!
While waiting for my chance to return,
We know him.
so that you may live as a zombie.
It will be a great asset!
And there is a giant version of me?
I have spent these past five years...
Forget all of your past relations
and become my obedient soldier!
We know that whale.
That's how you make a zombie?
The day I become the world's
"King of the Grave" is close at hand!
...growing stronger!
So we need to find a zombie in sandals,
Luffy's giant, and the cook's dogguin.
It's time! Awaken!
I can practically see the day I turn
the cute critters of the world
"A Man's Promise Never Dies!!
To the Friend Waiting Under the Distant Sky!"
I had no idea one of the people
Laboon has been waiting for...
Our shadows will come back if we
throw salt in their mouths, right?
into zombies and make them
serve me in my dream kingdom.
Arise from 500 years of slumber!
But honestly, I'm amazed you
discovered that weakness.
Heave, ho! Heave, ho! Heave, ho!
Heave, ho! Heave, ho!
All of our info came from that bag of bones,
--Luffy!
--Stupid! Don't pop out!
from how to defeat the zombies
to how to rescue you guys.
He won't die just because they took his shadow!
...was that skeleton!
Remember Brook!
Uh-huh...
He...
Here, guys, take this.
He's a real man!
Didn't you say, "I got so
lonely that I wanted to die"?
What is it?
"Evil..."
The zombies' weakness!
I love that bag of bones
and that whale, dammit!
This is their weakness? What exactly is it?
If I were you, I would have
taken my own life ages ago.
Shuddup!
It's salt.
You're doing all of this because
you want to keep a promise...
Now I'm getting excited!
To reiterate, please stuff salt into
a zombie's mouth to defeat it!
He's a musician, a talking skeleton,
has an afro, goes "Yo ho ho!"
A monster that could tower over giants?
What exactly did you promise your crewmates?
Yeah! He's the one who made
all that noise and screamed.
That's the trick! Even for this
bag of bones, that's a snap!
It's quite simple.
and was Laboon's pal!
--Snap! Snap! Snap!
--But Brook...
Long ago, we left a member of my
crew behind at a certain location.
I bet Luffy's zombie is hooting
and hollering as he runs rampant.
Why are you so knowledgeable
about the zombies and this island?
He's coming aboard our ship,
even if I have to drag him.
That has to do with when I lost
my shadow five years ago...
He's joining our crew! Any objections, guys?
It was unavoidable, yet sad.
Let's hurry!
When we set sail, we vehemently
swore that we would return.
Naturally, they sent me back out to drift at sea.
If there were, would you change your mind?
Hey, look! There's Sunny!
Fortunately, I was able to
turn back by the time I awoke.
I wanna help him see Laboon again!
But then we were annihilated on these seas,
Yeah! That skeleton knew
what he was talkin' about!
You've got my vote, dammit!
Magnificent!
preventing us from keeping our promise.
Same here, dummy!
I'm not afraid of that skeleton!
How truly overawing!
He's a piece of art! A real devil!
Indeed!
I believe it has been... fifty years
now since the day we died.
And thus I returned to the island and fought.
That's a given. I'm more concerned
about stopping Nami-san's marriage!
Meat!
Whoosh!
But in the end, I lost miserably.
Fifty years?! Hey, that was ages ago!
I'm hungry!
Hey, Zoro! Where are you going?
I wasn't even born yet!
Well, you'll have to pardon me.
Sorry, but I doubt he's been waiting that long!
I'm in a hurry. Take care!
Wh-What?! Ow!
I'm going to raid the place. Don't we
have one more shadow to recover now?
I get it! Those stairs led to the entrance.
Hey, let go of me!
Stop right there!
What right do I have to decide
whether or not he's still waiting?
This freak... is really strong!
On top of everything you've told us,
answer this one question before you go.
I couldn't tell through all
that fog when we barged in,
Care to say your last farewells?
Sweet! Guys, get ready for our counterattack!
This woman is going to marry me today!
We swore to reunite with my crewmate
off some capes. His name is...
but the stairway up was a shortcut
to the last boss's room...
We're gonna knock
Thriller Bark outta the water!
I can't wait!
Yeah!
...Laboon!
When I saw his corpse in the Land of Ice,
my body wouldn't stop trembling.
I doubt he will forgive us for
irresponsibly dying on him...
Huh? I'm disappearing too?
Why?!
I had never dreamed I'd get to see
that legend with my own two eyes!
"Food, Nami, and Shadows!!
Luffy's Enraged Counterattack!"
Folding stairs...? Is this how
we're supposed to get down?
We made a selfish promise
Nami vanished with him!
and died under a distant sky
where our voices couldn't reach him.
This is a zombie creator's--
Nami!
Hey, Cindry-chan! Why are
you walking in front of me?
Yet another legend shall come back to life!
"I'm sorry we died" could never cut it!
"A Belief Worth Begging to Live For!!
Brook Defends His Afro!"
Whoa! Man, we've been wiped clean!
We gave our word as men that we would return!
What's this pole?
Long time no see, No. 900.
♪ Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho ♪
I might as well see what's at the top.
The zombies must have done it.
There are muddy footprints everywhere.
And that's why he's still alive...
Here I go!
What?! They could still be around.
Laboon...
Now, it's time for him to awaken!
♪ Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho ♪
He is the only berserker to have
gone down in history as a "Devil."
Seriously?
It's him...
Oars!
What a mess!
♪ Yo ho ho ho... ♪
That's strange. I coulda sworn
my arms could stretch...
Yeah, they looted us, all right.
Not that we have anything worth taking.
Weird! Did I dream that up?
"Awakening After 500 Years!!
Oars Opens His Eyes!!"
Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Chopper wasn't there for this, huh?
I wonder if my legs can stretch.
We know him.
Are there any zombies...?
You refuse to quit even
after I flung you outside?
How about the guys in question?
Of course! I will continue to
come back until you return to me!
We know that whale.
Wh-What's that?!
I don't see them.
Is that an earthquake?!
Sheesh! He's a stinking zombie,
so why does Oars have such a free spirit?!
Hey, Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
Do you not know my name?
All cower at the mere mention
of the swordsman Ryuma!
Where are you?! Say something!
What the heck is he doing up there?
He's making a ruckus.
"I Swear to Go See Him!!
Brook and the Cape of Promise!"
Silence! You are my shadow!
They must be inside.
Our bodies are worlds apart!
You know him?!
What makes you so sure?
Why? How'd you meet?
Looks like they don't stretch.
You will come back to me!
You belong under my feet!
We heard that their zombies will also die
Well, darn. I'll just have to climb.
if Luffy and the guys are exposed to sunlight.
Twin Capes is at the
entrance to the Grand Line.
Gotcha. Chopper and Franky,
you two search the first floor.
A freakishly huge whale was there...
What a disaster!
The Humming Swordsman isn't the
only one here who knows our secret!
Robin and I will search the second floor.
Zombies could still be hiding
somewhere on board, so be careful!
Nami-san! I see a mountain up ahead!
This is rottin' bad!
Right!
Man! Hunting down the
zombies with our shadows
"I can't die" is like our secret code.
A mountain?! That can't be!
I don't wanna live in fear of death!
But it's really there!
sounds like it's gonna be a pain.
Who cares?! Go!!
I heard that after a person loses his shadow,
And Luffy's zombie is a real monster!
he gets taken down this long staircase.
Hm?
He's over twice the size of your average giant!
Right! Luffy got carried this way.
I'm not sure you guys can beat him!
Size isn't the only issue!
Luffy, he has your shadow!
We were chasing after him when Nami...
Oh, crap!!
Do you think Nami is okay?
Let's get this underway!
Don't be such a baby!
It's not a mountain!!
It's not like he wants to kill her.
Z-Zoro?
Found them! Hey, I found them!
It's a black wall!!
No, it's not!!
We'll save her when we come back!
Then what is it?!
Size and strength mean nothing.
They're in the dining room!
All three of them are up here!
That's all the more reason to hurry to Sunny!
I-I-It's a whale!!
The only way to get Luffy's shadow
back is to take him down, right?
We'll wake up Straw Hat and the
guys and recover their shadows!
What is that? A-A giant's... corpse?
But the island is infested
with zombies. That won't be easy!
Wh-Wh-What're we gonna do?!
We don't need to search for the zombies.
--Shall we fight?
--Idiot! There's no way we can fight that!
Even for a giant, it's freaking huge!
Luffy!
Speaking of zombies,
how did you take them out?
Although I would like to see mine!
B-B-But our path is blocked!
What're we gonna do?!
What's gotten into you?
That skeleton taught us how. We used this!
Don't make a sound, Chopper!
How... could they do such a thing...?
If we stay like this, we'll never get to
walk under the light of the sun again!
Oh, yeah! I've got an idea!
But remember what that
grandpa zombie told us?
Luffy...? Hey, what're you doing?!
Here, guys, take this.
The zombies had a blast "decorating" them...
I saw what you just did!
You're terribly strong, aren't you?
--What is it?
--The zombies' weakness!
Be still, Straw Hat Luffy's shadow!
It doesn't work! The ship doesn't turn!
You saw how effective it was in my
battle against this spider monkey!
So what did you wanna discuss?
They were merciless.
I am your new master.
This is their weakness? What exactly is it?
--Dammit!
--Don't give up!
There is a man I would like you to defeat.
Wake up, Luffy! Man, you can't
sleep looking like this!
It's salt.
I'm sure you could take him down!
Zombies have a weakness?
Luffy!
He has created countless victims,
C'mon!
I'm about to provide you with a voice and body
So we can purify them if we
stuff salt into their mouths, huh?
Leave this to me.
all of whom could be saved if you defeated him!
so that you may live as a zombie.
You saw what happened!
If we take out Gecko Moria,
everyone will get their shadow back!
Is this it...?!
Forget all of your past relations
and become my obedient soldier!
By the way, what exactly was that
monstrous roar that came from upstairs?
Hey, wake up! This isn't
the time to catch some Z's!
We've got a serious problem here!
Seriously! We followed that sound here.
Cannon?!
That was Luffy's voice.
We have a deal!
All right! Did it stop?
Say what?!
They're still asleep...
Wha...?
I'll tell you all about what we saw.
Do they even have a nervous system?
Y-Yeah, that's what he said...
We should have made Cindry-chan
agree to forget her past, too.
Long story short, we're in big trouble!
They're askin' for it.
He's cutting to the heart
of the problem again...
Guys, outta the way. I'm using my bazooka.
Then I'd actually get to eat on plates.
Ah... We're screwed...
And isn't Moria at the top of that staircase?
Keep it coming! He still wants more!
This might be it...
Nah, it's cool.
I wish I could break your knee caps like plates.
Whoa! He's dead on again!
How much does a Special Zombie eat?
At times like this...
Yikes! Cindry-chan, that threat was super scary!
My special seat...!
So anyway, I'm gonna kick Moria's butt.
He's going to consume
everything on the island!
Let's get out of here before it's too late!!
Cindry doesn't show Hogback
any mercy, does she?
What the heck is going on?!
There's a hot master swordswoman with meat!
That way everyone will get their shadow back.
Did he not notice the cannon attack
because his body's too big?!
Sanji, you're in charge of rescuing Nami!
That was a Hog-smackdown...
Or is he just slow?!
Who knows?! Anyway,
let's get out of here now!
Yeah!
Huh?
You'd better believe I am!
He really stuffs his face...
It's time! Awaken!
I don’t care if he’s an invisible
man or a dismissible sham!
Ahhh! My ears hurt!
Kumacy, why were you
harboring the pirates? Well?!
Paddle! Just paddle!!
I'll kick him to the ends of this fog!
--"Hot"?
--"Meat"?
We have to get away from him!
L-Luffy's shadow...!
--"Master swordswoman"?!
--These guys are hopeless!
B-But I--
Arise from 500 years of slumber!
I'll crash that wedding!
Don't talk! You're so not cute!
Oh, I forgot to mention this earlier,
Sorry, Mini-Shallot!
Luffy...?
but that invisible man
ogled at Nami in the bath.
You...! What the hell did
you do to my special seat?!
You've been feeding me and I
don't even know who you are.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
What?!
'Course, the quantity bites and the food's nasty.
Dumbass!!
Curse him!
Watch it, Special Zombie!
Don't step out of bounds!
Wh-What's happening?
Who do you think gifted us
with the ability to move?!
Did you hear that?
I wouldn't be so rude to the ruler
of Thriller Bark if I were you!
Yeah! Didn't he say 95-55-85?
These are truly...
Don't fire him up any more.
Someday the master is going
to become the King of the--
...miraculous measurements!
I'm afraid he might transform into something.
Wh-What?
Eh?
Damn you, invisible man! You're gonna pay!
I'm terribly sorry! He told me to say all of that.
Luffy's shadow...!
Dude! Don't sell a friend out!
Awesome! He exploded!
I'm hungry! I want more!
Bring him more food.
But he's gobbled up nearly
all of the food on the island.
I feel bad about letting Nami get
whisked away right before my eyes.
--Luffy!
What?
It went in!
We're storing food in the
treasure room in the basement.
This is the one.
I'm going with Sanji!
Feel free to serve that.
Besides, I don't wanna run
into that Warlord again!
That's my Cindry-chan!
Always prepared for anything!
I'm not gonna die!!
That skeleton's duel has me concerned.
--Great!
--I'm impressed that you set
aside emergency rations.
I'm going after him.
If Straw Hat throttles Moria
before he gets to fight,
Huh? But if you give that to Oars,
that will be the end of it.
But we'll have a problem on our hands
if his shadow trashes him first.
it defeats the point of the emergency rations!
I hope we completely run out of food.
I'll join you, Franky.
Thanks to Luffy's silliness,
we got swallowed whole.
That's not nice, Cindry-chan!
Yes, yes. You'll look lovely in this.
Gyoro, Nin, Bao! Run over to
Hogback's mansion and get the food!
Now let's get you changed right quick.
What's the zombie of a legendary samurai
capable of? I'm dying to find out.
Th... The whale ate you?!
We're on it, Master!
Nami-chan and the skeleton...
And that was Laboon, right?
We'll lend a helping hand!
Right. There was an ancient lighthouse
keeper who lived inside the whale.
Don't let those pirates find you!
Simply put, they're the ones
who need immediate help.
Same goes for the Humming Swordsman.
Finally, subduing Moria
is key to claiming victory.
If these guys could remove
the spider monkey's shadow,
What?!
Guys, you're making this sound simple,
they're super bad news!
Flower pops!
Gaaah!
but he's one of the Seven Warlords!
Is it the pirates?! The Humming Swordsman?!
Not a problem! So was Crocodile, remember?
I thought I dropped this,
but here it is! It's the basement key.
Oh, yeah!
And you don't see the problem?!
He nearly killed you!
Don't scare us!
He had been treating Laboon from the inside.
This leads to the basement!
I'm begging you! Please be careful!
Ow!
I've already spelled this out loud
and clear, but your zombie is insane!
What are you doing, geezer?!
Haul the stuff back up--all of it!
The lighthouse keeper was treating him?
Yeah! Hurry! Hurry!
I get it, I get it!
Supposedly he used to be
the medic on a pirate ship.
Now, now! I'm doing it for your own good.
I'm on my way, Nami-san!
If you leered at the naked flesh of
the woman about to wed Absalom-sama,
Yeah? But why did he
need treatment? Was he sick?
he would make you pay dearly!
These are for you. Guys, you each get a bag.
Isn't that right, Absalom-sama?
Master!
He was continually bashing his head
Feed him already!
against the Red Line, which is
like a wall dividing our world.
Yes, sir!
They contain my special
Zombie Ascension Salt Balls.
No! Don't scream!
He's been waiting fifty years for some
pirates who promised to come for him
Oh, is this what you were making
back there? I should have known.
D-Don't tell me...
He was... still...
after they traveled around the world.
You guys have no sense of danger,
so let me make this perfectly clear!
This batch is actually pretty good.
...in here?!
But fifty years...? Those pirates sure
are making him wait a long time...
A salted fish is somewhere in that pile.
We're in rottin' trouble!
Just because these waters
are shrouded in thick fog
I hope he eats it.
doesn't guarantee safety from the sunlight!
What?!
Idiot! This is the Grand Line.
I-It's salted?!
Damn it! He noticed I was still there.
If the Special Zombie eats that, its shadow will--
You're only safe because it's night!
They're dead.
In other words, consider your drop-dead
time limit to be dawn, when the sun rises!
No matter how long he waits,
they won't come back.
If that happens, the master
is going to let us have it!
Yeah, it's true that fifty years ago
the Grand Line was an uncharted sea
Hey! Have the General Zombies congregate
in the ceremony hall! Hop to it!
We have to find it before he does!
No matter what, you can't
forget about this time limit!
more terrible and chaotic than it is now.
Fish... Where is the fish?
C-Certainly!
You're absolutely right! It'd suck
if I couldn't eat before dawn.
Why are you talking so hopeless?!
You don't know that for sure yet!
P-P-Perona-sama...
Shut it! Don't say anything, Kumacy!
Fish! Fish! Fish! Fish!
They might come back!
It's a very touching story!
We're gonna make you rue the
day you picked a fight with us!
What are you doing?
Y-You jerk!
A whale continues to believe in the
promise with his friends... Right, pops?!
Gecko Moria, we're taking back
twice the amount of food you stole!
Help me!
--Give my shadow--
--Calm down! Moria isn't here.
Oh, it's a fish.
Yeah... But reality is cruel.
And before dawn!
Yeah!
Uh, no. That's not what I meant.
Is this salt?
I confirmed it using reliable information.
They ran away... from the Grand Line.
You have to recover your shadows by--
Stupid!
--Let's go!
--Yeah!
This is it! I just know it!
--Uh, no. I meant--
--Nami-san! Take my hand, honey!
The corpse moved!
Hide the thing!
Fine, ignore me!
Huh? Where am I?
That fish looks mighty yummy.
Can't be... Don't tell me...
they left without him?!
Who are they?
On Sunny.
Sunny?! What are we doing back here?
I-I don't think you'll find it to
your liking, Special Zombie-sama!
C-C-Crap! They found us!
This spells trouble! I need to
hurry and inform the master.
I screamed out!
R-Right!
Even if they are alive,
they'll probably never come back here.
A demon has awoken!
Wait... None of that was a dream...!
Hey, Kumacy! Don't tell me
you've been sheltering the pirates!
That's the sort of thing I
have to find out for myself.
Seasons. Weather. Current. Wind direction.
My shadow is missing! This feels so weird.
They are all random. Common sense
is useless in the Grand Line.
My bride! What are you doing down here?
Hey, this is bad! We have a disaster
on hand! We're all out of food!
What are you doing? Do you want
to get eaten along with the fish?
Awesome! This is a ship?
The terror of the Grand Line takes
over weak minds in an instant.
We won't let you escape!
Neat! Too cool!
Shut up!
They abandoned this whale?!
When he's been waiting for fifty years...?!
Crap!
No matter what, don't let him eat this!
We had our galley packed nicely,
but now it's empty.
That's cruel!
If you know that, why haven't you told him?
Hey! Why are you guys getting
between me and my fish?!
They took off with everything
but some emergency rations.
That whale can understand
what people say, right?
I can't live off cheese and
dried bread! Gimme meat!
I can't see squat on these waters,
Ummm...
I did tell him... everything.
but I see a great future ahead of me!
But...
W-W-We thought this might taste better.
That was a close one.
This is really humiliating. I wasn't
taking things seriously enough!
Right, right!
All righty! With this ship,
I'm gonna become King of the Pirates!
Yeah?
I lost my pirate lunch...
Cheese doesn't cut it! Cheese bites!
Dried meat! Yeah, it's really good!
Where is Oars right now?
I'm starving after all that hard work.
By the way, I don't see Nami-san.
He has climbed to the top of the mast, Master.
I think I'll help myself to some fish.
Oh, about that...
Magnificent!
Is that right?
Listen to me, Laboon! They're not gonna...
Yeah...
How truly overawing!
He's a piece of art! A real devil!
Hey! Really now, Master!
We can't enjoy our Laidback Fever
You let her get abducted?!
with that massive, dream-filled
zombie wandering around the island!
Why didn't you follow her
to the ends of the earth?!
Shhh! Hush!
Sorry! But it's not like
I could just run after them!
Listen, Oars! Five hundred years ago,
you left behind countless legends
That bastard is rottin' bad news!
I understand you don't wanna accept it.
Leave him be! It's just a matter of time.
Who the heck is the jerk?!
I'll get her back before you can bat an eye!
Meat!
as an infamous villain!
But you somehow have to accept it...
He'll calm down before long.
And just now, I resurrected you in
modern times to serve as my subordinate.
Whoa, wait! Please hear me out first!
Laboon!
With Oars on our side,
"Subordinate"? Forget it! I have a dream.
we'll be able to steal shadows
from stronger pirates!
Okay, I'll make this quick.
Laboon!
Generally speaking, there are
two things we need to get back!
I've never heard of a zombie like this before!
We'll start creating
Special Zombies left and right!
Our food, Nami, and our shadows, right?
That's three things!
Wow, I wasn't expecting you
to rank things in that order.
This room is cramped and boring.
Wh-What was that?
I'm going to need stronger mario, Hogback!
First off, let me fill you in
about Nami and your shadows.
It's since then that he started
howling at Reverse Mountain
I'm gonna head on outside.
Maybe I'll set sail and travel
once around the world.
Just leave that to me.
I'm hungry!
and that he started slamming
his body against the Red Line...
A voyage around the world?!
Moron! That's impossible!
It's as if he's insisting that they'll come back
from the other side of that wall any time now...
This special freezer is encased in
a super thick wall made of steel!
Kumacy, don't let go of me!
--Okay!
--What?!
You couldn't put a dent in--
What a whale...
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
When there's no point in waiting...
Wha--? M-M-Marriage?!
He refuses my words because if he accepts them,
it means that there is no point in waiting.
He's amazing!
Don't be stupid! I won't let that happen!
He's afraid of that more than anything.
H-Hogback-sama!
That's awesome!
He's got guts to marry Nami...
B-Big news! The pirates are...!
He's from the West Blue.
There's no way of going back there now.
--Now zoom!
--Yep!
--Uh-huh!
W-W-Wait, dude!
And there is a giant version of me?
That's why those pirates he came here
with are his only buddies and hope.
That's how you make a zombie?
What is the matter, Hildon?
So you've already found Luffy's
and the cook's zombies, Usopp?
The three pirates we just stole
shadows from awoke on their ship.
Hey! Where are the pirates?
Where did my bride go?
This is rottin' bad! Oars has gone outside!
They ran as fast as their legs could carry them!
They're coming back with their crewmates!
I-I had no idea he was one
of the Seven Warlords...
That's strange. I could have
sworn my arm could stretch.
Boy, can they run!
What?!
The people we stole shadows from
couldn't possibly be awake!
Fear suddenly set in...
Tch! I won't let them escape!
Oh, well.
You guys didn't know?
I-It looks like their friends
whacked them awake!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
Sanji, feed me!
How were we supposed to know?!
Oh, man! I don't have time for this.
They seem to have ties with
the Humming Swordsman!
Huh? Sanji? Who's that?
I believe he must have tipped them off.
That's right! If the zombies act just like us,
Look at the scars on his forehead!
If he continues to hit his head hard
like that, he'll die without doubt.
As proof, all of the pirates
know how to purify the zombies!
then I saw your zombie, Zoro.
What was he like?
It's a strange relationship, but
I've been with him for 50 long years.
Th-They what?!
No different from you.
I can't just stand by and watch him die now.
The zombies are afraid of the pirates.
Hmph!
As such, they are currently
running for their lives!
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame!
--Huh?
--What's that idiot doing?
But I am covered in scars.
When we looked away for a second...
Is he pretending he's mountain
climbing or something?
This is rottin' bad!
I knew he wasn't you,
since he was wearing sandals.
You are going to disgrace yourself by crying,
What was that? What did we just witness?
Gum-Gum...
Run for it!
"Anything but my afro! Anything but my afro!"
...Flower Arrangement!
The corpse started to move
after he inserted Luffy's shadow!
Okay, whatever.
So we need to find a zombie in sandals,
Luffy's giant, and the cook's dogguin.
as you beg me to spare
your life, just like last time.
That's the deal behind these zombies.
Isn't that a mast?
Yep. It's from our ship.
No, that's not how it will go down!
The Wild Zombies, Surprise Zombies,
and Soldier Zombies
This is how Dr. Hogback
brings people back to life...
It's the main mast... Hey! Don't break the ship!
didn't stand a chance against them
before they knew about salt.
Our shadows will come back if we
throw salt in their mouths, right?
That huge creep's ability probably stems from...
Yeah, that's how it works.
Send the General Zombies after them!
I'm getting nowhere!
...a Devil Fruit!
I mustered the courage to strike
down those scary-looking zombies,
Considering the first word out
of his mouth was "meat"...
What the hell are you doing?!
They can defeat the pirates
without getting fed salt!
but they got right back up!
Come to think of it,
where the heck is Absalom?!
...that monstrous giant clearly
has Luffy's personality, huh?
But honestly, I'm amazed you
discovered that weakness.
Uh, about that...
They must have some sort of weakness!
--Yeah...
--Then think back!
All of our info came from that bag of bones,
His wedding ceremony is about to start...
At this rate, I won't get my shadow back
We ran into a penguin in the
breezeway who resembled Sanji-kun.
from how to defeat the zombies
to how to rescue you guys.
The majority of the General Zombies
are attending his wedding.
even if I find my zombie!
Wha...?! Hey, kid!
Don't worry. He doesn't die
even when he's crushed!
And to top it off, zombies have
horrendously scary faces!
Really?! You saw Brook?
I won't kick a woman...
...even if it kills me!
Yeah, I did. And I asked him a
stupid question when I saw him.
What is wrong with those idiots?!
Oh, yeah! So does that mean
he had Sanji's shadow?
Ha! Dummy!
One of the guys got purified.
Oh, yes! Hogback-sama, he'd like
you to get everyone pumped up
What happened?!
See, I totally rejected his very
existence when you first brought him
This picky eater just had
to grill the fish with salt!
I'm sure it does!
There was the samurai who hit
us with the back of his sword!
at the reception in an hour
with your belly dance.
--Huh?
--The idiot! He must have been new.
aboard our ship to join our crew...
What does he think he's doing?!
He grilled the fish with salt...?
May I see your panties?
I suppose I could. Wedding ceremonies
are memories that last a lifetime.
He might be a flimsy skeleton,
No way!
Could this be the zombies' weakness?!
Luffy! What the hell are you trying to do?!
I should make it fun and exciting--
This isn't the time for that!
but when I talked to him,
he had an iron backbone!
B-Bastard! We stole your shadow
the other day, Skeleton!
That was Brook's shadow! And we had no idea!
One fitting for a skeleton...
Make him cancel the wedding right this instant!
All of the strange things on this
island are starting to make sense!
How did you get back?
It's a draw!
Answer my question!
I-I am merely a zombie, so I can't
tell Absalom-sama what to do...
Which zombie did you stuff my shadow into?!
He...
If you don't answer, I'll scatter
fish all across the island!
He was just pretending to make zombies!
I'm strong, aren't I?
He...
That man is making a mockery of human life!
"Fish"?
You wanna defeat me, don't you?!
This incident doesn't call for that beast.
He's a real man!
How is this fulfilling "mankind's dream"?!
Our fight isn't over yet!
So we have to fight again.
So what if you scatter them around?
What?
How is this "resurrecting the dead"?!
Huh? Uh, that's strange...
Your buddies're dead,
but I'm your rival forever.
But it couldn't possibly be salt...
If we weaken them with my ghosts,
I had to ask him...
Dr. Hogback is a truly
wonderful man! I respect him!
the Soldier Zombies should be
fully capable of capturing them.
Eh? "Salt"?
We definitely have to fight again
in order to decide who is stronger.
Don't freak out just because they
learned the zombies' weakness!
S-S-So what if you s-s-scatter that around?
He isn't the least bit
interested in saving people!
After going around the Grand Line,
we'll come back to see you again.
He's just a scumbag!
I will bring all of them here bound up,
It's salt!
When I come back, let's fight again!
Chopper...
so go prepare mario for the rest of the crew.
Well, you'll have to pardon me.
You don't have time to lament over that now!
I'm in a hurry. Take care!
I'm going back to my room.
Our pals fell victim to his
game of make-believe zombies!
Stop right there!
Come on, Kumacy.
On top of everything you've told us,
answer this one question before you go.
Zombies really are insanely scary!
I hate nighttime!
Okay! I'm coming.
Don't you see? We're the
only ones who can save them!
Let's hurry! They carried
Luffy's body down this way!
You know how people will react
She has a point. She certainly is reliable.
Hmmm. This is good.
Right! The perv said to take him to the ship.
I should have expected as much
from the Ghost Princess!
if you appear before them
as you are now, don't you?
J-Jeez... It was just a grasshopper.
This is the symbol of our
promise to fight again.
I wonder if he meant Sunny.
Yes?
You could learn a thing or two...
You're a talking skeleton!
You'll never make friends.
If Zoro and Sanji met the same fate,
we might find them there!
Until we come back, don't remove that
mark by hitting your head. Got that?!
It gave me a fright.
But it's dangerous for me to
be out during daylight hours.
...from Kumacy.
What?!
Plus it's easy for enemies to find me then.
I swear, those guys...
The abnormal are ostracized.
A-At any rate, it looks like everything
will be all right, Moria-sama.
...can be such a handful!
I've got it! I'll sing!
Franky, what are you...?
When I'm scared, singing can
serve as a good distraction.
Oh, really? That's no fun.
All right!
Even if you leave the Devil's Sea,
your fate is sealed...
I'll be careful not to look at the
zombies' faces as I swiftly purify them.
Really, now! We all know
you weren't going to help...
See ya, flower pops! Thanks for the log pose!
I'm bound to run into my shadow eventually!
Yeah. Have a safe trip!
I'm going to stay here for a while.
And to make matters worse, you've spent
the past several decades trapped here!
See ya, whale! I'm leaving now!
I want to play with Oars.
Then I have a favor to ask of you.
Didn't you say, "I got so
lonely that I wanted to die"?
To Whisky Peak...
Since Absalom is currently preoccupied,
If I were you, I would have
taken my own life ages ago.
...full speed ahead!!
please give me command over two zombies.
Usopp! Chopper!
Yeah!!
Whatever. Pick out two
and take them with you.
Your existence bites...
Where is that song coming from?
Sometimes you act like a gentleman
to hide the core of the conversation.
Who's humming?
Thank you very much!
You're doing all of this because
you want to keep a promise...
In that case, I know just the two I want.
Who're you?!
What exactly did you promise your crewmates?
Are you okay?
Wh-What?! Ow!
Luffy got him to stop killing himself
by hitting his head on the wall,
You're rather nosy, aren't you?
Hey, let go of me!
He's here!
It's quite simple.
so he's still alive...
Long ago, we left a member of my
crew behind at a certain location.
--Where is Moria?!
--Stay away!
Even now, he's waiting for his
crewmates back at those capes.
It was unavoidable, yet sad.
Get outta my way!
This freak... is really strong!
No!
Give my food back!
When we set sail, we vehemently
swore that we would return.
It's an unbelievable story.
What's the deal? What is
happening on this island?!
Both sides have been keeping
their promise for fifty years!
Care to say your last farewells?
He appears out of the darkness while humming.
But then we were annihilated on these seas,
This scary-looking swordsman
is searching for his shadow!
I had no idea one of the people
Laboon has been waiting for...
preventing us from keeping our promise.
Who's the bastard that peeped on
Nami-san when she was bathing?!
This woman is going to marry me today!
He's wiped out practically
all of the Soldier Zombies!
As the sole survivor from our ship,
it is my duty to tell him what has happened!
He's rottin' dangerous!
Show yourself!
Please do something!
Moron! If I can't protect a single woman...
...was that skeleton!
Perona-sama, we have a problem.
I believe it has been... fifty years
now since the day we died.
Shut it! Don't wake me up, Kumacy!
Get up!
...there was no point in being born a man!
Fifty years?! Hey, that was ages ago!
Wow! Usopp, that weapon--!
They don't even need salt.
Their hearts are burning with anger.
I, too, have grown stronger
during these past five years!
Wh-Why does Usopp have it...?
I wasn't even born yet!
Aren't they worried about their shadows?
Sorry, but I doubt he's been waiting that long!
At last we meet!
Eat this!
What right...?!
"Moria's Dance Hall"
C-Captain! Five pirates are headed
straight for the dance hall!
We share the same thought patterns!
"Gyaa!" "Waah!"
Six Chamber Viper Star!
"Racing to the Dance Hall"
What right do I have to decide
whether or not he's still waiting?
There are two on the lower bridge!
"Moria's Dance Hall"
"Perona's Room"
"Wonder Garden"
"Racing to the Dance Hall"
"Headed for Perona's Room"
All of them are too much for us!
Th-These guys are rottin' bad! Retreat for now!
He's vanishing again!
If he's still waiting for us,
believing that we'll keep our promise...
Huh? I'm disappearing too?
Why?!
--They're here!
--Run for it!
Can you imagine how lonesome he must feel?
I see you still hold your afro dear.
Nami vanished with him!
If he's still waiting while under
the belief that we've betrayed him,
Nami!
You cannot possibly hope to
defend such a large weakness.
Where are you?
Silence!
can you imagine how miserable he must be?
It ticks me off when I think about how
these weaklings managed to catch me!
Man...
What's that?
If you're willing to adore me for setting ya free,
Some strong odor is masking his scent!
Why is he so strong? Isn't this
zombie supposed to be me?
We swore to reunite with my crewmate
off some capes. His name is...
Laboon, do you still remember us?
I'll let ya call me "Bro."
Save me, Usopp! Cho--
In your dreams!
Hey, Nami! What happened?
...Laboon!
Where are you?
Crap! I completely forgot!
He was a young whale,
What's wrong? What is it?
so we couldn't possibly bring him
with us on our dangerous voyage.
Answer me, Nami!
My heart grows tight
whenever I think about you.
A whale...?
Ghosts!
Yeah...
Zombies, I'll let you take over from here!
I can't keep up!
And here we use the same style!
Although I don't have a heart anymore!
Catch those two and bring
them before Moria-sama!
Goodbye!
I can't take it anymore! In my next life,
I hope I'm reborn as a mosquito larva.
Later! Take care!
We were not strong enough to face
the harsh cruelty of the Grand Line!
I hope my eyebrows curl up
too much and I become an idiot.
Surrender!
It will end the same no matter
how many times you come after me.
Shoot! Which direction
is his voice coming from?
All of our friends have died!
Hey! Luffy! Sanji! What's gotten into you two?!
If you would like to increase
your speed somewhat,
Nami, where are you?
I imagine he's grown rather big by now.
I shall cut that troublesome afro.
Usopp, behind you!
Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive!
D-Don't! At the very least,
please leave my afro alone!
Your crewmate... is a whale?
Robin, what just happened?
What's that?! A zombie in armor?!
Those ghosts did it! They can
dishearten you with a touch.
That's right. I can't help but
think he still believes in us.
Anything but my hair!
Why don't you understand?!
As for me, I lost everything along with
my crewmates, including my face and body...
As of right now, we don't
know how to counter them...
If you're my shadow, why don't you
understand how important this afro is?
A bunch of zombies are downstairs, too!
What?!
Sweet! I caught him!
Time has stopped for my body,
Perhaps he thinks we'll play
our typical lively music
Even if we were to meet again,
you probably wouldn't recognize me
Wh-What now?
so it would never grow back!
We got this one!
Hey, this looks bad!
and come back waving.
We've got a bunch of zombies upstairs!
now that I've been reduced to a skeleton!
--Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive!
--Crap! They caught both of them!
Hey, pirates! Hand over your shadows!
What of it? I have forgotten
all about the days I served you.
I doubt he will forgive us for
irresponsibly dying on him...
Luffy! Sanji!
Ch-Chopper, don't get caught!
They'll take our shadows.
Shoot! Now that it's come to this--!
My current masters are
Moria-sama and Absalom-sama!
Lead Star!
We made a selfish promise
R-Right!
and died under a distant sky where
our voices couldn't reach him.
Hurry!
Shadows...!
A skeleton that treasures its afro
is nothing short of ridiculous!
Your shadows...!
"I'm sorry we died" could never cut it!
If we lose heart like them, it's game over!
Hand over your shadows!
P-Please stop! Anything but my afro!
Anything but my afro!
Our only hope is to carry them and run!
We gave our word as men that we would return!
There is even a zombie painting!
Anything but my afro!
Not my afro! Not the 'fro!
Don't! Don't!
No!
Don't hurt my afro!
The ghosts are coming after us!
No! I don't want everyone to get caught!
Damn it! You guys play dirty!
And that's why he's still alive...
You're immortal and get to
attack in numbers! It's no fair!
This looks seriously bad!
Laboon...
That's low! Aw, man!
S-Stay back!
All we want is your shadow, bro.
I have nothing left...
Set sail! Set sail!
Crap! Let go! Shoot!
Huh?
But I want to protect this hair,
which everyone said resembled you!
We can't let them catch us!
Seriously?
That was a dirty move!
Are you not ashamed of yourself?!
It's him...
Seeing them like this, they look just alike!
We're falling!
Brook's hair really resembles Laboon!
Say what you will! There is a reason
why I cannot afford to lose!
Usopp! Sanji!
Wait!
Hey, Brother!
Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Chopper wasn't there for this, huh?
There's more?!
I will protect the last remnant of who I was!
Fork over your shadows!
I swear I will go see you!
You are most pathetic, former master.
I am sorry. I admit defeat...
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
So I'd like you to keep waiting...
Wasn't that...? No, it couldn't be.
Please let me go...
...at the capes...
I will leave this island...
But I wasn't expecting that!
The stairs have completely vanished.
You...! What the hell did
you do to my special seat?!
Then leave at once!
Wh-Wh-What was that? What happened?
...where we made our promise.
A bunch of zombies, Usopp, and Sanji...
If you were to die, it would affect me as well.
Give us your shadows!
The whole lot of them fell
when the stairs gave out.
Grah! W-We... We're doomed...!
Save me!
Forget about those two
who came hurtling down.
I love that bag of bones
and that whale, dammit!
That was the epitome of disgrace.
What the hell is that?
Shuddup!
Say what you will!
It came out of nowhere
and it's blocking our path!
Now I'm getting excited!
Hey, someone else is here!
What is this wall?!
He's a musician, a talking skeleton,
has an afro, goes "Yo-ho ho!"
I'm strong, aren't I?
Our buddies are getting purified!
and was Laboon's pal!
Our fight isn't over yet!
So we have to fight again.
Dammit! What just happened?
Ow, ow, ow... What was that...?
He's coming aboard our ship,
even if I have to drag him.
While waiting for my chance to return,
Your buddies're dead,
but I'm your rival forever.
I have spent these past five years...
He's joining our crew! Any objections, guys?
We definitely have to fight again
in order to decide who is stronger.
...growing stronger!
This isn't made out of stone...
You'd better get your mitts...
If there were, would you change your mind?
After going around the Grand Line,
we'll come back to see you again.
Weapons Left!
I wanna help him see Laboon again!
...off my sworn little brothers, punks!
What?! It wasn't effective?
When I come back, let's fight again!
You've got my vote, dammit!
C-Certainly!
No! What the heck are you two doing?!
Hmmm. This is good.
Same here, dummy!
I'm not afraid of that skeleton!
This is the symbol of our promise to fight again.
See, this wall suddenly appeared in front of us.
That's a given. I'm more concerned
about stopping Nami-san's marriage!
Until we come back, don't remove
that mark by hitting your head.
Stupid! That's no wall!
That is Luffy's zombie!
Who the heck are those guys?
They're rottin' bad!
What?!
Absalom-sama!
Hey, Zoro! Where are you going?
You better be ready to hold the wedding.
Big Bro!
I'm going to raid the place. Don't we
have one more shadow to recover now?
Yes, yes. We can start whenever you like.
We know him.
Robin!
This is...
My, what a lovely bride!
Sweet! Guys, get ready for our counterattack!
Did we take too long? We're short one.
Luffy's...
We know that whale.
We're going to start right away!
...z-zombie?!
Get her dressed and bring
her to the ceremony hall.
We're gonna knock
Thriller Bark outta the water!
Usopp, Chopper, are you two all right?
All right! I'm on it.
Yeah!
--Go!
--You're coming, stupid!
"On the next episode, Oars' entry into
the fight suddenly changes everything!"
Unforgiveable! Who's trying
to marry Nami-san?!
That cape on the Grand Line...?
That right? So that skeleton
helped you out, huh?
Now do you see just how
terrifying my ghosts are?
If you're my shadow,
Whoa, wait! He's still waiting after fifty years?!
And that's not all!
Oh, I forgot to mention this,
I'm going to wipe out your entire crew!
why don't you understand
how important this afro is?
That punk said he's endured these past
fifty years to keep a promise with a friend.
but when Nami was in the bath,
that invisible man--
Wait! I won't let you wipe us out!
What did you just say?! Wh-Wh-What did
he do when she was in the bath?!
What a touching story!
There is a reason why I can't afford to lose!
Anyone can talk big!
I didn't expect that skeleton
to have a past like that...
He looked her up and down.
Negative Hollow!
A whale friend...
Not my afro! Anything but the 'fro!
"Nami, who has gone missing..."
You've made one terrible mistake.
The bastard!
A-A whale...?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"...is getting married?!"
"I Swear to Go See Him!!
Brook and the Cape of Promise!"
"A Belief Worth Begging to Live For!!
Brook Defends His Afro!"
"Food, Nami, and Shadows!!
Luffy's Enraged Counterattack!"
"Usopp's the Strongest?
Leave Anything Negative to Him!"
"A Man's Promise Never Dies!!
To the Friend Waiting Under the Distant Sky!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!