Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
You are going to disgrace yourself by crying,
"Anything but my afro! Anything but my afro!"
as you beg me to spare your life,
just like last time.
No, that's not how it will go down!
While waiting for my chance to return,
I have spent these past five years...
...growing stronger!
"A Man's Promise Never Dies!!
To the Friend Waiting Under the Distant Sky!"
"Evil..."
A monster that could tower over giants?
Yeah! He's the one who made
all that noise and screamed.
I bet Luffy's zombie is hooting
and hollering as he runs rampant.
Let's hurry!
Hey, look! There's Sunny!
Yeah! That skeleton knew
what he was talkin' about!
Indeed!
Whoosh!
I get it! Those stairs led to the entrance.
I couldn't tell through all
that fog when we barged in,
but the stairway up was a shortcut
to the last boss's room...
Folding stairs...? Is this how
we're supposed to get down?
Whoa! Man, we've been wiped clean!
The zombies must have done it.
There are muddy footprints everywhere.
What?! They could still be around.
What a mess!
Yeah, they looted us, all right.
Not that we have anything worth taking.
Are there any zombies...?
How about the guys in question?
I don't see them.
Hey, Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
Where are you?! Say something!
They must be inside.
What makes you so sure?
We heard that their zombies will also die
if Luffy and the guys are exposed to sunlight.
Gotcha. Chopper and Franky,
you two search the first floor.
Robin and I will search the second floor.
Zombies could still be hiding
somewhere on board, so be careful!
Right!
Found them! Hey, I found them!
They're in the dining room!
All three of them are up here!
Luffy!
How... could they do such a thing...?
The zombies had a blast "decorating" them...
They were merciless.
Wake up, Luffy! Man, you can't
sleep looking like this!
Luffy!
C'mon!
Leave this to me.
Hey, wake up! This isn't
the time to catch some Z's!
We've got a serious problem here!
They're still asleep...
Do they even have a nervous system?
They're askin' for it.
Guys, outta the way. I'm using my bazooka.
Nah, it's cool.
At times like this...
There's a hot master swordswoman with meat!
--"Hot"?
--"Meat"?
--"Master swordswoman"?!
--These guys are hopeless!
Did you hear that?
Yeah! Didn't he say 95-55-85?
These are truly...
...miraculous measurements!
This is the one.
Yes, yes. You'll look lovely in this.
Now let's get you changed right quick.
Oh, yeah!
Ow!
What are you doing, geezer?!
Now, now! I'm doing it for your own good.
If you leered at the naked flesh of
the woman about to wed Absalom-sama,
he would make you pay dearly!
Isn't that right, Absalom-sama?
D-Don't tell me...
He was... still...
...in here?!
We're in rottin' trouble!
Damn it! He noticed I was still there.
Hey! Have the General Zombies congregate
in the ceremony hall! Hop to it!
C-Certainly!
Y-You jerk!
--Give my shadow--
--Calm down! Moria isn't here.
Huh? Where am I?
On Sunny.
Sunny?! What are we doing back here?
Wait... None of that was a dream...!
My shadow is missing! This feels so weird.
Hey, this is bad! We have a disaster
on hand! We're all out of food!
Crap!
We had our galley packed nicely,
but now it's empty.
They took off with everything
but some emergency rations.
I can't live off cheese and
dried bread! Gimme meat!
But...
This is really humiliating. I wasn't
taking things seriously enough!
I lost my pirate lunch...
Cheese doesn't cut it! Cheese bites!
By the way, I don't see Nami-san.
Oh, about that...
Yeah...
You let her get abducted?!
Why didn't you follow her
to the ends of the earth?!
Sorry! But it's not like
I could just run after them!
Who the heck is the jerk?!
I'll get her back before you can bat an eye!
Whoa, wait! Please hear me out first!
Okay, I'll make this quick.
Generally speaking, there are
two things we need to get back!
Our food, Nami, and our shadows, right?
That's three things!
Wow, I wasn't expecting you
to rank things in that order.
First off, let me fill you in
about Nami and your shadows.
Wha--? M-M-Marriage?!
Don't be stupid! I won't let that happen!
He's got guts to marry Nami...
And there is a giant version of me?
That's how you make a zombie?
So you've already found Luffy's
and the cook's zombies, Usopp?
I-I had no idea he was one
of the Seven Warlords...
Fear suddenly set in...
You guys didn't know?
How were we supposed to know?!
Oh, man! I don't have time for this.
That's right! If the zombies act just like us,
then I saw your zombie, Zoro.
What was he like?
No different from you.
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame!
But I am covered in scars.
I knew he wasn't you,
since he was wearing sandals.
Okay, whatever.
So we need to find a zombie in sandals,
Luffy's giant, and the cook's dogguin.
Our shadows will come back if we
throw salt in their mouths, right?
Yeah, that's how it works.
But honestly, I'm amazed you
discovered that weakness.
All of our info came from that bag of bones,
from how to defeat the zombies
to how to rescue you guys.
Really?! You saw Brook?
Yeah, I did. And I asked him a
stupid question when I saw him.
See, I totally rejected his very
existence when you first brought him
aboard our ship to join our crew...
He might be a flimsy skeleton,
but when I talked to him,
he had an iron backbone!
One fitting for a skeleton...
He...
He's a real man!
I had to ask him...
Well, you'll have to pardon me.
I'm in a hurry. Take care!
Stop right there!
On top of everything you've told us,
answer this one question before you go.
You know how people will react
if you appear before them
as you are now, don't you?
You're a talking skeleton!
You'll never make friends.
The abnormal are ostracized.
Franky, what are you...?
Even if you leave the Devil's Sea,
your fate is sealed...
And to make matters worse, you've spent
the past several decades trapped here!
Didn't you say, "I got so
lonely that I wanted to die"?
If I were you, I would have
taken my own life ages ago.
Your existence bites...
Sometimes you act like a gentleman
to hide the core of the conversation.
You're doing all of this because
you want to keep a promise...
What exactly did you promise your crewmates?
You're rather nosy, aren't you?
It's quite simple.
Long ago, we left a member of my
crew behind at a certain location.
It was unavoidable, yet sad.
When we set sail, we vehemently
swore that we would return.
But then we were annihilated on these seas,
preventing us from keeping our promise.
As the sole survivor from our ship,
it is my duty to tell him what has happened!
I believe it has been... fifty years
now since the day we died.
Fifty years?! Hey, that was ages ago!
I wasn't even born yet!
Sorry, but I doubt he's been waiting that long!
What right...?!
What right do I have to decide
whether or not he's still waiting?
If he's still waiting for us,
believing that we'll keep our promise...
Can you imagine how lonesome he must feel?
If he's still waiting while under
the belief that we've betrayed him,
can you imagine how miserable he must be?
Man...
We swore to reunite with my crewmate
off some capes. His name is...
...Laboon!
He was a young whale,
so we couldn't possibly bring him
with us on our dangerous voyage.
A whale...?
Yeah...
Goodbye!
Later! Take care!
I imagine he's grown rather big by now.
Your crewmate... is a whale?
That's right. I can't help but
think he still believes in us.
Perhaps he thinks we'll play
our typical lively music
and come back waving.
I doubt he will forgive us for
irresponsibly dying on him...
We made a selfish promise
and died under a distant sky where
our voices couldn't reach him.
"I'm sorry we died" could never cut it!
We gave our word as men that we would return!
And that's why he's still alive...
Laboon...
Seriously?
It's him...
Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Chopper wasn't there for this, huh?
You...! What the hell did
you do to my special seat?!
I'm strong, aren't I?
Our fight isn't over yet!
So we have to fight again.
Your buddies're dead,
but I'm your rival forever.
We definitely have to fight again
in order to decide who is stronger.
After going around the Grand Line,
we'll come back to see you again.
When I come back, let's fight again!
Hmmm. This is good.
This is the symbol of our promise to fight again.
Until we come back, don't remove
that mark by hitting your head.
We know him.
We know that whale.
That cape on the Grand Line...?
Whoa, wait! He's still waiting after fifty years?!
What a touching story!
I didn't expect that skeleton
to have a past like that...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"I Swear to Go See Him!!
Brook and the Cape of Promise!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!