Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
That's right. You are the man
who stole one of my dreams!
He out-negatived the Negative Ghosts!
You're going to kick my butt?
Negative Hollow!
We're gonna make you rue the
day you picked a fight with us!
Yeah, you heard me!
Listen... When it comes to thinking negatively...
But considering your level of strength,
you couldn't even lay a hand on me!
Gecko Moria, we're taking back
twice the amount of food you stole!
Who the hell are you...?!
I put a lot of thought into my dream!
Brick Bat.
...I'll have you know I'm unbeatable!
And before dawn!
Gatling!
If I ate the fruit, I'd use my abilities
to watch women bathe!
Yeah!
Wow! He's super confident in a bad way!
This spells trouble! I need to
hurry and inform the master.
No! Just think of all the things I could
use it for. I could... watch women bathe!
Damn it! He's blocking all of my punches.
No, Just imagine how I could help others.
I could... watch women bathe!
What?!
Playtime is over, Special Zombie Oars.
Phantom Hand!
My name is Captain Usopp.
The people we stole shadows from
couldn't possibly be awake!
Phantom Leg!
Ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow!
Chop him down from the legs!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Why?! Why aren't you falling to your knees?!
I-It looks like their friends
whacked them awake!
Don't follow me!
I'm not about to let go, you sick beast!
Wait, Horo-Horo Chick!
Where's Oars?
My ghost clearly hit you!
There he is! Look up!
Come to think of it,
where the heck is Absalom?!
If you're a mix of a bunch of animals,
I bet you'll make lovely mincemeat!
Stop him, Kumacy!
How did you counter it?
Gum-Gum...
Don't mess with Perona-sama!
Uh, about that...
I didn't do anything to counter it.
...Gatling!
His wedding ceremony is about to start...
I've always been negative!
Extra Hach!
The majority of the General Zombies
are attending his wedding.
What?!
I had no idea that stuffed animal
was so nimble and powerful!
This incident doesn't call for that beast.
Nami-san!
And here he can't even reach
the zipper on his back!
Your lack of experience is going
to make you humiliate yourself
What?
I'm going back to my room.
"The General Zombies Are Down in a Flash!!
Oars Feels Like an Adventure!!"
I came for you!
when you underestimate others, greenhorn.
Why, you...!
Come on, Kumacy.
You jerk! Now I'm ticked!
Okay! I'm coming.
There she is!
I'm going to stay here for a while.
Skip! Skip! Skip!
Gum-Gum...
I want to play with Oars.
Nami-san!
Why did you jump over the rail?
Trying to run away?
"Blazing Knight Sanji!!
Kick Down the Fake Wedding!"
Then I have a favor to ask of you.
Get your grubby hands off her!
...Stamp!
Sorry to have kept your waiting,
Nami-san. Your knight is here.
Where is Moria?!
Stay away!
You're going to kick my butt?
I'm in a foul mood right now.
Give my food back!
That hurt, brat!
Yeah, you heard me!
I don't have time to deal with weaklings like--
Huh?
Take that! So much for me not being
able to touch you, Giant Shallot!
Even if you managed to throttle or kill me,
Shut up, Fur Face!
it would simply mean the zombies
would no longer be my servants.
Now then, I think I might teach
that Horo-Horo Chick a lesson,
Absalom-sama!
Basses Cte!
It wouldn't bring your shadow back.
since she's weaker than me!
It wouldn't?
We're falling!
Nope. My ability allows me
to reign over shadows.
Huh? Where did she go?
Usopp! Sanji!
Over here, Mr. Negative Nose.
This is what you'll have to do
to realize your dream:
You said that you were in a foul mood?
The ghosts' negative powers
don't work on him!
That doesn't begin to describe mine.
Huh? I don't see you.
What a formidable human!
The whole lot of them fell
when the stairs gave out.
Make the person currently
reigning over the shadows--me--
Could she be outside?
I'm so mad I feel like my body could explode!
My Negative Hollow is ineffective?
But that's impossible!
Forget about those two
who came hurtling down.
No, she couldn't be out there...
order the shadows to return to their masters.
There is no such thing as a
human immune to that move!
We're up on a really high fl--whoa!
What the hell is that?
And unfortunately for you, there is bad
blood between us over one other thing!
It came out of nowhere
and it's blocking our path!
Then they'll return to everyone?
D-Damn it...! I told them that
I couldn't defeat the zombies.
What is this wall?!
Yep! Isn't it simple?
I just figured out how
I'm going to take you down.
You'd need to hurt me badly enough
that I'd be willing to comply.
Once I knock you off,
the others will be easy pickings!
But considering your level of strength,
you couldn't even lay a hand on me!
Why didn't they take out a single one?
"A Clear-Clear History? Sanji's Stolen Dream"
This isn't made out of stone...
Wait a sec! This is not what I was expecting!
No! What the heck are you two doing?!
Even if I defeat that woman,
it's obvious that they'll take me out!
That is Luffy's zombie!
All righty!
Shoot! I'm gonna die like this.
"Save Me, Hero!! My Enemy
Is the Immortal Princess!"
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
It's hopeless! No matter
how I look at it, I'm doomed!
"Usopp's the Strongest?
Leave Anything Negative to Him!"
Wha--?!
A shadow?
"Moria's Dance Hall"
"Perona's Room"
I must have made some sort
of mistake a second ago.
I dare you to defeat my clone, Doppelman!
You're going to lose all will to
live when they strike at once.
Usopp and Sanji fell downstairs.
Aren't we going after them?
Four times the negativity! Negative Hollows!
Long ago, I was brimming with
overconfidence and arrogance.
Nah! Those two should be fine!
We need to make our way to Moria
But it didn't take long for me to learn how
important it is to have good subordinates.
and pluck that giant shallot
before it gets up and moves!
They got him!
A-Absalom-sama...
That stinking hurt! You're going
to regret that, Straw Hat!
All of them landed direct hits!
Got it! That's the quickest way
to solve all of our problems.
What's with that guy?
Hey! Outta the way!
That entrance leads to the dance hall
where he stole your shadow, Luffy!
I am the man who will become the
King of the Pirates without lifting a finger.
I will use the strength of others to get there!
Beyond there is a giant freezer.
That's the last place we saw Moria!
You... and I... have bad blood?
Sweet!
All right!
Ever since Thriller Bark got up and running,
Stuff it! I'll kick your butt
as many times as it takes.
I'm the one who will
become King of the Pirates!
no one has been able to
stand up to those ghosts!
Your zombie said the exact same thing.
That's right. You are the man
who stole one of my dreams!
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
He out-negatived the Negative Ghosts!
Why, you--! Get off of me!
Your wish is my command. Brick Bat!
Didn't Perona take you down?!
As you can imagine, when its new
body is nothing like the original,
A-A dream...?
Kumacy, sorry I'm always so mean to you.
The effect has spread back to Perona-sama!
Hogback...!
the shadow retains even more
of its original master's personality.
Is that man a sage or a saint?!
Doesn't ring any bells.
Not again!
Who is that reindeer?
There must be some sort of misunderstanding.
But that doesn't last forever!
You and I...
So that is Dr. Hogback...
Gum-Gum Finger Net!
Listen... When it comes to thinking negatively...
...met for the first time today!
Eventually, it will forget
everything pertaining to you.
He was with Moria!
It will become a zombie
that is completely loyal to me!
May I give him a sound beating?
...I'll have you know I'm unbeatable!
I'm going to send you flying...
H-Hold your horses!
No matter how strong a zombie's will might be,
...with my Hands of the Dead!
Wait, Luffy.
it will ultimately serve me unconditionally!
Wow! He's super confident in a bad way!
Could you leave him to me?
See that doorway in the back?
There's no end to this!
I'm getting it back in just a sec!
It leads to the freezer. Go on ahead!
Take them off.
Gum-Gum...
Okay, you got it!
Brick Bat.
But why is it? For someone bursting
with confidence, he looks mighty small.
I said to drop the bazookas
attached to your arms.
...Gatling!
You can't skip straight to Moria-sama!
Learn some manners!
Isn't he trying to escape?
Wha--?!
Cindry-chan, get him!
--Busted!
--Wait!
Damn it! He's blocking all of my punches.
Do I need to spell it out?
Certainly.
Crud! They saw through my plan.
One!
If Nami-san gets hurt
because you went overboard,
Wild Shot: Salt Star!
Two!
What was that? A plate?
no one will be able to tell you were ever
alive by the time I'm through with you!
Looking good, Cindry-chan!
Ow, ow!
Why... are you... flying in the sky?
He couldn't possibly know
what I've got up my sleeves!
Ow, ow, ow!
I won't miss again.
Curse you! You've started to purify
my darling Wild Zombies yet again!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
This doesn't make any sense!
I said to lose the bazookas!
Three!
Just a minute ago, she was running
like her life depended on it.
Where'd all this confidence come from?
Stay away from me! Salt Star!
What's the matter, Cindry-chan?
Ow, ow, ow!
He's got salt! Be careful!
What's that?!
Feel free to go ahead, Luffy.
'Kay! Thanks, Robin!
You merely caught me by surprise back there.
Wow! A bazooka magically materialized!
Covering your mouths is against the rules!
Wait, dammit! Straw Hat!
You're a rowdy brat.
Hogback!
I wish I had kept that "Salt Star" part to myself!
Yeah, that's about what I thought.
Shut up!
It seemed like the type of attack
you would come up with.
You jerk!
Why?! Why aren't you falling to your knees?!
You can make yourself invisible.
You've disappointed me!
I refuse to consider you a doctor!
While in that state, you can make
anything you touch go invisible as well.
I can't believe Usopp's
negative outlook came in handy!
I've always been negative!
Kick his butt! Trample him!
That is your current ability.
But watch out for his salt!
If it weren't for him,
she could have wiped us out!
I didn't recognize you, Dr. Chopper!
Invisible man born of the Clear-Clear Fruit,
What?!
She's got one terrifying ability...
I know every possible move you could make!
You were a Zoan type power holder?
Crap! I'm the only one who can
stand up to the Horo-Horo Chick!
No wonder I thought you were
such a peculiar creature...
--Hey...
--Huh?
Who the hell are you...?!
It never occurred to me that someone
might be immune to my Negative Ghosts.
This is where our paths diverge.
I'm gonna head over to Nami-san!
I don't know how you escaped
on your way to Perona's garden,
Has that man met Absalom-sama
somewhere before?
This was supposed to be
my time to shine, darn it!
Got it! Be sure to save her!
You bet! I'm the Will-o-the-wisp of Love!
Why does he know his powers inside and out?
I have just one thing to say to you.
but that won't happen again
now that I've run into you!
All of the other pirates quickly
succumbed to my Negative Ghosts...!
I will get your shadow!
What could this "bad blood" possibly be?
Nami-san!
There are plenty of good things in life!
Drop it!
Back when I was a kid, I read an
encyclopedia on the Devil Fruit.
Nah. How about I kill you
and use your body as a mario?
I won't let you get married!
So what if you can fly?!
I had no interest in a shady object that
would make the ocean grow to hate you.
He jumped...
I'm a sniper! I don't care if you
can fly or dance or whatever!
Wasn't this pretty high up?
They'll do the dirty work!
Allow me to explain.
Well, supposedly an adrenaline rush
can dull a person's sense of pain.
But there was one and one
alone that caught my interest.
My new weapon, Kabuto,
Mackerel... I'm worse than mackerel...
has greater stability and range
thanks to these five prongs.
Anyway, we need to reach
that mansion's top floor!
I decided that in the unlikely
event I came across that Fruit,
If I activate the Breath Dials I got
at the sky island when I shoot,
Yeah! I want a feral dog to step on me!
That penguin...!
--Yeah!
--That's where we'll find the skeleton!
I would eat it, even if it meant
losing the ability to swim!
Sanji's shadow is inside of it!
Huh? Then what about the other one?
the rotation of my ammo changes,
creating different effects!
I'm sorry for walking on the same earth...
But there aren't two identical
Devil Fruits at the same time!
It's like a super Pachinko!
...as everyone else!
I never expected one of the men to be immune!
Flame! Flash! Impact!
If I ran into someone with that ability,
my dream would go up in smoke!
By changing the Dials, my ammo
can grow even more powerful!
I've always been negative!
No one can escape this puppy!
Now do you get it? I wanted
to become an invisible man!
That's right! If the zombies act just like us,
What?!
then I saw your zombie, Zoro.
Now say your pray--
That's why I said that you've
crushed one of my dreams,
She's gone!
What was he like?
since you ate the Clear-Clear Fruit!
Huh? Where'd she go?
No different from you.
But that's all right. I'll just have
the Wild Zombies kill Mr. Long Nose.
He's venting?!
I put a lot of thought into my dream!
I'm behind you.
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame!
If I ate the Fruit, I'd use my
abilities to watch women bathe!
Drat! I can't use my Salt Stars like this!
They aren't anything alike!
No! Just think of all the things I could
use it for. I could... watch women bathe!
Indeed not.
How am I supposed to pull out of this? How?!
Go ahead and take your best shot.
No! Just imagine how I could help others.
I could... watch women bathe!
That's it!
Go! Wipe the floor with them!
Okay!
Ehhh?!
Okay, Hogback-sama.
All you're really thinking about is
how you could watch women bathe!
Wh-What in the world are you?!
Y-You got me! Ugh!
Who should we take out first?
Sweet! We killed him!
Shut up! After long years
of imagining what I'd do,
Stupid! Keep your hands over your mouth!
That damn reindeer.
Why, you...!
It might be another one of his tricks!
I am fully aware of what I could see--
Special Attack! Swallowtail Meteor!
Oh, you're right! He's fumbling
around with something.
no, what I could accomplish with that ability!
Hmph! You're wasting your time!
Gah! Sh-She reverted to her original size!
Are you quite finished yet?
Salt!
How are you going to get
the salt in our mouths?
Whoa!
Between this and endangering Nami-san,
Why don't you be a man and admit defeat?
Star! Star! Star!
you have compounded
transgression upon transgression,
You little...! I'm gonna shoot you down!
Just kidding.
making it impossible to forgive you!
Pepper Star!
Mantis Meteor!
Prepare to wave goodbye to watching
women bathe--no, to your life!
What's the problem?
Didn't you have perfect aim?
Here's my chance! Eat this!
This hallway is surprisingly long!
I was wondering what your problem was!
Salt Star!
You're picking a fight over the stupidest thing!
Darn it!
Y-Your complaint is beyond absurd!
Take this! And this, dammit!
Sweet! I finally reached the end!
Mr. Negative Nose, you weasel!
You are like a phoenix... Or perhaps a zombie!
Eat this! Mantis! Swallowtail!
Dragonfly! Mayfly Meteor!
It certainly is.
Now where am I?
I'm not done yet!
You're a freaking pervert!
When it comes to tricking people, I'm--
You shouldn't have the strength left to stand.
Shuddup! Drop the cool act!
You're not one to talk!
You're a loser!
Found ya!
He has a point!
Charge!
Hey! If it isn't you.
I'll stop you in your tracks! Firebird Star!
But they're equally bad!
I am just about ready to fully immobilize you
so that you will never come
after your shadow again.
You missed!
No!
What a klutz!
Sh-Shoot!
What shall I sever with my
special move, the Notch Slash?
Have it your way!
Get him!
Y-Your hands...!
What?!
I will throw your sudden claim of
bad blood and rage right back at you!
Wh-What...?
You don't...
Your hands sunk into my body!
Wh-Why is he so freakishly big?!
You don't know a darn thing...
I-I've been stabbed!
Y-You stabbed me with your bare hands!
Don't use that name!
The lion muzzle wasn't my only transplant!
I'm finished...! I'm gonna...!
Elephant skin!
What is he, some demon lord?!
I've never seen a giant this big before!
300kg of compact bear and gorilla muscle!
I'm dead meat! I'm gonna die from blood loss!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
It's rottin' hot!
Stupid! Take a better look.
Dr. Hogback has conducted one
transplant after the next on this body,
I came from a certain kingdom's assault convoy.
Isn't he a zombie?
Hey, you guys!
I haven't hurt you, but my
hands are inside your body.
The quick slash that I specialized in
was called "Requiem La Banderole."
This is...
Now! Special Attack!
allowing me to become the
ultimate beastly masterpiece!
Luffy's...?
--No!
--Out of my way!
Crap! We're doomed!
The Clear-Clear Fruit's ability is a mere bonus.
If you don't move, I'll start with--hey, wait!
He's here to kill us!
The nickname my crewmates gave
that technique out of admiration was...
Next to my strength, it's nothing
more than an accessory.
Do you know what this means?
Get it?
He's nuts! I can't let my guard
down for a second around him.
Eek! Gulp!
...Three-Pace Hum: Notch Slash!
It's true that you're about to die.
I need to come up with a way
to defeat Negative Nose!
But...
You still peeped!
You may share my personality and abilities,
but I don't want you to use that
name if you cannot remember
I won't let you escape!
You're absolutely right!
Wait, Horo-Horo Chick!
Let me tell you why. I'm just about to
crush your heart with my own two hands.
my past and the feelings I harbor!
Stop him, Kumacy!
If you feel that you are
the true master of this style,
If a normal person kicked me,
my body would break his leg...
The bear zombie?!
Wait!
prove as much by defeating my "fake" style.
Don't! Please don't crush it!
Don't follow me!
But he's kicking me like I'm a normal man...!
Wait, Horo-Horo Chick!
I'll die for real!
Don't follow me!
This is your last chance.
I'm going to kill you.
Don't mess with Perona-sama!
Regardless, I will be the last one laughing!
What's he gonna do now?!
Now writhe in agony as you die!
I have claimed the power you so desired!
No!
I had no idea that stuffed animal
was so nimble and powerful!
And the woman you longed to
protect is about to become my wife!
No! Please stop it! I don't wanna die!
And here he can't even reach
the zipper on his back!
I could not imagine a more bitter defeat!
Why, you...!
When he abducted her,
Nami vanished with him.
I'm sorry if I upset you!
We lost his trail after that!
Whoops! I wanna go this way!
You wanna make Nami-san go invisible!
Not that I can actually do that!
But you can't have her!
That was a bluff?!
I like this!
Ouch! I hit my head!
If I had the physical ability to crush your heart,
Yikes! Stay away!
Sweet! Now I feel the part!
you would have died the moment
my hands pierced through your body.
--Huh?
--Stay back, darn it!
Gah! Don't follow me, bear!
I said to stay back, bear!
I'm gonna become the
rottin' King of the Pirates!
Keep back, dammit!
Either way, that was bad for my heart!
Man, I totally freaked out
when the building collapsed.
You bastard! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Where do you think you're looking?
Wait, you...!
You're wasting your energy!
It's time I showed you...
Wh-What gives?
I merely passed through...
...the power of a Phantom!
Didn't he notice us?
Stay back! Stay away, dammit!
...your body.
I'm not about to lose!
Wait, wait, wait! You little--!
No!
He really sounded just like Luffy.
Huh? Where'd you go?
Huh? Are you over here?
Now I'm mad!
That body with Luffy's fighting
abilities might be a problem!
Three-Pace Hum...
Even though you can clearly see me...
What's this? You're going to
sacrifice yourself for that woman?
No way!
...my body can pass through anything.
Protect her! Assuming you've got what it takes!
Why don't we give up on your shadows?
...Notch Slash!
Stay away!
Phantom Hand!
Phantom Leg!
Keep back, Mr. Negative Nose!
No way!
Even if you convinced me to,
Special Attack! Six Chamber Viper Star!
Don't come after me, bear!
I'd still want to save Nami-san!
Pull yourself together!
Graah!
Seeing them like this, they look just alike!
Brook's hair really resembles Laboon!
The lack of stairs is going to be a problem.
Didn't I just say I can go through anything?
Hey, Brother!
It looks like Usopp and I got knocked
down along with the entire stairway.
Even if we switched to this path,
the bridge here is also toast.
Stop it! This is creepy!
Laboon!
In other words, your attacks can't touch me.
All of the paths leading to the mansion
by the mast have been cut off.
And none of us could make that jump.
More than anything,
I want to apologize to you...
Why, you--! Get away from me!
There goes our shortcut...
Shoo, darn it! You stupid little...!
There'll be gobs of zombies
along the long way...
I wouldn't drop that woman if I were you!
I want to apologize for my endless bad luck...
Just give me thirty seconds!
Now what are you going to do?
None of your attacks will work on me.
Fifty years on the dark sea...
Time has passed so slowly...
Something about this design
doesn't seem right...
Shut up! A second ago, you bluffed
that you could crush my heart!
Damn beast!
You built a bridge!
I bet you couldn't touch me if you wanted to!
I can't believe my life was in vain!
I can't attack you, but you can't
attack me, either! Isn't that right?
I could make a bridge or two easy with
all this wood and debris everywhere!
What a lonesome... life it's been!
Let's see...
Mini-Hollow...
But didn't you go a bit overboard with
the details for a makeshift bridge...?
Wh-What are those...?
Yeah!
I've been so lonely...
Are you telling me to do a half-assed job?
Hardly! This was a huge help!
Ghost Rap.
Anyway, you were a lifesaver! Now, let's go!
Sorry, Nami-san...
Now then, where should I begin cutting?
Nice! I'm starting to get really excited!
A-A shock wave?
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
For starters, this afro must go.
Get away from me!
Don't touch me! Get it off of me!
Get it off, meanie!
You dropped her! I guess you didn't
value her as much as your own life.
Rap.
I'm sorry...
What's with this room?
I can't soil your pure
white dress with my blood...
Isn't this room rather ostentatious?
Okay...! Special Attack! Firebird Star!
Skip! Skip! Skip!
Damn invisible man, sneaking around!
Nami-san!
Get your grubby hands off her!
I'm totally over my dream now!
Shoot!
I had planned on sacrificing you to the
zombies on the stairs and the bridge.
It's not fair!
For starters, this afro must go.
How come she can attack me
when I can't attack her?!
I never expected Oars to come crashing down.
I don't care if I can't turn invisible anymore!
How is this even a fight?!
Sorry to have kept you waiting,
Nami-san. Your knight is here.
He just had to interfere!
Whoa! Get outta my way!
I can't see where I'm going! Move it!
I'll peep without any special powers!
Move!!
You're still going to peep?!
What?! The mansion is shaking!
Hey, why is the mansion shaking?
Shake! Shake your hands!
Like I'd know! Maybe there's an earthquake.
Ghost Rap.
One, two, three, four!
Those ghosts...!
Is that the lab?
I never would have suspected
that she was controlling them.
There he is! Hey, Skeleton!
One, two...
What the heck are they?!
Shake your hands!
Dude! You took a royal beating,
but you're still with us, aren't you?
Let go, bastard!
Unhand me!
You already know just how
terrifying these ghosts can be!
You're still alive, right?!
Wh-What are you doing here...?
I'm not about to let go, you sick beast!
Man, I feel like I haven't gone
swimming in ages. I wonder why...
If you're a mix of a bunch of animals,
I bet you'll make lovely mincemeat!
Do I sink like a rock?
I can't allow this! You should
not touch the loser in a duel!
Shut up, jerk!
I can't remember!
Having eaten the Hollow-Hollow Fruit,
Let go of me!
Well, it's all good!
I am an incorporeal human
capable of creating ghosts at will.
Whoa, there!
Where did he go?
Ho-hoy!
These ghosts are my clones.
Is it you?
Are you the legendary samurai who
supposedly killed a dragon a long time ago?
They make people's hearts feel hollow.
I'm done going easy on him.
You've reached the end of the line!
Ghost Rap.
Extra Hach!
I can't believe that cutie is the mastermind
behind those annoying ghosts!
I've been wanting to see you!
Save that for later!
If her attack hits us, we'll be goners in no time!
Absalom-sama!
What's going on up there?
The whole place is shaking!
Our only option is to flee!
I can't fight ghosts!
The ship has probably gotten
caught in a weird current.
Run for it!
I think it's probably your fault, too!
Negative Hollow!
What the heck? Why am I failing so hard?
So, what do you want? What brought you here?
I never expected this!
Right. You had some nerve,
tearing off my shadow earlier.
A beast should be satisfied
with watching women bathe--
And here... I thought that
woman was weaker than me!
I'm drowning!
I'll be taking my shadow back.
Scratch that! With a beastly bride.
Tada!
Right along with Zoro's, Sanji's, Brook's,
the grandpa zombie's, and everyone's!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
The bear!
Careful, there. Kumacy is
stronger than a real bear.
Let go of me!
You're one greedy bastard!
How are you going to get them back?
Mackerel... I'm worse than mackerel...
That was rather rash of you.
Yeah! I want a feral dog to step on me!
Ow, that hurts!
What if you had swallowed the salt water?
I'm gonna kick your butt!
What gives?!
--Ow, ow, ow! L-Let go!
--Don't worry. They won't suck your blood.
I was so excited when I was
the only one in my entire crew...
You could handle a little,
I'm sorry for walking on the same earth...
but if you drank a lot,
the salt would purify you.
What was that about
kicking my butt? What a joke!
...who stood a fighting chance
against this chick's powers!
...as everyone else!
It's over! It's all over!
Man, I thought I was gonna die!
You guys--your abilities--
are powerless before this chick.
Really! You can be such a handful.
Get away from me!
Leave me alone!
I'll take her on!
Smooch! Smooch! Smooch! Smooch!
Apprehend them.
Yes, ma'am!
Smooch! Smooch!
Smooch! Smooch! Smooch!
Your lack of experience is going
to make you humiliate yourself
Nami-san, you're in safe hands--
when you underestimate others, greenhorn.
Smooch! Smooch! Smooch!
Smooch! Smooch! Smooch!...
That was too easy.
Damn it! Gum-Gum...
Now to deal with the group upstairs.
M-My word! Is she a goddess?
Brick Bat!
This is my chance to shine!
Just a second! Why is the ship shaking?!
Wild Shot: Salt Star!
After a declaration like that,
how could I end up like this?
Uh, no. It's Nami-san. It really is Nami-san.
I can't kiss my bride!
Ow, ow, ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow!
I'm screwed... This is the end!
There is no way I can beat her!
Absalom-sama!
What is it? Do you know what the deal is?
I'm sure of it!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Oh, I was so surprised.
Our giant ship, Thriller Bark,
is caught in a strange current!
Her beauty can be deceptive!
That woman's gonna kill me and then
she's gonna catch Luffy and the guys.
It's changing our course!
For a second, I thought I recued
a goddess by mistake. Phew!
The entire island is shaking!
Who did that?!
Our crew is doomed!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
How did that happen?!
A-A fairy?
The weight of saving everyone was...
too great for me to bear.
Well, it looks like that Special Zombie
is messing with the rudder.
I won't let you...
Oh, I was so surprised.
But this is definitely Nami-san.
What?!
...hurt my crew!
Save me!
Shoot! He only pretended
to get hit by my attack!
Ah, what a relief.
--I thought I accidentally rescued a fairy
by mistake. You're a deceptive little kitten.
--Sheesh! What are you going on about?
It's moving! It's moving!
Take that!
As I recall, you're part of the crew
that was on that pirate ship.
I'll finish you off for real this time.
Save me, Sogeking!
Move!
Move! Move! Move! Move!
You jerk! Now I'm ticked!
A-An angel?
Please tell me! How would you handle this?
Gum-Gum...
General Zombies, all of you are
to set out at once! Stop Oars!
Negative Hollow!
Why did you jump over the rail?
Trying to run away?
N-No, she's human. I'm sure of it.
Ah, she had me scared there!
...Stamp!
Sir!
I was born on the island of snipers
Move! Move! Move!
I don't blame you! I really don't blame you!
Kumacy!
Nami-san and rice are about the only
things that look this good in white!
Stomp!
I never miss my mark
Oars!
Monster! How dare you purify my Kumacy?!
Yeah, seriously!
That hurt, brat!
I know, right? You get it, right?
Lulu lala lu
Why must she look so stinking good in white?!
Take that! So much for me not being
able to touch you, Giant Shallot!
And what's with that goofy mask?!
Whether it's a mouse's eyeball, lock on!!
What?!
--What are they going on about?
--It throws me off.
Playtime is over, Special Zombie Oars.
Or even your heart, lock on!!
Lowly pirate! I don't need
to be chums with you!
My name is Captain Usopp.
It is hardly goofy!
It is a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Sogeking.
Chop him down from the legs!
Why?! Why aren't you falling to your knees?!
The man who hails from the island of snipers
You're totally goofing off!
You aren't a different person!
Where's Oars?
My ghost clearly hit you!
Hey!
How did you counter it?
Time to flee!
You nearly hit Nami-san.
You're making a run for it?!
He vanished! Oars vanished!
Lululu, lulu lala
I didn't do anything to counter it.
You bet I am! I'm not sticking
around for this crazy fight!
When a lady is in the vicinity,
you should avoid attacks that could hit her.
I've always been negative!
But he's so big...
Now... run away!
How could he be so quick?!
I'm impressed you dodged that, bastard!
I use my negative outlook and
bluffs to get through fights!
He's still in hot pursuit!
I see you've already lost your shadow.
What?!
If he was out of the picture,
I could take down the other pirates!
Sogege, soge, soge
Come to think of it, one of our new zombies
was oddly obsessed with that woman.
I never thought someone
would use those against me!
Sogeking!
Stupid Mr. Negative Nose!
There he is! Look up!
He retained some will of his own,
so he wasn't fully subservient.
Are you okay with this?
Gum-Gum...
He's still chasing after me!
Calm yourself! Face her and fight, Usopp-kun!
Actually, I'm not made of rubber.
If he was out of the picture, I could
take down that Horo-Horo Chick!
I won't let you pursue that lady!
Gatling!
Shut up! I've had it!
He held out against the ghost's negative power!
I suspect that was your zombie.
Stupid bear zombie!
There is no way I can beat her!
Wait!
That is not true! You are a very capable man!
This man is incredible!
Considering that your shadow
wasn't put into a General Zombie,
Stay away!
Perona-sama!
Wait, Horo-Horo Chick!
your fighting ability
can't be all that impressive.
Can you prove that?
Stay away! Kumacy, hurry and finish him off!
--No!
--You can't?!
In fact, that penguin talked big,
but was terribly weak!
That's absurd!
Mini-Hollow!
I'm known as one of the Phantoms
and lead the General Zombies.
No one in the world could possibly
be immune to my Negative Hollow...!
But think carefully! There are
several oddities about that woman.
It was impudent of that small fry to defy me!
Perona-sama!
Yeah, you have a point.
A-A heavenly maiden?!
Like how she suddenly got really confident!
People are alive...
That alone should be enough to
keep us looking forward with hope!
At first, she was definitely
running away in fear of me.
Oh, I was so surprised.
Wait!
I thought she was a heavenly maiden. Sheesh!
Horo-Horo Chick!
Listen to me, punk!
She's definitely Nami-san. No mistake about it.
Kumacy!
But this man...!
If my attacks were ineffective from
the start, she didn't need to flee.
Don't you dare harm Perona-sama!
I wasn't sure what I'd do
if she was a divine maiden.
Don't heave a sigh of relief!
She should have been able
to pass through walls and fly!
You know, it doesn't matter how
obsessed you are with that woman!
That was close! Too close!
But all she did back then
was whine while she ran.
I am going to marry her!
Perona-sama!
Now take a word of advice
and leave that woman with me
Why was she so negative?
Hang in there...
That's it!
Rap. Rap!
while you spend the rest of
your life hiding in the shadows!
--Hang in there!
Don't get in the way of my adventure!
Scary!
Hang in there!
The change occurred after I lost sight of her!
Hang in there! Hang in there! Hang in there!
"Live!!" "Hang in there!!!" "Fight!!"
I'm rather busy at the moment!
No!
--Hang in there! Hang in there!
--Don't try to cheer me up!
Your captain's zombie may have crushed
some of my most powerful subordinates.
Annihilated?! But they just left...
Something must have happened!
Sweet!
Uh, right. They're as flat as pancakes.
Snap out of it, guys!
Before I deal with that, I need to kiss my bride!
They composed the strongest
zombie army on the island!
You've gotta hurry and rescue Nami and Brook!
I'm sure you understand.
I'm in a foul mood right now.
They were General Zombies!
Right. They were out in a flash.
I don't have time to deal with weaklings like--
Absurd... Wasn't Oars on our side...?
You guys--your abilities--
are powerless before this chick.
Remember...
Shut up, Fur Face!
Why is he going on a rampage?
I'll take her on!
Absalom-sama!
Zombies have no choice but to obey our orders!
No way! He weighs 300kg!
How did that man send him flying?!
What happened during the brief moment
that bear stalled me and I lost sight of her...?
Dude...!
What will happen to Thriller Bark
if we let him run loose...?
Why does he seem so dependable?
Why is that stuffed animal
so freakishly strong?!
That didn't work on him?
You're the "invisible man"
Usopp mentioned, aren't you?
Wait! Wait!
What happened?
Curse you!
Nami-san!
But take out all of these
zombies before you go!
What was with that kick?
Well, I guess it's about time
I handed you over to Moria-sama.
Oh, yeah!
I can't defeat them! I'm sure I'd die if--
I came for you!
He sent me flying even though
Hogback has transplanted
I'll let you handle things here!
the power of wild animals into my body!
Eh? Uh, no! That's not what I meant!
There she is!
That's it! I've solved the puzzle!
Eat this! Special Attack! Flame Ball!
No! Hold up!
He's part of the Straw Hat Crew!
Yikes, this is bad! It's fire!
Wait!
Hands of the Dead!
Fire!
Are there any hiding spots nearby?
What's going on? Could he
tell what I was about to do?
It worked! It totally worked!
I'm done going easy on you.
Basses Cte!
A zombie is still a zombie!
And with this oil, I'll cast the
"You Cannot Cross This Point" spell!
Longe!
You're the beast that showed up on Sunny
and licked Robin-chan, aren't you?!
Like a hidden room...?
Something has caught me!
What?!
A room!
And you ogled at Nami-san's
bare skin in the bath, didn't you?!
Do you, Absalom, take Nami
to be your wedded wife?
Dumbbear! Now you can't come after me.
Be my blushing bride!
This makes me invincible.
Your trick...!
To have and to hold in sickness and
in health, to love for all eternity?
Tendron! Flanchet! Quasi!
If I don't have to worry about you,
that Horo-Horo Chick will be a pushover!
What is it? Are these your final words?
Why is he so strong?! This is their small fry?!
Amazing...! He pushed Ryuma back.
Yeah, I do!
Queue! Cuisseau! Jarret!
I, like, rule!
Wait! Where do you think you're aiming?!
Who is he?
Why is she unconscious?! You didn't
get rough with her, did you?!
Do you, Nami, swear to love
Absalom for all eternity?
He's a stinkin' aggressive pirate swordsman
who practices the Three-Sword Style.
Now then, I think I might teach
that Horo-Horo Chick a lesson,
That's it!
--Hey, wait!
--Special Attack! Atlas Comet!
He's damn strong!
since she's weaker than me!
If your pride will stand for it,
I bet he'd recover your shadow for you.
"Marriage," my ass!
Take a good look at my eyes.
Yes, I rottin' do! I love Absalom-sama!
Huh? Where did she go?
I'll crush you under my feet
and turn you into croquette!
Over here, Mr. Negative Nose.
What do you say?
Damn it! I'll have to retreat for now.
My shadow? Really? Oh, please do!
Skating!
I'm begging you!
Please recover my shadow for--
Huh? I don't see you.
Then you may kiss the bride.
Could she be outside?
I've got Usopp's salt balls.
Shut up! Keep quiet!
No, she couldn't be out there...
We're up on a really high fl--whoa!
Over there!
--Ploink!
--Hey! Skeleton!
What is that? It's salty!
You know, that looks like a good sword.
Veau Shot!
You have a good eye! This is in fact
one of the 21 O-Wazamono swords.
D-Dang! Why are you flying?!
I thought you could only control ghosts!
Insane! This guy doesn't even have a bounty?
It has a black blade with a reversed saw.
This famous sword is called Shusui.
Wh-What exactly is your power?!
You said that you were in a foul mood?
It's not the sort of thing you see every day.
That doesn't begin to describe mine.
Don't underestimate the power
of the Ghost Princess, moron!
So it's a sweet sword? Looks like
I've come across a nice find!
I found it!
I'm so mad I feel like my body could explode!
I just figured out how I'm
going to take you down.
It did!
Of course, I figured you'd have something
halfway decent since you're a samurai...
That is your real body.
Once I knock you off,
the others will be easy pickings!
And unfortunately for you, there is bad
blood between us over one other thing!
All right! I'll be using that sword from now on.
Wait a sec! This is not what I was expecting!
You're too cool!
Ploink!
Usopp Eye can find any opponent's weakness!
Nami-san! I will never
leave your side ever again!
What's this?
You and I have some bad blood?
When I pull it, the whole
ship moves. This is fun!
What's wrong? You haven't
landed a single attack on me.
That's right! You... You...!
Usopp Weapon has defeated
multiple formidable foes!
--Right! I will always be with you!
--Bastard! We were in the middle
Just a sec! See, I can attack
by sniping, being negative,
Nothing comes to mind.
And Usopp Brain can devise awesome strategies
to pull me out of any sticky situation!
Let's go starboard next!
--No, for all eternity!
--of an important ceremony!
I just met you for the first time today.
bluffing, and, uh, using my 8,000 subordinates!
Which way is starboard again?
Listen to me!
I can't remember!
Man, I'm screwed! Why doesn't any
of it work on that Horo-Horo Chick?
You stole one of my dreams!
Why do I have to listen to you?
Meatboard! I'll go wherever there is meat!
If you take me lightly, you'll get hurt.
What should I do? What now?!
Mincemeat is too good for the likes of you!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Clear-Clear History? Sanji's Stolen Dream"
"Perona Is Terrified!!
Usopp and Untruthful Share the Same 'U'"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Save Me, Hero!! My Enemy
Is the Immortal Princess!"
"The General Zombies Are Down in a Flash!!
Oars Feels Like an Adventure!!"
"Blazing Knight Sanji!!
Kick Down the Fake Wedding!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!