Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
He out-negatived the Negative Ghosts!
Listen... When it comes to thinking negatively...
...I'll have you know I'm unbeatable!
Wow! He's super confident in a bad way!
Playtime is over, Special Zombie Oars.
Chop him down from the legs!
Where's Oars?
There he is! Look up!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Nami-san!
I came for you!
There she is!
"Blazing Knight Sanji!!
Kick Down the Fake Wedding!"
You're going to kick my butt?
Yeah, you heard me!
Even if you managed to throttle or kill me,
it would simply mean the zombies
would no longer be my servants.
It wouldn't bring your shadow back.
It wouldn't?
Nope. My ability allows me
to reign over shadows.
This is what you'll have to do
to realize your dream:
Make the person currently
reigning over the shadows--me--
order the shadows to return to their masters.
Then they'll return to everyone?
Yep! Isn't it simple?
You'd need to hurt me badly enough
that I'd be willing to comply.
But considering your level of strength,
you couldn't even lay a hand on me!
All righty!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Wha--?!
A shadow?
I dare you to defeat my clone, Doppelman!
Long ago, I was brimming with
overconfidence and arrogance.
But it didn't take long for me to learn how
important it is to have good subordinates.
What's with that guy?
Hey! Outta the way!
I am the man who will become the
King of the Pirates without lifting a finger.
I will use the strength of others to get there!
I'm the one who will
become King of the Pirates!
Your zombie said the exact same thing.
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
As you can imagine, when its new
body is nothing like the original,
the shadow retains even more
of its original master's personality.
But that doesn't last forever!
Eventually, it will forget
everything pertaining to you.
It will become a zombie
that is completely loyal to me!
No matter how strong a zombie's will might be,
it will ultimately serve me unconditionally!
I'm getting it back in just a sec!
Gum-Gum...
Brick Bat.
...Gatling!
Damn it! He's blocking all of my punches.
Ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
You're a rowdy brat.
Shut up!
You jerk!
Kick his butt! Trample him!
But watch out for his salt!
Crap! I'm the only one who can
stand up to the Horo-Horo Chick!
This was supposed to be
my time to shine, darn it!
All of the other pirates quickly
succumbed to my Negative Ghosts...!
Mackerel... I'm worse than mackerel...
Yeah! I want a feral dog to step on me!
I'm sorry for walking on the same earth...
...as everyone else!
I never expected one of the men to be immune!
I've always been negative!
What?!
But that's all right. I'll just have
the Wild Zombies kill Mr. Long Nose.
Drat! I can't use my Salt Stars like this!
How am I supposed to pull out of this? How?!
That's it!
Okay!
Y-You got me! Ugh!
Sweet! We killed him!
Stupid! Keep your hands over your mouth!
It might be another one of his tricks!
Oh, you're right! He's fumbling
around with something.
Hmph! You're wasting your time!
Salt!
How are you going to get
the salt in our mouths?
Star! Star! Star!
Just kidding.
Pepper Star!
Here's my chance! Eat this!
Salt Star!
Mr. Negative Nose, you weasel!
I'm not done yet!
When it comes to tricking people, I'm--
Shuddup! Drop the cool act!
You're a loser!
Charge!
I'll stop you in your tracks! Firebird Star!
You missed!
What a klutz!
Sh-Shoot!
Get him!
What?!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
It's rottin' hot!
Hey, you guys!
Now! Special Attack!
--No!
--Out of my way!
If you don't move, I'll start with--hey, wait!
He's nuts! I can't let my guard
down for a second around him.
I need to come up with a way
to defeat Negative Nose!
I won't let you escape!
Wait, Horo-Horo Chick!
Stop him, Kumacy!
The bear zombie?!
Wait!
Don't follow me!
Wait, Horo-Horo Chick!
Don't mess with Perona-sama!
I had no idea that stuffed animal
was so nimble and powerful!
And here he can't even reach
the zipper on his back!
Why, you...!
I'm sorry if I upset you!
Whoops! I wanna go this way!
Yikes! Stay away!
--Huh?
--Stay back, darn it!
Gah! Don't follow me, bear!
I said to stay back, bear!
Keep back, dammit!
You bastard! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Wait, you...!
Stay back! Stay away, dammit!
I'm not about to lose!
Wait, wait, wait! You little--!
Huh? Where'd you go?
Huh? Are you over here?
Now I'm mad!
No way!
Stay away!
Keep back, Mr. Negative Nose!
Don't come after me, bear!
Graah!
Let's see...
Yeah!
Nice! I'm starting to get really excited!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Skip! Skip! Skip!
Nami-san!
Get your grubby hands off her!
Sorry to have kept you waiting,
Nami-san. Your knight is here.
Shake! Shake your hands!
One, two, three, four!
One, two...
Shake your hands!
Man, I feel like I haven't gone
swimming in ages. I wonder why...
Do I sink like a rock?
I can't remember!
Well, it's all good!
Ho-hoy!
I never expected this!
I'm drowning!
That was rather rash of you.
What if you had swallowed the salt water?
You could handle a little,
but if you drank a lot,
the salt would purify you.
Man, I thought I was gonna die!
Really! You can be such a handful.
Leave me alone!
Nami-san, you're in safe hands--
M-My word! Is she a goddess?
Uh, no. It's Nami-san. It really is Nami-san.
I'm sure of it!
Oh, I was so surprised.
Her beauty can be deceptive!
For a second, I thought I recued
a goddess by mistake. Phew!
A-A fairy?
Oh, I was so surprised.
But this is definitely Nami-san.
Ah, what a relief.
--I thought I accidentally rescued a fairy
by mistake. You're a deceptive little kitten.
--Sheesh! What are you going on about?
As I recall, you're part of the crew
that was on that pirate ship.
A-An angel?
N-No, she's human. I'm sure of it.
Ah, she had me scared there!
I don't blame you! I really don't blame you!
Nami-san and rice are about the only
things that look this good in white!
Yeah, seriously!
I know, right? You get it, right?
Why must she look so stinking good in white?!
--What are they going on about?
--It throws me off.
Lowly pirate! I don't need
to be chums with you!
Hey!
You nearly hit Nami-san.
When a lady is in the vicinity,
you should avoid attacks that could hit her.
I'm impressed you dodged that, bastard!
I see you've already lost your shadow.
Come to think of it, one of our new zombies
was oddly obsessed with that woman.
He retained some will of his own,
so he wasn't fully subservient.
I won't let you pursue that lady!
I suspect that was your zombie.
Considering that your shadow
wasn't put into a General Zombie,
your fighting ability
can't be all that impressive.
In fact, that penguin talked big,
but was terribly weak!
I'm known as one of the Phantoms
and lead the General Zombies.
It was impudent of that small fry to defy me!
A-A heavenly maiden?!
Oh, I was so surprised.
I thought she was a heavenly maiden. Sheesh!
Listen to me, punk!
She's definitely Nami-san. No mistake about it.
I wasn't sure what I'd do
if she was a divine maiden.
Don't heave a sigh of relief!
You know, it doesn't matter how
obsessed you are with that woman!
I am going to marry her!
Now take a word of advice
and leave that woman with me
while you spend the rest of
your life hiding in the shadows!
I'm rather busy at the moment!
Your captain's zombie may have crushed
some of my most powerful subordinates.
Before I deal with that, I need to kiss my bride!
I'm sure you understand.
I'm in a foul mood right now.
I don't have time to deal with weaklings like--
Shut up, Fur Face!
Absalom-sama!
No way! He weighs 300kg!
How did that man send him flying?!
You're the "invisible man"
Usopp mentioned, aren't you?
What was with that kick?
He sent me flying even though
Hogback has transplanted
the power of wild animals into my body!
Hands of the Dead!
What's going on? Could he
tell what I was about to do?
Basses Côte!
Longe!
You're the beast that showed up on Sunny
and licked Robin-chan, aren't you?!
Something has caught me!
And you ogled at Nami-san's
bare skin in the bath, didn't you?!
Be my blushing bride!
Tendron! Flanchet! Quasi!
Why is he so strong?! This is their small fry?!
Queue! Cuisseau! Jarret!
Why is she unconscious?! You didn't
get rough with her, did you?!
"Marriage," my ass!
Take a good look at my eyes.
I'll crush you under my feet
and turn you into croquette!
Damn it! I'll have to retreat for now.
Skating!
I've got Usopp's salt balls.
Over there!
What is that? It's salty!
Veau Shot!
Insane! This guy doesn't even have a bounty?
You said that you were in a foul mood?
That doesn't begin to describe mine.
I'm so mad I feel like my body could explode!
It did!
And unfortunately for you, there is bad
blood between us over one other thing!
You and I have some bad blood?
That's right! You... You...!
Nothing comes to mind.
I just met you for the first time today.
You stole one of my dreams!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Clear-Clear History? Sanji's Stolen Dream"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!