Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Big Bro!
Luffy...
Help me...
If there's anyone we can't
abandon, it's Bellemere!
Damn! Why did this have to happen?!
Don't act hasty, Bellemere!
Even if it's an injury that kills
ordinary people, I must not die!
Don't make our navigator cry!
Delicious! Nothing's quite like
my special tangerine sauce!
Ten more minutes for
the duck in the oven.
Got the side of vegetables...
Gum-Gum...
And the stew is boiling.
What's wrong, girlie?
Dragon Twister!!
Now just some fried rice omelets,
and everything's ready!
...Pinwheel!!
This'll be a big blow
to our family budget.
Luffy...
Do you want me to return
the village that badly?
I have to hurry up and rescue Luffy...
Then how's this?
Let's make an agreement.
Oh, are they back?
"Luffy in Big Trouble!
Fishmen vs. the Luffy Pirates"
Such an idiot!
Agreement?
That's right.
Sorry. This is all we can do right now.
Gather up 100 million
Berries and bring it here.
"Survive! Mother Bellemere
and Nami's Bond!"
What the... What the...
People with Devil Fruit
powers can't swim.
Do so and I'll let the village
go and give you freedom.
Though, even people without
powers would sink in this situation.
I see. That means that if
I kick and break that rock...
--Honest?!
--Honest!
I'd die before I break an
agreement concerning money.
He's gonna throw him into the sea?!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
It doesn't matter how
many years it takes.
Realize... that you all are mere humans!
I'll honor our agreement.
Darn you!
It's open! Come on in!
What the...?
--Luffy!!
--Damn you!
I absolutely will save up
100 million Berries!
Pardon me...
Which one of you is Arlong?!
"Proud Warriors!
Sanji and Usopp's Fierce Battles"
Bellemere-san! I will do it!
No matter how much time it takes!
This is bad... I'm out of strength...
Arlong?
"Luffy Rises!
Result of the Broken Promise!"
My name happens to be Arlong...
"Luffy Submerged!
Zoro vs. Hatchan the Octopus"
I'm Luffy.
Luffy?
So, what are you?
What do you think?
Isn't this a pretty fun game?
A pirate!
Gen-san? And the navy?
How many minutes will
that rubber man last?
Or will you guys die before that?
That's him! He's here!
The guy who likes taking walks!
Hmph! A man from Cocoyashi Village...
You're wasting your time...
Too bad. I'm a former marine.
Hold it, you.
Are you the girl thief known as Nami?
Dammit! He found me!
This isn't good, Johnny.
Big Bro Luffy is in big trouble...
What's the point of
extending his life like that?!
Where do you think you're goin'?!
What brings Grand Line pirates
all the way out to Cocoyashi Village?
Our information has it you've hidden
treasure you stole from pirates.
He can't help himself now!
You need to run things
by us first, kiddo.
I'll sink you as well!
We'll defeat him in five seconds.
Luffy! I'll come rescue you right away!
--Yeah!
--If you don't stop...
The government hereby confiscates
all the property you have stolen!
No way I'll let you!
Hachi Ink Jet!
What's so funny?!
Move!
You damn human!
Are you seriously trying
to fight me in the water?!
Powerless! Powerless!
Powerless! Powerless! Powerless!
What's the matter?
Did you not hear me?
You're an inferior species that has
to worry about holding your breath!
What does a pirate want with me?
My hair! You bastard! I'm gonna...
The government
hereby takes possession
How powerless your
inferior species is!
of everything you
stole from the pirates.
Okay, I'll fight.
...forgive you since it's just hair
and it's gonna grow back.
Fishman Karate! Duelling Hair Tether!
--Huh?
--Roronoa Zoro!
My, my. You're very passionate
about your duties, I see.
You can't cut me
because I have six hands.
You're not brave enough
to stand up to pirates,
Let's escape with her
out the back door!
--Go ahead and cut me if you can!
--You Octo-Man!
You son of a...
so you deal with sneak thieves
instead to earn brownie points.
But the pirates might already be there!
Hachi's... Triple... Sword... Catch!
What's that? The power of
your kick dropped in half.
Talk about superb!
We'll be fine!
Hold it!
That's the limit for humans.
Here's a warning for you.
But Fishman Karate's power
doesn't drop even in the water!
--Doctor!
--You mustn't return home!
I'm a leader of the Arlong Pirates.
Ouch!
--Wha...?
--Move! We have to save Bellemere-san!
Mess with me, and Arlong
won't sit by quietly!
I don't have time to play with you!
Rather, depending on the
technique, the power doubles.
Nojiko! Nami!
Listen closely, you two!
Who the hell are you?
Silly girl. Do you think you're
dealing with me on equal footing?
He throws me out of whack!
This may not be the best situation to--
no, because of the situation,
Could he possibly...
Fishman Karate! Instant Undersea...
I must tell you a somewhat cruel story!
Find the stolen goods!
If you're not paying attention,
you'll shorten your life!
...Bowel Buster!!
Fish shouldn't go against a cook!
Wait!
Doctor?
We're running out of time... No time...
Bellemere-san!
Fishman Karate!
Go down already!
Stop!
Flaming Axe Kick!
Luffy... Help me...
Hachi Suckers!
It's no good!
These guys are real monsters!
Is this what the navy
should be doing right now?!
Don't make our navigator cry!
The Arlong Pirates have killed people,
and even destroyed towns!
I'm gonna be killed!
Back Foot Jawbreaker!
Nojiko! Nami!
So what?! Come down already!
Why, you...
You know that!
How dare you insult Arlong-san?!
Bellemere!
He's ruling over this island and
trampling all over people's lives!
Don't waste your life for some
pathetic sense of justice!
Special Attack!
You damn octopus!
Butt out, small fries!
Some battles aren't worth fighting!
Is ignoring that major problem
Guffaw Palm Bomb!!
Some issues can be solved with money!
and raking in stolen goods from a thief
what the government stands for?!
Gen-san...
That octopus bastard!
He's moving wobbly and slowly!
Yeesh. You just had to
run on ahead by yourself...
That's right, marine girl.
Don't talk all big.
But then, if he goes
into the sea now,
Continue your search!
100,000 per adult. 50,000 per kid.
It's not like I'd lose on my own.
Yeah!
he'll be dragged to
the bottom of the sea.
People all over the island've been
waiting for your help for years now!
Idiot! When did I say
I was worried about you?!
If you can pay for your
whole family, I'll let you live.
But at this rate,
Big Bro Luffy's going to die!
You should be thankful I'm telling you.
How dare you just pass
them by and come here!
We have to do something about it!
My whole family?
I just don't want you
hogging all the prey!
--Yeah!
--Wait!
Colonel! This tangerine
orchard seems suspicious!
Ouch!!
Oh!
What're you going to do in
the sea with such serious injuries?
That's 200,000 total.
How much do you own, all together?
Dig it up!
I-I don't mind if you
hog them all, though!
You can't do much like that.
Including what I've squirreled
away... a little over 100,000...
Keep your filthy hands off of
Bellemere-san's tangerine orchard!
You sure got some guts.
If you're talking about that rubber
young man, I'll go and rescue him.
Air! Air! Air! Air! Oxygen! Air!
I let out too much air! I can't breathe!
Hey! There's a meal
for three people in here!
Y-You will?
That's him! He's the
unknown swordsman!
Whether we can save
that young man or not
I won't let you have my money!
That money's for...
Oh? A family of three, huh?
is probably what will
decide this fight, right?
It's Roronoa Zoro.
Yeah? Yeah, I thought so!
He tricked me!
I can tell that, too.
This girl's money is meant
to save Cocoyashi Village!
Gen-san!
I almost forgot!
--I'll go, too!
Where're you going?
Look, sine, and hinker...
Me, too!
What gives you the right
to take it away, navy man?!
Dammit! Let me through.
I need air! Let me breathe!
She invited me and my
friend to dinner tonight!
No! If many of us go
and take time rescuing him,
No! Hook, line, and sinker... right?
the fishmen will notice and it will
cause these people trouble, if anything.
Look! It's Long-nose!
Seriously, what amazing strength...
Come, Bellemere.
Hurry and pay your amount.
Oh? A lowly village representative,
talking down to a navy colonel?
I can't believe he's human.
D-Didn't Nami kill him?!
Our delicious food's going to get cold!
Gen-san!
It'll be pointless if we end up
putting a crimp in their fight.
Let me breathe...
Gen-san...
The bastard's alive. Which means...
Gen-san... How do you know about that?
I hear you have 100,000.
Thank goodness you have enough!
So I'll do it alone.
I knew it.
That's okay with you two, right?
Now everyone in the village is spared!
The girl was a traitor,
just as I suspected!
Sorry... Thank you!
It's true--
I've always known, Nami.
I'll leave it to you.
Sorry, but please be quick.
the village register has no record
of her getting married or giving birth.
Wait!
She's single.
--I'm... joining...
--Eh?
"Single" "No Family"
Gen-san, I'll go, too.
I'm joining... the Arlong Pirates...
Nojiko, you're injured!
Hey! Who are those guys?!
If I remember correctly,
Those guys're fighting
for my little sister!
Do you understand?!
Nami!
you said that those
who harm a lady are crap.
Hold it!
There's no proof that you two
and Bellemere are family!
You...
Nami...
--He sent Arlong flying!
--Unbelievable!
Leave this island before
they take notice of you!
I couldn't believe
what you'd done then,
Gen-san!
But look how it's turning out.
This is the outcome
of your cheap chivalry.
Escape across the sea!
so I confronted Nojiko later.
No ordinary human could do that!
There's no other way for
all three of you to survive!
Everyone in the village
has known since then
Okay. Come with me.
They're...
--Let's hurry!
--Okay!
that you stayed with the Arlong
Pirates so you could save the village.
You won't be able to escape
from me and will die.
I feel it's reckless to send you two
out to sea at such a young age!
Do you still want to
try to break in now?
I'm sorry...
That policeman and the
rubber man will also die.
If only we were a little stronger...
There's a chance
something bad could happen!
If you go, you'll wind up
putting a damper on this fight.
But we pretended we didn't know.
--But at least you'll have...
--No.
Zoro, that long-nose man and the
rebel villagers... They'll all be killed.
Please save... Big Bro...
You'll only get in their way!
Because our hopes would keep you
from running away from Arlong
I don't want to!
B-But... why are they fighting?
Why do we have to leave?
They're the ones who came here!
if you ever decided to.
With all that's happened, Nami
won't get away with betraying us!
What reason do they have to fight?!
You can't be serious...
Reason to fight?
I... want to live in this village...
What on earth are you talking about?
Do you get it?
Big Sis Nami was crying!
Is it because we're poor
You damn fish man!
With your superficial chivalry,
You're saying all the
villagers are thieves,
that I can't be
Bellemere-san's kid anymore?!
and we should arrest them?
you can't protect anyone,
let alone Nami, after all!!
Do they need any more reason than that
Why? Why?!
to put their lives on the line?
He's saying that each and every
one of us is fighting to live!
Roronoa Zoro! Do you mind if I ask
you a question? You don't, right?
Thank goodness. Now they won't kill.
But only because we can't rely
on any of you government people!
A pirate, huh? I see...
I heard you use the Three Swords Style.
Why are you using only one sword?
So that's what you guys' deal is.
--Alright, we'll leave the village!
--Nojiko!
If you're not gonna save our village,
then get the hell out of here!
You're already losing
big with one sword!
Even if you're kinda strong,
Let's go! Because that means
Bellemere-san gets to live!
You were after Nami
from the very start.
Sh-Shut up! I'm not fighting seriously!
that's just silly talk by a helpless human.
Dilly-dally and Arlong'll
go after your ship, too!
But...
Actually, there's a reason that
a human swordsman can't defeat me.
Mr. Arlong will?
I wouldn't be so sure...
What can you four inferior
creatures possibly do?!
You humans can't handle a sudden
change in water pressure, right?
Wanna hear what it is?
You wanna hear it, right?
When you hear it, you'll be
surprised, scared, blown away!
Fool! You're not worth Arlong's time!
You still haven't found it?!
We're looking for 100 million
Berries here! Not a grain of rice!
In other words, if you
rapidly dive into the abyss...
Dammit! I can't be in pain right now!
He'll be more than enough!
Hey, you! How do you
know how much there is?!
My fever's getting worse, too!
Hold it.
your organs will burst out of your body.
Who said I paid for me?
I thought it would come down
while I was moving around, but...
Oh, the 100 million?
That 100,000's for my two daughters.
I don't got enough for me.
I just got the feeling
there's that much.
Pulverizing Pressure Plunge!!
No!
It's coming!
--Bellemere! What are you...
--I'm sorry, Gen-san.
Just as I thought, the wounds...
I just can't say
I don't have a family...
What the... What the...
What's going on?!
...from your fight with Hawk-Eye are...
Even... if it costs me my life...
Big Bro!
I'm not gonna let him get away with this!
Don't tell me he...
What're you doing?
I can't protect anyone?!
How could she?!
Are you trying to fake
illness or something?
Yeah, maybe we're
not related by blood...
I won't fall for that. Roronoa Zoro!
Just check out my true form!
Don't tell me Arlong sent you here!
...but we're a family.
The whole lot of you
will be food for him!
I want to be their parent,
even if it's only in name.
Who knows?
Come out, Momoo!
We're simply dealing with theft
as any government workers would.
They're... my kids.
Look! This is my true form!
Here comes Hachi,
user of the Six Swords Style!
--Bellemere-san!
--Wait, you two!
Hey! That's not where you're
supposed to fall! Don't mock me!
This man won't die yet?
What rotten scum!
I wish someone richer
had adopted me instead!
A-A monster!
I can't believe the navy would
stoop to being pirate cronies!
It's the Grand Line monster that
destroyed the town of Gosa!
It was just a lie! I was lying!
Then, I'll give you that attack as you wish!!
--Ah! Big Bro!
--So he was bearing the pain!
Arlong!
Bellemere-san!
I found it!
Yeah. His injuries would
kill a normal person
They use pulmonary respiration on land
but switch to branchial respiration in water.
or leave them bedridden for half a year!
What?!
Which means that he's just
a talking fish right now.
I thought something was strange.
This is incredible!
It's here!
I'm impressed you could
gather this much, girl!
He looked as if nothing had happened
right after that fierce fight.
--T-That's...
--...the sea cow, Momoo!
Can you bear a second time?
I wanted... to buy you lots
more books and clothes...
Is he an idiot or what?!
It's all ragged and stained with blood...
A fish'll die if air is
shot into its branchia.
No matter! Money is money!
I'm sorry!
If you're also a fish,
you'll feel the same pain!
I was never able to do
anything mother-like for you!
Thirty percent of this is all mine!
Oh, it's him?
That's not true!
I thought I warned you
to pay attention.
He's a friend of the fishmen?
We don't need anything!
Just don't die!
Don't touch that...
Stay with us forever!
I have a fortieth dan
in Fishman Karate.
Don't touch that... Don't touch that...
I want you to see
the world map I draw!
Wh-What? Someone went flying?!
Nami...
B-Big Bro?!
Don't touch that... Don't touch that...
Yeah... Your map...
Hm?
Big Bro Cook!
Don't touch that!
Make your dream... come true!
You...
Ahh...
Big Bro Cook!!
Live!
--Hey...
--Don't worry. He's okay.
Wait! Momoo! Where are you going?!
Bellemere-san!
Hey! Stop! Get back here! Momoo!
Really?!
--Yeah, sort of.
--Sort of?
These're your girls, I take it?
He's been taken care of, Arlong-san.
I'll explain it later.
Momoo. What are you doing?
What do we do with Roronoa Zoro?
Anyhow, come out of the water,
you damn fish! Let's settle this!
Yeah, that's right!
Just ditch him in the sea.
What weaklings... How boring!
Nami!
Promise me you won't
lay a hand on them!
Of course! As long as
you die like a good girl!
Though, if you wanna
run away, I won't stop you.
You still don't get it, do you?
Nojiko!
Help!
That's all?
Nojiko!!
Whether it's in the water or
on the ground, it's the same.
Geez, they sure did
a lot of damage, though.
Understand, Momoo?
It's no big deal.
I'm really angry!
Arlong Park can't be destroyed
by this kind of damage.
A pinwheel, huh?
I'll make you experience the
essence of Fishman Karate!
Indeed...
The earlier attack I used to send you
flying was the Hundred-Brick Fist!
How dare you, Roronoa Zoro!
Now they're thirsty for blood...
You died from shock before I,
the great swordsman, could attack you?!
It's coming! It's coming!
Don't kill 'em.
Just handle 'em as you see fit.
--Alright!
--Follow after Momoo!
But my ultimate attack
is the Thousand-Brick Fist!
Man, that was so cool!
Perfect timing for our
first example to the others!
You could have left your name
in history if you died at least
after receiving my
Six Swords Style attack.
Your survival probability is... zero!!
Well, no matter how you struggle or
even if the world is turned upside down,
I thought up a good move!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
you humans can't even give a
scratch to me, wielder of six swords!
Doctor! Doctor!
Die with your pathetic love.
Collier!
What is it, Gen-san?!
I'll do it! This is a waste of time!
--Nojiko's been shot!
--By who?!
My chivalry is naive?
--The navy!
--The navy?
Epaule!
Nojiko!
Nojiko! Nami!
I can't protect anyone, you said?
I'm fine...
Stop it, Hachi. I know how you feel,
Arlong's been working with the navy.
Cotelette! Selle! Poitrine!
What's he planning now?!
What?!
but if you really go on a
rampage we'll be in trouble.
I don't get a very good
feeling about this...
I love you!
He's lied to Nami
for the last eight years.
Gigot!
Are you going to destroy Arlong Park?
He never intended to
honor their agreement!
Oh! Ahh...
N-no... Sorry.
--What?!
--Oh, no! Then...
I got too worked up...
You...
That bastard!
He lied to our Nacchan!
Son of a bitch!
Ultimate Fist! Thousand-Brick!
Don't get carried away.
You just never learn, do you?!
Nacchan!
You're right. Sorry.
Let go! I'll pay later!
The Six Swords Style, huh?
What a joke!
--With my body!
--You fool!
Nami...
You made another boy cry?!
Heya, Nami! What's up?
Need help with anything?
--He made me mad!
--Blehhh!
Mouton... Shot!!
His arms stretched!
It's okay. Kids will be kids.
He said your tangerines
suck, Bellemere-san!
Are you still here?!
He has a Devil Fruit power?!
--Say what?!
--Bellemere!
This has nothing to do with you!
Leave the damn island already!
--What?!
--Who cares?
Big Bro!!
Go!
Don't give in to anyone...
Roronoa Zoro!
Whoa! Run!
What? What's he doing?!
I'll tell you one thing, octopus.
Even girls need to be strong...
I dunno, but it doesn't look good!
There's a man I need to meet up with.
Gum-Gum...
Arlong... Arlong...!
It doesn't matter if
people don't praise you!
Until I see him again...
Don't have hate for this
era you were born in...
Arlong!
I guess...
I'd die before I break an
agreement concerning money.
...Pinwheel!
...my life can't be taken away
even by Death himself!
...he doesn't want dessert?
Never forget the strength to
be able to smile at any time...
It doesn't matter how
many years it takes.
I'll honor our agreement.
Arlong!
Bellemere-san!
What's her problem?
Under my rule,
anyone without money dies!
Understand, you inferior species?!
Damn that Long-nose! What speed!
That guy's face and ability
to run away aren't human!
What was that?! What's happening?!
What's this?
--A sea chart?
--No!
Arlong!
I drew that! It's important
to me! Give it back!
If I keep one of the Arlong Pirates
leaders away like this,
I didn't come here
to take on these guys!
Oh? What's wrong,
skilled surveyor of ours?
You drew it?
it should be beneficial to Luffy
and the other's fights.
--Give it back!
--Nami! No!
The one I wanna beat up...
Oh? This is quite impressive.
Why the angry look?
Good job, Usopp-sama!
How considerate you are towards them!
...is you!
That's perfect, then.
Though it just happened
to turn out that way...
The navy men you have under
your control stole all my money!
She's an invaluable asset!
Bring her with us!
--Right!
--No!
Whoa, as I expected,
he isn't catching up.
I was just thinking of killing you now.
What happened to dying before
breaking promises about money?!
Let go! Let go! No!
Darn. This isn't good.
Looks like I've got quite a lead.
That was dangerous, you!
Kuroobi...
--Let Nami go! Let go!
--Stop!
Why?!
Are you trying to kill us, too?!
When did I break our promise?
Fishmen are just turtles
on land, after all.
You got your money!
Hachi...
You promised not
to lay a hand on her!
Huh?
Don't play dumb!
You teamed up with the navy to--
He's far behind in no time.
They're small fish, after all.
Yeah. I ain't gonna hurt her.
I'm just gonna borrow her.
It's a million and fifty thousand years
too early for them to go against a cook.
Turtles... huh?
Gen-san! Help!
When did I break our
promise? Let's hear it!
Hey! Hey! Turtle! You slow turtle!
Keep up with me if you can!
Keep your hands off the children!
We win this game.
Kuroobi.
I'll outrun you again right away!
You waddling turtle!
How dare you bastards beat my
dear brothers one after another...?
Gen-san!
Gen-san! Gen-san!
Aren't you the one
who'll have to waddle?
Damn you... Damn you! Damn you!
Gen-san!
Aren't you getting a
little too carried away?!
I see! So your money's been stolen?
Ughhhhh!
Stop, you bastard!
I'll save you, Nami...
How unfortunate.
Hey, what do you mean
by Luffy being sort of okay?
But an agreement is an agreement.
I won't let you pass...
If you can't gather up
100 million Berries for me to see,
No! It's okay!
You don't need to save me!
He drank quite a bit of water.
It means that he won't
die for the time being.
I'm afraid I can't give
you the village back.
We need to bring him up
soon or it'll be too late.
Please!
But to revive him, I have to go
into the sea one more time...
--This is getting tedious.
--I'll... save...
Dammit! I guess I can't
break it in the sea.
Scum!
...though it doesn't seem like
that guy's gonna let me...
Please, no more dying!
The buoyancy is too strong.
Gen-san, hurry up.
It's only 100 million Berries!
Just start saving up again!
No good. I can't smash the rock.
An oxygen cylinder would be helpful
but we don't have time to go get it.
Amazing... They're really amazing!
And we can't carry him up
along with the rock, either...
They beat two of the
Arlong Pirates' leaders!
Or are you gonna run out on me?
What destructive power...
Oh, yeah!
I can't believe a human exists
who can throw that giant beast!
But if you do run away, I'll kill
everyone in Cocoyashi Village.
This is it. I can no longer hold my breath!
Is this battle of this world?
Gen-san, take my place.
I'll go in this time.
Nami...
His color has improved considerably.
We pretended we didn't know.
Huh?
All of the village's
ships have been sunk...
He spit out quite a bit of water.
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
Because our hopes would keep you
from running away from Arlong
What's going on over there?
Don't worry. Everyone's still alive.
Our idea of trying to let
Nojiko and Nami escape to sea...
What are you doing?!
if you ever decided to.
In fact...
Huh?
...although it's hard to believe,
Hm? Ahh!
How dare you hurt our brothers?!
...was too optimistic...
this fight is giving me hope...
That man's still alive!!
Just as I feared,
the navy won't listen to us.
Big Bro! Big Bro Cook!!
It would seem we need to fight, too.
the hope that I've been holding back...!
Oh? Finally running away, huh?
This island will be under his control.
Bellemere knew!
That fishman's punch was
a fortieth dan punch? I see...
Looks like we need to teach them
the differences between our species.
She fully knew how they work,
from her experience as a marine!
Shouldn't we chase after her?
The main forces finally show up, huh?
Then those kicks I used to take all
the time from that damn geezer
Chase? What for? She won't run away.
She knew not a single
person could ever escape...
are four-hundredth dan kicks.
She could never abandon
the lives of the villagers.
Arlong-san. Please stay there quietly.
Geez... Causing me all these troubles...
What is it, Roronoa Zoro?
If you go on a mad rampage,
you'll tear all of Arlong Park into pieces.
They took Nami with them...
I'm not sure what's going on,
but you look like you're in pain.
What amazing ability to run away!
You certainly do know
how to play dirty...
What... am I supposed to
do now... Bellemere-san?
You think you can defeat my
Six Swords Style in that condition?
No way would I let such an exceptional
surveyor as Nami go so easily.
But that was too easy... He died
instantly with a shot of my Squirt Gun.
Everyone in the whole world
thinks the same way.
But I'm not a heartless devil.
We'll take care of these guys!
Hmph! I guess I should head back.
The others should be done by now.
We've found out where
the Arlong Pirates are!
Yeah. Do as you wish.
That's none of your business.
Once she's done surveying
all of the world's seas,
Big Bro's in really bad shape!
It seems they intend to
settle down on this island!
Yikes!
I'll give her her freedom!
He's probably got a
fever from his wounds
It's time to decide!
Hey. Hey, there. There's something I...
and must be barely conscious.
Do we fight now and die defiantly?!
That's like decades from now!
If those wounds open up,
he's definitely going to die!
Or do we place our hope in waiting
for help from the government,
Not even a hundred years'd be enough!
while living under the fear
of being killed at any time?!
That octopus is up to something.
But it's no time to think
about things like that!
It's one or the other!
Octopus is best with
a little salt and sliced up.
Yeah! He's the only one who can
break through this situation!
Only Navy Headquarters
stands a chance against them!
Alright! Let's meet up with Luffy ASAP!
Add some olive oil and paprika
and it's a perfect snack while drinking.
But HQ has its hands full
in the Grand Line.
I'll show you the Three Swords Style.
I'm saved! It worked!
Hey, I'm kind of in trouble. Hear me out.
Our hopes of them coming all the
way out here are as good as zero!
Hey, Sanji. What're you doing?
I'm so glad I made Ketchup
Star for times like this.
Yosaku! Johnny!
Let me use your swords!
Take this! Zero vision!
Appreciating happiness.
But I can't let Nami go!
Hachi Ink Jet!
--Of course!
--Big Bro! Catch these!!
What're you talking about?
He thinks his Squirt Gun or whatever
actually hit me. Go back already!
Nami-san's lived with many times
the suffering of a normal person.
I'll fight!
Darn! I feel like
I'm about to pass out.
Me too! I doubt I can live my life
knowing I abandoned a child!
You idiot! Why didn't you dodge?!
I wonder how long
I can keep standing...
Seriously... What a scary species they are...
I'm going to take away
that suffering of hers.
Big Bro! We threw our swords!
I can't see!
We're all family here!
You said you wanted to
use them! Catch them!
They turned the houses
in town upside down...
Even if it means I die killing them,
I'm gonna save Nacchan!
Is there any happiness
greater than this?
Now to finish you off!
Ha! I'll show you the wall that you
humans with two arms can't surpass!
Bellemere gave her
life up to protect them!
Your ulterior motive's
way obvious, Love Cook.
Well, I feel sorry for Nami and
I really want to help her, but...
Hey, Luffy! Run!
Six Swords Style!
Let's fight 'em again!
Big Bro! Watch out!!
They'll blame us all anyway
if just one of us fights!
Yeah, that's the problem.
Tentacle-Sword Overload!
I'm fighting for a beautiful person.
What's wrong with that?
Big Bro!!
I can't seem to move!
Hm?
That's not what this is for!
It's for Nami and the villagers!
If you survive, lots
of fun things will happen!
Huh?!
I guess it was just my imagination.
M-My feet are stuck!
Three Sword Style!
Shaddup.
I think I'll pass on dying.
You're the one who
stuck them in the ground!
B... But actually, although
I'm covered in fake blood,
Why does he have to be so--
Streaming Wolf-Swords!
Quit your jabbering and let's go!
Nami!
Hachi Ink Jet on the Rocks!
I want something that shows
a trace of deadly combat.
--Nami!
--Nacchan!
You're all right?!
Oh, yeah. If I show up with my body all
covered in mud, it may look that way.
Nami! Nami!
He did it!
He handled the six-sword
random hits! He's really amazing!!
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Did they do anything to you?
No more of this!
Take up your weapons!
I'd say something like, "Ahh, sorry. I lost."
Let's fight!
--Nami?
--I'm... joining...
What concentration!
What spiritual strength!
Hmmm. I wonder if, "Well,
I let that bastard slip away,
Gen-san! Everyone!
Please! Don't be hasty!
Eh?
though I was this close," is better...
Ahh... How dare you have
the impudence to do such a thing!
I'm joining... the Arlong Pirates...
You can't die! It'll all be over!
I'm really mad, you son of a bitch!
Or that may not be quite convincing...
You have to survive,
or everything will end!
I'm going to join the Arlong Pirates...
I'm gonna kill you!
What a pain.
We're friends now, aren't we?
Eight years ago, we swore
not to throw away our lives!
If you just think about it,
you should know!
...to be a surveyor and draw sea charts!
Sanji! Great! Great!
"Well, don't cry, Nami.
We only did what was right."
I can hold six swords, so there's
no way you can defeat me
Seems I've wound up following
one hell of an idiot of a captain.
No matter how painful and insulting
it was to be ruled by them,
when you can hold only
three swords! Isn't that right?!
I'd rather die than lose.
What are you saying, Nami?
Are you in your right mind?
we swore to fight the patient fight
as long as Nami was cheerful!
Agreed.
Just think about it?
What a big miscalculation.
"Well, we all fought very well."
He's... awesome!
Did they do something
horrible to you? Did they?
But this is their answer!
What do you bear on your shoulders?
But he's 100 times better than
a damn gang that'd hurt a lady.
He's 100 times better than a
damn gang that'd hurt a lady.
What do you desire once
you've obtained power?
Now that our village's chance for
freedom is gone, we have no hope!
No.
--They threatened you, didn't they?!
--No!
I'm going to get stronger for her, too!
--Say it!
--Let go of me!
"Well, it certainly was a deadly combat."
More than that,
Lady?
we must make those fishmen pay
for toying with that girl's kindness!
Nami...
I'm going to get strong enough
that my name reaches to Heaven!
It's for my business!
This was my only choice!
Nami!
To think you'd bust in here
just for that one lousy girl.
Any objections?!
I'm going to be the world's
strongest swordsman!
You really know how to make us laugh!
Of course not! Let's go!
T-That's an Arlong tattoo...
"Well, my injuries aren't that bad."
We were always fully ready
to fight at any time!
Lousy girl?
You...
Just try and insult
Nami-san one more time.
Nami...
I refuse to let them
rule over me any more!
Big Sis Nami was crying.
I'll use a buttered frying pan to
turn you into meuniere, Fish Man!
Look at this...
They gave me all this money...
Do they need any more reason than
that to put their lives on the line?
Wait, everyone!
You seem somewhat
skilled for a human.
Nami was only ten. Do you know
how painful of a choice it was?
Whether it's three swords...
or six swords...
Nami!
And they say they'll
buy me anything I want...
Any sort of chivalry from a
pirate is obviously half-hearted.
Nami!
...it doesn't matter!
Just a little more!
Just wait a little more!
Let's fight!!
Unforgivable! Unforgivable!
Go ahead and see if my
chivalry is half-hearted or not.
I'll work hard again!
Joining pirates is
absolutely unforgivable!
Your sword and my sword
carry different weight!
I'll save up the money again!
I was raised by an unbeatable
pirate for half my life.
And them, of all people!
"Well, the way... I fought... was really..."
It'll be easy this time!
Do you even know what
kind of people they are?!
I'm used to it! I'll be fine!
There's no need to worry at all!
So what?!
If I'm gonna get killed living
a proper life like Bellemere-san,
It appears you don't know the
true level of the fishman species.
This is nothing
compared to back then!
then I don't wanna live properly!
How...
Please, no more dying!
How shameful...!
I can't believe this...
Everyone! I'm fine! I'm just fine!
Bellemere-san...
Weight, you said?
Bellemere-san was killed because of us!
How... shameful I am!
Oof! Oof!
I see. So your swords are heavy.
They're still really stuck.
--How can you just...
--That's enough, Nojiko.
Hold it, you damn fish!!
But my swords weigh at
least 300 kilos per sword
Still?! They're still stuck?!
Leave, Nami!
You can stop now... Even you
know there's no point now...
though they may not look like it.
Never step foot into this village again!
They weigh a lot more than you
humans' swords, you bastard!
Yep, they're still stuck.
Oh? You're still alive?
I get the feeling just pulling
me won't get them unstuck.
You fought very well, carrying our
lives on your back all this time...
Are you even trying?! Are you
even trying to pull your legs out?!
There's no point in
discussing with an idiot.
Of course! No way that staggering
shots by a half-fish would hit me!
Joining them must've been
even more painful for you
What're they playing
around in Arlong Park for?
Six Swords Style!
Octopus Pot Stance!
Nami!
than being cut through the heart...
New Year's...
The moment I left my village,
I gave up on things...
You fought very well.
I'll kill them!
...Open!
Hey, you! Get unstuck already!
...like peace and safety...
How could she be so foolish?
Gen-san...
Body Slam!
Did she not see
Bellemere as her parent?!
Because they live risking their lives
everyday, they laugh so happily!
That's dirty! He hit him
right in his wounds!
Get back here!
Hey, octopus.
That'll show you!
--Big Bro!!
--He's gonna die!!
They're busy right now.
Leave the village now.
I won't let you land
while you're still alive!
I'll take you on.
That's why I decided
to set out to the sea.
Gen-san?!
Six Sword Ultimate Technique!
Do it, Nami.
Roronoa Zoro! Yeah! I forgot!
Waltz of Six Swords!
I wanted to laugh from the
bottom of my heart, too!
W-What?!
You'll be mincemeat if you touch it
even for a second! Become mincemeat!
If I don't fight with all my might here,
How dare you trick me!
--Nacchan...
--Nami...
I won't have the right to be
on board the same ship as them.
No, that's not true...
You're crafty, and you have a dream.
Big Bro!!
Nami loved Bellemere-san...
I won't have the right to laugh from
the bottom of my heart with them!!
Yeah! And you cut down
tons of my brothers!
Nojiko! Everyone!
I won't let you go!
I'm not interested in these old stories.
What?!
Stop it, everyone!
Ow!
It doesn't matter what reasons
you have for wanting to kill me.
I don't want to see anyone
else get hurt by them!
Big Bro!!
Hey...
Bellemere-san said that if we survive,
fun things will happen, right?
The situation's changed now!
You'll die, you know!
Are you an idiot?
We know.
You're not trying to destroy us.
You should've just pretended to be dead...
We're trying to destroy you!
That bastard! He rolled on
my swords adjusting to the spin!
Even your brain is inferior...
Lots of fun things...
On top of that, he gave me
a free hand cutting service!
I'm done...
Yeah.
It's no use!
We've made up our minds!
After Arlong dragged me off,
A-Alright, Zoro!
That octopus is all yours! Nice!
How dare he make fun of me!
I'm not a circus acrobat!
five navy ships came to capture him,
Yeah, you're right!
You're already done for!
but they were all sunk easily...
I'm completely angry now!
I won't let him get away!
Get out of our way, Nami!
Luffy!
I'm done!
I'm gonna really kill him good!
I don't think the government will
send any more help to this island.
Usopp Hammer!
Let's go, everyone!
That's what made me realize
I have to do something.
Even if we can't win, let's
show 'em what we're made of!
Usopp Rubberband of Doom!
I'm back...
I made an agreement with Arlong
to buy Cocoyashi Village from him.
Big Bro... he looks like
he's in a lot of pain...
Ahhh! Dammit!
Why, you...
To buy the village?
My bad...
For 100 million Berries.
His wounds might've
opened with that attack.
What a stupid trap I fell into!
Seems you really do
want me to kill you.
Ahh... If I could, I'd wanna
take his place for him...
If I buy the village, we can be free.
That son of a bitch...!
No one else will have to die.
Even if it's an injury that knocks
ordinary people out, I must not fall.
In exchange, I have to join his
group and draw sea charts...
--Special Attack! Lead Star!
--Alcohol?
Wasn't that the guy
who saved Gen-san?
B-But, 100 million Berries?
I'm not sure you can earn that
much working your entire life!
How dare you do all these
impudent things, you feeble species!
I will earn it!
No matter what it takes!
You're the people
from Cocoyashi Village!
Six Swords Style!
Octopus Pot Stance!
Oh?
Everyone's working their
hardest to pay the tribute money,
Judging from the fact that you have
weapons, I take it this is a rebellion?
No matter where you hide, I'll blow
you away using this rice field water!
It's all over!
so my only choice is to do it alone.
Even if it's an injury that kills
ordinary people, I must not die!
Because if I ask for help from
anyone, more people will get hurt.
Then you're all--
Exploding Star!
Impudent or whatever... It doesn't matter.
Big Bro Usopp!
New Year's...
Arlong!
At any rate, as a man,
I can't run away from this fight.
In order to defeat the
extraordinarily strong Hawk-Eye,
You're dealing with me!
Arlong! Arlong!
--It'll hurt, you know...
--Yeah...
I can't just be ordinary!
Yeah, if I lose, I'll die.
Staying with the people who
killed Bellemere-san'll hurt.
If you wanna die that badly,
I'll get rid of you right now!
But I'm already a pirate!
Arlong! Arlong!
Arlong! Arlong! Arlong!
Squirt Cannon!
I'll be fine. I'll put on a big smile,
even when I see his face!
Arlong! Arlong!
Just who is that lad?
Dragon Twister!!
He's brave one minute,
then runs away the next.
Arl--
I've decided not to cry anymore.
He's a baffling man...
Oh, my... What power...!
I've decided to fight on my own!
Get back here, Nose!
Luffy...
Well, you got a big mouth!
Why do I have to fight
against an idiot like that?
Why are these people pirates?!
What do you want?!
You don't even know anything!
He's completely exposing himself!
You don't even know what's happened
on this island the past 8 years!
You're gonna be swiss cheese!
Squirt Machine Gun!
Hachi...
Yeah. I don't know.
You're all pathetic. Move.
I'm sick of watching this.
How could I be... defeated by...
the Three Swords Style?
Ahhh! H-How did he
figure out where I was?!
This has nothing to do with you!
Dammit! Dammit! Just watch me,
Usopp Pirates, Kaya!
I told you, leave the
damn island already!
Arlong-san! We asked you
not to go on a rampage!
Yeah. You told me.
Do you know how painful of
a choice it was for Nami
I set off to the sea and became a pirate!!
Leave! I don't need you!
I won't. I just thought up a fun game.
to decide to fight and survive on
her own, at the mere age of 10?
Leave! Leave! Leave! Leave!
I'll fight! In order to become a real,
brave sea warrior, not a fake one!
Octo-Man...
Game?
Leave! Leave! Leave!
For the only deal that
could save the village, she...
You now know the difference between
the weight in our swords, right?
I'm going to beat you up!
I'm done pretending to be a pirate!
Leave!
I'll make whoever makes
my beloved Nami-san suffer--
Do you really think you can beat us?
Are you happy now?
W-Why, Big Sister?
What'd you say's done?
So what if we do?
This fight! You know,
alcohol catches fire!
We do, stupid-head! Let go!
I told you! I came here
to tell you to stop!
Special Attack! Fire Star!
Sounds like he has something to say.
If you make a big fuss
about her being your friend,
the pirates'll grow suspicious of Nami
and her eight years of fighting
will be all for nothing!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Water! Water!
Water! Water! Water! Water!
Luffy...
Don't make her suffer
any more than she has.
--Ow! Ow! Ow!
--This isn't good!
Help me...
She has to fight alone,
so the most painful thing for her
Water, water, water! Water!
What the... What the...
I cried as much as I wanted.
I've whined enough, too.
Usopp Hammer!!
is having people who
call her their friend!
People with Devil Fruit
powers can't swim!
Though, even people without
powers would sink in this situation!
And I'm resolved as well!
I have to go. Everyone's fighting!
He's gonna throw him into the sea?!
Of course I will!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
--Get back here! Damn brat!
--How dare you steal our treasure?!
Don't touch my treasure!
Oww!
Fool.
Luffy...
Stealing from pirates?!
Darn you!
You son of a bitch...!
Yeah!
Sorry, but I don't care
about that Octo-Man.
Ugh! Usopp Hammer!
I'm using the huge number of
pirates in this era to my advantage!
How pointless.
Usopp Hammer!
Usopp Hammer! Usopp Hammer!
I have to hurry up and rescue Luffy...
It's like, "You get what you deserve!"
Usopp Rubberband of Doom!
Usopp Hammer! Usopp Hammer!
Big Bro! Watch out!!
Let's go.
You're covered in cuts, though!
How dare you beat Hachi!
--Luffy!
--Damn you!
Usopp Hammer!
Usopp Hammer! Usopp Hammer!
Yeah. I sorta screwed up.
Yeah!
Usopp Hammer! Usopp Hammer!!
You...
But look at this! One million Berries!
You sure did send me flying!
Forget that! You need
medical treatment, quick!
Hey! Are you guys alright?!
I'm fine! It's nothing!
Oh? I didn't know there was someone
Did Arlong do this to you?!
No one will ever find it here!
in the East Blue who
could survive my fist.
--I'm coming to save...
--Idiot! Don't get worked up!
Move aside.
I'll gather money little by little,
I win! I beat a fishman!
There're probably many...
especially at a certain restaurant.
We have business with the fishmen.
They want us to go in the water!
and it'll be 100 million
when I'm grown up!
Now that we know the
truth about Big Sis Nami,
The fishmen'd obviously have
the advantage in an underwater fight!
we felt the only thing
we can do was defeat Arlong.
You sure take me lightly, don't you?
I have a long ways to go...
There's only one way to save Luffy!
It serves you right!
So we challenged him...
100 million Berries...
I can do it, too, if I try!
Take these guys down in an
instant, then go into the water?
But we lost by a hair.
Did you see that?!
B-Big Bro! That's reckless!
It's taken a long time,
but just seven million left...
Don't make light of me, you bastards!!
Hey, stop it!
--Let's do it! There's no time!
--Yeah!
Sorry, but we're not letting
you through this door,
You'll die if you go into the
sea with wounds like that!
I can earn that much now in one try!
Just how many seconds
will Rubber Man hold out?
seeing as you have no hope for victory!
What?!
Shut up! He's at his limit!
Just one more journey,
and it'll all be over...
We're waiting for certain
men to arrive here, you see!
Oh, so that's the game?
There's no time to wait
until your fight is over!
I see.
Yeah, I know.
Certain men?
Everyone in Cocoyashi Village
and I will be free of Arlong.
I'd bet my life on it. They will come!
There's no time to waste
any more. I know that much.
You can have the fish.
Please... come back to life!
I'm trying to stop you when
I'm fully aware of that!
You can cut and trim the octopus.
And then...
You just shut up, you damn idiot!
And then, I think I can finally
smile from the bottom of my heart...
You can't complain if I do this, right?!
Come back to life quick!
Or it'll be too late!
This is interesting!
Your friends are... Your friends are...!
He wants to fight against me,
a fishman, in the water?
Bellemere-san...
He's a real idiot!
That's reckless! Fighting in
the water is what they want!
Here they come!
I thought that they had a chance in
this fight. Was it just a dream...?
This is bad... I'm out of strength...
What did that damn shark do?
I don't know.
What do we do?!
He can't help himself now!
As soon as he shot water,
they both vomited blood and flew...
What does the navy want with Nami?
If I remember correctly,
he's from Cocoyashi Village...
Big Bro Luffy's going to die!
You simply need to lead the way quietly.
It's them...
His neck! Luffy's neck is stretched!
Just who are they?
I can kill humans like you
without even directly touching
you if I have some water.
If they can't handle them,
Why does that old guy have
a pinwheel on his head?
Sorry, I'm not strong enough
to pull the whole body.
then there's no hope
for not only this island,
To think they can't
even breathe underwater...
Spit out water with your neck stretched.
Please at least breathe!
but for the future of
the entire East Blue!
That's the difference
between fishmen and humans.
So cool!
Humans are utterly pitiful creatures!
Give me a break!
The faces of those four men
who're here to change destiny...
Come back to life!
I hope it's not too late!
I'd better hurry up before I
can't hold my breath any more.
Bring it on! I challenge you, Octo-Man!
Burn their images into your eyes!
I see... He can't break the rock,
Guess I'll get started on
my final act of plundering!
This isn't funny...
but if Luffy's neck is stretched above
the water, he can at least breathe.
Just a water shooting game to him
is like a shotgun shot to us...
Game! Game!
I'll take care of you in five seconds!
Which means if I kick and break that
rock, I can leave the rest to that man.
No, three seconds!
So this is the power of a shark...
Move aside.
The navy?!
Don't be in such a rush.
And he's in a class by
himself among fishmen...
Fishman Karate... Forearm Sledge!
And why is Gen-san with them?
No matter what happens, none of
you have any hope of surviving!
He's in another league...
Are you the girl thief known as Nami?
Hey, do you think those two
idiots were part of Zoro's group?
Die already.
Realize... that you all are mere humans!
Your lives are not worth that much.
Our information has it you've hidden
treasure you stole from pirates
Zoro's? They seemed too weak for that.
in this tangerine orchard.
They're not even worth killing.
Arlong!!
That's for sure!
Big Sis Nami!
--Nami-san!
--Nacchan...
They were pirates, though.
I have no intentions
of condemning you.
Hachi Ink Jet!
Hey, Nami! I was about to
crush some pirates just now.
However, stealing is stealing.
Come back to life!
Therefore, as of this moment,
all of the property you've stolen
Hang on, Luffy!
What did you come here for?
now belongs to the government!
Please... hurry!
What the...?
I-I'm gonna be killed!
Now give us all of your stolen goods!
To kill you...
This guy's persistent! Ughhh!
Which one of you is Arlong?!
We're confiscating it!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Ughhh!
I'll hold back that half-fish bastard.
You go into the sea!
Alright! Now we know
all about this island!
You just had to run ahead by yourself!
I-I can't breathe!
Dammit! That topknot bastard!
He's attacking me from behind!
I said don't hog all the prey!
You damn octopus!
I don't care about you!
Let's hurry and meet up with Luffy!
Yeah! Leave Luffy to me!
Yeah.
This isn't good!
Really?
All right! I've got your back!
--What're you doing?
--Appreciating happiness.
I gotta hurry and save Luffy!
But in order to rescue Luffy...
--Huh?
--What's wrong?!
Yeah, that's the thing!
I'm kind of in trouble! Hear me out!
Even if I'm at a disadvantage,
I'll beat him up for sure!
Hey! You've got my back from that far?!
Hey! Are the wounds
you got from Hawk-Eye...
I can stop Nami-san's suffering
with my own two hands!
Oh, crap! That guy
plans to do something!
Ahh... My "Do Not Fight
Arlong" disease is...
It's all for Nami-san.
Shut up! I can't afford to faint here!
So that's what you're
thinking after all!
What do I do?
What do I do?! What do I do?!
Hey, Nami! What's wrong?!
That's a lie, isn't it?
Waaaah!!
You're still here?!
Just leave the island already!
Ahh! I'm saved!
Shut up!!
Wait, is running all I do?
Luffy!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Proud Warriors!
Sanji and Usopp's Fierce Battles"
"Luffy at Full Power! Nami's
Determination and the Straw Hat"
"Luffy Rises!
Result of the Broken Promise!"
"Luffy Submerged!
Zoro vs. Hatchan the Octopus"
"Luffy in Big Trouble!
Fishmen vs. the Luffy Pirates"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!