Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
That's right. You are the man
who stole one of my dreams!
Who the hell are you...?!
I put a lot of thought into my dream!
If I ate the fruit, I'd use my abilities
to watch women bathe!
No! Just think of all the things I could
use it for. I could... watch women bathe!
No, Just imagine how I could help others.
I could... watch women bathe!
Phantom Hand!
Phantom Leg!
I'm not about to let go, you sick beast!
If you're a mix of a bunch of animals,
I bet you'll make lovely mincemeat!
Extra Haché!
Your lack of experience is going
to make you humiliate yourself
when you underestimate others, greenhorn.
You jerk! Now I'm ticked!
Gum-Gum...
Why did you jump over the rail?
Trying to run away?
...Stamp!
That hurt, brat!
Take that! So much for me not being
able to touch you, Giant Shallot!
Now then, I think I might teach
that Horo-Horo Chick a lesson,
since she's weaker than me!
Huh? Where did she go?
Over here, Mr. Negative Nose.
Huh? I don't see you.
Could she be outside?
No, she couldn't be out there...
We're up on a really high fl--whoa!
I just figured out how
I'm going to take you down.
Once I knock you off,
the others will be easy pickings!
Wait a sec! This is not what I was expecting!
"Save Me, Hero!! My Enemy
Is the Immortal Princess!"
That stinking hurt! You're going
to regret that, Straw Hat!
Stuff it! I'll kick your butt
as many times as it takes.
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp!
Why, you--! Get off of me!
Your wish is my command. Brick Bat!
Not again!
Gum-Gum Finger Net!
There's no end to this!
Why... are you... flying in the sky?
This doesn't make any sense!
Just a minute ago, she was running
like her life depended on it.
Where'd all this confidence come from?
You merely caught me by surprise back there.
Why?! Why aren't you falling to your knees?!
I've always been negative!
What?!
It never occurred to me that someone
might be immune to my Negative Ghosts.
I have just one thing to say to you.
There are plenty of good things in life!
Drop it!
So what if you can fly?!
I'm a sniper! I don't care if you
can fly or dance or whatever!
Allow me to explain.
My new weapon, Kabuto,
has greater stability and range
thanks to these five prongs.
If I activate the Breath Dials I got
at the sky island when I shoot,
the rotation of my ammo changes,
creating different effects!
It's like a super Pachinko!
Flame! Flash! Impact!
By changing the Dials, my ammo
can grow even more powerful!
No one can escape this puppy!
Now say your pray--
She's gone!
Huh? Where'd she go?
I'm behind you.
Go ahead and take your best shot.
Ehhh?!
Wh-What in the world are you?!
Why, you...!
Special Attack! Swallowtail Meteor!
Gah! Sh-She reverted to her original size!
Whoa!
You little...! I'm gonna shoot you down!
Mantis Meteor!
What's the problem?
Didn't you have perfect aim?
Darn it!
Take this! And this, dammit!
Eat this! Mantis! Swallowtail!
Dragonfly! Mayfly Meteor!
No!
Y-Your hands...!
Your hands sunk into my body!
I-I've been stabbed!
Y-You stabbed me with your bare hands!
I'm finished...! I'm gonna...!
I'm dead meat! I'm gonna die from blood loss!
Stupid! Take a better look.
I haven't hurt you, but my
hands are inside your body.
Do you know what this means?
It's true that you're about to die.
Let me tell you why. I'm just about to
crush your heart with my own two hands.
Don't! Please don't crush it!
I'll die for real!
I'm going to kill you.
Now writhe in agony as you die!
No! Please stop it! I don't wanna die!
Not that I can actually do that!
That was a bluff?!
Ouch! I hit my head!
If I had the physical ability to crush your heart,
you would have died the moment
my hands pierced through your body.
Either way, that was bad for my heart!
I merely passed through...
...your body.
No!
Even though you can clearly see me...
...my body can pass through anything.
Special Attack! Six Chamber Viper Star!
Didn't I just say I can go through anything?
Stop it! This is creepy!
In other words, your attacks can't touch me.
Why, you--! Get away from me!
Shoo, darn it! You stupid little...!
Now what are you going to do?
None of your attacks will work on me.
Shut up! A second ago, you bluffed
that you could crush my heart!
I bet you couldn't touch me if you wanted to!
I can't attack you, but you can't
attack me, either! Isn't that right?
Mini-Hollow...
Wh-What are those...?
Ghost Rap.
A-A shock wave?
Get away from me!
Don't touch me! Get it off of me!
Get it off, meanie!
Rap.
Okay...! Special Attack! Firebird Star!
Shoot!
It's not fair!
How come she can attack me
when I can't attack her?!
How is this even a fight?!
Whoa! Get outta my way!
I can't see where I'm going! Move it!
Move!!
Ghost Rap.
Where did he go?
I'm done going easy on him.
Ghost Rap.
What the heck? Why am I failing so hard?
And here... I thought that
woman was weaker than me!
Tada!
The bear!
Careful, there. Kumacy is
stronger than a real bear.
What gives?!
I was so excited when I was
the only one in my entire crew...
...who stood a fighting chance
against this chick's powers!
You guys--your abilities--
are powerless before this chick.
I'll take her on!
This is my chance to shine!
After a declaration like that,
how could I end up like this?
I'm screwed... This is the end!
There is no way I can beat her!
That woman's gonna kill me and then
she's gonna catch Luffy and the guys.
Our crew is doomed!
The weight of saving everyone was...
too great for me to bear.
Save me!
Save me, Sogeking!
Please tell me! How would you handle this?
I was born on the island of snipers
Kumacy!
Stomp!
I never miss my mark
Monster! How dare you purify my Kumacy?!
Lulu lala lu
And what's with that goofy mask?!
Whether it's a mouse's eyeball, lock on!!
Or even your heart, lock on!!
It is hardly goofy!
It is a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Sogeking.
The man who hails from the island of snipers
You're totally goofing off!
You aren't a different person!
Time to flee!
You're making a run for it?!
Lululu, lulu lala
You bet I am! I'm not sticking
around for this crazy fight!
Now... run away!
I use my negative outlook and
bluffs to get through fights!
Sogege, soge, soge
I never thought someone
would use those against me!
Sogeking!
Are you okay with this?
Calm yourself! Face her and fight, Usopp-kun!
Shut up! I've had it!
There is no way I can beat her!
That is not true! You are a very capable man!
Can you prove that?
--No!
--You can't?!
Mini-Hollow!
But think carefully! There are
several oddities about that woman.
Yeah, you have a point.
Like how she suddenly got really confident!
At first, she was definitely
running away in fear of me.
If my attacks were ineffective from
the start, she didn't need to flee.
She should have been able
to pass through walls and fly!
But all she did back then
was whine while she ran.
Why was she so negative?
That's it!
Rap. Rap!
The change occurred after I lost sight of her!
Something must have happened!
Remember...
What happened during the brief moment
that bear stalled me and I lost sight of her...?
What happened?
Well, I guess it's about time
I handed you over to Moria-sama.
That's it! I've solved the puzzle!
Are there any hiding spots nearby?
Like a hidden room...?
A room!
Your trick...!
What is it? Are these your final words?
Wait! Where do you think you're aiming?!
That's it!
--Hey, wait!
--Special Attack! Atlas Comet!
I found it!
That is your real body.
Usopp Eye can find any opponent's weakness!
Usopp Weapon has defeated
multiple formidable foes!
And Usopp Brain can devise awesome strategies
to pull me out of any sticky situation!
If you take me lightly, you'll get hurt.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Perona Is Terrified!!
Usopp and Untruthful Share the Same 'U'"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!