Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Ow, ow, ow...
Look over there!
Didn't Curly Cook come out with him?
Don't take life so lightly!
Your trick...!
What's the hold-up?
You can be rather cruel.
Wait! Where do you think you're aiming?!
Weren't you going to kick my
butt as many times as it takes?
They're moving right before your very eyes,
and you think they aren't alive?
One-Sword Style!
Soaring Dragon...
Yeah! I will in just a sec, so hang tight!
That's it!
Behold!
Hey, wait!
Three-Pace Hum...
Special Attack! Atlas Comet!
Well, I don't mind the wait,
but he'll come back if you don't hurry.
Damn it!
...Notch Slash!
...Blaze!
Nami-san...
"He"? Who are you talking about?
Wait!
Now start licking the floor, Cindry.
Moria!
You!
Are you going to chase
after me no matter what?
Okay, Hogback-sama.
I have lost.
I'm worried about that huge zombie,
That's right. I don't have
time to be goofing off.
but taking you down is the only way
to recover everyone's shadows.
Once, a legendary samurai
wielded the great sword Shusui.
When a human's heart isn't linked
to her body, she is no longer human!
I need to hurry back.
I won't let you escape!
By using corpses that can't
stick up for themselves,
I am sure this katana would be
happy to have you as its master.
Oh, jeez. You're such a handful.
you're creating nothing but monsters!
Don't! Robin is a lady!
For every zombie you create,
you're making a person miserable!
Look! I am the last one laughing!
A lady...?
Don't lecture me on life when you're
a mediocre doctor, pirate reindeer!
What of it?!
I found it!
She sure is sound asleep.
Let's go elsewhere... and hold
the ceremony... one more time,
Robin!
That is your real body.
Cindry-chan, finish those two off!
Unbelievable! Sanji actually kicked...
One! Two! Three!
I'll take your sword, but I'll pretend
that our duel never happened...
Golden...
my quiet bride!
No!
...samurai of the Wano Kingdom!
...Pound!
"Perona Is Terrified!!
Usopp and Untruthful Share the Same 'U'!"
Oh, crap!
Usopp!
You don't have to listen to
that monster! Ow, ow, ow...
Chopper! Robin!
W-W-We've got a problem!
O-O-Our wanted posters are
a-attached to Zombie Luffy's arm!
I will kill you!
Sleep till dawn!
"Chopper Is Furious!!
Hogback's Evil Medical Practices!"
Is the ability to move all that matters?
Humans are freer than that!
You're the one who treats them
like they aren't humans!
I can see you flying around.
I-I'm sure of it!
You can pass through people and walls!
Didn't that samurai just say something?
And you can shrink and grow at will!
He is totally...
Dogguin! Jigoro! Help Cindry out!
That sounds just like a ghost
without a physical body!
Take out the pests!
Tell me: How does it feel to be
subjugated by the might of your friends?
Long story short, what just happened?
But considering how you fled
from me there for a while...
Three-Sword Style...
...108-Pound Phoenix!
...coming after us!
In short, the fight is apparently over.
I can't believe you tried to stuff salt
down my throat with your weird powers!
Don't follow me!
Come out, Straw Hat Crew!
I've never seen a duel like this before.
They're strong!
Wait, Horo-Horo Chick!
Why did you attack me along with them?!
Darn it! I never expected
Sanji to kick Robin.
Don't follow me!
That samurai wasn't taking me
the least bit seriously!
I'm sure you still had a
physical body back then.
He isn't Sanji anymore!
Who is that Sanji guy?
Don't make me kill you, jerk face.
Darn it, Luffy! Are you going
to crush your own crew?
Someone must have issued the order.
I'm afraid they don't have a single
memory of your days as crewmates!
I hope the real Luffy is all right.
"Slashes Dancing on the Rooftop!!
Showdown: Zoro vs. Ryuma!"
What is that?!
Wh-What are you--
Jump! Jump! I want you to
jump out the window together!
In short, you're a ghost that got
created when I was distracted.
Occasionally fresh zombies retain
some of the shadow's feelings,
Can we take that monster down?
but these shadows have
fully settled into their bodies.
They've completely lost their human hearts.
Your real body is tucked
away right over there!
They've become zombies that
will obey my every command!
You can't trick me any longer!
"Luffy Is the Enemy! The Ultimate Zombie
vs. the Straw Hat Crew!"
As far as zombies are concerned,
their orders are absolute!
I cannot...
move.
I'm actually happy... to see that
you're rotten to the core, Hogback!
C-Cindry!
In all actuality, you have
saved countless lives.
And here I thought you
were just a negative idiot.
I really did respect you as a doctor.
Wh-Wh-What is that? Its face freaks me out.
Did that mask boost your courage?
The same goes for your zombie research.
I'm surprised you could
calmly analyze the situation.
Death can come suddenly...
It's literally a monster.
But you're only 90% right.
I'm sure there are a lot
of things the deceased
Aren't they...?
I'm not a ghost being controlled by my body!
You think that you can steal
my black sword, Shusui?
and those they left behind
never got a chance to say.
Hey, Usopp! That you down there?
To be precise, I'm going to take
the sword from beside your corpse.
I'm not asking for years. If they
could have just a few minutes!
I can leave my body by having
an out-of-body experience.
What was that? I thought I
heard someone say my name...
This is a sentient Hollow of yours truly!
If there was a way to bring back the dead...
I see. You are full of spirit!
Z-Zoro! Why are you on the roof?
...even if people cast stones,
calling it "evil medicine"...
All righty, then! So what would happen
if you lost a body to return to?
He's here! He's here!
Franky! And Brook's okay, too.
I wouldn't provoke him if I were you...
...it would mean the world to those it saved!
At any rate, it looks like we can
check the skeleton off our list.
I see you also carry three swords.
If I go after your body,
my attacks will definitely hit home!
But it's too soon to check Nami-chan off.
Yeah, but one is a broken blade.
So when you said that you were
researching how to "resurrect the dead,"
Wh-Who's here?
I just carry it at my waist because
it doesn't feel right without it.
Jerk! Stop it!
Well, now you get to meet him,
I thought that you truly
were an amazing doctor.
Special Attack! Big Bang Star!
Straw Hat.
I'm a Three-Sword Style swordsman.
A Three-Sword Style swordsman?
I've never heard of such a thing.
Fool! Why would I go to
such lengths for others?
Is it a circus act?
That was close!
You missed! And it was a dud to boot.
Hey, move your butt!
You said that you respected how I used
to save lives, but it was the same deal!
It's a pity I can't let you
see it in action right now.
Why in the world are you
getting in our way, Luffy?
Here I go again!
I won't let you!
"Oars Roars! Come Out, Straw Hat Crew!"
I'd break that squat nose of yours!
I was simply a genius!
Special Hollow!
I conducted operations for money,
I'm sure. You seem quite strong.
Whoa! Is this like the ones from earlier?!
but there was no stopping
the unwanted flood of patients
Emotions beyond my
recollection are surfacing.
Mini-Hollow...
that came from around
the world for treatment!
I feel as though I am standing
face to face with a giant beast.
...Rap!
"Save my dad!"
"Save my child!"
"Save my beloved!"
It is a strange, exhilarating sensation!
So this is an "extra-large" version?
It got old!
Hey, what's gotten into you, Cindry-chan?
I feel as though I could start dancing.
Come on, Cindry-chan!
Luffy...?
It was a pain!
Oh, crap! Lemme go, punk!
Cindry-chan! Earth to Cindry-chan!
He is my enemy.
The run-of-the-mill quack
couldn't save them, but I could.
Struggle all you like! But I won't
let you hurt my physical body.
Hey, what's the matter?
What a shock!
Can you understand the hardships of a genius?
W-Wait! Hey, whoa! Time out!
My name is Oars.
I...
The dumpling-sized ones packed a wallop!
You're free to respect me if you want.
My body will get blown to pieces
if this big guy goes off!
cannot move.
But your disappointment is uncalled for.
Nice to meet ya!
I cannot stop crying.
If you can't forgive me as a doctor
because I don't match your ideals,
You can't touch it even if
you squirm. It's a ghost!
Aubade Coup Droit!
You can't move? What the
heck are you talking about?
then you never understood me
to begin with, stupid reindeer!
And dry those crocodile tears!
Are you going to start
lecturing me on medical ethics?!
H-He used a pistol?!
Do you realize who gave you a body
I wouldn't dream of it!
Stuff it! What's "nice" about this?
I-It was a thrust!
that can move as long as you have a soul?!
If I used that move,
it wouldn't be as impressive!
I don't consider you a doctor!
Sheesh! That is such a
birdbrained thing to say.
What?!
You exist to serve your master!
The same goes for these zombies.
You sound just like Luffy.
That is how zombies find
meaning in their existence!
All you've done is reanimate the dead.
He's trying to pick a
fight with that monster.
It looks like the owner of
her body is trying to resist him.
They aren't alive!
Did that moronic cook manage to save Nami?
He shot a hole through the wall!
Don't take life so lightly!
She died ten years ago.
To shoot a thrust like that...
Just how strong is he?!
He's in hotter water than the girlie!
Could the body still have a
will even if the soul has left?
You can be rather cruel.
They're moving right before your very eyes,
and you think they aren't alive?
I'd say it's a draw.
Even if we scoured every library in the world,
I doubt we could find an answer.
C-C-Crap! This looks really bad!
Yep.
Yeah, you heard me!
Dr. Chopper, the "dead" are being given
a second shot at life. It's a miracle!
Sanji's in trouble!
Gum-Gum...
This was unexpected.
I had assumed they were only
interested in our shadows.
...Bazooka!
You nearly got me.
I will kill those two.
I wonder if we got a little carried away.
What the heck?!
It's like all they care
about now is Luffy's shadow.
Gum-Gum... Whip!
Atta girl! You've finally returned
to your senses, Cindry-chan!
When did that
Haramaki freak get in a counter attack?!
Why would you want to reject these lives?
The attacks... were nearly simultaneous.
Scary! I'm scared! I
can't fight that monster!
Behold!
Be sure to buy lots of time!
Enough for me to get away.
So he can throw his attacks as well.
It looks like I should lend him a hand.
What a pity. I was hoping
for some kind of miracle.
The skirmish between them
just now truly did end in a draw.
Wait, wait, wait!
Don't move.
W-We should leave this to Sanji
so we don't trip him up.
The samurai zombie is currently
using my shadow to move,
Doce Fleurs!
Ow, ow, ow...
but the samurai was probably an expert
swordsman when he was still alive.
Don't worry. He should be able
to escape without too much effort.
Tsk!
Now start licking the floor, Cindry.
What's the hold-up?
I believe those two may possess
the same type of build as swordsmen.
Weren't you going to kick my
butt as many times as it takes?
Wait!
But won't that giant recognize him
from the wanted poster?
Okay, Hogback-sama.
Like I'm gonna wait!
Yeah! I will in just a sec, so hang tight!
I doubt the beast will
simply let him walk away.
Does it mean anything if
they share the same build?
Wh-Why is the room shaking?!
You've got a lot to learn, Robin-kun!
That's just the thing.
Well, I don't mind the wait,
but he'll come back if you don't hurry.
It means their strengths
lie in the same areas.
Do you think he'll recognize Sanji based off
the composite sketch on the wanted poster?
"He"? Who are you talking about?
Damn it! You're a pirate reindeer
just pretending to be human!
I doubt this duel will last long.
You're right! Sanji doesn't look anything
like the picture on his wanted poster.
How dare you side with a bunch of corpses?!
--Bingo!
--I see. You have a good point.
You!
You aren't even human, you stinking monster!
Huh?
Prelude Au Fer!
A monster, a cyborg, a pervert,
a guy with a long nose,
Damn it! Where'd it go?
Didn't you see that room, Dr. Chopper?
A sword-breaker assault?!
Oh, you look just like the
picture on the wanted poster.
That's weird!
and a moss head follow my captain!
Two-Sword Style... Flash!
What?!
Unlike you guys, he doesn't
have to boss around corpses
What looks the same?!
Nuh-uh!
that can't speak for themselves!
"What," huh? Your whole face.
Let go, freak!
Hmmm, nope.
No, it doesn't, stupid!
Robin!
All right! I'm on it.
At any rate, aren't you one of the pirates?
That is my room.
Demon Magma Bear!
Pierna Fleurs!
I can't find it!
So what if I am?!
The numerous photos were of the stage
actress Victoria Cindry before she died.
Huh? What's going on?
I'm gonna crush you.
Huh?
Shoot! Shoot!
What? What? What?!
I had been in love with
her for a very long time.
Sanji!
Oh, there it is! Found it!
I wasn't the only one. Her beauty had
charmed men from across the country.
W-W-Wait, Dr. Chopper! If I fall
from this height and hit my head,
Gavotte Bond en Avant!
Just doesn't feel right without this.
What was that, you bastard?
my genius noggin that is a gift
to the world will crack open!
Two-Sword Style Sword Draw...
I wanna become the rottin'
King of the Pirates!
...Rashomon!
Are you okay with that?
I don't care!
The zombies are less rotten
than the stuff between your ears!
I know! I should fire a
salute to liven things up!
Wait, Moria!
There!
Why don't you calm down a bit, Dr. Chopper?
He blocked my attack!
You're all set, Doctor.
Eat this! Robi-Cho Suplex!
S-S-Sorry! I shouldn't make a
patient sew a button back on.
Yeah, that'd be rottin' cool!
Jerk!
Hey, where are the cannons?
Drat! That shadow got in the way again!
They slashed through the support beams!
It's all right.
Huh? Well? Gimme a cannon!
You never learn.
He's twice the size of a giant.
Oops! This is a dead end.
So this is my zombie?
Thanks to you, I'll be
able to go back on stage.
Oh, crud! This floor is toast!
It's dangerous up here!
Ocho Fleurs!
I've finally got you cornered!
Say your prayers, Giant Shallot!
I've been waiting for you, Oars!
Shouldn't you be the one saying your prayers?
Thank you very much.
It looks like your shadow has
finally settled into your body.
Father! Mother! Sorry to
have kept you waiting.
While you're wasting time with me,
Have you become an obedient zombie?
Uh, excuse me...
your combat skills are being used
to wipe out your crew, Straw Hat.
Tell me! Who is your master?
Man, hang on! We're gettin' outta here.
Despite her popularity,
she was down to earth.
My master is Moria-sama.
Shut up! My crew won't go down that easily.
The whole roof's comin' down!
She was close to her family...
Is that right? Then I'd better make
a break for it before you do me in!
What?!
Seventy-two Pound Phoenix!
Hey, how could you say that?!
Are you really my shadow?
She was kind to everyone...
A truly wonderful woman.
Don't listen to this jerk!
Brick Bat!
Polka Remise!
But that woman...
Whoa! Crap!
Who are you, punk in the straw hat?
I'm Number 1!
Bye!
Gum-Gum Gatling!
Weapons Left!
Let me present your
commemorative first mission.
Look at the wanted posters
attached to your arm!
Wait! I won't let you escape!
Those ruffians are currently
running amok on Thriller Bark.
What brute strength!
They are the Straw Hat Crew!
Moria-sama, we've got trouble!
...rejected my proposal,
when my renown as a doctor
Dang, that was close!
Crush them mercilessly and
toss them onto their ship!
had let me obtain anything I wanted.
You still mean to fight back?
You don't know when to give up!
I don't care if any of them die.
She already had a fiancé.
What happened here?
Those worth over 100 million
won't die if you squash them anyway.
And shortly thereafter, I caught wind
of some news that left me dumbfounded.
Moria-sama, where did you go?
Cut loose! Let me see
the extent of your power.
Robin...
Hey,
Cindry had died in an accident.
Okay, Moria-sama.
where do you think you're looking?
Shouldn't you be a bit more nervous,
you stupid reindeer?
I felt drained.
Sanji...
I ultimately abandoned my work.
Huh? Who're you talkin' about?
Don't make me kill you, punk!
Wh-What are they doing?
Ah, there's one! It's Straw Hat!
That is when he came.
A giant man appeared before me.
Careful! You don't want to fall!
You're being obnoxious,
you poor excuse for a penguin!
Goodbye, Straw Hat!
Shut up, stinky old man!
It was my master, Gecko Moria!
Guys! This is no time for
arguing amongst ourselves.
You're running away?! You jerk!
Dr. Hogback, lend me a hand!
Gum-Gum...
Who gave you permission to bicker?
H-H-Hey, wait! That's dangerous!
We're following Hogback-sama's orders!
Beat it, you lousy bat!
...Bell!
That's absurd!
You have no hope of
defeating me, dumb reindeer!
Hogback-sama would never order
you to do something like this.
Falling...!
Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
What exactly did he say?
And I boarded this ship under the condition
"Take out the pests!"
that he would use his miraculous
ability to resurrect Cindry!
You pest!
Robin!
--Take out the pest!
--You're the pest!
--They're a lost cause...
--You are such a pest!
What?!
Jerk! Watch where you're aiming, moron!
What's that?
What was that, bastard?!
L-Luffy's zombie...!
You're a nuisance the way
you dart around everywhere!
Oars!
How can they fight with such poor footing...?
Now!
Now, Robin! Get the salt!
The floor is collapsing!
Chopper, come over here!
I'm on it!
Okay!
Damn! That still hurts.
Huh?!
Ouch!
That jerk tried to make a fool of me!
That was a close call.
But I'm not about to pass out.
I can't collapse until this
event of a lifetime is over!
Oh, jeez. You're such a handful.
Now then, let's resume the
wedding ceremony. Kiss the bride.
Don't! Robin is a lady!
I'll finally get to kiss her this time!
A lady...?
What of it?!
That's Absalom-sama!
I stole her body...
This... is Luffy...
I know! Absalom-sama might
know where Moria-sama went.
Robin!
--Here I go!
--Absalom-sama!
It was so easy to obtain the actress,
Cindry, and bend her to my will!
Unbelievable! Sanji actually kicked--
Hogback and Cindry fell down a floor.
I'm afraid my swords will break
if this drags out much longer.
Wh-What was that for, you perverted beast?!
He truly has the body and
spirit needed to support the
Crap! This is heavy.
strength of a legendary swordsman.
He insulted him! He slammed
him with an insult!
It's game over for you.
Crap! Now we're in for a storm!
Cindry-chan, get this stone slab off of me!
Hildon, what are you doing here?
Cindry-chan!
So? What did you want?
Huh?
He's surprisingly calm.
You see, I'm trying to find Moria-sama.
I wish plates would cease to exist.
Plates?!
This fight is over!
C-Cindry-chan, hurry! Save me on the double!
Can't you see for yourself? He isn't here!
Look! Oars is coming.
The personality of the woman who had
spurned me was of little consequence.
So it would seem.
Sorry, but could you get
someone else to help you?
As long as she retained her beauty...
One-Sword Style!
I... I can't get stepped
on when I'm a genius!
I'm busy at the moment.
Soaring Dragon...
That is the zombie, Cindry-chan!
Sorry for the intrusion. Goodbye!
Three-Pace Hum...
Hey! Why are you just standing there?
Of course I'm thrilled,
but I'm sure she is as well!
Wait a second, Hildon.
I'm your master!
Yes, what is it?
She gets to live in this
world as a human again.
How dare you call me a "perverted beast"?!
...Notch Slash!
...Blaze!
That was mean.
Cannon! Cannon! Cannon! Cannon!
It took that long to sink in?!
Cannon! Cannon! Can... Huh?
Why was I searching for cans again?
I... cannot move.
How could you call her a human?
Make her stop licking the floor!
Huh?
Wait, Giant Shallot!
What's this?
What gives? What am I doing out here?
My wound is bursting into flames!
Let's see... I think I'm gonna
become the King of the--
When a human's heart isn't linked
to her body, she is no longer human!
Huh? Who's there?
Nope, nope! That's not right.
Darn it! It's that stupid shadow!
It's not me who will become
King of the Pirates, but...
By using corpses that can't
stick up for themselves,
Just you wait, Moria!
you're creating nothing but monsters!
I... cannot move.
For every zombie you create,
you're making a person miserable!
Man, he really let me have it.
What?!
I figured that out, which is
why I can't forgive you guys!
I finally found him!
Moria-sama!
Moria-sama, I have news that
I'd like to report right away!
Don't lecture me on life when you're
a mediocre doctor, pirate reindeer!
Hildon? What is it?
To be honest, it would appear the ship
is moving in an unfortunate direction.
Cindry-chan, finish those two off!
We'll run into trouble if it
continues on its current course!
Is that right? If that's the case,
do something about it.
I have lost.
Okay.
You're repeating that nonsense again?!
I'm busy at the moment.
--Later!
--B-But...!
Your sense of loyalty is
the only will zombies have!
I'm going to turn you guys into marios!
You're in the way! Move it! Move!
Rejoice, Dr. Chopper! Once you are dead,
Once, a legendary samurai
wielded the great sword Shusui.
Now save me already!
I will make you my assistant,
since you admire me so much.
That's right. I don't have
time to be goofing off.
Your looks are all you
have, you crappy corpse!
I am sure this katana would be
happy to have you as its master.
I need to hurry back.
Square Plate Blades!
Didn't that samurai just say something?
One! Two! Three!
Long story short, what just happened?
Darn twerp's quickly darting every which way!
In short, the fight is apparently over.
I must hurry... Hurry back to Master...
I've never seen a duel like this before.
Stop it...!
Sanji!
That samurai wasn't taking
me the least bit seriously!
Damn you!
Hey! Hurry it up, Cindry!
Chopper!
Oars is coming!
Oars, look down! You imbecile!
It's me, you wretched ingrate!
I'm the one who modified your
body so that you could move!
Hey, Skeleton! What do you mean it's "over"?
It was an incredible duel...
I said to freakin' let me go, dammit!
You came so close, Mr. Negative Nose.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! What gives?! What gives?!
Sanji!
With my next signal, your body
will be blown to smithereens.
That last quake was way worse
than any of the ones before it!
Don't! Don't! No!
Don't underestimate her
just because she's a woman!
I don't wanna get blown to smithereens!
I've enhanced her muscles for combat.
Don't worry.
L-L-L... Luffy's zombie!
I'll be sure to tell
Hogback to use you as a mario.
You don't have to listen to
that monster! Ow, ow, ow...
It pains my samurai heart
that I must taste defeat...
Kamikaze Rap!
I will kill you!
You poor thing! And here you're already dead.
It vanished?!
The fact that you feel ashamed proves...
I swear, all that did was make a dust cloud!
How would the family you left behind
feel if they knew about this?
That was a close call!
The shock from that blast
went inside this shell.
...that you are a swordsman
in both mind and body!
Let go of me!
What's going--
If your family saw you covered in stitches
I wish we could have met
when you were still alive.
and being used as an expendable soldier,
Now it's my turn, you bastard!
I can't move! What is this?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
What is making everything shake?!
it would tear them apart!
I lied!
Let go of me!
Sanji!
You lied?
Are you okay?
I lied when I called the first attack
I shot at you the "Big Bang Star."
The heart you were born and
raised with is already dead,
What gives?!
It wasn't a dud, either.
It was actually my Birdlime Star.
but your body is being forced
to do the bidding of others.
You won't get away this time.
No way! Is that Luffy's zombie?!
What the hell?!
I made sure you couldn't move around
if you returned to your body.
I-Isn't that...?
It sure is! It's my shadow,
which Moria snatched away
Gum-Gum...
You what?!
Crap!
Are you questioning your eyes? Face facts!
from me five years ago!
Now I can deal with your
physical body and your Hollow!
Nami-san, seriously! This isn't
the time to get your beauty sleep!
It's one of Luffy's moves!
This is mankind's eternal dream!
I've resurrected the dead!
Can he extend his arms?!
Screw it! I'm gonna have to run for now.
Look! It's copying whatever I do!
Crap!
Is he a rubber man now?
Isn't that a given? It's your shadow.
The dead can come back to life!
...Sickle!
This might be hard for you to understand,
but I'm finally my old self again!
H-His arm didn't extend!
Huh? Nami-san?
Are you the one who purified Captain Kumacy?!
Is the ability to move all that matters?
But with power and reach
like that, who cares?!
Nami-san?
Wh-What?!
Perfect timing! Get him,
Lieutenant Gentleman Hippopotamus!
I'm touched! I'm moved!
Nami-san vanished...
Humans are freer than that!
So that freakishly huge
body isn't just for show.
These emotions are coursing through my veins!
You're the one who treats them
like they aren't humans!
Ah, not that I have any veins.
Impact!
Just one direct hit could
do some serious damage!
I guess they go "bone deep."
It couldn't be...!
It's back! After five years,
I have a shadow again!
It looks like the tables are turned.
Oars... I've heard that
name somewhere before.
Could he be the legendary Continent Puller
from ancient times, the Devil Oars?!
Jerk! You're still alive?
W-Was he actually strong?
Beast Man, show yourself!
Youch! My arm's gonna snap!
I'll take your sword, but I'll pretend
that our duel never happened...
That'd explain it. It sounds like
Luffy's zombie isn't a pushover.
Robin, hurry and feed her salt!
Gentleman Hippopotamus!
...samurai of the Wano Kingdom!
Right!
It looks like we finally
have control of this devil.
Dogguin! Jigoro! Help Cindry out!
Collier Frit!
I've won! This time she will be my bride!
Take out the pests!
I wonder if Sanji has already
found and rescued Nami.
Damn it! Give Nami-san back!
And how are Luffy and the others doing?
Where the hell are you?!
You don't have time to
be worrying about others.
At any rate, I've just gotta tell
everyone about how I beat
that Horo-Horo Chick when they
didn't stand a chance against her!
Have him play with you!
Enjoy the ultimate zombie!
Sanji!
I failed! Chopper!
He's stinking fast for a behemoth!
Three-Sword Style...
Special Attack! Shining Black Star!
I can't wait to see their faces!
...108-Pound Phoenix!
I've got ya, puny pirate!
Perona-sama!
Stop it, Zoro!
Crap! He's gonna get killed!
Do you think she's okay?
Hey, did you feel that just now?
Of course! Captain Kumacy and Lieutenant
Gentleman Hippopotamus went after her!
Yes, I did. It was so ominous
that it made my hair stand on end.
Doce Fleurs!
By now, Mr. Negative Nose
is the one crying like a baby!
Not... her again!
Oh! But since I'm a skeleton,
I don't have any hair!
Sanji!
Phew, that was a close call!
Take out... the pests!
Ah! I do have hair!
All of my hard work would go down
the drain if I got taken down now.
Punk! That's your precious afro!
Don't forget about it!
What is that monster gonna do?
Cockroaches!
There'd go my bragging rights.
Maybe you'd rather have
a pompadour hairstyle!
Also known as "Cockroach Star"!
--Jerk!
--Huh?
Hey, stop it!
Moving on! Sanji! Guys!
They're gross!
Sanji!
--Uh, pass!
--Come over here!
No, don't! Don't cut it!
Die, puny pirate!
Someone, get them off!
Why did you attack me along
with them?! Don't be a pest!
Help me! I can't get away!
Fire Bird Star!
They're getting in my clothes!
What happened here...?
Ew! I hate cockroaches!
Now you're asking for it!
Weren't they supposed to be
attending Absalom-sama's wedding?
I'm scared, Kumacy! Kumacy!
That's how I feel!
What is that?
The pests are supposed to get taken outside!
I'm getting goose bumps!
The Special Zombie did this to them.
This is hot.
Then get going! He issued that order to me!
Oh! I'm a skeleton, so--
I... I... I'm sorry!
Absalom-sama ordered them
to forcibly stop Oars,
It was meant for me!
I just said he issued it to me!
but he took them out in the blink of an eye.
Jerk!
Sanji!
I'm sure cockroaches are scary...
Absurd! Even though he's a
Special Zombie, he's still a zombie!
Hey! What are you two doing?
...but you should be more afraid of me!
Why would he attack his comrades?
There is the black-haired woman
and the reindeer eating cotton candy.
Oars is rather new to his life as a zombie.
You've underestimated me.
Hey, knock it off! You
need to actually work--
Apparently he still has
Straw Hat's personality.
Gah! Something just popped out!
--Robin!
--On it!
In the East Blue, I was renowned
for unparalleled brute strength.
What is that?!
T-Ten tons...? W-Whoa, where did
all of that strength come from?
He's headed our way!
Awesome! This is a ship?
Isn't this turning out to be fascinating?
Crap! Franky, lure him over here!
Th-That's... a zombie!
Knock it off! Don't pull
that out when I'm stuck here.
All righty! With this ship,
I'm gonna become King of the Pirates!
Now we're talking!
You ordered them to "take out the pests."
Eat this, monster!
It's Luffy's zombie.
They are obediently trying to
obey that order even as I speak.
Gum-Gum...
Look over there!
Didn't Curly Cook come out with him?
Actually, I'm not made of rubber.
I wonder what would happen
if you didn't issue a new order.
Gatling!
Look out!
Get off the roof, you two!
One Gorilla!
Don't get in the way of my adventure!
Two Gorilla!
Three-Sword Style...
...Two Gorilla Slash!
Even without their memories,
those two are still like water and oil...
Damn it!
I suspect it will take a while for him
to become an obedient zombie...
Y-You're gonna kill me! For real!
Unbelievable.
Get rid of the roaches! And drop the hammer!
Nami-san...
Gum-Gum...
Wh-What?! He took out all of these
General Zombies in an instant?
What is that stupid cook doing?
Enough with the roaches
and hammer! C'mon, please!
...Volcano!
Zoro, are you still alive?
Wait!
That's right.
They must have let their guard down!
No, he's dead if he falls from up there!
Otherwise this never would have happened.
Moria!
Isn't this a rather tall tower?
Are you going to chase
after me no matter what?
Usopp!
Huh?
Yes!
Why don't you order the two
of us to jump out the window?
I'm worried about that huge zombie,
No, stop it!
Chew on this, monster!
but taking you down is the only way
to recover everyone's shadows.
Stop it, please! I won't go after
your friends! Okay? Sound good?
Robin...?
If I were you, I'd start running!
Weapons Left!
What's gotten into you?
I won't let you escape!
Otherwise, Oars will do you in as well!
Please! Please, Usopp-sama!
He's so nimble! He dodged again!
I'll say that as many times as you like!
Golden...
Silence, Hildon! Are you mocking us?!
No!
Jump! Jump! I want you to
jump out the window together!
...Pound!
What's he up to this time?
The monster! How dare he kill our comrades?!
Look! I am the last one laughing!
--Sure.
--Huh?
Since Absalom-sama gave those orders,
She sure is sound asleep.
no one will mind if we
teach him a thing or two!
No, not you! Wait!
Let's go elsewhere... and hold
the ceremony... one more time,
Run faster! He wants us to jump out together.
I swear by our title as the strongest
that we will let Oars know just how
powerful the General Zombies are!
Don't tell me what to do!
Franky! Brook!
my quiet bride!
Zoro's coming down!
Is Perona-sama all right?
Shoot! He'll die if he hits the ground!
She's unconscious!
Cien Fleurs! Spider Net!
I don't see any injuries.
Captain Kumacy and the Lieutenant
were taken out! Curse Long Nose!
We don't want to.
--Ch-Charge!
--Yeah!
I won't forget this!
I survived? Damn it...!
You tricked me! You're horrible!
You're the scum of all mankind!
Don't get in my way!
Get her out of here!
This mansion is rottin' dangerous!
The Special Zombie will avenge them!
Luffy will purify all of the
zombies when he defeats Moria.
It's pretty lame when the princess
of the haunted mansion...
Gum-Gum...
Things look rottin' bad!
Get away from the mansion!
Eat this! You're still a zombie!
You're the one I want to throttle, Hogback!
...passes out over a balloon
and some toy cockroaches!
Special Attack! Salt Star!
The Special Zombie is fighting!
C-C-Cindry! Buy me some time!
I'm gonna run for the hills!
Get rottin' far!
H-He's huge! I can see
his head over the mansion.
Gotcha.
How do you like that?
Where is my answer? I'll give you
another shadow if they take you out.
You made a big mistake
Oh, oops! That's right. I'd forgotten!
Don't worry about dying!
when you challenged me to a
contest in lying and negativity!
I need to hurry on back.
Oh, crap!
I-It wasn't enough!
Sleep till dawn!
Usopp!
Not for his massive body!
Chopper! Robin!
W-W-We've got a problem!
Wha ha ha! Hee hee hee! Click my heels!
O-O-Our wanted posters are
a-attached to Zombie Luffy's arm!
Heavy Gong!
What happened to all of that
fire you had earlier, Straw Hat?
Damn it! Don't act so high-and-mighty
when you aren't fighting, Giant Shallot!
I-I'm sure of it!
I've already told you:
I am the man who will let others
make me the King of the Pirates.
What the--?!
He is totally...
And it looks like the day I realize my
dream has gotten a whole lot closer!
I cannot...
move.
I'll keep taking you down until
I recover all of the shadows!
C-Cindry!
...coming after us!
Like I said, defeating me won't--
When ya get down to it, I just need
to defeat you and this shadow!
Come out, Straw Hat Crew!
Didn't that samurai just say something?
The freak! Is he trying to get in our way?
Long story short, what just happened?
In short, the fight is apparently over.
Darn it, Luffy! Are you going
to crush your own crew?
Gum-Gum Rocket!
I've never seen a duel like this before.
Someone must have issued the order.
I don't care what happens to you,
but as things stand, your future looks bleak.
I hope the real Luffy is all right.
That samurai wasn't taking
me the least bit seriously!
What is that?!
D-Damn it, Luffy!
He's here! He's here!
Can we take that monster down?
A more powerful foe will be here
any minute now, you know?
I don't know any of you losers!
I am Moria-sama's servant, Oars!
Well, now you get to meet him...
...Straw Hat.
This should be fun.
Dr. Chopper, listen. The zombies are happy.
He's huge! This is my shadow?
You mean to steal my katana?
You are a feisty one.
Ab-sama! Forget that woman and pucker up!
Sanji!
He's insanely fast for someone so huge!
Learn when to quit! I won't kiss you!
If he lands a solid hit,
it could do serious damage!
After all, they are given a second
chance to live amongst us as humans!
So he has finally decided to submit to me!
--Then marry me!
--That isn't happening!
Let’s see what this "Two-Sword Style,"
or whatever it is, can do.
Crap! What is he going to do to Sanji?
--Then kiss me!
--Are you even listening?
--You're wrong!
--I'm wrong? Like your medical knowhow--
Tell me: Who is your master?
Hey, get back!
You just don't get it.
Shut up! That isn't a medical procedure!
No, you don't!
My master is Moria-sama.
I am tingling with excitement!
Don't underestimate me, monster!
Oh, shit! You made her wake up!
I'm so excited I could dance!
I'll never forgive you!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"You're Going Down, Absalom!!
Nami's Lightning Attack of Friendship!!"
"Luffy Is the Enemy! The Ultimate
Zombie vs. the Straw Hat Crew!"
"Slashes Dancing on the Rooftop!!
Showdown: Zoro vs. Ryuma!"
"Oars Roars! Come Out, Straw Hat Crew!"
"Chopper Is Furious!!
Hogback's Evil Medical Practices!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!