Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Your trick...!
Wait! Where do you think you're aiming?!
That's it!
Hey, wait!
Special Attack! Atlas Comet!
I found it!
That is your real body.
"Perona Is Terrified!!
Usopp and Untruthful Share the Same 'U'!"
I can see you flying around.
You can pass through people and walls!
And you can shrink and grow at will!
That sounds just like a ghost
without a physical body!
But considering how you fled
from me there for a while...
Don't follow me!
Wait, Horo-Horo Chick!
I'm sure you still had a
physical body back then.
Wh-What are you--
In short, you're a ghost that got
created when I was distracted.
Your real body is tucked
away right over there!
You can't trick me any longer!
And here I thought you
were just a negative idiot.
Did that mask boost your courage?
I'm surprised you could
calmly analyze the situation.
But you're only 90% right.
I'm not a ghost being controlled by my body!
I can leave my body by having
an out-of-body experience.
This is a sentient Hollow of yours truly!
All righty, then! So what would happen
if you lost a body to return to?
If I go after your body,
my attacks will definitely hit home!
Jerk! Stop it!
Special Attack! Big Bang Star!
That was close!
You missed! And it was a dud to boot.
Here I go again!
I won't let you!
Special Hollow!
Whoa! Is this like the ones from earlier?!
Mini-Hollow...
...Rap!
So this is an "extra-large" version?
Oh, crap! Lemme go, punk!
Struggle all you like! But I won't
let you hurt my physical body.
W-Wait! Hey, whoa! Time out!
The dumpling-sized ones packed a wallop!
My body will get blown to pieces
if this big guy goes off!
You can't touch it even if
you squirm. It's a ghost!
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
Gum-Gum... Whip!
Ow, ow, ow...
What's the hold-up?
Weren't you going to kick my
butt as many times as it takes?
Yeah! I will in just a sec, so hang tight!
Well, I don't mind the wait,
but he'll come back if you don't hurry.
"He"? Who are you talking about?
You!
Huh?
Damn it! Where'd it go?
That's weird!
Nuh-uh!
Hmmm, nope.
I can't find it!
Oh, there it is! Found it!
Just doesn't feel right without this.
I wanna become the rottin'
King of the Pirates!
I know! I should fire a
salute to liven things up!
Yeah, that'd be rottin' cool!
Hey, where are the cannons?
Huh? Well? Gimme a cannon!
Ocho Fleurs!
I'm Number 1!
What brute strength!
You still mean to fight back?
You don't know when to give up!
Robin...
Hey,
where do you think you're looking?
Shouldn't you be a bit more nervous,
you stupid reindeer?
Sanji...
Huh? Who're you talkin' about?
Don't make me kill you, punk!
You have no hope of
defeating me, dumb reindeer!
Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
Robin!
Jerk! Watch where you're aiming, moron!
What was that, bastard?!
You're a nuisance the way
you dart around everywhere!
Now!
Now, Robin! Get the salt!
I'm on it!
Oh, jeez. You're such a handful.
Don't! Robin is a lady!
A lady...?
What of it?!
Robin!
Unbelievable! Sanji actually kicked--
It's game over for you.
This fight is over!
Cannon! Cannon! Cannon! Cannon!
Cannon! Cannon! Can... Huh?
Why was I searching for cans again?
Huh?
What's this?
What gives? What am I doing out here?
Let's see... I think I'm gonna
become the King of the--
Nope, nope! That's not right.
It's not me who will become
King of the Pirates, but...
That's right. I don't have
time to be goofing off.
I need to hurry back.
I must hurry... Hurry back to Master...
I said to freakin' let me go, dammit!
You came so close, Mr. Negative Nose.
With my next signal, your body
will be blown to smithereens.
Don't! Don't! No!
I don't wanna get blown to smithereens!
Don't worry.
I'll be sure to tell
Hogback to use you as a mario.
Kamikaze Rap!
It vanished?!
That was a close call!
The shock from that blast
went inside this shell.
What's going--
I can't move! What is this?
I lied!
You lied?
I lied when I called the first attack
I shot at you the "Big Bang Star."
It wasn't a dud, either.
It was actually my Birdlime Star.
I made sure you couldn't move around
if you returned to your body.
You what?!
Now I can deal with your
physical body and your Hollow!
Crap!
Are you the one who purified Captain Kumacy?!
Perfect timing! Get him,
Lieutenant Gentleman Hippopotamus!
Impact!
W-Was he actually strong?
Youch! My arm's gonna snap!
Gentleman Hippopotamus!
You don't have time to
be worrying about others.
Special Attack! Shining Black Star!
Cockroaches!
Also known as "Cockroach Star"!
They're gross!
Someone, get them off!
Help me! I can't get away!
They're getting in my clothes!
Ew! I hate cockroaches!
I'm scared, Kumacy! Kumacy!
I'm sure cockroaches are scary...
...but you should be more afraid of me!
You've underestimated me.
In the East Blue, I was renowned
for unparalleled brute strength.
T-Ten tons...? W-Whoa, where did
all of that strength come from?
Knock it off! Don't pull
that out when I'm stuck here.
Y-You're gonna kill me! For real!
Get rid of the roaches! And drop the hammer!
Enough with the roaches
and hammer! C'mon, please!
Usopp!
No, stop it!
Stop it, please! I won't go after
your friends! Okay? Sound good?
Please! Please, Usopp-sama!
Golden...
No!
...Pound!
It's pretty lame when the princess
of the haunted mansion...
...passes out over a balloon
and some toy cockroaches!
Gotcha.
You made a big mistake
when you challenged me to a
contest in lying and negativity!
Sleep till dawn!
Wha ha ha! Hee hee hee! Click my heels!
Didn't that samurai just say something?
Long story short, what just happened?
In short, the fight is apparently over.
I've never seen a duel like this before.
That samurai wasn't taking
me the least bit seriously!
You mean to steal my katana?
You are a feisty one.
Let’s see what this "Two-Sword Style,"
or whatever it is, can do.
I am tingling with excitement!
I'm so excited I could dance!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Slashes Dancing on the Rooftop!!
Showdown: Zoro vs. Ryuma!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!