Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Look over there!
Didn't Curly Cook come out with him?
Damn it!
Nami-san...
Wait!
Moria!
Are you going to chase
after me no matter what?
I'm worried about that huge zombie,
but taking you down is the only way
to recover everyone's shadows.
I won't let you escape!
Look! I am the last one laughing!
She sure is sound asleep.
Let's go elsewhere... and hold
the ceremony... one more time,
my quiet bride!
Oh, crap!
Usopp!
Chopper! Robin!
W-W-We've got a problem!
O-O-Our wanted posters are
a-attached to Zombie Luffy's arm!
I-I'm sure of it!
He is totally...
...coming after us!
Come out, Straw Hat Crew!
Darn it, Luffy! Are you going
to crush your own crew?
Someone must have issued the order.
I hope the real Luffy is all right.
What is that?!
Can we take that monster down?
"Luffy Is the Enemy! The Ultimate Zombie
vs. the Straw Hat Crew!"
Wh-Wh-What is that? Its face freaks me out.
It's literally a monster.
Aren't they...?
Hey, Usopp! That you down there?
What was that? I thought I
heard someone say my name...
Z-Zoro! Why are you on the roof?
Franky! And Brook's okay, too.
At any rate, it looks like we can
check the skeleton off our list.
But it's too soon to check Nami-chan off.
Hey, move your butt!
Why in the world are you
getting in our way, Luffy?
Luffy...?
He is my enemy.
My name is Oars.
Nice to meet ya!
Stuff it! What's "nice" about this?
Sheesh! That is such a
birdbrained thing to say.
You sound just like Luffy.
He's trying to pick a
fight with that monster.
Did that moronic cook manage to save Nami?
He's in hotter water than the girlie!
C-C-Crap! This looks really bad!
Sanji's in trouble!
This was unexpected.
I had assumed they were only
interested in our shadows.
I wonder if we got a little carried away.
It's like all they care
about now is Luffy's shadow.
Scary! I'm scared! I
can't fight that monster!
It looks like I should lend him a hand.
Wait, wait, wait!
W-We should leave this to Sanji
so we don't trip him up.
Don't worry. He should be able
to escape without too much effort.
But won't that giant recognize him
from the wanted poster?
I doubt the beast will
simply let him walk away.
You've got a lot to learn, Robin-kun!
That's just the thing.
Do you think he'll recognize Sanji based off
the composite sketch on the wanted poster?
You're right! Sanji doesn't look anything
like the picture on his wanted poster.
--Bingo!
--I see. You have a good point.
Oh, you look just like the
picture on the wanted poster.
What?!
What looks the same?!
"What," huh? Your whole face.
No, it doesn't, stupid!
At any rate, aren't you one of the pirates?
So what if I am?!
I'm gonna crush you.
Huh?
Shoot! Shoot!
Sanji!
What was that, you bastard?
Wait, Moria!
Jerk!
Drat! That shadow got in the way again!
You never learn.
Oops! This is a dead end.
I've finally got you cornered!
Say your prayers, Giant Shallot!
Shouldn't you be the one saying your prayers?
While you're wasting time with me,
your combat skills are being used
to wipe out your crew, Straw Hat.
Shut up! My crew won't go down that easily.
Is that right? Then I'd better make
a break for it before you do me in!
Brick Bat!
Whoa! Crap!
Bye!
Gum-Gum Gatling!
Wait! I won't let you escape!
Moria-sama, we've got trouble!
What happened here?
Moria-sama, where did you go?
Wh-What are they doing?
You're being obnoxious,
you poor excuse for a penguin!
Shut up, stinky old man!
Guys! This is no time for
arguing amongst ourselves.
Who gave you permission to bicker?
We're following Hogback-sama's orders!
Beat it, you lousy bat!
That's absurd!
Hogback-sama would never order
you to do something like this.
What exactly did he say?
"Take out the pests!"
You pest!
--Take out the pest!
--You're the pest!
--They're a lost cause...
--You are such a pest!
Damn! That still hurts.
That jerk tried to make a fool of me!
But I'm not about to pass out.
I can't collapse until this
event of a lifetime is over!
Now then, let's resume the
wedding ceremony. Kiss the bride.
I'll finally get to kiss her this time!
That's Absalom-sama!
I know! Absalom-sama might
know where Moria-sama went.
--Here I go!
--Absalom-sama!
Wh-What was that for, you perverted beast?!
He insulted him! He slammed
him with an insult!
Crap! Now we're in for a storm!
Hildon, what are you doing here?
So? What did you want?
Huh?
He's surprisingly calm.
You see, I'm trying to find Moria-sama.
Can't you see for yourself? He isn't here!
So it would seem.
Sorry, but could you get
someone else to help you?
I'm busy at the moment.
Sorry for the intrusion. Goodbye!
Wait a second, Hildon.
Yes, what is it?
How dare you call me a "perverted beast"?!
That was mean.
It took that long to sink in?!
Wait, Giant Shallot!
Huh? Who's there?
Darn it! It's that stupid shadow!
Just you wait, Moria!
Man, he really let me have it.
I finally found him!
Moria-sama!
Moria-sama, I have news that
I'd like to report right away!
Hildon? What is it?
To be honest, it would appear the ship
is moving in an unfortunate direction.
We'll run into trouble if it
continues on its current course!
Is that right? If that's the case,
do something about it.
I'm busy at the moment.
--Later!
--B-But...!
You're in the way! Move it! Move!
Darn twerp's quickly darting every which way!
Sanji!
I swear, all that did was make a dust cloud!
Now it's my turn, you bastard!
Sanji!
Are you okay?
You won't get away this time.
Gum-Gum...
It's one of Luffy's moves!
Can he extend his arms?!
Is he a rubber man now?
...Sickle!
H-His arm didn't extend!
But with power and reach
like that, who cares?!
So that freakishly huge
body isn't just for show.
Just one direct hit could
do some serious damage!
Oars... I've heard that
name somewhere before.
Could he be the legendary Continent Puller
from ancient times, the Devil Oars?!
That'd explain it. It sounds like
Luffy's zombie isn't a pushover.
Collier Frit!
Sanji!
He's stinking fast for a behemoth!
I've got ya, puny pirate!
Crap! He's gonna get killed!
Sanji!
What is that monster gonna do?
Hey, stop it!
Sanji!
Die, puny pirate!
Fire Bird Star!
This is hot.
I... I... I'm sorry!
Sanji!
There is the black-haired woman
and the reindeer eating cotton candy.
He's headed our way!
Crap! Franky, lure him over here!
Now we're talking!
Eat this, monster!
Look out!
Get off the roof, you two!
One Gorilla!
Two Gorilla!
Three-Sword Style...
...Two Gorilla Slash!
Gum-Gum...
...Volcano!
Zoro, are you still alive?
No, he's dead if he falls from up there!
Yes!
Chew on this, monster!
Weapons Left!
He's so nimble! He dodged again!
What's he up to this time?
Franky! Brook!
Zoro's coming down!
Shoot! He'll die if he hits the ground!
Cien Fleurs! Spider Net!
I survived? Damn it...!
Eat this! You're still a zombie!
Special Attack! Salt Star!
How do you like that?
I-It wasn't enough!
Not for his massive body!
Heavy Gong!
D-Damn it, Luffy!
I don't know any of you losers!
I am Moria-sama's servant, Oars!
Ab-sama! Forget that woman and pucker up!
Learn when to quit! I won't kiss you!
--Then marry me!
--That isn't happening!
--Then kiss me!
--Are you even listening?
You just don't get it.
No, you don't!
Oh, shit! You made her wake up!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"You're Going Down, Absalom!!
Nami's Lightning Attack of Friendship!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!