Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Smooch...!
Gum-Gum...
Now, Usopp!
The sky is unexpectedly clear tonight.
Special Attack! Special Oil Star!
This is...
Three Chamber Shot!
What?! W-Wait! What're you doing?!
...one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
M-Moria! It's Moria!
No, stop it!
He's the "Tyrant" Bartholomew Kuma!
Where?! Where is he?!
Curse you, Namizo!
Armée de l'Air Power Shoot!
The sun will be rising soon.
If you were to go on a trip,
where would you like to go?
Should you really be farting around?
Zoro's coming down!
Cien Fleurs! Spider Net!
Why is he here?
Of all the stupid...! I nearly let
the weight of your title crush me.
Super Fencing!
Huh? I can hear Master's voice!
Damn it, Lola! Not only
did you crash my wedding,
What a dreadful man!
but now you have the gall
to attack my bride?!
Negative Ghost!
Usopp!
Run for it, Namizo! I will hold him back!
Cien Fleurs!
Eat this! You're still a zombie!
And Special Hollow!
Huh? What?!
Special Attack! Salt Star!
I came to rescue you, my friend!
Big Tree!
Lola!
Ab-sama!
Wh-What's that?
Crap!
How do you like that?
I can't ask Moria's whereabouts
when you're being belligerent.
Stay out of my way!
Clutch!
Usopp!
Whoa, this is dangerous!
I'm gonna fall! I'm about to fall!
You've made me... waste my energy on you!
Where'd she go?
I-It wasn't enough!
Aren't you the Cat Burglar?
Shit! Oars is acting intelligently
now that Moria is with him!
Skywalk!
You're part of the Straw Hat Crew!
Not for his massive body!
How dare you hurt Lola?!
Let's get a move on, Chopper!
Usopp!
Yeah!
What gives?! He got up there
in the blink of an eye!
Swing Arm!
Where are you?! Answer me!
Super Frapper Gong!
He's okay!
Heavy Gong!
Did he warp...?
It's not like that'll do anything!
That's why I'm going to...
Is he after Luffy? I've got to let him know!
I thought that you might need salt,
so I gathered it in bulk!
I've got ya, Moria!
Brook!
Bad Manner...
Huh?
You're a lifesaver!
...Kick...
I won! Yay!
"The Secret Plan to Turn the Tables!
Nightmare Luffy Makes His Appearance!"
...Course!
The shadow? I've been chasing after the...
Hey, Oars!
Sh-Shoot! He pulled a fast one on me!
D-Damn it, Luffy!
I don't know any of you losers!
If Luffy's shadow is inside of you...
Brook, you can move?
Bottoms up!
...you shouldn't underestimate the
underlying strength of your crew!
"Oars + Moria! The Most Heinous
Combination of Brains and Brawn!"
You seem to be doing really great.
I am Moria-sama's servant, Oars!
I owe ya one. Thank you!
Indeed, I was severely injured!
I dragged my battered body
to the kitchen in search of salt.
Darn it! When did he swap out with his shadow?
"You're Going Down, Absalom!!
Nami's Lightning Attack of Friendship!!"
Upon stumbling across some milk, I happily
We just scored our first knockdown.
"Knock Him Down!!
Special Attack: Straw Hat Docking?"
drank away and look what happened!
Why, you--!
Wait, just how regenerative is calcium?!
"The Silent Assault!!
The Mysterious Visitor, 'Tyrant' Kuma!"
Doesn't milk help mend broken bones?
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight...
Hey! Wait, Moria's Shadow!
Don't lie!
Whatever the case may be,
Don't leave me here!
we got a massive
amount of salt just in the nick of time.
Where am I?!
I'll be just fine, Namizo.
Eep! Th-That's one nasty woman!
Huh?
The path to the kitchen has been cut off.
You can go on without me.
Hey!
She's like a demon! She's a demonic pirate!
Brook's salt is our last hope.
I'll get you up to speed with
what's happening here on the island.
We're running out of time. We must fight!
But some outsiders got thrown into the mix.
Lola!
You know your friend, Straw Hat Luffy?
Shoot! This bites.
If we can stuff the salt
down that monster's throat
So that leaves the guy
I saw in the straw hat,
What is the meaning of this?
Would you care to explain?
Well, the Special Zombie
that possesses his shadow
I said that I would recover everyone's shadows.
and kick Moria's butt before dawn, we win!
is running amok on the island.
It'll be bad if I don't get our shadows back.
My lips are totally sealed!
the orange-haired woman, and the cool hero.
Uh... What happens if we don't have shadows?
Put me down!
The Special Zombie...?
Let's cut her to shreds!
You're so dead!
It's time! Awaken!
Do you think I'm going to
I'm still missing three people.
plop over dead and let the
treasure slip through my fingers?
Where could they be? Hmm?
I'm freaking scared!
I'll do whatever it takes to make you squeal!
Now I remember! As we are now,
I'm horribly scared as well.
I'm pretty sure the guys and I will melt in the sunlight.
I still can't believe he has a cockpit.
I thought that freak had a normal body.
Meat!
Sh-Shut up!
We'll be in a jam when the sun rises, huh?
Die!
Thunder Charge!
Shoot! I have to finish this up before dawn!
Swing Arm!
She must mean him.
No!
You should be grateful that
I have decided to join the fray!
Now get going! You can leave him to me.
I never dreamed this would happen!
We squealed! We told her
absolutely everything.
And I'd be extremely careful if I were you.
Thank you, Lola!
For now, all I can do is follow Moria's shadow!
But Perona-sama loves treasure.
I'm not simply a passenger here!
Lookie, Ab-sama! It's just the two of us.
I will show you the ultimate nightmare!
True! She won't let that woman steal it.
Let's savor the moment!
But we even told her about the shortcut.
No! I hate roaches! Gross!
We really blew it. Ploink!
The massive zombie I saw in
the freezer room spells trouble!
Of all the nerve! They're loading
Sunny with all the treasure,
I shall fight in this battle as well!
I will give it my all!
Will we be able to tear Luffy's
shadow out of that monster?
including ours, so she can
kiss this place goodbye!
But there is no way we're
leaving empty-handed
I could never begin to repay the debt
after what they've put us through!
Zoro, I really think we should
buy time until Luffy defeats Moria!
But I won't let her get away with it!
I owe you guys for recovering my shadow,
Usopp 10 Ton...
but I'll fight to the fullest!
I've got to hurry back to Sunny!
Bingo! The door is even open.
I just obtained the black blade, Shusui.
--I'm stiff!
--Don't push yourself!
No, no, no, no...
But what's up with this bridge?
Why is this part so narrow?
Stay on top of the salt!
...Hammer!
Can you blame me for wanting to test it out
on the monster standing before me?
--Let's go, Chopper!
--Yeah!
It's odd how well made it is...
Come on, man!
It... It... It's empty!
I'll give you a taste of
my anti-monster shells!
Oars!
You're a bunch of meanies!
She's awake!
Huh?
--Not the hammer!
--Perona-sama!
No way! Where'd my treasure go?!
Have at me! I will be your opponent!
Victory goes to those
who take the initiative!
--I hate cockroaches! Hurry and
get them off of me! Hurry!
--Perona-sama, please come to your senses!
Now I'm ticked!
I'm gonna send all of you flying!
Apparently it wasn't big enough last time!
There isn't a trace of it left!
--I hate roaches! Ew, yuck!
--There aren't any cockroaches.
All right.
Franky, I'm counting on you!
Isn't that...?
You're going to fight him alone?!
Special Attack! Special Oil Star!
I'm sure this is the place! So who took it?
But shouldn't I prioritize things
in order of importance?
We removed the sticky stuff
that was on your hand.
Okay! Now we're talking!
I'll... pass on this!
Where am I?
Oh, look! That's the woman who escaped.
I didn't see a thing!
Your foe is long gone.
Whoa, Zoro! There is no way
you can fight him by yourself!
You're right. It's her!
You'd better say your prayers!
I'm gonna flatten you guys like pancakes!
Transform!
Perona-sama, you were
out cold when we found you.
Aren't they...?
Super Size!
Come back here so we can regroup!
Sweet! Let's report this!
Fire Bird Star!
What did he do to you?
Report time!
Stop right there!
I can't believe someone knocked you out!
Comparing the two swords,
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
the black blade, Shusui, is considerably
heavier than my old Yubashiri.
Who trashed the mansion?
Was this the pirates' doing?
Hot! Hot, hot, hot!
You have impeccable timing.
Hot! Hot, hot!
You won't have a bone left in your body!
Sweet! Serves you right!
I'm dying to ask you two a question.
Hey, Zoro! Dodge!
The pirates are certainly causing mayhem,
but this looks like Oars' handiwork.
Okay, now get that one contraption ready.
Going by its weight...!
Huh? Oh, okay.
He's spitting mad!
Oars?!
Hot! Hot, hot! Hot!
Amazing! He used brute strength
alone to divert that punch!
Crap! Shoot!
Pathetic! Don't shrink back, Oars!
Here he comes!
You sure are tough, puny pirates!
You only think things "hurt"
or "feel hot" because
Three-Sword Style...
...108-Pound Phoenix!
What was he...?
of the time you spent as a human.
Things of this nature do not work
on you now that you are a zombie.
As a matter of fact, word has it
Oars wiped out the General Zombies.
It's huge!
I'm stuck! My horns are stuck!
Calm down and put out the fire!
Drat! It didn't hit him!
Drat! My horns are stuck
deep into the ground.
Now that you mention it,
this doesn't feel the least bit hot.
The ultimate corps?!
I can't believe he dodged that!
So we can't control Oars?!
Shusui's slash absorbed the ones
from the other two swords
Now, Zoro!
Well, I couldn't say one way or--
and became one big slash!
Okay!
Gleam!
But there is excess damage
around where it cut the stone.
Twinkle!
Huh? You can't pull your horns out?
--Guys!
--Brothers!
It's proof that I haven't
mastered this sword yet.
Just throwing this out there, but what
do you think of sending him flying?
It is several levels more
powerful than my old one,
Woman!
What?! S-Seriously, Zoro?
but it doesn't seem like
the most compliant of swords.
O-Oars?
I hear you...
Wha--?!
I bet that'd be a blast.
C-Come to think of it,
I heard he stepped on Hogback-sama.
Oomph!
S-Stop right there!
Wh-When you said, "sending him flying,"
What?!
You gave me a great blade, swordsman Ryuma!
Woman!
did you really mean that behemoth?!
I nearly had a heart attack when that
lummox started moving around like Luffy.
You're good! I bet that
woulda hurt bad if it hit,
Is the woman around?
Still, he isn't fit to be
the King of the Pirates.
you bastard!
Woman!
Three-Sword Style...
He's looking for a woman? Yikes!
I've gotta get away from here.
The question is how to topple him over.
Hey, could that be...?
...Great Buddha Slayer!
I'm gonna trample you!
We can go about it more ways than one.
It sounds like Oars is screaming...
Between the pirates and Oars,
Thriller Bark is toast!
He must have a weakness somewhere!
I'm telling you, that's just not possible!
Lemme step on you!
Eat this! Jenga Cannon!
It's standard to slowly weaken
a large fish over time...
Hurry and gather up the treasure and food!
He's the ultimate Special Zombie!
--Zoro!
--Will he be okay?
We're going to stuff it into their
pirate ship and make a break for it.
Jerk!
Whose ship?
At any rate...
The Straw Hats'! We're escaping
on their ship, so hurry it up!
Give it a rest!
Have seconds! Thirds!
Fourths! Fifths! And sixths!
...he's super scary!
Unless I make a bigger opening,
all I can do is dodge!
Okay, we're on it!
Retreat!
Yeah!
Sheesh...
Go crunch!
Woman!
Here he comes!
Stinking jerk!
You guys are like devils!
Gum-Gum...
Perona-sama!
...Butt Drop!
Even flinging the guy didn't cut it!
Kiss the bride.
Yeah, let's speed through this.
I'm growing impatient!
It looks like we need to regroup.
So, what's our next strategy?
The tower is flying straight at us!
Now!
Smooch...!
That attack is nuts!
Oh, no!
Three-Sword Style! 108--
To stand a chance against that monster...
Huh?
Scatter!
Veinte Fleurs!
Now I'm going to crush you!
...Tactics #15 really is our only hope!
Oh, thanks!
What?! W-Wait! What're you doing?!
I'm willing to give it another shot!
Gum-Gum...
Stop it, you idiots!
No, stop it!
Yeah! I'm confident it would
have worked earlier if Robin
Zoro!
Franky, he's going after you!
You've come to? Grah, give it up!
Tsk!
had gone along with it!
...Hammer!
Don't ask me to do that again!
Once I give you this binding kiss,
you will become my lifelong companion!
You stupid idiots!
Oops! He used them against us!
I bet he's as flat as a pancake.
There is no way Robin-chan
could ever do something that humiliating!
Hey, you guys okay?
I've already turned you down,
you perverted invisible beast!
Punk! You're just beggin' me
to teach you who's boss.
Huh?
It's so--huh? Wait...
I'm still at that age where
I want to go on adventures!
He isn't there!
Where did he go?
Behold our forces combined!
Shut up and rejoice! You will be
the King of the Grave's wife,
I might want to see
Robin-chan dock after all!
Darn! I can't see him through the dust.
making you the Queen of the Grave!
Guys!
Ew! What the hell?!
It's time for Tactics #15!
Heh, heh!
Three-Sword Style...
H-Here's my new weapon, Kuwagata!
...108-Pound Phoenix!
Curse you, Namizo!
What?!
K-Kidding! I'm just kidding, Robin-chan!
You want to do that right here and now?!
Yikes! That was close.
If you want to do it so badly,
you can do it by your--
Hey, hey, hey, hey, and whoosh!
Let's do it!
Zoro! Curly! Enter standby!
Damn! That stupid monster dodged again!
Hah! Super!
Enter standby, men!
--Lo...
--Lola!
Standby?
Shrimp, quit sneaking around!
Uh, drop the super pose...
Holding this back is killing me.
Just hold my legs!
Pirates Docking: Three!
Namizo...! Why, you...!
Zoro! S-Seriously, don't do anything crazy!
What the heck are they up to?
We're not giant, but we're the Robot Warrior!
So are you all set, Usopp?
Even if by some miracle
you managed to defeat him,
Here we come!
Y-Yeah, but I only made this to look cool!
Docking: Complete!
How dare you try to steal him from me?!
all you'd get out of it is Luffy's shadow!
Let's do it!
Hey, Curly! Lend me a hand--
er, scratch that! Lend me a leg!
I have no idea how it will actually work!
You said that you were shipping us!
That was a lie, wasn't it?
We don't even know where
your and Sanji's shadows are.
Don't worry about it!
I'm extra super this week.
But if Luffy defeats Moria, everyone will
instantly get their shadows back!
Sanji!
Do it, Sanji!
You were doing the opposite of shipping us,
and trying to steal Ab-sama.
Then get on!
I like your drive! You've got it!
You don't need to get hurt
fighting an immortal giant zombie!
All right! Aim for the
center of that lug's gut!
You're a two-faced jerk!
W-Wait, Lola! Just a second.
Let's believe in Luffy and work on
keeping this behemoth busy!
Go! Special Attack! Iron Man Comet!
Go! Armée de l'Air Robot Shoot!
I've been out cold this whole time.
I fully believe in him...
I don't even know what's going on.
Oh, I'm in a wedding dress.
Why am I wearing this? Cool!
...but even Luffy has a weakness.
Man, it's only three of you?
Huh?
This is going super!
There's nothing "cool" about this, traitor!
Trickery!
Don't sound so disappointed!
Say your prayers!
The invisible man, the ghost girl,
and the master of shadows...
We're a small, elite force, jerk!
Wait! You've got it all wrong!
I use this trench mortar
against sea monsters and Sea Kings!
Damn it, Lola! Not only
did you crash my wedding,
Eat this!
I'm gonna fill ya full of holes!
Pirates Robot Attack!
This island is a nesting grounds for
deceptive Devil Fruit power holders.
Pirates Docking: Six!
but now you have the gall
to attack my bride?!
Eat this, Moria!
Jerk! Jerk! Jerk!
Giant Robot Warrior!
I doubt the enemy will
fight Luffy fair and square.
Shut up and marry me!
Jerk! Jerk! Jerk! Jerk! Jerk! Jerk!
Big Emperor!
Hell, no!
Jerk! Jerk! Grrr! Jerk!
He's so agile!
Do they honestly consider
that a legitimate attack?
That's a good point.
Ab-sama, I bet you don't know, do you?
Sometimes I forget that he's Luffy!
Yeah.
That's rather unimpressive.
If he gives Luffy the slip and morning comes...
Tch!
A-About what?
Luffy, the cook, and I won't be able
to put up a decent fight anymore!
Damn it! I'm disappointed in you,
Pirates Docking: Three!
This woman's real name is Namizo!
"She" is actually a "he"!
Hold up, Franky!
That tickles! Stop it!
So at the very least, if we can get
Luffy back to normal before dawn,
Franky!
Is there a problem, Chopper?
What?!
She still hasn't docked onto your left arm!
Now it's show time!
he'll take over from there.
No, that can't be true... Seriously?!
We'll make you taste the terror
of Pirates Docking: Three!
What?!
I'd say we have less than
thirty minutes until sunrise.
Franky!
Oh, yeah. That's what I told Lola.
Hey! What's keeping you, Nico Robin?!
Huh?
But these are foggy waters.
The morning sun won't hit everywhere.
I heard you boasted big time that you were
Dock onto my left arm already!
So you're wasting your time!
Pursuing him will get you nowhere!
gonna become the King of the Pirates.
Robin, hurry!
Do you get it now?
Come, Robin! Copy what I'm doing!
Aside from your big body,
you'll never be big!
So morning is on the horizon...
This fog is the only thing in our favor.
I've been chasing a man this whole time?
No.
Yeah, you heard him!
And I came within an inch of kissing him?
What was that?!
Honestly, the fear of annihilation is
just now setting in with sunrise so close.
That would hurt my human pride.
Who was crying like a baby
after we pummeled him?
But I checked out his body in the bathroom...
It'd hurt...
Talk about a pathetic loser!
...her...
You're not done yet, Oars.
He's still hanging on by a thread.
...h-h-human--
It would hurt my human pride.
I didn't cry like a baby,
you darn puny pirates!
Finish him off!
I made it just in the nick of time.
She said it twice!
Okay!
Ah, I found the runts!
I'm sure this is the place.
Now!
So you're not going to dock?
Usopp, Chopper! Wait out in the hallway.
Why do you sound so shocked?
Wh-What's that?!
Sweet!
Okay...
Poopy! You got me worked up for nothing!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Why is the ship shaking?!
Well? How does it feel to have
your own punch rattle your brain?
Do it!
What's going on?!
Dock with him!
Nice!
The ship must have gotten caught
in another weird current like earlier!
Shoot! Isn't he going to stop there?!
Did you see that, Robin-chan?
It went just as I had planned!
Stop it! He can't move anymore!
--Oomph!
Franky!
Well done, Pirates Docking: Three!
Huh?! Hey, look!
I suck! I can't believe they
duped me into doing that.
It's the sky!
Since when was that all part
of your plan, stupid cook?
It's the pre-dawn sky!
No, just forget about it!
I must have imagined that...
Thunderbolt...
The fog is dissipating before our very eyes!
Nami, you okay?
All right! Fall over!
Huh? That cloud...!
Robin, we could have become Robot
Warrior Big Emperor if you'd joined us!
Everything's fine, so don't look in here!
Our second knockdown!
What's going on?!
...Tempo!
Okay.
I-I'm not going down, jerks!
Does this mean we've left the Florian Triangle?!
Th-That was close.
I never saw that betrayal coming! Never!
I bet Luffy would have
done it if he were here!
It's because Oars was fooling
around with the rudder earlier!
Robot Warrior, retreat!
Don't ask me to dock with you... ever again!
Damn it! Who did that?!
We were so close!
That bastard! Look at what he's done!
We almost had him.
What did they do?!
Dang, he can really take a licking!
Let's regroup, dammit!
While he's tying us up, Nami-san is...!
This is stinkin' bad!
Wait, Sanji. I have an idea.
--Franky!
--Huh?
Thriller Bark has pulled out of the fog!
It worked! Oars fell to his knees!
I'm gonna borrow your big toy.
I've had enough of your tricks.
Lightning! That attack
could only come from...!
We're doomed!
Boing! Boing!
Hear me out!
Sunrise is just around the corner!
Is this the end of the line?
Clima Takt! Nami-san, are you all right?
Ba-boing!
Hey, punk! That's my Heavy Nunchaku!
All of the bouncy parts were there...
It's too soon to give up!
It looks like he hasn't completely
lost all of Luffy's memories.
Fine! You can borrow it.
The Star of Hope's crew is
fighting even as we speak.
Make yourself scarce, Namizo!
He just sparked!
Lightning? Out of nowhere?
The bastard...! I need to hurry back
to Nami-san and rescue her again.
Stop it, Lola!
H-Hey, check that out!
But he said that he doesn't know us.
Oars summoned lightning! I'm sure of it!
Hey, hog! Stop it, Lola!
It's Moria's shadow!
He even called himself Moria's servant.
It's flying back to the mansion.
There you are!
Regardless...!
Beat it!
So what?
It's Nami-san!
Hey! What's keeping you, Nico Robin?!
Stupid! Don't you see?
She isn't hitting me?
Dock onto my left arm already!
Straw Hat has been chasing it.
Nami-san! Nami-san! Nami-san! Nami-san!
See how you like a taste of this!
Namizo...
Robin, hurry!
It should lead him right to us.
Lola?
Come, Robin! Copy what I'm doing!
Nami-san!
Run for it, Namizo! I will hold him back!
In other words, if we set up an ambush...
No.
That would hurt my human pride.
Oh, I get it!
Hey! Quit yelling my name!
I came to rescue you, my friend!
Was that you?
Great! Let's inform the captain and the others.
What if he notices me?!
So you're not going to dock onto him?
We have to stop Straw Hat!
Robin!
Lola!
Why do you sound so shocked?
Ab-sama!
Yeah, got it!
Go for the joints after I whack his left arm!
Thank goodness! What a relief!
Poopy! You got me worked up for nothing!
Now, if that's sunk in, swear your
vows to me instead, Absalom!
Moria-sama, something horrible has happened!
I'm so glad Nami-san is okay!
Roger.
Didn't his reaction and the way
he whined remind you of Luffy?
Thank God! Please forgive me for failing you!
Here I go!
After all this time, Thriller Bark
has left the foggy waters!
Lola...
--Nami-san, I'm sorry!
--What a loudmouth.
All because of Oars!
There goes the bride!
Your bride is right here!
--Woman!
--See?
It did!
So what do you have in mind?
I'm certain that she is a woman!
Moria-sama!
How dare you take us so lightly?!
When you get down to it,
he shares all of Luffy's weaknesses.
Lola, stay out of my way!
I could have sworn it was around here...
Oars, show them your true power!
Don't make a scene. So what if we left the fog?
Gum-Gum...
We're pirates! I don't care where
we are as long as we're on the ocean!
Oh, look! There is a mountain of meat!
Found it! This is the place.
Wh-What? What? What?! Can he stretch?
What?! Meat?! Where?
Uh, but...
He can't reach her from there, can he?
Wow, he's right! It looks yummy!
More importantly, zip your lips, because I
Now's our chance! Get Franky somewhere safe!
Where? Where?!
'Kay!
am entertaining the most unusual of guests!
The coast is clear, right?
...Pistol!
Isn't that right, Tyrant Kuma,
Knee Crush!
I'm coming in!
Lola!
the only Warlord who does the Government's bidding?
It looks like someone
has ransacked the place.
Does knocking him to his knees
count as a knockdown?
Even if we had a set of rules,
I doubt anyone would obey them.
But I'm sure they must have some in here...
What?!
Sweet! We made his knees buckle!
--Yay! We did it! His knees buckled!
--Yay! Yay! Yay!
Lowly zombie!
C-C-Could that be...
--We made his knees give out!
--That was embarrassing.
You've made me... waste my energy on you!
We're not done yet!
H-His arm extended?! Why?!
...milk?!
We just have to hang in there
until Straw Hat kicks Moria's butt.
Isn't that right, Tyrant Kuma,
As I am now, this is the ultimate medicine!
the only Warlord who does the Government's bidding?
Hurry and get your shadow back, Straw Hat!
Now all that is left is to
check the expiration date...
It stretched. That feels
more like how it should.
Why do we have to wait on him?
All we have to do is take the lug down.
I'm sure the Government finds you useful,
but what are you plotting?
Oh, dear...
What?!
What a pity...
Whoa, wait! Weren't we just
keeping this monster busy so he
People like you are the most unsettling!
But that's impossible!
No, this should just barely
be in the clear! It'll be okay!
--Nami!
--Nami-san!
doesn't get in Straw Hat's way?
If you were to go on a trip,
where would you like to go?
No!
I'll drink this for the sake of the others!
Do you seriously think you can defeat it?
Whoa, whoa! Don't go there!
There isn't any meat,
and I got knocked to my knees...
I see her! Nami is okay!
Bottoms up!
I know what your powers are.
Did you come to fight me?
Phew! Robin saved her.
I'm simply accepting the fight he picked!
But not only is he huge, he's a zombie!
State your business! What brought you here?
The only way to win is to purify him!
I can feel it! I can feel it!
Right, Zoro! Work on buying time!
I came to make a report.
I wasn't expecting that.
Are you all right, Nami?
I can feel it!
If you don't like it, start running!
A report...?
It has been decided who will
fill the empty Warlord seat
I don't plan on waiting for Luffy.
I can feel the calcium seeping
into every pore of my body!
Thank you. I'm okay, thanks to you.
Aw, man!
But since I'm a skeleton,
I don't have any pores!
created by Crocodile's dismissal.
It looks like there is no stopping them.
Something seriously bad just happened!
Why was he able to stretch his arm?
Gum-Gum...
You should have said so sooner!
There is only one rubber man in the world!
Who was it and what ocean was he from?
Oh, smart move!
I am alive!
There are a bazillion pirates out there!
Supposedly it won't bend a millimeter,
even if a dinosaur steps on it...
The name of his successor is Marshall D. Teach.
Oh, dear! That random outburst made
these poor eyes of mine see stars.
Have you decided to stop running?
I've heard that the black blade
is known for its "strength."
The man also goes by Blackbeard.
But since I'm a skeleton,
I don't have eyes...
It's Moria! He must have done something.
Blackbeard? I've never heard of him.
Ah! This is hardly the time to waste
energy on such silly nonsense!
Once, a legendary samurai
wielded the great sword, Shusui.
The bastard!
That's right. It's not like...
you could escape, anyway.
He ran away from Whitebeard's crew.
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
I am sure this katana would be
happy to have you as its master.
People are already starting to talk about him.
All right! I must find some quickly
and return to the others.
It's like we're fighting a
monster version of Luffy!
I'm an invisible man!
Vortex!
What is keeping Luffy?!
Thunder Charge!
I just obtained the O-Wazamono, Shusui...
St. Elmo's Fire!
Damn it!
How dare you?!
That screams "suspicious"...
This is the perfect chance
to test its strength!
I think you and Beast Man
would make an awesome couple!
No, wait! Luffy is gonna
take out Moria for us.
I was totally shipping you!
Really?
Die in darkness!
Flame Commandment...
No one has ever encouraged me to
pursue my feelings for him before...
Found it!
You're the first person to offer
such kind words of support.
Flame Emperor!
I need to hurry back!
I... I...!
But I don't have a tongue...
Raise your head, my friend.
I'm awful! I intentionally held
my leg out to trip you! Teehee!
This is what you call "friendship."
What's your problem?! I'm in a hurry!
Damn that jerk Moria! Where did he go?
I am Namizo. Please call me "Nami."
What do you want?!
Yeah, we know! We totally
get that you're in a hurry.
Friendship...? Nami!
Please give us a minute!
You're our only hope!
I can't find him anywhere!
News hasn't reached your foggy waters,
Namizo...
--We've been searching for you this whole time.
--Huh?
I know!
Lola?
but he joined after proving his strength.
Run for it, Namizo! I will hold him back!
We're the Risky Brothers,
members of the Rolling Pirates led by
Gum-Gum Rocket!
And what was his original bounty?
Captain "Marriage Proposal" Lola.
I came to rescue you, my friend!
Don't you want to defeat that Gecko Moria
Zero.
I see. So his capability is still unknown.
guy who lives in the mansion? Well?
How dare you hurt Lola?!
I'm amazed the Government approved.
Perona-sama!
So? What's your deal?
Found him!
All right!
What is it?
The fridge is stuffed! We can't
squeeze another morsel in.
But at least that seat has been filled!
We know the secret behind Moria's powers.
Don't they have a pantry?
Put the provisions in there.
We'll give incredible power to you,
so please! Take him down!
Won't this help stabilize
the world's power balance?
Okay!
Hurry up with the treasure!
Don't leave a single gem behind!
Secret? Power?
No, I imagine this will do the exact opposite,
C'mon!
Hey, you!
Okay!
Like I said, what's your deal?!
but that is irrelevant.
Who's that?
To cut to the chase, the Government
is rather concerned about something.
Allow me to introduce the Rolling
Pirates' captain, Marriage Proposal Lola.
It's one of the pirate women!
That's right! Dive into my arms!
Since the incident at Enies Lobby,
What are you doing with the
treasure I was supposed to take?
She has currently proposed 4,443 times!
they are constantly keeping
tabs on the Straw Hat Crew.
Robin!
Swing Arm!
My! I like you. Please marry me.
And Sunny for that matter!
Go for the joints after I whack his left arm!
They knew if the Straw Hats followed a
No.
Log from Water Seven to Fishman Island,
If it isn't the pirate woman.
Rejected! That was her 4,444th rejection!
Roger.
the chances of you stopping
them here would be high.
Here I go!
Is your wedding ceremony
with Absalom over already?
Do you see what the Government fears?
Like I'm gonna marry that
perverted invisible beast man!
So everyone here has lost their shadow
Over here, Monster Luffy!
It's not like that'll do anything!
That's why I'm going to...
and joined the Victim Association
that wanders these forests.
So you managed to get away?
He really is a stupid man.
The Government
Jerk! You're just a shrimp!
I'm in a hurry, since my
shadow was also taken!
is afraid that Straw Hat
will defeat yet another of the Seven Warlords.
So what are you going to do?
Aren't you Straw Hat Luffy?
Gum-Gum...
It's true that I intend to
leave the island on your ship.
Bluntly put, today is the first day
Thriller Bark has rocked and shaken like this!
Now, Usopp!
Huh?
Don't give me that! You're worried about me?!
Got it!
Eat this!
If you want to stop me, I'm up for a fight!
Special Attack! Special Oil Star!
The Three Phantoms who serve Moria
have been defeated one after the next.
Me, the person who took this seat
to suppress the weak pirates?!
Three Chamber Shot!
The mansion is already halfway demolished!
Yeah! You've filled us with non-stop
excitement ever since you arrived.
If necessary, I would be willing
to offer you my assistance.
My Mini-Hollow Corps will
blow a weakling like you to bits!
Ab-sama!
--Hey, Curly!
--Huh?
But your enemy is no pushover!
He has already awoken the Special Zombie!
That's right! Dive into my arms!
Who do you think you're talking to, bastard?!
Send me flying!
My nemesis is Mr. Negative
Nose and him alone!
While you're swinging that huge thing around?
Don't look so surprised!
We use the Victim Network to stay
up-to-date on the situation!
If you can't, that's cool.
Ab-sama!
We've gone three whole
years without our shadows!
Why, you...!
Who is that?
Are you saying I might lose to a
small band of inexperienced pirates?!
Of course I can, moron!
I don't want to spend
the rest of my life like this!
Armée de l'Air...
Perona-sama, please run for it!
If you defeat Moria,
everyone will get their shadows back!
...Power Shoot!
You cannot 100% guarantee victory in battle.
That's what we thought, but jeez!
Who would have predicted
the defeat of Rob Lucci
Super Fencing!
Do you even know where Moria is right now?
Who the heck are you?!
In its belly! The belly of that monster!
during the incident at Enies Lobby?
I have no idea who he is, but he's an enemy!
What?! Did he get eaten?!
Jet...
Just a second ago, he made my brothers
No! He climbed inside
of the monster's stomach.
vanish without a trace
right before my very eyes!
...Gatling!
Cien Fleurs!
He's no pushover! He's trouble!
In other words, you can't touch Moria
Anyway, he's rottin' dangerous!
if you don't defeat the Special
Zombie that has your shadow!
They vanished...?
Your friends are fighting the zombie
in the mansion courtyard right now!
Big Tree!
No kidding, guys...
Of course he's not a pushover!
Wh-What's that?
They're what?! Damn it!
I don't have time for this!
We need you to hold your horses!
Ow!
Clutch!
Jeez! We'll skip the circular explanations!
Whoa,
This is...
It'll be faster if he sees it for himself!
this is dangerous!
I'm gonna fall! I'm about to fall!
Even so, are you telling me
that the Government is so scared
Show him the secret behind
the shadows that we discovered!
...one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
Okay! Move, move! Coming through!
that they want to throw
two Warlords at them?! Well?!
He's the "Tyrant" Bartholomew Kuma!
Feast your eyes on this!
It's a super impromptu staircase!
This man used to be the
epitome of cruelty as a pirate!
Huh? A shadow?
I thought I'd help after delivering the report.
Right, it's a shadow.
It is not as though I was ordered to assist you.
When we feed salt to a zombie,
Franky Skywalk!
Eh?!
we can catch the shadow that comes out!
Then feast your eyes on what I do
to those pirates while you're here!
No way! He's one of the Seven Warlords?!
Ready, go!
And then tell those pampered
idiots what you witnessed!
Unfortunately, this stairway
won't last for long!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Tell them about how Gecko Moria effortlessly turned the
--The shadow is stabbing me!
--Sit still!
That's insane! He's as
powerful as Moria-sama?!
Let's get a move on, Chopper!
Why? It didn't even faze him
on top of the bridge...
Yeah!
What brought him to Thriller Bark?
Straw Hat Crew that outwitted them into zombie soldiers!
Knock it off! I'm feeling lightheaded!
Sure enough, he had already reached
his limit after fighting that man.
I can't believe it...
Super Frapper Gong!
It's no wonder.
Well, it's all cool.
The fog...!
I won! Yay!
Are you Moria's subordinate?
This sucks!
Great! It went in.
M-Moria-sama--er, Gecko Moria
and I have cut ties!
That thick fog... was our one ray of hope!
I must have hit some vital organs!
Even if he's big, he still has the same
weak spots as any other person.
Who planned for the fog to
clear up now of all times?!
Y-You caught me when I was
about to flee from this island.
Lola!
If we jolt his jaw, it will jolt his brain!
The morning sun is going
to shine straight onto us!
Are you okay? Hang in there.
Damn it! We've got enough problems on
This looks bad!
Well? Are you still yourself?
Thank you for coming to save me.
What is that monster
going to do to Perona-sama?!
our hands without having to deal with Oars!
Why are you thanking me?
That one leg is the only thing
keeping you up, Monster Luffy!
The sky is unexpectedly clear tonight.
We're friends, aren't we?
Yeah...
Can you use a sword?
If you were to go on a trip,
where would you like to go?
But I used to be so scared
of you that I told you a lie.
M-Moria! It's Moria!
Nope, not at all.
Where?! Where is he?!
--Shock!
--What?! Small talk?!
Give him a sword!
Hey, don't mess with us!
I'm sorry. I'm actually a woman.
Here!
Bad Manner...
Why do you care?!
The sun will be rising soon.
...Kick...
Should you really be farting around?
Silly! I know that.
...Course!
But if I could go on a vacation,
Why is he here? What happened to Luffy?
Lola...!
I'd like to stay at a dark, damp
old castle oozing with malice,
Huh? I can hear Master's voice!
Geh! What's going on?!
More importantly, isn't Ab-sama wide open?!
Hey! Hold up, Usopp!
Where the heck is Moria?
where I could spend my time
singing incantations.
The shadow we just put inside of you
belonged to a skilled Navy swordsman.
Be my groom, Absalom!
She answered him!
Can't you see him? Look up there!
Bottoms up!
And the answer was most
befitting for our Ghost Princess!
In the gut! He's in the middle of Oars' gut!
Jeez! Pull yourself together, Perona-sama!
Inside his stomach?
A Navy swordsman?
You made me march to the beat of your drum!
All of the shadow's combat abilities
will be added to your own.
I see him!
Flip over, monster.
Of all the stupid...! I nearly let
the weight of your title crush me.
Huh?
Nice! Go!
And we can put in as many shadows
as you can mentally handle!
Are they here? Nope.
Hogback! This was his doing!
What a dreadful man!
Well? Isn't it amazing?
We can use Moria's powers to
boost your strength several fold!
Everyone falls to their knees
after I hit them with my attack!
Wait!
What is Moria doing there?
So where's Luffy? Did Moria
seriously give him the slip?
Wait, darn it! Giant Shallot!
We still have a bunch
of shadows we've caught!
Or did he...?
Stop already!
But if you have weak
willpower, you'll pass out.
No one can take Luffy down!
Hold up!
S-S-Sweet! Now do you see how strong we are?
Yeah!
Were you listening to me?!
All of our hard work will go up in smoke!
That's strange. I could have
sworn I heard Master's voice.
I bet your shadow is
pretty darn strong, Kuma!
Why do you have so many shadows?
Man!
Whatcha think of that, Monster Luffy?!
I'll take you down and give you
to Moria-sama as a parting gift!
We desperately went around purifying
zombies in search of our own shadows.
There he is! Is that a cockpit?
Shoot! I lost sight of him.
I'll be! Is my tummy a cockpit?
Negative Ghost!
Wouldn't it tick you off if you released
some random stranger's shadow?
Gum-Gum Whip!
And Special Hollow!
So that's how we began our shadow collection.
Hey!
This is pretty well made!
Wow, there it is!
We just scored our first knockdown.
I wanna ride in the cockpit!
Listen, you need to remember this!
It's Perona-sama's ultimate combo!
Hey, stupid! Don't stick
your fingers in the cockpit!
When a shadow enters a corpse,
it turns into a zombie.
I can't find Moria!
Okay, Master!
But it won't stick around if there
is already a soul in the body.
Gum-Gum Whip!
Wh-What was that?
This is so cool! I'm like a robot.
Your power-up will only
last ten minutes at most.
Whip!
After that, the shadow will pop out
and return to its true master.
Roar! I'm a giant robot!
There he is!
Oh, man! You can barely
recognize the mansion now.
Creak, creak, creak, creak!
Got that? You must finish
the fight in ten minutes.
Wait!
Screech! Screech!
We will give you all of the shadows
that we risked our lives to obtain!
Whoa, that was close!
Who roughhouses like that?
Is it supposed to be a circus act?
I'm the giant robot, uh, Oarsbomber!
Nice to meet you!
Wh-What was that all about?
Geh! That many?!
I can't ask Moria's whereabouts
when you're being belligerent.
W-Wait... You don't think
someone flipped him, do you?
Wasn't that Straw Hat just now?
Now that the fog has cleared up,
we only have twenty minutes of
night left to get our work done!
Why Oarsbomber?
But didn't Straw Hat say that
he would "kick Moria's butt"
Oarsbomber?
Really! Try to use your head!
How could you be a robot
when you're a zombie?!
and race off to the castle?
You must hurry!
Where'd she go?
An army with a thousand men
couldn't pull that off!
Robots are like, "Ka-ching!" and "Ka-ling!"
What was he chasing after?
Don't forget who you are!
I am sure you can handle
twenty or thirty shadows!
Y-Yeah, but...
I wonder what he's hunting down, don't you?
Where are you, Perona-sama?!
I'm psyched that I get to be a giant robot!
Why else would
he be flipped upside down?
Perona-sama!
Although we could only handle two or three.
Hey, what just happened?!
Oars, give it a rest! Don't get so hyped up.
Huh?
Perona-sama vanished!
Ah, ouch! Ow, ow, ow, ow...
--Do it!
--Okay!
Jerk! What did you do to our princess?!
M-Moria!
Whoa! W-W-Wait!
I didn't say I'd go along with...!
Okay, Master.
He said he was going to kick my butt?
I won't forgive you for this!
Yeah, that was unforgiveable!
I'll never forgive you!
Okay, punks! I am going to
offer you the chance to fight me.
Do you seriously think
Straw Hat can pull that off?
--Perona-sama!
--I'll never forgive you!
If you are victorious, you can
set all of the shadows free.
J-Just how strong... is this man's willpower?
Sorry to burst your bubble,
but that's impossible.
All of you can attack at once!
But he's rottin' scary!
But if you don't defeat Oars,
you'll never pull me out of him.
Run for it!
He's amazing! I've never
heard of anything like this!
The most losers like you who hide in the
forest can do is spend your time praying.
W-We put in all 100 shadows!
That creep...
That's low!
We can't purify Oars if we don't defeat Moria,
Incredible! Just what I'd expect
from our Star of Hope!
but Moria went inside of Oars!
You're a bunch of meanies!
But doesn't that simplify things?
Our target is right there.
Aren't you the Cat Burglar?
You're part of the Straw Hat Crew!
Now I'm ticked! I'm gonna
send all of you flying!
We have to take them down!
Is it true that Monkey D. Luffy
has an older brother?
Usopp! If a little wouldn't cut it,
go find a boatload of salt!
Are they in here? Come on out,
Straw Hat! Woman! Cool hero!
H-Hey, did you lose your mind?
Are you still you, Straw Hat Luffy?
That is the only way to purify Oars.
Eh?!
We'll weaken him as much
as possible in the meantime.
What gives?! He got up there
in the blink of an eye!
Yep! Leave that to us!
Yeah, I'm me.
No way...! Is Oars actually losing?
Did he warp...?
Damn, that's one nasty monster.
Of course he does! Isn't his name Ace?
He's insanely powerful and fast.
Oh, well.
Power is surging through me. I can't stop it!
--Let's do this.
--Okay! You got it! I'll go get some!
I was mostly hanging out
with Moria-sama for fun.
What was his name again?
What of it?
Uh...
I'm pretty sure there was a kitchen
in the first mansion we went to!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!...
I see... So it was true.
I'm pretty sure it's Rose.
I don't see the need to stick
around if I sense mortal danger.
There should be a bunch of salt there!
No, that's not right!
What gives?! Are you after Luffy?
What do you want?
I thought they looked pumped,
but they're after salt.
It ended with an... "s."
Hurry it up, guys!
I'm leaving as soon as possible!
Are you really one of the Seven Warlords?
--Hughes?
--No, I think you're getting colder.
Hey, Oars! Crush the path to the mansion,
along with that long-nosed guy!
I am free to do as I will.
Take this, Straw Hat!
Okay!
Orse?
Hm? No, I still don't
think it's quite right...
All right, bring the rest
of the rations over here!
Make it impossible for them
to reach the kitchen!
Okay, Master.
It's Oars.
Sure thing!
You know, man... It's like you're
a completely different person now.
That guy is trouble!
That's it!
Uh, I'm sorry. I still can't...
Is he after Luffy? I've got to let him know!
Usopp!
Weren't you a little bit shorter before?
Huh? What?!
Yeah, we know how it is.
I wonder how strong he has become.
Could you give us some space?
Who're you? You don't look like a zombie!
Sure...
Try to avoid his attacks.
Crap!
Okay...
What brings you here?
I've got ya, Moria!
Usopp!
You're stinking huge!
You look like a bear [kuma].
Hey, Oars!
I am itching... for a fight!
Usopp!
You aren't getting away this time, jerk face!
Kuma? That was a good guess.
If Luffy's shadow is inside of you...
Shit! Oars is acting intelligently
now that Moria is with him!
Now fight me!
He'll do just great!
Give back everyone's shadows!
Go on! There isn't much time!
...you shouldn't underestimate the
underlying strength of your crew!
Gum-Gum...!
Usopp!
Go give Moria a nightmare,
our Star of Hope, Nightmare Luffy!
Where are you?! Answer me!
He's okay!
The shadow? I've been chasing after the--
Is this... where I can find Moria?
I thought that you might need salt,
so I gathered it in bulk!
Just you wait, Moria!
Sh-Shoot! He pulled a fast one on me!
Brook!
Wait! The mansion isn't that way!
You're a lifesaver!
I am your Brook!
No way! Why does Oars'
body stretch and contract?
If you could go on a trip,
where would you like to go?
I can't believe Oars is able to replicate
Luffy's moves with that massive body!
Who are you guys?
We're the Risky Brothers!
It's almost time for the sun to rise!
Who are you? Are you after Luffy?
We'll give you incredible powers!
Now that it's come to this, we'll have
to do "that." Let's teach him a lesson!
You're mistaken. Oars' body isn't stretching.
You'll run out of hiding
places if you dilly dally.
Say what?
What do you want? Are you really
one of the Seven Warlords?
Huh? What do you mean?
We'll show him the strength
of our powers combined!
S-Stop it!
It looks like Oars' body is changing to
match the movements of his shadow.
I am free to do as I like.
Moria, where are you hiding?!
No way...! Do you want
to do "that" here and now?!
What do you think?
Look carefully! I'm right here.
In that case, this is another
one of Moria's powers.
Let's do it, guys!
This guy is bad news!
What?! Moria is inside of Oars' stomach!
I'm bursting with power! Nothing can stop me!
Tactics #15!
I need to warn the others.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Silent Assault!!
The Mysterious Visitor, 'Tyrant' Kuma!"
"The Straw Hat Crew Gets Wiped Out!
The Shadow-Shadow's Powers in Full Swing!"
"Oars + Moria! The Most Heinous
Combination of Brains and Brawn!"
"The Secret Plan to Turn the Tables!
Nightmare Luffy Makes His Appearance!"
"Knock Him Down!!
Special Attack: Straw Hat Docking?"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!