Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Smooch...!
What?! W-Wait! What're you doing?!
No, stop it!
Curse you, Namizo!
Damn it, Lola! Not only
did you crash my wedding,
but now you have the gall
to attack my bride?!
Run for it, Namizo! I will hold him back!
I came to rescue you, my friend!
Lola!
Ab-sama!
Stay out of my way!
You've made me... waste my energy on you!
How dare you hurt Lola?!
Swing Arm!
It's not like that'll do anything!
That's why I'm going to...
Huh?
I won! Yay!
Hey, Oars!
If Luffy's shadow is inside of you...
...you shouldn't underestimate the
underlying strength of your crew!
"Knock Him Down!!
Special Attack: Straw Hat Docking?"
I'll be just fine, Namizo.
You can go on without me.
I'll get you up to speed with
what's happening here on the island.
Lola!
You know your friend, Straw Hat Luffy?
Well, the Special Zombie
that possesses his shadow
is running amok on the island.
The Special Zombie...?
It's time! Awaken!
Meat!
She must mean him.
Now get going! You can leave him to me.
Thank you, Lola!
Lookie, Ab-sama! It's just the two of us.
Let's savor the moment!
The massive zombie I saw in
the freezer room spells trouble!
Will we be able to tear Luffy's
shadow out of that monster?
But there is no way we're
leaving empty-handed
after what they've put us through!
Bingo! The door is even open.
It... It... It's empty!
No way! Where'd my treasure go?!
There isn't a trace of it left!
I'm sure this is the place! So who took it?
Oh, look! That's the woman who escaped.
You're right. It's her!
Aren't they...?
Sweet! Let's report this!
Report time!
Stop right there!
You have impeccable timing.
I'm dying to ask you two a question.
You sure are tough, puny pirates!
Just throwing this out there, but what
do you think of sending him flying?
What?! S-Seriously, Zoro?
I hear you...
Wha--?!
I bet that'd be a blast.
S-Stop right there!
Wh-When you said, "sending him flying,"
did you really mean that behemoth?!
I nearly had a heart attack when that
lummox started moving around like Luffy.
Still, he isn't fit to be
the King of the Pirates.
The question is how to topple him over.
We can go about it more ways than one.
He must have a weakness somewhere!
It's standard to slowly weaken
a large fish over time...
At any rate...
...he's super scary!
Go crunch!
Here he comes!
Gum-Gum...
...Butt Drop!
That attack is nuts!
Scatter!
Gum-Gum...
Franky, he's going after you!
...Hammer!
Punk! You're just beggin' me
to teach you who's boss.
Behold our forces combined!
Guys!
It's time for Tactics #15!
What?!
You want to do that right here and now?!
Zoro! Curly! Enter standby!
Standby?
Just hold my legs!
What the heck are they up to?
Here we come!
Let's do it!
Pirates Docking: Six!
Giant Robot Warrior!
Big Emperor!
Hold up, Franky!
Is there a problem, Chopper?
She still hasn't docked onto your left arm!
What?!
Hey! What's keeping you, Nico Robin?!
Dock onto my left arm already!
Robin, hurry!
Come, Robin! Copy what I'm doing!
No.
That would hurt my human pride.
It'd hurt...
...her...
...h-h-human--
It would hurt my human pride.
She said it twice!
So you're not going to dock?
Why do you sound so shocked?
Poopy! You got me worked up for nothing!
Do it!
Dock with him!
--Oomph!
I suck! I can't believe they
duped me into doing that.
No, just forget about it!
Robin, we could have become Robot
Warrior Big Emperor if you'd joined us!
I never saw that betrayal coming! Never!
I bet Luffy would have
done it if he were here!
Don't ask me to dock with you... ever again!
Let's regroup, dammit!
--Franky!
--Huh?
I'm gonna borrow your big toy.
Hey, punk! That's my Heavy Nunchaku!
Fine! You can borrow it.
The bastard...! I need to hurry back
to Nami-san and rescue her again.
See how you like a taste of this!
Was that you?
Robin!
Go for the joints after I whack his left arm!
Roger.
Here I go!
I could have sworn it was around here...
Found it! This is the place.
The coast is clear, right?
I'm coming in!
It looks like someone
has ransacked the place.
But I'm sure they must have some in here...
C-C-Could that be...
...milk?!
As I am now, this is the ultimate medicine!
Now all that is left is to
check the expiration date...
Oh, dear...
What a pity...
No, this should just barely
be in the clear! It'll be okay!
I'll drink this for the sake of the others!
Bottoms up!
I can feel it! I can feel it!
I can feel it!
I can feel the calcium seeping
into every pore of my body!
But since I'm a skeleton,
I don't have any pores!
I am alive!
Oh, dear! That random outburst made
these poor eyes of mine see stars.
But since I'm a skeleton,
I don't have eyes...
Ah! This is hardly the time to waste
energy on such silly nonsense!
All right! I must find some quickly
and return to the others.
That screams "suspicious"...
Found it!
But I don't have a tongue...
Perona-sama!
What is it?
The fridge is stuffed! We can't
squeeze another morsel in.
Don't they have a pantry?
Put the provisions in there.
Okay!
Hurry up with the treasure!
Don't leave a single gem behind!
Okay!
Robin!
Go for the joints after I whack his left arm!
Roger.
Here I go!
Over here, Monster Luffy!
Jerk! You're just a shrimp!
Gum-Gum...
Now, Usopp!
Got it!
Eat this!
Special Attack! Special Oil Star!
Three Chamber Shot!
--Hey, Curly!
--Huh?
Send me flying!
While you're swinging that huge thing around?
If you can't, that's cool.
Why, you...!
Of course I can, moron!
Armée de l'Air...
...Power Shoot!
Super Fencing!
Cien Fleurs!
Big Tree!
Wh-What's that?
Clutch!
Whoa,
this is dangerous!
I'm gonna fall! I'm about to fall!
Feast your eyes on this!
It's a super impromptu staircase!
Franky Skywalk!
Unfortunately, this stairway
won't last for long!
Let's get a move on, Chopper!
Yeah!
Super Frapper Gong!
Even if he's big, he still has the same
weak spots as any other person.
If we jolt his jaw, it will jolt his brain!
That one leg is the only thing
keeping you up, Monster Luffy!
Bad Manner...
...Kick...
...Course!
Bottoms up!
Flip over, monster.
Nice! Go!
S-S-Sweet! Now do you see how strong we are?
Whatcha think of that, Monster Luffy?!
We just scored our first knockdown.
Wh-What was that?
Oh, man! You can barely
recognize the mansion now.
Who roughhouses like that?
Is it supposed to be a circus act?
W-Wait... You don't think
someone flipped him, do you?
Really! Try to use your head!
An army with a thousand men
couldn't pull that off!
Y-Yeah, but...
Why else would
he be flipped upside down?
Ah, ouch! Ow, ow, ow, ow...
You're a bunch of meanies!
Now I'm ticked! I'm gonna
send all of you flying!
No way...! Is Oars actually losing?
Oh, well.
I was mostly hanging out
with Moria-sama for fun.
I don't see the need to stick
around if I sense mortal danger.
Hurry it up, guys!
I'm leaving as soon as possible!
Okay!
All right, bring the rest
of the rations over here!
Sure thing!
Who're you? You don't look like a zombie!
What brings you here?
You're stinking huge!
You look like a bear [kuma].
Kuma? That was a good guess.
Is this... where I can find Moria?
If you could go on a trip,
where would you like to go?
Who are you? Are you after Luffy?
What do you want? Are you really
one of the Seven Warlords?
I am free to do as I like.
This guy is bad news!
I need to warn the others.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Silent Assault!!
The Mysterious Visitor, 'Tyrant' Kuma!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!