Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
It's show time! I'm like a lightning arrow!
My name is...
O-Oars is back on his feet!
...Monkey D. Luffy!
Lightning Bone Sword...
I don't know what happened to Luffy,
but he dealt plenty of damage.
Gum-Gum...
Gavotte Bond en Avant!
H-Here's my new weapon, Kuwagata!
Come on, guys!
Pierna Fleurs!
...Rifle!
What is going on?!
Mission: Complete...
The weather forecast is rain!
Didn't we take down Moria?!
Cool Ball!
So are you all set, Usopp?
Gum-Gum...
Rain Tempo!
Y-Yeah, but I only made this to look cool!
H-He wouldn't...!
...Battle Axe!
Luffy!
Crank it like mad!
What?!
I have no idea how it will actually work!
Brook!
I'm cranking it!
I am the one and only Luffy!
All right! Aim for the
center of that lug's gut!
Here it comes! It's the Super Cold Cannon
connected to the extra-large freezer!
"Not Out of Danger Yet!
Orders to Annihilate the Straw Hat Crew!"
Go! Special Attack! Iron Man Comet!
Robin-chan!
Fire!
Gum-Gum...
...Storm!
Eat this, Moria!
Now it's my turn!
Darn it!
Now we're in for it.
Go!
Shoot!
Tch!
...Gatling!
Not a chain!
Be careful.
Franky!
Sanji! Chopper!
Third Gear!
Bone Balloon!
You're not done yet, Oars.
He's still hanging on by a thread.
Finish him off!
Hey, Zoro!
Zoro, push in Oars' stomach.
Okay!
Robin!
Sanji!
Three-Sword Style...
"The Incredible Battle Starts! Luffy vs. Luffy!"
...Secret Technique!
Three Thousand Worlds!
This isn't a dream, is it?
Their bodies are vanishing!
He won, didn't he?
Here goes nothing.
He did! The Star of Hope won!
Thunderbolt...
Huh? That cloud...!
Why?! Didn't we win?
He defeated Oars and Moria!
...Tempo!
Gum-Gum...
Dang it! Were we too late?
Everyone will get their shadows back!
...Giant Bazooka!
Thriller Bark has fallen!
Damn it! Who did that?!
What did they do?!
They're vanishing!
Still standing: three!
Captain Lola!
"The End of the Battle Is Nigh!
Pound in the Finishing Move!"
He did it!
Guys!
Nami-san!
Go on! Stomp all over them, Oars!
Now go smack Moria awake
and make him return our shadows.
I thought we won, darn it!
Hey! Quit yelling my name!
Gah! Here he comes!
What if he notices me?!
The sun is almost up!
Gum-Gum...
I don't need... a wakeup call.
Wh-What? What? What?! Can he stretch?
It's impossible! There is no way
we can take this monster down.
...Pistol!
Moria!
I'm fresh out of ideas!
Wh-What should we do?!
Straw Hat, how dare you
trash my Thriller Bark?!
You're incredible, Straw Hat!
"A Pirate Ship on the Grand Line"
He took out Oars!
--Usopp!
--Huh?
I don't believe it!
I'll create an opening.
Captain!
What?!
I lost my crew because they were alive!
Eh?
So do your thing!
Please come to the deck, Captain!
Eh? What? Zoro, what's that
supposed to mean?
But with undead zombies,
I have nothing to lose!
Quit being stupid and hit the hay!
Oh, I get it! That's what you meant!
The morning light will fry you!
H-His arm extended?! Why?!
Come to me, all of the
shadows on Thriller Bark!
You've got it!
It's been two years since Moria
stole our shadows. We'll never...
Huh? What's going on? Usopp!
But Captain, please take a look at my feet!
Hey, Luffy! Hang in there!
Serve as my power!
Gum-Gum...
--Luffy!
--Luffy, get up!
It stretched. That feels
more like how it should.
Shadows Asgard!
Huh?
...Pistol!
It's not my place to ask after
pushing him, but will he be okay?
You have... a shadow!
--Gum-Gum...
--What?!
I bet your shadow has also returned, Captain!
Bro!
I bet his body is absolutely exhausted.
108-Pound--
He's collecting all of the shadows
on the island and absorbing them.
...Bell!
"The Straw Hat Crew Gets Wiped Out!
The Shadow-Shadow's Powers in Full Swing!"
He single-handedly wielded
the power of a hundred men.
Straw Hat, I'd say you absorbed
around 100 shadows.
Anyway, we need to recover all of
the shadows as quickly as possible!
O-O-Our...
Gum-Gum...
Right! Let's hurry.
Incoming!
In that case, I'm absorbing 100...
The eastern sky is starting
to get dangerously bright!
...Bell!
Our shadows are back!
Dawn is on the horizon.
It's everyone, Captain!
All of our shadows have come back!
200!
So how do you get your shadows back?
Captain, do you think someone defeated Moria?
300!
Four of my crewmates have lost theirs!
No way! That's impossible.
I'm out of the game if I take any direct hits.
I'm in the groove now that my body stretches.
400!
What's taking Usopp so long?!
He's so powerful that he went up
against Kaido of the Four Emperors.
Gum-Gum...
I'm sure this has been
a trying ordeal for you.
500!
Really, I'd like Straw Hat
to recover them for us.
Here comes another attack!
Who could possibly take out Moria?
...Spear!
This is the battle of the century
for the great man, Usopp!
600!
Forget it! I bet he can't move a muscle.
You'd better not move!
Moria reigns over the shadows
in all of the zombies.
"Somewhere in the West Blue
on the Grand Line"
700!
Unless he personally says,
"Return to your original master,"
It's back! I have a shadow again!
Damn it! What is going on here?
Hey, monster!
His attack power has skyrocketed!
Yeah?
our shadows won't come back.
800!
I'd love to play with you some more,
but the sun is rising soon.
How come Oars can stretch
when he isn't a power holder?
Let's stop worrying and get to business.
Right! We'll just have to wake
Moria up and force him to say that.
How many years has it been
since I've seen the light of day?
What did Moria do?
900!
Why don't we finish this up?
Our zombies in Thriller Bark
finally kicked the bucket!
What was the point in defeating him
if we don't reclaim our shadows?
Poopy!
Yay! It's great!
Of all the things to say!
1,000 shadows!
Hurray!
Do you seriously hope to defeat us
when you're gasping for breath?
We're free from Moria's curse!
Good guess! I'm making you live this
nightmare with my Shadow-Shadow power...
Boss!
Yeah!
"Our Bodies Vanish! The Morning Sun
Shines on the Nightmarish Island!"
What?! You're getting under my skin!
I can watch the sunrise!
...Shadow Revolution!
Look! I have a shadow! It's following me!
I don't know how to give up!
R-Revolution?
Now bring it on, monster!
Shadows copy whatever your body does.
That's common knowledge!
Let's settle the score!
A thousand...
...shadows...
O-Oars is back on his feet!
Your body and shadow are always
mirror images of each other.
I have a reflection!
I can see myself in the mirror.
...are inside of Moria!
He shouldn't be able to move
after taking a beating like that!
We're in a load of...
Of all the nerve!
That is a hard-and-fast rule.
Oars, crush the idiot already!
Hey! What was all that
commotion about, Margarita?
Oars' shadow is supposed to obey him,
Yeah! Master, let me land the finishing blow!
My shadow! My shadow has come back.
This is horrible! We're screwed.
but I usurped control by
slipping my shadow inside of it.
This can't be real.
What?! Your shadow has returned?
The Straw Hat Crew can't fight anymore!
Do you know what that means?
You keep out of this!
As in the shadow that was stolen
by pirates ten years ago?
And we used up our trump card, the shadows!
I can freely alter the shape of Oars' shadow.
It's true...
We don't have enough strength
left to level this monster!
We're doomed. What the heck is that?
Gum-Gum...
But his shadow and body
must take the same form.
Sir, I'm terribly sorry!
Zoro!
I'm back to normal.
One Gorilla!
I was so surprised that I accidentally
dropped your prized dishes!
Two Gorilla!
Since the shadow stops
matching the shape of his body,
It's as good as dawn!
That didn't hurt at all.
Three-Sword Style...
...Pistol!
It's true I had hard feelings
towards plates, but I've reformed!
We're out of time!
...Two Gorilla... Slash!
Damn it!
his body transforms to match his shadow.
You really can't defeat a zombie
in a contest of strength.
Oars was a pushover for Straw Hat
when he had 100 shadows.
I didn't mean any harm.
That is how Shadow Revolution works!
We've reached our limit.
The sun is going to rise any minute now.
In other words, it's the
opposite of common sense.
And he has ten times that!
Where is he storing all of that power?
I am really sorry. I will leave
the manor immediately.
We'll never be free from this
life trapped in the darkness!
Moria made the arms and legs
in Oars' shadow extend,
Jerk!
so his body stretched to match.
Let's give up. If we stay here,
we're just gonna die.
Since it's his power, he must have
way better control of the ability!
Crap!
I'm stuck.
So instead of becoming a rubber man,
Oars' body can transform into anything?
How could you say that?
Let's hurry back to the forest.
I don't care about those plates!
Th-This is hopeless!
Aw, man! This bites!
Let's return... to the dark forest,
where the sun never shines.
Three-Sword Style...
Did you get hurt?
Give me a break. He's too big for that.
Really, this calls for a celebration!
We've come too far for
crap like this! It's not fair!
...Yaksha Crow!
Yeah. I can't get near him like this.
This is truly wonderful, Margarita.
Aren't you...?
I don't know what happened to Luffy,
but he dealt plenty of damage.
You must be so happy.
He even has Straw Hat's shadow.
This is far worse than rubber!
I am!
H-Hey, mister! You'll croak if you
try to run around as you are now.
Yeah.
If I make his shadow round...
I imagine he has ours as well.
H-He did it! That worked!
You can still stand after taking
a blow from that massive giant?
--Usopp, now!
--Not my right arm again! Quit going after it!
They're all inside...
Isn't it great, Margarita?
Oars will turn into a ball!
...of his stomach.
You're almost as immortal as the zombies!
No way...!
I said that doesn't hurt me!
Right.
What... is he doing?!
You're bouncing every which way!
Hey, where are the members of the
Straw Hat Crew that we moved over here?
Ow, ow, ow!
He vanished!
Run! This is a lost cause!
I-Is this for real?
B-Beats me! How could they
move when they're out cold?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Zoro!
Oars Ball!
Huh? What happened to
the two that were here?
You're right! The long-nosed guy
and the lady are gone.
Eat this!
Phew!
I'm very much alive.
You don't think...
they bailed out on us, do you?
Whoa...
Eh?! When did they run off?
For a second, I thought I
was about to go to Heaven.
I win.
Run for it!
He put a crack in the island!
Anyway, this looks bad!
Let's split this scene.
Sounds good to me! If we can go together,
I'd love to go to Heaven!
Hey, Oars!
The mansion attached to
the mast is collapsing!
Look over here!
This isn't funny, you jerks!
We seriously thought you were dead.
Hey, now! Just a sec, Master.
You nearly vanished!
Run for it! Head for the forest!
Keep out of my fight!
So that... didn't quite cut it!
That was terrifying!
It's over for real this time!
Huh? Straw Hat?!
Goodness! That was bad for my heart.
Aw, man! Not you too, Straw Hat!
My bad! I didn't mean to interfere.
Uh, not that I have a heart.
Just one more attack... Damn it!
I'm just here to offer assistance.
No! I'm gonna vanish!
My body is gonna vanish!
Go on, Oars! Crush each
and every one of them!
That really took a lot outta me.
Please save me!
By the way, where is Luffy?
Stupid! Hurry into the shadows.
I did it.
--Robin!
--Yes, I'm here.
The morning sun is coming through!
Moria must have tricked him
into going somewhere!
Make your way to the forest
through the shadows!
What was that? I swallowed something.
She didn't hightail it!
Don't leave the buildings' shadows!
There is no way he got his butt kicked!
I want up!
Seriously? I swear, he is such an idiot!
Captain Lola!
No... You didn't!
Roger.
Captain Lola, what's keeping you? Hurry up!
I'll provide the footing.
What should I do? Should I tell everyone?
It's the morning sun!
Guys, please run for it.
We're already in a tight spot...
Usopp, what was that...?
I'm not afraid of the sunrise anymore!
Do they need to know
If there is anything I could do for you...
that there is another Warlord
on this island right now?
I have a shadow!
H-How could you say that?
You're in the same boat!
I did it... I did it!
I can kiss goodbye to life in the dark forest!
So does this mean everyone
won't get their shadows back
Even the skeleton is up and moving!
I got Oars to eat salt!
Hurray! Hurray!
But I'm responsible...
What?! Why?
Woot! Yay! Yay!
Great! Brook, I have a favor to ask of you.
unless we defeat both Zombie Luffy and Moria?
It looks like all of them are okay, too.
...for this gamble!
I figured as much.
We nearly ceased to exist
when the morning light hit us,
Yeah, that sounds about right.
Everyone has taken positions
to offer support.
Just look at them.
No way! It's almost dawn!
but our bodies were fully restored when
That's part of the enemy's plan!
We just have to thwart it!
Salt? What's so great about salt?
our shadows returned just in the nick of time.
What is that lady doing way up there?!
--Excuse me!
--What?
It's probably along the same lines of
how Moria could alter a body's shape
Oh, yeah! You don't know.
Those guys...
Skeleton, you're here?
Zombies are weak against salt.
I-It never even occurred
to these guys to run!
They aren't the least bit fazed.
by manipulating its shadow.
Please...
Look! Oars is finished!
If I make his shadow round...
Please grant me this one request!
And here they've lost their shadows as well.
The moment Oars stood up...
Huh?
...they started to prepare
for a counterattack!
Do they still intend to win?
...Oars will turn into a ball!
Luffy's shadow is gonna come out!
But all it took was one hit for him
to put a crack in the island!
Oars Ball!
It's purification time, you zombie monster!
Right now, Moria is way more
powerful than Oars ever was!
We've won!
All I know is that our bodies
and shadows have to match.
You shouldn't get near him, Zoro!
Go!
Thank you so much, everyone!
As long as they intend to fight,
I'm not leaving this spot!
Relax! This is the only time we're ever gonna have the fun
This is nothing.
If we selfishly place our faith
in him as the "Star of Hope"
Have you lost your mind, Brook?
Just you watch.
of losing our shadows.
Didn't you see what happened to Franky?
and then split as soon
as the going gets tough,
Anyway, I'm just glad we didn't lose anyone...
we're no better than lowly insects!
Don't blame me for what happens!
This packs a wallop, so get ready!
Chopper, hurry! The sun is rising.
But this situation is hopeless!
Yeah!
All of a sudden, I feel totally wiped out.
I want you to escape.
Dark Cloud Tempo!
As the captain, our obligation
will be met if I stay behind.
There any cola around here?
All of the strange creatures and phenomena
we've seen since coming ashore
Guys... Treasure your lives.
Think you can use this, Franky?
Go ahead! Please do your thing!
That'll be great! Come lend me a hand!
were nothing more than
a ruse put on by Moria.
I didn't think I'd use Kuwagata again!
Captain Lola!
Now that he has been defeated,
there is nothing left on this island.
I can't believe it!
There is no greater pain than
being unable to repay a favor!
The sun is shining over there!
Hurry into the shade!
These guys haven't given up at all!
That was a close one!
I'm fine!
Just like waking from a nightmare in
the morning, everything has vanished.
Hey, you're in the way! Clear the area!
What is Moria's shadow doing there...?
This is what it means to
place your hope in someone!
It would be our pleasure!
I swear, this was one nasty haunted mansion!
I was internally guarding against that!
Pierna Fleurs!
Captain Lola!
I shall put in backbreaking effort!
Hey! Hey! Wake up, Absalom!
No...! Do you want to die?!
What a blissful dolt!
Okay! Then off you go!
I'm either going to live or die!
You were living in a fool's paradise if you
thought I was going to knowingly leave
I'm off!
Come on, Absalom!
Slalom Vine!
Here we go!
Hey, get up!
I don't care which way the coin flips.
Thanks!
his weakness wide open, stupid!
I will never go back to
hiding in the shadows!
Captain!
Lola!
Wait! Where are you going?
The electricity is so strong
you can see my bones!
Knock it off! I'm not going to marry you!
But I was nothing but bones to begin with!
Damn it!
He's practically going berserk.
Don't make a scene!
You dropped this, Long Nose!
She has already lost her shadow.
It's show time! I'm like a lightning arrow!
What is this? Smoke? Clouds?
He doesn't have full control of the shadows.
It looks like anger and foolish pride
made him overestimate himself.
Hogback?
Usopp!
The weather forecast is rain!
For the record, what happened to me?
Lightning Bone Sword...
Cool Ball!
I have no idea what happened to you!
Gavotte Bond en Avant!
Usopp!
Hey, guys. We're out of time.
I'd wager someone defeated you. Pathetic!
Awesome! He drilled through.
Rain Tempo!
I'm gonna push myself a bit.
Oh, no! He spilt the salt!
But more importantly,
I have bad news about Moria-sama...
He went through my body!
Please take care of things after that!
Brook got this salt for us!
He made an opening! Keep the attacks going!
Okay, you can count on us!
What?!
Wha--?!
Crap! Shoot! This is our last reserve!
It's raining! But why?
Send him flying!
Straw Hat defeated Moria-sama?!
Can that lady use magic?
Hey, you guys! What makes
you think you stand a chance?
Mission: Complete...
Dang it! Shoot! Shoot!
How dare he make fun of us?!
Shh! Not so loud! Lower the volume!
All right! The emergency
plumbing job is done.
There is no way you'll win!
Well done, Bones!
You're up against a monster
that's a thousand strong!
You're being loud!
Damn it! Curse him! Screw that--
Two-Sword Style... Nigiri...
Jeez! I'm sopping wet.
Right! Stop and think for a second.
Why are you so riled up, Hogback?
You should be called Rileback.
...Tower Climb!
Gum-Gum...
He even has your shadows!
Coup de Vent!
He has your monstrous power!
...Stamp!
Thriller Bark is of no use to me now,
What was that?
And we're running out of time!
Crank it like mad!
Why, you--no, first I'm going
to finish off that skeleton.
If you're here to watch, shut your trap.
Crush him!
but I don't plan on spending
the rest of my days as a loser.
I'm cranking it!
We've already won the fight with Moria.
What do you want to do?
Gum-Gum...
Well...
Usopp!
H-He wouldn't...!
But it all comes down to finishing
things before the sun rises.
...Battle Axe!
Here it comes! It's the Super Cold Cannon
connected to the extra-large freezer!
Usopp!
Brook...!
Moria plans to use his insane power
to buy that brief period of time.
Stop! Stop it!
Brook!
Didn't Luffy shrink back there?
Usopp! Usopp!!
Fire!
He told me that after he uses the Giant Gear,
Stop it!!
his body shrinks for however
long he used that gear.
Keep it up! Turn him into dust!
Don't you think Luffy's new fighting
style is too hard on his body?
Special Attack! Atlas Comet!
Same goes for that woman.
Second Gear!
I'm frozen!
I'm worried...
I can't move.
If the enemies waiting ahead of us
only continue to get stronger,
Will we get obliterated first?
Incredible!
That won't work!
he's gonna keep pushing himself!
The cold air froze him.
Crush her! Smash her!
Or will Moria self-destruct first?
We need to pull our own weight better.
Trample everyone here!
--Crap!
--Usopp, fight!
Go, Luffy!
"Fight"? Eh? Hey! Whoa, wait!
That includes the people who are out cold!
You're right.
You're up next, Long Nose!
They still have a little bit
of breath in their bodies.
Gum-Gum...
Squash them till they
aren't recognizably human!
Now it's my turn!
...Jet Rocket!
Gum-Gum Bazooka!
Darn it!
Go!
Look! The shadows are coming out.
I'm dead!
Not a chain!
It worked!
Gum-Gum...
Whoa, a zombie!
Hey, giant!
One of them still has its shadow!
...Jet Bazooka!
Darn rudder chain!
What do you think you're crushing?
No, I'm a severely injured old man.
You're amazing, Sanji!
Huh? Huh?
Jet Bazooka! Jet Bazooka!
That's confusing! Just pass
yourself off as a zombie!
Thanks!
My arm isn't stretching! Why not?
Aren't you the old man
we met at the graveyard?
Ochenta Fleurs Cuatro Mano!
I can't believe it! I never dreamed I would
There isn't a single soul under your feet.
Gobs of shadows are being released!
see the day I could walk under the sun again.
Why are the shadows leaving
if they're under his control?
Thank you! How can I ever repay you?
Huh? I...
Moria is losing control over them
as he starts to black out.
Throw me!
Where did these arms come from?!
They're annoying!
I'm really going to throw you.
I'm alive?
Hey! Grandpa Spoil!
Even Moria can't fully control
a thousand shadows at once!
I'll be fine! I'm a rubber man!
Could you stop manipulating
his shadow for the time being?
Gramps!
I have no idea who you are, but thank
you for saving me from--what?!
Honorary President of the Victim Association!
Be careful.
What?!
No way!
Third Gear!
--Gum-Gum...
--Brick Bat!
Hold!
Oh, guys! So you pulled through?
Who're you?
G-Gak! C-Can't breathe!
Bone Balloon!
My name is...
Gramps, are you all right?
Yeah!
Keep it up, Robin!
You know each other?
...Monkey D. Luffy!
Oh! Come to think of it,
we still haven't thanked you.
Zoro, push in Oars' stomach.
Do you think this will
keep me out of the fight?
Black Box!
I'm on it.
We're grateful from the bottom of our hearts!
Your plan doesn't amuse me in the least!
Three-Sword Style...
I'm trapped!
Sorry for all the trouble we've caused you.
I'm going to crush you!
When we saw all the mayhem you caused,
--L-L...
--L...
...Secret Technique!
we figured if you couldn't do it, no one could!
Luffy?!
Brick Bat.
Three Thousand Worlds!
Thank you, guys.
No one in Thriller Bark's Victim Association...
Wha--?!
Robin-chan!
That was a direct hit!
Veinte Fleurs!
It was just like the punch
that put a crack in the island!
...will ever forget the debt we owe you!
Now's our chance.
Calendula!
Here goes nothing.
Straw Hat!
Thank you very much!
If there is anything you'd like,
please say the word!
Luffy?! How do you figure?!
Robin!
Looking good, Sanji!
Oars' back is perfectly straight.
Stop it!
There isn't much,
but we have some food reserves.
What the heck are they doing?
I guess I can see the resemblance,
but are you sure?
Better yet, you're welcome to marry me!
This is your baptism!
A human spine normally bends in an S-shape
Is it really you?
What do you think you're
doing to Robin-chan?!
It's really me.
--We'll pass!
--Five men turned her down all at once!
to soften the impact
and weight that goes on it.
But even the way you talk is different...
She's been rejected 4,449 times!
But if you straighten it out,
it won't be able to disperse the shock.
This is what happens when a whippersnapper
What happened to you?
tries to act like a big shot on these waters!
Does he have the power to transform?
You really don't need to thank us...
It will take all of the damage!
Don't say that!
Remember what Luffy said, Gramps?
Or did he catch on...?
Go, Luffy!
--I'm especially interested in you!
--We simply fought to suit our own needs.
This is what you get for defying
one of the Seven Warlords!
Good luck.
Did he defeat everyone?
--Will you marry me?
--We just saved you while we were at it.
Eat my extra-large bazooka!
Uh, y-yeah...
I'll repel it with a bazooka of my own!
H-He's cruel!
Aside from us, that monster took everyone out.
How could you say that?!
They actually want to thank us!
Moria's shadow?!
Know your place! The world is devised
to crush anyone who stands out!
Gum-Gum... Huh?
I see. Get back.
Let's see who is the more powerful
long-distance power holder!
It won't move! I can't move my right arm!
Yeah! You should listen to her, Bro!
"Get back"?! Luffy, do you
realize what that is?!
Let us do something for you!
Your hold hurts pretty darn bad!
It won't extend, either.
We don't care if you
saved us on the side or not!
That's the zombie with your shadow!
The zombies' shortcoming is
their inability to perceive damage.
We're grateful that you defeated Moria.
Don't get distracted by his shadow!
To top it off, it can stretch out
and use your attacks!
That's your shadow. Settle the score, Luffy.
If we take out his body,
the shadow will disappear as well.
I know, right?
How are you going to fight it...?
Gum-Gum...
Uh, your eyes...
Luffy-san!
What are they talking about?
I know! Why don't you swipe
all of Moria's treasure?
Luffy!
Go!
Cuatro Mano!
Get him, Straw Hat!
We'll load it onto your ship for you!
Don't worry about it! Just crush them, Oars!
Luffy!
Whatcha think of that?
H-Hey!
Oh, it's already on...
What are you doing?! Stop it!
Of course! Gum-Gum...
...Giant...
...Bazooka!
Clutch!
Oh, yeah! I forgot about something important!
No!
What is it?
--Here it comes!
--...Rifle!
--Sweet!
--You're amazing, Robin!
I had totally forgotten about him...
What's the matter?
We've got a problem!
I see...
Hey, Robin! Watch out
for the shadow behind you!
What?!
I am the one and only Luffy!
It sounds as though my fears were justified.
He got back up!
So it would seem.
He did it!
Who is that?
There he is...
Hey, something is flying straight for us!
--What is it?!
--Is it a bird?
No way!
It's Oars!
Dude!
Everyone, remain calm and hear me out.
Is that really Luffy? I can't believe my eyes!
Huh? What is Moria doing down here?
It doesn't matter if I'm
a "whippersnapper"...
You were close! It's such a pity.
Doppelman and I can switch
places at any given minute.
...or if I stand out!
Even a zombie can't get up again
after a beating like that.
During our fight with Moria...
He lost...
No one...
Oars truly lost this time.
They switched places?
...I forgot to mention this.
...can...
D-Damn it!
Now what will become of Thriller Bark?
Huh? Then the one inside Oars is...?
...crush me!
There is one more member on this island...
What?!
No one can crush you?
My Shadow Substitute that
has no joints to dislocate!
That's right! It's the shadow that
was here until just a second ago.
Your ability to say that
without any justification
...of the Seven Warlords!
Wha--?!
proves just how green you are!
What did you say?!
I'm amazed they pulled it off.
It's because I'm rubber.
What's going on?
That's a...
They're something else.
He's doing it! He's actually fighting!
...Warlord?!
He's kicking Oars' butt!
Th-That's messed up!
Robin-chan!
We certainly invited a
fearsome crew onto our ship!
Now's our chance! Find them!
Huh? Who are all those people?
What are two of the Seven Warlords
doing on the same island?!
What happened to the master?
Any luck? Have you found them?
In just a sec, I'm gonna make you
spew out all of the shadows!
We have finally found a
replacement for Crocodile.
Nope! You?
They won! This time, they
really pulled it off!
What's with him? Is he immortal?
It would look bad if another one of the
Seven Warlords needed to be replaced.
He's incredible!
Oh, hey!
They won!
--Zoro!
--I found one! He's a member
of the Star of Hope's crew!
--They really won!
--Thank you! You guys are the best!
Is he still breathing, even if barely?
Here's another!
You really were the Star of Hope!
I don't know.
He's severely injured.
You were everything we
hoped you'd be, Straw Hat!
If he is still alive, I would
like to wait for his recovery
Everyone's hurt bad!
The morning light!
Crap!
One of them has even turned into a skeleton!
and let him retain his position as one
of the Seven Warlords for a while.
Stupid! Get in the shadows or you're toast!
It isn't safe to leave them unconscious here.
Help me! My hand is vanishing.
You're tiny!
Hurry and get them somewhere safe!
We can take further measures later.
Who are you?!
Hurry into the shadows!
The courtyard isn't safe anymore.
Why did you shrink?!
If we lose one Warlord after the next,
the title will cease to demand respect.
What are they doing?
And in such large numbers?
Third Gear!
That's three down!
Think they're zombies?
Even though it doesn't hurt, I can't move.
This information must not get out to the public.
What if they're after Zoro and the others?
Now he's got Robin's shadow!
Let's hurry down!
Bone Balloon!
I swear, those pirates
cause nothing but trouble.
Okay!
I can't believe he's still ticking
even after we crushed his bones.
Gum-Gum Stamp!
I don't have anything to put it in,
but I might as well take it.
I recognize him!
Hey, is it wise to use that
attack more than once?
Nearly as large as Moria,
that pirate was called the "Tyrant."
His vitality is making a mockery of life!
Of course not!
Oh, dang! What's going on?!
Don't you remember what using
Second Gear did to you that one time?
He's Bartholomew Kuma!
Oars is getting his butt kicked!
The morning light!
That's Tyrant Kuma?!
Diable Jambe!
I can't believe someone is flinging
him around when he's so big.
You mean the pirate whose
cruelty knows no bounds?!
You damn bastard!
You understand what I'm saying, don't you?
Use your Gum-Gum to shoot yourself over here!
Give Robin-chan's shadow back!
What's going on?!
Once you're here, I'll carry you!
Hey, Oars!
Extra Haché!
Do not leave witnesses to testify
that Straw Hat defeated Moria.
Brick Bat!
We're surrounded by the sea
and a bunch of battleships!
Hey, did you hear? Moria-sama is
currently inside of Oars' stomach!
The World Government is
assigning you a special mission:
If we stay here, we're gonna be killed!
I wonder why... I have shivers
running down my spine.
He switched places with his shadow again!
Annihilate everyone on the island,
including the Straw Hat Crew.
I-I can't...
What?!
What?
Yay! He did it!
That means the ruler over all
of the Thriller Bark zombies
Hurray!
My body... isn't moving at all.
If he switched with his shadow...
He won!
That will be easy.
is getting defeated along with
the ultimate Special Zombie?!
Don't be ridiculous! You defeated the enemy!
Moria is back inside Oars' stomach!
I just heard something!
Hey, Luffy! Hurry and get
everyone's shadows back.
H-He just said "annihilate."
We got Robin back, too!
All that's left is for us to go back!
What type of sick joke is this?!
This is no time for partying.
And everything has returned to how it was.
Oars is a legendary villain that was
called the "Devil" 500 years ago!
All of you are toast without them!
Please! Try hard!
Gosh darn it, Master!
Our shadows...!
You're right. We need to hurry.
This is supposed to be my fight!
We're ruled by one of the Seven Warlords
of the Sea, Gecko Moria-sama!
Now go smack Moria awake
and make him return our shadows.
I'm sorry, Oars. I had a bit
too much fun with them.
This really is nuts, Luffy!
The sun is almost up!
Huh?
Your body can't take this!
I don't need... a wakeup call.
I'll finish off that woman.
Moria!
Gum-Gum...
Say what?!
Nightmare Luffy?
...Giant Jet Shell!
So, bluntly put, you did that to Luffy
Gum-Gum...
Master!
by stuffing the shadows of
a hundred people into him?
I'm so glad you're all right!
His arms can stretch out again!
There is no way Moria-sama could lose!
Whoa, wait! Is he gonna annihilate...
Exactly, members of the Star of Hope's crew!
Shoot! He's going to attack
Robin when she's out cold!
It's so powerful!
More shadows are coming out!
...all of us?! Why?!
Honestly, the strength
of his power terrified us!
Give me a break!
I won't let them escape! They're my minions!
But he'll only retain that power
for two or three minutes.
We just got free from Moria's power!
I-If you're up, that works just fine for us.
Sanji! Robin! Run for it!
Now, if you don't want Straw Hat
to kick your butt again,
Before long, the shadows that we
crammed into him will fly back out.
...Bazooka!
Shadows, I am your sovereign!
Diable Jambe!
We feel bad about what we did to your captain,
you'd better return all of our shadows!
Frit Assorti!
Right! Give them back, jerk!
but we want to walk under the sun once more!
No way! We can't fight two Warlords in a row!
Huh?
We want to be human again!
That bastard! He doesn't
plan on giving up our shadows.
It took all we had just to defeat Moria.
He is our hope!
This isn't a schoolyard fight.
My shadow!
Even the threat of death is
meaningless before a true pirate.
The sun will be rising soon.
You repelled him!
Come back to me!
These few minutes will determine
the fate of everyone who has fallen victim to this island!
I'm able to solve the mystery behind
Straw Hat's excessive level-up
--Captain Lola!
We're counting on you, Nightmare Luffy!
Captain! Captain!
Now's your chance!
Get Robin-chan away from here.
if you "whipped dogs of
the forest" were involved.
Guys, get back! I'll take him on!
My shadow, can't you hear me?
You can count on me!
How vile of you to use my
shadow ability against me!
Hey! Sanji! Zoro!
We were always together,
clear from the time I was born!
Stuff it! Give our shadows back!
We came into this world together!
Be careful! He uses some sort of power!
Chopper, what are you doing up there?
Straw Hat, how dare you...
Come back to me!
I saw someone vanish when
he touched her with his hand.
I spent the past three years searching
for the zombie that contained you!
I've been searching for what
caused Oars to die 500 years ago!
He destroyed the mansion!
...trash my Thriller Bark
like there is no tomorrow?!
Hurry away from the mansion!
Negative Ghost!
Now you're in there, aren't you?
His cause of death?
That's what you get for
interfering with our voyage!
Go after his right arm!
And Special Hollow!
If you can hear me, come back! Come back!
This isn't his real arm!
Now give back our shadows
before the sun comes up!
Captain Lola!
Hogback reconstructed it, but there are signs
Please hide in the shadows!
of horrible frostbite around the stitches.
You're gonna turn to ash!
At your current strength, you would
have died if you continued your journey.
I can't say for certain, but I suspect
he froze to death 500 years ago!
But... But it's killing me!
Th-The people he touches vanish?!
You're nowhere near strong
enough to face the New World!
He really is amazing!
It's right there!
Sweet! Keep it up, Nightmare Luffy!
S-Scary!
You seem to have a pretty decent crew...
Even a monster like this is
no match for the elements.
You're right! Supposedly all of our
shadows are currently inside of Moria.
And he can also warp.
He died while wandering the Land of Ice!
...but you'd lose all of them.
They're right in front of us!
Even 500 years ago,
I'd wager Oars went around...
Do you know why?
We'll never get another chance like this!
Hey, Straw Hat! You don't have time to chat!
...mostly naked!
But we're up against one
of the Seven Warlords...
I don't wanna lose to someone that stupid!
Look at the sky! It's getting so bright.
Aren't you the Cat Burglar?
She's right... Come back!
Zombies may not feel pain,
but they still take damage.
Please get our shadows back already!
Jerk-face! You're just a shrimp!
You're part of the Straw Hat Crew!
Shadows, come back!
We're running out of time!
Is it true that Monkey D. Luffy
has an older brother?
All of the attacks we've
landed are accumulating!
Come back!
Gum-Gum Bullet!
I found the answer
through personal experience.
Come back!!
If we can render this arm nonfunctional,
it will halve his offensive power!
Come back!
Why did I lose such infamous
and skilled subordinates?
Eh?!
Come back! Come back! Come back!
What gives?! He got up there
in the blink of an eye!
Long story short, focus on this one arm!
Why are you talking up a storm...
...while standing on my shoulder?!
I'd like to say something to my shadow, too.
We've got a freak on our hands!
Ow, ow, ow...
Oars, this is pathetic!
Chopper!
How did Straw Hat come by all of this power?
If you want to become the
King of the Pirates...
Damn! If I stay in here,
I'll keep taking collateral damage.
I lost my crew because they were alive!
I should leave the cockpit for...
But with undead zombies,
I have nothing to lose!
...you had better...
Gum-Gum...
Huh?
...stick with me!
He's gone!
Zombies are immortal!
Since you're a zombie,
you have no idea how badly
...Pistol!
They are unlimited soldiers that can
be replaced if someone purifies them.
His hands... are dangerous!
you just hurt your own body
with that punch, do you?
With my army of the dead, I shall fight
to become King of the Pirates once more!
Huh? Oh, you went inside my fist!
Consider yourselves fortunate that your
shadows get to serve as my subordinates.
Heh! I'm tiny, so the crevices
in your fist are like caves!
Gum-Gum...
Rumble!
Jumping Point!
Arm Point!
Chopper!
...Battle Axe!
Glad you dodged that!
I'll lend you a hand!
Sanji, please do!
It stuck to me!
Gum-Gum...
Armée de l'Air...
...Storm!
Cloven...
Roseo Shoot!
Come to me, all of the
shadows on Thriller Bark!
What?!
Serve as my power!
He's here!
He's huge!
Shadows Asgard!
When'd he get down here?!
Oars...!
I see. I'd definitely call that warping.
Moria-sama!
You jerks!
Bro!
Stop hitting me in the same spot!
Damn it! We were finally set free!
His shadow came out.
Those attacks aren't going to work.
There is no way I'm gonna die here!
Straw Hat, curse you...!
They'll work! Pain is a signal
meant to protect the body!
Right! I'll never let someone stand
between us and our voyage ever again!
Watch out! He's collapsing!
The shadows...!
No way...!
Lacking pain doesn't make you strong!
Guys, get him!
I dare you to go to the New World!
He's collecting all of the shadows
on the island and absorbing them.
Yeah, you heard them!
Chopper!
Let's get him!
Save your fuzzy logic!
Stop, men! You don't stand a chance!
The real nightmare awaits
you in the New World!
Hey! That looks bad, guys!
Get away from there!
Gum-Gum...
Straw Hat, I'd say you absorbed
around 100 shadows.
Now we're in for it.
Our shadows are coming back!
Shoot!
I don't believe it...
We made it in time!
...Gatling!
Here come our shadows!
Oh, yeah! Where's Luffy?
In that case, I'm absorbing 100...
200!
Sanji! Chopper!
He pierced through the whole group
without even touching all of them...
300!
400!
D-Darn it!
The shadows... are leaving his body.
Hey, is Luffy gonna be okay?
H-Hey, guys!
500!
Whoa!
600!
There go another two...
Shadow, please hurry!
Luffy!
Dude, are you okay?
He's taking everyone out...
What the heck?!
700!
This isn't a dream, is it?
Darn it!
He won, didn't he?
No way!
Come on, guys!
He did! The Star of Hope won!
800!
W-Wait! What is going on?!
He defeated Oars and Moria!
Pirate Hunter Zoro...
Didn't we take down Moria?!
Four down! Five down!
900!
I will start with you.
Everyone will get their shadows back!
Thriller Bark has fallen!
Luffy!
1,000 shadows!
Three to go!
I have no idea who you are,
but thanks for rescuing me!
Three-Sword Style Secret Technique!
What is with the padding
on the palms of his hands?!
It sounds like my fears were justified.
Darn it! Gosh darn it!
Three Thousand Worlds!
And here I thought we'd won!
So who the heck are you?!
It repels all of my attacks!
Armée de l'Air Power Shoot!
So it would seem.
But now he's 1,000 times bigger and stronger.
Monkey D. Luffy.
Do not leave witnesses to testify
that Straw Hat defeated Moria.
It is my ability. Your time's up.
We're up against your shadow.
Size and strength don't mean squat!
Don't lie!
I am assigning you to a special mission.
Settle the score yourself, Luffy!
It really is me.
"When it rains, it pours."
I'll put everything I've got
into taking him down!
Annihilate the entire Straw Hat Crew!
Yeah! Here I go!
What the heck happened to you?!
I accept your challenge!
And you're stinking strong now!
I'm going back out onto the ocean!
Third Gear!
If I die, then that shows the limit of my ability.
That will be easy.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Our Bodies Vanish! The Morning Sun
Shines on the Nightmarish Island!"
"The End of the Battle Is Nigh!
Pound in the Finishing Move!"
"Not Out of Danger Yet!
Orders to Annihilate the Straw Hat Crew!"
"The Incredible Battle
Starts! Luffy vs. Luffy!"
"It Repels Everything!
Kuma's Paw-Paw Power!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!