Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
So you're gonna join our crew now, right?
Yes! I swear that we will come back for you.
Hey, Zoro!
Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
I promised one of my comrades something.
Robin!
And then let's go on adventures
together all across the ocean!
Sanji!
He repelled Zoro's attack with his bare hand!
I must tend to that first
or I will lose face!
We're buddies!
Their bodies are vanishing!
Is that your ability?
Why?! Didn't we win?
I have the power to repel various things.
Yeah. You're talking
about Laboon, aren't you?
Laboon! We'll now go into the
Grand Line and travel around the world.
I know all about it.
Franky and Robin told me.
Dang it! Were we too late?
I am a paw man,
having eaten the Paw-Paw Fruit.
Huh? Oh, that's right.
"The Promise from a Distant Day!
The Pirates' Song and a Small Whale!"
What is that supposed to be?
But you wait for us here.
Laboon! That is the name of the whale.
Air? Is he condensing the air with his paws?
Phew! I'm very much alive.
Okay, close the gate.
Are you sure we should leave Perona?
The bubble is getting smaller!
"Bink's Booze! The Song that
Connects the Past with the Present!"
He is at a certain cape--
For a second, I thought I
was about to go to Heaven.
Listen, Brook! We met Laboon
at Twin Cape. Honest!
We can't take someone we can't find.
Sounds good to me! If we can go together,
I'd love to go to Heaven!
He's applying pressure to
Sheesh! Where in the world did she go?
a large body
of air by repelling it with his paws!
That's making it shrink!
This isn't funny, you jerks!
We seriously thought you were dead.
J-Just a moment, please!
Phew! Okay, you can stop now.
You nearly vanished!
When all of that air depressurizes,
it will generate power!
Lift your invisibility power!
I'm shocked! This is so sudden.
Oh, yeah! I forgot about something important!
Is it true? Did you actually meet Laboon?
The giant sonic blast it creates
will be like a bomb.
What is it?
I had totally forgotten about him...
Yup.
Is that right?
What's the matter?
We're free and clear!
Wh-What?!
We've got a problem!
He's doing well?
I was terrified we'd get
caught the whole time!
There he is...
A bomb?
In other words, he's making a bomb?!
I never did find out what brought
Tyrant Kuma to Thriller Bark.
You understand what I'm saying, don't you?
A... bomb?!
I have never been this happy in my life!
About that, Absalom.
The World Government is
assigning you a special mission:
Tyrant Kuma came to tell us the name
Annihilate everyone on the island,
including the Straw Hat Crew.
of the successor to the
former Warlord, Crocodile.
Hey, Brook! Your quick draw is amazing!
His successor...?
Yeah, but that's not the important part.
Please teach me how to fight with the sword.
That will be easy.
The successor is a man called Blackbeard.
His hands... are dangerous!
I will spare your lives.
He's pulled a truly nasty stunt.
Guys, get him!
"Brook's Past! A Sad Farewell
with His Cheerful Comrade!"
Yeah, you heard them!
Read that.
Let's get him!
In exchange, all you need to do is
hand over Straw Hat Luffy's head.
"Fire Fist Ace, 2nd Division Commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates...
Stop, men! You don't stand a chance!
...has been imprisoned in Impel Down"?!
Laboon...
It's well known that Ace is
one of Whitebeard's top dogs.
The government just got
their hands on a powerful card.
As long as I get his head,
the government will not complain.
"Rumbar Pirates
Musician & Swordsman"
Definitely.
Hi, everyone! I hope you're doing well.
Waterspouts?! But we had
clear skies a second ago!
Depending on how they play it,
this could completely change the Pirate Era.
"Brook
(50 years ago - Age: 38)"
It's morning!
We have to get away from here!
You want us to sell out our friend?
We've got a serious situation on our hands!
Let's start the day with a song!
Common sense is meaningless on these waters!
It's no time for Moria-sama
to be dead to the world.
Now then, give Straw Hat to me.
I see where you're coming from,
Pirate Hunter Zoro...
but I'm more interested... in finding a wife.
Forget it!
I will start with you.
Eh... This week, Power
Tune will be presenting
Okay. Bring me a corpse that turns you on.
I swear, there is no telling what
this ocean will throw at us next.
the famous song, "The Black
Handkerchief of Happiness."
I don't want a zombie!
It's killer!
"It Repels Everything!
Kuma's Paw-Paw Power!"
I wanna marry a living woman!
Yeah, but that is what makes
Everyone, feel free to join in!
the booze at the end of
the day taste so great!
White handkerchief,
What a pity.
"One Day After Defeating Moria"
In the end,
Isn't that right, Brook?
everyone slept all day in that courtyard.
don't let him find you
Please play that song for us again today.
Run for it
"The Pain of My Crewmates Is My Pain!
Zoro's Desperate Fight!"
Well, sure. We were up all the
previous night fighting like mad.
I was expecting you to say that!
White handkerchief,
Are you ready?
I'm starving, Sanji!
Yeah! Let's hear it!
Don't let the octopus catch you
Nibble on some cheese.
That's a stain
-- And now a squid is coming
--S-Stop it! Not so loud in the morning!
Cheese doesn't cut it!
Cheese doesn't energize me!
-- There is another stain
--I'll get up! I'll get up, Brook!
Hey! Stay with me!
Then start hauling the ingredients
I need to the courtyard.
-- White handkerchief
--I'm up! I'm wide awake!
Are you gonna make it?
What did that scumbag do?!
Covered in stains, you're
the black handkerchief of happiness
I'm sure the members of the Victim
Association don't want to budge.
He didn't even touch the guys
to pierce them with something!
A mirror...?
Ursus Shock!
So we're eating over there.
Is that his ability?
Oh, yeah. I'm a skeleton now.
I'm sorry about that.
Everyone is just so happy to see
the sun for the first time in years.
This is beyond cruel!
Hey, Brook. Play that one
song--ballad version.
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
After many long years under
Moria's reign in the dark forest,
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
They are crying tears
of joy while sunbathing.
That hurts! That really hurts, Captain!
Why are you hanging me up?!
Roger! That's your favorite, Captain!
Where did all of that energy come from?
we only get a moment of happiness
before another Warlord appears
Shut it! You've got nerve to
fight over something so stupid!
It's so weird! It's a mystery!
Do you have enough food?
and declares that we must die!
But Captain, his stray bullet
nearly got me killed in combat!
We have a mountain of additional food
on top of everything that was stolen.
You're alive, aren't you?!
Besides, he offered you an apology.
We're doing great.
I wonder who did that. There are
some nice people out there!
Don't nag over the past! It's unsightly!
And they even loaded your ship
with all of this treasure.
That's low, dagnabbit!
Ouch!
Even assuming it was Christmas,
this is far too generous.
That pain is proof you're still alive!
You know good and well that the
Straw Hats just finished a fierce battle!
This is bliss!
True enough!
Oh, a glass armband!
You might be too much for us,
but we have the energy to take you on!
This is cool!
I claim this!
I don't care if you're a Warlord!
The stars!
H-Hey, you know what'll happen
if you take any of the treasure...
Compared to Oars and Moria,
you don't look so big!
It's a clear, starry night.
R-Right, Nami-san?
Do you think Laboon is
looking up at these stars?
He can have it! There aren't any gems.
Shut up and get back.
Well, Captain?
Huh? Is that how this works? Cool!
It's a whale!
Hey, guys! Check this out! Brook is
getting mushy on us!
He asked for me. Didn't you hear him?
But I don't have a single
piece of treasure for you!
It's the one from yesterday...
You're still here? Go look for your pod!
We wouldn't take treasure from
the people who saved us, Namizo.
Kn-Knock that off! You're embarrassing me!
I'll accept the challenge.
I don't need backup.
Huh?
Don't make me look bad!
This is a nice knife!
It's the Navy Headquarters!
What should we do?
Isn't it adorable?
What did you just say?
Don't go chicken on me! Fight back!
I'm sorry! This is out.
It's studded with gems.
Hey, how long are you gonna follow us?
I bet your mama's worried.
Huh? It popped right out.
Wow! Look at this.
Who is Namizo?
The captain's bounty went up again.
Come to think of it, this is rather strange.
Here! Eat up, Laboon!
For some odd reason, I don't feel
like this is the first time we've met.
Oh, man! When did you name him?
Aren't I great?
Let's party!
By any chance, are you Lola?!
Yorkie! Yorkie! Let your infamy
resound clear to the Twin Cape!
Yep. Did I tell you my name?
You and your crewmates have
earned quite the reputation.
We're under attack!
So you're Lola!
I'm happy to see you again!
L-Lola...? Wh-Whoa, wait! Just a sec!
It's said that Straw Hat Luffy has
several skilled subordinates on his ship.
That boar zombie was her...?
You must be confused, huh?
I'll fill you in later.
Are you two okay?
P-Please help us! He's severely wounded!
Well, well, well! But it's true, it's true!
Anyway, take this. It's
my way of thanking you.
Captain, an injured man fell overboard!
Huh? Are you sure? You're thanking me?
This is no time for all
of you to act flattered!
Toss him a life preserver!
We'll save him later.
Nami gave away some of our treasure!
You have stirred up trouble
in various places.
It's not like I can swim...
I guess that's all I can do.
Your captain was not the only one
to make a name for himself over time.
I'm going on ahead. Is this everything?
A storm is coming!
You're a lifesaver, Laboon!
Huh? A storm? Really?
Hey, we're okay!
This is bad!
Laboon!
Hey, the captain...! Something is
wrong with Captain Yorkie!
This is the life!
What?
The light is seeping into my body.
A plague?
We're really alive.
Yeah.
Hey, Zoro! Wait! This is totally nuts!
Shhh! No, no, Laboon.
Don't wake everyone up.
Don't go in his room.
A few dozen crew members have been infected.
You're battered and bruised
clear to the bone!
Hey!
I'll sing for you when the sun rises.
They may have contracted it
in that jungle we just visited.
The world is designed so that
when it rains trouble, it pours.
We brought food!
Straw Hat!
It's an unknown virus. I can't treat it!
If you told us, we would have carried it!
If I start making excuses,
will someone come rescue us?
All right! Everyone, sing that song!
We shouldn't let our savior work!
This is a nightmare!
Is Zoro up?
If I make one false move,
everyone onboard might die!
He needs absolute rest,
so he's in the mansion.
If I die, then that shows
the limit of my ability!
Hey, wake up.
Chopper!
Two-Sword Style...
Captain!
We brought the stuff you asked for.
Captain Yorkie!
...Sword Draw...
Oh, thank you.
...Rashomon!
How is he doing?
Don't sound so sad.
I've never seen Zoro so badly hurt.
He nearly lost his life.
You'll mar the name of the Rumbar Pirates
that make crying children laugh.
Laboon, are you cold?
I think something must have happened...
I am pulling out of the Grand Line
a little ahead of you.
...while we were unconscious.
I will take this worn-out ship...
What was that?!
Indeed. I sincerely doubt
that man simply left.
now that it has become
a carrier for the virus.
Treasure! We found treasure, Laboon!
Push forward on a new ship.
And it's strange how Luffy
is bursting with energy.
We're gonna party today!
Captain...!
I have no idea what's up with that, either.
I never dreamed I would drop out like this...
To be honest, I saw what went down!
We will take our chances... and try
to escape through the Calm Belt.
I saw what happened from beginning to end!
Sea monster sighting!
What?!
I'll give you the dirt.
Hey, everything will work out!
I'll fill you in on what happened!
I'm sorry, men.
Come.
Protect Laboon!
Wait! No, wait a second!
Give my regards to Laboon.
--Hold up!
--Sanji?
Yeah!
Wipe those sniveling expressions off
your faces! Get your acts together!
Wait, why?! You were pretty cool yourself.
Look! He hasn't even done anything
and Zoro's breathing heavy!
Yes, sir!
You were like, "Instead of the
swordsman's life, take mine."
We won't go easy on anyone
who picks on Laboon!
What is that guy's ability?!
It's not good for you
guys to hang out in here.
Drop it!
What's with the mark he
keeps leaving in the debris?
Now start talking. What happened afterwards?
Yay!
Get going! Take care...
I want to know what happened
after I blacked out.
Look at the palm of his hand!
Captain Yorkie is right.
A-A paw?!
Okay...
Come along. Let's head on out, everyone.
What is that doing on a human's hand?!
Laboon!
Laboon, are you all right?
That Warlord had yet
another shocking ability.
Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
Lion Strike!
Thank goodness!
He pressed his paw against Straw Hat.
I'm so glad!
Look out!
It repelled all of the "damage"
that Straw Hat had taken!
His damage...?
It was like a bubble of agony. And then...
He repelled Zoro's attack with his bare hand!
Is that even possible?
If you want to take his place,
What... are you?!
That's not an option, Laboon.
Please hang tight and wait here.
take all of his pain and
suffering unto yourself.
Is that your ability?
It will be impossible for you to survive
when you are already on the brink of death.
Be a good boy, okay?
Brook...
Yes?
I have the power to repel various things.
You will die.
I think like he likes you best, Brook.
Have a small taste.
No kidding!
I am a paw man,
having eaten the Paw-Paw Fruit.
Are you a cyborg like Franky?
It's because Laboon loves music!
Nope! The shape of your head
makes him think you're kin.
No, you're stronger than tempered steel!
A-A p-paw man?
Huh?
I'm filled with regret!
--Huh?
--Why does that sound so peaceful?!
Even the swordsman started
screaming bloody murder
when he touched a small portion of it.
Captain Yorkie...!
Are there soothing Devil Fruits?!
I will never forget those words!
Is that right?
I hate to say it, but I
thought he was a goner.
It's hard to say whether you're
a Warlord or a Purr-lord...
Do you hear me, Captain?!
That's what makes it so touching!
I have chiseled them into my heart!
It seriously made me cry!
Maybe he's not such a big deal after all.
Take care of yourself, Captain!
I see. That explains why Luffy is
doing well while Zoro is bedridden.
We're going to travel on separate ships now,
but let's survive so we
can see everyone again!
That was rash!
You'll take off that mask...
Where did all of this blood come from?!
...and sing with everyone again!
Hey, are you still alive?!
Where is he?!
Could you try to reason with him?
What happened here?!
No...
Franky...!
Nothing happened...!
Franky!
Cyborg Franky, is that
the extent of your strength?
Hey, Brook...
We tried to talk to him,
Please see me off...
Franky, breathe!
but he wasn't willing to listen to us.
Come on! Let's tell everyone
about the Straw Hats' heroic story.
...with that song I love so much...
Breathe, Franky!
You understand, don't you?
Yeah! I'm itching to tell them!
Wait!
Franky... got blasted away from the front!
Don't be insensitive.
We aren't strong enough to
protect him from here on out.
He didn't risk his life out of
a desire to earn our gratitude.
That attack is incredible.
What would happen if they learned that
Luffy's pain hurt a friend?!
He might be repelling air.
We're on our way...
Especially Luffy!
A normal cannon wouldn't hurt Franky.
...to deliver Bink's booze
He's still a child.
That melted... steel!
It's called "Pad Cannon."
When air is repelled at the speed of light,
Just how badly are you
dying to tell everyone?!
Sail leisurely with the sea breeze
There is no way we could
take him to the Grand Line.
Sail with the waves
We can't tell them?
You're killing me!
it creates a shock wave that
can shoot through people.
The setting sun romps about
on the other side of the tide...
All that matters is that everyone is okay.
Come on! Let's go eat.
"10 Years After Leaving Twin Cape
-Florian Triangle-"
Th... Th-Th...
Please hear me out.
A cyborg...
These guys are super cool!
Now, now! The music will have to wait.
Although an accurate description,
Their captain is so lucky!
I am nothing like Cyborg Franky.
It's true that we're comrades,
but you're a whale and--
I took off my pants!
Your time is up.
The Grand Line is dangerous! Honest!
Oh, dear! That was so embarrassing!
So that explains it.
Maybe you could come if you were an adult.
Thrust Pad Cannon!
But there will be ferocious beasts unlike
anything we've seen in the West Blue!
This is so fun! Even when
I'm alone, I can have fun!
Hey, you two!
I am the government's
Hello!
Weren't you acting like you knew
what happened? What did you see?
Laboon, listen to--
45 degree angle!
Streaming Wolf-Swords!
incomplete human weapon,
known as a "Pacifista."
Look! Someone, look!
Oh, yeah! I'm all alone!
A Pacifista?
Don't ask such an insensitive question.
All that matters is that everyone is okay.
Nope. He wouldn't listen to a word I said.
He wouldn't?
I-I wanna tell them!
K-Keep that manly heroic story to yourself!
Hey, Brook! Are you gonna sleep forever?
--Zoro!
--He got repelled with his attack!
My developer is the government's
genius scientist, Dr. Vegapunk.
Wake up! We spotted an island!
Wh-What gives?
Maybe we should sing that song for a while.
It's a summer island! It has a beach!
That would have the opposite effect!
Thank you for the food!
He is the most brilliant man in the world.
Huh? What?
Uh? Ah, uh, excuse me!
It's said his scientific knowledge is
500 years ahead of the rest of mankind.
Huh? What is this?
Wait! What gives?!
Curse you...
Delish! I've never eaten
such good food before!
What's keeping you, Brook?
We can't get started without you!
Oh, here! Try this! This!
He gave you an incredible body...
and you're a power holder!
Yeah! It's been years since
we've eaten a decent meal.
He's in trouble! He can't keep this up!
Everyone is here!
What's this? It makes me so happy!
I'm glad to be alive!
I feel like hope is fading away.
It's a miracle he's fought
for as long as he has!
I cooked up a storm!
Don't let it go to waste.
What's this? How come you are alive? Why?
As it is, that behemoth Oars
nearly beat the life out of him!
As you can imagine,
my body refuses to do as I tell it.
What are you talking about?
Isn't it time you woke up?
To think I get to eat your cooking again!
This really is lip-smacking good!
Zoro, behind you! Run!
Not that I have any lips!
Are you absolutely insistent
on taking Luffy's head?
Ow...
You need to shut up and eat!
That hurt...
Zoro!
For that to have hurt, it means
this isn't a dream. It's real!
That skeleton is hilarious!
That is the most I can compromise.
That's as far as you go!
But honestly--oh, pardon me.
That was all a dream! Thank goo--
After eating until I was full
both yesterday and today,
Concasser!
Captain!
I may have gained weight!
Sanji!
He didn't repel that with his paws!
"Even though I'm a skeleton!"
I can't take it anymore!
All right. I'll give you a head.
I bet Sanji cracked your skull, you bastard!
Forget it! I know it's hard,
but avoid eye contact with him.
Skeleton, you rock!
However, instead of taking his...
How come that skeleton is able to talk?
You are not allowed to sing or play your
And he's a hoot!
...I would appreciate it if
you took my life instead!
You're a clever skeleton, you know that?
instruments until Laboon leaves our ship.
Jerk! Stay out of this!
Why are you able to move around?
Hey, it doesn't really matter!
My bounty isn't worth much yet,
--Oh, dinner!
--Wow!
Do you think Captain Yorkie made it
through the Calm Belt in one piece?
--Dinner!
--Yay!
but I was going to become the
greatest swordsman in the world!
--Dinner!
--Oh, baby!
The ocean is a mysterious place...
--Dinner!
--Come on!
--Super!
Let's carry on his will and plow forward.
This should be a fair trade.
We will head toward Laboon on this new ship!
We didn't have a toast
and it still turned into a party.
Are you truly willing to die
It's morning!
for that man when you harbor
such great ambition?
I'm up! I'm up!
Black Foot Sanji...
This is a nasty storm!
The sails are gonna get torn to shreds!
He's sleeping right through all this noise...
So that would be you.
This is nothing! Let's
sing our way through it!
Right now, it's the only way
to save my crewmates!
Sanji's kick didn't even faze him.
And here he's the toughest guy in the crew...
At long last, Brook has
gotten a bounty on his head!
What's going on here?!
My ambition means nothing if
I can't protect my own captain.
Why is he so hard?!
Is his face made out of iron?
Laboon...
Luffy will become the King of the Pirates!
F-Firebird Star!
King of Snipers...
Hey, Chopper! Look!
What a presumptuous title.
--Luffy!
--This is for Zoro.
Huh?
Now drink away!
Don't give it to him!
Why not?! This will fix Zoro
right up, since it's his favorite.
The sails are about to rip, Captain!
What type of treatment is that?!
The rudder isn't responding!
That won't work? Then how about meat?
Wait! Wait, you stinking idiot!
Keep the rudder steady! Pull up the sails!
Okay, okay. I'll gladly accept
your sentiment alone.
We'll ride the storm!
The entrance to the Grand Line
awaits us on the other side!
But only your sentiment!
What good will come from your death?
What happened to your ambition, stupid?
There was a piano in this room?
Captain, there's light! Light dead ahead!
Why, you...!
Look! The guiding light points
to the Grand Line's entrance.
Hey, why'd you stop?
Keep the music going, Brook!
Hey, Colossus!
Whoa!
You heard him! I was dancing
with chopsticks up my nose!
This is too much for them!
They don't stand a chance.
Instead of taking that moss head
swordsman's life, take mine!
Sweet!
Yay!
Hey, I thought you only played the violin.
Please wait a moment.
Captain, it's time!
They're gonna get killed!
The Marines still don't think much of me,
Let's see...
Does anyone see Laboon?
but before long, I'll be the most
dangerous member of this crew.
--Awesome!
--That's how your head works?!
I can play most instruments.
No, I haven't seen hide
nor hair of him for a week.
Really? You're pretty good.
A long time ago, I bought this from a
merchant ship. It's called a "Tone Dial."
I'm Black Foot Sanji!
I feel bad for him, but
it was for his own good.
Um, I'd like to touch on
an earlier conversation.
Zoro! Sanji!
Why, that--!
With any luck, he can return to his pod.
To be honest, I also saw what happened.
It's an unusual shell that records sounds
and allows you to play them back.
Oh, it's from the sky island!
I was greatly moved by what you two did.
Men, are you mentally ready for this?
You've heard of it?
Yeah! We're ready when you are!
When I see Laboon, I want
him to listen to this.
Isn't it wonderful to have comrades?
Let's go to the greatest ocean in the world!
I keep it close to my heart at all times.
Don't include me in that.
I merely made a fool of myself.
But since I'm a skeleton,
I don't have a heart!
Yeah!
No, you bore the same resolve.
Have you recorded something onto it?
It's a song.
Would you like to pick a song?
I'll take a request.
It contains my crewmates singing
when they were still alive.
Yeah? I can request anything?
It's our message to Laboon:
We were happy and cheerful
In that case...
when we finished our journey.
And then...
May I play it for you now?
Oh, I wanna hear it! I bet Laboon'll love it!
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho...
Without further ado.
--Wait, didn't you just ask for a request?!
-- Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho...
How many people... are still alive?
I am Crocus, the lighthouse keeper.
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho
Congratulations on crossing Reverse Mountain.
We might be alive, but it doesn't
look like we'll pull through this.
Welcome to the Pirates' Graveyard.
We're on our way...
Oh, ouch! Don't jinx us, man!
...to deliver Bink's booze
So this is what it means to get wiped out...
Sail leisurely with the sea breeze
Sail with the waves
I'm the captain of the
Rumbar Pirates, Yorkie.
They laced their weapons with poison...
Now kill me!
The setting sun romps about
on the other side of the tide
In the West Blue, I've made a bit of a
reputation for myself as "Calico" Yorkie.
And we've lost the doc.
Don't take his life, take mine...
I'm a pirate. I've always
been prepared to die...
A ring of birds in the sky sing
Sorry, Crocus-san, but our ship
took a pretty bad beating...
As I feared, I will not derive
pleasure from killing you
Bid farewell to the port
of the weaving village
You're welcome to stay as long as you like,
My one regret is...
but provide my meals while you're here!
As we set sail, we
shall sing heartily
Laboon...!
while you are in this weakened state.
Dang! You want to sponge
off a bunch of pirates?
I've always been prepared to
sacrifice myself for the others.
The government ordered me
to annihilate everyone, but...
Brook, does your Revive-Revive Fruit work?
Silver and gold waves
turn into ocean spray
Okay, cool! Please celebrate with us.
This is where I'll die gloriously!
I'm not sure. I've never died before.
We're going to throw a party today!
We are off, bound for
the ends of the ocean
I know. If we're going to die anyway,
let's enjoy the experience.
"Bink's Booze." I thought
I recognized the song.
By the way, is the whale
that came with you a pet?
Hey, please give...
This takes me back.
Would you care to sing?
...my regards to the others.
Geh!!
If the power of the Revive-Revive Fruit
truly does bring me back to life,
What is that supposed to be?
Air? Is he condensing the air with his paws?
Laboon!
Sorry, but you'll have to
search for another cook.
The bubble is getting smaller!
I will take this to Laboon! I swear it!
Laboon!
A Tone Dial...
We will record the song that Laboon,
You came with us? That was--
the captain, and all of us loved so dearly!
Brook!
Laboon is waiting at that cape under
the belief that we'll return
today or tomorrow...
I will take it to him!
Y-You jerk!
Laboon, thank you! This
is great! I'm so happy!
That sounds great!
Whee! Yahoo! Keep it going!
Yeah! Guys, don't keel over
before the song is done.
You're injured?! I can't believe
you braved those stormy waters!
Let's give Laboon...
He's applying pressure to a large body
of air by repelling it with his paws!
Hey, Brook! I know this song.
That was nuts, Laboon!
...the Rumbar Pirate's
choral number of a lifetime!
Shanks and the guys used to sing it.
That's making it shrink!
Hey, Brook! Let's sing that song.
When all of that air depressurizes,
it will generate power!
Captain, you sure love that song.
You bet! It's perfect for pirates!
Yeah. A long time ago,
all of the pirates would sing this.
The giant sonic blast it
creates will be like a bomb.
Laboon, you like it too, don't you?
They sang it in good times and bad.
Wh-What?!
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho...
So you're gonna join our crew now, right?
Huh? I can sing along with this song!
A bomb?
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho
I'm begging you!
In other words, he's making a bomb?!
After all, you've got your shadow back!
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho...
You can hit the seas without
fear of the sun, right?
A... bomb?!
About that. There was one thing
I neglected to tell you.
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho
What is it?
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho...
"Bink's Booze"
I promised one of my comrades something.
We're on our way...
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho
I must tend to that first
or I will lose face!
...to deliver Bink's booze
Sail leisurely with the sea breeze
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho...
Sail with the waves
The setting sun romps about
on the other side of the tide
Yeah. You're talking
about Laboon, aren't you?
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho
I know all about it.
Franky and Robin told me.
-- A ring of birds in the sky sing
--Crocus-san, would you like to make a request?
If I harm Straw Hat now,
I will only bring shame upon myself.
Huh? Oh, that's right.
Brook, you can play anything, can't you?
Bid farewell to the port
of the weaving village
We're on our way...
Laboon!
...to deliver Bink's booze
That is the name of the whale.
I am in your debt.
-- As we set sail, we shall sing heartily
--Pirates love to sing!
Sail leisurely with the sea breeze
Sail with the waves
Silver and gold waves
turn into ocean spray
He is at a certain cape--
The setting sun romps about
on the other side of the tide
Listen, Brook! We met Laboon
at Twin Cape. Honest!
Trust me not to bring him harm.
I am a man of my word.
We are off, bound for
the ends of the ocean
A ring of birds in the sky sing
I will spare your lives.
In exchange, I will...
I already knew that Laboon
Bid farewell to the port
of the weaving village
had been waiting there for his friends
to return for the past fifty years.
In exchange, all you need to do is
hand over Straw Hat Luffy's head.
As we set sail, we
shall sing heartily
...show you hell.
Skeleton, what's wrong?
The tempo is getting slow.
Silver and gold waves
turn into ocean spray
Please understand. You can't
repeat what you did last time.
We are off, bound for
the ends of the ocean
The Grand Line is too dangerous.
I'm afraid that you are simply
too small to take with us!
What I just repelled from his
body was pain... and fatigue.
This is the symbol of
our promise to fight again.
Listen to me.
We have no idea what to
expect from here on out.
Until we come back, don't remove that
mark by hitting your head. Got that?!
This is all of the damage that he
accumulated in his battle with Moria.
As long as I get his head,
the government will not complain.
Now what do you think everyone would do
If you want to take his place,
We're on our way...
if harm should come your way?
take all of his pain and
suffering unto yourself.
...to deliver Bink's booze
All right!
We are pirates, sailing
across the seas
We wouldn't hesitate to save you.
It will be impossible for
you to survive when you are
We'd try, even if that spelled
the end of the Rumbar Pirates!
The waves are my pillow,
the ship my lodge
already on the brink of death.
See ya, whale! I'm leaving now!
You will die.
A skull flies proud
on our sails and flags
Have a small taste.
Please understand! I'm begging you.
A storm has hit a distant village
You want us to sell out our friend?
I don't want to leave you, either.
Boy, was I ever surprised when I learned
that you're the surviving member
The waves are dancing
Sound the drums
You don't know how hard
it was for me last time!
If the cowardly wind blows, that's it
of the band of pirates he's been waiting for.
But... But...!
There won't be a sunrise
tomorrow morning
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho...
And you still remember your promise to him.
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho
We aren't leaving him.
I bet Laboon would be thrilled if he knew!
Captain!
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho...
Laboon! Wait for us!
J-Just a moment, please!
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho
We're going to travel straight--
just straight--across this ocean!
Well?
We're on our way...
I'm shocked! This is so sudden.
Now then, give Straw Hat to me.
And you know what, Laboon?
Let me... do this somewhere else!
...to deliver Bink's booze
Is it true? Did you actually meet Laboon?
Amazingly enough, our ship will return
to the other side of the Red Line.
Either today or tomorrow,
I'll be lost in a dream
Yup.
Forget it!!
Even though fifty years have passed?
Never again will I meet...
We'll cross the wall again
and return to this cape.
...the hand that waves
Laboon is still waiting for us at that cape?
But why brood over it?
There will be another
moonlit night tomorrow
Please wait for us!
Are you telling the truth?!
We're on our way...
You just have to hang tight
for two or three years.
Yup!
...to deliver Bink's booze
We also bore witness.
We saw him with our own eyes.
Then you'll get to see everyone again!
As we sail on the seas,
we shall sing heartily
Yeah!
Captain!
What a pity.
Was he well?
Everyone turns into
bones someday anyway
Isn't that right, Brook?
Sure was!
Yes! I swear that we will come back for you.
He was as big as a mountain.
Life is a silly story
without an ending or direction
I'd love to see him!
When we left him, the cutie
was about the size of a boat.
By then, you should be big and strong.
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho...
He had a stubborn streak, but he loved music.
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho
--Later!
--See ya, Laboon!
He was a good boy...
Take care!
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho...
Laboon, let's go on adventures
together all across the ocean!
Even now, I can still...
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho
...picture him...
He has good companions.
We're buddies!
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho...
I should have expected no less
from your son, Dragon.
Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho
--Thank you!
--Goodbye!
--Laboon!
Where is everyone?
This has turned into a quartet.
I'm so glad you understand!
Is that right?
Hey, is everyone still alive?!
Thank you, Laboon!
He's doing well?
A trio...
Ursus Shock!
That Kuma guy must have thought we died
A duet!
in the blast and left! So much for that!
Ow, ow, ow...
Hey, man! You've gotta be joking.
I have never been this happy in my life!
What's gotten into you?
Laboon! We'll now go into the
Grand Line and travel around the world.
A solo!
Hey, look! My body feels light. Why is that?
But you wait for us here.
Don't lie! That can't be true.
Where did that whale come from?
It's following our ship.
Perhaps he has taken so much
damage that it's given him a high.
What is this? Why is the
accompaniment the last to go?
It must have gotten separated from its pod.
Yeah, right! I don't buy it!
The poor thing. The ocean is a big place!
If you want to join my crew,
you must have a love of music!
But it's true!
It looks sad. Well, it's still just a calf.
And I'm sayin' that's not possible!
Yahoo!
Raise the sail of the Rumbar Pirates
that make crying children laugh!
It's too hard to believe!
Captain Yorkie, why don't we play a song?
I'm light! Light!
Laboon, I swear that we will come back!
Great idea, Brook! Hey, everyone!
Grab your instruments.
"Three Years Later"
Okay!
Please be here waiting for us!
"Florian Triangle"
Let's show him what the
Rumbar Pirates that make
crying children laugh are made of!
Sounds good!
One, two, three, four!
There is no way everyone pulled through okay!
Where is that jerk?!
There he is.
Phew, you scared me!
Laboon, if you have been waiting
there for the past fifty years...
Hey, where did that Warlord go?
...could you give me just
another year or two?
Where did all of this blood come from?!
Hey, are you still alive?!
Where is he?!
What happened here?!
I take pride in being a pirate!
No...
If you are facing the wall, I want to greet
you from the front, just like I promised!
Nothing happened...!
Stay out of this, Moss Head!
I'm taking Kuma down!
I've never seen Zoro this
severely injured before.
Laboon, you are our dear comrade!
I am the dead and skeletonized Brook.
I will deliver this. I swear it!
It holds the song that Laboon,
the captain, and the rest of us loved!
That's why we can't take you with us.
What could have happened?
No, you're staying out of this!
I am a wanted man!
I saw what went down!
The Grand Line is so dangerous,
we want you to wait here.
You jerk... Why did you...?
I promised my crewmates
that I would take it to him.
I have a bounty for 33 million Berries.
Isn't it wonderful to have comrades?
We will swing around the Grand Line.
As of today, my life belongs to you,
Captain Straw Hat Luffy!
You're the cook.
It has the choral number of a lifetime
I swear we will come back
to this cape to see you again!
I must fulfill the promise I
made to my dear comrades!
It's the warrior's job to
risk his life in combat.
performed by the Rumbar Pirates,
who make crying children laugh!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Pain of My Crewmates Is My Pain!
Zoro's Desperate Fight!"
"A New Crewmate!
The Musician, Humming Brook!"
"Brook's Past! A Sad Farewell
with His Cheerful Comrade!"
"The Promise from a Distant Day!
The Pirates' Song and a Small Whale!"
"Bink's Booze! The Song that
Connects the Past with the Present!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!