Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Yes! I swear that we will come back for you.
And then let's go on adventures
together all across the ocean!
We're buddies!
Laboon! We'll now go into the
Grand Line and travel around the world.
But you wait for us here.
"Bink's Booze! The Song that
Connects the Past with the Present!"
Hey, Brook! Your quick draw is amazing!
Please teach me how to fight with the sword.
Waterspouts?! But we had
clear skies a second ago!
We have to get away from here!
Common sense is meaningless on these waters!
I swear, there is no telling what
this ocean will throw at us next.
It's killer!
Yeah, but that is what makes
the booze at the end of
the day taste so great!
Isn't that right, Brook?
Please play that song for us again today.
I was expecting you to say that!
Are you ready?
Yeah! Let's hear it!
A mirror...?
Oh, yeah. I'm a skeleton now.
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
That hurts! That really hurts, Captain!
Why are you hanging me up?!
Shut it! You've got nerve to
fight over something so stupid!
But Captain, his stray bullet
nearly got me killed in combat!
You're alive, aren't you?!
Besides, he offered you an apology.
Don't nag over the past! It's unsightly!
Ouch!
That pain is proof you're still alive!
True enough!
The stars!
It's a clear, starry night.
Do you think Laboon is
looking up at these stars?
Well, Captain?
Hey, guys! Check this out! Brook is
getting mushy on us!
Kn-Knock that off! You're embarrassing me!
It's the Navy Headquarters!
What should we do?
Don't go chicken on me! Fight back!
Wow! Look at this.
The captain's bounty went up again.
Aren't I great?
Let's party!
Yorkie! Yorkie! Let your infamy
resound clear to the Twin Cape!
This is bad!
Hey, the captain...! Something is
wrong with Captain Yorkie!
What?
A plague?
Yeah.
Don't go in his room.
A few dozen crew members have been infected.
They may have contracted it
in that jungle we just visited.
It's an unknown virus. I can't treat it!
This is a nightmare!
If I make one false move,
everyone onboard might die!
Captain!
Captain Yorkie!
Don't sound so sad.
You'll mar the name of the Rumbar Pirates
that make crying children laugh.
I am pulling out of the Grand Line
a little ahead of you.
I will take this worn-out ship...
now that it has become
a carrier for the virus.
Push forward on a new ship.
Captain...!
I never dreamed I would drop out like this...
We will take our chances... and try
to escape through the Calm Belt.
Hey, everything will work out!
I'm sorry, men.
Give my regards to Laboon.
Wipe those sniveling expressions off
your faces! Get your acts together!
Yes, sir!
It's not good for you
guys to hang out in here.
Get going! Take care...
Captain Yorkie is right.
Come along. Let's head on out, everyone.
Brook...
Yes?
I'm filled with regret!
Captain Yorkie...!
I will never forget those words!
Do you hear me, Captain?!
I have chiseled them into my heart!
Take care of yourself, Captain!
We're going to travel on separate ships now,
but let's survive so we
can see everyone again!
You'll take off that mask...
...and sing with everyone again!
Hey, Brook...
Please see me off...
...with that song I love so much...
♪ We're on our way... ♪
♪ ...to deliver Bink's booze ♪
♪ Sail leisurely with the sea breeze ♪
♪ Sail with the waves ♪
♪ The setting sun romps about
on the other side of the tide... ♪
"10 Years After Leaving Twin Cape
-Florian Triangle-"
I took off my pants!
Oh, dear! That was so embarrassing!
This is so fun! Even when
I'm alone, I can have fun!
Hello!
45 degree angle!
Look! Someone, look!
Oh, yeah! I'm all alone!
Hey, Brook! Are you gonna sleep forever?
Wake up! We spotted an island!
It's a summer island! It has a beach!
Huh? What?
Uh? Ah, uh, excuse me!
Huh? What is this?
Wait! What gives?!
What's keeping you, Brook?
We can't get started without you!
Everyone is here!
What's this? It makes me so happy!
What's this? How come you are alive? Why?
What are you talking about?
Isn't it time you woke up?
Ow...
That hurt...
For that to have hurt, it means
this isn't a dream. It's real!
That was all a dream! Thank goo--
Do you think Captain Yorkie made it
through the Calm Belt in one piece?
The ocean is a mysterious place...
Let's carry on his will and plow forward.
We will head toward Laboon on this new ship!
It's morning!
I'm up! I'm up!
This is a nasty storm!
The sails are gonna get torn to shreds!
This is nothing! Let's
sing our way through it!
At long last, Brook has
gotten a bounty on his head!
Hey, why'd you stop?
Keep the music going, Brook!
You heard him! I was dancing
with chopsticks up my nose!
Please wait a moment.
Let's see...
--Awesome!
--That's how your head works?!
A long time ago, I bought this from a
merchant ship. It's called a "Tone Dial."
It's an unusual shell that records sounds
and allows you to play them back.
Oh, it's from the sky island!
You've heard of it?
When I see Laboon, I want
him to listen to this.
I keep it close to my heart at all times.
But since I'm a skeleton,
I don't have a heart!
Have you recorded something onto it?
It's a song.
It contains my crewmates singing
when they were still alive.
It's our message to Laboon:
We were happy and cheerful
when we finished our journey.
May I play it for you now?
Oh, I wanna hear it! I bet Laboon'll love it!
Without further ado.
How many people... are still alive?
We might be alive, but it doesn't
look like we'll pull through this.
So this is what it means to get wiped out...
They laced their weapons with poison...
And we've lost the doc.
I'm a pirate. I've always
been prepared to die...
My one regret is...
Laboon...!
Brook, does your Revive-Revive Fruit work?
I'm not sure. I've never died before.
I know. If we're going to die anyway,
let's enjoy the experience.
Would you care to sing?
If the power of the Revive-Revive Fruit
truly does bring me back to life,
I will take this to Laboon! I swear it!
A Tone Dial...
We will record the song that Laboon,
the captain, and all of us loved so dearly!
Laboon is waiting at that cape under
the belief that we'll return
today or tomorrow...
I will take it to him!
That sounds great!
Yeah! Guys, don't keel over
before the song is done.
Let's give Laboon...
...the Rumbar Pirate's
choral number of a lifetime!
Huh? I can sing along with this song!
♪ Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho... ♪
"Bink's Booze"
♪ Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho ♪
♪ Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho... ♪
♪ We're on our way... ♪
♪ ...to deliver Bink's booze ♪
♪ Sail leisurely with the sea breeze ♪
♪ Sail with the waves ♪
♪ The setting sun romps about
on the other side of the tide ♪
♪ A ring of birds in the sky sing ♪
♪ Bid farewell to the port
of the weaving village ♪
♪ As we set sail, we
shall sing heartily ♪
♪ Silver and gold waves
turn into ocean spray ♪
♪ We are off, bound for
the ends of the ocean ♪
♪ We're on our way... ♪
♪ ...to deliver Bink's booze ♪
♪ We are pirates, sailing
across the seas ♪
♪ The waves are my pillow,
the ship my lodge ♪
♪ A skull flies proud
on our sails and flags ♪
♪ A storm has hit a distant village ♪
♪ The waves are dancing ♪
♪ Sound the drums ♪
♪ If the cowardly wind blows, that's it ♪
♪ There won't be a sunrise
tomorrow morning ♪
♪ Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho... ♪
♪ Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho ♪
♪ We're on our way... ♪
♪ ...to deliver Bink's booze ♪
♪ Either today or tomorrow,
I'll be lost in a dream ♪
♪ Never again will I meet... ♪
♪ ...the hand that waves ♪
♪ But why brood over it? ♪
♪ There will be another
moonlit night tomorrow ♪
♪ We're on our way... ♪
♪ ...to deliver Bink's booze ♪
♪ As we sail on the seas,
we shall sing heartily ♪
♪ Everyone turns into
bones someday anyway ♪
♪ Life is a silly story
without an ending or direction ♪
♪ Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho... ♪
♪ Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho ♪
Where is everyone?
This has turned into a quartet.
A trio...
A duet!
A solo!
What is this? Why is the
accompaniment the last to go?
If you want to join my crew,
you must have a love of music!
Raise the sail of the Rumbar Pirates
that make crying children laugh!
Laboon, I swear that we will come back!
Please be here waiting for us!
Laboon, if you have been waiting
there for the past fifty years...
...could you give me just
another year or two?
I take pride in being a pirate!
If you are facing the wall, I want to greet
you from the front, just like I promised!
I am the dead and skeletonized Brook.
I am a wanted man!
I have a bounty for 33 million Berries.
As of today, my life belongs to you,
Captain Straw Hat Luffy!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A New Crewmate!
The Musician, Humming Brook!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!