Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
On the voyage to their next destination,
Wealth, fame, power...
"Hot Water"
Luffy and crew drop by
the resort ship, Spa Island.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
While enjoying their vacation,
they meet the sisters Sayo and Rina.
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
The words he uttered just before his death
--Catch!
--That was too high!
This is the ocean raccoon dog, Nukki.
Here I go!
drove people around the world to the seas.
drove people around
the world to the seas.
I'd like a Rainbow Rock.
Big Sis Sayo!
I'll get right on it.
My treasure?
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Yeah, I'd like to give it a shot.
If you want it, you can have it!
You're doomed now that
I've run into you, Straw Hat!
This is awesome!
Find it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
I left everything
It's hard to believe this resort was
just outside the Florian Triangle.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
Gum-Gum Bazooka!
I know!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I am honored that you
are enjoying yourselves.
Spa Island has twelve heated pools.
It's about that notebook.
Laboon, I swear that we will come back!
Foxy and his goons are after it, aren't they?
--You're lovely!
--There are three lazy rivers...
Hold Land of Marie Jois
Incoming!
This notebook explains how to create jewels!
Isn't it a quiet night?
...and a pool dedicated to diving.
Please be here waiting for us!
I'm on watch, but it's
been calm all night long.
Everyone, please help--
We also have waterfalls for
meditation and fifty baths,
Bartholomew Kuma-sama has returned!
Luffy and crew managed
to repel the Foxy Crew,
There is no need to man the helm.
including a cola bath and a milk bath.
which was after the sisters' notebook.
"Milk Bath"
"Women" "Men"
I'm working myself to the bone for nothing.
Furthermore, we have water ping pong
It held the secret to their father's
research on making jewels.
Never mind that I'm all bones!
and a floating casino for those
who would like to play games.
Laboon, if you have been waiting
there for the past fifty years,
But now Sayo has been taken hostage
by the mastermind, Doran!
Don't be ridiculous!
You can enjoy exquisite cuisine prepared
by master chefs at several restaurants.
Bartholomew Kuma, you're telling
me they escaped your powers?
I'm so bored.
Laboon...
Give me a better excuse than that!
could you give me just another year or two?
As your host, nothing could make me happier
"The Great Scramble for Treasure!
Collapse! Spa Island!"
You know Luffy-san and his buddies?
I've joined their crew.
I'm the one who has to
report this to the top!
than to melt away the fatigue
from your long voyage.
Big Sis Sayo!
Some lucky visitors may even get to
see a circular rainbow and candy rain.
That's my grandson for you!
I take pride in being a pirate!
Quiet, Garp!
They are great people.
Dang! This ship is loaded with traps.
You were assigned a special government
mission to eliminate them all,
If you are facing the wall,
Oh, aren't circular rainbows
But they are more than just that.
yet you couldn't even bring back the
head of Luffy of the Straw Hats?
a rare natural phenomenon
called the "ocean's treasure"?
I want to greet you from the
front, just like I promised!
I found something incredible
earlier this afternoon!
You're a disgrace!
But I've heard there hasn't
been a sighting in years.
Boss, hang in there!
Don't worry, Sengoku.
As I said, "some lucky
visitors" may see them.
"A New Crewmate!
The Musician, Humming Brook!"
Luffy isn't the sort of man who'd go around
telling the world that he defeated Moria.
That was pathetic, "Silver Fox" Foxy.
It told of Luffy-san and his crew's fearsome
adventures and their battle-filled days.
Is something the matter?
They won despite your trickery.
We might see some candy rain in just a bit.
Hey, skeleton!
Oh, well. Now I simply have to wait for
them to solve the secret of the jewels.
Eh?!
Now that I have joined them,
Are you done singing?
Kuma, you didn't take pity on those pirates
because they were injured, did you?
Surely you jest!
Sing another song! Just one more!
I must prove that I am worthy
to call myself a crewmate!
I'm sure it must be difficult
to run a resort on these waters.
Wouldn't you agree, Laboon?
Even if you let them escape,
we will not stop pursuing them!
My crewmates and I poured
our lives into this song.
This just isn't enough to go by!
Since our opening, we've earned
10 billion Berries a year.
They're following the Log toward
the Navy Headquarters as we speak!
Good morning, everyone!
Didn't you search all over the ship?
Wasn't there a large "X" mark?
I'll wake you up with a song.
We're endorsed by the World Government,
so we haven't run into any problems.
It is the Rumbar Pirates'
"Great Choral Number."
-- White handkerchief,
--Shut up!
No... What should I do?
Our security is rock solid.
I listened to this countless
times while wandering
-- don't let him find you
--The sun hasn't risen yet!
I'm confident that our
-- Run for it
--Let me catch some more Z's!
This notebook really is full of lies.
Oh, that's right!
Tea
regular guests have nothing to
fear as they kick back and relax.
I brought fresh tea leaves!
-- White handkerchief...
--Forget Brook. Someone make
Luffy stop snoring!
the dark, dark foggy seas
by myself for 50 years.
And now my sister is...
Bring some rice crackers!
--Ha! Hi-ho! Hi-hi!
--Heehaw! Heehaw!
10 billion Berries a year?!
Damn it, Garp, shut up!
Naturally, that applies to pirates as well.
"Brook's Great Struggle! Is the Path
to Becoming a True Comrade Rigorous?"
--Luffy!
--Huh?
When I was all alone on that large ship,
Thanks for your hospitality.
"Halfway Across the Grand Line!
Arrival at the Red Line!"
I'm sorry if that spoiled your mood.
Please save... Big Sis Sayo.
As long as you're a paying customer,
this song was the only thing
that helped me feel alive.
Sure.
What's the plan, Navigator?
I don't care if you're a pirate or
part of the Revolutionary Army.
Huh? You're sure? Really?
If we use the paddle, we could keep
moving through these calm waters.
Yeah, I wanna see those jewels.
What the heck is going on?
Based on the weather,
this lull should only last today.
But now that I bear new
determination in my heart,
You two are rather similar.
Even though this notebook could be lying?
It's hopeless.
10 billion Berries! Berry, Berry, Berry!
Then we don't need to use our precious cola.
But how are we going to save her, Luffy?
today I shall seal this Tone Dial.
Let's see... Why don't we destroy this ship?
Oh, dear...
This is good!
Sanji, your cooking really is the best!
Whaaat?!
"The Slow-Slow Menace!
'Silver Fox' Foxy Returns!"
We're not catching a thing.
What?!
Where did that come from?!
This is weird.
Robin-chan, have a second
helping of the seafood salad.
Times are tough...
Hey, man! Are you thinking straight?
Thank you.
Man, this is boring!
What about Sayo?
We'll find her if we destroy the ship.
It's sealed!
Now, let's be patient.
And the hint about the jewels?
What's gotten into you, Brook?
Ready, go!
It'll be easier to look for if we destroy the ship!
Why have you been so hyper all morning?
Your head really is a storage unit?!
Boo-yah!
Did something exciting happen, Brook?
--Whoopee!
--Yeah!
Hey, Nami!
Let's get started.
Zoro?
He said that he saw our ship's log
while he was on watch yesterday.
Aren't we at Fishman Island yet? Huh? Huh?
There is no point worrying about something
I learned that Laboon is
happily waiting for me!
that might not be on this ship, anyway.
Right! I just so happened
to read a small portion of it.
I have my shadow back!
Oh, give it a rest! I'm
sure we're getting close!
I swear, you guys don't
have a shred of delicacy!
I'm out of the Devil's Sea!
To be honest, it left me astonished!
Fishman... Mermaids!
Nami-san, the idea of meekly obeying
The voices we recorded on this dial no
I haven't been able to
settle down ever since.
that dastardly mustache irks me to no end.
The incident at Thriller Bark was
only the tip of the iceberg for you!
longer exist to help me recall the past.
I don't care if we sink this ship.
Oh, beautiful mermaid!
You stopped a civil war in
the desert kingdom, Alabasta.
I am supposed to take this song to Laboon!
Where is the mermaid I have dreamed of?!
Gah! Not you too, Robin!
You had a grand adventure
on the legendary sky island!
Isn't someone going to stop them?
Every single day was filled with pain.
Huh? What are those things?
Those were the Captain's orders.
Furthermore, you took on
the World Government in a
To be honest, I couldn't see a ray of light.
Gah! I'm sick of this!
Oh, you're quick on the uptake!
massive fight at Water Seven!
Sanji! I need food!
Franky!
I was so surprised, I
nearly had a heart attack!
Please look after Sunny.
Candy! It's raining candy!
You've got it.
Oh, but I don't have a heart.
Candy ball raindrops!
And they're only raining here.
But you know, Luffy-san...
Super!
Is that...
Talk about lucky!
There goes the resort...
Incredible! A huge school of fish!
We're super lucky! Lucky!
Yeah. I wonder what sort of stories
will get added to the log.
All right! Destroy this ship!
I-I...
108-Pound Phoenix!
Brook, your name is going to
start appearing in it now, too.
Candy too heavy!
You see? With some patience,
everything works out!
Concasser!
Stupid!
I'm glad to be alive!
About that! Now that I am your crewmate,
Fish 'em all up!
Gum-Gum Whip!
They're coming this way!
it is imperative that I make myself useful!
I get why you're eager to work hard,
Want to try it too, Nami?
I am truly glad to be alive!
but first let me give you a word of advice.
What is it?
Tabasco Star!
Something isn't right.
I'd love to hear it, Nami-san!
Huh?
Of course you are!
With this crew, never let your
guard down during a meal.
Hoofprint Roseo!
And it's all because of today!
You guys are so stupid!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Hey, wait up, fish!
Got it! I, Quick Draw Brook, shall be
ready for the enemy to strike at any time!
Clutch!
Huh?
Three-Pace Hum... Notch Slash!
That's...
What is that?
Apparently we didn't warn you soon enough.
Everyone is strong!
Ah!
This is the ocean raccoon dog, Nukki.
I claim those noodles!
Give Sayo back!
May I join your crew?
He can transform into anything!
P-Please wait a second! Luffy-san!
This is...
Yeah, sure.
What?! That was quick!
They're good!
What is that obviously
foreboding look on your face?
Outta my way! Move! Move! Move!
I should not have let my guard down,
even for a moment.
Wow, awesome!
He joined!
Very well! I shall work
myself to the bone to become
Eh?!
Like those puny bullets can hurt me.
Wh-What?!
But we're glad to have you!
a true pal as soon as possible!
He repelled the bullets?
Hurray for the musician!
He said that this girl is called Rina.
But I'm already nothing but bones...
The musician died and now
he's nothing but bones!
The raccoon dog talked!
I'm not a raccoon dog! I'm a reindeer!
Owie!
Serpent Currents!
Sanji-san!
Jerks! Now I'm ticked!
I've been wanting a musician!
Serpent Currents?
Eh?
I appreciate it. Since
you're washing the dishes,
Everyone, be careful!
Weapons Left!
The musician is extremely light!
"Eh?" Be nice!
I can take my time with Nami-san's tea.
And that is one of your charms!
Are you hungry?
Hey! Come on and give Sayo back!
As your pal, I am dying to help
everyone in extravagant ways,
It's one of your charms!
Yeah...
Yep! I'm as light as bones!
Want my lunch? But it's not a pirate lunch.
Curse you!
but I'll do anything to make
myself useful for the time being.
--I'm as light as bones! I'm as light as bones!
--He's hilarious!
Huh? You're pirates?
Honest?
--I'm as light as bones! I'm as light as bones!
--I get it already!
It's almost like they're alive...
That's a great attitude.
Our ship is going to grow even livelier.
I'm Luffy, the man who will
become King of the Pirates!
Since I'm a skeleton, I should work
till I'm bone tired on the small stuff.
This looks a little dicey.
Why do we always attract such a quirky crowd?
I'm the ship doctor, Chopper!
I'm Captain Usopp, the sniper.
Well, I'm going to give Nami-san her tea.
I'm not sure what happened,
but you guys seem happy, Namizo.
Ah! Sanji-san, where do these go?
Wow! I didn't know there were
funny pirates like you guys.
Well, this is quite...
Yep! Thank you.
Cool!
Oh, over in the...
We don't know what the deal is, but...
Cheers!
What is that?!
We're totally lost, but...
Thank you! Now to chow do--
Sanji-kun!
Cheers!
Don't drop them, even if it kills you!
Is that a cannon?! I thought it was a chimney!
Leave it to me, Nami-san!
Huh? What's wrong?
But I'm already dead!
45 degree angle!
I forgot about my big sister.
--And "kaboom!"
--Don't say that!
It won't budge!
What the heck?
Your sister?
Hold this!
Big Sis Sayo!
Splendid!
Don't give me that!
I can't trust you to do the dishes!
Oh, then I'll take this
tea to Nami-san instead.
Laboon...
Wait! Wait! I was gonna take it to her!
Weapons...
Left!
Nami-san, I've brought you some tea.
You're eating up a storm!
I will not pull back.
Big Sis!
Come in!
This guy will eat anything.
Hey! What are you doing?!
Rina!
May I see your panties?
Steer the ship!
We have always looked
straight ahead in our voyage.
Ocean raccoon dogs are omnivores.
Damn it! He's taken her hostage.
Shut up!
Think he'll eat this?
--Bam!
--That came out of nowhere!
That was the path that
would take us back to you.
In these waves, it won't
do what I tell it to!
Of course not!
How dare you wreak havoc on my ship?!
Is that a nautical chart?
As I travel around the world,
you're waiting at the goal!
We've been pretty busy lately.
Gum-Gum...
This is a great chance to work on it,
since the ship isn't going anywhere.
Do you realize how much
it cost to build Spa Island?
What is that?!
Isn't that right?
Pistol!
What?! He can transform into anything?
That is why I will not pull back.
Isn't it your dream to
draw a map of the world?
I swear that I will go to you.
Pretty much.
Please wait for me!
Right. I want to navigate
across the oceans of the world
A babe! Please transform
into the hottest babe ever!
Wait just a little longer...
and make a world map based on what I've seen.
That's wonderful!
If there is anything
I could do to help, please let me know.
Oh, would you like another cup?
Are you all right?
Thank you.
Yeah! You saved us!
Ah, if only I was better with words!
That sentiment is enough for now.
Huh?
Serpent Currents...
You are both beautiful and humble!
Nami-san, you truly are wonderful!
Damn that rotten mustached jerk!
Transform into Nami-san!
Please turn into Nami-san!
They certainly do move like serpents.
Sayo!
They're very aptly named!
Really! I'm not that great.
What's the matter, Laboon?
Big Sis!
No, you truly are--ouch! Hot! Hot!
Big Sis Sayo!
Hey, you! This is no time to be impressed!
Whoa, are you okay?
Gum-Gum...
My, I nearly burned my fingers.
Gatling!
You're puny!
Not that I have any skin to burn!
Next I'm gonna blow that brat sky high!
I am a stinking idiot!
Star Shield!
My map!
What have I done?!
That was horribly careless of me.
But even if you're puny,
Nami-san is still Nami-san!
Stop it!
You're in an unusually good mood today.
Don't you worry!
Nami-san!
We keep cutting them down,
but there's no end to them!
Look! I wiped it clean.
I had originally wanted you to
solve the puzzle in that notebook,
Jerk!
Yeah, you wiped it clean of everything...
See? Aren't they goofy?
but forget it! I'll be taking that notebook.
That's not what I wanted!
I'll give her back after you hand it over.
How long are these currents gonna last?!
I'll be taking my leave!
You can have the notebook,
so give Big Sis Sayo back!
How much farther do they go on?!
Don't!
I get the feeling that I won't be
the least bit useful if this keeps up...
Are you going already?
Should we fly out of here with Coup de Burst?
Don't give it to him!
Uh-huh.
Let me introduce myself anew!
Oh, yeah! That's one way!
Big Sis Sayo...?
Hey, Brook!
A wanted poster? You're a wanted man?
It won't work!
Rina, solve the secret in the notebook
and finish Dad's research!
Luffy-san?
Thank you for the feast!
I can't see any end to the currents.
These two are about to do something neat.
Oh, are you leaving?
I apologize for the late introduction.
Yes. Thank you for the meal.
I am the dead and skeletonized Brook.
No! Why should I?
Even if we fly away with Coup de Burst...
You should watch.
Are you all right?
Believe in Dad, Rina!
Uh, okay...
Don't give Dad's research to that jerk!
I have a bounty.
I had a blast! Thank you, Luffy.
Chopper-san, what are you doing up here?
I am known as the Humming Brook.
We can't escape them.
I'm drying these herbs in the sun,
since the weather is so nice.
Aw! Is the ocean raccoon dog leaving already?
What?! No way!
Dad was working to make his
My bounty is for 33 million Berries.
That's who you'll miss?!
A long time ago, I was the leader of
a certain kingdom's assault convoy.
dream come true for you, me, and everyone in the village.
You see, Franky is gonna test his new weapon.
I've been looking for you two.
Shall I play a song?
After that, I was the acting
captain of the Rumbar Pirates.
All right! This is the long-distance
"Super Franky Cannon."
Please! For my sake,
don't throw away Dad's dream!
Huh?
It runs on cola energy.
At times like these, we need to boost morale!
I am a musician and a swordsman!
Its range is several times
All storms and currents
will eventually recede.
This is getting old!
You're lying! Dad is just
a self-absorbed researcher.
that of a conventional cannon.
Plus it's super accurate!
As of today, my life is in the hands
of Captain Straw Hat Luffy!
I didn't expect you to get this far.
Your drive is impressive.
Let's just be patient.
Combined with my sniper skills,
we'll be totally unstoppable!
Sounds good, Brook! Go for it!
Rina...
I'd love to catch you here and now,
but that'll have to wait.
I mean... I mean, he was
always in his own world!
I will work myself to the bone
to avoid tripping everyone up.
Then
This is exciting!
I've run into some rather familiar faces.
"For Dad"
I have butterflies in my stomach!
--It's done!
We're in the air!
I know, right?
Hey, we're...
Excuse me! Let me know if there
is anything I could do to help.
Do you think Dad will like his birthday cake?
You're doomed now that
I've run into you, Straw Hat!
...gonna fall!
All right. In that case, please get
another barrel of cola to play it safe.
All right! Let's have another drink!
Yep!
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Chopper!
Not a problem. It would be my pleasure!
Who are you?
He isn't coming home!
He doesn't know who I am...
He doesn't remember!
I'm sure he must have found something again.
This must be it.
Oh, no! Boss! Don't let it get to you!
Here's the barrel of cola!
I'm going to bed!
Great! Now if you could pour it in.
I thought I was gonna die...
Okay.
Certainly!
By any chance, are you...
Target: That rock.
Got it! Locking on to the rock at 2 o'clock.
...the guy that Zoro and Sanji beat up?
He's doing it on purpose!
It has to be intentional!
"Two Days Later"
--Fire!
--Firing!
Boss!
Hey! Straw Hat, you jerk!
Hey, look!
You tarnished my undefeated legacy
This is wonderful! Thank you,
Franky-san and Usopp-san!
That's...
--Huh?
--That's strange.
Usopp, increase the pressure.
"Fox"
and stole our pride--our Jolly Roger!
Okay, you've got it.
It's cool, really! Don't
think anything of it.
Don't tell me that you've forgotten!
I see it... I see it!
Ah! Now I remember.
My design won!
You're Split-Head Fox!
Man, this doesn't look good.
"For Dad"
I picked the flowers.
A cake? Oh, yeah.
I'm "Silver Fox" Foxy!
It's the Red Line!
Thank you so much, Chopper-san.
Luffy, be careful. As I recall,
he can shoot a weird beam.
They must have baked a cake for me...
Crap!
Stupid! That doesn't make me
the least bit happy, silly!
Really?
The Red Line!
Hey, he isn't much of a threat
if we know what's up his sleeve.
We finally made it this far!
Dad...?
This was a huge flop!
This is a truly wonderful grave.
There was a nasty storm that day, too...
Did I wake you up?
Don't expect me to rely
on the same tricks forever!
It should have worked.
I couldn't possibly put all of those
bones on that cute Lion-chan.
Look!
What are these?
Cast-off Thirty Year Cicada shells.
This is kinda salty.
I can probably use them in my research.
From now on, call her the Thousand Sunny.
A mirror?
Something is mixed with the cola.
There was a big outbreak of them
for the first time in thirty years!
High-Speed Rotation Mirror Ball Amplifier!
Strangely enough, the island on Thriller Bark
This is soy sauce.
Thousand-Armed Kannon, Slow-Slow Beam!
I'm gonna find the All Blue!
Is that right? Ah! But last night...
came from the West Blue,
which is where we were from.
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
What's the matter, everyone?
--Shoot!
--That's against the rules!
Show a little remorse!
Perhaps they will find some rest
if they sleep on familiar soil.
I'm gonna be a great swordsman!
You mistook a soy sauce barrel
for a cola barrel, didn't you?!
A cake! That cake looks delicious!
I'm gonna make a map of the whole world!
Oh, you're right! This
was a soy sauce barrel.
I-I'm gonna become a
brave warrior of the sea!
Darn... it...
Well, Brook, we're gonna head on back.
I cannon believe I made that mistake!
But that cake...!
--See ya!
--Later!
Shut up, you jerk!
Let's go!
We made that yesterday.
--I'm terribly sorry!
--Why did you grab a soy sauce barrel?!
All right.
To the Grand Line!
--I'm sorry!
--This is no time for puns!
It may have gone bad. It is summer and all...
I... told... you... so!
Brook, you're hilarious!
Hey! I can see the Mystery Mountain!
--Don't give me any "I'm only bones" crap!
--Now I'm all sticky!
Aw, I have to wash all of
the herbs I had set out to dry.
It's gigantic!
Doctor... Get a doctor...
The entrance to the Grand Line...
He already saw you and left!
This meat tastes great
with the soy sauce and cola!
Anything struck by my beam is
slow for thirty seconds afterward.
I don't care about him!
He doesn't know a thing about us!
So that's the Red Line!
Can you find a bright side to anything?
I-I can't even see the top
through all the clouds!
I'll be taking this.
Everything I try ends up going horribly awry.
He doesn't think about us!
Hey, this isn't the time to get in a fight...
Now do you remember me, Straw Hat?
Excuse me, Zoro-san...
Don't butt in.
It has taken me 50 years...
This is their problem.
Rina, you're mistaken! Listen to me! Dad...
Let's go, everyone!
I'm sorry about the cake.
This is no time to watch in admiration!
I'm a fellow swordsman.
Dad...
That's...
You were looking forward to having
a birthday party, weren't you?
Isn't this meditation?
Yeah...
It's huge!
I need the materials in the
You'll start to fall in ten seconds!
You enter a state of nothingness
while making your mind and body one.
cast-off Thirty Year Cicada shells to make the jewels.
Make sure you steer.
Nine!
Eight!
I shall join you.
I don't want you giving me orders.
Seven!
If I didn't get them now, I'd have
to wait another thirty years...
What a lovely bath.
It made my skin so smooth. It's great!
I had to go.
Excuse me, Zoro-san...
Should we use the paddles to retreat?
But I'm a skeleton, so I don't have any skin.
Uh-huh.
I am fully aware that it is improper to
talk during meditation sessions, but...
There's no time.
You aren't angry?
Sanji-kun! Get us on that wave!
No...
I see. But I bet Rina is mad at me.
You got it!
Wait, "get us on" it?!
I don't mind.
What are you guys up to?
Leave it to me!
--Well, you see...
--What is it?!
I dealt with bigger stuff than
this when I was on the Sky Island!
Franky! Brook! Beat them up!
I need to use the restroom.
You are just like your mother,
but Rina takes after me.
The Knock Up Stream, huh?
I didn't need to know that! Head on over--
Weapons Left!
Yeah, that was really fun!
She's a handful when she gets upset!
--The thing is...
--What?
...my legs went numb, so I can't stand!
That wasn't fun at all!
After I make some jewels,
let's eat a cake that's this big!
Do you have any muscles to go numb?!
Oh, you startled me.
Of course, there's no way
this time is gonna be...
Zoro-san, I'm on the verge
of having an accident.
Are you sure you should be up?
What's going on?!
Yeah. I overslept a bit.
For real? W-Wait, hold it!
Yeah!
Let's get one that Rina could hide in.
--I'm gonna leak! It's coming!
--I'll take you! W-Wait! Hey, hold it in!
What is that?
My dead sword, Yubashiri.
Go!
Please let me lay it to rest here.
Nukki says that it's all true.
Despite what I want, I've
been nothing but a nuisance.
Now we can use Coup de Burst!
Luffy?!
Cien Fleurs!
This is awful!
Lower the sails, everyone!
And he said that your father
left home to protect you and Sayo
Thank you, Robin-chan!
Robin-san!
I owe ya!
Excuse me...
Luffy will become the King of the Pirates!
Is everyone okay? Gosh, you scared me.
from some bad guys who
were after his jewel research.
Is there anything I could
do to be of assistance?
Here we go!
Oh, no...
Coup de Burst!
Not in particular.
Excuse me...
Is that right?
Brook, why are you so anxious?
N-No, it's nothing...
You're amazing, Luffy!
What's this...?
Anxious?
Yeah, I'm a rubber man. I won't
let that Slip-Head defeat me!
I get the feeling you're afraid
of something.
Oh, yes! I've joined your crew.
Am I mistaken?
Damn it! You've added new
members to your crew, Straw Hat!
You are absolutely right, Robin-san.
I can't find one...
That right? Your luck really does bite.
You have to work to find a four-leaf clover.
That's right. I am terribly
anxious and scared.
But Big Sis found three of them!
B-Boss, they have a skeleton!
Our crew is a handful.
That's because she believed with all
When Luffy-san first asked me
to join his crew, I was thrilled!
So it would seem! I'll work myself to death!
Shoot! Let's try again!
of her heart that she would find them.
Victory is mine as long as
I have this mirror ball.
Ah, but I'm already dead.
Whew, we're saved!
--She believed?
--Right!
Those simple words filled me with joy.
Conducting research and searching
for four-leaf clovers are similar.
Stupid! What are you doing?
Shut the door already.
Man, that was a close one.
And then my heart danced
If you never stop believing and work hard,
it will pay off in the end.
with excitement when I defeated
Oars alongside everyone.
We're here!
Really? Then I'm going to find a five-leaf clover!
Gum-Gum Bazooka!
May I join your crew?
We finally made it here!
Yeah, sure.
What?!
Huh? Five leaves...?
I can't see the top...
It's huge!
But does he truly want me in his crew?
That'd be amazing!
So this is the Red Line...
If we continue to head toward the New World,
I found one!
It's kind of nostalgic... Makes
you feel really emotional, huh?
I have no doubt that powerful foes and
trials beyond our imagination await us.
All right! Now that Zoro
is up, let's hit the seas!
I found a five-leaf clover!
I'm afraid that I will be
both useless and a hindrance.
Time to head out for our next adventure!
Th-That's... Rina!
Yeah!
I wonder if we've grown
a little since then...
I swear I'll get him!
Huh? Zoro, did you remove
your bandages again?!
You were right! I believed I could find one.
And if that proves true, I
I feel like crying!
Yeah, they hampered my movement.
That's right, Rina! That's amazing!
So much has happened!
might get kicked off the ship!
They were meant to keep
you from moving! Wait!
Anyway, we're halfway there now!
Yay!
That's right... I'm afraid
of losing my friends again
You seem awfully anxious to go.
Are you really setting sail?
All right, Rina! I'm gonna
succeed with my research!
The Twin Capes, where we met Laboon,
and returning to that
painfully long life of solitude.
You guys can have Brook's ship.
are connected to this wall on
the other side of the world.
I fixed the rudder and sails.
Yeah... I had forgotten all about that...
I'm glad we all made it here together!
I was...
Thank you.
You guys have been such
a big help in so many ways!
Please remain calm!
...also anxious for the longest of times.
I used to believe he could pull it off.
"Hot Water"
I owe you so much!
I couldn't begin to thank you.
Apparently, I crossed Reverse Mountain from
South Blue before I was old enough to remember,
This is Dad's dream! It has to come true.
I'd love to marry you.
You're a great catch, but unfortunately,
but I guess that was more than 30 years ago.
Rina!
I'm just too cool. It wouldn't work out.
I've changed my mind! You can't
have the notebook after all.
I entered this sea five
years ago, from West Blue.
I hate to see you guys go!
Wh-What?!
Let's party for another two or three days.
Once we go around the
second half of the world,
It's show time!
Nope! Our next stop is Fishman Island.
we'll get to see this wall
again, and when we do...
Why is everyone leaving?
I was...
I'm dying to get there!
I bet it's full of fascinating people!
...also anxious for the longest of times.
I'd like to ask you two something.
I'll be King of the Pirates!
I'll get to frolic with beautiful mermaids!
Wh-What?
I was constantly afraid that I
was unworthy to be their friend.
It's about that notebook.
Would it be all right if I asked the
mermaids to show me their panties?
Foxy and his goons are after it, aren't they?
That is why I believed I could
become worthy of them
Foxy?
Hey, man! Don't be stupid!
The pirates from earlier.
Don't play games with me!
by throwing away my life for their sake.
Sure, we have a history with them,
Seis Fleurs!
Mermaids don't wear panties.
Robin-san...
but I'd say they were more
interested in your notebook.
Tabasco Star Onslaught! Star! Star!
No matter how far I go on the sea,
Mermaids are stinking gorgeous!
We have to remain alert.
I have a huge enemy that I can't shake off...
The Pirate Empress Hancock
is nothing compared to them!
I called it, didn't I?
We're right next to Marie Jois,
the holy land of the Navy HQ
...because the world and
its darkness are my enemy!
This notebook explains how to create jewels!
Nami, get on.
Uh-huh.
Mermaid! Mermaid!
and the World Government.
How to create jewels?!
That's why I didn't want
you to come to rescue me!
--Mermaid! Hurray!
--Doesn't their lower half look like a fish tail?
Sayo-chan!
--Rina!
--It's okay. Leave this to me.
Hurry! Untie her.
If I'm going to die someday anyway,
--Mermaids! Love them!
--How come you know so much about them?
Huh?
What is that?
I want to die right here, right now!
--Mermaid! Mermaid! Oh, baby!
--Oh, we passed through on
our way here three years ago.
It's true that they're pirates, but they
seem trustworthy. Plus they're strong!
A lock?!
I didn't realize that was how you felt...
--Mermaid! They're wonderful!
--Fishman Island was incredible!
This surprise pool is the best!
If we try to deal with this on our own,
we may never reach our goal.
But I was mistaken.
Lola, you went to the New World?
Where did you come from?
I didn't go there. That's where I was born.
That isn't what it means to be a true friend.
Wait! What are you going to do?
My mama is a pirate.
Robin-san...
Please wait!
Oh, yeah!
I'm sure you'll be fine.
You see, this notebook
belonged to our father.
Three-Sword Style...
This is my mama's Vivre Card.
You may have a piece.
Oh, wow! It's full of numbers!
Oomph!
It's paper?
...Great Buddha Slayer!
Brook, we've got food! It's lunchtime.
Wow, you're lucky! Captain Lola's
mama is an amazing pirate!
Our father is an inventor, and those
formulas explain how to make jewels.
Luffy-san...
Sanji worked extra hard to make
a full-course seafood lunch!
You can read this?
I just know it'll be good!
Take good care of that!
I'm sure it will come in handy later.
Luffy-san!
Big Sis Sayo can. It goes right over my head.
What is a Vivre Card?
What's keeping you? Get a move on!
Really? You're something else, Sayo-chan!
Huh? You don't know?
Captain Lola, Vivre Cards are
only available in the New World!
They're doing a great job.
Are you absolutely certain I'm welcome?
I'm not good enough...
What about this? He included
a nautical chart...
Just try it.
Oh, really?
Hey, you need to do a great job!
That I may join the Straw Hat Crew?
It has a hot water mark and an "X."
This isn't your typical sheet of paper.
Curse you!
Yup.
Water and fire can't hurt it.
That's his secret message.
Jeez, give it some thought!
We think it's a hint regarding
how to make jewels.
If you take your nail clippings to a shop,
I decided to let you join,
so I'm glad to have you.
Huh? This?
they will make a special sheet
of paper that mixes them in.
The formula for making
them is about 99% complete.
Hey, you're alive?
Where is he?
What's that?
It is known as the
"Paper of Life," the Vivre Card!
What happened here?!
The jerk! He released all
of the steam in the ship!
And he hid the remaining 1% in this clue.
Now forget about that. Let's eat! Food!
You can tear off a piece and give it
to family and friends who are leaving.
Right.
Nothing...
Everyone's waiting!
Nothing... happened!
Could the hot water mark
mean a hot springs...?
In which case, the "X" might mean Spa Island.
And then?
Just watch. This is the Vivre Card
that my mama gave to me.
That's better!
I have to get stronger!
Now die!
Yep. We reached the same
conclusion and snuck aboard.
I'm still weak!
Ah, it moved!
Impressive!
But despite all of our searching,
No matter where in the world you are,
the pieces will pull toward each other.
I'm still...!
we can't find anything to indicate
we're on the right track.
So I always know which
direction my mama is in!
I doubt that notebook alone could
tell you how to make jewels...
Let's go, Rina!
How does it look, Robin? Brook? Luffy?
Yeah!
Of course, it doesn't
indicate how far away she is.
Third Gear!
Wow, that's amazing! Is the New World
filled with things like that?
But the Foxy Crew has come this
far in pursuit of that notebook!
Not good. It's pitch dark.
Bone Balloon!
It might be legit.
Isn't it handy? I'll sign
my mama's Vivre Card,
It's pitch dark!
It might be fake.
Hey, I just saw something flash!
Huh?
Giant Axe!
so if you ever run into trouble,
use this to get to her.
Y-Y-You think it was some monster's eyes?!
Rina!
I'm sure it's fake.
When you see her, let her
know that I'm doing well.
M-Monster?!
There is no way you can make jewels!
W-We're gonna die!
Thank you, Lola!
What?
I might have one of those.
My father is a stupid liar!
That thought just occurred to me as well.
He is really stupid!
I hate my father!
Isn't this identical to the white
paper that Ace gave to you?
Wait, I'm already dead!
That scrap of paper will bring you
and me together again sometime.
"Rina and Sayo's Village
-Three Years Ago-"
Oh, right. Nami-san, pardon
me for asking, but...
Boss!
What kind of panties are you wearing today?
So that's what he meant...
What on earth is going on...?
This is it! Huh?
What the heck?!
Shut up! Be serious about this!
It's kinda burnt. And it's smaller now.
Scary!
Even the Straw Hats have
calm days like this...
Let me see that right quick!
Dad!
He's got some guts.
Later!
Welcome home.
Hey, you guys!
Sayo! Rina! This is horrible!
This is definitely a Vivre Card.
The Shark Submerge III can't
dive deeper than 5,000 meters!
What is?
It's a golden beetle!
I hadn't told you this yet, but it
also reveals the owner's vitality.
Be careful!
L-Legend says that our village
will perish when one appears!
Hm? The hull seems to be creaking...
Isn't this person dear to you?
What should I do?! What should I do?!
Usopp, let's catch dinner!
Yeah! He's my big brother.
Yes, because...
Dad...
Yeah!
Stupid! Don't forget about
everyone who has to abandon ship!
We're more than 5,000 meters under.
The paint is coming off.
How many years--no, decades--has it been
Ah, so that's why.
Lola...?
Luffy, you're amazing!
Wait! That's a bad idea!
The pressure will crush us!
Oops! I forgot that I shrink
when I use that move.
since I enjoyed such a carefree nap?
He fell for it!
I hate to say this, but his life...
What an idiot!
Huh?
Scram!
Hey, Brook! Are you gonna sleep forever?
is burning out.
Hey, that monster from
before is still around!
I can't believe them!
Wake up! We spotted an island!
What?!
It sure has a big mouth!
It's a summer island! It has a beach!
What a relief! Thank goodness!
Sheesh! Think ahead a little, will you?
Huh? What?
Huh?
When I was wandering the ocean alone,
Well, isn't this great?
The village isn't doomed.
That was close!
It's gonna eat us!
I would dream about my old
friends and Laboon in my sleep.
Isn't it wonderful that it was a prank?
It's coming again!
Our father loved our village.
I would jump awake with happiness,
Looks like this isn't gonna go well.
I never want to ride in the Shark Submerge.
only to face the painful reality
filled with despair and solitude.
A giant "X."
He loved it because that was
where our mother was born.
Ditto.
Nami-san!
Sleep was by no means a peaceful escape.
My tart made of horror pears
from Thriller Bark is done!
Hey!
--Take care!
--Hey!
But if I listen carefully now...
Wow, it looks delicious!
Goodbye, guys!
We did it!
My research can save the entire village.
Behind us! Behind us!
Serves the jerk right!
I will never forget what you've done for us!
Here it comes! We're gonna get eaten!
Everyone will be able to live in comfort.
This is a problem, though...
The sun! Thank you for
bringing the sun back to us!
What type of research
are you conducting, Dad?
Wow! This is great!
An "X"! And it's huge.
Yum!
Everyone, careful not to get wiped out!
So, Robin, what do you
think of these outfits?
Jewels! How to create jewels!
Yep! Dad was referring to that
underwater volcano on the map.
Looks like another dead end,
just like at the Sky Island.
Well, I think you'd look
good in this and this.
Don't jinx them, jerk!
Jewels...? Those aren't
something you make, Dad!
Doran built his ship right above
the treasure he was searching for.
That's right.
Lola, thank you for the
Vivre Card! Take care!
I knew it!
I know which way we need to go, but
I don't know the means to get there.
The doof didn't realize the key
to the secret was right under him.
Say hi to Mama if you see her!
Let's meet again, Namizo!
How do we get to Fishman Island?
Your dad sounds neat!
He isn't the least bit neat!
He's a horrible father!
We're off!
We're out!
Perfect.
That was fun!
Three years ago, he went on a journey
for his research and never came back.
Welcome back! Good job!
Amazing!
It was no good. We couldn't
see the sea floor.
He abandoned us!
That's... a circular rainbow!
You sure Fishman Island is really here?
It's been just the two of us ever since.
I've never seen a round rainbow before.
That was my first time riding a submarine!
Same here.
We've had to grit our teeth
as everyone made fun of us.
If it's any deeper, we'll
die before we get there.
They're gone, aren't they?
It's a mysterious rainbow! Awesome!
They sure are.
"I don't have a dad. He's dead!"
That's what I've told myself.
I'm sure the Log Pose was
pointing right beneath us...
The fog is rolling back in.
We'll set sail tomorrow!
W-Wait a sec! Is that the treasure?
What a problem. I should have
talked with Lola about it more.
But then a month ago...
Huh?
Come to think of it, circular rainbows
are referred to as the "ocean's treasure."
No one knows what happens in the
Florian Triangle's mysterious waters.
My pals are near me.
Nukki suddenly came back
with this notebook in his mouth.
What?!
Even dead and skeletonized...
Oh, man!
Every year, over 100 ships
disappear in the fog.
It's the thing from before!
There was a letter in the notebook.
What do you think it said?
...I'm truly glad to be alive!
It followed us back!
Th-That's it?
That is an old mystery that began before
the giant pirate ship, Thriller Bark,
You better not tell me that this is the treasure.
"Dear daughters.
Please complete my research."
Don't underestimate us!
began to lurk in the shadows
of that sea ten years ago.
Uh, well...
Can you believe him?
Don't think you can beat me
when we're above the water!
You can have all of the treasure!
He was so busy with his research that
he forgot about us for three years!
Don't give us that!
Why must we risk our lives and
travel to these dangerous waters?!
Gum-Gum Rifle!
Huh? That rainbow looks weird...
The order of the colors is inversed.
It just so happens that, once again today,
He's stupid! Stupid!
I don't believe a word he says.
The order...?
the dense, white fog is covering the
It actually didn't seem all that huge.
He's fudging over his lies about
the jewels with this picture.
eerie face of the sea with its white vale.
What's wrong?
Just maybe...
Yeah, since we've seen Oars. We're okay now!
Why did he give us this quiz at the end?!
"-Several Days Later-"
Your dad really is neat!
Luffy!
It spit something out.
Huh?
Are you really sure?
Oh, you mean about Ace's paper?
I think that might be...
Huh? A fish?
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
I wanna see those jewels.
A person?!
Luffy-san, I don't mind.
We can take a detour.
You're the monster raccoon dog
from the other day!
No, it's not.
Did you pay attention to a word I said?!
No, it's an ocean raccoon dog.
By now, time is of little
consequence to me and Laboon.
That's a...
Ah, there you are!
It... It couldn't be!
A letter?
You're late, Zoro!
"Live" and "Reunite." Those are my mottos!
Hey!
It looks like Sayo-chan's guess
was dead on back there!
But didn't you come to
search for the treasure?
Luffy, everyone is cool with taking a detour.
I didn't--my sister did!
"Dear Luffy and friends. Are you well?
It's cool! It's cool!
I'm her bodyguard.
Yeah! Let's go see your whale of a brother!
My big sister and I went straight
home and tested out her idea."
Her bodyguard?
My sister was insistent
about searching for the secret,
Nailed it!
No, it's okay. Honest!
If he is in trouble, I doubt he'd want me
to worry every time this happens.
We followed my father's formulas
and made seven different medications.
so I came to protect her.
What are you guys doing?
When we mixed them together in
the order of the circular rainbow...
Ace hates it when people see him look weak.
I am certain that there
is a way to make jewels!
You saved me!
Even if we went, he'd just yell at me.
This is a short break time
before the next adventure
eventually falls upon us.
I believe in him.
That was awesome!
When we meet, we will be enemy pirates.
You're not supposed to be impressed!
Ace has adventures of his own.
Big Sis Sayo...
We were about to be digested!
Yes, let your weary bones rest.
That Vivre Card shrinks when
its owner is in a weakened state.
It worked!
You just had to stroll right
by that monster, didn't you?!
She says it created a jewel!
When he gets better,
it returns to its original size.
Well, I didn't see it there...
Yay! We did it! We did it!
How do you miss something that huge?!
Laboon,
Everyone, please help--
Yep! We won't meet until then.
Sayo... Rina...!
it looks like I will have
That's why Ace gave this paper to me, right?
Hey, not that it matters, but
you're sitting on something.
a slew of stories to
share when we meet again.
Huh?
Big Sis Sayo!
Gah! I crushed a human!
I hope you're looking forward to them!
Is this it?
Cool!
Come to think of it, Zoro,
you still haven't done this,
I've got the girl. If you want
her back, do as I say!
I'm sorry! Are you okay?
That's a sign of their gratitude.
since you were asleep the whole time!
They say, "Thank you, guys."
Oh, no, it's okay... More
importantly, are you...
Doran?!
So, I'll take it from the top.
Let me get a better look at it, Luffy.
Who is that?
--I wanna see it! Lemme see!
--Huh? Let's see it.
The ship's host.
Let's drink to our new crewmate,
the musician, Brook!
Wait! Just a sec.
What?!
Hey, guys! This isn't a toy.
Cheers!
The wind has picked up.
I'd like you to uncover the secret
behind that notebook.
Thank you for having me!
Everyone!
Okay! Pull up the sails!
Please snap out of it! Are you okay?
I'll return the girl in
exchange for the answer.
What's going on?
Let's fly with a Coup de Burst!
It's candy rain! Ow, ow!
Is that...
Guys!
Oomph!
Yeah!
It's yummy!
It's about time we set out.
...a tail fin?
Coup de Burst!
Shoot! Foxy wasn't our only enemy!
Oops. I dropped the jewel.
No way... It's really...
--Which one is it?!
--Beats me.
Yeah!
Find it! Find it fast!
I promise to work my butt off!
What should we do, Luffy?
What is this?!
You guys had better find it!
But I'm a skeleton, so I don't have a butt.
Okay!
A mermaid?!
Please save my friend, Hatchin!
Blue waters and a shining sun! This is bliss!
Please, Rina! Finish the research.
We've reached the Red Line at last!
Why are you so excited, Brook?
We'll finally get to see Fishman Island.
Leave it to us!
Don't let Dad's dream fall
into the hands of that jerk!
After learning about the great feats
you've accomplished on your voyage,
We just have to knock out
that guy in the mask, right?
Where are the mermaids?
There are a bunch of neat things here.
He's the boss of the Flying
Fish Riders, Duval!
I don't see any mermaids,
but there is a sea monster.
Dad's research was nothing but lies.
I've realized I must work
to become a true comrade!
You're... Split-Head!
I've been waiting.
The jerk!
I cant believe Sayo got caught
because of his notebook!
Who are you calling "Split-Head"?!
"A true comrade"? That's not
something you work toward.
I'll kill him.
Something popped out
when I whacked its stomach.
I'll put an end to your wisecracks
with my new technique!
I'll kill the man who ruined my life!
Please, Luffy! Save Sayo!
Oh, dear!
Could that be a--?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Brook's Great Struggle! Is the Path to
Becoming a True Comrade Rigorous?"
"The Great Scramble for Treasure!
Collapse! Spa Island!"
"Hatred for the Straw Hats!
Iron Mask Duval Appears!"
"The Slow-Slow Menace!
'Silver Fox' Foxy Returns!"
"Halfway Across the Grand Line!
Arrival at the Red Line!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!