High Tide
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around
the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
As Luffy and his friends continued their
voyage in search of Fishman Island,
On the way to their next
destination, Fishman Island,
During their voyage to Fishman Island,
During their voyage in
search of Fishman Island,
As Luffy and his friends continued their
voyage in search of Fishman Island,
Luffy and his friends fought a fierce battle
against Duval and the Flying Fish Riders.
Luffy and friends helped save
Camie's friend, Hatchin.
they finally reached the Red Line,
the halfway point of the Grand Line.
Luffy and friends met the mermaid, Camie.
they made it halfway to the Grand Line.
The Straw Hats fought a hard battle against
the kidnapping gang, the Flying Fish Riders.
To save Camie's friend Hatchin,
who had been captured by
It's the Red Line!
Chopper!
Curse you Straw Hats!
I can't see the top...
It's huge!
a kidnapping gang, the Flying Fish Riders,
That's when they saw the true identity of
Duval, who held a burning hatred for Sanji.
In response to Duval's unjustified hatred,
So this is the Red Line...
the crew headed to the Flying
Fish Riders' hideout.
Coup de Burst!
Sanji's outrage reached its peak.
Anyway, we're halfway there now!
Whether it's from the sea
or the sky, bring it on!
Œil!
But the towering Red Line blocked their way,
Nez!
I'll go nuts on 'em!
Joue! Bouche! Dents!
Stop screwing around!
and they lost their path to Fishman Island.
Menton!
Boys!
Parage...
I know which way we need to go, but
I don't know the means to get there.
I can't see the top...
Shot!
It's huge!
They finally reached the Red Line.
Unleash the Sunny's Super Secret
Weapon, the Gaon Cannon!
Gum-Gum Rifle!
It's battle time!
There, they met the mermaid Camie
Yeah!
"Landing on the Way to Fishman
Island! The Sabaody Archipelago!"
It spit something out.
and the starfish Pappug, and became friends.
Huh? A fish?
"Tragedy! The Truth Hidden
Behind Duval's Mask!"
Thanks for saving me.
That face... Is that even possible?
It... It couldn't be!
Camie, you're okay?
Incredible...
Camie asked them to save her
imprisoned friend, "Hatchin,"
There's actually someone who looks just
like that scribble on Sanji's wanted flyer!
Head! Head!
so they headed toward the hideout of the
kidnapping gang, the Flying Fish Riders.
Stuck at a dead end with no options,
Where are you?!
Luffy and his friends met Camie the
mermaid and Pappug the starfish.
"Black Foot" Sanji, it's all your fault!
What? What's going on?
Head!
There they are! The Flying Fish Riders!
Are you all right, Head?!
Hey, Sanji! Where are you going?
He's...
"Hatred for the Straw Hats!
Iron Mask Duval Appears!"
Damn, he's all beat up.
Head, are you alive?
Do you know how scared I was when
people suddenly wanted me dead?
Hey! Did you see?
Yeah! There's no mistake!
It's the Straw Hats!
Well, now, which one's
got the most fight in it?
Head!
Why? Why did I have to be chased
all the way to Navy HQ?!
I've been waiting. I've been waiting so long.
Are you okay? You're not hurt, are you?
Damn it...
Why do I have to be nearly killed
by famous bounty hunters?!
Sure...
I finally had Black Foot
right where I wanted him!
That pirate ship is the
one I've been waiting for.
Hey, hey, hey!
That's the one!
Why?!
I'll kill him.
Sanji?
That surprised me! Look at all the humans!
I'll kill the man who ruined my life!
Huh? What is it?
Gotcha!
Wh-What?
All because you made a name
for yourself as a pirate,
Why are you all gawking at me?
We're the one who're surprised!
Wha?
I'm takin' over!
Thanks for saving me when
I was about to be digested.
H-Hey!
Head, please stay calm and look at this.
I've had to live every day in
fear, running around and hiding!
I'm such an easy target
for sea monsters to eat...
Whoo! This is awesome!
That was about the twentieth time.
"The Fated Reunion! Save
the Imprisoned Fishman!"
Yeah!
You get eaten too much!
Th-This is... Wh-Wha—
I'm flying!
I need to do something to thank you.
What did I even do?!
I know! Would you like some takoyaki?
Luffy's flying one of them!
What happened to me?!
Takoyaki?! That's my favorite!
Give me my life back!
Leave him be.
The flying fish left.
Eat this!
Really? Okay, that'll be
500 Berries per person!
"Black Foot" Sanji!
They were obviously taking
the offensive, though.
What?!
Bombs!
You're trying to sell 'em?!
It looked like they received
some kind of message.
I messed up!
Yum!
Maybe they were ordered to retreat?
Mermaid! Mermaid!
Mmm, this is great!
Damn!
Though I don't know why...
I wanna ride one!
Yes! The most admired of
all races, the mermaid!
What do I care?!
Those flying fish can fly
for five whole minutes?!
The jewel of the sea, the mermaid!
See? Hatchin's takoyaki is
the best in the world, right?
Nami-san! Robin-chan! Are you okay?
And yes! I got to meet one of them!
That's so cool!
Anyway, those flying fish will be at
the place we're heading for, right?
I can't stop! I can't put them down!
Head!
That was close! They almost got us!
She's so cute!
This takoyaki is incredible!
Then we'll need to be prepared to fight.
It's my first time meeting a mermaid!
Damn them. If they'd hit the ladies,
I would've had to kill them.
How can you not care?!
You're name's Camie-chan?!
Who else could be responsible
for this but you?!
It's not your first time.
Hoist the sails! They're in the way!
You met the old woman Kokoro, didn't you?
I never expected them to
come from the sky, though...
Ow! Hot! Hot! Hot!
Shut up! I'm the one who's
pissed about that wanted flyer!
Right!
Why don't we bring the cannons up on deck?
It really is good. What is this stuff?
Then I can shoot 'em out of the sky!
We're gonna dive!
Roger!
All right!
The deep flavor of this sauce...
I know how the poor guy feels...
Thriller Bark?
No, that doesn't scare
me. It doesn't scare me!
I hope Hatchin is okay...
But Sanji was really upset
about that wanted flyer, too.
And it's impressive that he
runs the business from a ship.
If you want to know what scared
me the most in my life, it was...
You're the one Macro is really after.
Who is this?
This is my first experience
with the culture of takoyaki.
Luffy!
Uh, sorry, Sanji! Pretend I didn't say that!
You should be careful yourself.
Luffy-san!
It is delicious!
Are you gonna be depressed forever?
It's your first time seeing a mermaid!
Wait! You idiots!
You're right.
I could stuff my cheeks with this!
Shut up! Why is mine the
only hand-drawn one?!
You guys are rude!
Uh, not that I have cheeks...
Huh? The old woman Kokoro was a mermaid?
You can eat all you like for free today!
That's all you're worth.
But she was walking.
Duval-sama! The three Riders have returned!
Speak in actual words, would you?
This is to thank you all for saving us.
Oh, that's right, you didn't know.
They'll laugh...
All the ladies in the
world will laugh at me...
These are made with broth,
and these have mochi in them.
It was while you were fighting Lucci.
What do you think you were doing
in the middle of a fight?!
Careful, they're hot!
I never knew stuff like this could happen...
Don't you...
Sorry...
Duval-sama, why did you order us back?
What a shocker. The world
sure is a big place.
So...
...die!
And why did you guys try to save him?
Yeah!
How about you, um... Nami?
Sanji must've been born
under a star of miracles.
If you'd left it to us, we could've
nabbed the mermaid and the pirates!
I really don't want to think
of Kokoro as a mermaid.
You've got powers!
He's going to have such an
interesting death someday.
Fools!
You're too blunt!
Sorry...
I feel so sorry for that Duval guy...
That hurt! What'd you do that for, Nami?!
Er, um... H-How does it taste?
I... I'm sorry for causing trouble...
I swear, when it comes to guys and
their desires toward mermaids...
You guys...
Yes, sir!
Think of how we felt, having to save
you three lumps who can't swim!
Hey, they look just like each other!
Do you know how I have felt
as I waited for those pirates?
She is quite a cute mermaid, though.
This doesn't mean I'm going
to forgive you for anything.
Two peas in a pod.
This is my first time
meeting a mermaid, as well.
I'm sure you know the story.
No, of course not! That's not why I asked!
Idiot! Don't make more work for us!
Pardon me, but would you lend me some money?
Duval
I really just wondered how
you liked the taste...
The Macro Pirates!
When I think about that man,
Brook! I'm gonna pound you later!
Now's our chance! Get Camie!
Why should she?!
A skeleton!
Okay, Sanji, we're going on ahead.
Look at that! How could
you scare her?! Go away!
Right!
the huge wound on my back throbs terribly.
Hey, Straw Hats! Pay attention to us!
You think this is my fault?!
Luffy-chin!
I can open my head, too. Fun, right?
Camie! Pappug!
If you don't want to look like the
flyer, cut your hair or grow a beard!
Damn little...
How fun!
Nami...
Uh-oh... The Head is mad!
She's quick to accept people...
There are plenty of things you could change!
Day after day, I have continued
to loathe that man...
By the way, do you poop?
They're really tasty!
Camie! Pappug!
What are you asking her?!
Sure, I—
She does not!
I see, I see!
She really doesn't!
I'm glad! I'm so glad to hear that!
Camie, Camie?
Oh! I never thought of that!
That's strange. Aren't you missing someone?
Head, please calm down...
Are you just stupid to the core?!
Okay, you guys, eat up! Have all you like!
What's missing from that
little circle of fun?
I'm free from the cage and the binds!
Shall I kill him here today?
I'm not stupid!
Thanks, Roronoa! You're a good guy!
The answer is me.
Yeah! Keep 'em coming!
We'll eat every last one!
What do you think?
Just following captain's orders, idiot.
That is the biggest question in my life!
You know, Black Foot, we...
Oh, yeah, I've been wondering.
Hey, Camie, what's this talking glove thing?
Do you realize that?!
Hachi!
Hatchin!
We...
Y-Yes! In that case, you
should not let him live!
Sorry, I totally forgot.
You guys took advantage of
the fact that I couldn't move
That's my pet, Pappug. He's
a starfish, and my master.
...used to be plain old mafia
guys out in the country.
That's exactly why I must be careful
and thorough in eliminating him.
to beat me up, didn't you?!
Master?
Yeah, yeah! I didn't get
to do enough beating!
Yep. My master.
Hey! You guys!
So do as I tell you!
This thing?
Young Master!
Yep!
I'll use my Fishman Karate to finish you!
Nice to meet ya!
Yes, Head!
Who's that?
Hey, Macro Pirates.
Do starfish talk?
You really have no luck!
That voice...
Yeah? You called?
Isn't it weird to have a
pet that's your master?
Wait up!
What is it, Duva?
Since you kept mouthing off at us,
You can't leave without saying goodbye!
Gyaro, how could you call him Duva?!
I let her keep me as a
pet. I've got my reasons.
we're gonna pound you even more!
And Tansui, "Yeah?" isn't right!
Who's that?
You're both being rude!
Hey, kid! What did you do to our leader?
Let's go! I'll stain the sea red with
the new Goldfish Fencing techniques
Ha, ha. "Duva" sounds funny.
Camie always gives me clams...
I'm Handsome— Oh, my mistake.
Oh, damn it!
I developed just for you!
Hey, Master Duval! Hey,
hey, you called for us?
Food, eh?
I'm Duval!
Are you her dad?
Hatchin!
Boss, he's too worked up.
I-I'm sorry!
Here we come!
Takoyaki Punch!
Quiet! Shut your mouth!
"Are you a person?" I'm
a starfish, not a person.
Is that what he looked like?
Please forgive us!
I'm so sorry, Master.
Honey!
They truly are idiots. They don't
know how to speak properly.
Daddy!
We'll let you off the hook for today!
How are you gonna pay me back for this?
I altered his bone structure.
What a brute!
Now he can't complain to me again.
Hatchin!
Camie! Pappug!
I'm not a person, I'm a starfish.
That's fine, boys.
Huh?!
Wow, Master Black Foot!
To me, you're like messengers from
heaven who bring me happiness.
I'm so glad you're safe, Hatchin!
When I woke up after you kicked the
crap out of me, were we ever surprised!
Daddy!
I'm sorry, Camie, Pappug!
Honey!
"Are you busy?"
I'm so grateful, I can't
find the words to thank you.
I meant to come save you!
We went around tormenting
the village folk every day.
You made me this handsome!
Don't worry about that, Hachi!
No, no!
I'm just enchanted!
I've got plenty of hands.
It was a happy life, in its own way.
Look out!
S'okay.
The ladies won't be able ignore this!
I told you to shut up, Tansui!
Don't forget, this is our hideout!
This is truly...
seeing life through rose-colored lenses!
Thanks to you boys, I'll
finally... finally... meet them.
But then, all of a sudden, tragedy
fell upon my peaceful life...
The ones who are gonna sell you all are us,
the Flying Fish Riders!
I'd love to head straight back
to the country and relax,
I'll finally meet the Straw Hats!
What did he do?
That's a ton of money.
Yay! Thank you!
but if I left without thanking my saviors,
I wouldn't be able to sleep at night!
Shouldn't we report him to the Navy?
Laugh! This is where you laugh!
Straw Hats? Huh? Who are they?
Roronoa!
It's your first time in these waters, right?
Here he comes!
Zoro-chin!
It's dangerous to be around him!
If there's any way we can help
you, just ask us anything!
The Straw Hats... So I
didn't hear that wrong.
So, this T-shirt is by
a brand called Criminal.
We'll get in trouble, too!
Run!
It's all the rage on Fishman Island.
You left the fight too soon.
Wow!
The man...
It's so cool!
What? Why'd everyone run away?
Don't wink if you're not used to it.
Leave the rest to us and go hide.
Pappug is the designer.
...I have been praying...
Well, if you have no complaints,
that's enough for me.
I want to be a designer someday, too.
Ah!
Thank you for everything, Roronoa!
You could totally be one, Camie-chan!
If I were to request something, it'd be
that you never show up around us aga—
At the time, I thought I had finally
been recognized throughout the village.
...for a chance to kill is on that ship!
Thank you, Sanji-chin!
I'm really sorry for what I did back then!
I will never forgive him!
Nobody's listening...
Beautiful. Too beautiful.
Are you listening?!
Back then?
Head, please calm down!
I should ride a white horse.
Hey, how can you talk, anyway?
I caused you so much pain
with my Six Swords Style.
But then...
That's quite a grudge you're carrying.
Hey, you!
That's a very good question!
Head, Head! You need to listen!
I never expected to hear the
Straw Hats spoken of here...
He got over that quick.
Not one of those swords even hit me!
Oh, right...
When I was little, I mistakenly
thought I was a person.
What? Handsome?
Really? They didn't?
I didn't say anything like that!
Hey, you! Big guy!
By the time I realized I was a starfish,
I could already speak human language.
Here they come, Chopper!
Gah! This is Duval-sama, you damn octopus!
We never expected you to escape
this far to the countryside.
Want me to make you look
like that scribble again?!
Take this, scum!
You can learn to talk because of that?
Fire!
Was Camie captured by the Straw Hats?
We're locking you up!
It's scary when you get on a roll!
Why's the Navy after me?
That momentum drives the world!
This is bad... Of all people, why them?
Bullseye! Did you see that?!
My condolences, suckers!
Just do as we say,
So anyway, I'm Pappug the starfish.
"Black Foot" Sanji!
You're awesome, Usopp!
I'm an up-and-coming designer.
What?!
Are they coming here?
I'm embarrassed, but I accept...
Would anyone like to try the Zero Fight?
Thanks for saving us!
That's right. They're headed here.
I'm glad we met you, actually.
No way! There's a price on my head?!
your blown kiss!
Zero Fight?
We had just lost our way,
and I wanted to ask—
Whoo, whoo!
Hey, does that mean your mermaid
went to pirates for help?
Sounds fun! But if I'm gonna do
it, I'm giving it all I've got!
I didn't blow a kiss! I just
wiped sauce off my lips!
A bounty of 77,000,000
Berries... and "Sanji"?!
Hey, Nami! Takoyaki comes first!
You'll give us plenty of
medical coverage, right?
I don't know the details, but
she didn't seem like a prisoner.
Oh, right. I wanted to
repay you with takoyaki.
What kind of optimistic
delusion are you seeing?!
Apprehend him!
Well, no matter who she brings,
How about a million?
Then we'll have to meet up
with Hatchin somewhere...
Oh, mirror, mirror! Is the
most handsome man of all me?
as long as we're here, they'll all be
captured and sold at the human shop.
It's a deal, Head! I'm going!
I'm not him! I'm not Sanji, I tell you!
Hatchin?
A single-choice quiz?!
Outta my way!
Stop!
Ring ring ring... Ring ring ring...
We get that you're handsome,
Some huge guy is coming this way!
Ring ring ring... Click.
As if that's possible! Those
guys are crazy strong!
I'm gonna be killed!
but you were dumb to start
with, so you're still hopeless.
Hello, Hatchin? It's Camie!
He's swinging an iron rod!
He isn't holding the handlebars.
Man, this is a problem... Nami's
probably with them, too...
Do you understand, Black Foot?
Sorry we got separated. Where are you now?
Ah. You're jealous?
He's not planning to
charge us head-on, is he?
I am not!
She's probably holding a grudge against me.
I've never done anything
worse than shakedowns,
What?!
Don't bother, Usopp! You're
no match for his personality!
Of course she would.
The ship won't withstand
a crash from that monster.
Hey! Is that Camie I hear?
and suddenly I had a price of
77,000,000 Berries on my head...
Well, Young Master, this is
my Transponder Snail number.
I did awful things to her
with Arlong and the boys.
Luffy, you go after the fish.
Hatchin?
You don't know who I am? I'm not Hachi.
Call me anytime!
I've gotta get out of
here before they arrive,
All right!
The terror of having Navy guys on a totally
I'll definitely help you all out!
You're about to find out
that a crash at this speed
What?! You're not Hatchin?!
different power level chasing me around...
or they're sure to pulverize me.
I really caused you a lot of trouble.
I finally ended up with
a huge wound on my back,
is like being hit by a meteorite!
I'm Macro! The very same one,
from the Dopey Macro Pirates!
This is a huge problem!
Sanji's right! He's charging right at us!
and donned an iron mask so my
face would never be seen again.
Sorry you all got mixed up in this.
Hey, I just said it myself...
But the impact of that crash
is gonna be just as hard...
My life was ruined because of you!
Sounds like there's some trouble.
Just stop winking.
...on you!
Why do you have Hatchin's Transponder Snail?
Bye, now!
I will chase you to the ends of Hell itself!
Let's go, Rosy Life Riders!
Gum-Gum...
Because I beat up that Hachi punk, of course!
If you don't want that,
then kill me here and now!
Yes, Handsome!
Balloon!
That's...
So leave already.
You're lying! Hatchin would
never lose to you guys!
Duval-sama!
It's the Straw Hats!
Yeah, normally we're no match for Hachi,
Finally... they're here...
I'm gonna be killed!
Whew, thanks for the feast!
Why did Nami-san and Robin-chan have
but this time, we've teamed up
with the Flying Fish Riders!
Hey, Macro.
Man, I'm stuffed! This is bliss!
to be put in danger just for your
stupid baseless accusations?!
Huh? What do you want?
I'll give you takoyaki, so please let me go.
That was tasty!
The Flying Fish Riders?!
I can't eat any more...
That's the ship that allowed you to
make a name for yourself as a pirate.
I'm not letting you go, idiot! You
think I'm that obsessed with food?!
Camie, you're okay? Thank goodness.
I'm exhausted.
That means its crew is included
in my hatred for you, too!
You guys sure eat a lot.
Hatchin! Did they really beat you?
This'll be dinner tonight!
I should've expected that of the Straw Hats.
Are you sure he's on the ship?
You were both so cool!
I wish I had six more arms.
They sort of caught me off guard...
You can all die!
Seeing it up close, it really is big.
Yes! He's definitely there!
But you mustn't come here!
Good work, Hatchin.
Damn! The usual methods aren't
working on these guys!
Poison harpoons!
It's curtains for you
now. I hope you're ready!
I'll wreak a little havoc and be
back home soon, so it'll be fine.
Looks like everyone is happy.
Usopp!
Are they? Then I'm happy, too.
Hey, Gyaro, I'll give you
takoyaki, so please let me go.
Hatchin...
There are more of them flying
around than I realized!
Who do you think is gonna fall for—
It's been a wonderful afternoon, Master.
Hey, Camie, I'm about to sell off your buddy!
Assume formation!
How many do we have to
bring down to finish this?
Huh? Pervert?
Hey! Just how obsessed with food are you?!
I'm also more than happy with
my first takoyaki experience.
Octopus fishmen are rare,
so he's worth a fortune!
All of you, get in position!
Yes, sir!
If you want to come save
him, you're welcome to.
Ah, pardon me.
Damn! I wanna ride one!
Hey, Tansui, I'll give you— Huh?
We're five kilometers east of Grove
#44 in the Sabaody Archipelago,
Don't think I've given up after last time!
I'm gonna skewer you, Black Foot!
Shut up! You come with us!
Give up! I'm not saving you again!
Die!
Everything about that is disgusting!
That's enough, all of you.
at the hideout of the kidnapping
gang, the Flying Fish Riders.
Hey, octopus and starfish and Camie-chan!
How can this be?
Hey, I see something!
No! Camie, don't come!
What's wrong, Brook?
If you're taking a break,
come up to the deck.
My first battle as one of the Straw Hats,
Looks like that's the Flying
Fish Riders' hideout.
Shut up, you octopus!
I'll serve you tea, too.
You took the bait, Black Foot!
Sure!
and I nearly drowned...
Bye, now.
So that's where this
Hatchin guy is imprisoned?
If I can't be of use now,
I'm a failure as a man!
Crap!
Hatchin...
This tea is delicious.
Hey...
Sanji-kun!
How many of those flying
fish can I bring down?
Hey! Let's hurry up and save the takoyaki!
They're gonna drag him underwater!
Camie-chan...
We're on the right path.
We know! Just hold on!
Sanji! Break the net!
I cannot say, but I can show you...
Our destination is the Sabaody Archipelago.
So, where's the takoyaki?
Damn it! An iron net?!
Do we have to go there
to get to Fishman Island?
what I can do!
Is this really the time?!
Wait a minute...
We'll save him in a flash, Camie-chan!
Suffer and drown to death!
We fishmen and mermaids can
get there easily by diving,
The voice of that "Hatchin" guy on the
Transponder Snail sounded familiar...
Sanji!
Thanks, Sanji-chin!
He can really jump!
but you're humans, so if you
dive, the pressure will kill you.
Oh, but be careful, everyone!
I must be imagining it. Surely it's not...
What's that skeleton guy doing?!
The Macro Pirates alone
have captured me 30 times!
I'll skewer him!
Sorry, Luffy-chin.
Yeah, we barely held out
even in the submarine.
Damn it! I'm coming to save you!
Can I treat you to takoyaki some other time?
Lullaby Song.
You can't, you idiot! I'll go!
You get captured too much!
I have to go save my friend right away.
The hull seems to be creaking...
Well...
Wait! Humans are too slow to catch them!
Aww...
And eaten too much, too!
Hey!
Yes, because...
Hang on, Camie.
Leave this to me!
I don't mean to butt in, but if you
want to save your friend, we'll help.
We're more than 5,000 meters under.
Wow! They all fell... asleep...
Fool! Even if you're a fishman,
you'll never catch them!
You guys, too?!
Ah, so that's why.
Looks like we've entered their territory.
Flying fish are among the
fastest creatures in the sea.
Oh, my mistake. I meant these guys will help!
Wait! That's a bad idea!
The pressure will crush us!
Ugh, there's that "we shouldn't go
to this island" syndrome again...
Music is
You little...!
And their riders are equipped
with oxygen tanks,
So, what say you tell us how to
get to Fishman Island in exchange?
How are we gonna get to
the bottom of the sea?
power!
This isn't an island.
Pardon me!
It's more like a living
complex built on the sea.
so they can stay under as long as they like!
Whoa! I fell asleep!
Okay, attention!
Really? Are you sure, Nami-chin?
He's gonna suffocate and die for sure!
My "we shouldn't go to this living
complex built on the sea" syndrome!
It looks like you guys don't have a clue,
Of course!
Damn that guy! What was that?
so I'll tell you all you need
to know about these seas.
Right, Luffy?
Huh? Yeah.
Why would they go to the
trouble to live here?
He must've used some kind of dirty trick!
You'll help me rescue Hatchin, Luffy-chin?!
What? Who's going to do that?
That would be...
Who knows?
The next time Black Foot
appears on the surface,
It was no trick.
Sure, but who's Hatchin, anyway?
Me!
It was music!
He owns the takoyaki place where I work!
it'll be as a pathetic drowned corpse!
Sure is quiet, though.
Huh?
His takoyaki is the best in the world!
Wait!
What'd you say?!
Um, please listen...
I have a bad feeling...
Well, that's an important matter!
Luffy! We should...
Okay, boys! We're gonna rescue the
takoyaki if it means our lives!
Feel the Head's wrath, Black Foot!
As I was saying, there are two routes
that can take you to the new world.
...go forward!
Yeah!
Hey! Come up with a plan or something!
That Brook's pretty good!
Takoyaki! Takoyaki!
Can't breathe...
It's getting fun now!
But for outlaws like you
guys, only one is possible.
I'm going, too!
They agreed. Do you know where he is?
Hey! Hatchin! Are you okay?!
Wait, Luffy! Not again!
Why?
Yeah... Um...
Because...
Don't worry!
One of them, at the request
of the World Government,
All right, gotcha!
Grove #44 is the easternmost
island in the archipelago.
Get out here, Macro!
involves crossing the city built on top
of the Red Line, the holy land Marie Jois.
If you try to go under, you'll pay!
Give Hachi back!
Camie?!
Hey!
And he's five kilometers east of that...
He's asleep!
Hey, cowboy, I think you
forgot about someone.
What?
Hey, you! Wake up!
So the Flying Fish Riders'
hideout is around here.
Naturally, there's no way they'd grant
permission for pirates to cross.
And we're right here,
It's true that flying fish
are faster than fishmen.
Oh, no! It really is the Straw Hats' ship!
We'd have to walk over the Red Line?
so it's a straight shot from
here to the Sabaody Archipelago.
That jerk! He dove in to the Head's room!
They're among the top of their class.
What would we do with the ship, then?
Damn!
Let's start heading west!
You'd have to abandon your ship and
buy a similar one on the other side.
From there, we can ask
the fish for directions.
But the race that sits at
the very top of that class
Yeah, sounds good. Let's hurry!
is mermaids!
Abandon the ship?!
Nope, I can't get out...
Yeah. It costs money, and
getting permission takes time,
Then I'll have to..
Takohachi Black!
but it's safe, so that's what most do.
There's nothing in all this world's oceans
that can match a mermaid's swimming speed!
However!
Hey!
For the route you'll take,
you can keep your ship!
There's someone in that cage.
It's called...
What is that black thing?
The Sea Floor Route Via Fishman Island!
It'll be okay!
What?! Let me see!
I'll save you, Sanji-chin!
You saw, didn't you?
Hey! You're—
But the Sea Floor Route has many dangers.
Could that be Hatchin?
Huh? Camie? Camie?
She's that amazing?
What do you mean?
I didn't pass you the baton...
They're not a race that can be caught unless
they're completely spacing out, really.
Many ships that use it are eaten
whole by sea monsters and sea kings.
You know me, don't you?
We've got this, Camie! There
are no enemies around!
Camie? Camie?
I see. That is dangerous.
Oh, okay!
It must be their snack time!
Camie! Take care of Sanji!
Can you hear me?
You see?
Yeah!
Are you being serious?!
I don't think I want to
go to Fishman Island...
Wow! The fish are sticking their heads out!
No matter how you look at it, that's a trap!
I need you to give me directions!
They're all hiding nearby
and keeping an eye on us.
Me, either...
Hang on, Camie. Did you say
ships have been eaten whole?
What incredible insight!
What is that?!
Huh? Yeah.
A giant ship anchor? That's too huge!
I-I never thought of that!
What kind of ship do we use
to get to the sea floor?
They're afraid of the Flying Fish Riders,
That's why you keep getting caught!
This ship.
so they'll take us as far as
the vicinity of their hideout.
What?
Aim for the Straw Hats' pirate ship!
I'm right here! Camie, I'm
all right, so don't worry!
Hey, this ship can't go underwater.
That's amazing! You can talk to fish!
Hit it smack in the middle and sink it!
No, it'll be fine.
I had no idea mermaids could do that!
I knew it! Hatchin!
Roronoa!
Some of them have powers! If we fight
them underwater, victory is ours!
And that big wall that goes
around the world, the Red Line,
Zoro-chin!
Camie, with you around, we'd
have all the fish we could eat!
This is bad! We're gonna go down in one shot!
Watch your mouth! I oughta kill you!
Dodge it! Use Burst or the
paddle wheels! Is there time?!
has a small hole in just one spot.
But how can we follow fish
if they're underwater?
No, it's too late!
Oh, it's a big hole from
our perspective, though.
You're all black! What happened?!
Come with me, Usopp! Hurry!
Well... I had my own reasons.
That's where Fishman Island is!
O-Okay!
Just watch.
Stand by at the bow!
It's basically directly below Marie Jois.
More importantly, this is a
trap! You have to turn back!
G-Got it!
You dive about 10,000
meters down to get there.
We're using our emergency secret weapon!
You know I'm strong, right?
I'll be fine, so go!
Awesome!
I can't run any longer!
That far?
Secret weapon?
Is that even possible? I can't believe it!
It's a great place!
My legs are about to cramp up!
I think the sky island was 10,000
meters in the air, too...
Uh, not that I have any muscles to cramp...
That same voice, and that
unusual silhouette...
The Sunny's in trouble!
The fish are making an
arrow on the water for us!
This is very bad!
What do you think, Nami?
You really went all out, Brook.
That's great! So we just have to follow that!
Drop it!
But how do we get to the
sea floor in this ship?
You took out a lot of the flying fish.
I suspect... In fact, I'm almost sure...
No way!
You're pretty amazing, Camie!
You'll get a coating on your ship
at the island we're heading to now.
It'll be a direct hit from there.
I had to do something useful...
Sure of what?
Aww, I still have a long way to go.
We could always ask him and find out.
But... I need a break...
A coating?
Hey! How's Arlong doing?
Nah, I'm really impressed!
You'll see once it's on.
Sink!
All right! I'll steer!
Oh, Arlong-san?
It's coming down!
To four o'clock.
Well, he and Chew and Kuroobi
were all captured by the Navy!
All right, look ahead!
Got it!
We're here, everyone!
Zoro-san, you're still suffering from
the damage you took at Thriller Bark...
I was the only one to break out,
and now I'm running a takoyaki shop
like I always dreamed of doing.
Wow! It's beautiful!
Let's go, boys!
It's not enough to let
these fish bring me down.
What is that?!
Yeah!
There's stuff flying around...
Don't worry.
My goodness!
You let your guard down, Roronoa!
Arlong?
Drop it!
It's like a fantasy.
The Sunny's in trouble!
Six Swords Style!
I knew it...
This is very bad!
Tentacle Sword Overload!
Bubbles?
Have faith in this ship!
It's you, octopus?!
This is...
The Sabaody Archipelago!
Whoa! Its mane is spinning!
Crap!
Sink!
It's coming down!
Huh... You saved me?
That's right. 'Cause you
weren't paying attention.
Emergency escape secret
weapon: Chicken Voyage!
Hatchin! You were so cool!
That's my boy, Hachi!
So you see, Master Duval, I've
lured a mermaid toward us.
C-Crap!
Really?
You're that octopus from Arlong's crew!
Die, fishman!
Yes, all is going as planned.
So you're the takoyaki maker called Hatchin?!
What?! They dodged it?!
Pardon me!
No way!
Awesome!
I've never heard of a ship that can back up!
What?
Well, some stuff happened...
Usopp, get inside the bow!
Understood. Hey, you guys.
Inside the bow?
Nami's hometown was controlled by a fishman
I thought I was a goner! Thanks!
Oh, you can go in!
Yes, Head.
pirate gang called the Arlong Pirates.
Go out and meet her.
You're welcome.
Roger.
There are bubbles flying everywhere!
I told you, you left the fight too soon.
They put Nami through all
kinds of terrible stuff.
So pretty...
Don't rush in individually! Formation!
Wow!
Franky even made all this?
That octopus used to be
an officer in their gang.
Formation (Hentai)
U-Um...
Pervert?
Don't think it's over just
because we dodged that!
She's valuable merchandise,
so please try not to harm her.
Pervert (Hentai)
What is all this, though?
You talking to me?
They're floating from the ground to the sky.
There's still more to this ship's strength!
Attack in flight formation!
Nami, are you thinking of running away?
Who's blowing them?
Formation (Hentai)  Flight (Hikou)
Perverted misbehavior?
They're emitted by the island.
If you do that, everyone in Cocoyashi
Village will be killed on your account.
Perverted (Hentai)  Misbehavior (Hikou)
Emitted? You mean...
You mean me?
Awesome!
Not you!
Really? Why?
How encouraging...
Here they come!
Pour in the cola energy!
Hey, Hachi! Your Camie is finished this time!
May I ask a question?
Sorry to interrupt.
Well? Are you ready for that?
Here! Over here!
Is the Log Pose all right?
Which one of you is Arlong?
Come on down!
What now?
Oh, yeah...
Oh, at a loss for words, are you?
It's pointing toward
Fishman Island now, but...
A woman?!
Seems like a waste, but our
orders were to kill you all!
Hey, this island won't overwrite
the Log Pose, will it?
You think you can kill me?
Huh... So he's a known enemy?
No need to worry about that.
Charge complete!
What?!
Well, naturally, I took Luffy
and the others there to
Hey! What do I do now?
The Sabaody Archipelago is
really a bunch of trees.
Get as much of them in the circle as you can?
Too bad! That's Mirage Tempo!
It has no magnetic force.
bust some heads, and the
whole gang was annihilated!
The circle?
Oh...
Watch for thunder clouds ahead!
Wow! You're amazing, Usopp!
So these aren't islands, then?
You mean this?
Y-Yeah, well...
Well, have you heard of
trees called "mangroves"?
Hey, Zoro.
I thought all of those fishmen
were dragged off by the navy...
Dos Mano!
Setting sail already? You're
not going to Fishman Island?
Mangroves?
Clutch!
Got 'em!
The kind that expose and cover
their roots depending on the tides?
Forget about that, just check her out!
But it looks like he escaped by himself.
Lock on with the button on the
handle and pull the lever!
Carving Hoof Diamond!
She's Camie, a mermaid. A
real mermaid! She's awesome!
That's right.
So this... and this!
I see. Every man has a history.
Hello.
Though, on this island, their
roots are exposed all the time.
A mermaid?
Don't break formation!
Hey, you octopus!
You talking to me?
Now that we know it's you,
there's no way we're saving you!
The Sabaody Archipelago is home
to the world's biggest mangroves,
No, he's not!
First one I've ever seen.
What's that?
Now!
He erased it! He just erased the memory!
Oh, they didn't mean me?
the Hustle Muscle Mangroves.
Hustle Muscle Mangroves?
What the heck?! Guns don't work on him!
We're just gonna make a little
detour to save her takoyaki friend.
B-But...
Sounds like they've got a lot of hustle!
Gaon Cannon...
I-I-Is...
Strong Hammer!
I'm worried, though. Hatchin sounded so weak.
I do, too!
Fire!
There are a total of 79 trees.
Is your takoyaki really that good?!
I know they've done something awful to him.
Amazing!
Each one is an island with
its own towns and facilities.
Well, he's pretty tough. He'll be fine.
They really are strong, Pappug!
Don't waver between your
reason and your appetite.
I never would've thought
they could do all this.
More importantly, you guys
accepted this task so easily.
They are collectively called
the Sabaody Archipelago.
This is stupid.
I thought we'd just get
Hachi and hightail it home.
Are you that confident in your skills?
You mean...
You know Hatchin?
Yep! We're strong!
There are numbers written on the trees.
Were you friends with him before?
Take this!
Just so you know, there are several
kidnapping gangs operating around here.
Yes, each of the 79 trees
is marked with a number.
We were not friends!
Damn!
Franky, dock the ship!
The one straight ahead, Grove
#44, is the commercial entrance,
The human trade is a booming business
in the Sabaody Archipelago.
They have the advantage as long
as we're drifting on open seas!
Turn the ship around!
so let's dock the ship a bit further in.
Amazing!
Nami-chin...
I know that. That's why I'm doing this.
I'm sorry, Camie.
They buy and sell humans?
I wasn't expecting your friend to be him.
These guys aren't giving
us time to move the ship!
The roots are even bigger up close!
That's nasty business.
Mermaids are sold at particularly high costs,
No...
Wow...
Then you won't help me rescue him?
so the three Macro Pirates are
constantly out to kidnap Camie.
It's pitch black inside them.
How remarkable!
Hatchin!
Camie, that's fine! You should
leave! This is a trap!
Hachi the takoyaki shop owner
Is that a bridge?
probably doesn't realize we
were eaten by that sea monster,
Yeah, all the islands are connected
with bridges like that.
No way!
and thinks we were taken
by the Macro Pirates,
I will save you!
Ah, I see!
Luffy!
Run! There's a big one coming!
which would be why he went after them.
You always save us, Hachi!
Okay, we're here!
The Iron Mask?!
A guy in a mask, and a cow!
That's probably right.
This is Grove #41. Let's dock here.
Hatchin is very kind and upright.
A cow?
Pappug!
You're too moved!
Right!
I had no idea these people were so heartless!
It's my fault.
Stupid! Stupid!
That's Motobalo's voice!
The Head's here!
Shut up!
Did ya see what the Sunny can do?!
Hearing about octopus and "Hachi"
makes me think of that idiot fishman.
Just wait, Hatchin!
I'm first!
You just let them shoot
you down left and right?
I'll never abandon you, Hatchin!
That took down almost all of the flying fish!
What is that?! Something just burst out!
That was all Usopp's skill.
Excellent for a first try!
Here we go!
If it's really him, I'm not saving him.
You're not mosquitoes or flies!
You're Flying Fish Riders!
Okay, everyone, remember
the number of this island!
Camie-chan!
That idiot.
Okay, I guess that's not true.
As I said before, all the islands
are connected by bridges,
What awesome power!
Normally, Hachi would wipe
the floor with them easily,
He trampled his own house down
to make his appearance...
Sunny!
Will they be okay?
The lion is so amazing! I thought
my eyes were about to pop out!
I don't need this hideout anymore.
so if you remember the
number, you won't get lost.
Given all that stuff they said,
they must have some kind of plan.
but if the infamous Flying
Fish Riders are involved...
Not if I get to kill the Straw Hats!
I know someone who'd still get lost.
What are they?
We're sorry, Head.
Yeah, me too.
Not that I have any eyes to pop out!
They're a kidnapping gang that's been
throwing their weight around in this area lately.
I've got you, Camie!
Huh? What?
We'll sink all of these guys to
the bottom of the sea right—
You guys are the definition of "all talk"!
Move!
What?!
To keep the ship from blowing out
Everyone says once they set their
sights on you, you're doomed.
of the water with three barrels
of cola energy sent to the bow,
I have no need for fishmen,
mermaids, or gloves!
Now we're gonna be rich!
we pump two barrels of Coup de Burst
into the stern at the same time.
Look what happened to Hachi after
he always came to save you!
Their boss is a guy in
an iron mask named Duval.
If you want to run, then get out of here!
It popped out of the ground! Cool!
You're not gonna get away, Camie!
This baby burns through
cola, so I rarely use it.
I'm a starfish!
No one knows what he looks
like under the mask.
I hear he's searching for someone,
I'm not in the human trade
because I want to be.
Amazing!
so he checks every ship that goes by here.
I'm stuck in the net!
I told you!
You all know that very well, don't you?
Damn that agile mermaid!
Camie! Pappug!
I'm on!
I'm almost there, Sanji-chin! Hang on!
Bastards!
Of course, Head!
It's not popping.
Sounds like a pain in the neck.
That looks fun!
Camie-chan did nothing wrong!
Well, anyway, Camie, don't worry.
Today is a joyous day.
Wait, Sanji-kun!
We'll save the takoyaki!
The man I have wanted to kill
so badly that I dreamed about it
These bubbles really are mysterious.
He's a takoyaki maker!
Camie!
Okay! Thanks, Luffy-chin!
How do they work?
Thank goodness! Is Sanji okay?!
is right in front of me!
The roots of Hustle Muscle Mangroves
secret a special natural resin.
All right, then!
I'm so grateful! There truly is a God!
I'm coming to save you, Camie!
Everyone, it looks bad!
Sanji-chin lost a lot of blood!
Brook, play something to cheer everyone up!
What?
The man who showed up that day and
plunged me into the depths of Hell...
With pleasure!
They got him?
I thought I'd saved him, but then a
bunch of blood flew from his nose...
Gross! It's all sticky!
Wha— A nosebleed?
Hey, does it look like he's
talking in our direction?
Don't wipe it on me!
That resin expands into bubbles
when the roots breathe.
On this day, here and now,
even if I go down as well,
Forget it. Just let him die there.
It's okay. We'll set Hachi free, too.
What?
Yeah. He looks happy, anyway.
I get it...
Hachi's all right. He's actually harmless.
I will kill you!
So that's how they float up to the sky.
Hang in there, Sanji-chin!
The pirate, "Black Foot" Sanji!
Am I in heaven?
So this scenery is all natural?
Besides...
This isn't what we promised Camie.
Damn... That bastard is alive?
Hey!
I have so longed to see you.
Whoa, Luffy! When did you get up that high?!
N-Nami-san...
You've lost a lot of men now.
Crap! The Head's really mad now!
That strong-willed attitude
of yours is beautiful!
I can see an amusement park over there!
Let's go! I wanna ride the ferris wheel!
Curse you!
Huh? He wants to kill me?
Hey, Nami!
An amusement park?!
You sure?
Then I'll show you what makes
Motobalo so terrifying!
Yeah.
That's Sabaody Park.
Luffy!
Sanji, who's that guy?
A ferris wheel sounds fun...
To this day, countless men have
fallen victim to these tough horns.
If it's okay with you, we have no choice.
Does he have some kind of grudge against you?
It was always my dream to ride one.
We'll save the octopus, too.
Maybe it's from when you
worked at the restaurant?
Hey! Your eyes are takoyaki!
Your dream? Why don't you just ride one?
These horns even tore a
hole in the village dam!
Try to remember!
Don't be a fool! You can't, Camie!
That was three years ago...
Put him in a cage, and he'll bust out!
Yeah, I know.
All I ever did back then
was piss people off...
H-Huh?
It was thanks to his horns that I managed
to escape my Navy pursuers with my life!
Hey! There's trouble!
Just get shot! You'd get what you deserve!
I want to ride it, too... Can I not?
People call them "Heart-smashing Horns"!
What is it, Camie?
Don't you play dumb, Black Foot!
The fish said sorry, but this
is as far as they'll go.
It was just recently!
All right. I'll stop him.
What? What's going on?
Are you ready,
Watch it! Get down! They're harpoons!
There they are! The Flying Fish Riders!
Go, Motobalo!
I'm really high up!
But if it was recent, I'm even more stumped.
Flying Fish Riders?
Look out, Luffy!
Where? I don't see anything.
What is that? Something's
weird about these harpoons...
What's going on?
Camie! Where are you going?
The horns had nothing to do with it!
They're suddenly popping!
These are Scorpion's Poison harpoons.
You have to hide!
Fighting you is a waste of time!
No! Not in the sea! They're in the sky!
If one pierces you, you'll
be dead in three minutes.
Of course! Anytime!
Gum-Gum...
Feel my wrath!
Pistol!
Nami-san, look out!
And one more!
Luffy-chin!
Oh, no! Are you okay?!
Damn that bastard! I can't remember!
Hey... What's wrong, Motobalo?
It's fine, Camie-chan.
He has powers?!
Who are you?!
His cow's acting weird.
The fish are flying!
No need to worry about him.
I'll murder you and your whole crew!
Cool!
A Straw Hat?!
This isn't the time to be impressed!
I saw him without his mask.
Damn! They're attacking!
That bastard!
You did? Who is he?
Do flying fish fly like that?!
Luffy-chin!
You did it!
Don't be too surprised.
It's a face you know, too.
All right! I got 'em back!
What?
It fainted?
Me?
Hey! Did you see?
Man, I was really stuck!
What happened?
Yeah! There's no mistake!
It's the Straw Hats!
Thank you, Straw Hat! I owe you one!
Luffy, what did you do?
See?
Contact the boss!
Roger!
I didn't do anything!
By the way, Hachi, what did
we come to this island for?
Zoro! Cut the rope holding up the cage!
We came to nab one mermaid,
but this is a huge catch!
Motobalo! How could this be, damn it?!
That fool!
You said something about a
coating for the ship earlier.
Duval-sama is gonna be quaking with joy!
Got it!
Right. We'll go see a coating craftsman
Luffy didn't shoot anything at him.
Straw Hat! Be careful!
It looked like he just intimidated him.
Duval-sama's iron mask!
and have your ship coated in resin.
You're right in their trap!
They're coming back!
Stay away!
The Flying Fish Riders have
you surrounded from the air!
In simple terms, that'll allow
your ship to go underwater.
What does that mean? He
won by pure intensity?
That giant thing just passed out!
That's fine. Take a good
look at my scarred face.
For real?
Get them!
That's the only way you humans
can get to Fishman Island.
Is that possible?
Yes, sir!
Curse you Straw Hats!
Wha— Huh?!
No way...
Bombs?!
But if you get an unskilled
coating craftsman,
What?!
Bastards!
Luffy-chin!
Gum-Gum...
Wait just a minute, Luffy.
the ship and its passengers will be
crushed underwater, and that's the end.
72 Pound...
Whether it's from the sea
or the sky, bring it on!
-Pistol! -Cannon!
I know just one craftsman that you
can trust, so I'll take you to him.
I'll go nuts on 'em!
Sanji, I'm glad you're okay.
This all happened because
of false accusations.
Boys!
When all is said and done,
the octopus is a good man.
That was close!
He's...
Be careful! Those flying fish can
fly for five minutes out of water!
I'll finish it.
No, a good octopus!
Wow.
Oh, my...
Finish it?
Black Foot, so long as you live as a pirate,
Damn!
In exchange...
Yes, there's no mistake,
Duval-sama! It's them!
I could cry!
I want you to keep one promise for me.
I have waited for this day.
I will never live in peace!
It's battle time!
Right. Right... What?!
Sure! What is it?
After I decided to kill
you, I took to the seas.
I've had enough of being
persecuted for nothing!
Sometimes, there are World
Nobles walking around in town.
Go back! We're withdrawing for now!
Yeah!
Shut up.
But searching for you was not easy.
What? Don't be stupid!
I never wanted to see the
scribble on that wanted flyer.
World Nobles?
Duval-sama's orders!
You look nothing like your
wanted flyers, after all.
Damn it! We'll have to move while we can!
Damn... Just when it was about to get good!
Who are they?
It wasn't supposed to exist in real life!
Residents of the holy land Marie Jois.
Even if the Navy or bounty hunters saw
you, they might totally overlook you!
Get Camie back!
Hmm...
Then you should die!
Yeah!
So, what about them?
Camie! Pappug! It's dangerous, so stay back!
No matter what may happen in town,
Huh?
No, that's not true.
Œil!
Stretch! You can do it, Luffy-chin!
Go! Go!
What happened?
Nez!
They do find you!
Joue! Bouche! Dents!
Macro.
promise me that you will
not defy the World Nobles.
Come on, flying fish!
Yes, Master Duval?
Head...
Menton!
It seems the mermaid you lured
out is on a pirate ship.
Go! Go!
Huh?
They find you, and they say...
P-Please, no more!
What? Camie's on a pirate ship?!
"I found you,
No matter what happens?
Parage...
They're coming!
You mean...
Black Foot Sanji!"
Right!
Shot!
I've been waiting. I've been waiting so long.
Understand?
And then I tell them...
Even if someone is killed before your eyes,
That pirate ship is the
one I've been waiting for.
you must pretend you saw nothing.
"I don't know who that is!"
I'll say it once more.
"I'm not even a pirate!"
I'll kill him.
You must pretend
I'll kill the man who ruined my life!
you saw nothing!
Enjoy the fine flavors produced
by a weave of supreme techniques,
Stop screwing around!
you bastard.
The Sunny's in trouble!
Attention!
I found you, "Black Foot" Sanji!
The Sabaody Archipelago is fun!
Camie, run! It's a trap!
I'll teach you clueless people
how to get to Fishman Island!
We're gonna get sunk!
There's so much stuff I've never seen before!
Does he know you, Sanji?
The voice we heard, and that silhouette...
Hey, relax! This week, I'm the
most super I've ever been!
Hey! Here comes someone
wearing a bubble on his head!
That man ruined my life!
First, you have to get a coating
on this ship at a certain island!
Hey, what do you think?
Huh? Oh! So it was him?
There's a dog with a bubble on its head, too!
He really has it in for you.
That island is—
I'll show you the Sunny's true power!
Look! That's the island!
Oh, no! Everyone get on your knees!
Go to hell!
Now that we know that, there's no
way we're saving you, you octopus!
Cool! A bubble!
Don't look them in the eyes!
Hey, I was still talking...
Wow! The Sunny is amazing!
What did you do, Sanji?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Tyranny! The Roles of Sabaody,
the Celestial Dragons"
"Unleash the Sunny's Super Secret
Weapon, the Gaon Cannon!"
"Tragedy! The Truth Hidden
Behind Duval's Mask!"
"The Fated Reunion! Save
the Imprisoned Fishman!"
"Landing on the Way to Fishman
Island! The Sabaody Archipelago!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!