Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around
the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
As Luffy and his friends continued their
voyage in search of Fishman Island,
they finally reached the Red Line,
the halfway point of the Grand Line.
It's the Red Line!
I can't see the top...
It's huge!
So this is the Red Line...
Anyway, we're halfway there now!
But the towering Red Line blocked their way,
and they lost their path to Fishman Island.
I know which way we need to go, but
I don't know the means to get there.
Gum-Gum Rifle!
It spit something out.
Huh? A fish?
It... It couldn't be!
Stuck at a dead end with no options,
Luffy and his friends met Camie the
mermaid and Pappug the starfish.
"Hatred for the Straw Hats!
Iron Mask Duval Appears!"
Are you okay? You're not hurt, are you?
Sure...
That surprised me! Look at all the humans!
Wh-What?
We're the one who're surprised!
Thanks for saving me when
I was about to be digested.
I'm such an easy target
for sea monsters to eat...
That was about the twentieth time.
You get eaten too much!
I need to do something to thank you.
I know! Would you like some takoyaki?
Takoyaki?! That's my favorite!
Really? Okay, that'll be
500 Berries per person!
What?!
You're trying to sell 'em?!
I messed up!
Mermaid! Mermaid!
Yes! The most admired of
all races, the mermaid!
The jewel of the sea, the mermaid!
And yes! I got to meet one of them!
She's so cute!
It's my first time meeting a mermaid!
You're name's Camie-chan?!
It's not your first time.
You met the old woman Kokoro, didn't you?
Thriller Bark?
No, that doesn't scare
me. It doesn't scare me!
If you want to know what scared
me the most in my life, it was...
Uh, sorry, Sanji! Pretend I didn't say that!
It's your first time seeing a mermaid!
You guys are rude!
Huh? The old woman Kokoro was a mermaid?
But she was walking.
Oh, that's right, you didn't know.
It was while you were fighting Lucci.
Don't you...
...die!
I really don't want to think
of Kokoro as a mermaid.
You're too blunt!
That hurt! What'd you do that for, Nami?!
I swear, when it comes to guys and
their desires toward mermaids...
She is quite a cute mermaid, though.
This is my first time
meeting a mermaid, as well.
Pardon me, but would you lend me some money?
Why should she?!
A skeleton!
Look at that! How could
you scare her?! Go away!
I can open my head, too. Fun, right?
Damn little...
How fun!
She's quick to accept people...
By the way, do you poop?
What are you asking her?!
Sure, I—
She does not!
She really doesn't!
Camie, Camie?
That's strange. Aren't you missing someone?
What's missing from that
little circle of fun?
The answer is me.
Oh, yeah, I've been wondering.
Hey, Camie, what's this talking glove thing?
Sorry, I totally forgot.
That's my pet, Pappug. He's
a starfish, and my master.
Master?
Yep. My master.
This thing?
Yep!
Nice to meet ya!
Do starfish talk?
Isn't it weird to have a
pet that's your master?
I let her keep me as a
pet. I've got my reasons.
Camie always gives me clams...
Food, eh?
"Are you a person?" I'm
a starfish, not a person.
What a brute!
I'm not a person, I'm a starfish.
"Are you busy?"
No, no!
I've got plenty of hands.
Yay! Thank you!
Laugh! This is where you laugh!
So, this T-shirt is by
a brand called Criminal.
It's all the rage on Fishman Island.
Wow!
It's so cool!
Pappug is the designer.
I want to be a designer someday, too.
You could totally be one, Camie-chan!
Thank you, Sanji-chin!
Nobody's listening...
Hey, how can you talk, anyway?
That's a very good question!
He got over that quick.
When I was little, I mistakenly
thought I was a person.
By the time I realized I was a starfish,
I could already speak human language.
You can learn to talk because of that?
It's scary when you get on a roll!
That momentum drives the world!
So anyway, I'm Pappug the starfish.
I'm an up-and-coming designer.
Thanks for saving us!
I'm glad we met you, actually.
We had just lost our way,
and I wanted to ask—
Hey, Nami! Takoyaki comes first!
Oh, right. I wanted to
repay you with takoyaki.
Then we'll have to meet up
with Hatchin somewhere...
Hatchin?
Ring ring ring... Ring ring ring...
Ring ring ring... Click.
Hello, Hatchin? It's Camie!
Sorry we got separated. Where are you now?
Hey! Is that Camie I hear?
Hatchin?
You don't know who I am? I'm not Hachi.
What?! You're not Hatchin?!
I'm Macro! The very same one,
from the Dopey Macro Pirates!
Hey, I just said it myself...
Sounds like there's some trouble.
Why do you have Hatchin's Transponder Snail?
Because I beat up that Hachi punk, of course!
You're lying! Hatchin would
never lose to you guys!
Yeah, normally we're no match for Hachi,
but this time, we've teamed up
with the Flying Fish Riders!
The Flying Fish Riders?!
Camie, you're okay? Thank goodness.
Hatchin! Did they really beat you?
They sort of caught me off guard...
But you mustn't come here!
I'll wreak a little havoc and be
back home soon, so it'll be fine.
Hatchin...
Hey, Camie, I'm about to sell off your buddy!
Octopus fishmen are rare,
so he's worth a fortune!
If you want to come save
him, you're welcome to.
We're five kilometers east of Grove
#44 in the Sabaody Archipelago,
at the hideout of the kidnapping
gang, the Flying Fish Riders.
No! Camie, don't come!
Shut up, you octopus!
Bye, now.
Hatchin...
Hey...
Camie-chan...
So, where's the takoyaki?
Is this really the time?!
Wait a minute...
The voice of that "Hatchin" guy on the
Transponder Snail sounded familiar...
I must be imagining it. Surely it's not...
Sorry, Luffy-chin.
Can I treat you to takoyaki some other time?
I have to go save my friend right away.
Aww...
Hey!
Hang on, Camie.
I don't mean to butt in, but if you
want to save your friend, we'll help.
Oh, my mistake. I meant these guys will help!
You little...!
So, what say you tell us how to
get to Fishman Island in exchange?
Really? Are you sure, Nami-chin?
Of course!
Right, Luffy?
Huh? Yeah.
You'll help me rescue Hatchin, Luffy-chin?!
Sure, but who's Hatchin, anyway?
He owns the takoyaki place where I work!
His takoyaki is the best in the world!
Well, that's an important matter!
Okay, boys! We're gonna rescue the
takoyaki if it means our lives!
Yeah!
Takoyaki! Takoyaki!
They agreed. Do you know where he is?
Yeah... Um...
Grove #44 is the easternmost
island in the archipelago.
And he's five kilometers east of that...
So the Flying Fish Riders'
hideout is around here.
And we're right here,
so it's a straight shot from
here to the Sabaody Archipelago.
Let's start heading west!
From there, we can ask
the fish for directions.
Yeah, sounds good. Let's hurry!
Hey!
Wow! The fish are sticking their heads out!
I need you to give me directions!
They're afraid of the Flying Fish Riders,
so they'll take us as far as
the vicinity of their hideout.
That's amazing! You can talk to fish!
I had no idea mermaids could do that!
Camie, with you around, we'd
have all the fish we could eat!
Watch your mouth! I oughta kill you!
But how can we follow fish
if they're underwater?
Just watch.
Awesome!
Is that even possible? I can't believe it!
The fish are making an
arrow on the water for us!
That's great! So we just have to follow that!
You're pretty amazing, Camie!
Aww, I still have a long way to go.
Nah, I'm really impressed!
All right! I'll steer!
To four o'clock.
Got it!
Let's go, boys!
Yeah!
So you see, Master Duval, I've
lured a mermaid toward us.
Yes, all is going as planned.
Understood. Hey, you guys.
Yes, Head.
Go out and meet her.
Roger.
U-Um...
She's valuable merchandise,
so please try not to harm her.
How encouraging...
Hey, Hachi! Your Camie is finished this time!
Well? Are you ready for that?
Oh, at a loss for words, are you?
Hey, Zoro.
Setting sail already? You're
not going to Fishman Island?
Forget about that, just check her out!
She's Camie, a mermaid. A
real mermaid! She's awesome!
Hello.
A mermaid?
First one I've ever seen.
He erased it! He just erased the memory!
We're just gonna make a little
detour to save her takoyaki friend.
I'm worried, though. Hatchin sounded so weak.
I know they've done something awful to him.
Well, he's pretty tough. He'll be fine.
More importantly, you guys
accepted this task so easily.
Are you that confident in your skills?
Yep! We're strong!
Just so you know, there are several
kidnapping gangs operating around here.
The human trade is a booming business
in the Sabaody Archipelago.
They buy and sell humans?
That's nasty business.
Mermaids are sold at particularly high costs,
so the three Macro Pirates are
constantly out to kidnap Camie.
Hachi the takoyaki shop owner
probably doesn't realize we
were eaten by that sea monster,
and thinks we were taken
by the Macro Pirates,
which would be why he went after them.
That's probably right.
Hatchin is very kind and upright.
It's my fault.
Hearing about octopus and "Hachi"
makes me think of that idiot fishman.
If it's really him, I'm not saving him.
Okay, I guess that's not true.
Normally, Hachi would wipe
the floor with them easily,
but if the infamous Flying
Fish Riders are involved...
What are they?
They're a kidnapping gang that's been
throwing their weight around in this area lately.
Everyone says once they set their
sights on you, you're doomed.
Their boss is a guy in
an iron mask named Duval.
No one knows what he looks
like under the mask.
I hear he's searching for someone,
so he checks every ship that goes by here.
Sounds like a pain in the neck.
Well, anyway, Camie, don't worry.
We'll save the takoyaki!
He's a takoyaki maker!
Okay! Thanks, Luffy-chin!
All right, then!
Brook, play something to cheer everyone up!
With pleasure!
H-Huh?
Hey! There's trouble!
What is it, Camie?
The fish said sorry, but this
is as far as they'll go.
What? What's going on?
There they are! The Flying Fish Riders!
Where? I don't see anything.
Camie! Where are you going?
You have to hide!
No! Not in the sea! They're in the sky!
The fish are flying!
Cool!
This isn't the time to be impressed!
Damn! They're attacking!
Do flying fish fly like that?!
Hey! Did you see?
Yeah! There's no mistake!
It's the Straw Hats!
Contact the boss!
Roger!
We came to nab one mermaid,
but this is a huge catch!
Duval-sama is gonna be quaking with joy!
They're coming back!
Stay away!
Bombs?!
Bastards!
Gum-Gum...
72 Pound...
-Pistol! -Cannon!
That was close!
Be careful! Those flying fish can
fly for five minutes out of water!
Damn!
Yes, there's no mistake,
Duval-sama! It's them!
Right. Right... What?!
Go back! We're withdrawing for now!
What? Don't be stupid!
Duval-sama's orders!
Damn... Just when it was about to get good!
What happened?
Macro.
Yes, Master Duval?
It seems the mermaid you lured
out is on a pirate ship.
What? Camie's on a pirate ship?!
I've been waiting. I've been waiting so long.
That pirate ship is the
one I've been waiting for.
I'll kill him.
I'll kill the man who ruined my life!
Camie, run! It's a trap!
The voice we heard, and that silhouette...
Hey, what do you think?
Huh? Oh! So it was him?
Now that we know that, there's no
way we're saving you, you octopus!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Fated Reunion! Save
the Imprisoned Fishman!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!