Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Luffy...
Help me...
Don't make our navigator cry!
Gum-Gum...
...Pinwheel!!
What the... What the...
People with Devil Fruit
powers can't swim.
Though, even people without
powers would sink in this situation.
He's gonna throw him into the sea?!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Darn you!
--Luffy!!
--Damn you!
This is bad... I'm out of strength...
"Luffy Submerged!
Zoro vs. Hatchan the Octopus"
What do you think?
Isn't this a pretty fun game?
How many minutes will
that rubber man last?
Or will you guys die before that?
This isn't good, Johnny.
Big Bro Luffy is in big trouble...
He can't help himself now!
We'll defeat him in five seconds.
Luffy! I'll come rescue you right away!
Hachi Ink Jet!
My hair! You bastard! I'm gonna...
...forgive you since it's just hair
and it's gonna grow back.
--Huh?
--Roronoa Zoro!
You can't cut me
because I have six hands.
--Go ahead and cut me if you can!
--You Octo-Man!
Hachi's... Triple... Sword... Catch!
Ouch!
I don't have time to play with you!
He throws me out of whack!
Could he possibly...
If you're not paying attention,
you'll shorten your life!
Fish shouldn't go against a cook!
We're running out of time... No time...
Go down already!
Hachi Suckers!
So what?! Come down already!
You damn octopus!
That octopus bastard!
He's moving wobbly and slowly!
But then, if he goes
into the sea now,
he'll be dragged to
the bottom of the sea.
But at this rate,
Big Bro Luffy's going to die!
We have to do something about it!
--Yeah!
--Wait!
Ouch!!
What're you going to do in
the sea with such serious injuries?
You can't do much like that.
If you're talking about that rubber
young man, I'll go and rescue him.
Y-You will?
Whether we can save
that young man or not
is probably what will
decide this fight, right?
I can tell that, too.
Gen-san!
--I'll go, too!
Me, too!
No! If many of us go
and take time rescuing him,
the fishmen will notice and it will
cause these people trouble, if anything.
Gen-san!
It'll be pointless if we end up
putting a crimp in their fight.
So I'll do it alone.
That's okay with you two, right?
Sorry... Thank you!
I'll leave it to you.
Sorry, but please be quick.
Wait!
Gen-san, I'll go, too.
Nojiko, you're injured!
Those guys're fighting
for my little sister!
Gen-san!
Okay. Come with me.
--Let's hurry!
--Okay!
I'm sorry...
If only we were a little stronger...
Please save... Big Bro...
You damn fish man!
Roronoa Zoro! Do you mind if I ask
you a question? You don't, right?
I heard you use the Three Swords Style.
Why are you using only one sword?
You're already losing
big with one sword!
Sh-Shut up! I'm not fighting seriously!
Actually, there's a reason that
a human swordsman can't defeat me.
Wanna hear what it is?
You wanna hear it, right?
When you hear it, you'll be
surprised, scared, blown away!
Dammit! I can't be in pain right now!
My fever's getting worse, too!
I thought it would come down
while I was moving around, but...
Just as I thought, the wounds...
...from your fight with Hawk-Eye are...
Big Bro!
What're you doing?
Are you trying to fake
illness or something?
I won't fall for that. Roronoa Zoro!
Just check out my true form!
Look! This is my true form!
Here comes Hachi,
user of the Six Swords Style!
Hey! That's not where you're
supposed to fall! Don't mock me!
--Ah! Big Bro!
--So he was bearing the pain!
Yeah. His injuries would
kill a normal person
or leave them bedridden for half a year!
What?!
I thought something was strange.
He looked as if nothing had happened
right after that fierce fight.
Is he an idiot or what?!
I thought I warned you
to pay attention.
I have a fortieth dan
in Fishman Karate.
Wh-What? Someone went flying?!
B-Big Bro?!
Big Bro Cook!
Ahh...
Big Bro Cook!!
He's been taken care of, Arlong-san.
What do we do with Roronoa Zoro?
Just ditch him in the sea.
What weaklings... How boring!
That's all?
Geez, they sure did
a lot of damage, though.
It's no big deal.
Arlong Park can't be destroyed
by this kind of damage.
Indeed...
How dare you, Roronoa Zoro!
You died from shock before I,
the great swordsman, could attack you?!
You could have left your name
in history if you died at least
after receiving my
Six Swords Style attack.
Well, no matter how you struggle or
even if the world is turned upside down,
you humans can't even give a
scratch to me, wielder of six swords!
Stop it, Hachi. I know how you feel,
but if you really go on a
rampage we'll be in trouble.
Are you going to destroy Arlong Park?
Oh! Ahh...
N-no... Sorry.
I got too worked up...
Don't get carried away.
You're right. Sorry.
The Six Swords Style, huh?
What a joke!
Big Bro!!
Roronoa Zoro!
I'll tell you one thing, octopus.
There's a man I need to meet up with.
Until I see him again...
...my life can't be taken away
even by Death himself!
Damn that Long-nose! What speed!
That guy's face and ability
to run away aren't human!
If I keep one of the Arlong Pirates
leaders away like this,
it should be beneficial to Luffy
and the other's fights.
Good job, Usopp-sama!
How considerate you are towards them!
Though it just happened
to turn out that way...
Whoa, as I expected,
he isn't catching up.
Darn. This isn't good.
Looks like I've got quite a lead.
Fishmen are just turtles
on land, after all.
He's far behind in no time.
Turtles... huh?
Hey! Hey! Turtle! You slow turtle!
Keep up with me if you can!
I'll outrun you again right away!
You waddling turtle!
Aren't you the one
who'll have to waddle?
Ughhhhh!
Stop, you bastard!
He drank quite a bit of water.
We need to bring him up
soon or it'll be too late.
Dammit! I guess I can't
break it in the sea.
The buoyancy is too strong.
Gen-san, hurry up.
No good. I can't smash the rock.
An oxygen cylinder would be helpful
but we don't have time to go get it.
And we can't carry him up
along with the rock, either...
Oh, yeah!
Hm? Ahh!
That man's still alive!!
Big Bro! Big Bro Cook!!
That fishman's punch was
a fortieth dan punch? I see...
Then those kicks I used to take all
the time from that damn geezer
are four-hundredth dan kicks.
What is it, Roronoa Zoro?
I'm not sure what's going on,
but you look like you're in pain.
You think you can defeat my
Six Swords Style in that condition?
Everyone in the whole world
thinks the same way.
That's none of your business.
Big Bro's in really bad shape!
He's probably got a
fever from his wounds
and must be barely conscious.
If those wounds open up,
he's definitely going to die!
But it's no time to think
about things like that!
Yeah! He's the only one who can
break through this situation!
I'll show you the Three Swords Style.
Yosaku! Johnny!
Let me use your swords!
--Of course!
--Big Bro! Catch these!!
Darn! I feel like
I'm about to pass out.
I wonder how long
I can keep standing...
Big Bro! We threw our swords!
You said you wanted to
use them! Catch them!
Ha! I'll show you the wall that you
humans with two arms can't surpass!
Six Swords Style!
Big Bro! Watch out!!
Tentacle-Sword Overload!
Big Bro!!
Three Sword Style!
Streaming Wolf-Swords!
He did it!
He handled the six-sword
random hits! He's really amazing!!
What concentration!
What spiritual strength!
Ahh... How dare you have
the impudence to do such a thing!
I'm really mad, you son of a bitch!
I'm gonna kill you!
If you just think about it,
you should know!
I can hold six swords, so there's
no way you can defeat me
when you can hold only
three swords! Isn't that right?!
Just think about it?
What a big miscalculation.
What do you bear on your shoulders?
What do you desire once
you've obtained power?
I'm going to get stronger for her, too!
I'm going to get strong enough
that my name reaches to Heaven!
I'm going to be the world's
strongest swordsman!
Whether it's three swords...
or six swords...
...it doesn't matter!
Your sword and my sword
carry different weight!
Weight, you said?
I see. So your swords are heavy.
But my swords weigh at
least 300 kilos per sword
though they may not look like it.
They weigh a lot more than you
humans' swords, you bastard!
There's no point in
discussing with an idiot.
Six Swords Style!
Octopus Pot Stance!
New Year's...
...Open!
Body Slam!
That's dirty! He hit him
right in his wounds!
That'll show you!
--Big Bro!!
--He's gonna die!!
I won't let you land
while you're still alive!
Six Sword Ultimate Technique!
Waltz of Six Swords!
You'll be mincemeat if you touch it
even for a second! Become mincemeat!
Big Bro!!
What?!
Ow!
Big Bro!!
That bastard! He rolled on
my swords adjusting to the spin!
On top of that, he gave me
a free hand cutting service!
How dare he make fun of me!
I'm not a circus acrobat!
I'm completely angry now!
I won't let him get away!
I'm gonna really kill him good!
Big Bro... he looks like
he's in a lot of pain...
His wounds might've
opened with that attack.
Ahh... If I could, I'd wanna
take his place for him...
Even if it's an injury that knocks
ordinary people out, I must not fall.
Six Swords Style!
Octopus Pot Stance!
It's all over!
Even if it's an injury that kills
ordinary people, I must not die!
New Year's...
In order to defeat the
extraordinarily strong Hawk-Eye,
I can't just be ordinary!
Dragon Twister!!
Hachi...
How could I be... defeated by...
the Three Swords Style?
Octo-Man...
You now know the difference between
the weight in our swords, right?
Are you happy now?
I cried as much as I wanted.
I've whined enough, too.
And I'm resolved as well!
I have to go. Everyone's fighting!
Sorry, but I don't care
about that Octo-Man.
I have to hurry up and rescue Luffy...
Big Bro! Watch out!!
How dare you beat Hachi!
You...
You sure did send me flying!
Oh? I didn't know there was someone
in the East Blue who
could survive my fist.
There're probably many...
especially at a certain restaurant.
You sure take me lightly, don't you?
B-Big Bro! That's reckless!
Hey, stop it!
You'll die if you go into the
sea with wounds like that!
Shut up! He's at his limit!
There's no time to wait
until your fight is over!
Yeah, I know.
There's no time to waste
any more. I know that much.
I'm trying to stop you when
I'm fully aware of that!
You just shut up, you damn idiot!
You can't complain if I do this, right?!
This is interesting!
He wants to fight against me,
a fishman, in the water?
He's a real idiot!
That's reckless! Fighting in
the water is what they want!
If I remember correctly,
he's from Cocoyashi Village...
His neck! Luffy's neck is stretched!
Sorry, I'm not strong enough
to pull the whole body.
Spit out water with your neck stretched.
Please at least breathe!
Come back to life!
I hope it's not too late!
I'd better hurry up before I
can't hold my breath any more.
I see... He can't break the rock,
but if Luffy's neck is stretched above
the water, he can at least breathe.
Which means if I kick and break that
rock, I can leave the rest to that man.
Fishman Karate... Forearm Sledge!
Realize... that you all are mere humans!
Come back to life!
Please... hurry!
This guy's persistent! Ughhh!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Ughhh!
Dammit! That topknot bastard!
He's attacking me from behind!
This isn't good!
But in order to rescue Luffy...
Even if I'm at a disadvantage,
I'll beat him up for sure!
It's all for Nami-san.
So that's what you're
thinking after all!
Waaaah!!
Shut up!!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Proud Warriors!
Sanji and Usopp's Fierce Battles"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!