High Tide
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around
the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
During their voyage to Fishman Island,
Luffy and his friends fought a fierce battle
against Duval and the Flying Fish Riders.
Curse you Straw Hats!
In response to Duval's unjustified hatred,
Sanji's outrage reached its peak.
Œil!
Nez!
Joue! Bouche! Dents!
Menton!
Parage...
Shot!
"Landing on the Way to Fishman
Island! The Sabaody Archipelago!"
Head! Head!
Where are you?!
Head!
Are you all right, Head?!
He's...
Damn, he's all beat up.
Head, are you alive?
Head!
Damn it...
I finally had Black Foot
right where I wanted him!
Huh? What is it?
Why are you all gawking at me?
Head, please stay calm and look at this.
Th-This is... Wh-Wha—
What happened to me?!
Yum!
Mmm, this is great!
See? Hatchin's takoyaki is
the best in the world, right?
I can't stop! I can't put them down!
This takoyaki is incredible!
Ow! Hot! Hot! Hot!
It really is good. What is this stuff?
The deep flavor of this sauce...
And it's impressive that he
runs the business from a ship.
This is my first experience
with the culture of takoyaki.
It is delicious!
I could stuff my cheeks with this!
Uh, not that I have cheeks...
You can eat all you like for free today!
This is to thank you all for saving us.
These are made with broth,
and these have mochi in them.
Careful, they're hot!
So...
How about you, um... Nami?
Er, um... H-How does it taste?
This doesn't mean I'm going
to forgive you for anything.
No, of course not! That's not why I asked!
I really just wondered how
you liked the taste...
Nami...
They're really tasty!
I see, I see!
I'm glad! I'm so glad to hear that!
Okay, you guys, eat up! Have all you like!
Yeah! Keep 'em coming!
We'll eat every last one!
Hey! You guys!
Young Master!
Who's that?
That voice...
Wait up!
You can't leave without saying goodbye!
Who's that?
I'm Handsome— Oh, my mistake.
I'm Duval!
Is that what he looked like?
I altered his bone structure.
Now he can't complain to me again.
Wow, Master Black Foot!
When I woke up after you kicked the
crap out of me, were we ever surprised!
You made me this handsome!
I'm just enchanted!
The ladies won't be able ignore this!
This is truly...
seeing life through rose-colored lenses!
I'd love to head straight back
to the country and relax,
but if I left without thanking my saviors,
I wouldn't be able to sleep at night!
It's your first time in these waters, right?
If there's any way we can help
you, just ask us anything!
Don't wink if you're not used to it.
Well, if you have no complaints,
that's enough for me.
If I were to request something, it'd be
that you never show up around us aga—
Beautiful. Too beautiful.
Are you listening?!
I should ride a white horse.
Hey, you!
Head, Head! You need to listen!
Oh, right...
What? Handsome?
I didn't say anything like that!
Want me to make you look
like that scribble again?!
I'm embarrassed, but I accept...
your blown kiss!
Whoo, whoo!
I didn't blow a kiss! I just
wiped sauce off my lips!
What kind of optimistic
delusion are you seeing?!
Oh, mirror, mirror! Is the
most handsome man of all me?
A single-choice quiz?!
We get that you're handsome,
but you were dumb to start
with, so you're still hopeless.
Ah. You're jealous?
I am not!
Don't bother, Usopp! You're
no match for his personality!
Well, Young Master, this is
my Transponder Snail number.
Call me anytime!
I'll definitely help you all out!
I really caused you a lot of trouble.
Sorry you all got mixed up in this.
Just stop winking.
Bye, now!
Let's go, Rosy Life Riders!
Yes, Handsome!
So leave already.
Whew, thanks for the feast!
Man, I'm stuffed! This is bliss!
That was tasty!
I can't eat any more...
I'm exhausted.
You guys sure eat a lot.
I should've expected that of the Straw Hats.
I wish I had six more arms.
Good work, Hatchin.
Looks like everyone is happy.
Are they? Then I'm happy, too.
It's been a wonderful afternoon, Master.
I'm also more than happy with
my first takoyaki experience.
Ah, pardon me.
Everything about that is disgusting!
Hey, octopus and starfish and Camie-chan!
If you're taking a break,
come up to the deck.
I'll serve you tea, too.
Sure!
This tea is delicious.
We're on the right path.
Our destination is the Sabaody Archipelago.
Do we have to go there
to get to Fishman Island?
We fishmen and mermaids can
get there easily by diving,
but you're humans, so if you
dive, the pressure will kill you.
Yeah, we barely held out
even in the submarine.
The hull seems to be creaking...
Yes, because...
We're more than 5,000 meters under.
Ah, so that's why.
Wait! That's a bad idea!
The pressure will crush us!
How are we gonna get to
the bottom of the sea?
Okay, attention!
It looks like you guys don't have a clue,
so I'll tell you all you need
to know about these seas.
What? Who's going to do that?
That would be...
Me!
Huh?
Um, please listen...
As I was saying, there are two routes
that can take you to the new world.
But for outlaws like you
guys, only one is possible.
Why?
Because...
One of them, at the request
of the World Government,
involves crossing the city built on top
of the Red Line, the holy land Marie Jois.
What?
Naturally, there's no way they'd grant
permission for pirates to cross.
We'd have to walk over the Red Line?
What would we do with the ship, then?
You'd have to abandon your ship and
buy a similar one on the other side.
Abandon the ship?!
Yeah. It costs money, and
getting permission takes time,
but it's safe, so that's what most do.
However!
For the route you'll take,
you can keep your ship!
It's called...
The Sea Floor Route Via Fishman Island!
But the Sea Floor Route has many dangers.
Huh? Camie? Camie?
What do you mean?
I didn't pass you the baton...
Many ships that use it are eaten
whole by sea monsters and sea kings.
Camie? Camie?
I see. That is dangerous.
Can you hear me?
You see?
I don't think I want to
go to Fishman Island...
Me, either...
Hang on, Camie. Did you say
ships have been eaten whole?
Huh? Yeah.
What kind of ship do we use
to get to the sea floor?
This ship.
What?
Hey, this ship can't go underwater.
No, it'll be fine.
And that big wall that goes
around the world, the Red Line,
has a small hole in just one spot.
Oh, it's a big hole from
our perspective, though.
That's where Fishman Island is!
It's basically directly below Marie Jois.
You dive about 10,000
meters down to get there.
That far?
It's a great place!
I think the sky island was 10,000
meters in the air, too...
But how do we get to the
sea floor in this ship?
You'll get a coating on your ship
at the island we're heading to now.
A coating?
You'll see once it's on.
All right, look ahead!
We're here, everyone!
Wow! It's beautiful!
What is that?!
There's stuff flying around...
My goodness!
It's like a fantasy.
Bubbles?
This is...
The Sabaody Archipelago!
Awesome!
There are bubbles flying everywhere!
So pretty...
Wow!
What is all this, though?
They're floating from the ground to the sky.
Who's blowing them?
They're emitted by the island.
Emitted? You mean...
Really? Why?
May I ask a question?
Sorry to interrupt.
Is the Log Pose all right?
Oh, yeah...
It's pointing toward
Fishman Island now, but...
Hey, this island won't overwrite
the Log Pose, will it?
No need to worry about that.
The Sabaody Archipelago is
really a bunch of trees.
It has no magnetic force.
Oh...
So these aren't islands, then?
Well, have you heard of
trees called "mangroves"?
Mangroves?
The kind that expose and cover
their roots depending on the tides?
That's right.
Though, on this island, their
roots are exposed all the time.
The Sabaody Archipelago is home
to the world's biggest mangroves,
the Hustle Muscle Mangroves.
Hustle Muscle Mangroves?
Sounds like they've got a lot of hustle!
I do, too!
There are a total of 79 trees.
Each one is an island with
its own towns and facilities.
They are collectively called
the Sabaody Archipelago.
There are numbers written on the trees.
Yes, each of the 79 trees
is marked with a number.
The one straight ahead, Grove
#44, is the commercial entrance,
so let's dock the ship a bit further in.
The roots are even bigger up close!
Wow...
It's pitch black inside them.
How remarkable!
Is that a bridge?
Yeah, all the islands are connected
with bridges like that.
Ah, I see!
Okay, we're here!
This is Grove #41. Let's dock here.
I'm first!
Okay, everyone, remember
the number of this island!
As I said before, all the islands
are connected by bridges,
so if you remember the
number, you won't get lost.
I know someone who'd still get lost.
Yeah, me too.
Huh? What?
What?!
It popped out of the ground! Cool!
Amazing!
I'm on!
It's not popping.
That looks fun!
These bubbles really are mysterious.
How do they work?
The roots of Hustle Muscle Mangroves
secret a special natural resin.
Gross! It's all sticky!
Don't wipe it on me!
That resin expands into bubbles
when the roots breathe.
I get it...
So that's how they float up to the sky.
So this scenery is all natural?
Hey!
Whoa, Luffy! When did you get up that high?!
I can see an amusement park over there!
Let's go! I wanna ride the ferris wheel!
An amusement park?!
That's Sabaody Park.
A ferris wheel sounds fun...
It was always my dream to ride one.
Your dream? Why don't you just ride one?
Don't be a fool! You can't, Camie!
Yeah, I know.
I want to ride it, too... Can I not?
I'm really high up!
What's going on?
They're suddenly popping!
Luffy-chin!
Oh, no! Are you okay?!
It's fine, Camie-chan.
No need to worry about him.
Man, I was really stuck!
See?
By the way, Hachi, what did
we come to this island for?
You said something about a
coating for the ship earlier.
Right. We'll go see a coating craftsman
and have your ship coated in resin.
In simple terms, that'll allow
your ship to go underwater.
For real?
That's the only way you humans
can get to Fishman Island.
But if you get an unskilled
coating craftsman,
the ship and its passengers will be
crushed underwater, and that's the end.
I know just one craftsman that you
can trust, so I'll take you to him.
When all is said and done,
the octopus is a good man.
No, a good octopus!
In exchange...
I want you to keep one promise for me.
Sure! What is it?
Sometimes, there are World
Nobles walking around in town.
World Nobles?
Who are they?
Residents of the holy land Marie Jois.
Hmm...
So, what about them?
No matter what may happen in town,
promise me that you will
not defy the World Nobles.
Huh?
No matter what happens?
You mean...
Understand?
Even if someone is killed before your eyes,
you must pretend you saw nothing.
I'll say it once more.
You must pretend
you saw nothing!
The Sabaody Archipelago is fun!
There's so much stuff I've never seen before!
Hey! Here comes someone
wearing a bubble on his head!
There's a dog with a bubble on its head, too!
Oh, no! Everyone get on your knees!
Don't look them in the eyes!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Tyranny! The Roles of Sabaody,
the Celestial Dragons"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!