Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around
the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Luffy and company, realizing that
the Sunny will need to be coated
To reach Fish-Man Island,
Luffy and company found themselves
In search of a coating craftsman
to help them reach Fish-Man Island,
Having defeated
Duval's Flying Fish Riders,
After landing on the
Sabaody Archipelago,
in order to reach Fish-Man Island
, their next destination,
Straw Hat Luffy and company
now head for Fish-Man Island.
looking for a coating craftsman
on the Sabaody Archipelago.
Luffy and friends gained
information from bar owner Shakky
the Straw Hat crew
visited the Sabaody Archipelago
stopped off at the Sabaody Archipelago.
along with Hachi and Camie's group.
about a coating craftsman
and eleven rookie pirates.
However, also on the archipelago
are the Celestial Dragons,
So, umm...
This is it!
However, Camie was abducted,
What do you say, Nami?
Sabaody Archipelago!
We're here! Sabaody Park!
world nobles powerful enough
to hold sway over Navy Headquarters,
and is about to be sold
as a slave at a human auction!
This doesn't mean
you're suddenly somehow forgiven.
At the seemingly enjoyable archipelago,
Yay!
and formidable rookies
headed for the New World!
Luffy and company searched
for a coating craftsman...
No! Of course not!
That's not what I meant!
...but they encountered world
nobles known as Celestial Dragons
But I'm worried about
the old craftsman guy,
I was just wondering how it tastes!
"Time Limit
-- The Human Auction Begins"
and were witness to their
domineering behavior.
Camie's been kidnapped!
It's really good!
if he's in such a rough town.
What?!
Damn it!
If only... If only it wasn't for this!
My husband will be fine.
Really?! It is?!
"Rescue Camie The Archipelago's
Lingering Dark History"
"Navy Headquarters"
First, there are actually two routes
that lead to the New World!
After all, he's 100 times
stronger than you kids...
Honestly, now!
You're terrible at taking care of them!
But for outlaws like you guys,
there's really only one.
You make me sick.
"The Target is Camie!! The Looming
Clutches of a Professional Kidnapper"
Just maintain course
for the route you'll use,
She's...!
"Dark King" Silvers Rayleigh, huh...
Stop! Please!
which is known as Fish-Man Island's
Apparently, no one around him
recognizes him,
Please! Just endure it!
Damn, what's taking 'em so long?
so he's being sold
as a regular old man...
"Sea Floor Route"!
That pirate could've easily
beaten that old man and lady!
Are you in?
Young Master!
The Red Line is a large barrier
that stretches all around the world,
Yeah!
Well, take care.
They're here?
So why...?!
Just so you know,
the navy is obviously aware
Harm a Celestial Dragon
Yahoo! It's me, Handsome!
The Dark King,
being sold at a human auction?
but there is one small hole
in one part of it,
and a Navy HQ admiral will
lead an entire army here!
that big-name rookies
have made landfall here.
Oh, I mean, it's me, Duval!
and that's where Fish-Man Island is!
And we're his men!
In order to make their ship
capable of submerging to the sea floor,
They share the Creators' blood!
It is hard to believe something like this
would happen to the real one.
Th-That's not good!
Hello, Young Master Black Leg!
Then, does that mean there's
no telling when they might strike?
Luffy and company
needed to visit a certain island first.
Took you long enough,
Flying Fish Riders!
My men aren't 100% sure
it's really him, either...
Creators?
The twenty kings who created
the huge World Government organization
Hold on, Young Master!
Tea!
But don't worry.
Oh, thank you.
Perhaps this is another
case of rookie's luck,
This is it!
We're the Rosy Life Riders now!
What should we do, Vice-Admiral?
800 years ago!
Sabaody Archipelago!
but I believe Navy HQ
Shall we report this
to Fleet Admiral Sengoku?
Their descendents are
the Celestial Dragons.
Fine, whatever! You're annoying!
No, I'll handle this myself.
And then a dark shadow
loomed toward Luffy and company...
probably has its hands full
with something else right now.
Awesome!
Anyway, a mermaid has been kidnapped!
Don't tell anyone about it, now.
Straw Hat Luffy.
Not even Sengoku!
That's why I called for you!
Unless something especially
problematic happens,
300 million Berries.
Give your men a convenient story!
Eh?! You encountered kidnappers?!
they won't waste major military
resources on things here.
Oh! It came outta the ground!
But, what if it really is him?
What horrible villains!
"New Rivals Gather! The 11 Supernovas"
So, to be more precise,
It's him, all right.
Neat!
Hey, now! You guys are
kidnappers too, you know!
I'm sure of it.
"Take care not to cause
any trouble." Okay?
It's like they say,
set a thief to catch a thief.
I'm riding it!
I hear reports of him
being seen on occasion.
Oh, okay!
That looks fun!
So you guys help out, too!
Say, Hachi.
Gum-Gum...
Got it! Thanks!
What's our purpose
on this island, anyway?
If I had to guess,
But of course!
I'd say he probably lost
while gambling and sold himself.
Thank you for calling upon us!
We're gonna go find the
old coating craftsman now!
...Pistol!
Oh, we're going to see
a coating craftsman
Thank you!
He may be an old soldier,
Can we really count on these guys?!
and have him cover your ship in resin.
but if we take Rayleigh on foolishly,
By the by, I tried visiting
a town with girls in it!
our forces will lose an
unthinkable number of men.
Simply put, that'll make it
so your ship can go underwater.
What's with this skeleton freak?!
Here's hoping you do find him.
Time to die!
Are you serious?!
Head! Head! Look, girls!
And so Luffy and company landed
on the Sabaody Archipelago
Why, you!
Now is an especially bad time.
Nice. Let's go!
Gavotte Bon en Avant!
to find a coating craftsman Hachi knows.
Are you suggesting the navy
take on two "legends" at once?!
How was it?
It was great!
Hey there, girls!
Gotcha!
Hello! I'm Handsome!
"Tyranny! The Rulers of Sabaody,
the Celestial Dragons"
What do you say we take a drive
on the sea on my Motobalo?
We're here! Sabaody Park!
Watch out! He's quick as a monkey!
Yay!
It looks so fun!
And...?
Okay, ladies and gentlemen!
I wasn't as popular
as I thought I'd be...
Are you even trying
to find the old guy?!
It's the moment you've been waiting for!
Damn! The others are strong, too!
But that lady did say
he likes this place!
You can fix how you look on the outside,
Grove #1's monthly
Only if we couldn't find him
in the lawless area!
but there's no fixing how
you look on the inside...
In that case...
Great Human Auction is about to begin!
...I'll just take her hostage!
Wow! The Ferris wheel!
But that's all right!
I understand, Young Master!
Everyone's gone into town.
I've never seen it from
this close before!
And your emcee, of course, is this man!
You guys aren't going?
We just need to find the mermaid
before she gets sold, right?!
Alright, guys! Let's have fun!
Nah, we used up all the cola
in that last sea battle.
That's right.
Oh no! Camie! Pappagu!
I figure you must have some knowledge
of the Sabaody Archipelago.
See, you're not trying to find him!
Yay!
The ship's maintenance is my job!
Alright! C'mere!
Camie! You are forbidden to go in!
But of course!
And I'm stayin' behind
because I wanna help, of course!
Gum-Gum...
Sometimes known as the
Walking Super Bazaar...
These waters are
pretty much like our backyard!
I absolutely forbid it!
Let's all three of us
go when we're done!
...Bazooka!
You can count on us!
...Mr. Disco!
This island looks like fun!
Oh, it's moving at quite
a leisurely pace indeed!
Okay! Hop on!
No,
I'm gonna wait for someone to come back
and then go shopping.
We're gonna take these Flying Fish?
Hello, everyone!
Oh, what a truly wonderful view!
We sure are!
Okay! Ready when you are!
I have some great-quality
slaves again for you today!
Huh? How come?
Alright! You okay?
Actually, you see...
Right!
So, how're we gonna find her?
Thanks, Straw Hat.
You're lucky!
Young Master!
Thanks, Luffy-chin!
We even have a super-great
showcase item for sale today!
Yahoo!
Those of a trade know each other's ways!
It's because my beloved
Nami-san said this...
Yeah!
Are you done beating yours up, too?
I pray from the bottom of my heart
Whatever will I do?
Indeed!
I know of several kidnapping teams
that could be behind this!
that you'll get to take home
the slaves of your choice!
The ship is so full
of treasure right now...
You guys really are amazing!
I'm full!
I wish there was a knight somewhere
who could protect it for me...
We'll start by picking up
your Straw Hat friends
What are you planning to purchase today?
I could take those guys
on any time and never lose!
scattered around the
Sabaody Archipelago!
Tadah!
The last human slave I bought
It's me!
didn't even last 10 days
before it broke down.
At the same time,
Damn!
You sure know how to fall
right into Nami's hands.
we'll figure out which kidnapping
team abducted the mermaid!
Yahoo!
So I'm hoping to procure a young
and durable male giant today.
He's too strong!
I'm a slave of love!
Admitting it yourself saves me trouble.
300 million is too much
to handle after all!
I'm considering buying two
or three young girls for eye candy.
Let's go, men!
There are so many big shots
on these islands right now, too...
Oh, you certainly do love those!
Awesome!
I can't wait to see what
cuties they'll have today!
Hey! Zoro!
Let's do it again!
Damn... Can't we bag at least one?
Were you scared, Camie?
Earth to Zoro-kun!
Yeah!
No, wait...
Where are you going all by yourself?!
It was really scary, but really fun!
Oh, you!
I think that girl might be a...
Alright! We're coming to
save you now, Camie-chan!
I just had a good idea!
My heart's still beating so fast!
Just for a walk...
Well, then!
Let's get this auction started!
Hey, Duval! Go faster!
That's nothing! I was in the very front!
Stop!
Don't you dare, you damn bastard!
You always get lost!
Young Master!
Get #2 and #3 ready.
We went so fast my head
almost wound up behind my back!
Motobalo is already at full speed!
This is an archipelago, you know!
Right!
We'll never be able to find you!
What on earth is going on?
Great! We're at full speed!
I-I thought my heart
was going to stop...
I ain't gonna get lost!
Entry #1!
Eh?!
All these bounty hunters
suddenly appearing out of nowhere...
As if anyone could get lost on such
straightforward islands as these!
This is full speed?!
From Troa in West Blue!
That makes three surprise attacks now!
Let's go!
Though I don't have a heart.
A proud pirate from a
long line of musicians
All the trees are numbered!
I don't see any more taste-testing--
"Navy Keep Out"
Worst case, even a kid could make
it back by asking for directions!
and versatile with musical instruments!
I mean, souvenir shops, either.
I hope it'll be all right...
Give him an instrument, and he'll play
any background music you request!
Oh!
Sanji! What are we going to do?!
I never expected you
to have such street-smarts!
It's almost strange seeing shops
and streets without anyone around...
He's a human music box!
Listen, Chopper!
We underestimated you!
He's also a great cleaner!
Don't go anywhere,
no matter what!
Sorry! Take care!
Give him a mop, and he won't
miss a single speck of dust!
It's hard to believe
there's a coating craftsman here!
I will send someone to get you!
Make sure to ask for directions!
In addition,
he's skilled at making wine!
Okay!
Don't trust yourself!
This is a big archipelago,
A hard-working 25 year old male human!
so there are always places
outside the government's watchful eye.
Hey, Luffy! Sanji says not to go--
I dunno what the hell
they're talking about!
Yes.
192 centimeters and 130 kilograms!
Camie!
Gentle rides like this
are more my style.
Marines can't go very far
into the interior, either.
I just need to remember
this tree's number.
Goes by the name of Byron!
Oh, what a delightful view...
Look here.
Bidding will start at the special
offer price of 480,000 Berries!
I think it's dangerous to split up
at a time like this, Brook...
A map?
Okay! Raise your bidding paddles
and name your price!
#1. Okay.
It shows all the different areas here,
divided into 10-grove sections.
They can mock me all they want;
Wow! Look!
None of it's set in stone or anything.
Eh?
I'll never get lost on these islands!
Well, 480,000 is a steal!
You're too calmed down!
It's just how they are generally.
Unlike some other guy
with no sense of direction!
This is a major shock, you know!
Camie was kidnapped!
#7 bids 480,000!
For example,
the area we've come through...
She's gonna get sold and be a slave
for the rest of her life!
Any other bidders?!
Your ship is docked at #40,
The World Nobles are also known
as the Celestial Dragons.
Chopper-san.
500,000!
Don't spin too much, now!
a tourism area filled
with souvenir shops.
Sanji-san gave us precise instructions
about what we should do.
#82 has just bid 500,000 Berries!
They act so high and mighty
that they wear masks
Spin! Spin! Spin! Spin!
And #30 is an amusement park area
to keep from breathing
the same air as common people.
520,000!
However we act, we'll spend the
same amount of time waiting.
Yes! #105 bids 520,000 Berries!
centered around Sabaody Park.
Whatever you do, don't defy them!
Spin!
Oh! #60 is a naval post
I see!
Spin! Spin! Spin!
That's one thing you have to promise!
Acting flustered won't solve anything.
I have 520,000!
Sure!
where the government comes and goes!
This is a great value, you know!
There are a couple other things
to watch out for, too.
He can play music, perform housework,
Yeah, #60 is like the front door,
you could say.
In which case, why don't we spend our
time waiting calmly and tranquilly?
Spin!
and as a pirate,
he'll make a great guard-dog!
Like I mentioned before,
Then what area is this place?
Oh! Now I see!
people heading for the New World
gather on these islands.
Are there any other bidders?!
Any other bidders?!
Here?
What the heck's your problem?!
530,000!
We're in Grove #16 right now.
There are infamous
pirates like you here,
You idiots spun too much!
550,000!
600,000!
Most of #1 through #29
is a lawless area!
as well as marines and bounty hunters
who are out to catch them.
#7 bids 600,000!
Head!
We've reached Sabaody Park!
Any other bids?!
That's why there are
so many bounty hunters.
Not to mention kidnappers!
Pick up one Straw Hat member each!
Wow! We're so high up!
Couldn't you have told us sooner?!
There's no law here at all
against buying and selling pirates.
Right!
And then Zoro and Sanji
could've come instead!
Do anything to stand out
and they'll set their sights on you,
It's okay!
They were told to wait by
Public Transponder Snail #5,
We're headed for #13, the next one over!
so be very careful what you do!
which should be right around here!
Sold, for 600,000 Berries!
The marines here
aren't pushovers, either.
Chopper-chin!
You and Skeleton-chin were really cool!
There they are!
Oh! They're selling
ice cream, Luffy-chin!
Two of them, down by those benches!
Navy Headquarters is in
nearby waters, you see.
For reals?!
That doesn't make me happy, you dumbass!
Wow! Everyone's so tiny!
Which is why the bounty hunters
are all just as ferocious.
I'm blushing so much
that my ears are red!
Though I have no ears,
because I'm a skeleton.
It's the ocean! The ocean, Luffy-chin!
Hey, you two! We're here to--!
And one other thing!
Yeah!
Oh, come on!
"Sabaody Archipelago - Grove #13"
There are too many things
to watch out for!
All right! We're here!
What are you guys relaxing for?!
Hey, when did you get hurt there?
Oh, Usopp-san is here to pick us up...
Using by-bidders to enliven the place
and raise prices to their limits...
Wow! Wow!
We finally made it...
Oh, this? Don't worry about it.
It's the shop on top of that root.
So this is how it looks!
Luffy and the others went off somewhere,
This is the pro technique and skill
Camie and I aren't merfolk
or fish-men here.
of Mr. Disco-sama,
the Walking Super Bazaar!
Is it still in business?
but we tranquilly stayed put
like we were told to.
Treat us like we're human
on these islands.
It makes you happy enough to cry?
It's been 10 years now...
Okay! There are many more
great deals to come!
Yeah, I've always dreamed of this,
ever since I was a little girl!
Huh? How come?
Hey, is the coating craftsman
a fish-man too?
It'll make things a lot simpler.
Let's go!
Oh, Pappagu and I don't know him.
Be sure not to miss your chance,
ladies and gentlemen!
Operation: Save Camie
With Everything We Got!
Now, then!
Let's move on to the next item!
We heard he's incredible, though.
All right! It's time to go all out!
Oh? Really?
When in a city,
do as its citizens do, Luffy.
Let's go!
Well, we'll find out when we meet 'im!
He got mad at us, Brook!
Let's do as Mr. Octopus says.
"Human Buying and Selling"
I regret it!
I regret it a little now!
Keep checking up on all the kidnapping
teams on the archipelago!
"Shakky's Rip-Off Bar"
What is this disgusting list, Duval?!
Shakky's Rip-Off Bar!
Harder! And push into it slowly!
Figure out who's behind this!
Hachi.
They're market prices!
It really sounds like they intend
to rip you off at this place...
And don't forget to retrieve
the other Straw Hat members!
Market prices?
This craftsman isn't super-violent
by any chance, is he?
Roger! Let's split up!
The general minimum value
of humans is 500,000 Berries...
Right!
I'm inside!
Male giants are worth
50 million Berries...
Don't worry!
Alright!
They're nice people!
Hurry, Rosy Life Riders!
Neat!
What?!
I've known 'em since I was little!
How curious!
We have no time to lose!
Female mermaids are worth
70 million Berries?!
I can get in! I can get in!
Hey, why are we going to a bar?!
It's not leaking at all!
That should be good enough.
Now do you see why everyone
wants to catch mermaids?
Looks like they're still in business.
Good enough, my ass!
All right, then!
Can't you do something about this cow?!
They're in a class of their own!
Rayleigh? Shakky?
I should've ridden a Flying Fish, too!
Put this inside.
Eh? Did you say "handsome" just now?
Once you buy one,
you're free to have it do whatever you want,
"Bar Owner & Former Pirate
Shakuyaku (Shakky)"
Hell, no!
Come on in.
but most are used by rich people
as decorations.
Like this?
You're the head of your gang, Duval!
What'll it be?
Is that high enough for ya?
Why aren't you the fastest
one in your team?!
They spend the rest of their lives
in cramped fish tanks as eye candy.
You'll go forward now if you peddle.
Oh?
Is that you, Hatchan?
Eh? What are you talking about?
Long time, no see!
What the hell are you trying to say?!
Of course I'm the most
handsome person in my team!
Oh, it's just that when I think about it,
that's not living at all.
Oh! It's going forward!
It's good to see you again, Shakky!
Just step on it, you idiot!
Yes.
If you feel that way,
then find her already!
How long has it been? 10 years?
Awesome!
Alright, here we go!
Have a seat for a second.
I was in the middle
This is fun!
of ripping these kiddos off
for an excessive amount.
Yahoo!
It really doesn't pop!
Take your time.
It won't take long.
This is Fish #20!
I've checked all the kidnapping groups here!
Hey! Any doctors here?!
Convenient, huh?
You, there!
They're Sabaody Archipelago's
famous Bubble Bikes!
This is a general outpatient clinic!
There's no word in this area
about a mermaid being abducted!
I wanna ride too!
What's wrong with him?!
Oh?
Whadya say?
No mermaid info here, either!
He needs urgent care.
You gave up being a pirate, Hatchan?
It's 500 Berries a day to rent one,
or 10,000 Berries to buy one!
This is bad!
Damn!
Yeah, a lot happened...
No leads at all here, either!
Let's see... Nope, no collar.
But that's okay.
After all, an honest
life is the best life.
Pretty cheap, huh?
I've never been so high up before!
Does having a collar matter?
I think we'll rent--
I want it!
Say, it's rare for merfolk
to be above water.
Yes.
Hurry up already!
I'll cherish this memory forever!
Thank you!
I'll buy this one
with my spending money!
Medical treatment for
slaves costs 50% more,
Gimme a break!
Me, too! Me, too!
Hatchin and Pappagu
only let me come here
so sometimes it's quicker
to buy a new one...
It ain't a bird!
It needs a running start!
Forget it!
Are you Hatchan's girlfriend,
Camie-chan?
Let's just rent.
There's no point in buying one.
because you guys are strong!
This guy is hurt, that's all.
Eh?!
Why do you get to decide?!
M-M-Me, Hatchan's wife?
You gonna help him or not?!
Yeah!
I-I-It's too s-s-soon for...!
Urgh! I'll explain later!
Camie! Where are you?!
Yes, yes! Right away!
Jumpy much?
Carry him right inside!
We'll rent two more, mister!
We run a takoyaki shop together.
Huh? You're from around these parts?
What a bummer...
Oh, really?
Oh, right.
What an annoying island...
It pisses me off!
Let me get you some drinks--
Shakky-san.
I mean seriously, it's a giant!
Guess I'll head back to the ship.
These boiled beans are delicious.
Catching one that was asleep
was nice and all,
My dreams as a kid
have come back to life too!
They're raiding the fridge!
Grove #1, as I recall.
but it took so much work
just to haul the thing here!
Luffy! Brook! She's gonna rip you off!
This feels so nice!
Merfolk and fish-men always dream
of coming here when growing up!
"Human Shoppe"
It's okay. Go ahead.
Doesn't it, though?!
You'd normally think our item
would be the main event, right?!
They even have different kinds.
Here, I have something you'll like.
A mermaid?
So high up!
It makes me want to sing now!
Get out if you're just
window-shoppin', kid!
Here.
So high up!
But then some guy brought in a mermaid
just before the auctions started!
Cotton candy!
That one next!
Someone caught our friend!
I think I'm gonna buy
a Bubble Bike after all!
Sweet! Yum!
Gondola!
Has anyone come here trying
to sell a mermaid, old guy?!
Straw Hat.
Okay, that'll be 100,000 Berries.
You know how you first went up
into the sky on those bubbles?
So how can I not drink now?!
Any information at all!
H-Hold on! Who was this guy?!
If you know anything, please tell us!
Why did you come falling down?
I... I... don't have that much...
Oh! Actually, I went
past the tops of the trees
I'm sorry. I was only teasing.
This is Fish #5!
and wondered if I could
go any higher up...
Attention, all Rosy Life Riders!
I can't charge friends of Hatchan.
Don't know nothin'.
Besides,
Do you read me?
Really?!
it's in your best interest not to stick
your nose into that kinda stuff...
It was Peterman who
kidnapped the mermaid!
Lady.
How do you know what Chopper likes?
You're sure nobody's come here
trying to sell a mermaid?!
He sold her to the
auction house on Grove #1!
...when all the bubbles
around me disappeared
You're Monkey-chan's group, correct?
and the bubble I was on
suddenly popped too...
I-I'm sure! No one's tried to!
You know about me?!
Peterman?!
Stop it, Straw Hat!
Do you know where that is?!
Of course.
Yeah! Let's step on it!
It'll be harder to look for her
if you cause trouble!
Everyone's talking about you.
Then I fell.
You must have left
Sabaody Archipelago's climate area, then.
Plus I stay well-informed.
This is a bit fast!
It's frightening!
Let's go in!
Y-You're free to look around
the place if you want!
Wow!
You're famous, Luffy-chin!
This place has a suitable climate
for Hustle Mustle Mangroves to grow.
But I had no idea
you had a skeleton on your crew
Octoguy! Let's look around the shop!
Don't tell me she's been
sold to someone already?!
Outside that area,
or that skeletons could
even move about, though.
Okay!
the resin components in the bubbles
lose a lot of their capabilities.
Hurry!
Oh, pardon my late introduction.
Grove #1 is right nearby!
Leave it to me!
I am the dead and skeletonized Brook.
All these guys are
being caught and sold?
I see.
Our destination is the auction house!
Then that means the bubbles
can't be ridden outside of these islands?
We know where she is?!
It's a pleasure to make
your acquaintance.
Camie...
Thank goodness!
Nice to meet you.
That's right.
Camie!
Oh, look at how much you've dropped...
Hurry!
Newcomers here often buy Bubble Bikes
and take them with them.
Hey!
That's a dirty business.
Well, Octoguy?! Pappagu?!
Shakky-san...
Renting Bubble Bikes is all you need.
She's not here...
No! I'm buying one!
Camie!
What a delightful person!
I'm tryin' to get back to my ship.
'Cause I can't agree
with that explanation!
Do you have any others, old guy?!
Do you know where the #1 trees are?
What color are your panties?
I don't got a warehouse,
so all you see here is all I got.
Why're you asking that?!
I-I never thought they'd
be that strong...
You just don't understand it!
Sure, I'll tell you!
Let me think... I believe today's are...
Basically, the bubbles will pop
outside of these islands,
We have no choice!
Oh? I appreciate it.
Don't tell him!
Sounds like you had it rough.
Let's check elsewhere, Straw Hat!
mysteriously enough!
Listen!
Just a minute, now!
Oh, my! How incredible!
So, what's this proposition of yours?
You ain't going back anywhere now...
It sounds like you folks
are in real need of a mermaid!
What?! They pop mysteriously?!
My nosebleed won't stop!
Right, Peterman-san.
Why didn't you say so sooner!
...Pirate Hunter Zoro-san!
You have a mermaid?!
I have no nose, though! Kaboom!
I think the girl that was with
Straw Hat Luffy might be a mermaid.
We have been trying to tell you!
The only mermaid I have
is this girl here: Marin!
Your 120 million Berry bounty is mine!
But you can use it on
Fish-Man Island, Luffy-chin!
"Marin"
When I think back...
I'll give you a discount! Whadya say?!
Here you are!
There's a bubble civilization
on the sea floor, too!
Thanks!
Please buy me, kiddo.
I wanna go to Fish-Man Island
right away!
I read your news stories.
You ain't no mermaid!
Oh no! Camie! Pappagu!
How much of the Enies Lobby
incident is true?
I can't wait!
You're just that old guy from earlier!
Then you should meet
the Mermaid Princess!
When her shoe came off,
It's so hard to breathe underwater.
Is it true you picked a fight
with the government?
U-Uhh, let me think! Grove #1 is...!
She's a girl of matchless beauty!
I saw a tail fin instead of a foot!
Forget about that.
Hey!
Okay! Let's move on!
I'm a panderer; shall I hook you up?!
It's too much of a pain to explain.
C-Camie...
Next up is Entry #6!
Camie!
That sounds splendid!
You're not going to brag?
You really are a big-shot...
Where are you?!
I love having an eyeful
of beautiful girls!
A 10-pack of male human laborers!
I see.
Though I lack eyes,
due to being a skeleton.
But these strong companions of hers
sound like trouble.
That reminds me...
You have the same name
as someone in the navy named Garp.
Whoa, check it out!
Head here!
Attention all units!
It's Straw Hat Luffy from East Blue!
Wait, are you even listening?
Yeah. He's my grandpa.
Check today's auction schedule!
Even so, a mermaid on land
is a golden opportunity.
Ooh, that smells good!
That's him?!
I thought so.
What's a "Grand-Bun"?
It starts at 4:00,
It's possible she hasn't been sold yet.
Garp once chased me a long time ago.
"Grand-Bun" "GR Famous Food"
so it's been going for 30 minutes now!
They're impossible to catch
in the water, after all.
"GR Famous Grand-choco!!"
"GR Famous Grand-Bun!!"
If we can just figure out
which kidnapping team it was...!
Hey, are we gonna make it?!
How come?
Shakky used to be a pirate.
Thanks for telling me, boys.
Don't worry.
Hey! There's no reason to cry that much!
Really?
Mermaids are always the
big showcase items,
S-Sure thing...
Grand Line Manju buns!
Commonly called Grand-Buns!
For the info, you can have
10% of her selling price.
I washed my hands of it
40 years ago, though.
We will find Camie!
so they won't auction her off
until the last half!
Darn it...!
How about a taste test?
We'll make it in time!
Agreed?
It's all my fault!
A-Actually, we were
hoping more like 20%...
Wait! How old are you, lady?!
Just take the shortest distance!
The amusement park is the perfect spot
You're slower than the flying fish!
Nowadays I have fun
cheering on rookies like you.
See how they say
"Grandline First Half" here?
for kidnappers to do their work!
Just stay calm, Young Master Black Leg!
No, 10% is plenty!
Anyway, Shakky...
I knew full well how badly
they want mermaids, and yet...!
They're very popular as souvenirs
for going into the New World!
No, don't say it.
I am the head of the team!
I know. I know everything.
They last for three whole months,
so you can rest easy!
Hey! Look at all these
kinds of ice cream!
Have I changed course
after hearing where the mermaid is?!
You guys came all this way by land
These are delicious!
What do you guys want?!
Wait, let me choose some, too!
No...
Could I ask you to open the next box?
Wait here a minute, Camie!
to help Monkey-chan's group
get their ship coated here, right?
Wait here a minute, Camie!
That's because
Are you planning to pay?!
I've been heading for Grove #1
from the very start!
Okay! Choose something yummy for me too!
Okay!
Choose something yummy for me too!
That was good!
Here you go!
Look ahead! That's Grove #1!
Grove #35.
So basically,
you have a coating job for Rayleigh?
Crashing the place first goes to show
why I'm head of the team!
I don't want that to be my
last conversation with Camie!
There seem to be a lot of hotels here.
Seriously?!
They're for the sailors who're waiting
for their passes from Marie Jois.
That's right.
He isn't here, though.
Was it "colleague's intuition"
or something?!
It's my fault!
Building hotels is easy, you know!
I let her go to the amusement park!
Eh?!
The craftsman isn't here?!
See, look over there!
Yeah,
We wanna go to Fish-Man Island!
Paint a giant bubble with a metal alloy
and you have your foundation!
I've always dreamed of this,
ever since I was a little girl!
Well, seeing as he wouldn't
leave this archipelago,
That's how round buildings are made!
why don't you check around
some pubs or gambling houses?
We're here, Mr. Reindeer!
Oh?
I've never been so high up before!
Robin!
Yes! Thanks!
I'll cherish this memory forever!
Look! Is that a shopping mall?!
High Priest Urouge. Look...
We'll just wait 'til he gets back, then.
Thank you!
Oh, Sanji!
Come again!
I dunno why exactly,
but she was really happy!
Yes, he'll be back eventually.
Oh!
Grand-cracker! Grand-choco!
He's been gone half a year now, though.
Going to the amusement park
was a good idea!
Keychain!
No, it wasn't!
Half a year?!
Pennant!
In fact,
You guys are all about the memories!
it's not even a good idea for fish-men
or merfolk to come to these islands!
He's probably shacked up
with some girls he's picked up,
You really bought a lot!
It'd be tough to lug all that around.
But Hachi was so intent
on being helpful to you guys that--!
so I'm not worried about his wellbeing.
Have 'im bubble pack it for you.
Bubble pack?
Maybe it's the former pirate in him
Pappagu! Don't say any more!
You didn't make it here first!
What are you talking about?!
A Celestial Dragon, huh?
It's so light!
that keeps him away for
so long once he leaves.
Why isn't it good for you guys
to come to these islands?!
You don't need strength
to carry stuff on these islands!
Sanji-kun! Chopper!
To think they'd swagger about the
lawless area with nary a care...
The old craftsman guy
was a pirate, too?!
Upsy-daisy...
Uhh, well...
That's right.
Kidnappers aren't the only enemies
Camie and Hachi have here.
This is bad.
Nami-swan!
Huh? Where are Nami and Robin?
This is a real problem for us, though.
Our only choice is to kneel
and let him pass.
Hey! Everyone!
If he's not here, then our only option
is to go look for him.
They went to the shopping mall
in Grove #30.
All of the people living on this
archipelago are their enemies!
Camie!
They left us in charge
of getting the ship coated.
Do you know where he might be?
Oh? They did?
Hmm...
Okay! Leave it to us!
200 years ago?!
He's probably somewhere in #1 to #29,
if I had to guess...
Yes.
Where are we headed again?
A terrible history that actually
took place up until 200 years ago...
Grove #13.
It's still a ways away,
even by Bubble Bike.
Groves #1 through #29...
The fish-man and merfolk races
were classified as fish
Where on earth could Shalria
and Father have gone,
Let's go!
and were persecuted
by people all over the world.
That's the lawless territory!
leaving me behind like this?!
Everyone looked down on them.
He's notorious, too.
We do know their final destination,
so please rest easy.
Camie-chan didn't come along
when we invited her...
He can't relax with the
navy keeping watch...
They looked down
on those strong fish-men...?!
Yeah.
She's been a bit reserved
ever since we landed on these islands.
Be careful!
And let's see...
No one can stand up to the
power of sheer numbers.
Yeah! Thanks!
Another area he's fond of
is Sabaody Park.
Hey, you!
I wonder what's up with her...
It's all because you walk like a turtle!
The persecution continued unabated
Who's this guy?!
until the World Government
declared its friendship
The amusement park?!
You also sway too much and
make for a horrible ride!
Two million berries!
Alright! Let's look there!
Any other bids?
Who knows, perhaps this island
has a bad history...
with Fish-Man Island.
You irritate me to no end!
--Yahoo!
--Yay! Amusement park!
Sold!
One other relic of humankind's
terrible history
Camie! Stop that!
This the place?!
Bad history?
Amusement park! Amusement park!
Why can't you give her back?!
is the culture of human
trafficking and slavery...
In any case, be careful,
wherever you end up looking.
You have no business selling Camie-chan!
And on this archipelago,
it's still quietly condoned.
You're the one who has no business here!
Which is why I wondered
if they might still discriminate
Hey! Wait, you!
According to my information network,
If you keep pestering us,
we'll take legal action against you
including you, there are now 11 people
on the Sabaody Archipelago
And why are you moving?! You're humans!
against fish-men and merfolk here.
for obstruction of business!
Discrimination?
whose bounties exceed
100 million Berries.
Unless you take these islands
for what they are,
Damn them...!
I-I'm sorry! Please overlook this!
you'll only make a fool out of yourself!
Business my ass, you damn bastard!
Which is why I should've stopped Camie,
He's losing blood and needs urgent care!
A business like this has
no place in this world!
It's a race against time!
The hospital is just ahead!
even if it meant being mean and strict!
11 people with bounties
over 100 million?!
An outlaw pirate has no business
lecturing me about being humane!
Is that why Hachi and Camie are both
concealing their identities here?
Yahoo!
Yes, this is very bad, indeed!
Buying and selling people
is taboo throughout the world!
I only hope it's an ungrounded fear...
In that case, you must be swift...
How much are you paying the government?!
Girl! Robin!
That's not a very nice thing to say.
But, yes...!
Franky!
Will you quit calling me
"girl" already?!
Even when people from the government
or navy talk with us,
Get on the Flying Fish!
It's so fast!
...and be out of your misery!
The mermaid's been kidnapped!
they apparently have a hard time
hearing the phrase "human trafficking"
Camie-chan's...
...been kidnapped?!
Amusement park! Amusement park!
so it's as if they don't know
about the existence of this industry at all!
Huh? Where's Straw Hat?
In any case, be careful,
wherever you end up looking.
Over here!
What a load of crap!
You're all in this together!
I can't believe the
government quietly allows this!
According to my information network,
Straw Hat!
How can this be happening?!
including you, there are now 11 people
on the Sabaody Archipelago
This is horrible!
I'm in the lead now!
whose bounties exceed
100 million Berries.
Be out of your misery!
You won't beat me!
That's just the way it is.
We still have a long way to go!
There's nothing you can do about it.
Go, Hatchin!
Camie...!
Which is why you're also--
What?!
This is annoying!
I'm sorry, Straw Hat.
Please stop!
When did this suddenly
turn into a race?!
11 people with bounties
over 100 million?!
Oh no!
I wanted to help you out,
but I caused you trouble instead...
If we're sure the mermaid's here,
then this is all we need to do!
Yes.
Talk about utterly selfish.
Excluding Monkey-chan and Roronoa-chan,
that still leaves nine.
Weapons...!
What're you guys talking about?
No!
There are Celestial Dragons inside,
There isn't one thing
you guys should be sorry for!
When you entered the Grand Line,
and if Camie is being held here,
you chose one of seven routes
then she must have a collar on by now!
All three of you are my friends now!
Which is more important,
courtesy toward me,
and followed your Log all the way here.
Eh?!
Those ones that explode?!
We will rescue Camie, no matter what!
or a commoner's life?
Yeah.
So, naturally, there are others
Commoners owe their existence
to the Celestial Dragons.
We can't just go
and take her out of there then!
I'm sorry!
So stop crying!
who took one of the six other routes
and had to overcome many difficulties
Straw...!
You're...!
similar to yours to get here.
Please, feel free to leave!
Straw Hat!
U-uhh, umm...
Damn you!
All routes run into the Red Line,
It's the Flying Fish Riders!
We've been lookin' everywhere
for ya! Jump on!
No, we can't do that, Sanji!
I-I'm sorry!
so everyone gathers on this
archipelago to cross that wall.
Let go, Chopper!
Octoguy! Can you jump up?
Please stop!
No, Sanji!
Dammit...!
Y-Yeah!
Take it off!
Pappagu!
There's no getting through to you!
Understand?
Please! Take...
It's not every day
that so many of the world's rookies
Hey, girl!
Where are you going?!
Take this off!
Calm down, Sanji!
I...
all show up at the same time, though...
Octoguy!
I'm...
Nami-san?!
I'm okay!
...going back home now!
Especially Kid, Luffy,
Pappagu!
If we can't use force,
Hawkins, Drake, Law...
Let's go save Camie!
then we'll get Camie back
using their rules!
Straw Hat...!
These names showed up
in newspapers all the time.
"Sabaody Archipelago - Grove #1"
Okay! I'm making you my wife!
"Human Auctioning House"
What's all that noise?
I don't read newspapers.
Then I shall arrange to send her
to the Holy Land as your 13th wife.
Bring out #15 and #16.
Please! Hey!
I beg of you!
Information is a weapon.
Shouldn't you at least learn
the names of your rivals?
Right!
Oh, and I'm tired of
wives #1 through #5 now,
Anyone will do!
Let's see... Kid, Hawkins, and...
Oh, Peterman!
Just lend me an axe or a saw
so I'm sending them back
to the commoners.
Have an item to auction, do you?
or anything!
Drake, was it?
As you wish, sir.
Is there still time to submit an entry?
No!
Wait! I'm...!
In terms of bounty amounts...
Please!
Stop! Please!
Today's big item is a giant.
I'm just going to break this collar!
Stop!
you'd be #2.
She's my fiance!
Your entry won't fetch a very high price
unless it's really something!
I won't hurt anyone!
I don't want this!
I'd much rather stay locked up!
There's someone worth more than Luffy?!
Please let me go!
Here, have a look for yourself.
I don't want to be a slave!
On these islands?!
I don't want to die!
Stand up in front of me, will you?!
Wh-Whoa! That's a mermaid!
Help me! Help me!
Hey! Where did you catch it?!
"Grove #24 - Restaurant"
Sedate him!
I've given up on the New World!
That's a secret.
Call the navy! Please!
Please don't sell me to someone!
This is gonna be today's
main attraction!
I have a wife and kid back home!
Marie...
Come on! Please!
Help me out!
Hatchin... Save me...
No!
Look at her eat!
I wanna go home!
You murderer! How could you?!
My kid was just a baby back then!
Where does all the food go?!
Alright, make sure you
sell it good, now!
The bugger still doesn't
even know what I look like!
Oh, that top-quality item will sell!
For a lot!
Someone!
Bring more food!
Someone please help him!
I'm begging you!
Come by later to get your money!
Who's that?
Vulgar woman...
I look forward to it!
Someone!
I wanna go home! Please!
They're even more screwed up
than the rumors say...
I beg of you!
She's ruining my meal.
Don't get involved, now.
He's probably a pirate who was caught
by kidnappers and then sold!
What was that?
Go shut her up.
What a pleasant surprise,
Saint Roswald! Saint Shalria!
Are you telling me off?
Boss.
That's not a good idea, Father!
Isn't that the Straw Hat crew?
Welcome!
Navy Headquarters is just
a stone's throw away!
His owners brought him to this island,
The Straw Hat captain ain't with 'em.
and then he ran away!
I humbly ask that kneeling and such
be unnecessary inside the building...
If we were to cause a scene now...!
I was hoping to see just how much
of a crazy bastard he is, but...
Let go of me!
Please!
Even though he surely knows
there's no escape!
That will be fine.
Now, then! Next up is Entry #14!
Take her on ahead to the harbor.
They would make for poor
auctions otherwise.
"From West Blue Captain
of the Firetank Pirates"
Yes, sir!
Capone "Gang" Bege.
Thank you very much!
This item is a female human!
Who's he?!
A 138 million Berry bounty.
Please, use the VIP seats!
Aside from housekeeping,
Brother Charloss is certainly
taking a long time!
she's also an expert in games,
ranging from cards to chess!
Captain Apoo!
Where's my seconds?!
He's an East Blue pirate hunter!
She'll be great to have
when you want to pass the time!
W-What's that sound?
That's what he gets
for riding a sluggish human.
Bring it now!
Why's he walkin'
in the middle of the street?!
If you're going to ride something,
make it a fish-man.
Damn this collar!
Let's start the bidding
at 600,000 Berries!
T-They said they're working
as hard as they can, Captain.
Doesn't he know anything?!
They have ten times
the strength of humans.
If only... If only it wasn't for this!
Oh, this could be an excellent bargain!
He's gonna cause trouble!
It's not fast enough!
Damn it! No!
Drat!
No! Stop!
I used up my entire budget
on the female human I just bid on!
More pizzas!
I... I...!
Celestial Dragons...
"From South Blue Captain
of the Bonney Pirates"
Damn it!
Slaves...
This one is clearly much better, too!
Jewelry Bonney, the "Glutton".
Human Shoppes...
A 140 million Berry bounty.
That's a shame!
But I do believe I'll bid on this one!
That's...!
Captain Kid from South Blue!
I'll bring it right away!
Compared to the callowness
of greedy authority figures,
700,000 Berries!
I-I'm very sorry!
900,000 Berries!
the criminals of the world
have much more humanity.
1 million 200 thousand!
What?
It's because scum rules
the world that new scum is born.
1 million 500 thousand!
Why, you little...!
You need directions or somethin'?
Stop.
2 million!
Bastards...
Don't they understand?
Why, Captain?!
3 million!
He got spaghetti all over my clothes!
Slaves always have leashes
around their necks
We're as endearing as we are mean.
#51 has bid 3 million Berries!
Such was the fate of those clothes.
Right, Killer?
that are set to explode if the slaves
try to remove them and escape.
Whoa! What is he doing?!
Without a doubt.
Are there any other bids?!
If there's someone interesting,
should we buy 'em?
I apologize for scaring you.
Any other bids?!
Taking a life on this particular day
will only diminish fortuity.
Boss. Look...
Sold to #51 for 3 million Berries!
I'm gonna buy souvenirs and go home...
"From North Blue Captain
of the Hawkins Pirates"
I'm giving up the pirate business...
Basil Hawkins, the "Magician."
I recognize him...
A 249 million Berry bounty.
Trafalgar Law, from North Blue.
Worth 200 million...
Is Camie going to wind up
like this, too?
A kid?!
We will get her back! Just you watch!
I've heard pretty bad rumors about him.
It's an escaped slave!
Brother!
Get away!
Who's the guy with the stupid face?
Why did you have to die, Brother?!
But, in this situation, how...?!
Don't get involved with him!
H-Hey! We need to help that person!
Oh, that'd be Sea Roar.
We have quite a lot of treasure
on our ship right now.
You idiot!
You promised not to get involved,
no matter what happens!
Altogether, I think it's
worth at least 200 million.
Just stay still, guy.
He's got a bad attitude, too!
What's with this town?!
What's the market price for mermaids?
Boss!
Hatchin! What should we do?!
Brother!
Disco-san!
There are Celestial Dragons nearby!
That should be more than enough,
but I can't pay you back!
You stood up to a Celestial Dragon?!
We have an incredible item today!
It's okay.
Then it's only natural that you died!
Today's big entry is a giant, right?
What're you talking about, Hachi?
Just stay calm, Camie.
I already know.
Are you Camie's guardian or something?
Straw Hat.
I hit him?
You can count on me.
What's going on?! A fight?!
Come down from the Bubble Bike.
I'll make sure it sells
for a high price.
I could've sworn he managed
to dodge my shots...
It's not like that!
If you want a fight,
let's save it for the other side!
How come?
Are the by-bidders ready to go?
Just hurry!
If it's to get our friend back,
No, not that! It's a mermaid!
It must've been my imagination.
Okay... Got it.
then I don't care how much it costs!
A young mermaid!
You guys okay with that?!
Or do you not know how strong I am?
Of course we are!
It's going to be one heated auction!
This isn't about money!
Well, as long as he's dead.
Here they come!
"From Grand Line (Longarm Tribe)
Captain of On Air Pirates"
Seriously?!
Scratchmen Apoo, the "Sea Roar."
Guys... Thank you!
A 198 million Berry bounty.
I'll never forget this
for the rest of my life!
Let me go! You're hurting me!
That's a Celestial Dra--?
Then quit yer damn starin'.
Let go, I said!
You kneel down, too!
I love Nami-san when she's like that!
What's the big idea?!
Stop!
Boss! Don't!
Whoever comes,
don't look them in the eyes!
Hey, quit thrashing around!
Damn, you're one creepy bastard.
Shut up. Come on.
Same for you guys, too!
We need to figure out your collar size!
Extra! Extra!
Right!
I can get rid of you
right now, if you'd like!
Why'd you get in the way?!
Oh, my! How disgraceful, Saruu!
Is the World Government crazy?!
"From South Blue
Captain of the Kid Pirates"
Eustass "Captain" Kid.
Huh?!
Is this for real?! If they do that...!
Don't gimme that, you idiot!
Is that them?
A 315 million Berry bounty.
Yeah.
What the hell were you thinking?!
Damn this collar!
Are you trying to attract
an admiral to these islands?!
Captain! This is bad!
If only...
If only it wasn't for this!
So that's why?
Tomato juice...
Damn it!
If you're a pirate, you must know
some of the unwritten pirate rules!
What is it, Captain Drake?!
The Mad Monk's on a rampage!
It finally makes sense.
Don't get us caught up in your trouble!
I wondered why there were
so few marines on these islands,
We gotta get outta here, quick!
No! Hatchin!
despite being so close
to Navy Headquarters...
Trouble?
Why, you!
Who are...?
You'd best behave
unless you wanna get hurt!
What's happened?!
Huh? Wasn't there a kid?
Whitebeard's second division commander,
Hold it!
Don't be roughhousing
our important merchandise!
Fire Fist Ace, is being
given a public execution!
Are you even listenin' to me?!
You alright in the head?!
Disco-san!
Dear me, Father.
Oh, yeah, I'm not hurt.
Oh, is this the mermaid
that just came in?
But won't Whitebeard
take action if they do that?!
Another one has broken down.
You idiot!
I'm talking about on the inside!
Did you remember to give it
a sedative every day?
Yes, sir!
You're a dumbass!
A genuine dumbass!
There's going to be a war!
I most certainly did.
It has no effect on the poor fool.
We managed to avoid the worst-case
scenario thanks to Jewelry Bonney...
Okay!
Things are really picking up
here at the Great Human Auction!
If you wanna go wild...
That man is Pirate Hunter Zoro,
a member of the Straw Hat Pirates.
...do it in the New World!
Please buy me a new one.
How truly rare!
Next up is another
highly-recommended item!
Lively and strong!
"From North Blue
Captain of the Drake Pirates"
Honestly, now!
"Red Flag" X. Drake.
I heard their crew's crazy,
This should fetch a high price!
You're terrible at taking care of them!
Entry #15 is an unbelievably
beautiful female slave!
A 222 million Berry bounty.
Who submitted it?
You keep breaking everything
in my ship captain collection...
but attacking a Celestial Dragon?
The Hound Pets.
Peterman, huh?
Just look at these
miraculous proportions!
That really is insane.
He does damn good work.
It's this thing's fault.
This is Pashia, a 20 year old dancer!
It's only natural he was saved.
And yet, the Flying Fish Riders
haven't submitted anything this time...
I see.
A grown man, always crying
about family this, family that!
The sight of Pashia--
I don't see the shadow of death
upon him at this time.
Drake, the fallen navy officer...
Well, in any case,
there's no question this'll sell for a lot!
one of our showcase items today--
That bastard unleashed an absurd
amount of bloodlust for a moment.
When he's nothing but a mere human!
"From Sky Island
Captain of the Fallen Monk Pirates"
Blehhh!
"Mad Monk" Urouge.
is guaranteed to beguile
and lead you to heaven!
Honestly, now!
He's a beast...
A 180 million Berry bounty.
800,000!
Worth 120 million,
yet only #2 on his ship...
Already, bidding for the beautiful
dancer Pashia is at 800,000!
He's not doing anything now...!
He doesn't seem like the type
to play second fiddle to anyone,
You're lucky to be alive, masked fellow.
What was that look for?!
1 million!
1 million 500 thousand!
Damn you!
but I guess that goes to show
the caliber of his captain.
You're just a lousy fish!
Don't get any wrong ideas!
3 million!
"From South Blue
Combat Crewman for the Kid Pirates"
Killer, the "Massacre Soldier."
Bidding has jumped straight
to 3 million Berries!
Hey. Where's the hospital?
Stop, Disco-san!
That's important merchandise!
Are there any other bids?!
You make me sick.
A 162 million Berry bounty.
Hospital?
I gotta take him there.
It'll lose its value if you hurt it!
What the hell?!
He's been shot.
Huh?!
What do all these people
take ladies for?!
At least kick it in the stomach
or somewhere that's covered up by clothes!
Forget about 'im! He's a total stranger!
--She's--!
--Stop! Please!
What the hell?
I think I would like
a giant for a slave next.
We will save her!
A pirate that helps people?
I refuse to let Camie
get sold to the likes of them!
Things were just getting good, too...
No, you will start with a human child.
Ain't ever heard of that before!
Hatchan is going to beat you up so bad!
I don't like such weak ones!
Drake-ya...
Why, you...! Still talking back, huh?!
Hurry!
How many people have you killed?
Please! Just endure it!
Hurry!
Hey! Gimme that collar!
I know!
It's the navy!
"From North Blue
Captain of the Heart Pirates"
Y-Yes, sir!
Hurry to Grove #1!
Trafalgar Law, the Surgeon of Death.
Outta the way!
I'll put the collar on it myself...
When I looked into town earlier,
A 200 million Berry bounty.
I saw some bubble bicycle
things flying around!
We need to get out of here for now!
Yeah, I saw! They're so cool!
Hold it still, now!
Let's buy some!
We'll need to see how nice they ride.
This is Grove #2...
A countless number of pirates
have entered the Grand Line,
Oh?
The next one must be it.
Could that be Nami-san?
Would you like some tea?
but only a countable few
have made it this far.
It will help you relax.
No!
Hello, Nami-sa--!
I don't feel very good now...
The Grand Line is a lot like
an enormous survival tournament.
Hello?! It's me!
And you call yourself
a member of the Straw Hats?!
That guy...
Me, Chopper!
Do you think he'll survive?
You've been doing nothing
but scream this whole time!
Basically, they have so
many kinds of ice cream
Those pirates who've made it
this far through each route alive
Even if he does,
he'll probably go to prison,
seeing that he's a pirate.
Disco-san?!
and we got so caught up in it all...!
Hey! What happened, Disco-san?!
are truly the cream of the crop.
That pirate could've easily
beaten that old man and lady!
Hey, why are you freaking out?!
The auction's just
about to start, too...!
I can't help it;
One of them
it's even more frightening
than the rides at Sabaody Park!
Sanji?! It's really bad!
Doctor! Get a doctor!
So why...?!
might even usher
in the next generation of pirates.
Harm a Celestial Dragon
What do we do?!
It's like my heart
is about to fly out...
and a Navy HQ admiral
will lead an entire army here!
I don't have a heart, though!
I'm not following you!
In any case,
Calm down first! What happened?
with so many rookies here
all at the same time,
An admiral?!
Geez!
Your face is a whole lot scarier,
if you ask me!
things are going to get ugly
in the New World.
I-It's Camie!
Aokiji?!
What's going on, Sanji?
It could even be Akainu or Kizaru...
Also, as for why Captain Kid's
bounty is higher than yours...
Camie's been kidnapped!
There's no way of knowing.
What?!
Navy Headquarters
is very close by, you see.
I wonder if everyone's already there?!
It's because he causes
serious harm to civilians.
A kidnapping team probably did it!
What makes them so high and mighty?!
Hey. Old man.
They share the Creators' blood!
I dunno why, but they let people
sell merfolk and fish-men
Not very charming, is he?
Don't play innocent.
even if they aren't bad guys!
That Haki energy just now
was you, wasn't it?
That's why I'm behind you guys 100%.
Creators?
Camie's gonna get sold!
We will save you!
The twenty kings who created the huge
World Government organization
Just who are you?
She's gonna be a slave forever
and it's all our fault!
Hang on, Camie!
Well, for now...
800 years ago!
A simple old man who coats ships.
There are lots of Human Shoppes
on these islands,
I just wanna have fun!
Their descendents are
the Celestial Dragons.
Get #17 ready!
so there's no telling
when or where she'll be sold!
With each passing generation,
they grow more reckless with power,
We don't even know who kidnapped her!
But I'm worried about
the old craftsman guy,
which is why they act like that now.
The archipelago is too big,
but for now let's all split up and...!
if he's in such a rough town.
Celestial Dragons...
Tell us exactly where you are
My husband will be fine.
"Former Vice Captain
of the Roger Pirates"
and then wait there.
Eh?! But...!
I just have a real penchant
That him?
After all, he's 100 times
stronger than you kids...
There are pros
when it comes to this sort of thing.
Yeah.
"Silvers Rayleigh,
the Pirate King's Right Hand Man"
No doubt about it.
100...
for young girls, you see...
Straw Hat Luffy.
I'm calling the Flying Fish Riders!
...times?
300 million Berries!
--Eh?!
--Huh?!
Camie's auction has started!
It's ok!
We've got 200 million berries, after all!
Shakky's Rip-Off Bar?!
We're not gonna let Camie-chan be sold!
Right! We're gonna go find the old coating guy!
The Celestial Dragons!
A young mermaid!
Are they planning to buy Camie, too?
Monkey-chan, is it? Welcome.
This one will go for quite a price!
Yeah!
Bastard...
You know about me?!
My friend's about to be bought and taken away.
Oh! It's the Sabaody Park!
Let me go!
You think I'll let this auction happen?!
Of course, I would know of the 300 million Berries, Luffy.
She's quite lively, too!
Let's try looking here for him!
I can't let that happen!
Alright, let's welcome our
customers and start the auction!
I'm not gonna lose!
Yeah! He might be hiding in the ferris wheel!
That's enough. Let's go, Sanji-kun!
However, there are currently,
I'll get Camie back, no matter what!
Nami-san!
We're sure to get a lot of high bids!
On the next episode of One Piece!
If we can't use force,
Alright, let's have fun!
people with higher bounties than you.
The Fist Explodes! Destroy the Auction
Save me, Hatchin!
then we'll get Camie back
using their rules!
You're not trying to find him!
Higher than Luffy?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
"The Target is Camie!! The Looming
Clutches of a Professional Kidnapper"
New Rivals Gather! The 11 Supernovas
Rescue Camie The Archipelago's
Lingering Dark History
Time Limit -- The Human Auction Begins
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!