Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around
the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
After landing on the
Sabaody Archipelago,
Luffy and friends gained
information from bar owner Shakky
about a coating craftsman
and eleven rookie pirates.
We're here! Sabaody Park!
Yay!
Camie's been kidnapped!
What?!
"Rescue Camie The Archipelago's
Lingering Dark History"
Damn, what's taking 'em so long?
Young Master!
They're here?
Yahoo! It's me, Handsome!
Oh, I mean, it's me, Duval!
And we're his men!
Hello, Young Master Black Leg!
Took you long enough,
Flying Fish Riders!
Hold on, Young Master!
We're the Rosy Life Riders now!
Fine, whatever! You're annoying!
Anyway, a mermaid has been kidnapped!
That's why I called for you!
Eh?! You encountered kidnappers?!
What horrible villains!
Hey, now! You guys are
kidnappers too, you know!
It's like they say,
set a thief to catch a thief.
So you guys help out, too!
But of course!
Thank you for calling upon us!
Thank you!
Can we really count on these guys?!
By the by, I tried visiting
a town with girls in it!
Head! Head! Look, girls!
Nice. Let's go!
How was it?
It was great!
Hey there, girls!
Hello! I'm Handsome!
What do you say we take a drive
on the sea on my Motobalo?
And...?
I wasn't as popular
as I thought I'd be...
You can fix how you look on the outside,
but there's no fixing how
you look on the inside...
But that's all right!
I understand, Young Master!
We just need to find the mermaid
before she gets sold, right?!
That's right.
I figure you must have some knowledge
of the Sabaody Archipelago.
But of course!
These waters are
pretty much like our backyard!
You can count on us!
Okay! Hop on!
We're gonna take these Flying Fish?
We sure are!
Okay! Ready when you are!
Right!
So, how're we gonna find her?
Young Master!
Those of a trade know each other's ways!
I know of several kidnapping teams
that could be behind this!
We'll start by picking up
your Straw Hat friends
scattered around the
Sabaody Archipelago!
At the same time,
we'll figure out which kidnapping
team abducted the mermaid!
Let's go, men!
Alright! We're coming to
save you now, Camie-chan!
Hey, Duval! Go faster!
Young Master!
Motobalo is already at full speed!
Great! We're at full speed!
Eh?!
This is full speed?!
Let's go!
I hope it'll be all right...
Sanji! What are we going to do?!
Listen, Chopper!
Don't go anywhere,
no matter what!
I will send someone to get you!
Okay!
Hey, Luffy! Sanji says not to go--
Camie!
I think it's dangerous to split up
at a time like this, Brook...
Eh?
You're too calmed down!
This is a major shock, you know!
Camie was kidnapped!
She's gonna get sold and be a slave
for the rest of her life!
Chopper-san.
Sanji-san gave us precise instructions
about what we should do.
However we act, we'll spend the
same amount of time waiting.
I see!
Acting flustered won't solve anything.
In which case, why don't we spend our
time waiting calmly and tranquilly?
Oh! Now I see!
Head!
We've reached Sabaody Park!
Pick up one Straw Hat member each!
Right!
They were told to wait by
Public Transponder Snail #5,
which should be right around here!
There they are!
Two of them, down by those benches!
Hey, you two! We're here to--!
What are you guys relaxing for?!
Oh, Usopp-san is here to pick us up...
Luffy and the others went off somewhere,
but we tranquilly stayed put
like we were told to.
Let's go!
Operation: Save Camie
With Everything We Got!
All right! It's time to go all out!
Let's go!
He got mad at us, Brook!
I regret it!
I regret it a little now!
Keep checking up on all the kidnapping
teams on the archipelago!
Figure out who's behind this!
And don't forget to retrieve
the other Straw Hat members!
Roger! Let's split up!
Right!
Alright!
Hurry, Rosy Life Riders!
We have no time to lose!
That should be good enough.
Good enough, my ass!
Can't you do something about this cow?!
I should've ridden a Flying Fish, too!
Eh? Did you say "handsome" just now?
Hell, no!
You're the head of your gang, Duval!
Why aren't you the fastest
one in your team?!
Eh? What are you talking about?
Of course I'm the most
handsome person in my team!
Just step on it, you idiot!
Alright, here we go!
Hey! Any doctors here?!
You, there!
This is a general outpatient clinic!
What's wrong with him?!
He needs urgent care.
This is bad!
Let's see... Nope, no collar.
Does having a collar matter?
Yes.
Medical treatment for
slaves costs 50% more,
so sometimes it's quicker
to buy a new one...
This guy is hurt, that's all.
You gonna help him or not?!
Yes, yes! Right away!
Carry him right inside!
What an annoying island...
Guess I'll head back to the ship.
Grove #1, as I recall.
"Human Shoppe"
A mermaid?
Get out if you're just
window-shoppin', kid!
Someone caught our friend!
Has anyone come here trying
to sell a mermaid, old guy?!
Any information at all!
If you know anything, please tell us!
Don't know nothin'.
Besides,
it's in your best interest not to stick
your nose into that kinda stuff...
You're sure nobody's come here
trying to sell a mermaid?!
I-I'm sure! No one's tried to!
Stop it, Straw Hat!
It'll be harder to look for her
if you cause trouble!
Y-You're free to look around
the place if you want!
Octoguy! Let's look around the shop!
Okay!
All these guys are
being caught and sold?
Camie...
Hey!
Well, Octoguy?! Pappagu?!
She's not here...
Camie!
Do you have any others, old guy?!
I don't got a warehouse,
so all you see here is all I got.
We have no choice!
Let's check elsewhere, Straw Hat!
Just a minute, now!
It sounds like you folks
are in real need of a mermaid!
You have a mermaid?!
The only mermaid I have
is this girl here: Marin!
"Marin"
I'll give you a discount! Whadya say?!
Please buy me, kiddo.
You ain't no mermaid!
You're just that old guy from earlier!
It's so hard to breathe underwater.
Hey!
C-Camie...
Camie!
Where are you?!
Whoa, check it out!
It's Straw Hat Luffy from East Blue!
That's him?!
It's possible she hasn't been sold yet.
If we can just figure out
which kidnapping team it was...!
Hey! There's no reason to cry that much!
We will find Camie!
Darn it...!
It's all my fault!
The amusement park is the perfect spot
for kidnappers to do their work!
I knew full well how badly
they want mermaids, and yet...!
Hey! Look at all these
kinds of ice cream!
What do you guys want?!
Wait, let me choose some, too!
Wait here a minute, Camie!
Okay!
Choose something yummy for me too!
I don't want that to be my
last conversation with Camie!
It's my fault!
I let her go to the amusement park!
Yeah,
I've always dreamed of this,
ever since I was a little girl!
I've never been so high up before!
I'll cherish this memory forever!
Thank you!
I dunno why exactly,
but she was really happy!
Going to the amusement park
was a good idea!
No, it wasn't!
In fact,
it's not even a good idea for fish-men
or merfolk to come to these islands!
But Hachi was so intent
on being helpful to you guys that--!
Pappagu! Don't say any more!
What are you talking about?!
Why isn't it good for you guys
to come to these islands?!
Uhh, well...
Kidnappers aren't the only enemies
Camie and Hachi have here.
All of the people living on this
archipelago are their enemies!
200 years ago?!
Yes.
A terrible history that actually
took place up until 200 years ago...
The fish-man and merfolk races
were classified as fish
and were persecuted
by people all over the world.
Everyone looked down on them.
They looked down
on those strong fish-men...?!
No one can stand up to the
power of sheer numbers.
The persecution continued unabated
until the World Government
declared its friendship
with Fish-Man Island.
One other relic of humankind's
terrible history
is the culture of human
trafficking and slavery...
And on this archipelago,
it's still quietly condoned.
Which is why I wondered
if they might still discriminate
against fish-men and merfolk here.
Discrimination?
Unless you take these islands
for what they are,
you'll only make a fool out of yourself!
Which is why I should've stopped Camie,
even if it meant being mean and strict!
Is that why Hachi and Camie are both
concealing their identities here?
I only hope it's an ungrounded fear...
Girl! Robin!
Franky!
Will you quit calling me
"girl" already?!
Get on the Flying Fish!
The mermaid's been kidnapped!
Camie-chan's...
...been kidnapped?!
Camie...!
I'm sorry, Straw Hat.
I wanted to help you out,
but I caused you trouble instead...
What're you guys talking about?
There isn't one thing
you guys should be sorry for!
All three of you are my friends now!
We will rescue Camie, no matter what!
So stop crying!
Straw...!
You're...!
Straw Hat!
It's the Flying Fish Riders!
We've been lookin' everywhere
for ya! Jump on!
Octoguy! Can you jump up?
Y-Yeah!
Pappagu!
Octoguy!
I'm okay!
Pappagu!
Let's go save Camie!
Straw Hat...!
"Sabaody Archipelago - Grove #1"
"Human Auctioning House"
Oh, Peterman!
Have an item to auction, do you?
Is there still time to submit an entry?
Today's big item is a giant.
Your entry won't fetch a very high price
unless it's really something!
Here, have a look for yourself.
Wh-Whoa! That's a mermaid!
Hey! Where did you catch it?!
That's a secret.
This is gonna be today's
main attraction!
Alright, make sure you
sell it good, now!
Oh, that top-quality item will sell!
For a lot!
Come by later to get your money!
I look forward to it!
What a pleasant surprise,
Saint Roswald! Saint Shalria!
Welcome!
I humbly ask that kneeling and such
be unnecessary inside the building...
That will be fine.
They would make for poor
auctions otherwise.
Thank you very much!
Please, use the VIP seats!
Brother Charloss is certainly
taking a long time!
That's what he gets
for riding a sluggish human.
If you're going to ride something,
make it a fish-man.
They have ten times
the strength of humans.
Celestial Dragons...
Slaves...
Human Shoppes...
That's...!
Captain Kid from South Blue!
Compared to the callowness
of greedy authority figures,
the criminals of the world
have much more humanity.
It's because scum rules
the world that new scum is born.
Don't they understand?
We're as endearing as we are mean.
Right, Killer?
Without a doubt.
If there's someone interesting,
should we buy 'em?
Boss. Look...
I recognize him...
Trafalgar Law, from North Blue.
Worth 200 million...
I've heard pretty bad rumors about him.
He's got a bad attitude, too!
Disco-san!
We have an incredible item today!
Today's big entry is a giant, right?
I already know.
You can count on me.
I'll make sure it sells
for a high price.
Are the by-bidders ready to go?
No, not that! It's a mermaid!
A young mermaid!
It's going to be one heated auction!
Seriously?!
Let me go! You're hurting me!
Let go, I said!
Stop!
Hey, quit thrashing around!
We need to figure out your collar size!
Damn this collar!
If only...
If only it wasn't for this!
Damn it!
No! Hatchin!
Why, you!
You'd best behave
unless you wanna get hurt!
Hold it!
Don't be roughhousing
our important merchandise!
Disco-san!
Oh, is this the mermaid
that just came in?
Yes, sir!
How truly rare!
Lively and strong!
This should fetch a high price!
Who submitted it?
The Hound Pets.
Peterman, huh?
He does damn good work.
And yet, the Flying Fish Riders
haven't submitted anything this time...
Well, in any case,
there's no question this'll sell for a lot!
Blehhh!
What was that look for?!
Damn you!
You're just a lousy fish!
Don't get any wrong ideas!
Stop, Disco-san!
That's important merchandise!
It'll lose its value if you hurt it!
At least kick it in the stomach
or somewhere that's covered up by clothes!
Hatchan is going to beat you up so bad!
Why, you...! Still talking back, huh?!
Hey! Gimme that collar!
Y-Yes, sir!
I'll put the collar on it myself...
Hold it still, now!
No!
Disco-san?!
Hey! What happened, Disco-san?!
The auction's just
about to start, too...!
Doctor! Get a doctor!
Hey. Old man.
Don't play innocent.
That Haki energy just now
was you, wasn't it?
Just who are you?
A simple old man who coats ships.
"Former Vice Captain
of the Roger Pirates"
I just have a real penchant
"Silvers Rayleigh,
the Pirate King's Right Hand Man"
for young girls, you see...
We're not gonna let Camie-chan be sold!
Bastard...
You think I'll let this auction happen?!
That's enough. Let's go, Sanji-kun!
Nami-san!
If we can't use force,
then we'll get Camie back
using their rules!
On the next episode of One Piece!
Time Limit -- The Human Auction Begins
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!