Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
And so men rushed onto the Grand
Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
After Luffy and friends set out
in search of a coating craftsman,
The crew, on its way to the New World,
Camie was kidnapped at Sabaody Park.
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
...Some guy brought in a mermaid
just before the auctions started!
Sabaody Archipelago!
After landing on the Sabaody Archipelago,
The Straw Hat crew landed
on the Sabaody Archipelago
H-Hold on! Who was this guy?!
The Straw Hat crew landed
on the Sabaody Archipelago
the Straw Hat crew succeeded in
rescuing the kidnapped Camie.
After learning that she had already been
taken to the auction house on Grove #1...
to search for a ship coating craftsman
to help them reach Fish-Man Island.
Realizing that their ship needs to be
coated in order to reach Fish-Man Island,
However, a battle began
with marines lying in wait.
During the adventure, Camie, a mermaid
who was with them, was kidnapped.
who was with them, was kidnapped
We're all set to escape!
...Nami and company were the first to arrive.
the Straw Hat crew and Hachi's group
stopped by the Sabaody Archipelago.
and about to be sold as a slave.
After determining her location,
The group then attempted to break
through the navy's siege and escape.
And, while the auctioning continued,
Nami and company attempted
to win her in an auction.
It's time for the unveiling!
Take a good look!
Luffy, after storming the
auction house to save her...
Luffy and four others had yet
to reach the auction house!
However, Camie, a mermaid accompanying them,
All the way from Fish-Man
Island, the mermaid Camie!
found herself kidnapped and auctioned off.
"Roger and Rayleigh
-- The King of the Pirates and His Right Hand Man"
We will save you! Hang on, Camie!
500 million!
Camie!
They're selling Camie now!
Alright! We're gonna get her
back! We have 200 million here!
Are you alive, Peterman-san?!
I'll buy it for 500 million Berries!
"The Fist Explodes! Destroy the Auction"
How dare they do this to our boss!
However, Nami's plan failed
in an unforeseen manner.
Dammit!
Damn them!
Quit your squirming!
Still...
Damn...!
I'll buy it for 500 million Berries!
I never expected Duval to have such
a handsome face under that mask!
Entry #15! The beautiful dancer, Pashia!
Now you die!
So suddenly?! We don't have that much!
We can't let this happen!
Incredibly, her starting
price of 800,000 Berries
We can't let our friend get
bought and taken away like this!
Well, see ya! Feel free
to call us again anytime!
has rocketed to the sky-high
price of 7.2 million Berries!
Stop, Straw! You guys'll
get in huge trouble too!
Just then...
We'll be at your beck and call until you
can safely set sail for Fish-Man Island!
Luffy!
Luffy-chin!
You annoy me, too!
I've been wanting to meet you...
Okay! Thanks, you guys!
Camie! We've been looking
everywhere! What a relief!
...Monkey D. Luffy.
No problem at all!
I'm finally here...
Just quit winking.
Hold on, Straw Hat! What are you doing?!
Oh, and one other thing...
Hachi tried to hold Luffy back as
he went to rescue Camie, but...
Okay! Now that things are
starting to getting fired up,
"Admiral Kizaru Takes Action! Sabaody
Archipelago Thrown into Chaos"
Quit your squirming!
Don't forget this, Miss Mermaid!
He's a fish-man!
Oh! My backpack!
what do you say to this
next piece of merchandise?!
That idiot Peterman had it!
Hachi was then gunned down
by a Celestial Dragon!
What a relief! It's still going on!
This is bad! This town-- this
whole archipelago-- is in danger!
Thank you!
However, I heard him say
"Entry #15" just now,
Don't... Don't be mad...
Alright! Let's go, Life is Rosy Riders!
Straw Hat Luffy supposedly kicked
a Celestial Dragon's ass!
You promised not to defy
the Celestial Dragons,
so I believe it's almost over.
Yes, Hand-Rose!
This thing really annoys me to no end!
At the auction house on Grove #1!
even if you saw someone get shot...!
Their shouts sure change a lot.
What?!
It'll be all right. Just stay still.
They're probably trying
to find one that clicks.
Apparently Kid and Law are there, too!
That Straw Hat bastard!
What was he thinking?!
Take this! And this!
You lousy fish, still blabbering
on even though I shot you!
Stop! Stop it!
Now, then. Let us hurry inside.
Doesn't he know that an admiral
from Navy Headquarters
You annoy me!
Hey. Go sell this one too, while
we're here. I don't need it anymore.
We need to get Hachi into a bed!
will bring a warship here if
anyone hurts a Celestial Dragon?!
Camie!
What's with that look, you?!
"Shakky's Rip-Off Bar"
Hey, Shakky! I'm back!
Has our ship been coated?!
I will make arrangements at once.
It was completed yesterday!
We set sail for Fish-Man Island immediately!
You guys'll get in huge trouble too!
He took the collar off barehanded?!
A Celestial Dragon...
Oh, welcome back, Ray-san. That
was sooner than I expected.
We can't just sit around
while an admiral shows up!
Another World Noble is here...
Thanks to the help of Rayleigh, a coating
craftsman who suddenly appeared,
Straw Hat-ya...?
Yes, sir!
Defy them and a navy admiral
will come running, huh...
Is he serious?!
I'm impressed you guys managed to find him.
Captain! Let's get out of here!
Luffy and company succeeded
in rescuing Camie.
Ol' Hachi's been seriously hurt.
We need to get him into a bed.
I want a mermaid. I hope
they have one this time.
There's no point in staying here!
You annoy me, too!
However...
Guess that dumbass's captain
is an even bigger dumbass!
Alright, you criminals! Release
the Roswald family at once!
What happened?!
Merfolk are apparently a
rather hard species to catch,
This is bad! I'll get a bed ready right away!
An admiral will be arriving shortly!
so I'm unsure if one will be up
for auction this time or not...
Oh, you said you had something
to tell me afterward, old guy...
If I ever run into 'em in the
New World... I'll destroy 'em!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Wh-What a pleasant surprise, Saint Charloss!
Take me to my seat already.
Repel!
Eh?!
Yes, right away!
On the Pirate King's ship?!
Room.
Causing trouble with Navy Headquarters
with the New World right in sight...
Yes. I'm Silvers Rayleigh,
the ship's vice-captain.
Wh-What's this circle?!
Please watch your step!
Shambles.
"Major Panic! Desperate
Struggle at the Auction House"
What a truly troublesome lot they are...
Nice to meet you.
Watch out! All three of 'em have powers!
Vice-captain?!
Focus on getting ready to set sail.
Yes, sir! Right away, Captain Drake!
You didn't tell them, Hatchan?
Now, then. Who's going to show up?
We only needed his help
with the coating, so...
"Break Through the Siege! The
Navy vs. the Three Captains"
Brother Charloss is finally here.
Oh? You didn't realize it?
I know his name so well!
It's in so many books!
Given the situation, I somehow doubt
this is an all-out arrest plot.
It's definitely a name everyone
hears at least once...
It's Straw Hat Luffy they're after, right?
I think I'd like to see what
an admiral is actually like.
Gold Roger...
I seem to vaguely recall a rookie named
that long ago, but I'm not sure...
Hey! Get walkin'!
You can't be serious, Apoo-san!
Let's just get out of here!
How do such a big-shot and
an octopus know each other?
Okay! It looks like we're ready to continue!
Entry #16 is none other than
the captain of a pirate ship!
Hachi rescued me over 20 years ago,
when I was stranded in the sea.
Rescue team has arrived at the back
entrance! Now entering the building!
Captain Hawkins! It's dangerous
here! Let's set sail immediately!
A captain?
Calm down.
He saved his life. He was still
a child at the time, though.
Feast your eyes on this man, with
a bounty of 17 million Berries!
I am not destined to die today.
S-Saint Charloss...
Hachi and I remained close after that,
until he joined the Sun Pirates.
"Holy Land of Marie Jois"
Goes by the name of Lacuba!
He's known as a tactful strategist,
You mean Arlong, right?
but his well-trained body
is another great attribute!
You can use him as a horse, for heavy
physical labor, or as a punching bag!
Still...
That brat again?! It's one
thing after the other!
Even though Gold Roger was
executed 22 years ago,
He has many uses, indeed!
The rescue team has made it inside!
What's with that entire family's bloodline?!
you didn't get your head chopped
off for being vice-captain?
All soldiers will commence attack
as soon as the hostages are secured!
Now, then!
Reports indicate the presence
of the Straw Hat crew,
Yes, sir!
Eustass Captain Kid and his crew,
and Trafalgar Law and his crew.
The navy caught the entire crew, didn't it?
Hurry! On the double!
Ch-Charloss!
Thirteen people with bounties
have been confirmed!
Rescue team has reached the stage!
Of them, five are rookies
worth over 100 million each!
Bastard! Don't tell me you just--!
Naturally, the key offender
appears to be Monkey D. Luffy,
There they are! Should we capture them?!
Sorry, guys.
who assaulted the Celestial Dragons!
Punching this guy means a navy admiral
is gonna come here with a warship...
No, we can't! Our orders
are to secure the hostages!
We've lost contact with the
guards at the Human Shop--
He collapsed!
What happened?!
oh, I mean Employment Office.
The Celestial Dragons' lives
take precedence over all else!
I saw blood!
I missed my chance to cut him down
because you beat him up first.
I believe they may have all been subdued...
We need to ascertain their well-being first!
Hey! Shut the curtains!
Hachi! Hang on!
In any case, this act of taking
three Celestial Dragons hostage
We weren't caught.
You're all in big trouble now...!
What happened?!
is a vile and unprecedented transgression!
We can't help it! That's just how Luffy is!
Roger turned himself in.
Have they made any demands?
Alright, then...
I can't believe mortars don't
work on any of them...!
No, none at the moment...
What just happened?
Guess that makes it clear
what we gotta do now.
They really do live up
to their notorious names!
He bit his tongue off.
The government might've made it
sound like they had caught him
He decided he'd rather die here
This is no time to be impressed!
Hold out until the admiral arrives!
I think the key to Camie's collar
is probably somewhere backstage!
Whatever the case may be, Sengoku-san,
we'll need to take action
as a way to show its power, though.
than live a wretched life as someone's pet.
Like we can really wait that long.
The King of the Pirates
turned himself in?! Why?!
I need to tend to Hachi's
injury! You get the key!
given that World Nobles are the victims here.
In some cases, that could
be the smart choice.
Guys...!
Kizaru...
Allow me to go. Rest easy; I won't be long.
Because we saw an end to our journey.
A head!
Charloss...!
Hey! Don't drop me!
Brother Charloss! Not even
Father has ever struck you!
How are you talking?!
I dunno! My body feels
hot for some reason, too!
Camie...
"Justice"
About four years before the
day of his public execution,
Where's the mermaid already?!
Curse you!
Body?! What are you talking about?!
How dare you, a commoner,
lay a hand on my son!
Camie must be so scared...
This guy's body is burning up over there!
Roger caught a fatal illness.
Just hang on a little longer!
It's burning up! My body's burning up!
Th-They've made the Celestial Dragons mad!
We will save her!
Not even Roger could avoid the suffering
Huh?! You can feel it?!
Run! Get outside!
Good thing we have that
treasure from Thriller Bark!
Oww! Oww! Hot!
Someone! Pour water on it, hurry!
that this terminal,
incurable disease brought.
Thank you so much, you guys...
Leave! Quick!
But, there was one man with the
skill to ease his suffering:
Quit pushing!
I thought I was a goner...!
No good.
Watch out, guys!
I'll teach you what happens
when you assault us,
Damn! I'm not gonna make any
money off of you now, you idiot!
That guy! Don't enter the circles he makes!
a man at the Twin Capes named Crocus,
the descendants of this world's Creators!
who was the most respected lighthouse
keeper and doctor in the sea.
Room.
Disco-san!
Hell if we care, you bastard!
A doctor's on the way!
Y-You mean this?
We asked for his help and brought him
on as ship doctor for our final voyage.
This is no laughing matter!
How dare you strike Saint Roswald!
Yeah, just like this!
Geez! Do you know how much it's
gonna cost to treat you now?!
Joue!
This is your shop, you know!
Concasser!
Finally, three years later,
while managing to escape death,
The mermaid's next, right?!
Mister Doflamingo...!
Where are you right now?!
We've been cut!
Go, Franky! Free Camie-chan!
Yes! Everything's all set!
It can go on at any time!
What in the world's going on?!
Roger achieved what was
said to be impossible:
Alright! Super leave it to me!
The shop has lost all credibility, and
then there's Roswald's family too!
Good!
This super big-event item should blast
away the chilly mood in the air!
Make yourselves comfortable.
Guards! Get them! Seize the pirates!
he conquered the Grand Line.
They're definitely going to lash out at us!
This'll be over before you know it.
They just keep coming!
Bring her out now, men!
Do something to fix things!
Third Gear!
Right!
Hatchin... Everyone...
Bone Balloon!
Seriously... Human trafficking
is so old-fashioned, you idiot.
What?!
C-C-Crocus-san?!
This is the arm of a giant!
At the Twin Capes?!
What a ruckus. Sounds like
something's happened...
Don't be scared! Ready your
weapons! Fire! Fire like crazy!
It's all about smiles now! Smiles!
Oh, that brings back memories!
Huh?! That old guy wasn't
there for 50 years straight?!
Disco, I'm giving the shop to you.
#13? Didn't I pass by #2 just now?
But, Brigadier General! Our weapons...
So don't be callin' me anymore!
...are flying away!
Must be my imagination.
He was a member of the Pirate King's crew?!
All out...
That man had so much bloodlust...
Wh-What?!
Well, then...
Come to think of it, he did mention
being a ship's doctor for a few years!
Pirate Hunter Zoro... He ain't
worth 120 million for nothin'!
What?! You're abandoning us during
the worst crisis we've ever had?!
So he was a pirate for
those three years, then?!
Old man...
Get mixed up with him and you won't survive,
Quiet, you annoying bastard!
Only a fool would protect a lousy fish!
no matter how many lives you have!
The fact that you've met him
must mean he's still doing well!
While you sit there blaming
me for your own misfortune
I never wanna meet that guy
again, that's for sure...
Gum-Gum...
a "New Era" draws ever closer, Disco-kun.
Crocus agreed to come aboard
...Whip!
What the...?!
because there was a certain group
of pirates he wanted to look for.
The navy has given orders forcing
me-- no, us-- into active duty!
Hey! Hold it!
Brook! It was you guys he set
out to find, no doubt about it!
Gotcha!
Aren't you guys...
What's going on?!
Tatsu...
What is this?!
...Maki!
Crocus-san...! You even
went to such lengths...!
He was only a crewmember for three years,
What brings you here again?
You guys gave me fake
directions, didn't you?!
Knowing this, what do you see
on the horizon, Disco-kun?
but he was unquestionably one of us!
Strong Right!
Nothing of the sort! We gave you
genuine directions to Grove #1!
At this age now, it'd be
great to see him again...
What in the...?
The Whitebeard Pirates versus
the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
...And Fresh Fire!
Then why'd you run away?!
So, what happened after he conquered the sea?
B-Because you glared at us
with such a vicious look!
Outta the way, outta the way!
Huh?!
Such violence!
Zoro!
That's when it all began.
The world started calling
Roger "King of the Pirates."
We gotta hurry to Grove #1! Just get on!
Curse you all...!
Please evacuate as far away as you can!
Halt!
Stay away!
No watching, please! These
are dangerous people!
He hadn't been King of the Pirates
the entire time before or anything.
What is that guy?!
This is no time to be admiring people.
Hold on! Not this again...!
The slave I bought is still inside!
"Aaaaaaaah"
Titles hold no meaning
for a man about to die.
Watch out for thunderclouds!
What are you doing?!
Wh-What the...?!
Have the mortars arrived yet?
Oops...
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Yes, most of them! We're
hurrying to set them up!
But Roger was overjoyed.
Someday I'm gonna cut you in two...
Has HQ said anything?
That Admiral Kizaru is coming, but
the vanguard will consist of...
Hey! Those are my legs!
Sorry, Zoro.
Let's hurry to Grove #1!
Then whose are those?!
You have too many chests!
Of them?! They're coming here?!
He loved doing everything in a flashy way...
Don't look at me!
#16, pirate Lacuba, was extremely nervous
and collapsed after a nosebleed,
Giant Pistol!
Yes, sir! That's what they said...
Eat this!
So sorry!
Whether it was celebrating or fighting...
He even seemed to enjoy thinking
out a plan for the future,
so his introduction will have
to wait for another day.
even though he wouldn't be a part of it.
Nervous?
Yeah!
What crap...
But, ladies and gentlemen!
Eventually, as per captain's orders, the
Roger Pirates were secretly disbanded.
The next item I have for you is a
super-incredible piece of merchandise
Whoa, now! This, already?!
Amazing! I don't believe my eyes!
sure to instantly blow all this trouble away!
One by one, everyone discretely left.
You sure know how to go berserk, Captain...
You intend to defy us to
the very end, do you?!
As comrades, we all risked
our lives together,
They're quite reliable, indeed!
but I know almost nothing about where
they are or what they're doing now.
What an impatient bunch.
Gum-Gum...
I'm going to remove your collar
now. Are you ready, girl?
...Battle-Axe!
Camie isn't for sale!
Hold on, old man! Don't
be crazy! It'll explode!
Then, about a year after we disbanded,
What's with that, Straw Hat-ya?
That's not a very good finish...
Roger turned himself in and was arrested.
We've seen a slave's collar explode before!
Call for a navy admiral and a warship!
Really?
It was then announced that
he would be publicly executed
Their formations don't amount to crap now.
That's a bad idea! A very bad idea!
Let them see who's boss!
in Loguetown, the East
Blue town he was born in.
When are we gonna get there?!
Are you sure about this, Luffy?!
Soon! We're in Grove #1 now!
Brigadier General! It appears all the
pirates have exited the auction house!
A highly sought after item, to be sure!
W-Wait! Franky is looking
for the key as we speak!
Straw Hat, the busty girl, the
young master, the swordsman,
Observe this silhouette!
We should really wait until he
finds it and brings it back!
the panties guy, and the
reindeer have already arrived!
Yeah! Stop him, Straw Hat!
Oh! Could it be?!
Yes! An incredible item!
Huh? That means the only ones
who are late are Robin, Brook...
I hear that many of the young
faces in the town square that day
I won't say much. Look upon
it with your own eyes!
They intend to escape! Don't let
these runts make mockeries of us!
...and me?!
went on to make names for themselves
on the high seas today.
Now for the moment you've been waiting for!
Oh! How could this happen
to the great Usopp-sama?!
It's time for the unveiling!
Take a good look!
We have plenty more reinforcements!
Damn! Not here, either!
The three hostages have been
secured at the back entrance!
Hurry! Go!
Quit thrashing around! That's dangerous!
Dammit!
The world focused its attention
on the Pirate King's execution.
Aim the mortars at those without powers!
Come on! Faster!
Go!
It'll be all right. Just stay still.
Firing squads to the rear! We're
now commencing our all-out attack!
Oh, what a beautiful sky!
Wait, huh?!
All the way from Fish-Man
Island, the mermaid Camie!
Take those pirates down!
I didn't attend it.
It's real! A young mermaid!
Whew, I owe you one...
You know better than to jump off early!
Amazing!
I dunno what kind of power he used...
What a find!
You're the one who shook me off!
Here we go. They got no plan at
all. It's a free-for-all now.
The final words he said went like this...
You were going too fast. Bye.
We'll be going on ahead!
Oh! I'm back to normal!
It's Hatchin and the others!
They came to rescue me!
Wait for me, guys!
Alright, Straw Hat...
...but the one thing for sure is
that he's no ordinary old man!
Camie!
I'm glad I got a chance to meet you.
A pirate struck a Celestial Dragon!
They're selling Camie now!
And that somehow means it's okay
to leave Camie-chan in his hands?!
Alright! We're gonna get her
back! We have 200 million here!
But next time we meet,
I won't show any mercy.
Navy Headquarters is going
to send a warship now!
Dammit! What's Franky doing?!
I'm telling you, it's too dangerous!
It won't come off without the key!
Camie!
Hooray! A mermaid! They're selling a mermaid!
"Justice"
I see that there's immense interest
in this, our first mermaid in a while!
I'm not going to die, partner...
I can't believe this! I should have
just paid for my slave and left!
But I'm going to find the One Piece!
It's ringing! What're we gonna do?!
Now, then! How much shall we start from?
Watch it, you!
It would be a waste to
use that to buy someone.
The World Government and the
navy must've been shocked.
I think I'll use it in a
more productive way instead.
Let's make the first move to
win! We will get her back!
With only one last remark from Roger,
Stop! Stop it!
the public execution meant to serve
as an example to other pirates
All right, then! Let's begin!
There's no end to 'em!
That's for sure! I'm gonna wear
down my heels at this rate!
Camie!
instead became the opening
ceremony of the Great Pirate Age!
Bidding will start at...
500 million!
Say your prayers!
Duck!
Hey, Kid! What're you
just standing there for?!
36 Pound Cannon!
My treasure?
Hold on! I'm coming!
You know, Killer...
If you want it, you can have it!
Are you trying to kill us?!
Find it!
What?!
On our journey up to this point,
we've been laughed at and ridiculed
I did warn you.
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
I'll buy it for 500 million Berries!
We couldn't hear you!
Hey! What was that?!
whenever we mentioned getting
our hands on the One Piece.
In his last few seconds, he
changed the dim flame of his life
See, I told you! Now Camie's...!
And each time that happened, I
slaughtered everyone who laughed.
into a hellfire that spread across the world!
But what lies ahead is a sea of death
Camie!
for those who don't got
the guts to mention it.
What's all this now?!
Don't scare me like that!
Hatchin!
Your collar and handcuffs are already off!
Are you okay?! They didn't do
anything bad to you, did they?!
Let's meet again in the New World!
I've never laughed as much
as I did on that night.
I'm fine! But you've been hurt!
500 million...?
Nor have I ever cried as much...
Don't worry! Who do you take me for?!
It's no good. We can't compete with him.
Let's go, men!
...or drank as much as I did on that night.
Yeah!
I'm Hachi, the takoyaki seller!
It came off...
Our captain lived one hell of a life!
Just hang on a little
longer! Wait right there!
How could that happen so suddenly?!
We don't even have close to that much!
C-Camie!
Yeah! Hatchin! Everyone!
What another waste of money. You have
piranhas in your aquarium, you know.
Just like the rumors said...
Yeah. He's one crazy bastard.
Trafalgar Law!
I'm going to have them chase her for fun.
Camie! Thank goodness!
Straw Hat-ya Luffy...
How dare you toy with my comrades earlier!
Merfolk are the fastest
swimmers in the world!
A 300 million Berry bounty, huh...
Bepo.
I can't hear what they're saying outside...
What the hell?! I finally manage
to find 'em, but then...!
Help me get out of here, Hatchin!
Oh! You found them? Well done!
Camie...
Is she gonna get sold to a Celestial
Dragon while we stand here, helpless?!
But we no longer need them.
Here, you carry this girl.
Huh? You're going back inside, Captain?
U-Umm... Th-Thanks!
It's like we just heard something incredible!
Camie...!
It's almost like a different story,
hearing it from someone who was there!
What in the hell's going on
here?! Who are you, anyway?!
Then it's almost as if Roger created
this Great Pirate Era on purpose!
An uproar is already underway. There's
a flood of people at the entrance.
Huh? What did he do?
That... we still can't say.
That geezer did something mysterious again!
Hey, Luffy!
Our only choice is to jump into the
fray! Just crash into it, if you would!
Oh! There you are!
Roger is dead.
Alright! It's time for us to go, too!
Understood!
Huh?! I-I need to prepare myself first!
Only the people living
now can create this era.
Here we go!
Let's do it!
I'm certain there are people who
inherited something from Roger
My "can't go to auction houses" disease...!
on that day in the town square.
Everyone seems to be at a loss for
words, but I'll ask just the same.
Your good friend, Shanks,
is probably one of them.
More flying fish!
Just who is that old guy?!
Eh? You know Shanks, old guy?
Thank you!
Are there any bids higher than 500 million?
Take care!
Have you also heard of the East
Blue pirate known as Buggy?
Cien Fleurs!
Alright! Bring it on!
Can't we do something about this?!
Isn't there anything we can do?!
Stop! Stop it!
Wing!
Buggy...
Oh, Sanji!
Alright! Good luck!
The two of them were apprentices on our ship.
Isn't there, Sanji?!
Off I go!
Luffy! Look over there!
Nami!
Clutch!
Hey! Young Master and friends!
Eh?! Shanks was on the Pirate King's ship?!
We can't let this happen!
He took the collar off barehanded?!
We can't let our friend get
bought and taken away like this!
Hey, almost-slaves!
Flying Fish!
Hey!
What? He didn't tell you about that?
All the buyers took off! You
should scram while you can, too!
This is bad... I never even
imagined this happening.
I just cracked my back...!
Eh? Did you just say "handsome"?
Brook.
I ran into him again on these
islands about 10 years ago,
Oh, that's right! Milk heals
me since I'm nothing but bones!
Here!
No. I didn't. Not at all.
We stepped back, thinking money
could solve this problem,
Anyway, we're all set to escape! Right, men?!
but things've just gotten worse!
and he'd lost his trademark straw
hat, along with his left arm.
If not, then that'll bring
bidding straight to a close!
If that geezer took out these
guards all at once too,
I'm nothing but bones
and bones! Viva calcium!
Yes! Life is rosy!
When I asked what had happened,
he cheerfully spoke about you.
then he must know how to use
magic or some type of sorcery!
I'll just have to help her
escape into the ocean by force!
I wasn't expecting help from them again,
but I guess we are in a hurry...
Now, then! Pardon my late entrance!
He's got powers or something!
Damn pirate!
Don't be stupid! What about that
collar?! It'll make Camie blow up!
He said something about
your straw hat, though...
Clutch!
Alright! Let's go!
It was a real shock, Rayleigh-san!
Guess I have no choice...!
There was a kid in East Blue who said
the same thing Captain Roger did.
Straw Hat's getting away!
Then... we'll have to get the
key to the collar somehow!
Damn! Guard the mermaid at all costs!
That straw hat suits dauntless men very well.
Lullaby Flanc!
500 million! She sold for 500 million!
Those same words of our captain!
I've been wanting to meet you...
Exterminate them at once!
...Monkey D. Luffy.
And I've wanted to meet you--
Monkey D. Luffy-- ever since.
Escape while you can, you two!
Sorry to keep you waiting, folks!
Yeah!
How do you know him, Luffy?!
There's nothing to fear now
that Usopp-sama is here!
I don't know him! Really!
Quit sleepin'!
Time is up!
I think he used what's called "Haki."
Are you guys with those pirates?!
The hero is always the
last to make an entrance!
I did it!
N-No, not us! We aren't pirates!
It's almost like a miniature
version of the world.
I don't know much about it either, though...
Shanks!
What a pathetic farce. Let's go.
I am the headliner here, after all!
I'm afraid I can't, in good mind, babble
on about things Shanks hasn't told you.
Nueve Fleurs!
Sorry about that, fellows. I didn't
realize other pirates were watching.
The bidding has ended!
Huh?
Twist!
S-So high up!
In any case, you've done
well to come this far!
You must be quite strong to have
withstood that with no problem at all.
Today's super showcase
item, the mermaid Camie...
Since I'm here, maybe I'll
just fret for a little longer!
I'm sure he's eagerly waiting
for you in the New World.
...goes to the World Noble,
Saint Charloss for his bid of...
I never expected to meet
such a big-shot here...
Get going already!
Really?! Do you think so?! I
can't wait to see him, too!
Oh, that was scary...!
I actually would've preferred
to do it at my own pace!
"Dark King" Silvers Rayleigh...
No doubt about it. What's a legendary
man doing in a place like this?
I'll punish these cretins by
stuffing and preserving the women
Head!
...500 million...
You have trauma from nearly being killed
by Navy Headquarters, and yet...!
Now, then. Let's get down to business.
and making the men slaves and starving them!
On these islands I'm Ray-san,
the coating craftsman.
You wanted your ship coated, is that right?
You endured it anyway!
What a fantastic person!
What's that?
I should get back to my real work, anyway.
...Berries!
Q-Quiet! This is no time to talk
about trauma or anything else!
Don't go calling me that other name.
That reminds me, coating
costs a lot of money...
Father!
I'm an old soldier now. I just
want to live in peace and quiet.
We owe the young master our lives! We
hafta help him out of this trouble!
Oww, oww...!
No, that's all right, Hachi. I can't
take money from friends of yours.
Wait, that didn't hurt that much...
I take it you'll survive, Hachi?
After I told you all those times
not to walk around these islands...
That's a relief. Thank you, Rayleigh.
Sorry, mister!
What the...?!
Multi-shot! Flame Star! Flame Star!
S-Saint Roswald, too?!
I'm sorry...
How noisy.
I dunno why, but he's doing it for free!
You just repeated your crime, pirate!
Thanks for saving my friend, fellows.
We appreciate it! You're one generous guy!
Colonnade Rose!
Luffy!
Usopp! Robin! Brook!
What's your problem?! You
can land better than that!
So, what's this about wanting
to meet me, old guy?
It sounds like we just saved a ton of money!
Looks like everyone's here!
I can't! It's a flying fish!
Besides, you said to run into it!
Yes, let's save that for later.
We first need to get out of here.
Luffy! Where's Camie?!
Over there! We'll run away as soon
as the bomb around her neck is off!
You told me to "just get on,"
They have the place completely
surrounded, Boss.
Old man! Franky! Go on ahead!
We have to hurry before the
warship and admiral get here!
but why're you guys in such a
hurry to get back to the Sunny?!
Right! I appreciate it!
Rayleigh-san.
Alright, you criminals! Release
the Roswald family at once!
Don't let 'em escape! After 'em!
Eh?!
I have a question!
The navy's already here, Straw Hat-ya.
Where are we, anyway?!
Zoro, too?!
How many of these guys are there?!
You guys...
An admiral will be arriving shortly!
I recommend immediate surrender!
What exactly is the "Will of D"?
Who're you?
What's with that bear?
That's Straw Hat Luffy...!
Roger's name was engraved in ancient writing
Don't blame us for whatever
happens, you rookies!
This is certainly exciting!
They've had the place surrounded
before the auctions even began.
You're one lively old geezer!
on Poneglyph I saw on a sky island.
Camie!
Hey! Hurry, you three!
Who are they?! Where'd they come from?!
How was he able to use that writing?!
Yeah!
Don't let the Straw Hat crew escape!
They're the main criminals!
We're not only caught up in this, we're
being treated as accomplices now.
Navy Headquarters has a post
on this archipelago, you see.
Camie!
"I made it here. I will guide this
text to the ends of the earth."
Fire! Fire!
Luffy-chin!
Please leave the area immediately!
It's all right! We're here!
I got a good glimpse of the insanity
that makes Straw Hat Luffy so notorious.
"Pirate Gol D. Roger"
Camie! We've been looking
everywhere! What a relief!
Do you people know what happened to the world
I have no complaints, but I'd rather not
run into an admiral now if I can avoid it!
How's it look inside?!
What the...?!
We've finished evacuating the patrons!
during the Blank Century
that began 900 years ago?!
Oh, I'd prefer not to use that power of
mine anymore, so I leave this to you!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Hold on, Straw Hat! What are you doing?!
The three Celestial Dragons are still inside!
Bring them out at once!
What do you mean?! Camie's right there!
You damn pirates! Don't think
you'll get out of here unhurt!
She is, but she's wearing an explosive
collar! We can't take her away!
It'll be hard for me to stay settled
down if the navy discovers who I am.
I have no intention of helping
out a senior citizen!
Plus, there are Celestial
Dragons involved now...!
Yes. We know.
I dunno who they wanted to catch,
So what?!
The longer we stay here, the
more troops there'll be!
Did he just call him "Straw Hat"?
Why?
but I doubt they expected anyone
would beat up the Celestial Dragons.
I think I'll go on ahead!
We learned the entirety of history.
He's a pirate!
While I'm at it, I'll help you guys out too!
Camie!
Please, stop!
I'll clean things up outside, so don't worry!
He just freed Saint Roswald's slave!
That was an interesting show
you gave, Straw Hat-ya crew.
I told you, I'll do it!
How did he uncuff him?!
Shut up!
You must be Trafalgar Law.
But, Miss. You mustn't be hasty.
Will you come along with me,
pirate captain Jean Bart?
His arms...! His arms...!
I'm gonna do it!
He's a fish-man!
Get outta here!
Luffy. He's a pirate.
Shut up, you guys!
Continue to move forward one
step at a time on your own ship.
I'm going to do it.
Huh?! The bear, too?
Disgusting!
What're you talking about?!
What's a fish-man doing here?!
I told you, leave it to me!
We-- and Ohara-- might have
hurried a bit too much.
It's an octopus monster!
No! I'm gonna do it!
I'm coming to save you, Camie!
Don't tell me what to do!
You guys just don't get it!
And the man over there...
Seize him!
You're the one who doesn't get it!
It's been a long time since
I've been called that name.
You guys! Camie isn't for sale!
Alright!
Even if I told you everything
about history right here,
Eustass Captain Kid.
Eh?! That's the one with a
higher bounty than Luffy-san?!
You guys can go back inside!
Keep him away from the stage!
If it means I can be free
from the Celestial Dragons...
you still wouldn't be able to
do anything as you are now.
Hey! Are you even listening?!
I told you two to stay back!
What's a fish-man doing on land?!
Yuck, stay away! Your
very existence is scary!
Once you've taken the time to see the world,
...I'll gladly serve under you!
Tell me what to do again and I'll start
by getting rid of you, Eustass-ya!
it's possible you'll be led to
a different answer than we were.
Hey, staff! Apprehend him already!
Give half of your thanks to Straw Hat-ya.
Get ready!
Eww! Get away!
But, if you still insist on hearing it,
All three of them are captains!
They're spearheading the attack!
This is unforgivable!
Go back to the sea, you freak!
In which case, I'll kill this
mermaid that they're after!
I can tell you everything
about this world right now.
Yeah!
Don't let 'em get away! After 'em!
Get off these islands!
Monkey D. Luffy, worth 300 million!
After 'em!
Get out of here!
I'm going!
Alright! It's up to you now!
The 500 million Berries!
Leave it to us!
Eustass Captain Kid, worth 315 million!
P-P-Please wait, Saint Shalria!
Yahoo!
That item hasn't been paid for yet!
Let me handle it.
Hachi! Let's run for now!
You're the one in danger now!
Trafalgar Law, worth 200 million!
No, I'll pass. I'll continue my journey.
Please wait, Saint Shalria! Saint Shalria!
You can stay here and
bicker all you want. I...
Never mind me! It's Camie who's in trouble!
Quiet, commoner!
What the hell's going on here?!
It will all come into sight someday.
Don't let them escape! Fire! Fire!
...can handle this all by myself!
It's exactly like Robin said...
I'm sorry for what happened
to your homeland of Ohara.
Damn! Can't this slowpoke cow go any faster?!
All three of them have bounties
well over 100 million!
Huh?
All right, fish! This is
the end, once and for all!
They discriminate against fish-men
and merfolk on these islands!
Crap! Camie-chan's in trouble!
Geez, they're so simpleminded!
However, Roger didn't decipher that writing!
Actually...
Discriminate..? Against Camie and Hachi?
Hey! There's gonna an all-out brawl!
...this is his top speed...
Quit your squirming!
Let's use that chance to escape! We
can't just sit around here anyway!
We're pirates.
Damn...!
We can't possibly match
the intellect of geniuses
They've caught up?
Hatchin...
Now you die!
like Clover and the scholars of Ohara.
Thanks... I'm sorry for
causing you trouble...!
He heard the voice of the
universe, that's all.
Can't we speed this thing up somehow?!
Camie!
Never mind me! I'm just
glad you're all right!
Oh no! We can't stop her in time!
Camie! It's my fault this happened to you!
They fled that way!
Whoa, are you sure, Robin?!
Don't let them get away!
I shouldn't have let you
go to the amusement park!
Are you sure you didn't just
pass up an incredible chance?!
No, I'll always cherish the memory
of going to the amusement park!
Umm, old guy! There's one
more thing I wanna ask!
The legendary great treasure, the One Piece!
There's no reason to apologize, Pappagu!
They're still chasing us, even
after we demolished the bridge!
Is it really--?!
Usopp!
Straw Hat said the same thing, actually...
Of course they are. There should
be soldiers back in town, too.
Eh?
What're you guys talking about?
Let's get the hell off these islands.
There isn't one thing you
guys should be sorry for!
S-Saint Shalria!
Kid!
Boss!
All three of you are my friends now!
H-Hachi...
I don't wanna know where the treasure is!
We will rescue Camie, no matter what!
I don't wanna know if the
treasure exists or not!
There.
We've put all our lives on
the line and set out to sea,
So stop crying!
Luffy-chin...
I shot it! I took down a fish-man!
even though we don't know anything!
Let's follow them. We're going
to break through in one go.
Is that...?!
I'd rather give up being a pirate than
have the old guy tell us stuff now!
Hachi!
All right, then.
Let us meet up on Grove #13, should
we find ourselves separated.
What's...
Thank heavens someone shot him.
I won't go on a boring adventure!
It would've been terrible if it'd come
close enough to spread its diseases!
he doing on these islands?!
Grove #13? Got it!
It was definitely plotting something.
You don't "got it" at all!
S-S-Sorry! I knew that, but it
just slipped out of my mouth...!
But even if it can walk upright,
it still has a fish's brain!
What will you do, Mr. Giant?!
We were all on the verge of becoming slaves.
I-I don't wanna know, either!
Oh, I forgot! I have the "I'll Die If
I Learn About the One Piece" disease!
I'm going to flee somewhere
with these people!
What an agile bear! He's too much to handle!
Hold on, old guy! Don't say anything!
I see! Be careful not to
draw attention to yourself!
How is it even talking?!
I'm sorry...
Old man! Straw Hat's friends!
Do you think you can do it?
He's weak-hearted!
Hurry, Bepo!
Look, Father! I caught a fish-man!
I will repay this favor if we
ever meet again! Thank you!
The Grand Line still far surpasses
anything you can imagine!
See, Mr. Giant?
Thanks so much!
I caught it myself, so
I can have it for free!
Thank you!
Your foes will be powerful, too.
The place is in a real uproar.
I'd say the auction's over.
Free! Free! An octopus for free!
Can you rule this mighty sea?!
Sure, no problem!
Crap! They destroyed the bridge!
You're taking credit?!
I've stolen some money now,
What a deal! What a deal! An
octopus slave for free! Free!
Mortars! Fire!
so guess I'll head back
to the gambling houses...
Gum-Gum...
Free, free, free!
You're one disagreeable old man.
You're a new guy, which
means you rank under me.
...Balloon!
You were only here to get some money?
As long as I'm not a slave,
anything's fine with me!
I'm not gonna rule anything!
W-
I was hoping for a chance to steal
from whoever bought me too...
Repel!
It's the freest person in this sea
who's the King of the Pirates!
Wait...
Room.
Wh-What's this circle?!
But I guess it wasn't meant to be.
Straw Hat...!
Did we manage to lose them?!
Oh, right. I'm all out.
First thing is more alcohol.
Shambles.
Alright! Let's go straight
to the amusement park now!
I see...
Don't... Don't be mad...
Think about it.
I really am a fan of yours, Monkey-chan.
I've been killed!
Are you crazy?!
I don't know about you, but I wouldn't
want an old man like me for a slave.
I'm the one... who screwed up...
Wait... Huh?!
Your ship is in Grove #41, was it?
Watch out! All three of 'em have powers!
I think I'll head over there.
What will you do?
Leave enough people to rescue the
hostages, and gather all our men here!
There could be an admiral on
these islands as we speak.
You promised not to defy
the Celestial Dragons,
We'll only be a nuisance if we stay here,
Mortars, too!
even if you saw someone get shot...!
Yahoo!
so maybe we should go shopping somewhere?!
Oh? Looks like we've
garnered some attention...
Ready! Aim!
How pleasant!
W-Wait! Please wait!
What is this, "Laid-Back Life"?!
You're quite skilled to be able to
remodel it in such a short time!
Who's that old man and that giant?!
We're being chased! We gotta hide, you idiot!
I was a pirate at one time...!
Those are today's merchandise! How
did they get out of their cell?!
Yeah. The people chasing us might
show up if we all stay together.
Don't either of you do anything!
You'll just get in the way!
That's for sure! You're
amazing! It's so fast now!
This is what I deserve... for
doing those horrible things...
I already told you! Tell me what to do and--
It'll help him finish the work more
smoothly if we lay low in town.
I do what I can!
Leave it to me!
They don't have collars!
How did they unlock them?!
Fire! Fire! Fire!
Then let's just split up and then
meet back there when he's all done.
Gum-Gum Finger Net!
I'm sorry... I didn't mean
for it to be like this...!
What do we do?
What do you mean? Catching people is
outside of our field of expertise!
He can stretch?!
Who're you to talk strategically about
meeting up and stuff like that?!
What kind of weird power is that?
This is where Peterman's hideout is...
We can't hold back an unshackled giant!
Shakky. Do we have any?
Peterman?
R-Rayleigh!
Yes, there's one left.
I just wanted to make amends with
Nami... even if it wasn't much...
You mean Rayleigh, the coating craftsman?!
Captain! Look!
This is a Vivre Card!
Which one is he?!
Oh, if you know what it is,
that simplifies things.
Oh! Is that you, Hachi?! It is!
What are you doing?!
Eustass-ya and...
Since I happen to be a bit notorious myself,
So I wanted to be helpful to you guys...
It's good to see you again!
What are you doing here?!
I thought I was a goner!
That's...!
I think I'll move it from Grove #41 to
somewhere else before I start on it.
Sorry!
Straw Hat! You really are
screwed up in the head!
How did you get that injury?!
But I guess I've always been a
screw-up... no matter what I do...!
I'll need three days to complete the coating.
Start with Straw Hat Luffy! Charge!
No, that's okay, you needn't say a thing!
It takes three whole days?!
Your life depends on this work.
It's the fastest I can go.
I guess it's three days of
wilderness survival then!
Damn, you! Fire! Fire! Fire!
I'm a real screw-up...!
How frightening!
What is a Warlord of the Sea doing here?
Sundown in three days, let's say.
Hachi...
Now! Stay sharp! Go! Go!
I don't know what grove I'll be on then,
so wherever the Vivre Cards lead you,
All I ever do is cause trouble...
Gum-Gum Whip!
I'll be there finishing the
coating and waiting for you.
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry...!
Don't falter! Fire!
You should probably also
buy whatever you'll need
for your underwater voyage
to Fish-Man Island.
You lousy fish, still blabbering
on even though I shot you!
Oh no!
Luffy-chin! Everyone! Thank you so much!
Trafalgar Law...
You annoy me!
That was close...!
Yeah! Thanks so much!
Now! Get him!
You know my name?
Straw!
I'm sorry I caused you so much trouble!
What's with that look, you?!
In short... I see. I understand
the situation now.
I can't thank you guys enough!
We'll show you the way to Fish-Man
Island, so don't worry about a thing!
Huh?
Watch out for the navy
for the next three days!
You sure got yourself into
a heap of trouble, Hachi.
Toward himself?!
Captain!
Hachi! Get plenty of bed rest!
Does he want to die?!
And you folks saved him?
Stop, Straw! You guys'll
get in huge trouble too!
Let's meet again in three
days. We'll see you off.
Repel!
We're right next to Navy
Headquarters and Marie Jois!
Well, then...
See you later, lady!
Just about anyone can show up here!
Please, stop!
We're up against an admiral! We gotta
make sure none of us gets killed!
Marines are coming up the rear!
Do you not see this?!
This can't be! Are these
guys really rookies?!
Don't say unlucky things like that!
Has Admiral Kizaru arrived yet?!
This guy acts at random!
Three days, huh...
What's he going to do?!
No, sir! But I think he'll be here shortly!
Alright! Let's go!
Trafalgar! Stay out of my way!
Is he...
To the amusement park!
Straw Hat-ya...?
It couldn't be!
Hey, now!
Reinforcements from the navy
post have arrived, though!
Is he serious?!
Huh?! How?! What did you just do?!
A navy warship's been
spotted from the harbor!
The admiral's here!
Who is this old guy?!
Do you want to be destroyed? I told
you not to tell me what to do.
You annoy me, too!
H-Hold on! What's going on?! Help me!
Yeesh. There's a lot more than I expected...
We're running into unexpected
big-shots today.
I'd rather not add an admiral to that list...
You guys sure got weird powers!
That straw hat suits dauntless men very well.
I'd say yours is the weirdest.
...so you will let us pass...
Really?
This is Kizaru.
I've been wanting to meet you...
I've arrived.
...Monkey D. Luffy.
Please respond.
...Bartholomew Kuma!
Is the admiral really coming?
What?! Swords are flying toward him?!
I see it! The auction house!
That brat again?
You were on the Pirate King's ship?!
What is that?!
He's always causing problems,
one after another!
I don't want to meet him!
Amazing! Marines are flying through
the air, whirling, twirling...
The Marines have gathered around the auction house!
But the Pirate King was
caught. How did you survive?
The one we met before, Aokiji, was crazy
strong with that freezing Devil Fruit power!
Given that World Nobles are the victims
here, we will need to take action, Sengoku-san.
This could be trouble!
There are guns and even cannons
flying! What's going on?!
We weren't caught.
Wait a minute,
Luffy and the others must have started some trouble!
Oh, dear! I bet the other
admirals have powers, too!
I don't believe my eyes!
And I don't even have eyes!
Roger turned himself in.
Huh?!
We have to hurry and save them, or they'll be ambushed.
I didn't know Kid-san and Law-san had powers!
Kizaru...
Would you like to know the whole story?
Allow me to go.
I'm scared!
I don't wanna!
Rest easy.
It's getting interesting now!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"No Escape!? Admiral Kizaru's
Light Speed Kick!!"
"Major Panic! Desperate
Struggle at the Auction House"
"Roger and Rayleigh
-- The King of the Pirates and His Right Hand Man"
"Break Through the Siege! The
Navy vs. the Three Captains"
"Admiral Kizaru Takes Action!
Sabaody Archipelago Thrown into Chaos"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!