Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the Grand
Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
After Luffy and friends set out
in search of a coating craftsman,
Camie was kidnapped at Sabaody Park.
...Some guy brought in a mermaid
just before the auctions started!
H-Hold on! Who was this guy?!
After learning that she had already been
taken to the auction house on Grove #1...
...Nami and company were the first to arrive.
And, while the auctioning continued,
Luffy and four others had yet
to reach the auction house!
We will save you! Hang on, Camie!
"The Fist Explodes! Destroy the Auction"
Entry #15! The beautiful dancer, Pashia!
Incredibly, her starting
price of 800,000 Berries
has rocketed to the sky-high
price of 7.2 million Berries!
I'm finally here...
Okay! Now that things are
starting to getting fired up,
what do you say to this
next piece of merchandise?!
What a relief! It's still going on!
However, I heard him say
"Entry #15" just now,
so I believe it's almost over.
This thing really annoys me to no end!
Take this! And this!
Hey. Go sell this one too, while
we're here. I don't need it anymore.
I will make arrangements at once.
A Celestial Dragon...
Another World Noble is here...
Defy them and a navy admiral
will come running, huh...
I want a mermaid. I hope
they have one this time.
Merfolk are apparently a
rather hard species to catch,
so I'm unsure if one will be up
for auction this time or not...
Wh-What a pleasant surprise, Saint Charloss!
Take me to my seat already.
Yes, right away!
Please watch your step!
Brother Charloss is finally here.
Hey! Get walkin'!
Okay! It looks like we're ready to continue!
Entry #16 is none other than
the captain of a pirate ship!
A captain?
Feast your eyes on this man, with
a bounty of 17 million Berries!
Goes by the name of Lacuba!
He's known as a tactful strategist,
but his well-trained body
is another great attribute!
You can use him as a horse, for heavy
physical labor, or as a punching bag!
He has many uses, indeed!
Now, then!
Bastard! Don't tell me you just--!
He collapsed!
What happened?!
I saw blood!
Hey! Shut the curtains!
What happened?!
What just happened?
He bit his tongue off.
He decided he'd rather die here
than live a wretched life as someone's pet.
In some cases, that could
be the smart choice.
Camie...
Where's the mermaid already?!
Camie must be so scared...
Just hang on a little longer!
We will save her!
Good thing we have that
treasure from Thriller Bark!
Thank you so much, you guys...
No good.
Damn! I'm not gonna make any
money off of you now, you idiot!
Disco-san!
A doctor's on the way!
Geez! Do you know how much it's
gonna cost to treat you now?!
The mermaid's next, right?!
Yes! Everything's all set!
It can go on at any time!
Good!
This super big-event item should blast
away the chilly mood in the air!
Bring her out now, men!
Right!
Hatchin... Everyone...
#13? Didn't I pass by #2 just now?
Must be my imagination.
That man had so much bloodlust...
Pirate Hunter Zoro... He ain't
worth 120 million for nothin'!
Get mixed up with him and you won't survive,
no matter how many lives you have!
I never wanna meet that guy
again, that's for sure...
Hey! Hold it!
Aren't you guys...
What brings you here again?
You guys gave me fake
directions, didn't you?!
Nothing of the sort! We gave you
genuine directions to Grove #1!
Then why'd you run away?!
B-Because you glared at us
with such a vicious look!
Huh?!
Zoro!
We gotta hurry to Grove #1! Just get on!
Hold on! Not this again...!
"Aaaaaaaah"
What are you doing?!
Oops...
Someday I'm gonna cut you in two...
Sorry, Zoro.
Let's hurry to Grove #1!
#16, pirate Lacuba, was extremely nervous
and collapsed after a nosebleed,
so his introduction will have
to wait for another day.
Nervous?
What crap...
But, ladies and gentlemen!
The next item I have for you is a
super-incredible piece of merchandise
sure to instantly blow all this trouble away!
A highly sought after item, to be sure!
Observe this silhouette!
Oh! Could it be?!
Yes! An incredible item!
I won't say much. Look upon
it with your own eyes!
Now for the moment you've been waiting for!
It's time for the unveiling!
Take a good look!
All the way from Fish-Man
Island, the mermaid Camie!
It's real! A young mermaid!
Amazing!
What a find!
It's Hatchin and the others!
They came to rescue me!
Camie!
They're selling Camie now!
Alright! We're gonna get her
back! We have 200 million here!
Camie!
Hooray! A mermaid! They're selling a mermaid!
I see that there's immense interest
in this, our first mermaid in a while!
Now, then! How much shall we start from?
Let's make the first move to
win! We will get her back!
All right, then! Let's begin!
Bidding will start at...
500 million!
I'll buy it for 500 million Berries!
500 million...?
It's no good. We can't compete with him.
How could that happen so suddenly?!
We don't even have close to that much!
What another waste of money. You have
piranhas in your aquarium, you know.
I'm going to have them chase her for fun.
Merfolk are the fastest
swimmers in the world!
I can't hear what they're saying outside...
Help me get out of here, Hatchin!
Camie...
Is she gonna get sold to a Celestial
Dragon while we stand here, helpless?!
Camie...!
Everyone seems to be at a loss for
words, but I'll ask just the same.
Are there any bids higher than 500 million?
Can't we do something about this?!
Isn't there anything we can do?!
Isn't there, Sanji?!
Nami!
We can't let this happen!
We can't let our friend get
bought and taken away like this!
This is bad... I never even
imagined this happening.
We stepped back, thinking money
could solve this problem,
but things've just gotten worse!
If not, then that'll bring
bidding straight to a close!
I'll just have to help her
escape into the ocean by force!
Don't be stupid! What about that
collar?! It'll make Camie blow up!
Then... we'll have to get the
key to the collar somehow!
Time is up!
I did it!
It's almost like a miniature
version of the world.
What a pathetic farce. Let's go.
The bidding has ended!
Today's super showcase
item, the mermaid Camie...
...goes to the World Noble,
Saint Charloss for his bid of...
...500 million...
What's that?
...Berries!
What the...?!
How noisy.
Luffy!
What's your problem?! You
can land better than that!
I can't! It's a flying fish!
Besides, you said to run into it!
You told me to "just get on,"
but why're you guys in such a
hurry to get back to the Sunny?!
Where are we, anyway?!
Zoro, too?!
You guys...
That's Straw Hat Luffy...!
Camie!
Who are they?! Where'd they come from?!
Luffy-chin!
Camie! We've been looking
everywhere! What a relief!
Hold on, Straw Hat! What are you doing?!
What do you mean?! Camie's right there!
She is, but she's wearing an explosive
collar! We can't take her away!
Plus, there are Celestial
Dragons involved now...!
So what?!
Did he just call him "Straw Hat"?
He's a pirate!
Camie!
Please, stop!
His arms...! His arms...!
He's a fish-man!
Disgusting!
What's a fish-man doing here?!
It's an octopus monster!
I'm coming to save you, Camie!
Seize him!
You guys! Camie isn't for sale!
Keep him away from the stage!
What's a fish-man doing on land?!
Yuck, stay away! Your
very existence is scary!
Hey, staff! Apprehend him already!
Eww! Get away!
Go back to the sea, you freak!
Yeah!
Get off these islands!
Get out of here!
Hachi! Let's run for now!
You're the one in danger now!
Never mind me! It's Camie who's in trouble!
What the hell's going on here?!
It's exactly like Robin said...
Huh?
They discriminate against fish-men
and merfolk on these islands!
Discriminate..? Against Camie and Hachi?
H-Hachi...
I shot it! I took down a fish-man!
Hachi!
Thank heavens someone shot him.
It would've been terrible if it'd come
close enough to spread its diseases!
It was definitely plotting something.
But even if it can walk upright,
it still has a fish's brain!
Look, Father! I caught a fish-man!
I caught it myself, so
I can have it for free!
Free! Free! An octopus for free!
What a deal! What a deal! An
octopus slave for free! Free!
Free, free, free!
W-
Wait...
Straw Hat...!
Don't... Don't be mad...
I'm the one... who screwed up...
You promised not to defy
the Celestial Dragons,
even if you saw someone get shot...!
I was a pirate at one time...!
This is what I deserve... for
doing those horrible things...
I'm sorry... I didn't mean
for it to be like this...!
I just wanted to make amends with
Nami... even if it wasn't much...
So I wanted to be helpful to you guys...
But I guess I've always been a
screw-up... no matter what I do...!
I'm a real screw-up...!
Hachi...
All I ever do is cause trouble...
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry...!
You lousy fish, still blabbering
on even though I shot you!
You annoy me!
Straw!
What's with that look, you?!
Stop, Straw! You guys'll
get in huge trouble too!
Please, stop!
Do you not see this?!
What's he going to do?!
Straw Hat-ya...?
Is he serious?!
You annoy me, too!
I see it! The auction house!
What is that?!
The Marines have gathered around the auction house!
This could be trouble!
Wait a minute,
Luffy and the others must have started some trouble!
We have to hurry and save them, or they'll be ambushed.
I don't wanna!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Major Panic! Desperate
Struggle at the Auction House"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!