Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Another big haul today!
Buggy-sama won't be mad at us,
now that we got all this!
Huh?
Hey, check it out...
What's with that boat?
I-It's a girl!
Hey! What's wrong with you?
Oh! Am I dreaming?
Running into someone
on this wide open sea...
I-I don't know who you are, but... water...
Might I ask for a cup of water?
I can give you all the money you'd like.
Please, help me!
No problem! We'll help you!
But not until we see what treasure ya got!
Don't mind us!
I can't get it open...
Does it go like this?
You can keep my entire boat, if you'd like!
Our boat!
You tricked us!
A cold front accompanied by low
clouds spotted in the southern sky!
Intense winds and
squalls expected very soon!
All small boats take
caution not to capsize!
Bingo!
See ya! I'll just take
your treasure now!
Wait! You bitch--!
We'll get you for this--!
"Luffy's Past!
Enter Red-Haired Shanks"
I'm starving...
When the hell're
we gonna reach land?
Who knows. We're just going
with the wind and waves, after all...
I wonder if we'll reach land...
Nah, I'm sure we will, sometime.
Isn't it kind of weird that someone
tryin' to be King of the Pirates...
doesn't even have
any navigational skills?!
It's not weird.
I just drifted around.
But aren't you a bounty hunter
who wandered the high seas?
I have no memory of ever even
calling myself a bounty hunter.
I set onto the sea in
search of a certain man...
but then couldn't
get back to my village.
I had no choice, so I just went
after pirate ships to earn a living.
Oh. So you're just lost.
Don't put it like that!
Shanks!
This straw hat is dear to me--
it's been with me through many a fight.
Luffy. I can't give this even to you.
Then take me on your
next voyage, Shanks!
I wanna be a pirate too!
As if you could ever be a pirate!
Why not?!
Luffy.
Just bein' a good swimmer doesn't
mean you'd make a good pirate.
I'm good at fighting too!
My punches are like pistols!
Oh, really?
What's that mean?!
He means you're too
much of a kid, Luffy!
Seriously, you're as old as my own kid!
I'm not a kid! I'm a grownup!
Now, now. Don't get so mad.
Here! Have some juice!
Wow! Thanks!
--See, you are a kid! Ha!
--That wasn't fair, Shanks!
Don't laugh!
Stupid cheapskate Shanks!
Pardon us.
Oh... So these are "pirates."
Look pretty damn dumb.
Welcome...
We're mountain bandits.
But we ain't here
to tear up the place.
Sell us some booze.
Ten barrels oughta do.
I'm sorry.
I just ran out of alcohol.
That's odd.
These pirates seem to be drinking
something... What is it, water?
No, what they're
drinking is the last of it.
My apologies. Looks like we
drank the whole place dry.
Sorry!
You can have this, if you'd like.
It hasn't been opened yet.
There's an eight million Berry
bounty on my head, you know.
One bottle ain't even enough for
a bedtime drink! Don't insult me!
Now the floor's all wet.
Sorry about that, Makino-san.
Do you have a rag?
Oh, I'll do that!
Seems you like to clean.
Then maybe you'll find this more fulfilling.
Not worth our time if
they're out of booze. Let's go!
Later, wimps!
Are you all right, Captain?
Are you hurt?!
Oh, I'm fine. No problem at all.
--He got you good, boss!
--Talk about lame!
Why are you laughing?!
That was so uncool!
Why didn't you fight them?!
No matter how many there
are or how strong they seem,
you're not men-- or pirates--
if you laugh after something like that!
I can understand how you feel,
but he only spilled some booze on me.
It's nothing worth getting mad over.
Whatever!
--Eating out of frustration, Luffy?
--Shut up!
Wait, what're you eating?!
That box! Did you eat
what was in that box?!
Y-Yeah...
Spit it out! Right now!
Every last bite!
W-What're you doing, Shanks?!
What... was that?
What you ate was
the Gum-Gum Fruit!
The Gum-Gum Fruit
is known as a Devil Fruit!
Eating it turns your body to rubber,
and makes you lose the ability
to swim for the rest of your life!
Eh?! No way!
You dumbass!
People were drinkin'
and havin' a nice time.
What's the idea, boy?
Dammit! Apologize!
How dare you make fun
of Shanks and his crew!
Did I say something to offend you?
You did! Now apologize!
Mayor!
You see the looks
on those pirates' faces?!
He got covered in booze
but didn't say a word!
Talk about pathetic!
Pirates are just a bunch of wimps.
They're nothing but talk.
Stop it!
Stop making fun of
Shanks and the others!
They are not wimps!
Stop, Luffy!
Stop making fun of Shanks and
the others! You stupid bandits!
You oughta watch your mouth, boy.
No one who's ever made me
mad has lived to tell the tale.
Wait!
Let the boy go! Please!
I don't know what Luffy has done,
nor do I intend to fight with you!
If you're not offended,
I'll even pay you!
Just, please!
Spare the boy's life!
Mayor!
Leave it to senior citizens
to know how the world works.
But no, it's too late for him now.
After all, he's made me angry...
You're the bad guys!
You mountain apes!
You're a lost cause, kid.
You can regret all this in the next life!
--Luffy!
--Please! Let him go!
I was wondering why
the bar was empty...
...looks like it's those
mountain bandits from before.
Captain!
Shanks!
So you pirates are still here, huh?
Have you been scrubbing the
village clean this whole time?
Luffy!
I thought your punches
were as strong as pistols?
S-Shut up!
I dunno why you're here, but
you'd best leave before you get hurt.
Any closer and he'll
shoot your head off, wimp.
He said no closer!
Don't make me blow your head off!
Put your life on the line.
Huh?!
Now that you've drawn your pistol,
put your life on the line.
What the hell're you talkin' about?
I'm saying those aren't
for threatening people.
--N-Now you've done it!
--These bastards fight dirty!
--Dirty?
--Cut the crap.
What, do you think you're
dealing with saints or something?
You're looking at pirates!
Shut up! You got nothin' to
do with this in the first place!
Listen, bandits.
Whether I'm splattered with
alcohol or food or even spit on,
most of the time I'd just
laugh and forget about it.
But!
No matter what the reason,
anyone who hurts
my friends has to pay!
Shanks...
Has to pay, huh?!
Lousy pirates! Kill 'em, men!
I'll handle this.
Should be easy enough.
Don't get cocky, bandit.
If you wanna fight us, then go
drag a warship here or somethin'.
So strong!
H-Hold on! The kid attacked us!
You are a wanted man.
Damn it!
A smokescreen!
Luffy!
Crap! I let my guard down!
Luffy's gone!
What do we do, guys?!
Quit freakin' the hell out, boss!
It won't take us long to find him!
I can't believe this guy...
I made a clean getaway!
They'll never expect a mountain
bandit to escape onto the sea!
Dammit! Let me go, you stupid ape!
I hope you die!
You wish!
You're the one who's gonna die!
After all, you've made me mad!
So long!
Dammit! Dammit!
Those guys are scum,
but I couldn't even
hit them once! Dammit!
Sorry! I got no use for you anymore!
W-What the hell?!
Help!
Shanks!
Get lost!
I'm in your debt, Luffy...
Makino-san told me everything.
You fought for us.
Hey, don't cry! You're a man!
But... Shanks!
Your arm!
It's only an arm. It's no big deal.
I'm just glad you're alright...
You're leaving, then?
Yeah. It was a long stay,
but now we part ways.
Bet you'll miss me, huh?
Well, yeah, but I won't
ask you to take me anymore.
I've decided to become
a pirate on my own now!
I wasn't gonna take you anyway!
You'll never be a pirate!
I will too!
Someday, I'm gonna gather
a crew every good as yours,
and I'm gonna find the
greatest treasure in the world,
and I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates! I'll show you!
You're gonna surpass us, huh?
In that case...
...I'll leave this hat with you.
It's dear to me.
Take good care of it!
Come bring it back to me someday!
Once you've become a great pirate!
That's our promise, Luffy!
Hey.
You're gonna drop it
again if you space out.
Isn't it important?
Yeah.
Thank you, Zoro!
Man, I'm hungry...
A bird...
Let's eat it!
Huh? How?
Leave it to me!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
I see...
Help!
Moron!
What the hell're you doing?!
Hey! Stop! You there! Stop!
Shipwrecked people,
at a time like this?!
I can't stop!
Jump in on your own!
What?!
I'm impressed you got on!
Are you trying to run us over?!
Hey! Stop the boat!
We're members of Buggy
the Clown-sama's crew!
This boat is ours now!
Huh?!
We had no idea you were the
famous Pirate Hunter Zoro-san!
--Forgive our rudeness!
Thanks to you guys,
I lost sight of my friend.
Just keep padding straight ahead!
--Yessir!
Knowing Luffy, he'll manage
something once he spots land.
But what now, Bro?
Good question...
If Captain Buggy finds out a
girl stole our boat and treasure...
Y-Yeah...
Who's this Buggy guy?
You've never heard
of Buggy the Clown?!
Nope.
He's the head of our pirate ship!
He's eaten one of the Devil Fruits,
and is just an
all-around terrifying person...
Yes! I finally got it!
--Get back here, you!
--You wench! Give the map back!
We just stole that
chart of the Grand Line!
Dammit! If we don't get it back,
we're dead meat, too!
I don't wanna be killed by one
of the captain's cannonballs!
Captain Buggy!
I see something in the sky above the port!
Shoot it down!
W-What the--?
W-What?!
What the--?!
A person fell from the sky!
Dammit! What are
cannonballs flying at me for?!
But now I'm safe!
That was a pretty
neat experience I had!
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Whoa! Being alive while all
chopped up is no human technique!
What? As a rubber guy, you're
plenty of a monster yourself!
Nothing makes sense anymore!
A rubber guy, a chopped-up guy...
Who are these people?!
--Pirates.
--No! That's not what I mean!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Terrifying, Mysterious Power!
Captain Buggy, the Clown Pirate!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!