Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Wait, PX-1.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This one's...
...the real deal!
This is exciting!
If you were to take a trip,
where would you want to go?
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
Come on, Zoro!
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
We gotta get outta here, quick!
Seeking a ship-coating craftsman
Seeking a ship coating craftsman
to help them reach Fishman Island,
After the Straw Hat crew
rescued the mermaid Camie,
Seeking a ship coating craftsman
to help them reach Fishman Island,
to help them reach the
deep-sea Fish-Man Island,
the Straw Hat crew landed
on the Sabaody Archipelago,
they met Rayleigh, the craftsman they
were looking for, at the auction house.
Zoro-san...?
the Straw Hat crew landed
on the Sabaody Archipelago,
where they met Rayleigh, a craftsman and the
former vice-captain of the Roger Pirates.
where they met Rayleigh, a craftsman
where they met Rayleigh, a skilled craftsman
What happened...?!
and the former vice-captain
of the Roger Pirates.
Roger turned himself in.
Luffy and company headed into town to
hide while Rayleigh coated the Sunny,
Zoro...
Luffy and company had decided to
hide while Rayleigh coats the Sunny,
Luffy and company decided to hide
until Rayleigh finished the coating
disappeared!
I'm not going to die, partner...
when Bartholomew Kuma,
one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea,
when suddenly a cyborg with
Bartholomew Kuma's body appeared!
My treasure?
but Admiral Kizaru, an assassin
dispatched from Navy Headquarters,
appeared before them.
If you want it, you can have it!
Diamble Jambe!
has already arrived at the
Sabaody Archipelago...
Find it!
Flambé Shot!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Hello? This is Kizaru. Hmm? How odd...
Three-Sword Style...
Demon Aura Kyutoryu!
Do you think you can do it?
...Gum-Gum...
"Eliminated Friends --
The Final Day of the Straw Hat Crew"
The Grand Line still far surpasses
anything you can imagine!
Asura's Nine Lightning Slashes!
...Diable...
...Mouton...
...Jet...
Hello?
...600 Pound...
Your foes will be powerful, too.
Gear Third!
...Cannon!
Can you rule this mighty sea?!
--Now! Take this!
--S-Stop...!
Gigant Rifle!
I'm not gonna rule anything!
Hello?
It's the freest person in this sea
who's the King of the Pirates!
I see...
Z-Zoro...?!
Fierce battles broke out everywhere
between the navy and the rookies...
"No Escape!?
Admiral Kizaru's Light Speed Kick!!"
Let's rest a little...
It turned big--!
However, Zoro had doubts about this Kuma...
I didn't expect it to turn into
such an all-out fight so suddenly...
If this is a fake, then
that's the real problem.
You!
What's going on?!
Take care!
What the hell did you do to Zoro?!
He didn't do anything himself!
That'd mean there are two
guys who're this strong.
Don't do anything crazy!
He was...!
However, Sentomaru,
head of the Navy Science Unit,
Well, actually, if I can't find him,
then that leaves me with spare time...
He was right here just now!
Meanwhile, the rookies
took on Admiral Kizaru,
blocked their way,
accompanied by yet another Pacifista.
Yeah! Same to you guys!
Say bye to Hachi for us, too!
an assassin sent by Navy Headquarters, but...
And if I'm not busy, I obviously
can't let a wanted man go...
How over-the-top. We're going to
see them again in three days...
Especially one like you,
with a 249 million bounty...
Let's get away from here!
Zoro...
..."Magician" Basil Hawkins!
But not all together!
We'll split up in groups!
It's always sad to say goodbye.
Zoro...
See you later!
They're splitting up! After them, PX-1!
Zoro...
Speed is weight!
Well, then. I should be off, too.
Gum-Gum...
Have you ever been kicked
at the speed of light?
Zoro!
...Gatling!
Okay! We're counting on you!
Hoisa!
This is Borsalino.
Ashigara Dokkoi Shove!
What the hell, Uncle! You do
have a Baby Transponder Snail!
Captain!
Still, it was a real shock
to run into a member
Why didn't you contact me?!
Oh?
of the Pirate King's crew
in a place like this.
Zoro!
Oh, Sentomaru-kun!
Captain!
Don't give me, "Oh!" What are you doing?!
Wh-What?! Who are you?!
Stop, Chopper!
Impressive. You far surpass what I imagined.
He's a real intimidating guy,
for an old geezer.
Don't do anything crazy!
You're on the island now, right?!
Get away! Get away from Zoro, you dumbass!
And yet another "Bartholomew Kuma"
appeared before Luffy and company...
Oh, I wasn't able to get
a hold of you, you see...
Zoro! Where did you go?!
Z-Z-Zoro-san!
Well, he is the most
renowned man in Roger's crew!
Zoro-san's been hit by a beam!
Whatever! Just get to work now!
Kizaru?!
The culprits have split up!
--Get back, Luffy!
--He's one of the Warlords of the Sea!
Navy Admiral Kizaru also appeared,
So that's what crewmen on
the Oro Jackson were like...
Straw Hat Luffy,
Captain Kid, Trafalgar Law...
A Warlord?! How come you guys know that?!
I am boomingly proud of the fact
that I helped the man named Roger!
and the crew found itself in an
extraordinarily desperate situation.
Which do we start with?
Don't let that attack hit
you! It's a shockwave!
Oh, you don't say? In that case...
I'm glad to have met him!
"Admiral Kizaru's Fierce Assault
The Straw Hats Face Certain Death!"
What is this?!
I didn't know you were the type
to respect your superiors...!
He can do this, too?!
He's attacking at random...
W-Well, sometimes I do!
But more importantly,
Hey! You lied about it being a shockwave!
Bastard...
what is that bastard Kuma-kou doing here?
If you ain't Bartholomew Kuma,
then who are you?!
Hey.
Second Gear!
We know he's strong, so let's
go all-out at the very start!
Wanna go to the amusement park?!
You look exactly like
the Warlord of the Sea...
Here it comes!
Shut up, you!
What the hell's goin' on here?!
Do you even understand the situation?!
Bartholomew Kuma...
Something's off here...
He seems different from last time.
You still haven't learned your lesson?!
This is exactly why pirates can't be trusted!
I want to go...!
"An Even Stronger Enemy Appears!
The Battle Axe-Carrying Sentomaru"
Not you guys, too!
I'd like to cover for them, but...
It's Admiral Kizaru!
The only thing to do now is run!
He better hurry.
Zoro... was erased!
Get the pirates!
They're going to...
Does this mean the real one's
finally showed up?!
Hello?
No question about it!
There are wanted men everywhere!
I've seen that power before!
Watch out for the ones
worth over 100 million!
...get rid of all the rookies!
You're in the way!
--Run!
A girl on Thriller Bark was erased
like that and never came back...
Get the hell outta here, Trafalgar!
Hello? This is Kizaru. Hmm? How odd...
H-He got me...
I'm taking this guy down!
Hey, you, damn Warlord of the Sea!
You're the one who's in the way, Eustass-ya!
"Overwhelming!
The Navy's Fighting Weapons, the Pacifistas"
Bring it on!
This time, I will kick the crap outta you!
"Navy Headquarters Admiral --
Kizaru (Real Name: Borsalino)"
Hello?
That's odd...
Th-This is really bad!
That can't be good...
Room!
Th-There's still a slight chance!
Hey! What did he do to Zoro?!
If by some luck I can take him down,
I'll suddenly become famous!
Where did he send him?!
I don't have to answer you!
Huh?! Don't be an idiot!
I'm the world's most tight-lipped man!
Kid!
This is the navy's greatest
military force we're talking about!
You're a Warlord of the Sea,
yet all you can do is shoot beams?!
I don't know if it's true or not,
but they say that his paw pads
Repel!
can send a person flying through the
sky for three days and three nights!
There they are! Trafalgar Law,
captain of the Heart Pirates
Hello? Do you read me?
and Eustass Captain Kid,
captain of the Kid Pirates!
--Now! Take this!
--S-Stop...!
Only he knows where he sent him.
Don't let them escape!
At the very least, he's not on these islands
Damn! Now there's a whole load of marines!
or anywhere easily accessible.
Hello?
This is no time for us to get stuck here!
Could even be on the other side of the world.
Bepo!
--H-Hey!
--Damn! I'll get you this time!
We're bustin' straight through! Let's do it!
What?!
Unbelievable...
Hold on, Jean Bart!
From his hands and his mouth...
No one's ever been hit by
that and gotten up afterward!
You're the new guy! Don't give me orders!
Frightening!
Here comes another! Here comes another!
Huh?! What the...?!
I definitely hit him that time!
Say something, damn it!
Here it comes!
We just took down one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea!
Take this!
It went right through his head, right?!
Where did you send Zoro?!
How odd...
So you finally show yourself,
real Warlord of the Sea...
He's obviously got some kind of powers!
This is the extent of
Bartholomew Kuma's strength?
That bastard took all the fun!
Guns ain't gonna work on him! Let's run!
You're the third to look like that...
What's the deal?!
R-R-Real Warlord of the Sea...?
Wh-What the hell are those things?!
What?!
Say, I was wondering if you could help me...
They're beams, obviously!
This thing's a machine?! A cyborg?!
Beams of light would make incredible
weapons, but that's just fantasy!
S-Stay away!
I'm looking for a man named Sentomaru...
Stop, damn it!
Wait... what are you doing?
He's a subordinate of mine, you see...
Playing dead.
Repel!
He's already seen through that!
Stay away! Stop!
Sheesh. All I did was ask a question...
I-I have 8,000 men under
my command, you know!
That's Bartholomew Kuma,
one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea?
Hey! Are you listening?! Stay away!
Look out, Usopp! Behind you!
Why the hell did you do that?!
Behind--?
You place too much confidence
in your techniques, Eustass-ya.
What?!
Do you honestly think
this is a Warlord of the Sea?
Three-Sword Style...
Usopp-san!
...Gum-Gum...
What do you mean?
...Diable...
Our next guests have arrived.
We can talk later.
...Mouton...
...Jet...
...600 Pound...
Charge!
Stay out of the way.
...Cannon!
Damn! There's not even time to strike back!
A polar bear?!
He erased his own ally?
Uhh, I think Kizaru-san is
going a bit overboard...
He knows better than to break
the Hustle Muscle Mangroves!
Hey, you...!
Hey, Trafalgar.
About what you said earlier...
He even attacked PX-1?!
I think I might've overdone things a tad...
If he ain't a Warlord, then what is he?
What are you doing to your allies, Kuma-kou?!
Now what?!
Hey, Zoro!
Run! All three of you!
Talk about crazy...
Th-Three-Sword Style...
So that's Admiral Kizaru, huh?
Luffy?!
Apoo-san! We're in danger, too!
We should really get out of here!
Just get out of here!
--Zoro!
--That idiot!
Zoro!
You can think things over after you're safe!
Go!
You're such a fool.
Hey! He shoots beams, too!
This ain't good! Do something!
Where's the fun in slinking away?
Hoofprint...
...Blizzard Rose!
Yes! Did they get him?!
Nothing beats running away
after making an enemy mad...
At that distance, the beams'll kill him!
They're amazing!
What are you planning to do?!
Chopper!
Oh no! Zoro's in trouble!
Come on! Let's go!
This is a Warlord of the Sea.
But, Zoro...!
I don't think it'll be that easy,
judging from their expressions...
He told us to think about stuff later!
Come on! Pick up the pace!
Come on!
A lot got away...
Let's go! The beam only grazed me!
I'll lend you a shoulder! Hurry!
Yeah.
He's that different?!
Usopp!
Maybe he's a twin, then?!
H-Hey, you! Stop that!
Strong Hammer!
Look out, you two!
Requesting backup at the harbor!
Yeah, it's a possibility!
Brook!
Take this!
What's happening?!
I don't know!
Brook!
I don't know why,
Franky Boxing!
Anyway, the real one would've
teleported and dodged our attacks...
Take this!
but all the soldiers have
turned into kids or old people!
Damn! What's going on?! Why can't I hit him?
I will protect you,
even if it costs me my life!
More than that, he doesn't use shockwaves,
What's going on?!
Oh... My aching back...!
and doesn't got paws, either!
Oh, wait, I'm already d--
I-I can't even stab him!
Hold on! What should we do?!
But if this is a fake,
then that's the real problem.
Spider Net!
Take this! Dammit!
Brook!
A masterpiece!
That'd mean there are
two guys who're this strong.
His hand-to-hand combat
abilities are insane, too!
Move your foot!
It was her doing!
It was Jewelry Bonney!
She has a bounty of 140 million!
Move it aside!
All right! Get ready, now!
Bastard did it again!
It's no use;
Here I come!
Damn! What am I doing?!
I ate the Glint-Glint Fruit, you see.
Swallow Bon en Avant!
Which one do you prefer?
I just let two friends
disappear while I watched on!
I'm made of light. I'm a Logia.
You gave me quite a thrashing.
Made of light?!
H-Huh?
Damn it!
This can't be for real! He's going to die!
Sanji?!
I'm stuck!
Don't think I'm the same
as I was before, though!
What happened?!
Zoro! Run!
Go, Usopp!
Hello?! Respond!
Karma Exposure!
Don't be stupid! You're coming too, Sanji!
W-Wait! That's dangerous!
Zoro!
Why, you...!
Are you trying to kill me?!
Watch out for the rookies
worth over 100 million!
Stop! Sanji!
My body's... at it's...
Oh, I'm already dead, though...
I repeat, watch out for the
rookies worth over 100 million!
Damn you, you pawed bastard!
It's no good! The bastard's at his limit now!
But this is no time to be saying that!
You're Capone Gang Bege,
worth 138 million, aren't you?!
Special Attack: Atlas Comet!
Veinte Fleurs!
You can just forget about setting sail!
Now's our chance! Run!
All right! Way to go, Robin!
Th-Th-That was scary! Th-Thank you!
Where's your crew?! Gone off on their own?!
Sanji!
You're one unlucky bastard! Give yourself up!
That must've hurt a little...
Mad Monk Urouge, a man who has
continually escaped death to this day,
In terms of troop strength, you lose!
S-Stay away...
H-Huh? He's acting strange!
has such power after growing in size...
Stay away!
He just instantly...!
So how can this be?
How did he do that?!
What?! Now explosives work on him?!
Stay away! Stay away!
Hot!
Flame Star! Flame Star!
I won't let you move, either.
What's this commotion?!
It's no use.
Captain Hawkins!
Dammit! Flame Star! Flame Star!
One went in his mouth!
There is no need to hurry.
Something shorted out inside his body!
Flame Star! Flame Star!
Fate has already been decided.
Now you will die.
His body's hard, but he still bleeds.
Say, I was wondering if you could help me...
Usopp!
He's just like me, a regular living person
Run! Run!
K-Kizaru?!
whose body has been modified with weapons!
--W-We'll keep him busy here!
--Please escape, Captain!
That was Kizaru's laser!
Don't panic. I will not die today.
Vegapunk! You've recreated
Kizaru's offensive abilities
using Bartholomew Kuma's body?!
Usopp!
Nami-san! Look out! He's spotted you!
I had no idea the Pacifistas
had already reached this point!
Oh no!
Ochenta Fleurs!
Sanji!
Cuatro Mano
You're getting involved in this...
Damn you!
Shock!
How do you like that?! You're charred black!
This is no ordinary situation!
Stop! Sanji!
...Dark King Rayleigh?!
Yes! The beam went off inside his mouth!
Definitely not! Not even three
people worth over 100 million
He blew himself up!
Don't be plucking these young sprouts!
can survive against a
Warlord and a navy admiral!
Get back, Kid Pirates!
Their era is just about to begin!
Even Sanji...
Sorry to interrupt your little break, mister,
What is this? What do we do...?
Rear Admiral Drake.
Oh, I mean former Rear Admiral.
Old guy!
but there's a lightning advisory
right where you're standing!
This can't be... They're all...
He's saved!
Don't tell me you're here to
conduct surveillance on them?
From the dark clouds to the Climate Baton!
Oww! So hard!
Thunder Lance Tempo!
Thank goodness!
Go ahead, try fighting it.
Sounds like the situation
over there isn't normal!
The "Dark King"? Him?!
I think your inside knowledge will make
your despair all the greater, though.
Room.
I wish I could lend them a hand...
I'd heard on occasion that
you were on these islands.
What a pain growing old is!
Shambles!
I suggest that you little
hatchlings exercise caution.
If fending off a navy admiral
still isn't enough to satisfy you,
I guess those reports were true.
That had quite an effect! Spectacular!
Are you defending these chicklings
because you're still a pirate
I got you now!
then that leaves me in an awkward position.
Oww! Huh?
Just give it up, already!
even if you aren't what you
once were, Rayleigh-san?
I'm here too, you see!
How irritating!
I would be able to retire freely and peacefully
That didn't affect him at all!
He's still in tip-top shape!
How about this, then?!
if you people would kindly
take down my wanted posters.
Dark King Rayleigh, yes?
The crimes of a pirate cannot just go away.
Especially not those of the Roger Pirates.
Troublesome bastard...
Kuma...
But, to capture you,
But what is he aiming at?!
I would first need to make
some preparations, so...
Is he acting out of desperation?!
It's not over yet, Eustass-ya!
The freak's starting to go berserk!
Wh-What a relief, Zoro!
What another incredible sight!
Luffy!
This guy really is awesome!
A rare ancient Zoan type!
I've never seen one before!
You want me to trust you?
Every attack we tried went
right through his body!
Looks like you still
haven't had enough of me!
Give in to despair and the fight's all over!
How did he stop him just now?!
That choice is yours.
I fear for my own situation as well.
I don't suppose you could
overlook them, Kizaru-kun?
Hey! Knock him this way!
What do you think you're doing, Kuma?
Give me a break!
I'll teach you to be stubborn!
If I don't catch these kids,
we at Navy Headquarters
Diable Jambe!
We have no obligation
to act friendly with the navy
Flambé Shot!
in matters that do not have
the government's backing.
will lose face with the
Celestial Dragons in Marie Jois.
I'm telling you, we should
hide in the amusement park!
I will not answer your question.
Could I ask you not to get in the way?
Liar.
Why, you...!
Alright! He's finally starting to fall apart!
You just wanna go and have fun!
Usopp! Brook!
Second Gear!
Demon Aura Kyutôryu...!
Take Zoro and escape!
Luffy!
Let's go!
Oh? I'm surprised red blood flows inside you.
Asura!
Come on! Let's go, Brook!
It can't be!
Wh-What is that?!
Right!
Everyone focus on escaping!
Zoro multiplied!
Who're you?!
What a rare sight...
Nine Lightening Slashes!
As we are now, we can't beat these guys!
Outta the damn way!
Strong Right!
As I said, I'm here too.
Enemy attack!
How noble! Yet, how annoying...
What?!
Franky!
Hurry it up!
Gear Third!
I'm gonna use up all of my cola energy!
Wait! Don't, Luffy!
Commence attack! Cannons, ready!
Here goes!
This is my final attack!
Gum-Gum Jet Pistol!
Open the gunports!
Go, Luffy!
Coup de Vent!
Just one last push!
Gum-Gum...
Commence bombardment!
What?!
Try that on for size, you dumbass!
Fire!
Crush him, Luffy!
Now run!
Old guy! Thanks!
...Giant Rifle!
What the...?!
All you people worth over 100 million
are monstrous and frightening...
There's stuff inside his body!
Yes! I pray for your safety!
Luffy!
Yata Mirror!
No!
It turned big--!
Demon-Conquering Form!
I-It's too bright!
Light?! Is he going to do something to us?!
What's going on?!
He didn't do anything himself!
He disappeared?!
Luffy... Help m--
Whoops!
Cavalry! Charge!
Nami!
You're not going anywhere!
Something else is coming
out of his stomach now!
It's nice to be holding a sword again.
M-My eyes!
Ama no Murakumo Sword!
Troops keep coming out!
Captain Hawkins!
I-It's horses this time!
I... can't see...
Dear me.
And I came to these islands
with such casual intentions too...
I don't know what power you have,
but you do have a physical form.
Capone Gang Bege!
I'm shrinking!
What the hell power does that guy have?!
Confusion is what life
is all about, Kizaru-kun!
You don't seem to be a Logia type...
Firing squad! Aim!
That light from before is gone!
What's this smoke?!
It looks like the old guy saved us again!
Father! There's too much smoke!
Th-Th-That was so frightening!
Captain!
I told you you don't have
enough troop strength!
This is bad!
He's going over his damage limit!
He's really gonna die!
It would appear he really is the Dark King.
You'll be the first to go...
That's the first time I've ever
seen someone stop Uncle.
Luffy... Help m--
You did well to journey all this way.
But we're just about finished with Roronoa,
who's worth over 100 million...
PX-1! Roronoa is barely alive!
Start with him!
Get outta here! Hurry!
Luffy!
I still haven't eaten enough...
That stopped the bastard, right?
I'm sure there'll be good food
on the next island, too!
Yeah, it had to have...
He's...!
Hey! Did you hear?!
Franky! Look after Nami-san!
It's creepy...
It looks like it could still start moving...
A Warlord of the Sea has joined the attack!
Chopper...
Go on ahead!
Watch yourself, now! We'll be fine!
Are you serious?! Who is it?!
If it does, we're done for...
Sanji-kun?!
A Warlord?!
They're going after Usopp's group!
I'm so worn out I can't move...
Maybe we should've run away
instead of fighting it...
I was fully expecting an admiral...!
Who is that?
No, it's best to defeat
whoever we can ahead of time.
We are being chased, after all.
I guess quietly passing by Navy
Headquarters is out of the question.
Still, after all is said and done,
what was this guy?!
But...
Given that he's a cyborg,
he must've originally been a person
--Put me down...
--Huh?!
...I have my pride to think of, too!
Chopper!
who looked just like Bartholomew Kuma.
I'm letting you guys get away...!
Please, just escape, Captain Hawkins!
Don't be stupid!
The most natural possibility
is that he was a twin brother
You're even more useless than me right now!
Captain Hawkins!
Combat: Chance of Defeat: 100%.
or a super look-alike who was modified.
We're escaping together!
That's what Luffy decided!
Say, can you help me?
There's definitely no way to
create a live person from scratch.
Chopper...
Escape: Chance of Success: 12%.
I-It couldn't be!
It's coming!
I'm looking for a man named Sentomaru...
PX-4...?
Defense: Chance of Evasion: 76%.
Let's rest a little...
Usopp-san!
I didn't expect it to turn into
such an all-out fight so suddenly...
Hey...
Usopp-san! Please, go on ahead!
♪ Yo! Yo-yo-yo! Yeah! Yo! ♪
I know no such man.
I'd love to rest,
but we really should hide first...
Don't, Brook! You know how strong he is!
Ask someone else.
Stop... Stop... Stop...
♪ Is this music reaching you?!
If you can hear it, stay tuned! ♪
If we get spotted again now,
we'll all be caught in one fell swoop!
Well, actually, if I can't find him,
then that leaves me with spare time...
Quickly!
All for one! One for all!
Stop... Stop...
♪ Navy Admiral Kizaru! ♪
That's true...
Sometimes a man's gotta do
what a man's gotta do!
But... wait just a tiny bit longer...
And if I'm not busy,
I obviously can't let a wanted man go...
♪ Yeah! Yo-yo-yo! Yo! ♪
Especially one like you,
with a 249 million bounty...
You guys got some nerve!
Stop it! That's enough!
He's "Sea Roar"...
That was in vain, no bones about it...
..."Magician" Basil Hawkins!
What?! Another enemy?!
Where's that voice coming from?!
♪ Everybody! Listen to
this fighting music! ♪
Brook!
Robin!
Speed is weight!
I mean, waaah!
Above! Above!
♪ Scratch! ♪
Luffy!
Have you ever been
kicked at the speed of light?
Stay away!
Hoisa!
Stop, you damn bastard!
Who are you?!
Captain!
What's this?
Hey, now! You're a real disgrace, PX-4!
Here we go!
We're ready to set sail!
It costs as much as an entire warship
to build one Pacifista like you!
Sanji!
Alright! Let's scram!
My leg!
Run, Sanji! He's aiming at you!
Geez, now what am I supposed to
tell that lousy punk in my report?!
Wh-What happened?!
H-Hey! What happened?!
Check it out!
I don't know! He suddenly went flying!
You idiot! Get outta here!
"Captain of Navy Headquarters Science Unit"
"Sentomaru"
This guy's strong, all right...
Whoa! He's still going!
Got 'em!
My subordinates are quite
powerful too, I must say...
Though I doubt that'd be
enough to beat a navy admiral!
The Warlord of the Sea is still here!
I-Is that the real one?!
Whew, I managed to see
so much interesting stuff!
Real or not, we don't got enough
strength left to fight that thing!
Well, it's time for me to scram! So long!
What is this? What is this?!
Did you just say "Pacifista"?!
H-Hey! What happened?! He just suddenly--!
Zoro! I'm sorry!
Pacifista? That's like a pacifist, right?
I'm...!
I dropped you! You alright?!
Where'd the attack come from?!
How terrible...
Is that the name of the guy we just beat?
Who the hell are you, Battle Axe?!
How dare you call people
by their weapons' names...
Hold it, you damn bastard...!
It's no use asking me questions!
Captain!
I ain't gonna tell you anything!
Impressive. You far surpass what I imagined.
Damn it...!
I got the toughest defense in the world!
Stop!
That's odd...
As such, my mouth is sealed just as tight!
Zoro...
To think two would be destroyed already...
You can at least tell us your name!
Against an admiral,
ten isn't enough to feel secure.
I have no reason to answer anything!
It looks like they're in trouble there!
I already told you!
There's no need to even use my battle axe!
I'm Sentomaru, the most
tight-lipped guy in the world!
And I'm pretty sure you don't have
time to worry about your friends!
Oh, okay. So you're Sentomaru?
That's "Mad Monk" Urouge!
Ashigara Dokkoi Shove!
What a shock that was...
That's not all!
Just so you know, I
voluntarily told you that.
Luffy!
That's Bartholomew Kuma,
one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
I wasn't answering your question.
Luffy's made of rubber!
Why do his body blows work on him?!
Never mind that!
Yata Mirror.
Let's begin, PX-1!
Darn it!
I'm at a loss! What strength!
Chopper! Don't stop!
Join my crew!
There's an even stronger foe to worry about.
Sanji!
You can't be serious! That's Kizaru!
What's that?
What tragic fate!
I'm so glad I'm alive!
Sanji!
A navy admiral ahead, and a Warlord behind!
He shoots beams from his palms too! Not paws!
Is this the end of the line?!
Come out, Straw Hat!
Not necessarily. I do not yet see
the shadow of death upon you.
I don't wanna think about it,
but that means this is a third one!
What's going on?!
Our safety is more important
than that mystery right now!
You don't say...
Alright! Get on, Franky!
Hawkins, of North Blue, huh?
Darn it! Everyone's being beaten!
Get on my ship!
O-One more fight,
and we will be critically injured...
Thank you for the joke, foe as you may be!
Fine! I'll take care of ya!
No, Chopper!
I, Franky, accept the job
of your ship's shipwright!
...before we even run into the admiral!
All of you quit it!
Yeah...
Rumble!
Why do you keep coming to save me?!
What the...?!
Someone else has joined the fight!
I just want to die!
Let's get away from here!
That's...
"Red Flag" X. Drake!
But not all together!
We'll split up in groups!
I still haven't heard it from your mouth!
Why is he here?!
Is that the extent of your power, Mad Monk?!
Say you want to live!
You, again?!
Rear Admiral Drake.
I want to live!
Running sounds good to us!
Crap! I hadn't planned
on running into Kizaru!
Even if I don't have
friends, I can still fight!
The three of us should split up!
Alright! You gonna be okay?!
Chopper!
As long as the doctor's flag exists...!
That's that thing from before!
You do have friends!
Shut up!
I'm your friend!
I'll protect you, Nami-swan!
What is this?
Even if it costs me my life!
I'll stay here, but...
I'd heard about this, but...!
Okay, thanks! Now let's get going!
I've taken quite a beating,
Mellorine!
but let's find out now if
I really have any hope left or not!
One day, if you feel like it, stop by agai--
If you're ready to give up your life,
Shut up! Let's go!
then you can act as a decoy for all of us!
Offer's for ladies only, you damn bastard!
That's an interesting power you got,
You can protect your own
damn self, Panty-Man!
What do you want?
You don't even know anything..
but it appears you don't
have control over it.
I think I'll start with
a small counterattack.
This has nothing to do with you.
Look! Things are really crazy now!
Luffy! Look out!
I told you, leave the damn island already!
This is great stuff!
Zoro-kun! Do everything you can
to protect me, okay?! Please?!
This is really dangerous!
They're all going to die!
Luffy...
Hold on, Usopp! I'm hurt enough as it is...!
This is our chance to escape!
Help me...
Are you crazy?
The real fun is just about to begin!
Hello?
Fear not! I shall cover you!
Nami!
I would imagine you're still quite damaged!
Huh? Hello?
You're my friend!
Chopper went and did that again?!
I was witness to the entire
incident on Thriller Bark
Wait!
Who're you?!
We both have foolish dreams.
when you stepped in for him!
Oh...
--Get back, Luffy!
--He's one of the Warlords of the Sea!
I'll be the cook for your ship.
Thanks!
I dunno what's going on, but he's distracted!
Let's run there!
A Warlord?! How come you guys know that?!
Oh, here it is.
Yes!
I'm so scared of beams now!
Now's our chance!
Thank you for all the damn things
you've done for me all these years!
Sanji! Brook! Get up!
Guys! Meet on the Sunny in three days!
This is Borsalino.
Don't let that attack hit you!
It's a shockwave!
What the hell, Uncle!
You do have a Baby Transponder Snail!
Now's our chance to get away from here!
They're splitting up! After them, PX-1!
What're you talkin' about? Get on already.
Hurry! Before another beam comes!
Why didn't you contact me?!
Don't let 'em leave Grove #12!
Things'll get ugly if they do!
We're friends now, aren't we?
Oh?
Oh, Sentomaru-kun!
Gum-Gum...
Special Attack: Super Smoke Star!
Hey! Hurry and get up!
Don't give me, "Oh!" What are you doing?!
...Bullet!
Brook! Sanji!
What is this?!
You're on the island now, right?!
He can do this, too?!
Now's our chance!
Oh, I wasn't able to get
ahold of you, you see...
You idiot...
Hey! You lied about it being a shockwave!
You certainly are dependable!
You know you can't beat me!
Wait, PX-1.
Don't tell me you were talking into
the Black Transponder Snail again!
That was...
...a beam!
Crap! The bridge!
Please let me join your crew again!
This is no time to be excited, you morons!
I told you before that the black one
on your wrist is for eavesdropping!
Here he comes!
No! Why's he coming after us?!
Oh, yes...
Whoa, hey, you! Stop it!
Bartholomew Kuma! Why are you back?!
You idiot! Just grab on already!
Whatever! Just get to work now!
Quit pushing!
That bastard...!
He went that way! You guys alright?!
Wait, is he the guy you said
showed up on Thriller Bark afterward?!
The culprits have split up!
Straw Hat Luffy,
Captain Kid, Trafalgar Law...
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame...
This is no time to be
worried about other people!
Yeah, that's him!
Now there's another one!
Not that pirates mean anything to me, though!
I... I will not be defeated ever again!
Things got real bad when he hit us with
shockwaves from the paws on his palms!
Which do we start with?
Oh, you don't say? In that case...
Gum-Gum...
Wh-What in the world's going on?!
Got any problems with that...
...Gatling!
I've had enough!
He had planned to wipe us out there...
...King of the Pirates?!
Just how many of these guys are there?!
Hoisa!
Wh-What the...?!
What did he just do?!
Zoro...
Your attack power is quite nice,
Usopp...
Sanji...
but I have the greatest defense in the world!
...so he must've come back
when he found out we survived!
Nami...
Chopper...
Ashigara Dokkoi Shove!
Robin...
You gave us plenty of trouble back then!
Franky...
This one's...
Luffy!
Brook...
What the...?! This guy is strong, too!
...the real deal!
Everyone...
108 Pound Cannon!
Coup de Vent!
Just so you know, I don't have powers.
Oww...
There's something weird about his moves!
Concasser!
Did that work?!
No, the guy's still right as rain...!
I couldn't save even one of my friends...!
108 Pound...
What's the big idea?!
And you call yourself a friend, you brute?!
Get back!
Luffy-san!
Second Gear!
What happened here?!
We know he's strong,
so let's go all-out at the very start!
So, you're going to
send him off and that's it?
Zoro!
N...
Nothing... at all...!
I hope you have a
good explanation for this...
So, you're still alive, Roronoa...
Guess we have no choice!
Wh-What?! Who are you?!
This will be a major issue, you know...
Thanks to... your mercy...
Something's off here...
He seems different from last time.
Get away! Get away from Zoro, you dumbass!
H-Hold on, Zoro!
Z-Z-Zoro-san!
This is no time to be talking! Hurry and...!
You idiot! What're you doing?!
Zoro-san's been hit by a beam!
Hey, Zoro! Hang in there!
If you were to take a trip,
where would you want to go?
We will never meet again.
Is it just my imagination?!
Geez, took you long enough!
Come on, Zoro!
About time you got here, Uncle Kizaru!
Zoro!
We gotta get outta here, quick!
Kizaru?!
Be careful! That man is a navy admiral!
Hey, Zoro! You got hurt so
much you can't even move?!
Let's go!
Admiral?!
Farewell...
Forget about him, Luffy!
It's too late for you now...
We need to beat this thing first!
A 120 million bounty...
Yeah...!
Huh?!
Pirate Hunter Zoro...
What's taking so long?!
The warship should have arrived already!
Where's Zoro?!
Zoro-san...?
I'd heard that you're quite the swordsman,
How odd...
Why hasn't Uncle Kizaru contacted me yet?!
but a one-hit knockout?
Zoro?! Zoro?! Zoro!
He hasn't even had the chance
to fully heal from last time!
Your exhaustion must have really built up...
Grove #12 of the Sabaody
Archipelago on the Grand Line...
What happened...?!
Just standing up to him
must be pretty damn painful,
D-Damn...
judging by that look of his again!
The admiral...?
He better hurry.
Zoro...?!
On this day, the Straw Hat pirate crew
led by Captain Monkey D. Luffy...
Now you can have a nice, long rest...
Bastard...
If you ain't Bartholomew Kuma,
then who are you?!
They're going to...
Zoro!
You look exactly like
the Warlord of the Sea...
What the hell's goin' on here?!
suffered a complete collapse...
Zoro...
disappeared!
...get rid of all the rookies!
Everyone's been erased.
We've got a Warlord of the Sea,
a weirdo with a battle axe,
Is he that different from the Warlord
of the Sea that we met before?
Another enemy?!
Next time, we'll be having
a period drama specials!
I got the toughest defense in the world!
Brook... Franky...
and now a navy admiral?!
Yeah. The real one would've
teleported and dodged our attacks.
This time, we'll be holding
the once every 100 years,
If we let you guys escape,
As such, my mouth is sealed just as tight!
Robin... Chopper...
we'll end up losing face.
Great Portable Shrine Race, with
a sacred treasure as the prize.
Who are you?!
So he's a fake?
I have no reason to answer anything!
Sanji... Usopp...
But that's the real problem.
I'll have to make an appearance as well!
I'm the most tight-lipped guy in the world!
As we are now, we can't beat these guys!
Nami... Zoro...
That'd mean there are two
guys who're this strong.
Sacred treasure, eh? Sounds yummy.
Everyone focus on escaping!
And my name is...
Why can't I save even one of my friends?
You're gonna tell us, then?!
You're gonna eat it?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An Even Stronger Enemy Appears!
The Battle Axe-Carrying Sentomaru"
"Feudal Era Side Story –
Boss Luffy Appears Again"
"Overwhelming!
The Navy's Fighting Weapons, the Pacifistas"
"Admiral Kizaru's Fierce Assault
The Straw Hats Face Certain Death!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Eliminated Friends --
The Final Day of the Straw Hat Crew"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
I'm gonna be a detective!