Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Seeking a ship-coating craftsman
to help them reach the
deep-sea Fish-Man Island,
the Straw Hat crew landed
on the Sabaody Archipelago,
where they met Rayleigh, a skilled craftsman
and the former vice-captain
of the Roger Pirates.
Luffy and company decided to hide
until Rayleigh finished the coating
when suddenly a cyborg with
Bartholomew Kuma's body appeared!
Diamble Jambe!
Flambé Shot!
Demon Aura Kyutoryu!
Asura's Nine Lightning Slashes!
Gear Third!
Gigant Rifle!
Let's rest a little...
I didn't expect it to turn into
such an all-out fight so suddenly...
However, Sentomaru,
head of the Navy Science Unit,
blocked their way,
accompanied by yet another Pacifista.
Let's get away from here!
But not all together!
We'll split up in groups!
They're splitting up! After them, PX-1!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Hoisa!
Ashigara Dokkoi Shove!
Zoro!
Wh-What?! Who are you?!
Get away! Get away from Zoro, you dumbass!
Z-Z-Zoro-san!
Zoro-san's been hit by a beam!
Kizaru?!
Navy Admiral Kizaru also appeared,
and the crew found itself in an
extraordinarily desperate situation.
"Admiral Kizaru's Fierce Assault
The Straw Hats Face Certain Death!"
Here it comes!
H-He got me...
Hey, you, damn Warlord of the Sea!
Bring it on!
This time, I will kick the crap outta you!
Kid!
Repel!
No one's ever been hit by
that and gotten up afterward!
We just took down one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea!
This is the extent of
Bartholomew Kuma's strength?
What?!
This thing's a machine?! A cyborg?!
Why the hell did you do that?!
You place too much confidence
in your techniques, Eustass-ya.
What?!
Do you honestly think
this is a Warlord of the Sea?
What do you mean?
Our next guests have arrived.
We can talk later.
Charge!
A polar bear?!
Hey, you...!
Hey, Trafalgar.
About what you said earlier...
If he ain't a Warlord, then what is he?
Now what?!
Zoro!
Hey! He shoots beams, too!
This ain't good! Do something!
At that distance, the beams'll kill him!
Oh no! Zoro's in trouble!
Usopp!
H-Hey, you! Stop that!
Take this!
Damn! What's going on?! Why can't I hit him?
I-I can't even stab him!
Hold on! What should we do?!
Take this! Dammit!
Move your foot!
Move it aside!
It's no use;
I ate the Glint-Glint Fruit, you see.
I'm made of light. I'm a Logia.
Made of light?!
This can't be for real! He's going to die!
Zoro! Run!
Zoro!
My body's... at it's...
It's no good! The bastard's at his limit now!
Veinte Fleurs!
All right! Way to go, Robin!
He just instantly...!
How did he do that?!
I won't let you move, either.
It's no use.
Now you will die.
You're getting involved in this...
...Dark King Rayleigh?!
Don't be plucking these young sprouts!
Their era is just about to begin!
Old guy!
He's saved!
Thank goodness!
The "Dark King"? Him?!
I'd heard on occasion that
you were on these islands.
I guess those reports were true.
Are you defending these chicklings
because you're still a pirate
even if you aren't what you
once were, Rayleigh-san?
I would be able to retire freely and peacefully
if you people would kindly
take down my wanted posters.
The crimes of a pirate cannot just go away.
Especially not those of the Roger Pirates.
But, to capture you,
I would first need to make
some preparations, so...
Wh-What a relief, Zoro!
This guy really is awesome!
Every attack we tried went
right through his body!
How did he stop him just now?!
I don't suppose you could
overlook them, Kizaru-kun?
Give me a break!
If I don't catch these kids,
we at Navy Headquarters
will lose face with the
Celestial Dragons in Marie Jois.
Could I ask you not to get in the way?
Usopp! Brook!
Take Zoro and escape!
Come on! Let's go, Brook!
Right!
Everyone focus on escaping!
As we are now, we can't beat these guys!
How noble! Yet, how annoying...
Franky!
I'm gonna use up all of my cola energy!
This is my final attack!
Coup de Vent!
Try that on for size, you dumbass!
Now run!
Old guy! Thanks!
Yes! I pray for your safety!
Yata Mirror!
I-It's too bright!
Light?! Is he going to do something to us?!
Whoops!
You're not going anywhere!
It's nice to be holding a sword again.
Ama no Murakumo Sword!
Dear me.
And I came to these islands
with such casual intentions too...
Confusion is what life
is all about, Kizaru-kun!
That light from before is gone!
It looks like the old guy saved us again!
Th-Th-That was so frightening!
It would appear he really is the Dark King.
That's the first time I've ever
seen someone stop Uncle.
But we're just about finished with Roronoa,
who's worth over 100 million...
PX-1! Roronoa is barely alive!
Start with him!
He's...!
Franky! Look after Nami-san!
Go on ahead!
Watch yourself, now! We'll be fine!
Sanji-kun?!
They're going after Usopp's group!
--Put me down...
--Huh?!
I'm letting you guys get away...!
Don't be stupid!
You're even more useless than me right now!
We're escaping together!
That's what Luffy decided!
I-It couldn't be!
It's coming!
Usopp-san!
Usopp-san! Please, go on ahead!
Don't, Brook! You know how strong he is!
Quickly!
All for one! One for all!
Sometimes a man's gotta do
what a man's gotta do!
That was in vain, no bones about it...
Brook!
I mean, waaah!
Stay away!
Stop, you damn bastard!
Sanji!
My leg!
Run, Sanji! He's aiming at you!
You idiot! Get outta here!
My subordinates are quite
powerful too, I must say...
Zoro! I'm sorry!
I dropped you! You alright?!
Hold it, you damn bastard...!
Damn it...!
Stop!
Zoro...
It looks like they're in trouble there!
There's no need to even use my battle axe!
And I'm pretty sure you don't have
time to worry about your friends!
Ashigara Dokkoi Shove!
Luffy!
Luffy's made of rubber!
Why do his body blows work on him?!
Darn it!
Chopper! Don't stop!
Sanji!
Darn it! Everyone's being beaten!
No, Chopper!
All of you quit it!
Rumble!
Chopper!
That's that thing from before!
What is this?
I'd heard about this, but...!
That's an interesting power you got,
but it appears you don't
have control over it.
Luffy! Look out!
Chopper went and did that again?!
I dunno what's going on, but he's distracted!
Now's our chance!
Sanji! Brook! Get up!
Now's our chance to get away from here!
Hurry! Before another beam comes!
Hey! Hurry and get up!
Brook! Sanji!
Wait, PX-1.
Now there's another one!
Wh-What in the world's going on?!
I've had enough!
Just how many of these guys are there?!
This one's...
...the real deal!
What happened here?!
N...
Nothing... at all...!
So, you're still alive, Roronoa...
Thanks to... your mercy...
H-Hold on, Zoro!
This is no time to be talking! Hurry and...!
If you were to take a trip,
where would you want to go?
Come on, Zoro!
We gotta get outta here, quick!
Huh?!
Where's Zoro?!
Zoro-san...?
Zoro?! Zoro?! Zoro!
What happened...?!
Zoro...?!
Zoro...
disappeared!
Everyone's been erased.
Brook... Franky...
Robin... Chopper...
Sanji... Usopp...
Nami... Zoro...
Why can't I save even one of my friends?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Eliminated Friends --
The Final Day of the Straw Hat Crew"