Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wait, PX-1.
This one's...
...the real deal!
If you were to take a trip,
where would you want to go?
Come on, Zoro!
We gotta get outta here, quick!
Zoro-san...?
What happened...?!
Zoro...
disappeared!
"Eliminated Friends --
The Final Day of the Straw Hat Crew"
Z-Zoro...?!
You!
What the hell did you do to Zoro?!
He was...!
He was right here just now!
Zoro...
Zoro!
Stop, Chopper!
Don't do anything crazy!
Zoro! Where did you go?!
He's attacking at random...
But more importantly,
what is that bastard Kuma-kou doing here?
Bartholomew Kuma...
This is exactly why pirates can't be trusted!
I'd like to cover for them, but...
Zoro... was erased!
Does this mean the real one's
finally showed up?!
No question about it!
I've seen that power before!
A girl on Thriller Bark was erased
like that and never came back...
That can't be good...
Hey! What did he do to Zoro?!
Where did he send him?!
I don't have to answer you!
I'm the world's most tight-lipped man!
I don't know if it's true or not,
but they say that his paw pads
can send a person flying through the
sky for three days and three nights!
Only he knows where he sent him.
At the very least, he's not on these islands
or anywhere easily accessible.
Could even be on the other side of the world.
What?!
Say something, damn it!
Where did you send Zoro?!
So you finally show yourself,
real Warlord of the Sea...
You're the third to look like that...
What's the deal?!
R-R-Real Warlord of the Sea...?
S-Stay away!
Stop, damn it!
Stay away! Stop!
I-I have 8,000 men under
my command, you know!
Hey! Are you listening?! Stay away!
Look out, Usopp! Behind you!
Behind--?
Usopp-san!
Stay out of the way.
He erased his own ally?
He even attacked PX-1?!
What are you doing to your allies, Kuma-kou?!
Run! All three of you!
Luffy?!
Just get out of here!
You can think things over after you're safe!
Go!
Come on! Let's go!
But, Zoro...!
He told us to think about stuff later!
Come on!
Let's go! The beam only grazed me!
I'll lend you a shoulder! Hurry!
Look out, you two!
Brook!
I will protect you,
even if it costs me my life!
Oh, wait, I'm already d--
Brook!
Bastard did it again!
Damn! What am I doing?!
I just let two friends
disappear while I watched on!
Damn it!
Sanji?!
Go, Usopp!
Don't be stupid! You're coming too, Sanji!
Why, you...!
Stop! Sanji!
Damn you, you pawed bastard!
Sanji!
S-Stay away...
Stay away!
Stay away! Stay away!
Flame Star! Flame Star!
Dammit! Flame Star! Flame Star!
Usopp!
Run! Run!
Sanji!
Damn you!
Stop! Sanji!
Even Sanji...
What is this? What do we do...?
This can't be... They're all...
Sounds like the situation
over there isn't normal!
I wish I could lend them a hand...
What a pain growing old is!
If fending off a navy admiral
still isn't enough to satisfy you,
then that leaves me in an awkward position.
Just give it up, already!
Dark King Rayleigh, yes?
Kuma...
Luffy!
You want me to trust you?
That choice is yours.
I fear for my own situation as well.
What do you think you're doing, Kuma?
We have no obligation
to act friendly with the navy
in matters that do not have
the government's backing.
I will not answer your question.
Why, you...!
Second Gear!
Luffy!
Let's go!
Outta the damn way!
Strong Right!
What?!
Wait! Don't, Luffy!
Gum-Gum Jet Pistol!
Luffy!
No!
Luffy... Help m--
Nami!
Luffy!
Chopper...
Chopper!
Stop... Stop... Stop...
Stop... Stop...
Stop it! That's enough!
Robin!
Luffy!
What is this? What is this?!
I'm...!
Never mind that!
Join my crew!
I'm so glad I'm alive!
Come out, Straw Hat!
Alright! Get on, Franky!
Get on my ship!
Fine! I'll take care of ya!
I, Franky, accept the job
of your ship's shipwright!
Why do you keep coming to save me?!
I just want to die!
I still haven't heard it from your mouth!
Say you want to live!
I want to live!
Even if I don't have
friends, I can still fight!
As long as the doctor's flag exists...!
You do have friends!
I'm your friend!
I'll stay here, but...
One day, if you feel like it, stop by agai--
Shut up! Let's go!
What do you want?
You don't even know anything..
This has nothing to do with you.
I told you, leave the damn island already!
Luffy...
Help me...
Nami!
You're my friend!
Wait!
We both have foolish dreams.
I'll be the cook for your ship.
Thank you for all the damn things
you've done for me all these years!
What're you talkin' about? Get on already.
We're friends now, aren't we?
Gum-Gum...
...Bullet!
You idiot...
You know you can't beat me!
Please let me join your crew again!
You idiot! Just grab on already!
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame...
I... I will not be defeated ever again!
Got any problems with that...
...King of the Pirates?!
Zoro...
Usopp...
Sanji...
Nami...
Chopper...
Robin...
Franky...
Brook...
Everyone...
I couldn't save even one of my friends...!
So, you're going to
send him off and that's it?
I hope you have a
good explanation for this...
This will be a major issue, you know...
We will never meet again.
Farewell...
Grove #12 of the Sabaody
Archipelago on the Grand Line...
On this day, the Straw Hat pirate crew
led by Captain Monkey D. Luffy...
suffered a complete collapse...
Next time, we'll be having
a period drama specials!
This time, we'll be holding
the once every 100 years,
Great Portable Shrine Race, with
a sacred treasure as the prize.
I'll have to make an appearance as well!
Sacred treasure, eh? Sounds yummy.
You're gonna eat it?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Feudal Era Side Story –
Boss Luffy Appears Again"
I'm gonna be a detective!