Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Previously...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
"Feudal Era Side Story -
Boss Luffy Appears Again"
Boss Luffy and company entered
a festival's Great Portable Shrine Race,
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
with the prize being a sacred treasure
passed down in Grand Jipang.
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
Greetings once again!
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
It is the height of summer in the
legendary city of Grand Jipang,
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
a veritable mishmash of cultures
from all places and all times.
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
Everyone appears to be as heated up
and energetic as the great sun itself,
Together with an amnesic Brook,
they enjoyed their time before the festival.
This is exciting!
but why might that be?
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
Big news! Big news!
But, the night before the festival,
everyone's shrines were destroyed
by Hogback of Thriller Co.,
Big news!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
Great Portable Shrine Race?
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
which is bent on having the sacred treasure.
Yeah! The whole town is abuzz
with the news about it!
Oh? It's a big race that takes
place once every 100 years?
Realizing their ship needs to be
coated to reach Fishman Island,
It's all over!
Luffy was ejected from
the Sabaody Archipelago
We can't enter the race like this!
by Bartholomew Kuma, a Warlord of the Sea.
the Straw Hat crew landed
on the Sabaody Archipelago.
I've heard about that! They
say the prize is incredible!
Our only choice is to drop out now...
He landed in the female-only
empire of Amazon Lily!
There they met Rayleigh, a skilled craftsman
Supposedly, the winners get to ask
the Grand Shrine's sacred treasure
If this was all meant to destroy
their portable shrine before the race...
and the former vice-captain
of the Roger Pirates.
...then ours is in danger too!
for any wish they want!
However, Sentomaru,
captain of the Science Unit,
It'll grant any wish?
I have my Vivre Card!
"Everyone Falls in Love!
Pirate Empress Hancock"
Good thing we all got one!
I remember.
stood before the crew.
Here you are! Have some cold water!
Your memory is back?!
Ashigara Dokkoi Shove!
I'm sure I'll see everyone again!
Yes.
Oh! Thanks!
I remember everything now.
Luffy!
After being separated from his friends
and sent to an unknown isle alone,
Navy Admiral Kizaru appeared next,
That's good!
Luffy intended to rely on his
Vivre Card to reunite with the others, but...
You sure are thoughtful! Who are you?
She's our newest hired hand.
and Luffy and friends found
themselves in a grave situation!
Wh-What's with that get-up?
Where are you going?
I'm Omao. It's nice to meet you!
Aren't these Laughing Mushrooms?
I should not be here.
Seconds!
Sorry I can't pay you back for
everything you've done for me.
Here you are!
Hurry! The smoke is rising from over there!
This is because...
A heaping bowl! Awesome!
Now you can have a nice, long rest...
What good service!
...I'm actually a member of Thriller Company.
Well, I should be going now!
What do you suppose this is?
Yum! Yum!
And so, with his memory returned,
Zoro!
You don't need to give him so
much extra food, Omao-chan.
Men are so mysterious.
Brook disappeared into the dark night alone.
Luffy, after accidentally
eating a Parasite Mushroom,
Their arms stretch, they suddenly grow fat,
He's just going to put it on
his tab without paying his bill.
their chests are flat,
was carried to a village by mysterious women.
and between their legs they have...
Okay!
So, what is this sacred treasure?
Huh? Look here!
Hate to ask for help again,
but could you take these off?
What's wrong?
Oh, right...
There's still one mushroom left!
They say that the sacred treasure has
the magical power to grant any wish.
You're getting involved in this...
Your family jewels?!
"Feudal Era Side Story -
Defeat Thriller Company's Trap"
No! I mean these!
...Dark King Rayleigh?!
I'm going to look for my friends now!
But doesn't this one seem
different from the others?
It's kept in the Grand Shrine's treasure
room, which is opened once a century.
Don't be plucking these young sprouts!
But they'll laugh if they
see me dressed like this!
Their era is just about to begin!
It's oddly shaped!
Anyway, I guess we better pull it off!
I think it looks very nice on you...
What's this? What's this?
Old guy!
That was a great rampage tonight!
One policeman supposedly
made it big and became a samurai
What's going on?
There.
Thanks to Rayleigh's help,
Oh, Granny Nyon!
Perona-sama should be quite pleased.
after his wish was granted,
Thanks!
it appeared the crew had escaped danger,
There's a mushroom growing
on this girl that won't come off!
and one cook married the
prettiest girl in town
Hating frills...
but then Bartholomew Kuma,
a Warlord of the Sea, also appeared!
Men really are strange creatures.
and lived in complete happiness!
Who're you?!
Well, yeah, I guess so.
Oh, my!
That sounds great!
Thanks for taking it off!
That sounds neat!
You have strayed from the path of humanity...
Well, bye!
I'll never feel relaxed
until I find my friends!
Th-This person...
Alright! Let's enter the
Great Portable Shrine Race!
We will never meet again.
Though you aren't human to begin with.
You certainly are hasty...
Forget it!
...is a m-m-man!
I refuse to take part in a sweaty
competition for something so suspicious!
I will punish you on Heaven's behalf!
As long as the others are still alive
like I am, that's all that matters.
Th-This is a m-man?!
The winners also receive
one million Ryo-Berries.
Farewell...
C'mon, you guys! Let's get ready!
I've never seen one before!
As long as they're alive,
We're gonna win the
Great Portable Shrine Race!
I can keep fighting again and again!
She suddenly has life in her...
"Hurry Back to Your Friends!
The Maiden Island Adventure"
Okay, we'll need a great
portable shrine if we want to win!
And so the Straw Hat crew
suffered a complete collapse.
Oww, oww...
"Maiden Island  Amazon Lily"
There, that should do it.
This is the all-female land of Amazon Lily.
So, where are we going, Onami?
I'm gonna surpass all of those guys!
Thanks...
The race is tomorrow,
but I let them destroy the portable shrine...
"Landing! The All-Female Island,
Amazon Lily"
--The lumberyard.
--Lumberyard?!
Alright! I'm gonna walk on my hands
all the way to Sabaody Archipelago!
I hear the greatest builder
in all of Jipang lives there!
I'm a failure as a carpenter!
On occasion, women will leave
the island and return with child,
It's not your fault, Master Builder!
That'll make me stronger!
D-Damn...
but oddly enough,
they only give birth to girls.
So it's Hogback's cronies who're to blame...
Hello!
I can't seem to wink right...!
"Kuja"
Inside a tall mountain surrounded
by thick jungle is a large hole,
Could you give me a ship?
Is there no one home?
Brook...
You really are hasty...
and inside it a fortress-like village
was built and a country created.
You don't have any ships?!
Duval-sama! We found it! A bay by Grove #41!
This is a Calm Belt?!
Wh-What is this?!
Where do you suppose Brook went?
Yes. This maiden island is surrounded
Oh, what a nice roll of fabric!
Got it! I'll be right there!
by a giant Sea King den known as a Calm Belt.
Oh, sorry 'bout that!
Alright, men!
Would you like me to tell you?
Protect it at all costs,
in the name of the Rosy Life Riders!
Which is why sailors never dare come near.
Come on in!
Yes, sir!
Who're you?!
Oh, you picked it up for me? Thanks, girlie!
Hurry, Motobalo! Grove #41!
Castaways will sometimes
miraculously drift here,
Just a city girl who's passing by.
Oh, that ribbon!
but most of the time only as corpses.
How beautiful!
We both have one!
But you said there's a pirate group here!
It went flying off when I tried drying it
Again?!
with my Special Franky Workshop
Super Drying Clockwork Mechanism!
The Snake Princess's pirate ship, the Yuda,
Still, what were those
island-shaking shockwaves?
That skeleton was indeed a
member of Thriller Company,
I found it!
is pulled by vicious, poisonous sea snakes,
Master Builder!
--You shouldn't go out in public...
--...looking like that!
so Sea Kings can't attack it.
but he grew sick of its despicable
ways and left the organization.
I hope they're okay...
It's the only ship on Amazon Lily!
You still haven't caught them?!
But he may feel responsible for
the shrines that were destroyed today.
That was a close call...
Now what do I do?
Admiral Kizaru is currently pursuing them,
There's no wind...
You didn't make it in time!
Should I build a raft and
paddle all the way there?
so it should only be a matter of time!
Okay, girlie. Could I have that back?
Please have patience!
Step right up! We have
Sea King meat on hand today!
You pathetic, dimwitted dogs!
Eh?
That's ridiculous!
Boss Luffy...
That.
"Thriller Company"
Okay! I'm gonna build a raft
and paddle all the way there!
It looks good!
Pinwheel members...
This?
It'll make your skin nice and smooth, too!
Not only did they do this
to my father and brother,
I will make amends for how I have lived.
It is my loincloth, after all! Super!
That's what you just thought up!
How about some fresh-picked
fruit from the jungle?!
but they also let all of our slaves escape!
Wait, Boss!
Sheesh, he never thinks things through!
L-L-L...
It's done!
What do they take the blood
of this world's Creators for?!
That's terrible! It's already about to break!
All the wage-earning and manual labor
is done by women too, of course.
Brook!
Loincloth?!
When I get my hands on them,
I'm going to put them through
a living hell so horrible
I brought it!
No way! I thought he was a pirate!
that they'll crawl on the ground
and beg for forgiveness!
Thanks! Just set it right there!
Fool!
Sure thing!
Awesome! What's this doohickey?!
I don't like hurting!
It's my Super Drying Clockwork
Mechanism Fun Fan Sunny Wind!
Duval-sama.
Raised from birth as warriors,
What's taking Young Master Straw Hat
and the others so long?
Shut up!
I never imagined you were still alive!
they truly are burly and large-hearted,
Maybe they're busy with
the people chasing em?
It's so cool!
Not after we hurt you so much
and sent you down the river
but they also have an air of
elegance about them as well.
I heard the port's in a real uproar!
The loincloth...
when you left the organization...
The loincloth landed right on my face...
Yeah. I saw it from the air.
There is no place here
for greedy, foolish men at all.
Why have you come to throw away
the life you managed to cling to?
Marines and pirates were having at it.
So, what kind of super portable
shrine do you want me to make?
It was a real mess!
"Fighting"
And, more than anything, the
women of this island are strong.
I had no obligation to save you!
Then that's all the more
reason to stay sharp!
There is no point in explaining!
Well, one that's...
Are all men unable to swim,
even if they're pirates?
You would never understand!
One that can win!
We don't want any idiots showing up
and taking off with this ship!
Here are today's odds!
Add another weight!
Yeah! One that's super cool and
that can absolutely win for sure!
1,000 Gol on Poppy!
Right! Another weight!
1,500 on Pansy!
That was close!
Yes, that's easy to say,
Guard it well until the
coating craftsman arrives!
Darn it!
but the other people participating
in the race sound tough.
If only Franky were here!
You're acting unsightly!
Enough! Finish him off!
I dunno what to do!
I'm the one who doesn't know what to do!
Rosy Life Riders!
Hold on! Time out! I don't want to die yet!
The legendary Flying Fish Riders,
the fastest gang in Grand Jipang.
You could've at least escaped
to somewhere far away...
Yes, Duva-some!
Wait, I'm already long dead...
I'm suddenly feeling uneasy.
But I don't want this!
Rolling Express, who are speedy
when it comes to love and work.
I hope Luffy-chin and the others are okay...
What's with you, Camie?!
Oh! I like you!
Marry me! Marry me! Marry me!
Don't say worrisome stuff like that!
Shut the hell up!
But...
Brook!
They're all especially quick people.
They're strong.
There's nothing to worry about, Camie...
There are many other rivals, too.
Boss!
In this land, the strong are beautiful.
What's the big idea, leaving like that?
I hope you're right...
If we keep this up,
I'll only grow attached to you!
Thriller Company?
You "hope"? Knock that off!
Come on! Let's go back!
Who? I've never heard of them before...
Should a man ever approach this country,
Whoa, now! Stop!
Not so fast!
You saw for yourself how strong they are!
eradication is all that awaits him.
You're that policeman from earlier!
They'll be fine!
What're you doing?!
"Prison"
They're up against a navy admiral.
The man's awake!
Let me see! Let me see!
Not even Monkey-chan's group
stands a chance strength-wise.
I want to see, too!
Move.
You guys piss me off, but I have
no business with you right now.
He's moving around!
The seas ahead will be rough.
Look! He has no breasts at all!
We can't quietly let an enemy leave,
not even if he's a public official!
Oh, yeah! These arrows!
Giant waves they've never
seen before are coming.
What a weird, rugged creature!
They were strong enough
to destroy stone walls
Destroy him!
He looks so weak with his
shaggy hair and scrawny body!
They mustn't let these waves do them in.
You're annoying the neighborhood, dammit!
when I was being chased earlier!
Who're you guys?
They're the ones you were just talking about.
There. Can you hear it?
He slept for quite a long time...
They don't seem like
special arrows, though...
Three-Sword Style! Tatsu-Maki!
But I heard he ate meals while asleep!
What are you talking about?
They're Thriller Company.
They specialize in import wholesale.
Did you know that?
The arrows possess "Haki"!
Their strength is only natural!
What do men usually eat anyway? Raw meat?
Gum-Gum Billy Club!
They moved into the 13-story tower
built over in the Foreign District.
Little by little, the tide of
the times is beginning to change.
I get the feeling he'll eat anything...
Haki? What's that?!
What's going on?
Eh?! Does that mean you guys came
to ask for a portable shrine too?!
There she is!
Don't falter!
--What's all the noise?
--Oh! He can talk!
Overwhelm them with sheer numbers!
Margaret is all right!
Meanwhile, Monkey D. Luffy,
after being ejected
Where am I?
Everyone!
There's no end to 'em!
Our portable shrine has long been completed!
The man is with her! Kill him!
from Sabaody Archipelago
by Bartholomew Kuma...
What was I doing again?
Uh oh!
Halt!
We're here today to warn you
that it's pointless to enter the race!
Damn it!
Zoro! Nami!
Stop!
Usopp! Sanji! Chopper!
Margaret! Are you alright?!
What?! What do you mean?!
They're...
We need to hurry and finish the man off!
Yeah! There's no way to know until we try!
Oh, yeah!
Robin! Franky! Brook!
The Snake Princess has returned!
...gone!
Everyone was separated
at Sabaody Archipelago!
Where they hell did they go?! Find them!
Nice and feisty...
Where did you send all my friends?!
Just my type!
I can't hear!
In any case, it's in your best
interest to heed our advice!
Everyone! Shh! He's saying something!
Where did you disappear to, guys?!
We're back!
You don't want to get hurt, now do you?!
Hold on, Cindry-chan.
Why are you in front of me?
I remember eating mushrooms,
but everything after--
That bear-like Warlord
of the Sea is gonna pay!
My word...
You don't scare us!
My hat's gone!
How far am I gonna fly, anyway?!
There it is!
We have Boss Luffy on our side!
He's a policeman!
You have real guts to lay anchor in
the middle of monster-infested waters.
Give it back, you jerk!
Boss! Brook! Welcome back!
Oh, come to think of it...
Welcome back!
You must be hungry!
Have some special Stamina Rice Balls!
His arm stretched!
Let us leave for now!
Yes. We were attacked
only moments ago, in fact!
What kind of body does he have?!
I don't know if it's true or not,
but they say that his paw pads
Ooh! They look yum!
But you'll be sorry if you
dare oppose Thriller Company!
can send a person flying through the
sky for three days and three nights!
The Sea Prism Stone in this warship
may conceal our presence,
That's a relief!
What are you all doing?
M-M-Men can stretch their arms!
but staying anchored here for so long
We're fixing our portable shrine!
Then, could that mean that
instead of disappearing,
How shocking! Notes! Notes!
Hey.
is bound to attract attention visually.
You can't be serious...
Your friends left.
This is most intriguing!
they were all sent flying like this too?
The race is tomorrow, you know!
You'll never make it in time!
It's not easy,
Say! What's your name?
but the agreement between
the Kuja and the government
I wonder if that axe guy
was telling the truth...
Not if we can help it!
Th-They ditched me?!
I'm Luffy.
forbids us from getting any closer
Why? Why would you go to such lengths?!
A-All right! You've been warned!
Three whole days of this...
than three kilometers from your island.
I'm dead if I fall into the ocean...
I'm naked!
Pride!
What was that?!
You're slow!
I feel breezy!
Consequently, we're forced to wait
in the middle of the monsters' den.
What a weirdo!
Turning tail and running
isn't our style at all!
Do you know where my clothes are?
I'm hungry, too...
It doesn't get any creepier than that!
Men are slow and want to conceal
their heads before their bodies!
But... I'm feeling sleepy...
Yes!
Have you heard?
It almost sounds like they'll
try and mess with us...
They say the Kuja are specters
that turn people to stone!
We're the exact same way!
Zoro... Nami...
Listen, guys!
Rolling Express!
Get real!
Don't you dare lose to those creepy freaks!
Did you kill that Sea King?
Usopp... Sanji... Chopper...
I hear you're lacking raw materials!
I'm gonna make you guys
a super portable shrine!
Umm, before you get dressed, umm...!
Please use any pieces you want
from our broken portable shrine!
Robin... Franky... Brook...
One that definitely has a chance
of winning! So you better win!
Sea Kings are hardly rare in the Grand Line,
What's inside that bag
sewn between your legs?
Everyone!
Of course we will!
Let's win this thing, everyone!
You're the Flying Fish Riders!
but in the Calm Belts,
they're certainly larger...
Bag?
Yeah!
We brought ours too, so you can use it!
Through the sky he continued to soar.
no, monstrous.
Wait, you don't know what these are?
Come on!
We're placing our spirit in your hands!
What a weirdo! These are balls!
Really?!
And then...
Guys...!
Balls?
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Any sign of the Kuja ship?!
Balls?
Now I can build a super portable
shrine just like the one I imagined!
Balls?
Not yet, Vice-Admiral!
I can't hear you!
Balls?
How annoying.
--Balls?
There are no approaching ships at all!
That's right!
What's all the noise?
Let's do it!
Looks like we're going to
need more food for supper!
How long is she going to keep us waiting?!
I can't see them! Scoot over, Margaret!
Stop! Stop!
Or has the Kuja empress decided to...?!
That's a lame chant! What are
you, palanquin carriers?!
Sorry!
I'll go and make a lot!
Your notebook's in the way!
Sanji-kun! We're counting on you!
Right, sir!
What are balls?
But we couldn't think of anything else...
Nami-swan!
There's gotta be something
better that's more worthy
They're the family jewels, of course!
Just leave it to me!
of the Flying Fish Riders,
the fastest gang in all of Jipang!
What's the matter, Brook?
S-Sea King!
Wow!
Don't just stand there, help!
Handsome! Handsome! Handsome! Handsome!
Fire! Fire!
So men have family jewels!
But how can I ever have the face to?
--That's it! Say it more!
--Handsome! Handsome! Handsome! Handsome!
Gorgeous!
Just come on!
Family jewels!
Not the knees!
Just a bunch of idiots...
Now victory in the portable
shrine race is as good as ours!
Could you take your jewels out
and let us see them?
You're already one of the
shrine bearers, you know!
Hell no!
Impossible! Not even cannons have an effect?!
And then...!
Are you trying to kill me?! You idiot!
I'm alive...
Duval-sama! You're so wonderful!
I declare my love for you!
Do I have to spell it out for you?
Here are your clothes then!
He means you're our friend.
I don't think my being rubber
is why I'm still alive...
Yours were all torn up,
All those who want a kiss, form a line!
Friend...?
so I made new ones with the same design!
The ship'll be smashed to pieces
if we don't do something!
Oh?! That's great!
But what's this bear paw-looking thing?
What do we do?!
Oh! You cut in line!
Thanks! I don't even know who you are!
There's no way to defend against it!
I just hope the others
were saved the same way...
You know that's naughty of you!
I'm sure you'll like them!
Thank you!
Anyway, I gotta get back!
Is it planning to eat the entire ship?!
Hey, you! There are no free meals, boy!
Wh-What's going on?!
Where is this...
...and which way is Sabaody Archipelago?!
Boss! We're suddenly missing four people!
To think the very first to greet us
is this beast and not the Kuja...!
Oh, yeah!
Oh.
What?! Count again!
I have my Vivre Card!
Oh! I'll play a song to liven things up!
One!
Two!
Good thing we all got one!
Three!
What did you...?
Four!
Five!
Alright! I gotta go back!
I gotta get back there!
I added sexy flower frills too!
Six!
Seven!
I'm sure I'll see everyone again!
Outdoor outfits are all about the frills!
See? You're all here!
So we are!
Great job, Margaret!
That way!
He seems so happy he's shaking!
Oh, I'm rarin' to go now!
Who're you guys?!
Alright! Let's do it!
He's thanking you on his hands and knees!
Just some zombies passing by.
Yeah!
Z-Zom...?
Everyone focus on escaping!
Wh-What did you do with our friends?!
That's...
As we are now, we can't beat these guys!
...the vice-admiral!
I'm sorry for acting so tough...
Allowing an entire warship
to be food for a Sea King
I'm sorry for being loud every night...
Don't be stupid!
Just get out of here!
I'm a man, you know!
I just wanted someone to
pay attention to me...
would belittle the name of justice!
You can think things over after you're safe!
What is that?!
Please dry me overnight and
then make a broth out of me...
Go!
It's huge!
Why're you guys so down in the dumps?!
Because I did this!
Prepare to attack!
Those cuts...
Negative Hollow!
What?!
Did you slice it from inside its stomach?
What a vicious temper!
Is that your true nature?!
It's enormous!
I have not come to hunt Sea Kings.
None of the other entrants
even stand a chance!
What's wrong with me?!
Wantonly yelling without any care
for the fact that we saved his life...
I would like to finish my business here
and leave these waters quickly.
What other entrants?
--Negative! Negative!
--I'm depressed... Totally depressed...
What a savage temperament!
I couldn't save even one of my friends...!
We destroyed everyone's shrines
and made them drop out of the race!
His words and actions haven't shown
a shred of elegance whatsoever!
--Negative! Negative!
--Extremely depressed...
It looks like you have some skill.
Boss?!
Carrying shrines or winning races
won't help us make it in this world!
It won't be long now!
I was growing tired of waiting!
His kind really is incompatible
with us after all!
At last you've returned, Kuja Pirates!
We only need to get this jumbo
portable shrine across the finish line
This junk is nothing but a pipe dream!
Ouch!
I am Vice-Admiral Momonga
of Navy Headquarters!
and the treasure's all ours!
Even so, Kikyo!
He hasn't done much!
I'd feel sorry for killing him!
Hold on, Cindry-chan! Why
are you in front of me?!
Actually, that doesn't hurt,
Warlord of the Sea and
Pirate Empress Boa Hancock!
Boss!
but oh, there's something in the way...
It's almost noon.
Wait! Hold on!
Let the victory parade begin.
Show yourself! I've come for you!
Still...
You saved my life?!
That's another one down!
What happened?! Tell me!
So sorry, but the
Snake Princess isn't coming out.
...the card is pointing this way...
Please wait!
She's sent many replies now!
These girls saved you after you ate
a lethal mushroom and collapsed.
Alright!
That's men for you!
Such unsophisticated creatures!
Giant Pistol!
I haven't seen a live man in a long time!
The Pinwheel Eatery will
also be participating!
Pirates and merchants always escape
by boat when they see the Kuja flag!
Oh, really?! Thanks, you!
Sorry for complaining about the clothes!
What?!
N-No good...
Stop. That's a crude laugh.
Just don't shoot me!
I'm out of strength...
We have received her replies of,
Thriller Company!
Your apologies and excuses mean nothing!
Sanji! Food!
The treasure is ours!
"I will follow your orders
to convene at once."
This is the woman empire of Amazon Lily!
Oh, wait, he's not here...
But she shows no indication
of coming whatsoever!
Nothing's biting...
You can do it, Pinwheel!
Men are forbidden!
This morning's newspaper.
That has been the absolute
rule here for centuries!
I got one!
A place and date has been decided
for the public execution
Alright, you!
Bring it on, then!
Whoa, it's huge!
of Portgas D. Ace, 2nd Division
Commander of the Whitebeard Pirates!
Never in history has it been broken!
The Great Portable Shrine Race for
the sacred treasure will now take place!
"Stomach rumble"
Woman empire?!
There is no turning back now!
I won't let you beat me!
The World Government has issued strict orders
Thriller Company!
Pinwheel Eatery!
forcing the Seven Warlords
of the Sea to assemble!
Bones... on... a...
Both teams will battle it out!
Refuse and the agreement is off!
--piece... of... wood...
--Help...
Your title of Warlord of
the Sea will be revoked!
Thanks for the food!
Think about what that would mean!
...me...
This brings back memories
Until now, the World Government
has allowed you to do as you wish,
of when Grandpa would throw me
into the jungle when I was a kid!
but without the title, you would be
nothing more than ordinary pirates,
Ready!
I don't wanna remember that.
and therefore adversaries of the
World Government and the navy!
This place sure is quiet, though...
Do you hear that, Boa Hancock?!
You're in the way!
Woman empire?!
Now that you've regained consciousness,
He sure eats a lot...
we have no sympathy for you!
He sure does.
Yeah! Now that I look closer,
it's nothing but women!
This guy doesn't know the
first thing about manners!
What a weird country!
Aren't these Laughing Mushrooms?
Geez, no one decent ever comes here!
I can't see!
We'll put an end to that
disdainful way of talking as well!
You sure do eat a lot!
This is no time to be foolin' around!
Hey!
Yeah! This is perfect for times like this!
Do we really have to put an end to him?
They've taken the lead!
More yakitori!
Aphelandra!
Don't eat with him!
Here's the bill!
When the Snake Princess returns,
Why me?!
Now I'm having fun!
she will absolutely disapprove
of this situation!
Even though I'm all alone!
My Flying Fish!
My, how delectable!
There are some weird ones over here, too!
You'll also be charged with the crime
of bringing a man into the village!
That was truly delic--
I'm borrowing this!
Thief!
Now I'm feeling mad!
Oh, how rude of me.
You got that right!
Who are you, anyway?!
Margaret.
Laughing Mushrooms! Laughing Mushrooms!
Sweetpea.
Oh, please excuse my late introduction.
Aphelandra.
Oh! There are weird mushrooms here, too!
This is for your sake!
It is a pleasure to meet you.
Crying Mushrooms!
It is best that we cover up this incident!
I am the dead and skeletonized Brook.
I was born in...
This is too heavy, Master...
You feeble fools!
Hurry! The smoke is rising from over there!
Wait! Let me go!
Now they'll catch up to us!
I forget.
Stay calm!
I have to get to the place
my friends and I agreed on!
What?!
Who placed a kitten...
They've been anchored offshore for a while;
The genius Hogback-sama's
portable shrine isn't on this low a level!
If you're gonna introduce yourself,
do it all the way to the end!
you don't think they secretly
made landfall, do you?!
That makes me feel sick!
Shoot!
...in my path?!
I only remember my name.
If so, then this is very serious!
No! There's heavy security
all around the island!
It's possible that some sort of shock
caused you to lose your memory!
M-My deepest apologies!
Besides, if by some chance
they did get through,
I'm the one responsible!
it's hard to believe they'd do anything
to draw attention to themselves!
Be more careful.
Y-Yes!
Say, is it just me, or is something
inside your head making a sound?
S-Stop that!
So you've come out, Boa Hancock!
Then who is it?
Maybe you have a screw loose?
I don't know.
Let's split into two groups now!
Eh?! That's not good!
Got it!
It opens up?!
Awesome!
Oh! I found this in there!
So long!
He broke through the roof!
Huh?! What is that?!
Don't let him escape!
It's a sideways flute...
Looks like it's time to
show off our true power, too!
Don't let your guard down, men!
A flute?
Here we go...
He's right!
How do things work in there?!
We're dealing with the boss
of a bunch of specters!
Boss! Feed this cola to the shrine!
You're a funny guy!
There's no telling how terrifying she is!
Don't let your guard--!
Okay!
These arrows are really strong!
Here?
Th-That's the Pirate Empress?!
Wh-Whoa!
Well?
Yikes!
What is that?!
She's the definition of the most
beautiful woman in the world!
Margaret! Margaret!
Looks pretty good on you!
Everyone get on the shrine!
Over here!
What is it, Sweetpea?
He's nimbler than he looks!
What do you make of this?
Here we go!
Of what?
Aphelandra!
Right!
What do you suppose this is?
Hey! That's against the rules!
Sorry for saving you and then doing this!
Like you're one to talk!
Halt, man!
Neither one is a portable shrine anymore...
These girls are terrifying!
He fell!
Now he's bouncing!
Wh-What the...?! This is a person!
Nami's much better by far!
Hmm, now what do I do?
Is it someone from the village?
I don't know.
Take him down!
There are so many mushrooms
growing out of her body...
We're getting nowhere like this!
Don't let him escape! After him!
Or not...!
Leave it to me!
Do you think maybe it was actually
a signal fire calling for help?
One direct hit from these
arrows and I'm a goner!
There he is!
Try this on for size!
Alright!
That's a cannon!
This is it.
Only one meat chop left
until they're sold out!
Look! She ate this mushroom!
Look out!
First come, first served!
A Parasite Mushroom.
If that's how it's gonna be...!
When eaten, mushrooms
grow out of your body!
Hold on! You gotta pay for that!
This is bad!
Treasure payment plan!
If we don't do something, the mushrooms
will sap away her vitality and kill her!
Is that man a gibbon?!
Victory is ours now!
Damn! We lost him!
So it's a race against time!
We cannot have a living man
in this land whatsoever!
This can't be!
Enemy on the loose!
Aphelandra! Carry her to the village!
Look!
We have to find him and kill him
as quickly as possible!
The man has escaped!
"Portable Shrine Race Participants"
"Fang-Frog Shipping Agency"
"Big Helmet Clan"
Okay!
My food disappeared!
"Flying Fish Riders"
Let's split up and search!
To the village it is!
What is that?!
The Flying Fish Riders have dropped out too.
He went that way!
All right! Find him and
kill him, without fail!
My meal is gone too!
Let's hurry!
That just leaves the Rolling Express
and Pinwheel Eatery teams!
Understood!
Kill him!
Is it a good idea to be here?
Just give yourself up!
Once they're out of the way,
victory will belong to Thriller Company!
"Rolling Express"
"Pinwheel Eatery"
This is where I ran from earlier...
Support Paddle!
We have an urgent patient!
No other choice!
This is no time for that!
I-Is it just me, or are
there a lot more of em?!
Hey! Down in front! I can't see!
The race is tomorrow.
There he is!
Get back here!
Uh oh!
Let's go finish our work now, Absalom.
I won't miss this time!
I can't talk!
What happened to her?!
She's covered in mushrooms!
I'll get him! Aphelandra!
Keep it as a pet.
Have you seen her in the village before?
Right!
I don't need you to tell me that.
Guys! Keep moving along the river!
No, never...
Did you get him?!
You're not getting away from me!
It's a quicker route than on land!
Hey, who is she?
Not yet! He fell into the jungle!
Things are going to be fun tonight!
Got it!
The mushrooms are covering her face...
Where do you think she came from?
He dodged it!
Is she even alive?
Oh, Cindry-chan.
Why do you keep getting in front?
She ate a Parasite Mushroom.
I can't stop!
Sweetpea!
What should we do, Belladonna?
You're not going anywhere!
Get them!
They come off when pulled,
so pull them out. All of them.
That's far enough!
"Amazon Lily Empress,
Captain of the Kuja Pirates Warlord of the Sea
Empress Boa Hancock"
They come off?
So you've finally come for me...
We've cornered you!
They really do!
I've brought some food, everyone!
You guys just don't give up...
What meddlesome people.
But some of the roots are left behind!
Oh! Thanks!
They just keep coming...!
"Youngest of the Gorgon Sisters
Boa Marigold"
Lucky!
I thought this might happen!
My recent replies were lies.
I'll get rid of them afterward,
so don't worry about the roots.
You have a trick of your own?!
Oh, right! My Vivre Card!
"Second of the Gorgon Sisters
Boa Sandersonia"
You've certainly brought
a strange one home, Margaret.
I will not go to war!
I couldn't help it!
But...
She was barely alive,
and she might be from the village!
I want you to let me keep
my title of Warlord of the Sea.
"Express Delivery"
I left the old guy's piece
of paper in my other pants!
Drive right, now!
That's all of them!
Talk and you'll bite your tongue off!
There she is! That's her!
And...
Okay. Now step back a little.
Shut up!
I also want all of
the cargo on your ship.
36 Pound Phoenix!
What nonsense is this?!
You're not a selfish little child!
I can't talk here!
Do you honestly think we'll accept
such outrageous demands?!
Sorry! There's something I wanna ask you!
It's the Grand Shrine!
Who's taking our shrine?!
Let go! Help!
No idea!
Is it a thief?!
Oh no! Margaret's been abducted!
Boss! This is the last of the cola!
Ouch! Hot! Hot!
Hurry and haul it over!
Alright!
I-It's floating!
What a beautiful woman!
I-I-I'm on fire!
I'll give her anything!
I'm stuffed! That was great!
Put me out! Ouch!
Why are you hauling our cargo?!
Hold on, Belladonna! What are you doing?!
Simply being with you
makes me overeat as well!
Come to your senses!
Oh no! I blindly listened to what she said!
This is the only way to keep
them from growing back.
You guys do eat too much!
What?!
Gum-Gum Balloon!
Portgas D. Ace's public execution
is in exactly one week from today!
But isn't that a little excessive?
Wh-What the...?
A portable shrine is flying off!
She passed out again!
Stop!
Fire Fist Ace's life will be ended
in the town square of Marineford,
Come back, portable shrine!
This sucks!
Still, she was covered in injuries
before she was covered in mushrooms.
They're not getting away!
Let's follow it!
where Navy Headquarters stands!
Yeah!
In other words, Whitebeard will
make a move within the next week
Oh, you're wonderful! Marry me!
Really?
Hey. You alright?
They seem like marks
from a tremendous battle.
Stay away!
No way.
You... turned fat just now, didn't you?!
Rejection!
to rescue Ace!
We'll need to treat her wounds, too.
That's her 4,450th rejection!
I hate to ask, Margaret,
Navy Headquarters, led by three admirals,
This thing... sure is heavy...
but could you go wash her off in the river?
is prepared to counter Whitebeard
with full military force!
Get back here!
O-Okay! Sure!
You must be crazy to jump from way up there!
Stop, you portable shrine!
Look! It's the goal!
Will you lose the title of Warlord,
or accept the orders to assemble?!
Marry me!
I was ready to die!
Who're you guys?
Go!
Decide now!
It's a miracle we're still alive!
Time is nearly up!
Really?
They're...!
Stay away!
I'm not gonna do anything.
How frightening! Zombies!
This...
I've heard that you men have a virus!
...is the giant portable shrine's...
...true form?
Do all men suddenly grow fat?!
I like the title of Warlord.
It sounds like she's not from
this village after all, Sweetpea.
I don't have any kind of virus,
I don't want it taken away.
Monkey! Monkey!
Yeah...
But I hate the World Government.
What a huge spider!
and it'll be a pain to explain,
so let's just say all men suddenly grow fat.
Huh? Look here!
I commend you for forcing my trump card!
I don't want to obey its orders.
What's wrong?
Anyway, was there something
in my torn-up pants pockets?
There's still a mushroom
between her legs that we missed!
However...!
Gavotte Bond en Avant!
This is the end!
How does this sound?
Spider Sticky Net!
The marines who came to get me
There's one left!
It's really important!
had a mysterious accident on the sea
and were wiped out when
they all turned to stone?
But doesn't this one seem
different from the others?
We're stuck!
She's planning to do something!
Is this it?
Hey! Can't you do something?!
It's oddly shaped!
Don't let your guard down!
Huh? There's something
weird underneath it, too!
I've heard about this before!
I do have one last trick up my sleeve...
This is it! This is it! What a relief!
What is this? A Sack Mushroom?
A ship was attacked by the Kuja pirate ship,
Anyway, I guess we better pull it off!
I wouldn't know what to do without this!
and when it was discovered later,
...but I'm out of cola!
Wow! You're awesome, Brook!
Alright!
only strange statues were found onboard!
Cola?!
Huh?
Thanks for holding onto it!
How did I know how to do that?
Onami-san! Down there!
It won't come off! How come?!
H-Hey! Look at that!
Hey, you guys!
It's stretching!
L-Let go!
What's all the ruckus?!
Hey, what's going on? What happened?
Wh-What are those?!
Onami! Sanji!
This is the end!
She says it stretches...
What the...?!
Oh, what a relief!
S-Strange statues?!
What does?!
A mushroom!
There was something written
on it, so I figured...
Seriously? Is it a Neat Mushroom?
Monkey! Monkey!
Marry me...!
I already told you!
Your childish selfishness
will not be allowed!
That's enough gawking, all of you!
This isn't a freak show!
Boss!
Big Sis has a terrible personality.
This is horrible...
What is it?
You're watching too, you know!
Win!
Here, look!
It's all over!
But she gets everything she wants.
Look! There seems to be a problem!
We can't enter the race like this!
Yeah!
Yes. There is a reason for that.
Still, she's not very well-endowed.
Our only choice is to drop out now...
How odd! It looks like it's moving!
She even seems sort of rugged.
Gaon Cannon!
When will I finally get to marry someone?!
Fire!
If this was all meant to destroy
their portable shrine before the race...
Do you know why that is?
It's no use.
No way!
Because no matter what I do...
Maybe Aphelandra can pull it off!
A bunch of stuff happened
Th-This can't be!
...then ours is in danger too!
and all my friends went flying
through the sky in different directions.
Hold on!
Huh? Me?
No, Omao-chan is in bigger trouble!
...even if I kick a kitten...
Yeah, yeah!
Wait, where is Cindry-chan?!
...even if I pull your ears off...
I bet it'll come off if you
pull as hard as you can!
Omao-chan?
She hasn't returned from delivering
meals to the Franky Workshop,
But thanks to these pieces of paper,
Maybe we should all pull it together!
...or even if I kill someone,
When did she...?!
we can all get together again!
everyone in the world would forgive me.
so we were just on our
way to check things out!
No.
The reason for that is, yes...
If that mushroom won't come off...
Look out! Outta the way, outta the way!
They're all tough, you see!
...because I'm beautiful!
Oh, I've been thanking you non-stop!
...then we should simply
burn it off as Belladonna did!
W-Wait! Let's discuss this!
Because I'm beautiful!
Omao-chan!
You ruined the festival everyone
was looking forward to!
Is there anything I can do for you?
Oh! Yes! That's a good idea!
Snake Princess!
Don't you agree, Margaret?
Could you take out your family
jewels so I can see them, then?!
Gum-Gum Bazooka!
Now you're going to pay!
Yes!
We'll let you do anything!
We are?!
After all, you're beautiful!
I told you, they don't come off!
What's this? What's this?
What's going on?
Stop that, all of you!
Oh, Granny Nyon!
Men are cheapskates after all!
Boss! Franky-san and the others are...!
You're really serious about taking them!
There's a mushroom growing
on this girl that won't come off!
Put the sword away!
And the winner is Pinwheel Eatery!
Who are these "friends" of yours?!
So we're deciding whether
we should pull it off all together
For being charmed by me,
your guilty consciences...
Oh, I'm a pirate!
or burn it off.
Now, now. Wait. Just who is this?
...will turn your bodies solid!
Do you know what a pirate is?
Congratulations!
Get Dr. Bluenose right away!
You're a pirate?
Now, then...
Right!
The million Ryo-Berry prize!
This land's empress is a pirate, too.
This is it here.
I'm afraid I'm going to have to keep this.
Love-Love Beam!
Really?
Hey, you alright?
Then she has a women-only pirate group?
Let's see here...
Huh?!
My head hurts...
Just look at the disastrous
state of this town!
Hanco--!
I'm bleary-eyed...
Are they strong?
Where is this mushroom?
That's a foolish question!
I don't have eyes, though,
as I'm nothing but bones...
You can't be serious...!
Oh, my!
But...
As promised, the sacred treasure is yours!
Granny Nyon!
The most elite warriors of this land
ride aboard her pirate ship!
Are you all right?!
I'd say you're too okay.
Alright!
I'd expect no less from
a navy vice-admiral...
Y-Yes, th-there's nothing to worry about...
We did it!
I wonder what the sacred treasure is like!
They're very strong!
Th-This person...
I see.
It's been 100 years since
its last exhibition,
You used pain to block out the evil thoughts.
so this will be my first
time seeing it as well.
You've much experience, indeed.
Everyone here looks up to the Snake Princess!
However...
I wish I could say the same about your men.
Th-This person...
Okay!
She's strong, noble, and the most
beautiful woman in the world!
This is the magical sacred treasure
passed down in Grand Jipang...
Fools...!
The Pirate Empress, Boa Hancock!
I remember.
...is a m-m-man!
It looks like you're the only one left now.
Your memory is back?!
This land is closely protected
by her and her two sisters!
Yes.
I remember everything now.
One and zero are not the same!
Wh-What's with that get-up?
Where are you going?
I should not be here.
"Instructions for the Maiden Panties..."
This is because...
Oh no! The Snake Princess's ship is nearby!
...I'm actually a member of Thriller Company.
"Make a wish with these panties on
and it will be granted forthwith."
What?!
Brook-san...
Th-This is a m-man?!
"Limited to beautiful women only"?!
Come on, now!
Wonderful!
I've never seen one before!
We will now return to the
peaceful Amazon Lily!
This is bad!
That's not a very funny joke!
Omao-san.
We need to end the
incident with the man quickly!
Do you think you could
put those panties on for me?
Yes, Snake Princess!
Here sits the maiden island of Amazon Lily,
"Kuja"
Thank you for everything.
Yuck!
Kikyo...
inhabited by the tribe of
female warriors known as the Kuja.
Boa Hancock!
It looks like the man jumped
into the jungle after all!
Hey...!
I will wait here as long as I can!
Huh? Where am I? Who am I?
I will not return empty-handed!
Warriors! To the jungle!
May you never dream of it or step foot on it,
If you do not reappear in two days' time...
You've lost your memory again?!
Kill the man and rescue Margaret!
Brook-san!
...the agreement is off!
The Snake Princess has returned!
should you still value your life.
"To Be Continued"
Do as you wish.
After being sent flying away from
Sabaody Archipelago by Kuma,
The imprisoned Luffy
Vice-Admiral Momonga of Navy Headquarters
Hoping to borrow a ship,
What's with those Thriller Company guys?
Luffy makes his way into the Kuja Castle,
plans an escape so he can rejoin his friends.
waits for the Kuja Pirates
to speak with Hancock,
Destroying the portable shrines
so they can win without trying...
Luffy lands on a unique island.
but in his rush, he bursts in on
Hancock as she's taking a bath.
one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
That's beyond cowardly!
Fearful that the Snake Princess, Hancock,
In the jungle, Luffy eats the
wrong mushrooms and collapse.
Yeah! They won't get away with this!
However, Hancock refuses to
comply to the navy's summons.
We'll win this fight!
will find out that they brought
a man into their tribe,
As he sees Hancock's form through the steam,
There, he is found by a group of beautiful
female warriors bearing snakes.
In return, she unleashes her Devil
Fruit abilities on the marines.
Everybody, attack!
they begin to pursue him.
something on her back catches Luffy's eye...
Do it yourself!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Hurry Back to Your Friends!
The Maiden Island Adventure"
"The Secret Hidden on the Backs --
Luffy and the Snake Princess Meet"
"Feudal Era Side Story -
Defeat Thriller Company's Trap"
"Landing! The All-Female Island,
Amazon Lily"
"Everyone Falls in Love!
Pirate Empress Hancock"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
I'm gonna be a detective!