Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
"Feudal Era Side Story -
Boss Luffy Appears Again"
Greetings once again!
It is the height of summer in the
legendary city of Grand Jipang,
a veritable mishmash of cultures
from all places and all times.
Everyone appears to be as heated up
and energetic as the great sun itself,
but why might that be?
Big news! Big news!
Big news!
Great Portable Shrine Race?
Yeah! The whole town is abuzz
with the news about it!
Oh? It's a big race that takes
place once every 100 years?
I've heard about that! They
say the prize is incredible!
Supposedly, the winners get to ask
the Grand Shrine's sacred treasure
for any wish they want!
It'll grant any wish?
Here you are! Have some cold water!
Oh! Thanks!
That's good!
You sure are thoughtful! Who are you?
She's our newest hired hand.
I'm Omao. It's nice to meet you!
Seconds!
Here you are!
A heaping bowl! Awesome!
What good service!
Yum! Yum!
You don't need to give him so
much extra food, Omao-chan.
He's just going to put it on
his tab without paying his bill.
Okay!
So, what is this sacred treasure?
Oh, right...
They say that the sacred treasure has
the magical power to grant any wish.
It's kept in the Grand Shrine's treasure
room, which is opened once a century.
One policeman supposedly
made it big and became a samurai
after his wish was granted,
and one cook married the
prettiest girl in town
and lived in complete happiness!
That sounds great!
That sounds neat!
Alright! Let's enter the
Great Portable Shrine Race!
Forget it!
I refuse to take part in a sweaty
competition for something so suspicious!
The winners also receive
one million Ryo-Berries.
C'mon, you guys! Let's get ready!
We're gonna win the
Great Portable Shrine Race!
She suddenly has life in her...
Okay, we'll need a great
portable shrine if we want to win!
So, where are we going, Onami?
--The lumberyard.
--Lumberyard?!
I hear the greatest builder
in all of Jipang lives there!
Hello!
Is there no one home?
Wh-What is this?!
Oh, what a nice roll of fabric!
Oh, sorry 'bout that!
Oh, you picked it up for me? Thanks, girlie!
It went flying off when I tried drying it
with my Special Franky Workshop
Super Drying Clockwork Mechanism!
Master Builder!
--You shouldn't go out in public...
--...looking like that!
That was a close call...
You didn't make it in time!
Okay, girlie. Could I have that back?
Eh?
That.
This?
It is my loincloth, after all! Super!
L-L-L...
Loincloth?!
Awesome! What's this doohickey?!
It's my Super Drying Clockwork
Mechanism Fun Fan Sunny Wind!
It's so cool!
The loincloth...
The loincloth landed right on my face...
So, what kind of super portable
shrine do you want me to make?
Well, one that's...
One that can win!
Yeah! One that's super cool and
that can absolutely win for sure!
Yes, that's easy to say,
but the other people participating
in the race sound tough.
The legendary Flying Fish Riders,
the fastest gang in Grand Jipang.
Rolling Express, who are speedy
when it comes to love and work.
Oh! I like you!
Marry me! Marry me! Marry me!
They're all especially quick people.
There are many other rivals, too.
Thriller Company?
Who? I've never heard of them before...
Who're you guys?
They're the ones you were just talking about.
They're Thriller Company.
They specialize in import wholesale.
They moved into the 13-story tower
built over in the Foreign District.
Eh?! Does that mean you guys came
to ask for a portable shrine too?!
Our portable shrine has long been completed!
We're here today to warn you
that it's pointless to enter the race!
What?! What do you mean?!
Yeah! There's no way to know until we try!
Nice and feisty...
Just my type!
In any case, it's in your best
interest to heed our advice!
You don't want to get hurt, now do you?!
Hold on, Cindry-chan.
Why are you in front of me?
You don't scare us!
We have Boss Luffy on our side!
He's a policeman!
Let us leave for now!
But you'll be sorry if you
dare oppose Thriller Company!
Hey.
Your friends left.
Th-They ditched me?!
A-All right! You've been warned!
What was that?!
What a weirdo!
It doesn't get any creepier than that!
It almost sounds like they'll
try and mess with us...
Listen, guys!
Don't you dare lose to those creepy freaks!
I'm gonna make you guys
a super portable shrine!
One that definitely has a chance
of winning! So you better win!
Of course we will!
Let's win this thing, everyone!
Yeah!
Come on!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
I can't hear you!
How annoying.
What's all the noise?
Stop! Stop!
That's a lame chant! What are
you, palanquin carriers?!
Right, sir!
But we couldn't think of anything else...
There's gotta be something
better that's more worthy
of the Flying Fish Riders,
the fastest gang in all of Jipang!
Handsome! Handsome! Handsome! Handsome!
--That's it! Say it more!
--Handsome! Handsome! Handsome! Handsome!
Just a bunch of idiots...
Now victory in the portable
shrine race is as good as ours!
And then...!
Duval-sama! You're so wonderful!
I declare my love for you!
All those who want a kiss, form a line!
Oh! You cut in line!
You know that's naughty of you!
Wh-What's going on?!
Boss! We're suddenly missing four people!
What?! Count again!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Seven!
See? You're all here!
So we are!
Who're you guys?!
Just some zombies passing by.
Z-Zom...?
Wh-What did you do with our friends?!
I'm sorry for acting so tough...
I'm sorry for being loud every night...
I just wanted someone to
pay attention to me...
Please dry me overnight and
then make a broth out of me...
Why're you guys so down in the dumps?!
Because I did this!
Negative Hollow!
--Negative! Negative!
--I'm depressed... Totally depressed...
--Extremely depressed...
Boss?!
Carrying shrines or winning races
won't help us make it in this world!
This junk is nothing but a pipe dream!
Boss!
That's another one down!
Nothing's biting...
I got one!
Alright, you!
Whoa, it's huge!
I won't let you beat me!
Bones... on... a...
--piece... of... wood...
--Help...
...me...
He sure eats a lot...
He sure does.
This guy doesn't know the
first thing about manners!
Geez, no one decent ever comes here!
You sure do eat a lot!
More yakitori!
Don't eat with him!
Here's the bill!
Why me?!
My, how delectable!
That was truly delic--
Oh, how rude of me.
You got that right!
Who are you, anyway?!
Oh, please excuse my late introduction.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
I am the dead and skeletonized Brook.
I was born in...
I forget.
What?!
If you're gonna introduce yourself,
do it all the way to the end!
That makes me feel sick!
I only remember my name.
It's possible that some sort of shock
caused you to lose your memory!
Say, is it just me, or is something
inside your head making a sound?
Maybe you have a screw loose?
Eh?! That's not good!
It opens up?!
Awesome!
Oh! I found this in there!
It's a sideways flute...
A flute?
Here we go...
How do things work in there?!
You're a funny guy!
Well?
Looks pretty good on you!
"Portable Shrine Race Participants"
"Fang-Frog Shipping Agency"
"Big Helmet Clan"
"Flying Fish Riders"
The Flying Fish Riders have dropped out too.
That just leaves the Rolling Express
and Pinwheel Eatery teams!
Once they're out of the way,
victory will belong to Thriller Company!
"Rolling Express"
"Pinwheel Eatery"
The race is tomorrow.
Let's go finish our work now, Absalom.
I don't need you to tell me that.
Things are going to be fun tonight!
Oh, Cindry-chan.
Why do you keep getting in front?
I've brought some food, everyone!
Oh! Thanks!
Lucky!
"Express Delivery"
Who's taking our shrine?!
No idea!
Is it a thief?!
I-It's floating!
I'm stuffed! That was great!
Simply being with you
makes me overeat as well!
You guys do eat too much!
Wh-What the...?
A portable shrine is flying off!
Stop!
Come back, portable shrine!
Let's follow it!
Yeah!
Oh, you're wonderful! Marry me!
No way.
Rejection!
That's her 4,450th rejection!
This thing... sure is heavy...
Get back here!
Stop, you portable shrine!
Who're you guys?
They're...!
How frightening! Zombies!
Gavotte Bond en Avant!
Wow! You're awesome, Brook!
Huh?
How did I know how to do that?
Hey, you guys!
What's all the ruckus?!
Onami! Sanji!
What the...?!
Marry me...!
This is horrible...
It's all over!
We can't enter the race like this!
Our only choice is to drop out now...
When will I finally get to marry someone?!
If this was all meant to destroy
their portable shrine before the race...
...then ours is in danger too!
No, Omao-chan is in bigger trouble!
Omao-chan?
She hasn't returned from delivering
meals to the Franky Workshop,
so we were just on our
way to check things out!
Look out! Outta the way, outta the way!
Omao-chan!
Gum-Gum Bazooka!
Boss! Franky-san and the others are...!
Get Dr. Bluenose right away!
Right!
Hey, you alright?
My head hurts...
I'm bleary-eyed...
I don't have eyes, though,
as I'm nothing but bones...
I'd say you're too okay.
I remember.
Your memory is back?!
Yes.
I remember everything now.
Wh-What's with that get-up?
Where are you going?
I should not be here.
This is because...
...I'm actually a member of Thriller Company.
What?!
Brook-san...
Come on, now!
That's not a very funny joke!
Thank you for everything.
Hey...!
"To Be Continued"
What's with those Thriller Company guys?
Destroying the portable shrines
so they can win without trying...
That's beyond cowardly!
Yeah! They won't get away with this!
We'll win this fight!
Everybody, attack!
Do it yourself!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Feudal Era Side Story -
Defeat Thriller Company's Trap"
I'm gonna be a detective!