Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Realizing their ship needs to be
coated to reach Fishman Island,
the Straw Hat crew landed
on the Sabaody Archipelago.
There they met Rayleigh, a skilled craftsman
and the former vice-captain
of the Roger Pirates.
However, Sentomaru,
captain of the Science Unit,
stood before the crew.
Ashigara Dokkoi Shove!
Luffy!
Navy Admiral Kizaru appeared next,
and Luffy and friends found
themselves in a grave situation!
Now you can have a nice, long rest...
Zoro!
You're getting involved in this...
...Dark King Rayleigh?!
Don't be plucking these young sprouts!
Their era is just about to begin!
Old guy!
Thanks to Rayleigh's help,
it appeared the crew had escaped danger,
but then Bartholomew Kuma,
a Warlord of the Sea, also appeared!
We will never meet again.
Farewell...
And so the Straw Hat crew
suffered a complete collapse.
"Landing! The All-Female Island,
Amazon Lily"
D-Damn...
I can't seem to wink right...!
Duval-sama! We found it! A bay by Grove #41!
Got it! I'll be right there!
Alright, men!
Protect it at all costs,
in the name of the Rosy Life Riders!
Yes, sir!
Hurry, Motobalo! Grove #41!
Still, what were those
island-shaking shockwaves?
I hope they're okay...
You still haven't caught them?!
Admiral Kizaru is currently pursuing them,
so it should only be a matter of time!
Please have patience!
You pathetic, dimwitted dogs!
Not only did they do this
to my father and brother,
but they also let all of our slaves escape!
What do they take the blood
of this world's Creators for?!
When I get my hands on them,
I'm going to put them through
a living hell so horrible
that they'll crawl on the ground
and beg for forgiveness!
Duval-sama.
What's taking Young Master Straw Hat
and the others so long?
Maybe they're busy with
the people chasing ‘em?
I heard the port's in a real uproar!
Yeah. I saw it from the air.
Marines and pirates were having at it.
It was a real mess!
Then that's all the more
reason to stay sharp!
We don't want any idiots showing up
and taking off with this ship!
Guard it well until the
coating craftsman arrives!
Rosy Life Riders!
Yes, Duva-some!
I'm suddenly feeling uneasy.
I hope Luffy-chin and the others are okay...
What's with you, Camie?!
Don't say worrisome stuff like that!
But...
They're strong.
There's nothing to worry about, Camie...
I hope you're right...
You "hope"? Knock that off!
You saw for yourself how strong they are!
They'll be fine!
They're up against a navy admiral.
Not even Monkey-chan's group
stands a chance strength-wise.
The seas ahead will be rough.
Giant waves they've never
seen before are coming.
They mustn't let these waves do them in.
There. Can you hear it?
Little by little, the tide of
the times is beginning to change.
Meanwhile, Monkey D. Luffy,
after being ejected
from Sabaody Archipelago
by Bartholomew Kuma...
Damn it!
Zoro! Nami!
Usopp! Sanji! Chopper!
Robin! Franky! Brook!
Where did you send all my friends?!
Where did you disappear to, guys?!
That bear-like Warlord
of the Sea is gonna pay!
How far am I gonna fly, anyway?!
Oh, come to think of it...
I don't know if it's true or not,
but they say that his paw pads
can send a person flying through the
sky for three days and three nights!
Then, could that mean that
instead of disappearing,
they were all sent flying like this too?
I wonder if that axe guy
was telling the truth...
Three whole days of this...
I'm dead if I fall into the ocean...
I'm hungry, too...
But... I'm feeling sleepy...
Zoro... Nami...
Usopp... Sanji... Chopper...
Robin... Franky... Brook...
Everyone!
Through the sky he continued to soar.
And then...
I'm alive...
I don't think my being rubber
is why I'm still alive...
But what's this bear paw-looking thing?
I just hope the others
were saved the same way...
Anyway, I gotta get back!
Where is this...
...and which way is Sabaody Archipelago?!
Oh, yeah!
I have my Vivre Card!
Good thing we all got one!
Alright! I gotta go back!
I gotta get back there!
I'm sure I'll see everyone again!
That way!
Everyone focus on escaping!
As we are now, we can't beat these guys!
Just get out of here!
You can think things over after you're safe!
Go!
What's wrong with me?!
I couldn't save even one of my friends...!
Ouch!
Actually, that doesn't hurt,
but oh, there's something in the way...
Still...
...the card is pointing this way...
Alright!
Giant Pistol!
N-No good...
I'm out of strength...
Sanji! Food!
Oh, wait, he's not here...
"Stomach rumble"
Thanks for the food!
This brings back memories
of when Grandpa would throw me
into the jungle when I was a kid!
I don't wanna remember that.
This place sure is quiet, though...
Aren't these Laughing Mushrooms?
Yeah! This is perfect for times like this!
Now I'm having fun!
Even though I'm all alone!
There are some weird ones over here, too!
Now I'm feeling mad!
Laughing Mushrooms! Laughing Mushrooms!
Oh! There are weird mushrooms here, too!
Crying Mushrooms!
Hurry! The smoke is rising from over there!
They've been anchored offshore for a while;
you don't think they secretly
made landfall, do you?!
If so, then this is very serious!
No! There's heavy security
all around the island!
Besides, if by some chance
they did get through,
it's hard to believe they'd do anything
to draw attention to themselves!
Then who is it?
I don't know.
Let's split into two groups now!
Got it!
What is that?!
Margaret! Margaret!
Over here!
What is it, Sweetpea?
What do you make of this?
Of what?
What do you suppose this is?
Wh-What the...?! This is a person!
Is it someone from the village?
I don't know.
There are so many mushrooms
growing out of her body...
Do you think maybe it was actually
a signal fire calling for help?
This is it.
Look! She ate this mushroom!
A Parasite Mushroom.
When eaten, mushrooms
grow out of your body!
This is bad!
If we don't do something, the mushrooms
will sap away her vitality and kill her!
So it's a race against time!
Aphelandra! Carry her to the village!
Okay!
To the village it is!
Let's hurry!
We have an urgent patient!
Hey! Down in front! I can't see!
What happened to her?!
She's covered in mushrooms!
Have you seen her in the village before?
No, never...
Hey, who is she?
The mushrooms are covering her face...
Where do you think she came from?
Is she even alive?
She ate a Parasite Mushroom.
What should we do, Belladonna?
They come off when pulled,
so pull them out. All of them.
They come off?
They really do!
But some of the roots are left behind!
I'll get rid of them afterward,
so don't worry about the roots.
You've certainly brought
a strange one home, Margaret.
I couldn't help it!
She was barely alive,
and she might be from the village!
That's all of them!
Okay. Now step back a little.
Ouch! Hot! Hot!
I-I-I'm on fire!
Put me out! Ouch!
Hold on, Belladonna! What are you doing?!
This is the only way to keep
them from growing back.
But isn't that a little excessive?
She passed out again!
Still, she was covered in injuries
before she was covered in mushrooms.
Really?
They seem like marks
from a tremendous battle.
We'll need to treat her wounds, too.
I hate to ask, Margaret,
but could you go wash her off in the river?
O-Okay! Sure!
It sounds like she's not from
this village after all, Sweetpea.
Yeah...
Huh? Look here!
What's wrong?
There's still a mushroom
between her legs that we missed!
There's one left!
But doesn't this one seem
different from the others?
It's oddly shaped!
Huh? There's something
weird underneath it, too!
What is this? A Sack Mushroom?
Anyway, I guess we better pull it off!
Alright!
It won't come off! How come?!
It's stretching!
Hey, what's going on? What happened?
She says it stretches...
What does?!
A mushroom!
Seriously? Is it a Neat Mushroom?
That's enough gawking, all of you!
This isn't a freak show!
You're watching too, you know!
Look! There seems to be a problem!
Still, she's not very well-endowed.
She even seems sort of rugged.
It's no use.
Maybe Aphelandra can pull it off!
Huh? Me?
Yeah, yeah!
I bet it'll come off if you
pull as hard as you can!
Maybe we should all pull it together!
No.
If that mushroom won't come off...
...then we should simply
burn it off as Belladonna did!
Oh! Yes! That's a good idea!
Don't you agree, Margaret?
Yes!
What's this? What's this?
What's going on?
Oh, Granny Nyon!
There's a mushroom growing
on this girl that won't come off!
So we're deciding whether
we should pull it off all together
or burn it off.
Now, now. Wait. Just who is this?
This is it here.
Let's see here...
Where is this mushroom?
Oh, my!
Granny Nyon!
Are you all right?!
Y-Yes, th-there's nothing to worry about...
Th-This person...
...is a m-m-man!
Th-This is a m-man?!
I've never seen one before!
Here sits the maiden island of Amazon Lily,
"Kuja"
inhabited by the tribe of
female warriors known as the Kuja.
May you never dream of it or step foot on it,
should you still value your life.
The imprisoned Luffy
plans an escape so he can rejoin his friends.
Fearful that the Snake Princess, Hancock,
will find out that they brought
a man into their tribe,
they begin to pursue him.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Hurry Back to Your Friends!
The Maiden Island Adventure"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!