Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
What's the terrifying
difference between you and me?
The look in Arlong's eyes changed!
You inferior human!
What do you think you're doing?!
Nose.
What did you do to me, a fishman?!
Stop that!
You raised your price again?!
Jaw?
What are you doing to my sea charts?!
Webs!
Don't you think your
place charges a bit much?!
Species!!
A Shark Saw!
"Fishmen" and "sea charts" this,
"circumstances" that...
Raise it again and I'll stop buying it!
I don't know about any of that...
...but I'm gonna destroy everything!
What's the big deal?
It's just a paper or two.
Gum-Gum...
Not when you're buying it everyday!
Such a fool! He hurt
himself by biting on a rock!
There's no need for
you to save up money
...Battle-Axe!
Now his teeth're brok...
That room is...
to buy your village back
from Arlong now, you know.
Or to be so obsessive about money.
He crushed the stone
pillar with his teeth!!
You're so dumb!
You can no longer escape.
Now that everything's over,
I'm going to earn money for me now!
Ahh! That's scary!
This is the top floor of Arlong Park.
Nami!
I don't wanna be some poor
pirate who can't even dress up!
You're my friend!
What's this room?
Full of papers...
Usopp Hammer!
Whoa, calm down!
These're not just ordinary papers.
"Explosion! Fishman Arlong's
Fierce Assault From the Sea!"
Usopp Rubberband of Doom!
I'm in the middle of developing
my special Tabasco Star!
This room is where I make that
woman draw sea charts. It's...
...the survey room!
An eyeful of this
will make any bad guy--
Nami's room...
Yeah!
These're all sea charts that Nami drew.
Did you see...
"Setting Out with a Smile!
Farewell, Hometown Cocoyashi Village"
--C'mon! Just one!
--Water! Water! Water!
...the inherent power of a fishman?
She's good. She draws
quite accurate sea charts.
No!
Heaven created you humans as
creatures that bow before fishmen.
This is Nami-san's tangerine orchard!
In the past, as well as in the future,
I won't let anyone lay a finger on it!
her talent should be
used for us fishmen!
Nami-san! Your love
security is infallible!
You humans are inferior creatures.
Special Attack!
We were on a different level
from the moment we were born.
Fire Star!
Arlong Park has fallen!
Yeah. Thanks, Sanji-kun.
Nami is our friend.
We're free!
Ol' Sanji's letting himself be used...
Usopp Hammer!!
Friend?
So don't interfere anymore...
C'mon! Just one tangerine!
--We're free!
--Free!
...you damn rubber man!
Everyone! Celebrate! Dance!
Arlong Park has fallen!
I win!
You're such a cheapskate, Sanji!
I'll show you... the real
difference between you and me...
What's that look in your eyes?!
No!
It serves you right!
We've lived these
past eight years for this!
Yeah, why don't you?
Well, oh, well! I'm happy now, anyways!
She is...
No way I'll lose
against someone like you.
We've lived so we can smile today!
Nami is...
I am the man who'll be
King of the Pirates!
The world sure is a turbulent place.
Another coup in Villa...
...our navigator!
I can kill humans like you
We're gonna party 'til we drop,
even into tomorrow and the day after!
without even directly touching
you if I have some water.
A flyer?
"End of the Fishmen Empire!
Nami's My Friend!"
That's the difference
between fishmen and humans.
Lady!
Chabo...
I just saw Arlong Park for myself!
It's awesome! It's in pieces!
You plan to make her the
navigator of some shabby boat?
King of the Pirates?
Don't make me laugh.
"Bounty! Straw Hat Luffy
Becomes Known to the World"
Arlong!!
Pretty awesome, huh?
You'd only end up wasting her talent.
Can you inferior humans do something
Yeah! The guy who did
that must be really cool!
Big Sis Nami!
Nami-san!
Who was it?! The guy who
beat Arlong is here, right?!
like crush a pillar with your teeth?
Just look! How many people in this
world can draw such accurate charts?
Hey, Nami!
I was about to crush
some pirates just now.
Yeah. Right over there.
It's true that humans can't crush
that thick pillar using their teeth.
Which one?! Which one?!
The guy with the straw hat.
"Navy"
What did you come here for?
The girl has a gift.
If that jaw gets you,
To kill you...
it won't just give you bite marks...
"Luffy At Full Power! Nami's
Determination and the Straw Hat"
There's nothing as
unfortunate and foolish
It'll bite clear through your bones!
as letting a natural-born
talent go to waste.
Are you sure he saved the island?
Staying here and drawing sea charts
is the greatest happiness for her!
So, at the very least, they're now
too much for our branches to handle?
Unbelievable as it may seem.
To kill... me?
So what?!
Stop...
This pen is stained with blood...
Meat! Is there any more meat?!
Yes. Even before
forming his pirate group,
...bragging over stuff like that!!
Nami's charts are absolutely vital
if I'm to attain world supremacy!
You never learn, do you?
he defeated Navy Branch
Captain Axe-Hand Morgan,
How many times did you try to kill me
He's still at it.
It's not like biting is the
only way to break stone.
and he's showed no signs
of slowing down since.
during the eight years
you were with us?
Sounds like ol' Zoro's really hurtin'.
She's going to continue drawing
sea charts! For my ambition!
Well, yeah.
You tried assassination,
poison, sneak attacks...
Buggy the Clown, 15 million.
A normal person with those wounds
would take two years to fully heal!
Pirate Fleet Commodore,
Don Krieg. 17 million.
All right, Big Bro Luffy!
You sure told him!
Were you able to actually kill me?
And once her charts give me full
knowledge of all the world's seas...
That's right!
The outcome is the same!
You fool!
Fishman Pirate,
Saw-Tooth Arlong. 20 million.
You must be completely aware
that you mere humans can't kill me.
we fishmen will be invincible,
and the world will become our empire!
Trying to take care of such
a big injury on your own...!
Th-That's besides the point!
Oww!
These major pirates have all crossed
the big 10 million Berry mark
Honestly! Are you folks really pirates?!
A stupid and weak species...
That's what humans are.
Now, listen. I won't kill you...
Don't you even have... a ship doctor?!
Our first stepping stone is this
island... and the East Blue!
in the East Blue, where the average
bounty is 3 million Berries...
What can you do when you can't
even pull yourself out of the water?!
...and you can't escape from me...
A doctor? That sounds good, too!
...but they've all been taken down.
--Luffy?
--But a musician comes first. Right, Zoro?
30 million Berries as a starting
bounty is globally unprecedented,
Nami...
Could you use the girl
as efficiently as that?!
Why's that?!
You'll be our surveyor forever.
Nothing! That's why I need help!
Pirates sing, you know?
but it is not an
excessively high amount.
So why does that come first?!
It may be best to nip such
seeds of villainy early on,
But, as you know,
I'm a good-natured man.
Hey, Doctor. Where's Nami?
before they have a
chance to get out of hand.
If possible, I want you to be our
surveyor of your own free will.
She doesn't seem to be here...
Hm? He can also use swords?
Nami, huh?
Absolutely.
If you can't find her around,
then she's probably "there."
--Take that... and that... and that!
--What're you doing?
So, how about this?
It looks like you're just
swinging swords around.
Huh?! The Shark Saw
won't move one bit!
I'll be killing everyone here except you.
But if you happily come
back to the Arlong Pirates
What?! You're still here, Nami?
If you're just playing around,
I'm not going to join your little game.
and draw sea charts
as one of the leaders,
Everyone who wants
to run away, do so now!
Your friends've been
looking for you, you know.
What?!
This bastion of peace will not tolerate
any weakness in this pirate age!
I don't mind letting those people
from Cocoyashi Village live.
"Use"?!
Say, Nojiko, Gen-san.
What's goin' on inside?!
The public's weakness and feebleness
is not a sin! We have justice!
Enough of this nonsense...
Dammit...
What happened, Big Bro Luffy?!
If Bellemere-san were alive,
But I can't let these guys live.
Clench your teeth!!
do you think she would
stop me from being a pirate?
If there is tenacious evil on the seas,
They went too far.
I can't tell what's
going on up there at all...
then we, the Navy, must drive
it away with utmost force!
A pirate?!
The question is who you'll be with.
Give me a break!
Of course she'd never let her
precious daughter be a pirate!
You either take my side now and
get saved along with the villagers,
Luffy...
In the name of absolute justice!
--She wouldn't stop you!
--Nojiko!
What do you take her for?!
"Justice"
or be on these weaklings' side and
try fighting against me with everyone.
Even if she did...
Yes, sir!
...would you really listen to her?
An inferior creature, but a smart girl.
But with these guys
you depend on in this shape,
Absolutely not!
If all other humans are sewer rats,
I'd say she's a cheeky-as-hell cat.
Miss!
it's obvious that
it'll be a tragedy for you.
Wha?! He shattered
Arlong's teeth!!
I see...
After all, she is adorable.
Miss Kaya!
What's with you, Gen-san?
And I'm going to keep on feeding
her and buying clothes she likes.
Nami...
Are you my friend?
Miss!
You two are definitely
Bellemere's kids, all right.
I don't know how to use
swords, you bastard!!
What's wrong, Merry?!
Or... their friend?
She'll have everything
she needs to live.
Have a look at this!
Gen-san?
Huh? What's he saying that now for?
Nami. You've already
made up your mind, right?
All she needs to do
is keep drawing charts for me.
Usopp-san!
Not fair...
Then live how you want!
If I say I'm friends
with Luffy and the others,
Just as your mother did!
That's definitely Usopp-san
facing the other way!
I don't know how to sail the oceans.
She will forever be my tool...
everyone will get killed.
I'm sure that's what
Bellemere wants, too.
And if I say I'm Arlong's friend,
Now that you
mention it, you're right...
I can't cook...
...no, my friend.
then everyone from
the village will be saved.
I can't lie, either...
With my words,
everyone will be...
Hey...
I'm confident that
I can't live without help!
That's despicable!
No matter what she chooses,
he's not going to give Nami freedom!
Heya! You're looking
a lot better, Kaya!
What's that?!
Fully admitting how pathetic you are...
What sort of story
shall I tell you today?
But!!
A desk...
It's a desk!
Usopp-san is moving toward his dreams!
You sure are honest.
Whew, I'm stuffed!
Luffy...
Sometimes it's nice to only eat!
I bet your crew is bothered by having
W-Whew, just a desk.
Are your wounds all better now, Zoro?
such an incompetent captain like you.
Man, that scared me. I thought
it was Big Bro Luffy for sure...
This's nothin'! Some food
and drink'll fix it right up!
Help me...
I'm moving toward my dream of being
a doctor to help everyone, too!
Yeah?
I wonder why your crew tried
so desperately to save you...
Hold on, partner!
Of course I will!
But how long is this
dumb party gonna last?
Are you sayin' you don't have
faith in Big Bro Luffy's strength?!
This is the third day now!
Huh?! You were scared too, Johnny!
I'm sure that someday, somewhere,
I must not doubt his words!
Someone like you without any pride
has the caliber to be a captain?
What's wrong with that?
When you wanna celebrate,
you should go all out.
my dream and Usopp-san's
dream will come together!
D-Don't be stupid!
I was, uhh, you know...
What on earth can you do?
O-Of course I thought
it was that damn Arlong!
Hey, Sanji! That melon you just had!
Everyone, I'm sorry!
Huh?! That sounds
kinda fake if you ask me!
Please die with me!
Was there something on it?!
I can defeat you!
What's with the meat in your hands?!
Say what, you jerk?! Of course
there's no way Big Bro Luffy'd lose!
Sure was. It's "raw ham melon,"
so there was raw ham on it.
All right!
"Chore Boy"
We'll go for it!
Raw ham melon?! That sounds yum!
W-Where did you get it?!
Luffy?
Of course, you damn idiot!
We'll fight!!
What do you think you're doing?!
Dunno...
If he dies, I'm gonna kill him!
Finally... Finally... Finally!
The whole village is a buffet party,
so I dunno where I got it...
I see...
What in the...?!
There's an awful lot of stuff flying!
Everyone wants to be killed...
I've got your back!
Luffy-san! You've finally
set foot into your dream!
He's long gone.
All right, Gum-Gum!!
He's been eating non-stop
for three days straight!
Get him, Big Bro Luffy!
I'm Luffy! The man who's
gonna be King of the Pirates!
Now, then. I'm done eating.
Go for it by a hair!
Now I think I'll...
Go ahead and babble,
you inferior species!
P... Please! Please!
...pick up some girls!
See ya!
Live! Live! Live! Live! Live!
Alright! As of today, this is your room!
Ugh! He's got new teeth!
But the next time we meet,
we may be enemies!
I'm a shark. New teeth
grow one after another.
Your desk, your pens...
Everything you'll need is here!
--I am Captain Usopp...
--Way to go, kiddo!
And they're stronger
than the previous ones.
--...hero of love and courage...
--Can I have your autograph?!
...who finished off the
strongest fishman boss!
Hm?
Stop that!
What the...?
As many times as needed...
Here's an Usopp Support Song!
The charts!
Finally...
Who was it? Who was it?
Who beat the fishman?
All we have to do now
is remove his leg weight...
Whoa!
M-My charts!
As many times...
Oh...
--Hmph. How boring.
--What is?
You damn brat!
I thought you'd be
more down in the dumps.
So that's what you meant...
Don't think you can trick me,
Could it be?!
Like, "Why didn't this happen
before my dad died?!"
drawin' fake charts like that!
Big Bro Luffy!!
Captain!
What?!
This is a distinctive
quality that heaven gave us.
Hey, hang in there!
Do you have the time to be
drawing crap like this in secret?
Come back to life!
That's how I felt at first.
Amazing!!
But now I'm thinking about the future.
Are you starting to realize what a
superior species the fishmen are?
The future?
Try to fool me again and I'll drag
people from the village one by one
We've been saved by that
straw hat guy and his friends.
and make you watch as I crush them!
But starting tomorrow, we have
to start from scratch on our own.
30 seconds!
Just like I did with her!
Tooth Attack!
I won't last longer than that.
There's no way we can forget
what's happened in the past,
Huh?
Zoro!
and I don't think we need to.
Damn you! I spent eight
years making her draw those!
That'll be enough!
But, I think what's most important
is what happens from now on!
Stop!
I invested eight years in
those charts! In my ambition!
There isn't a fountain over there.
What we do now.
What things we need to do.
Could it be that rubber man?!
We're the ones who're gonna
support the villages now,
Bellemere-san...
Big Bro Luffy!!
so I decided to think that way instead!
Nojiko...
Don't worry about it.
I'm the one who's gonna
be King of the Pirates!
It's nothing, you damn half-fish!
--Cheeky kid!
--Oww!
We both have foolish dreams.
Why're you pinching me?!
I don't understand! Why?!
I thought I told you not
to say those words ever again...
This... is a pretty intense fight!
And here I was hoping to harass
you some more for good measure!
I'm doing it so I can
achieve my own goal.
A-Arlong-san...
Yeah! Looks like a fight to the death!
You've harassed me plenty,
you dumb tattoo punk girl!
...dying Zoro!
Definitely!
That hurt...
Wha! B-Brother!
If I kick and break that leg weight,
Phew...
"Punk" will do just fine!
he can fight.
You damn rubber man!
Luffy, you're the only one
who can fight now!
Thank you...
Will it come off?
How dare you use
my brother as a shield!
I'd like to say, "No problem,"
but there's no way to remove it fully.
What're you saying?
You're the one who attacked me.
Say... do you know the All Blue?
In the sea, one with Devil Fruit
powers is supposed to lose
There'll be some scarring.
That's how tattoos are.
Phew... Was I scared...
Thank you for all the damn things
you've done for me all these years!
even the energy to struggle,
as well as his powers, and die.
Yeah. I know it's stupid of me.
They stay on for life.
If he's still alive,
Don't move...
I don't want anyone to see this!
that means someone is
putting a damper on this game.
...you damn rubber man!
This... this tattoo...
Oh, yeah! I've got an interesting idea.
Are you all right?!
Glad you're okay!
I'm not even really Arlong's friend...
An interesting idea?
Yeah! Oh?
What on earth will he...?
What?! What's the matter?!
...but it's like I've
been branded a pirate!
Did he come up with a
secret scheme or something?
Pops, what did you do with your
pinwheel? That was a cool one.
Tooth Attack!
Who cares about that right now?!
Nami...
We're wanted criminals now!
Putting a damper?
"Dead or alive"...
"30 million Berries"...?!
Nojiko! What is that?!
It didn't seem like
a fair game from the start.
Oh? You mean this?
It's no big deal! It's just a decoration!
It says I'm 30 million Berries!
You've gone too far,
you damn rubber man!
At any rate,
Now me and you are the same!
if there's a hindrance,
I need to check on it.
Look! I'm gonna be seen around
the world! Girls might fall for me!
"Fishmen are great"
and "sea charts" this,
Out of my way.
What?! They put Long-nose
in but left me out?!
"circumstances" that...
Egg Star!
Say, Doctor.
I don't know much
about any of that stuff...
Where are you?!
I don't see you anywhere!
There's a tattoo I'd like to have...
I've got your back, Zoro!
But I finally figured
out how to save her!
See!
Here.
Big Bro Usopp! Is he all right?!
There we go!
It's just the back of your head.
That's nothing to brag about.
Those two can dance!
How brave! What a gallant arrival!
Here's Usopp Support Song 185!
Don't be so glum!
You...
You can get on these without being
captain if you get more important!
Fight to the full extent!
She can't go because this room is here!
That's where you are?!
There's no point in crushing
my teeth repeatedly...
Seriously?!
Just keep on tryin' hard!
If she doesn't want to be here,
then I'll just destroy it all!
Usopp!
Bellemere.
Listen, Nami!
You still don't get it?!
Your daughters have grown up
to be truly strong and respectable!
I beat one of the leaders!
Let's rush into the Grand Line, men!
One of the leaders!
Gum-Gum...
B-Big Bro Luffy...
You surely don't mean
your interesting idea is...
The guy with a face like this.
It's almost as if I'm
seeing you in life again!
Yet again, you guys don't understand
the seriousness of the situation!
Don't get cocky!
Look! I've got fangs, too!
Arlong Park can't ever be brought
down by you inferior beings!
What?! You're going to be a marine?!
Fishmen are a piece of cake!
This means our lives are in danger now!
There's no use trying
to stop me! I'm going!
Shark Tooth Drill!
You defeated... Choo?!
This is no time to be taking it easy
and relaxing in the East Blue...
My mind's set!
S... So there wasn't any secret scheme?
...Battle-Axe!
Serves you right!
We're going to live life
to its fullest from now on.
With my arrival, the fight
comes to a climax at once!
I thought as much...
30 million Berries...
It heads into the final chapter!
We've lost and sacrificed far too much.
At that amount, I bet
Headquarters will take action,
and strong bounty hunters
won't leave us alone...
Which is why we're going to smile
as insanely much as possible now.
How long are you going to...
...keep fooling around?!
They're gonna be on a completely
different level than everyone so far!
Hey, can't you somehow escape on your own?
Let's go! Let's go! Grand Line!
I got bitten by a shark!!
Oh, that's impossible.
Raw ham melon!
I don't have any strength at all.
That's because
you're playing around!!
Huh? There's no food around here.
That's no good. Time to go back.
Come out! Come out! Come out!
It's not like I'm playing around.
Hold it, boy!
Tooth Attack!
A grave? Did someone die?
Big Bro Cook!
I don't know what's
going on in the water,
Yeah. A long time ago.
but his action must be the key!
Oh, my deepest conveniences.
Big Bro Zoro!
Stand strong and stop Arlong!
Huh? Deepest concussions.
Huh? Deepest compli--
Okay!
Deepest condolences.
We have to somehow prevent
Arlong from going into the sea, huh?
L-Look! That shock's
caused Arlong Park to...!
That.
Hey, boy.
I'll stop him from moving.
Impossible! It's gonna collapse!
Nami is going to ride your ship.
She's going to be a pirate.
This is dangerous!
Everyone, get away!
He got bit!!
It'll be a dangerous journey.
--Big Sis Nami! Hurry!
--But Luffy's still inside!
I won't let you have your way!
That's fine. There's no way around that.
--Big Sis!
--Luffy! Luffy's still...!
Hey, Arlong! Look this way!
But, if you guys ever do anything
to take away Nami's smile...
How do you like your own teeth?!
Wha?! Big Bro Usopp!!
...I will come kill you!
Even if it's my teeth that you used,
How brave!
Damn... Cheap booze
makes me feel sick...
Luffy!
Yeah. I'm not gonna
take it away, though.
Usopp!
it's your weak jaw after all.
Got it?!
How I long for the old days
--Rubberband of Doom!
--Standing in my way...
Listen up.
when I was surrounded by
beautiful women and fine wine...
I got it!
Looks like you want
to die first, Roronoa Zoro.
Shark teeth become useful
when they come with a strong jaw
Now! Go Zoro!!
Usopp Support Song 368!
that can bite off the meat!
What do you actually wanna do?!
Who is he? Who is he?
Ahh!! Big Bro's arm's
gonna get bitten off!!
My one encounter with that
horrible waiter changed my fate...
He's the coolest guy in the world!
His name is Great Captain Usopp!
No way I'll die.
I'll break your proud nose!
Luffy!!
I finally figured out how to save her!
Tarnishing the Navy's name lost
me my rank of Navy HQ Lieutenant
She can't go because this room is here!
You fool...
If she doesn't want to be here...
It's a proud nose
because it's unbreakable.
and put me in charge of this hunk
of junk in the middle of nowhere...
...then I'll just destroy it all!
If you were at your full strength,
Former Lieutenant Fullbody!
you might've been
able to give it a scratch.
Whadya want?! You're annoying!
Luffy!
I-I have a new wanted poster!
Oh. Just leave it there.
I doubt it means anything to us,
seeing as we're all the way out--
This face... I've seen it
somewhere before...
Luffy...
I've never seen that pirate flag before.
Big Bro...
Look over there!
Hm?
I'm Iron Fist Fullbody,
Lieutenant at Navy Headquarters!
Ahh! That damn octopus is up!
Who's your captain?! State your name!
And... what's he doing?
Luffy...
I'm Luffy!
I'm Usopp!
Dammit! I thought the rubber
band was going to fly at me!
We just made our pirate flag
the day before yesterday!
--What?!
"I'm leaving this behind.
This belongs to all the villagers. --Nami."
Yes! It's him!
Thank you!
God has given me a chance to climb
out of this hellish pit of boredom!
See?! He was my target!
Oww!
You were yelling "Arlong," weren't you?
Wow! Today's a big feast!
I can catch that brat easily!
What's all this damn noise?
Octopus...
And I'll use that feat to get my
rank of Navy HQ Lieutenant back!
Do you two know what today is?
Is his arm okay?
Roronoa Zoro! I won't
let you have your way!
Today is the day I first met you two!
If he backed off even a step,
it would've been bitten off!
Fall in!
Luffy...
I'll crush your friend
who went into the sea!
In his case, it's not that he thought
about how animal's fangs work, though.
It's the day you two
became my daughters!
Wow!
C'mon, stop crying!
You don't have to be concerned
since you'll all be dead, after all.
Men! We're going into battle!
A storm destroyed
the orchard. So what?
Battle? Where are we gonna do that?
Arlong Park... has collapsed!
You need to be strong girls who
can smile even during hard times!
Is Big Bro's arm okay?
W-Well... The sea restaurant, I suppose?
Big Bro...
Do that, and then nice
things will come to you!
What on earth happened inside?
--Oh! A restaurant!
--Awesome! A big feast!
Big Bro!!
It'll come, I promise!
--It's the captain's treat!
--Oh, really?!
Which one won?!
Nami! Could you get me the salt?
Given all this debris...
Don't tell me it was--!
--No, you got it all wrong!
--Hurray! Hurray!
First you learned how to draw
sea charts, and now land maps!
Luffy...
I'm studying navigation too now!
Oh...?
Where'd he go?
Navigation, too?!
That was...
It is Nami's dream!
--Luffy! The sea!
--The sea?
Hard to port! Our target's
right in front of us!
I'm gonna use my navigation skills
to travel to all the world's oceans!
There's a shark!
And then I'm gonna make a
world map of everything I see!
That's Arlong!
Do you think some pirates
attacked it? That warship is scrapped...
Luffy!
Big Bro!
So your map of this island is your
first step toward your dream, then?
It's not nice of the Navy to toss
its scrapped ships into the ocean...
Huh? Did he dive in?
Yeah!
This isn't good!
His ability doubles in the water.
This is not a scrapped ship!
Do you guys got knotholes for eyes?!
Have you forgotten what
Iron Fist Fullbody looks like?!
Is he okay?!
Oh! You're that navy
guy from sometime!
No one can stop me once my
speed accelerates in the water.
Are you stranded? Want us to help you?
This is precisely an ability
that is given only to fishmen.
Quit fooling around! Our meeting
here spells the end of your luck!
Nami!
Nami-san's big sister!
Leave the rest to me!
Monkey D. Luffy! You're under arrest!
Did he run away?
Yeah! That's a good
picture of me, huh?!
A fishman!
And of the back of my head!
You're my friend!
Move away, Big Sister.
I'll break a rock
like that with my kick!
It says, "Dead or alive"...
It's all over, Bellemere-san.
Aim the turret!
Shark... Darts!!
It took eight years,
but we're finally free!
--That octopus!
--Octopus-Fritter Frenzy!!
What's all the noise? What's going on?
Me, and all the others...
Big Sister!
It's exactly like you said.
Yeah!
Oh? You're gonna shoot?
"If you live through it,
nice things will come."
They're aiming right at us! This is bad!
What was that?!
You were right!
Alright! Leave it to me!
I'll bounce it back again!
A torpedo?!
All the villagers are smiling so happily
from the bottom of their hearts!
Zoro!!
Luffy. Let me handle this one.
H-He won?!
Something flew out from the sea!
--Yeah, yeah! You stay back here!
--H-How come?
He won...
And me! I'm thinking
of leaving this island!
So that was it?
Ow... Ow, ow, ow, ow...
'Cause you mess things up.
C'mon! Over here!
He won!
That was too quick.
He won!!
It's all right! Don't worry!
Tremble and sleep!
What's up with these bandages?
Arlong Park has fallen!
They're really pleasant people,
and pretty strong, too!
Wow, I'm impressed you dodged it.
Did you fall somewhere?
--We did it, older sister!
--Gen-san!
For eight years, I drew
lots of charts and maps...
This... This isn't a dream, is it?
Awesome!
That's impossible!
But the more you dodge it,
the longer your hell continues.
...but this is the only one that's left.
I never thought this day would come...
What's this scar?
Huh? What's all this damn noise?
But that's exactly it! This time,
I'm going to draw charts for me!
Shark... Darts!!
Don't bother people
when they're napping.
I'm going to travel the world
with them-- my friends!
There's plenty more
where that came from! Fire!
That was my dream, so... so...
Way to go, Luffy!
You get my praise, too!
--Huh? This is bad.
--It is?!
How can he still be alive
with a body like this?
Though I'd be praising you even more
if you would've been the
star performer instead of me!
...I'm not sure when I'll
come back to this island...
How can he still be standing?!
Wha...! What kind of bones
does that damn shark have?!
Man, talk about being
on pins and needles...
His nose crushed the ground...!
See? There were cracks in the cannon.
Take care of things quicker
from now on, you damn jerk!
Shark... Darts!!
Yeah, that's definitely bad.
I'm... going now.
You damn brats!
What kind of eyes are they?
Don't you dare mock the power
of a former Navy HQ Lieutenant!
Are they the eyes
of someone who's dying?
We'll just have to
fight you hand-to-hand!
Men! Follow me!
He's a man I need to kill for sure,
Your head is mine!
right here right now!
Gum-Gum...
Hey, Luffy, hide!
Arlong went into the sea again!
...Bell!
Big Bro! Please hurry up and hide!
If a person stays put,
He'll target you again!
their wounds won't be opened...
--This the last of it?
--Yeah!
--Alright!
This is awesome!
That's right.
Get out of there!!
--Are you finished loading it all?
--Yeah!
You got some real balls, pickin'
a fight during mealtime, tough guy.
You find your situation amusing?
Now, then. We got lots of
provisions now. We're good to go.
N... No...
Don't got any soup bowls today.
I'm not talking about me...
Don't be stupid! Are you knowingly
going to become a target?! Hide!
We were only here a few days,
but this island's full of memories, huh?
You plannin' to lick
the deck or somethin'?
I'm talking about the Octo-Man.
I don't want to!
I'll catch him and break his nose!
W-What's that waiter doing here?!
Yeah!
--What?!
--I thought I told you...
Hold it right there, you!
We win this game.
Come on! Shark!
He's...!
What a lucky day today is!
We owe you a lot for
everything you've done.
Well done. I watched the entire fight.
Huh? He's done already?
You've got some nerve.
We're gonna get back to our
profession of bounty-hunting again!
Or have you realized that
it's useless to run away?
He was nothing but talk!
Fluke as it was, I never once
imagined the fishmen would lose
He's as damn wimpy as ever.
This is goodbye for now,
but we look forward to the day
we meet again somewhere!
Didn't you hear us saying
you should hide, Luffy?!
C'mon, you guys! Keep it down!
to a bunch of nameless pirates like you.
Take care!
You barely dodged his attacks
and they all grazed you!
Honestly! I can't even relax
and read a newspaper here!
You guys, too!
However, thanks to you,
all the money I was to give Arlong
Dammit!
Nami-san! I'm finished
preparing your meal!
Well, we should get going, too!
If you take a direct hit,
you'll die instantly!!
That scared me a bit!
and all the money and valuables
stored in Arlong Park are now mine!
Hey! Hold on! What about Nami-san?!
Ooh! I'm starving!
Let's eat! Food! Food!
Gum-Gum... Shield!!
Maybe she's not coming?
Everyone drop your weapons!
I, Colonel Nezumi of Navy Branch 16,
You're the one who made this whole
thing complicated in the first place!
W-Why not?!
hereby take credit for
what you've done here!
You! You made another pass
at Nami-san again, didn't you?!
What's that position?
All right!
Surely he isn't going to
stop the attack like that?
Why would I do that?
Go and beat up that shark bastard,
Zoro!
--No, you definitely did!
--Oh, yeah. She achieved her goal,
Don't ruin people's fun
when they're finally happy!
This is double the acceleration
distance from earlier.
--You can't stand that me and
Nami-san are all lovey-dovey!
--and she has no reason to be a pirate,
you damn idiot!
What's that?
I'll pierce your heart!
--Are you an idiot?
--What'd you call me?!
--so she might be happier here.
Lemme see.
Shark Darts!!
Is it coming, kid?
It's coming!!
What about my happiness?!
If Nami-san isn't on the boat,
J-Just you try laying a
finger on me! You'll be sorry!
then 98.72% of my reason
for being on the boat is gone!
Hawk-Eye! Why the hell are you here?!
He's still sayin' it?
He got hit!!
Hey, you! I couldn't find
the raw ham melon anywhere!
Calm down. I have no business with you.
Wahhhhh! I'm back!!
Hey! Where's Nacchan?
This is for shooting Nojiko
Where is your leader?
That's the thing! Nobody's
seen her since this morning!
and tearing up Bellemere-san's
tangerine orchard.
What?! She's leaving
all the money behind?!
Camping on an island like this...
What a carefree man.
Rubber boy!
Big Bro Luffy!!
The 100 million Berries?!
Huh?
She left it in our house,
along with a letter.
What?! Did he get hit?!
B-B-Boss!
Colonel!
She's planning to journey
without her money?!
No! He flung himself off!
But she's the one who
risked her life to earn it!
Luffy!
She says it's okay, because
she'll just steal some more.
Thanks, Nami! That felt good!
You lose.
That attack won't work any more.
Give 'im 1,000 more of those!
That damn rubber man...!
Shark Darts!!
Once that girl says something,
there's no changing her mind.
You're late, idiot!
That fool! We're the ones who
still haven't thanked her enough!
H-H-Hawk-Eye!
Zoro!!
You guys are gonna clean
up after those fishmen now!
Huh? Hey! Stop it!
You bastard!
That was by instinct, wasn't it?!
You aren't gonna...
And you're gonna help
rebuild the town of Gosa!
Hey there, Hawk-Eye.
What a rare visitor...
This is the final blow!
And you're not gonna touch any
money or valuables in Arlong Park!
Nami-san!
You won't hit me!
--Nami!
Gum-Gum... Finger Net!!
I'm not feelin' so good at the moment...
Have you come to fight me?
Let's switch places!
--Nami-san!
--Nacchan!
That's the island's money! Got it?!
Get the ship moving!
Oww! Oww! I-I'll do what you say!
You idiot!
I don't have any intention
of settling things with you
Fishing! Fishing!
Gum-Gum... Bell!!
now that you've lost your left arm.
And one other thing!
Give me my money back!
Huh? She's started sprinting!
I found an interesting pirate,
I'll give it back! I'll give it back!
I don't care anymore...
And, Whip!!
She says to get the ship moving.
And...!
and was suddenly reminded
of a story you used to tell.
But...!
Don't tell me she's planning to leave
Spear!!
without letting us
thank her or say goodbye?!
A story about an interesting boy
from a certain small village...
I'll get you, you rotten pirates!
Gum-Gum... Pistol!!
--You can't be serious!
--Set the sails!
Straw hat man!
Your name's Luffy, right?!
You don't mean...!
You're the captain, right?!
Don't forget this!
Some major stuff's gonna happen
to you now! You've made me mad!
Whoa!!
--H-Hey!
--They're setting sail!
Gatling!!
It's too late to regret
what you've done!
So you've made it, Luffy!
Wait! We still haven't thanked you!
I'm gonna get revenge on you!
Just you wait and see!
Hm...? Did he die?
In that case, Hawk-Eye...
--Stop, Nacchan!
--At least let us thank you!
Says some major stuff's
gonna happen now.
How does he know I'm
gonna be King of the Pirates?
All right!
Hold it! I won't allow
you to leave like this!
...I can't just let you leave now.
The look in Arlong's eyes changed!
That's not what he means!
Man, you're stupid!
They look the same as the eyes
that Sea Kings show when they snap.
Hey. Is it okay to let her leave like this?
H-Hey, what do we do?! What if we
really do wind up in big trouble?!
Why not? It's her decision.
Hey! Hey! Hey, I said!
He must've snapped
with Luffy's last attack!
That so, Hawk-Eye?!
Alright, everyone! This is no time
for us to be the only ecstatic ones!
Okay! Drink up! Drink up!
Today's a celebration!
I've never seen
Arlong's eyes like that...
We need to tell everyone on the
island about this big incident!
I thought you had a hangover?
Don't sweat it!
It's a celebratory drink!
Did you do something?
You inferior human!
C'mon, now! C'mon, now!
It's not working!!
Arlong Park...
Just drink it straight down!
Arlong Park has fallen!
What did you do...
Yep. That was my warm-up.
...to me, a fishman?!
I like ya!
Let's drink! Let's drink!
Nami!
Yeah!
But, wait! Boss! You said you felt
sick 'cause you drank too much!
That idiot!
I'm gonna kill him!
You idiot! I can't not drink
on a joyous day like today!
Why?!
The sun is still high.
Nami!
Don't sweat it!
Boy, was I stunned!
Let's party hard!
What a bunch of scum,
It doesn't hurt, but I can
see he's really mad.
nobly hanging on...
Good for you, Nami!
You'd have been happier if you
died at the bottom of the sea...
To think we'd end up
being saved by pirates...
Hey! Luffy's a wanted man now!
Good for him!
Hm? Not really.
You never know what's
gonna happen next.
I'm happy that they saved me.
Who knows, maybe a great pirate
will've come from this village!
That'd be great!
What the heck is that?
You seem to be in excellent
spirits, pathetic humans!
Quiet, you fools!
Shark Saw!!
Can you understand my anger?
It's a giant saw!!
Mayor!
As of this moment,
What's so good about a criminal
coming from our village?!
It's the anger of seeing my
dear brothers crushed by worms.
this village-- no, this island--
is now under my control!
She didn't!
--Huh? My wallet's gone!
--Mine, too!
A toast!
--Same here!
You'll realize soon enough that
you should've died without fighting.
Honestly! Every last one of them...!
Gen-san! Help!
Take care, everyone!
Keep your hands off the children!
Is Big Bro Luffy gonna be okay?
Look, Mayor! Luffy looks so happy!
--How dare you?!
--You damn brat!
All his fierce attacks
weren't effective at all...
A pirate's a pirate!
More importantly,
how far did Big Bro Zoro fly?!
Hey. She hasn't changed a bit.
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
Who knows when she'll betray us again?
--Big Bro Luffy!!
--Hang in there, Luffy!
Go Luffy! I've got your back!
But it is his dream. Are you worried?
Nami-san! Good!
You don't have to worry about his back.
--Run!! Watch out!!
--The attack won't stop...
He's getting cornered...!
T-That's an Arlong tattoo!
--You lousy sneak thief!
--Get back here!
You...!
Dreams... Fate...
--Give back our wallets!
--You punk!
--Come back anytime!
--Take care of yourself!
You can stop now...
If he loses, you guys will all die, too.
You fought very well, carrying our
lives on your back all this time...
We're grateful to you guys!
He escaped into the building!
Boy!
Yeah, we will...
We're finally nearing the Grand Line...
If that happens, it's the
end of the East Blue, too.
Gen-san...
Don't forget our promise!
It looks like the only way into it
is through Reverse Mountain here.
The left window on the top floor...
Bye, everyone! I'll be back!
What a pain.
Can't we just sail straight into it?
That room is...
What's the terrifying difference
between you and me?
Nope.
That was close...
From what the geezer told me,
that's the only way boats can enter.
She got us good!
You can no longer escape.
My own little sister got me!
Nose.
How come?
--And then it went boom!
--We didn't know each other long!
'Cause it's supposedly dangerous.
This is the top floor of Arlong Park.
Have fun!
Jaw?
But how come?!
I don't know any more than that!
I wonder if Big Bro's joking...
Looks like your final
moment is finally here.
The reason for that is...
Here, Genzo.
No, he's definitely serious.
Alright! I got it!
Then let's head straight into it!
What's this scrap of paper, Doctor?
Now, Bellemere's spirit
can finally go to heaven...
Webs!
What's this room?
That fool. She never learns.
She got another tattoo before she left.
Are you even paying attention?!
Full of papers...
Species!!
These're not just ordinary papers.
But it sounds fun!
This is a room where I make that
woman continue to draw sea charts.
Plus it'd feel way better
going straight into it!
What mark is this?
It's a tangerine and a
pinwheel, apparently.
The survey room!!
Talking to you makes me
feel like I'm gonna go crazy...
Huh? Gen-san!
What happened to your pinwheel?
Hello?! Hello?!
Nami's room...
Anyways, let's stop at
an island first and get meat!
Yes. This is Navy Headquarters.
These're all sea charts that Nami drew.
Headquarters?! Navy Headquarters?!
Such a fool! He hurt
himself by biting on a rock!
Hello! This is Colonel Nezumi
of Navy Branch 16!
Meat! Meat!
I doubt there's any need for it now.
Now his teeth're brok...
Aren't they great?
There's a famous city on
this island... Loguetown.
Marine Code 00733!
They're my treasure, one that I
made her draw for eight years.
I have a request for HQ!
To us, getting data about
the oceans is very simple,
Loguetown?
You don't need to shout.
I can hear you.
What? Is it famous for its meat?
He crushed the stone
pillar with his teeth!!
Listen! There's a pirate named Luffy,
but it's a different story when we
have to create sea charts based on it.
Also known as the city
of the beginning and the end...
Ahh! That's scary!
who wears a straw hat!
I'll be back!
Listen! There's a pirate named Luffy,
We need a talented surveyor.
I'm pretty sure I've heard that before.
What a man!
who wears a straw hat!
If he gets you with that,
I deem him and his four crew members
That's why I had my eye on that woman.
It's the town where Gold Roger,
the old King of the Pirates,
he won't just give you bite marks,
he'll bite clear through your bones!
as enemies of the government!
Hold on, Gen-san!
Stay away from Nami!
was born... and executed.
She's good. She draws
quite accurate sea charts.
I deem him and his four crew members
No, but, I want to see her smile, too!
as enemies of the government!
You see? This is the
inherent power of a fishman.
"Luffy"...
The town where the
King of the Pirates died...
She's too good for
you inferior humans.
She starts crying because
you have such a scary face!
They managed to take down Arlong,
the fishman of Arlong Park who
was purported to be invincible!
In the past as well as in the future,
But what am I supposed
to do about that?
Wanna go?
Heaven discriminated
against you humans
her talent should be
used for us fishmen!
Yeah! I wanna see it!
Based on their threat
and dangerousness,
I know!
and made you powerless
creatures that bow before fishmen.
I wanna see the town where
the man who got the One Piece--
This'll make you laugh, right?!
If I always keep it here like this?!
a large bounty has been placed
on their captain, Straw Hat Luffy!
everything this world has to offer--
Hm?
What do you say, Nami-chan?
Nami is our friend.
Now sending a photograph!
was born and then died!
Look. I really don't think a dumb
pinwheel is going to make Nami...
Roger that.
You humans are inferior creatures.
Friend?
We were on a different level
from the moment we were born.
So don't interfere any more...
Huh?!
Couldn't you have taken
a better one than that?!
...you damn rubber man!
No, that's all I could get...
I'll show you...
After a quick verification,
I will submit it for approval.
Oh. She laughed.
What's that look in your eyes?!
...the real difference
between you and me...
She is...
Don't forget, now!
He's a vile pirate! "Dead or Alive"!
Nami is...
Yeah, why don't you?
Hm?
Put him on wanted posters
throughout the world!
No way I'll lose against a fish.
...our navigator!!
I am...
...the man who'll be
King of the Pirates!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
It's finally goodbye
to Cocoyashi Village!
--Oh, no!
--What's the matter?!
Oh? Where did Arlong go?
Amazing! What a fierce battle this is!
Hey! What's that
red-nosed thing called again?
Luffy! The sea!
The newspaper's gone up in price!
Nami! Bet you're happy to be onboard
with Great Captain Usopp again!
I finally figured out how to save her!
A reindeer?
The sea? Whoa! There's a shark!
--What kind of problem is that?!
--Then don't buy it!
--No, that guy with the big nose!
--Oh, him.
Show us your determination,
you damn rubber man!
You idiot! Nami-san is joining
me on a journey of love!
That's Arlong!
What're you saying? We hafta
know what's going on in the world!
His name was Boogey or Baggy
the Brown or something like that!
Oh, he ran away?
I'll completely destroy the room
that she wants to be free of!
This isn't good! His ability
doubles in the water!
No! Raw ham melon!
No! Buggy the Clown! Buggy!
Plus we can use the backs
of the flyers as notepads!
Bellemere-san. It took eight years,
but we're finally free!
Go! Get Arlong!
Ahh! Watch out!
--Oh! Good thinking!
--See, like so!
Yeah! That!
Wahhh!
I wonder what
happened to him after that...
Luffy... Thank you...
Huh?! This is...!
Luffy!!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Chase Straw Hat!
Little Buggy's Big Adventure"
"Setting Out with a Smile!
Farewell, Hometown Cocoyashi Village"
"Explosion! Fishman Arlong's
Fierce Assault From the Sea!"
"End of the Fishmen Empire!
Nami's My Friend!"
"Bounty! Straw Hat Luffy
Becomes Known to the World"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!