Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After being ejected from the Sabaody
Archipelago by Bartholomew Kuma,
Luffy was ejected from
the Sabaody Archipelago
After being ejected from the Sabaody
Archipelago by Bartholomew Kuma,
Luffy was ejected from
the Sabaody Archipelago
by Bartholomew Kuma, a Warlord of the Sea.
Luffy was separated from
his friends and arrived alone
Separated from his friends,
Luffy was separated from his
friends and arrived alone
Separated from his friends,
he arrived alone at the female-only
empire of Amazon Lily!
he arrived alone at the
female-only empire of Amazon Lily!
at the female-only empire of Amazon Lily.
Captured by the Pirate Empress Hancock,
After his capture,
Big Sis!
Sentenced to death,
it appeared that Luffy had
successfully escaped, but...
Big Sis! What happened?!
Luffy battled in mortal combat
with her younger sisters,
Luffy was forced to fight
Snake Princess Hancock's sisters
Don't let him escape!
Sandersonia and Marigold who had
eaten the Snake-Snake Fruit.
What in the world happened?!
There she is! That's her!
The Snake Princess is about to bathe!
Oh, I, uhh...
in a combat arena.
How rude!
Luffy fled the village with Margaret,
a Kuja warrior, in tow, but...
He saw my back.
Mari! Get him now!
I can't wait to see Marigold-sama's
"Salamander" with my own eyes!
After seeing the secret hidden on the
back of Pirate Empress Boa Hancock,
I can't, Sister Sonia.
Is this a bath?
If we keep this up,
I'll only grow attached to you!
Luffy was caught by the Kuja Pirates
and taken to a fighting arena.
We are now... being protected...
And Sandersonia-sama's
"Eight-Headed Serpent"!
Whoa, now! Stop!
...by that man!
Love-Love Beam!
You said that you'd rather die
than show it to someone.
There!
A man!
You're not cracked, are you?
Hey...
I am Vice-Admiral Momonga
of Navy Headquarters!
That thing on your back...
Hey...!
Hey, you! What did you do to them?!
Wait here, you guys!
Warlord of the Sea and
Pirate Empress Boa Hancock!
They saved my life, you know!
It seems familiar somehow...
Sorry you got turned
into stone because of me!
This is the warrior nation of Amazon Lily.
Show yourself! I've come for you!
The strong are beautiful.
You saw it, didn't you?!
"Hancock's Confession
The Sister's Abhorrent Past"
Alright, then...
I like the title of Warlord.
So I just gotta kick your asses now, right?!
Fight your hardest and perish.
I don't want it taken away.
"Heartless Judgment!
Margaret is Turned to Stone!!"
We will watch and see you off.
But I hate the World Government.
What a joke!
I don't want to obey its orders.
What did he just say?!
Big Sis!
Big Sis! What happened?!
He intends to beat the younger sisters!
Love-Love Beam!
Hilarious! Making people laugh
after being sentenced to death!
Who is that? A man?!
If you do not reappear in two days' time...
Men really are hilarious!
What is a man doing in this land?!
Kill him, Sandersonia! Marigold!
...the agreement is off!
Through combat, give him
the ultimate punishment
You guys are screwed up.
Do as you wish.
for the great crime of sneaking onto
our maiden island and offending me!
That woman...
"The Secret Hidden on the Backs--
Luffy and the Snake Princess Meet"
What in the world happened?!
She turned your comrades into stone,
Is it okay, now?
Oh, I, uhh...
so how can you all sit
there and laugh like that?!
He saw my back.
Sister Sonia!
What the...?!
Th-The savage is yelling at us!
Unbelievable! What a vicious creature!
Then he'll have to die.
Poison?! That was close!
Open the gate!
Huh?! H-How come?! I only saw her back!
I feel bad about those three,
We're sorry, Big Sis!
Gum-Gum
but the Snake Princess was
right to do what she did!
The Snake Princess has returned!
We're sorry that we lost and
had to be saved by our enemy.
Stamp!
I dunno why,
They're the ones to blame! They
broke the rules of our land!
but I could swear I've seen it
somewhere before...
It bounced off!
Are you up next?
We would rather die
Whatever I do,
Welcome back!
than let anyone see
what you saw on my back!
I will be forgiven.
Welcome back, Kuja Pirates!
That hurts!
The reason for that is,
That thing? How come?
How...?! I'm made of rubber!
Who are you? How come?
yes...
Snake Princess!
Gum-Gum...
...because I'm beautiful!
Take everything you saw to the grave!
That's enough.
--...Gatling!
--Snake Dance.
You piss me off!
Love-Love Beam!
I don't feel like it.
Ran-sama!
Slow-Slow?!
What's going on?!
Daisy-sama!
Oh, yeah?
She's guessing my every move!
A Slow-Slow Beam?!
We had a big haul!
I hope that she's not damaged.
Snake Stick!
They're so cool!
Ouch!
I'm gonna join the pirates someday too!
Alright then,
these people you turned to stone;
turn them back.
These guys have powers?
Oh no!
I'm turning slower! Slow...er...
Hey! What're you doing?! Don't touch them!
What did you say?
You can do something, right?
"A Difficult Fight for Luffy!
The Snake Sisters' Haki Power!!"
What if she breaks?!
They were just trying to defend me!
She saved my life, you know!
It's the Gorgon Sisters!
We are going to break her.
They didn't do anything wrong!
Stop it!
Hey, please?!
Execution! Execution!
Snake Princess! Snake Princess!
I said stop!
Love-Love Beam!
Execution! Execution!...
Yes, indeed,
I can revert them if I want.
Ran-sama!
Daisy-sama!
But...
Rindo-sama!
You said that you want
to go someplace by ship.
Blue Fan-sama!
Cosmos-sama!
Yes, my crew's waiting for me.
Marigold-sama!
Oh, that's nice.
Sandersonia-sama!
But I can only make
one of your wishes come true.
Why won't he petrify?!
They're always like this.
Does he not feel any excitement
from seeing me in the bath?!
It's either revert them
It was a long trip.
They must've really missed our big sister.
or help you to get off this island.
The warriors are fainting!
That's not possible, Big Sis!
That was the Conqueror's Spirit just now...!
Choose one wish and give up on the other!
The beauty of your naked body would
charm anyone of any age or gender!
The younger sisters'
Snake Pit Dance is about to start!
This can't be real!
Only one out of a million
people can master that Haki!
She looked at me!
No, she looked at me!
His fear of death must be
overpowering his wicked thoughts!
Snake Princess. You are so...
Only a chosen few can use it!
I've never seen any person who
can use it other than our big sister!
He's a pathetic, yet lucky man!
You can't fool me.
I can't wait to see Marigold-sama's
"Salamander" with my own eyes!
I dunno what's going on,
but I'm getting outta here!
Welcome back. Your Monkey Carriage is ready.
Reveal your true nature, Man.
"Youngest Sister, Marigold Snake-Snake
Fruit, Model King Cobra"
This boy has the "qualities of a conqueror"
to stand above others!
I just wanna talk to someone important!
Has anything happened?
That's great! Thank you!
And Sandersonia-sama's
"Eight-Headed Serpent"!
No. Nothing at all...
He jumped out from this height!
That means you're going to help them, right?
He has the Conqueror's Spirit, just as I do?!
"Middle Sister, Sandersonia
Snake-Snake Fruit, Model Anaconda"
He won't get away!
How can this be?!
Pistol Kiss!
Is he no mere boy after all?!
Thank you... very much!!
Carry it slowly and carefully!
Alright!
Iron ore, gunpowder, alcohol,
and crops from the north...
You showed me you're strong!
Huh?! They don't bounce off!
What a tremendous haul!
They're not metal bullets?!
Now let's get on with the duel!
We plundered two merchant
ships and one pirate ship.
He doesn't hesitate at all.
How magnificent she looks!
That man is an intruder!
How is it that a man who has such great Haki
She was a strong warrior
to beat the Gorgon monster,
The center sea people just offshore
also gave us their cargo.
Seize him, Kuja Pirates!
bows his head in order
to save his benefactors...
"All-Out Special Power Battle!!
Gum-Gum vs. Snake-Snake"
and this is proof of it!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
The cursed younger sisters are lovely too!
The Kuja Pirates truly are elite!
A man?! What's a man doing here?!
Maybe, he is...
I suppose so!
Let's just catch him for now!
Big Sis...
Where's the Snake Princess's present?
Don't worry. It's been sent to the castle.
Ran. Any books at all?
That hurt!
Down here.
It's in your best interest to do as we say!
Cursed? What're they talking about?
Granny Nyon!
Ran! No man would ever try
to defy the Kuja Pirates!
Let me think.
Oh, those center sea people
did give us a newspaper.
They look like they've
eaten Devil Fruits to me.
Besides, he looks weak anyway!
Here you are!
He's finished for sure now!
It's a man!
What are you hesitating for?!
A live man in the village...!
What?!
I can't wait anymore! Hurry and start!
Men are undeserving of fear!
Are you the all-women pirate group?
Execution! Execution!
Sonia-sama! Mari-sama!
Welcome back!
Do you know where your boss is?
Anyway, that man...
Execution!...
Beat that man up!
Why do you want to know that?!
I can't believe he defeated the sisters.
Perhaps I should swallow him whole...
Yes.
Your boss owns a ship, right?
Or squeeze him to death...
Welcome back, Snake Princess.
There's nothing to fear, Mari...
Yes, but...
So I wanna find her
Thank you for holding down the fort.
Yes.
Don't tell me he's scared stiff!
I don't think Snake Princess will forgive him
and ask for a ride on her ship
and hurry onto the sea!
If he can't control his enormous Haki,
then it's nothing but zeal!
I've prepared the finest, most exquisite
jewel from your spoils of war.
Just stand there and die!
after he was so rude to her
What nonsense!
Men are forbidden in Amazon Lily!
nor will she forgive the people
who let him in to this country.
Hold on! Time out!
But first...
Do you honestly think
you'll get to leave alive?!
What? Going to beg for your life?
If we're gonna go all out, we
better move her outta the way.
Stupid man!
Apologizing now won't
make your crimes go away!
I wouldn't want to break her.
Margaret!
This is no time for me to get caught!
No, it's not that.
Sweetpea!
Aphelandra!
Oh, you sound quite confident.
Even the jewel pales in
comparison to her smile!
What's going on?
Oh, here you all are!
Gum-Gum...
It seems you still don't
understand the position you're in.
Great! She turned you back from stone!
Seize him!
...Rocket!
Look!
Who cares about that lousy statue?!
Snake Princess!
I was so worried because you
suddenly started to vouch for him.
A decoration of that quality
would only spoil my beauty.
What the...?!
Margaret!
After him! Quickly!
She's right.
The Snake Princess's orders!
I was afraid of what would happen to you.
Don't let him escape, no matter what!
Enishida. What is this?
Turned us back?
Why do you insist on protecting the statue,
Oh, it's a clay model that
children from the village
A man!
even at the expense of being hit yourself?!
What happened to us?
worked hard to make for you!
I have absolutely no recollection.
There's a male intruder!
She has nothing to do with it...
A male?!
They must have worked hard to paint it, too.
Don't you remember?
The Kuja Pirates are chasing him!
She has nothing to do with this fight!
No I don't...
The next thing I knew, that man
was there and he was really happy.
Let's help out, too!
Alright! Let's go!
Oh, I'm so relieved!
Very well. Let him move the statue.
Oh!
I was worried that you were going to die.
Big Sis!
Let the man fight to his heart's content.
Of all things, allowing a man onto the
island when the Kuja are in peril...
No one's here...
We made this for the
Snake Princess to look at!
Is it all finished now?
And then beat him completely senseless
Thank you!
This is unprecedented.
The way they carefully carried it to
the castle to prevent it from breaking
I can't help but worry what
the future holds for this land.
and teach him just how insignificant men are!
Snake Princess!
was truly tender and innocent!
There!
You're not cracked, are you?
Um...
Oh, I see.
Right!
Keep dedicating yourself to
your duty to protect our country.
Catch the man!
So they made me...
Wait here, you guys!
...out of mud and clay...
The Kuja Pirates!
Sorry you got turned
into stone because of me!
So he did return to the village...
If Chopper were here,
he could've examined you right away,
There he is!
Over there!
Snake Princess!
...And that was it.
but maybe you'll go back to normal again
Don't bring such filthy
things into the castle!
Great!
I would've thought she'd
be in a tall building...
Wait here just a little longer.
When you're turned to stone,
like when Aokiji turned
me and Robin into ice!
it's hard to remember what
happened before and after.
Throw it away at once and clean the floor.
Where do I go to meet someone important?
I'll figure something out once I beat 'em up.
Are you sure you shouldn't be
more concerned about yourself?
I'll tell you what happened.
Anyway, Enishida...
Margaret.
Y-Yes?
What happened to the man?
Shut up! I can do whatever I want!
I didn't see any of our defense warriors
there to greet us on our arrival...
Those pirates caught up to me already?!
What about Snake Princess?
That man...
Okay! All set!
Did she turn him to stone this time?
Let's kill him before the
Snake Princess catches him!
Is he trying to save Margaret and the others?
Oh, you're already ready?
That can't be!
I don't know that much,
Oh, well, actually...
He's already been sentenced to death!
Ready for us to beat you to a pulp?
but it seems like he got
summoned to the Kuja Castle.
Oh, it's them again?!
A rather violent monkey
appeared in the jungle, and...
What?!
I already told you.
Alright, then...
So I just gotta kick your asses now, right?!
It was such a savage and crude beast
You're the ones who're gonna get beat up.
He fell off!
Hey, I want to know!
What do you want from me?
that they all had to go after it...
You're still as insolent as ever!
Oh!
Is there a meal after the battle?
There he is! The man!
A monkey?
Crap!
If that's what it is, I'll be happy!
Halt!
Ouch! Damn!
What kind of food is popular here?
I bet it's some kind of meat!
Yahoo!
I should be thanking you.
That attack doesn't scare me
if you can't hit me with it!
Thank you.
There he is!
No, please!
Take this!
"Thank you" isn't something I can eat!
What a joke!
Gum-Gum...
If anybody had seen what's on our backs,
there is no way that we
could stay in this country.
What is this smoke...?!
What did he just say?!
Did you get him?!
You may come in.
He intends to beat the younger sisters!
L-Look!
My poison dissolves whatever it touches.
Wait, you!
Come inside, Man.
Hilarious! Making people laugh
after being sentenced to death!
But that's not all...
Inside?
Men really are hilarious!
Inside of the curtain.
Marigold-sama's poison attack!
Oh, is that where the food is?
The man fell for it so easily!
It can't be!
Men certainly are stubborn...
Why would this rookie worth
300 million be in Amazon Lily?!
I'm coming...
Heh. This is nothing at all.
Oh, we're not eating.
Is that okay, beating you up?
Hey, what are you doing
with your clothes off?
H-Huh?
There he is!
Yes, that's fine!
Well, I gotta run!
What the...?!
Don't think you can get away from us.
As always, you are reacting rudely.
I feel kinda woozy!
If you haven't given up on your life yet,
then I'll warn you in advance:
Wait! Let me see your face again!
I won't take you lightly anymore.
Don't worry. They'll be back shortly.
But that's okay.
I wouldn't fall into the pit between
the seats and the ring if I were you!
I said wait!
I'm truly sorry they
weren't there to greet you.
You're my prey.
I'll weaken you with poison, corner you,
Well, no matter.
Would you like something to drink?
You can fall if you'd like,
and then kill you for sure!
but the bottom is filled with blades, so...
Even the old ladies here are strong?
Are you ready to go now?
White sake.
I think I'll have some, too.
There's no escape now!
Yeah! All set!
Granny Nyon.
Good.
This is the mark...
Just one whiff of my poison
will dull one's consciousness!
This is my room. Why are you here?
...that you said...
Then let's begin!
G-Granny Nyon!
Oh no! The Kuja Pirates caught him!
How did you get in?!
Kill him, Sandersonia! Marigold!
...you had seen somewhere.
I guess there's nothing we can do now!
I can get in any way I want.
Through combat,
give him the ultimate punishment
Throw her out.
Take a good look at it, again.
Wait, Snake Princess!
for the great crime of sneaking onto
our maiden island and offending me!
Where did you see this?
This man really is...
That hurts, dammit!
Do you know the meaning of this mark?
I've been waiting for this!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Gum-Gum Pistol!!
What's the matter?
You forgot "please"...
You can't even scratch us!
Answer me, now!
"Please."
Damn! Come off, you stupid things!
It's not something I want to show people.
You seem to be at a real loss...
Pardon me. Please wait, Snake Princess.
What are these iron rope-like snakes?!
No matter how tough you may be,
The center sea people's ship
is anchored off shore.
We were too slow.
if you can't control your power,
you're no different from a puny rat!
Let's just hope they don't
ask how he arrived here...
As I suspected, it's a bit different
from what I've seen before.
They've come here to get you, have they not?
He's going to be killed, isn't he?
Just give it up!
I guess he has some skill...
I have a friend called Hachi
who is a fish-man...
They've ordered you into
active duty, have they not?
What's with this place?
Get him, Marigold-sama!
There really isn't even one guy here.
A fish-man?
Yeah.
That's right. An invitation to war.
And he has a similar mark on his forehead
Why aren't you going?! You must go!
so I thought it was the same.
I don't know anything about your mark.
What the...?!
If you go, the agreement will be upheld!
Snake Princess!
If he doesn't know, why don't you tell him?
Marigold-sama!
Poison?! That was close!
Certainly someone with your abilities
Sandersonia-sama!
Granny Nyon!
Yes! He fell into the pit of blades!
Where did you come in from?
won't meet an untimely fate!
Wrong! It's powerful poison!
Be honest, Snake Princess.
You have seen clearly
how tolerant that man is.
But...
Let me ask you this, man.
...I'm scared!
How and why did you come to this island?!
I can see right!
She's almost like a puppy!
I'm healed! The poison's gone!
Don't be afraid.
Wait, this is no time for that!
Seriously, I don't know, either!
Tell him everything that you want to share.
Granny Nyon...
I suddenly went flying through the sky
His hand! It's the man's hand!
and before I realized it, I was here!
This land is currently protected by
your title of Warlord of the Sea!
You!
Lies.
You are a pirate,
Monkey D. Luffy, am I right?
You can't fool me with that ridiculous story.
Yes, I am.
Up until recently, this island was
protected from outside enemies
Gum-Gum...
You must be after something.
How do you know about me?
...Stamp!
Well, you could give me a ship!
Look at that!
by the great defense network
that is the Calm Belt!
How can you be so casual
He just won't give up!
I'd appreciate getting a lift most of all,
after you caused such
a sensation in the world?
Mari-sama! Sonia-sama!
The man is still alive!
It bounced off!
but anyway, there's a place
I need to leave for right away!
Look at this newspaper!
Just days ago, this man...
However, now the center sea people
are using new ship-crafting techniques
But what do I do about that poison smoke?
If you're the most important person here,
...at Sabaody Archipelago
near the center sea,
then please! I want to set sail!
That hurts!
How...?! I'm made of rubber!
to come and go through
these waters as they please.
What nonsense is this?!
caused a horrific and grave incident
See! He really is all bark and no bite!
The Snake Princess is right!
when he dealt a blow to a Celestial Dragon!
The fact that you're a Warlord of the Sea
But it's true that men stretch! How neat!
He's obviously lying!
is the only reason they
won't set foot on this island
He must be plotting something!
You can't fool us!
to put a stop to the Kuja's pirate ways.
Huh?! Am I not rubber anymore?!
Dealt a blow to a Celestial Dragon?
The island is also home to the
very young and the very old.
Gum-Gum...
Oh, I've been thanking you non-stop!
No, that's not it!
Then why do impact blows hurt?!
Is there anything I can do for you?
...Balloon!
It is a miracle that he was able to get away
If you lose the title
That's not fair, Mari!
and we return to being
a regular pirate nation,
Go flying!
from the supreme powers
at the center sea after that.
As long as the others are
still alive like I am,
You're hogging him all to yourself!
only tragedy will await us!
I want to have some fun with him too!
that's all that matters.
And in only a couple days,
As long as they're alive,
Are you sure you're not just afraid?
he arrived here so far away.
I can keep fighting again and again!
My life could end at any time now.
How dare he speak so rudely and
tastelessly to the Snake Princess?!
It's all beyond our understanding.
Why does that hurt?! I'm made of rubber!
Look closely at this crystal ball!
W-Who are you?!
Come to think of it, that axe guy also...!
He's appalling!
I told you!
That's Granny Nyon's fortunetelling
ball that's right 200% of the time!
Gum-Gum...
I was blown away suddenly.
...Gatling!
I have no idea where this place is!
Hoisa!
Alright! That's much better!
Let us shed light on your future...
Oh, and another thing -
Wh-What the...?!
I don't feel sorry for that Celestial Dragon.
Ashigara Dokkoi Shove!
All the poison and smoke is gone now!
That bastard!
It's exactly the same!
Don't think you can leave this place alive.
Guess what he did to my friend?
Now I can fight with an easy mind!
But he didn't have powers!
Your death is inescapable!
T-Then...
Does that mean it's not a Devil Fruit power?
it is true that you punched
a Celestial Dragon.
I see your future!
"Go!"
The man used his breath to
send the poison flying away!
I take it you have powers, too.
Please wait, Snake Princess!
A Paramythia type, from the looks of it?
Unbelievable!
T-There are still...
I knew it!
...foolish people like that...
Why are you lying and saying you're cursed?!
Men are so mysterious!
Aren't they, though?!
That's a secret we can't tell anyone,
Detestable!
not even an opponent about to die.
Throw her out!
This instant!
...in this world?!
Damn!
I-I don't think he's the
kind of person who can lie!
Y-Yes! Right away!
You can fight with an easy mind, you say?
But I take it you can't use Haki?
Wait! Snake Princess!
Most outsiders can't.
Margaret!
Stop! What are you doing?!
After being beaten so horribly,
you still spout such insolence?!
I watched quietly,
only for you to put on a pathetic act.
That's why you're weak.
The ones who put their lives at risk
to challenge those celestials...
What are you trying to pull here?
Left kick...
Alright...
Your era is long over...
...like him!
Over here!
...Gloriosa, ex-empress of Amazon
Lily from three generations ago!
She read what I was going to do!
Who are you talking about?
Snake Slam!
Now it's my turn to go full-power too.
Even if this land should be
destroyed by one of my whims,
Yes!
everyone will forgive me.
Second Gear!
That one didn't hurt.
The reason for that is,
Same as usual.
What is that?!
yes...
Gum-Gum...
Smoke's coming from his body!
...because I'm beautiful!
...Gatling!
Snake Dance.
Is that how men are?!
There it is!
The Snake Princess's
"excessively looking down on others" pose!
What amazing moves!
What kind of creatures are they?!
Long ago, despite your status of empress,
With Sonia-sama's Haki,
there's no attack she can't dodge!
I will tell you everything
you deserted this land
and left for outside waters!
Smoke! He's giving off smoke!
You Kuja traitor!
Full power?
including the meaning of the symbol
You're very straightforward.
Meaning you weren't at
full power this entire time?
that your fish-man friend
has on his forehead.
That's why I live quietly on
the edge of the village now!
I can read you like a book.
So what if there's smoke
coming from your body?!
Snake Princess...
What's going on?!
Hachi's mark?
She's guessing my every move!
Then you should continue
to live there quietly.
Have you forgotten that we
can read your every move
Focusing entirely on offense
is nice and all, but...
I will not have you interfering with me,
the current empress!
This is...
Snake Princess.
Snake Stick!
and that your attacks have no effect on us?
E-Everything this man says is sincere.
"The Claw of the Celestial Dragon."
Ouch!
Snake Princess!
Don't forget that there are two of us!
Hey! Let go!
He hardly seems like the type
to bring harm to our land!
I'm gonna try anyway.
It's an emblem of the Celestial Dragons!
That said, I can't help but admire your zeal.
Oh! You!
Gum-Gum Jet...
Yeah! Tell her for me!
Not good!
You win.
A defense warrior?
It's no use!
My name is Margaret!
You agree to what I said, Snake Princess?
...Pistol!
People who were fed by
the World Nobles all get...
Men are forbidden here.
It really does pay to talk things through!
His death sentence was set in stone
Thank you!
the moment he stepped foot on this land.
...this permanent brand to
show that you are subhuman!
You'll go, then?!
Big Sis Sonia!
Why do you protect him?
I feel I owe him.
Celestial Dragons?
It looks like you weren't bluffing
about going full-power...
I lied. Don't get cocky!
The person who let him into this country...
The three of us were...
Get out of my sight!
He's falling into the pit!
...once...
In that case, I'll bite you to death
with all the power I have too!
Something seemed unnatural
about that just now...
...was I!
Curse you, Snake Princess!
Margaret! Why?!
That man...!
Medusa Hair...
...slaves of World Nobles!
...Eight-Headed Serpent!
S-Snake Princess...
What have you done?! She's an old woman!
Snake Princess! W-We can explain!
I don't know what came over me...
Yes! Yes! That sort of thing
happens to all of us!
Yes!
We found him in the forest
covered in mushrooms!
Clean up the broken window too!
Yes, ma'am!
We thought he was from the village
and carried him here!
Sweetpea! Aphelandra!
You were... slaves?!
Annoying woman!
We're also responsible for
the crime of bringing him here!
Go!
Sandersonia-sama!
That's right!
Stop, you two!
I'm the one who suggested
bringing him to the village!
Does she know what this means?
The fence around the arena!
It happened when I was 12...
Margaret is way too honest!
The giant serpents are actually her hair,
yet it's like they have fangs of iron!
Th-That was close!
Oh, you guys!
So close!
Starboard, all clear.
You guys tried to kill me,
but you're actually nice after all!
Port, all clear, too.
He should've just kept falling!
Bow, all clear.
Why can't I hit him?!
However tenacious he is,
High visibility, all serene!
I'm reading his every move ahead of time,
he still doesn't stand a chance
against the younger sisters!
Granny Nyon!
but I can't keep up!
Don't fall into the sea!
Aged as I may be, I am still a Kuja warrior.
They're at the very top of the Kuja Pirates!
Don't make fun of me!
I have not grown decrepit!
I've become a warrior!
Okay, okay.
We trust you!
My hands are dirty.
Only I'm guilty of letting
him into the country!
Is the bathwater ready?
That's our Big Sis!
Margaret!
We'll support you!
Yes, ma'am! I will issue
the advisory at once!
The Snake Princess put
her hair behind her ear!
I bet you're hungry! I brought a snack!
Her loveliness knows no bounds!
The Snake Princess is about to bathe!
Hancock?
This man is the very definition
of "nothing but talk."
Sonia! Mari! Where are you?
Three of us were taken
from the Kuja pirate ship...
I can't help but laugh.
Okay! Stay still now!
...and we were sold!
Oh! Sorry!
Shut up, you dumbass!
From that point,
all we have are terrible memories
that we don't even want to remember.
Leave the castle premises immediately!
Oh, my!
Big Sis Sonia!
He spoke abusively to
the Snake Princess again!
Come on! Let's hurry!
Unforgivable! Hurry and kill him!
I-I just started eating!
Gum-Gum...
Hurry outside!
Sonia! Mari!
It's all right.
It's no use!
Everyone who's on duty today, to your posts!
Your attacks bounce right off,
as I showed you before!
End that man's life at once!
Look up, honest Margaret.
To ensure there are no further outbursts...
It's time for their bath!
We saw men for the first time
As long as I can surpass your speed,
I like honest people.
and they were nothing but figures of horror.
your brute strength attacks
cannot defeat my defense!
...from his filthy mouth!
Get ready!
The people in the castle are coming,
so it's about to get packed in here!
Tell me.
Do you wish for forgiveness?
Sister Sonia, calm down!
Y-Yes...
The memory haunts us.
I was hoping to have
a little more fun with you,
...Jet...
W-Wow! H-Hey! That's enough!
You may rise.
but you heard our big sister!
No need to force the memories!
You don't have to tell me!
...Bazooka!
It looks like playtime is over now.
"Bath"
It was awful.
Let's give the criminal despair and death!
There was no hope.
For the next several hours,
We kept thinking about death!
entrance into the castle
is strictly forbidden!
Hey! You...
But...
...one night four years later,
Margaret!
What are you doing?
something happened that made
the World Government tremble.
Is the Snake Princess going to forgive
those three for their great crimes?!
You're not allowed past here, you know.
Say...
"Nobody will challenge
the Celestial Dragons."
Why does everyone make such a big deal
Hey! What're you doing?! Don't touch them!
That's the Snake Princess for you!
She's not only beautiful,
she's so compassionate too!
when the Snake Princess takes a bath?
That was the cardinal rule in their world.
Sonia! Mari!
But there was a man who climbed
the Red Line with his bare hands
How old are you now?
Snake Princess!
What if she breaks?!
Eight.
She saved my life, you know!
Then I'll tell you.
What are you two playing around for?!
and slipped into the Celestial
Dragons' Holyland of Marejois.
Love-Love Beam!
The Gorgon Sisters' secret?!
We are going to break her.
B-Big Sis...!
That's right.
You said she saved your life.
Don't tell me you've forgotten
that man's transgressions!
Then that's all the more reason to.
What the...?!
I feel bad for her,
You're in charge of keeping watch.
He was an adventurer who
later led the Fish-Man Pirates,
but this is your punishment.
Yes, Big Sis.
Please take your time.
S-Sorry, Big Sis!
named Fisher Tiger.
Don't be stupid!
This duel is between me and you!
We'll finish him at once!
The fools...
In order to free all the slaves
Stop it!
Hey! What happened to you guys?!
from the town there his fellow
fish-men were being tortured,
What happened?!
Above.
he fought with all his might.
They turned to stone! How come?!
Gorgon was the name of a monster
that once lived in the center ocean.
Medusa Hair...
We are free! We are free!
Hey, you!
He disliked humans as a species
...Eight-Headed Serpent!
Anyone who looked at this terrifying
monster would instantly turn to stone.
Hey...
but he was being fair to all slaves,
and let thousands of slaves
of different species go free.
Hey...!
She's on fire!
Damn! Let go!
Medusa Hair...
At the end of an adventure,
the Snake Princess and her sisters
We prepared to die and ran among the others.
Hey, you! What did you do to them?!
...Salamander!
You're the only one who
thinks this is a duel.
managed to slay the Gorgon monster.
They saved my life, you know!
We won't give you anywhere to run!
This is a public execution!
He's surrounded!
Yes.
Just sit there and watch!
There's no escape now,
no matter how nimble he is!
They were punished
because they helped you.
The emotional trauma you gave our
sister goes much further than this!
There's no better attack than this!
It's my fault that they...
But when the monster uttered its death howls,
Everyone here looks up to the Snake Princess!
Wait! Turn them back to normal!
it placed a horrible curse
on the three warriors.
Just who do you think
you're giving orders to?
She's strong, noble, and the most
beautiful woman in the world!
Gum-Gum...
We owe him an immeasurable debt.
Turn them back now!
The monster's large eyes
were etched onto their backs,
The Pirate Empress, Boa Hancock!
and everyone nearby who's lured in
by their charm and looks at them
Tiger released many fish-men to the sea,
Bring out Bakula!
...Jet...
Bakula?!
It's all over for that man now!
...Gatling!
I told you to turn them back!
but ones who were slaves had
a mark that cannot be erased.
is turned to stone and killed.
Hey! Stop it!
This is the warrior nation of Amazon Lily.
She looked up to you guys, you know!
Tiger has made the World Government his enemy
The strong are beautiful.
Everyone in this land does.
and he formed the
Sun Pirates with former slaves
Fight your hardest and perish.
So I think this is what she would want!
We will watch and see you off.
The Gorgon Sisters never remove
their clothes in front of people.
and sailed out into the open sea.
The hell it is!
What are you, stupid?!
Oh, my. What crude language.
As though breaking a curse,
And when they bathe,
they always post guards
like this to keep people away.
he changed the Celestial Dragon's
emblem on everyone's bodies...
That black panther's name is Bakula.
After her, we'll break the other two as well.
Oh no!
Big Sis Sonia! Get away, quickly!
A carnivorous beast that
has served as executioner
for this land's empresses for generations.
Nice and slowly, too.
What?! I'm being dragged!
...into the symbol of the sun.
After each execution,
not even a single bone remains.
That'd make it more painful
for you too, right?
Our tails! When did he...?!
What you thought was similar
to the mark on my back is
It's hot! It's hot! Help!
Wait, Big Sis! Don't pull me!
the sun symbol of the Sun Pirates.
Bakula seems to be quite starved.
Yeah, you're right.
Here goes!
Three...
The one Hachi has on his
forehead looks like the sun.
Big Sis Sonia! Watch out!
Yes, Big Sis.
Hey! Stop!
That's the pit of blades!
Hold on to the stands!
I'm told it hasn't been fed
for several days now.
Does that mean he was a slave, too?
Two...
Stop it! Do you hear me?!
Be happy, man!
It doesn't necessarily mean that he was.
Bakula will gladly eat even
a scrawny monkey like you!
The mark is made in such a way
that it is impossible to tell...
It's no use.
One...
...whether they are former slaves or not.
Never mind that...!
Th-That was close...
Margaret!
I'm pretty sure that he once was
a member of the Sun Pirates.
S-Sandersonia-sama?!
What about these guys?!
Will they go back to normal?!
Oww...
How dare he speak so rudely
to the Snake Princess?!
How pathetic!
In fact, Fisher Tiger is already dead and...
Get 'im, Bakula!
I said stop!
...the Sun Pirates have split
up into several groups.
Ouch!
Sonia's back...!
Bakula!
If...!
That's the man's voice!
Go!
Hey, when did you get hurt there?
If the citizens should see it...!
Have the snakes found him?!
Ouch! Ouch!
Oh, this? Don't worry about it.
Ouch! Hot!
Let go, you!
That man!
He has a complicated past, too...
He's kicking her when she's down!
So this is the reason
that the mark on our backs
He's inhuman!
He's going to knock Sonia-sama
Ninto the pit and skewer her!
is similar to the fish-men's mark.
Damn you, man!
Okay, I pretty much understand.
Don't move!
Surprisingly, when we were slaves,
Even if you guys wanna kill me,
we were forced to eat Love-Love Fruit
I don't wanna kill you!
and Snake-Snake Fruit
for their entertainment,
Where did he run to?!
You insolent little...!
He went up the craggy mountain!
and that enabled us to deceive our nation
Mari! Use this chance to kill him!
Don't tell me he went back into the village?!
and preserve the secret.
What are you doing, Mari?!
He wanted a ship!
What?!
If you didn't cover up
Sonia's back at that moment,
I can't, Big Sis Sonia...!
Because...
it would have been impossible
for us to stay on this island.
he's protecting us right now...!
That hurt...
Look! Sandersonia-sama's
clothing burned off
I don't want to let anyone
know about our past!
and her back is showing!
If that man gets off her,
her Gorgon Eyes will be exposed!
Hmm, what do I do now?
Oh no!
He's strong!
Everyone who sees them
will be turned to stone!
He knocked out Bakula in one hit!
I'll get spotted again if I just sit here...
I won't stop at deceiving
our whole nation to hide it!
My back...!
She did mention this island
has a pirate ship...
You guys said so earlier!
He didn't use Haki!
Then that was just brute strength?!
You guys are screwed up.
He saw my back.
If I can just borrow it somehow...
We won't open ourselves up at any price!
That woman...
We don't want anybody to
take advantage of us again!
Then he'll have to die.
She turned your comrades into stone,
No, wait. Nami's not here.
Huh?! H-How come?! I only saw her back!
so how can you all sit
there and laugh like that?!
I'll end up drifting around
if I go all by myself.
The warriors are fainting!
I'm scared of being caught off guard.
We would rather die
Th-The savage man is yelling at us!
It terrifies me. I can't take it!
than let anyone see what you saw on my back!
Oh, I know!
Asking for a ride on the
ship is the best way!
Unbelievable! What a vicious creature!
You'd rather die than let
people see this, right?!
I'll ask if they'll take me to
Sabaody Archipelago!
I feel bad about those three,
Big Sis...
but the Snake Princess was
right to do what she did!
Which means...
They're the ones to blame!
They broke the rules of our land!
So don't move!
Ho!
But this is the first time in a long time
I'll have to talk to someone important,
that you've shown your emotions like that.
Whatever I do...
and since important people
live in tall buildings...
...I will be forgiven.
Recently, I've thought
that the Snake Princess
Could this be...?!
The combat is over!
The reason for that is,
I'm thinking so hard I might get a fever!
must have turned to ice or something.
Everyone leave the arena at once
yes...
Okay! I'll just go into
a tall building first!
...because I'm beautiful!
before you're exposed to the Gorgon Eyes!
Shut up!
Oh no! We gotta get outside!
You are a traitor who
left the country behind!
We'll be petrified!
Snake Princess!
You shut up!
What a relief!
Hurry! Hurry!
I'll try that one!
You three were miserable
She isn't hurt anywhere!
The Gorgon's curse!
and didn't know how to
return to this island...
Oh, I guess you guys are sensible after all!
Wouldn't you agree, too?
...after you ran away from
the Celestial Dragons!
Hurry to the village!
You piss me off!
The Snake Princess has
probably already returned!
Who brought you back?!
If she finds the man,
things will turn serious!
That was the Conqueror's Spirit just now...!
Big Sis! Stay strong!
This can't be!
You should be thankful that
I was living outside of this country!
This can't be real!
No man exists that won't be my slave!
Only one out of a million
people can master that Haki!
It's brittle!
What you are talking about was a small favor.
What was that?!
Only a chosen few can use it!
The castle tower's roof collapsed!
What did you say?!
I've never seen any person who
can use it other than our big sister!
Granny Nyon...
What's happening?!
I always keep an eye on
you three as a mother would!
The Snake Princess is taking a bath in there!
I cannot stand that man's existence!
This boy has the "qualities of a conqueror"
to stand above others!
How dare you say that to the Snake Princess?!
And you call it "small
favor", Snake Princess?
More water?!
Hurry and execute him!
Ouch, it's hot! Wait, this is bathwater!
Hey, get your hands off of me! Mari! Sonia!
Execution!
Execution! Execution!
I'm gonna die! I'm gonna drown!
I was fighting you just moments ago.
Are you going to...
Go! Marigold! Sandersonia!
He has the Conqueror's Spirit, just as I do?!
...look down on me; a former slave?
My feet are on the ground. I'm safe!
Why are you protecting me?
Take that man's head!
How can this be?!
Our fight and the thing you don't
want seen are two separate things.
Is he no mere boy after all?!
Huh?
Is this a bath?
Yes! Leave it to us, Big Sis!
You now owe your lives to
the man you tried to execute.
Just who is that guy?!
What's everyone blabbing about?
What are you talking about?
What's the big deal?
Maybe you can fool the country,
Like I told you - I hate
the Celestial Dragons!
He doesn't realize he used Haki?!
A man!
but you cannot fool yourself
forever, Snake Princess.
I guess he hasn't figured
out how to control it.
These guys have powers?
The thing etched onto the
backs of you three sisters is...
Hey...
Execution!
Alright!
I like you!
That thing on your back...
Execution!
You showed me you're strong!
Didn't you say that you had one more wish?
Execution!
All right!
Execution!...
It seems familiar somehow...
Where do you want to go?
I'll give you a ride!
For real?!
Now let's get on with the duel!
You saw it, didn't you?!
Luffy is captured by the women again
after seeing the Snake Princess's secret.
Sandersonia and Marigold transform
using the power of the
After Luffy saves the
sisters from a tight spot,
The Kuja Pirates hold a banquet.
Luffy activates Second Gear,
and the sisters respond by unleashing
their true Snake-Snake powers.
they reveal their secret to him.
When Luffy is mobbed by curious women,
Snake-Snake Fruit, in order to execute Luffy.
Margaret and two other
Kuja warriors defend him,
Hancock suppresses the fear
rising from deep within her
Margaret saves him and takes
him to Granny Nyon's house.
Sandersonia's hair turns into giant serpents
but the enraged Hancock turns them to stone.
Luffy does his best to
dodge and counter-attack.
But there, Luffy finds out that
his brother Ace is in trouble,
as she reveals the wounds in her heart.
Seeing his saviors petrified
infuriates Luffy,
while Marigold cloaks her body in flames,
It turns out a wicked shadow
lurks in her past...
and he's forced to make a big decision.
but a terrifying executioner
approaches from behind him...
and the sisters continue their attack.
However, it proves useless.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Saving Ace!
The Next Stop: the Great Prison!"
"Hancock's Confession
The Sister's Abhorrent Past"
"All-Out Special Power Battle!!
Gum-Gum vs. Snake-Snake"
"A Difficult Fight for Luffy!
The Snake Sisters' Haki Power!!"
"Heartless Judgment!
Margaret is Turned to Stone!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!