Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
After realizing the purity of his heart
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
and hearing about his fight
against the Celestial Dragons,
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
Hancock finally came to trust Luffy.
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
"Saving Ace! The Next Stop:
the Great Prison!"
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
Are you really gonna give me a ride?!
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
Don't worry. I wouldn't lie.
That's great! It doesn't have to be
a great boat as long as it sails.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
Departure will be tomorrow morning.
The crew, on its way to the New World,
The Kuja Pirates will give you a
ride to the Sabaody Archipelago.
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
--What?! By our pirate ship?
--Sorry to be a pain!
Rest well tonight to prepare for tomorrow.
Luffy was ejected from the Sabaody
Archipelago by Bartholomew Kuma, a Warlord of the Sea.
After hearing that his brother Ace was
captured by the navy and is waiting to be executed,
Luffy is heading to the
Great Prison - Impel Down
Leaving the female-only island of Amazon Lily
I can't wait to get off this island tomorrow!
to rescue his brother Ace, who's
been captured by the navy.
to rescue his brother Ace who
is waiting to be executed,
Luffy stowed away on a navy ship
with the Snake Princess's help
Separated from his friends,
I really wanna see everybody soon!
he arrived alone at the female-only
empire of Amazon Lily!
Luffy stowed away on a navy ship with
the Pirate Empress Boa Hancock's help
Meanwhile, his friends have
been sent to separate islands.
and headed to the Great Prison - Impel Down!
He gained the favor of
Pirate Empress Boa Hancock
and headed to the Great Prison - Impel Down!
"The Friends' Whereabouts! The Science
of Weather and the Mechanical Island!"
"The Friends' Whereabouts! An Island
of Giant Birds and a Pink Paradise!"
and was granted a ride to
the Sabaody Archipelago
Really. What a strange man.
Meanwhile, the rest of the Straw Hat crew,
in a Kuja pirate ship due
to leave the next day.
Sonia! Mari!
who had been ejected from the Sabaody
Archipelago by Bartholomew Kuma are...
If you were to take a trip,
where would you want to go?
Invite Luffy to tonight's banquet!
Granny Nyon!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
--A man to our banquet?!
--Big Sis, that's too...
What's wrong, Enishida? Why
are you in such a hurry?
Zoro!
--Didn't you understand what I said?
--Y-Yes...
Snake Princess...
Brook!
What banquet?
...has come down with an unknown illness.
"The Friends' Whereabouts! Bridging
the Islands and Vicious Vegetations!"
It's a banquet to celebrate the Kuja
Pirates' safe return with a big haul.
M-My shin! You kicked my shin!
Usopp!
Why couldn't you get it, you blockhead?!
Sanji!
You got any food at this banquet?
Franky!
I require at least 100
kilograms of food per meal.
Love-Love Beam!
Curse the Pirate Empress!
Nami!
I haven't been to one in
a while! Yes!! A banquet!
Anything less than that won't suffice.
Chopper!
Are we gonna survive this trip?!
Are you really not going to obey these
strict orders from the World Government?
Robin!
They'll never learn!
Are you gonna come, too?
Luffy, the food is here!
No, I'm a little tired.
Do you want to be turned to stone again?!
Luffy?
If they revoke your title
of Warlord of the Sea,
N-No! I'm very sorry! I'll be careful!
I'll go to bed early.
Luffy?
Hey, haven't we reached Ace yet?
Okay. You'll give me a ride and food.
you know what will happen to your country.
Bring her another meal to replace this one!
Yes, I'm afraid it'll take more time.
It was just a dream.
I can't hardly believe it!
You were screaming.
I see.
"Love is a Hurricane! Love-Love Hancock!"
Here, Luffy! Bon appétit!
Oh! Yum-yum!
I saw my friends.
Doesn't he mean he can hardly believe it?
Big Sis! Hang in there!
It's extremely delicious!
I see.
Big Sis!
Luffy.
When I'm fed by you, the food tastes
sweeter than it actually is!
What can I say to cheer him up?
Banquet! Banquet! Banquet!
Do you want some tea?
I heard Snake Princess is sick.
I didn't think that Snake Princess
would trust him this much.
Yeah, please.
Oh, I'm glad!
Yes, please.
Oh, Granny Nyon!
Oh no!
Luffy.
...A-And that's how it'd all play out!
A-All right, I'll make some.
Don't worry.
I like you!
You have to think first
about saving your brother.
You, wait outside for a while.
Say, Luffy,
What?! But I have to hurry!
tell me about your friends.
You have faith in your friends.
What're you doing over there in the corner?
I know that!
Well, I mean, it's no big deal!
I'm just making conversation!
Don't you?
It's not like I want to know more
about you or something like that!
Aren't you gonna eat? This
Sea King ham is good as hell!
You...
It's dinner time!! A banquet!!
Plus,
I can't breathe.
I-I-I'm okay! You eat it!
you are not alone now.
The way she's clutching her chest,
I'm gonna eat!!
Well, which one of them should I start with?
I'm totally satisfied as I am!
I think there's something
wrong with her heart.
This tastes great!
Zoro, Sanji, Usopp, Brook,
Franky, Nami, Robin...
I am here for you.
This one's good, too!
Damn! I can't see anything.
The curtain's closed.
Hancock!
There's a lot of good food!
Aren't you gonna eat anything?
Nami? Robin?
But I can't figure out what it is.
There are girls?!
Yeah, it's totally covered! Oh,
there's an open space here!
How foolish I've been!
Yeah. You're spilling the tea water.
I've never seen symptoms like these, so
I don't know what to prescribe.
I didn't notice there's
been a goddess on my side!
I'm sorry, but I can't be with you.
Snake Princess seems to be in a lot of pain.
Why?! Why, Luffy?!
Luffy!
Love-Love Beam!
Then, I'll eat yours,
alright? Oh, you guys, too.
She didn't eat a thing.
Hancock!
Because I'm with them!
...And that's how it'd all play out!
No, I won't back off!
Something wrong?
That man saved our lives.
There were two bad-mannered rats
so I just taught them a lesson.
I can't wait to get off this island tomorrow!
--No, I can't do it! Yes, I want to! No, I can't!
--What're you doing, Hammock?
What're you talking about?
I heard he'll leave tomorrow morning.
I really wanna see everybody soon!
I see!
Tomorrow morning...
T-This is...
Meanwhile, a few days ago...
Men's bodies are strange as the rumors said.
This can't be happening!
This must be a warning!
Mon...
If we ever try to look into her
room, she'll do this to us!
I saw it at the arena. They can
stretch their legs really long!
Lu...
--Snake Princess!
--Granny Nyon, stop fooling around with her!
I wanna get my hands on Luffy-sama
to see how much he can stretch.
She's scary!
She's in agony!
I'm not fooling around!
--"Luffy-sama"?
--That's his name.
Oh my god!
W-What happened?
I can't believe this!
Oh, Luffy-sama!
That's a person!
What an untimely virus!
Watch your mouth!
Silently...
Meanwhile, a few days ago...
It's unthinkable to address
a man in such a way.
I've never seen clothes like these...
--A virus?
--Do you know what it is?
She's from somewhere else.
On an island in the South Blue...
Don't forget the rule of Amazon Lily!
Granny Nyon... I can't breathe!
Then, why is Luffy-sama here?
She's alive!
Right?
Am I... going to die?
Yes, you are.
Luffy!
Why is a man who once got the
death sentence here, Ran?
Are you okay?
--What're you saying?!
--Stop making stupid jokes, Granny Nyon!
Everybody!
Well... I'm not sure.
Oops!
And of all places, our celebration!
Where am I?
The former empress died
from the same illness.
I can't believe that Snake
Princess has forgiven him.
Why isn't anybody here?
You're in Tequila Wolf, a
country in the East Blue.
Maybe, it's...
Did they kill them?
I heard the empress before
that died from this, too.
...a trap laid by Snake Princess.
Are you cold? Do you want
to come to our house?
That can't be it! I won't believe it!
Where am...
I caught it, too, but left this country
A trap?
If it won't put you out,
yes, I would like to.
Are you up?!
He surprised them at the arena by putting
up a fight so she wants him to eat a lot
Everybody!
and survived.
Snake Princess, Monkey
D. Luffy is here with me.
and catch him off guard and give him hell.
Hey, hustle up!
Chopper!
Hey, Granny Nyon!
So it's our role to give him hell, right?
What? Who the heck are you?!
He wants to ask you a favor.
Can you at least listen to him?
Where am I?
You're in my house. Now, calm down...
Luffy!
--Big Sis is suffering!
--What are you thinking?!
Don't mess with me!
Oh! You're scaring me.
She's standing!
Alright. I'd like to hear it.
Everybody!
It's not good to move around
so much. You're in bad shape.
Are you ready?
Let's take care of the man!
--And the weather is...
--Stay away!
Soran! Did you go out without asking again?!
Bad shape or not, I'm getting out of here!
How lucky he is, Monkey D. Luffy!
You can't do that! You hid
from the officers, right?
Wait!
He's starting to act strange.
If I'm not there, they can't go anywhere.
Will he move this mountain
that no one could move?!
Yes.
I wasn't scared at all when you guys
weren't there. I really wasn't!
Who's that?
--Quietly...
--Get lost!
Seems like she's from somewhere else.
Oh, no! Did he notice?
Hey! Screw you people!!
She was lying down in this snow.
Do you want something? Luffy?
Ow!
A drifter?
Ouch! Stop it, Luffy, Usopp!
Forgive me.
Maybe, a wanted person.
--I can't help wanting to help you.
--I said get lost!
I gotta ask you something!
That's enough!!
Anyway, she wouldn't come to the
place like this if she were sane.
Are you alright?
I said stop, damn it!
He sensed the trap!
No sickness can overtake me.
Looks like I'm not welcomed here. I'll go.
Maybe he wants to fight us
with the pan and the ladle.
Ouch! You jerk!
I'll look after her.
There's a Whitebeard pirate named Ace who's
waiting to be executed. He's my brother!
That sounds like something
that stupid man would do.
Don't be selfish!
Don't get beaten!
What would you do if the officers find
out that we're giving a stranger shelter?
I want to rescue Ace!
But I heard a pirate ship
can't make it in time!
I'd take all the responsibility!
Why aren't you singing?!
What are these birds?!
Your brother is... that Whitebeard pirate?
They're huge!
She's hopeless!
Where are you gonna hide her?
Are you gonna eat me?!
What are you doing?
Can you board the navy ship
In my room.
In the loft?
and take me to Ace's prison?!
Look, you people! This is
how you have a banquet!
It'll be okay for a while there.
I-I can't move my body!
Are you people serious? Shouldn't
we turn her in before it's too late?
How self-centered can
you be? Straw Hat Luffy!
I gotta run!
Yo ho ho ho… Yo ho ho ho…
You know Big Sis's pain but you still
ask her to go to that abhorrent place?!
It's too late. She's already in our house.
Oww! Stop it!
Yo ho ho ho… Yo ho ho ho…
I don't wanna regret it later.
Oh, my head is spinning!
Gather up all of the crew!
Time to ship out Binks's Brew!
--How cruel you are!
--We showed you mercy and then you become arrogant!
Keep me out of it!
Sea wind blows to where, who knows?
The waves will be our guide!
Thank you!
This is why we hate men! Big Sis's
patience is wearing very thin!
Don't get any ideas. She has to
leave as soon as her wounds heal.
O'er across the ocean's tide,
the sunset is goin' wild
No! Let me go!
Turn him to stone and
throw him over the edge!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Even if she gets well, there's
nothing for her in this country.
You bastard!
See the sky! Birds singing
in circles passing by!
So you want me to follow their order for
the Seven Warlords of the Sea to convene.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, little girl.
--What's that?
--Men are funny!
They are kind.
Little girl, who flew through
the sky to get here.
It's funnier than Sweetpea's drunk dance!
--Big Sis!
--Kill him!
Yes.
If you want me to...
What's wrong with this island!
I hate to admit it, but I can't top this.
I heard you the first time. What do you want?
Is this a dream?
Thank you.
I'll go anywhere!
Please tell me this is a dream!
Sailing out on our journey
to the ends of the sea!
Something smells so nice.
Are you calmed down a bit now?
Hey! Yo ho ho ho… Yo ho ho ho…
I didn't use any perfume.
Good! Thank you! This way I can
make it before the execution!
Are you sure you're not
going to flip out again?
No, stop it!
Maybe, that's the scent of the outside world.
Yo ho ho ho…
S-Snake Princess decided to
go to the World Government HQ!
Stop it!
The outside?
Yeah.
I am not your toy!
What happened to her, Granny Nyon?!
Why can't you get it? It's like this!
The Snake Princess is
suffering from lovesickness!
I haven't left this country since I was born.
Like this! This!
This is good!
The former empresses died
from being burnt by love!
No wonder. You were sleeping for
two days since you crashed here.
Are you a traveler? Did you
come from a hot climate?
This!
Is it like this?
There is a saying around the East Blue:
For that long?
Yes, I've been traveling
around on a ship but...
That's so funny, Luffy-sama!
Yes. You must have had a rough time, huh?
Is it a big ship? What kind
of island did you come from?
"Love is always..."
Men stick chopsticks in their nasal cavities
to their mouth
"...a hurricane!"
Have you seen any beautiful
flowers or birds? And...
and hold baskets in their hand...
What a classless dance!
Soran! The break is over!
Hurry and get ready!
Ta-dah!
Let me show you something! These
are tightly tied Wind Knots!
It's time to work.
You work this late at night?
What's happening to me?!
Gum-Gum Belly-talk!
If I untie one...
I don't think I can turn
down any request from Luffy.
It's over... right?
We work all day and night.
there is a gentle breeze.
I said I'd go without even thinking.
If I untie two...
You can rest.
there is a strong wind.
And I don't have any regrets.
Tell me about the outside world later.
What is this place?
If I untie three...
That's what we call love!
it really starts blowing!
Okay. I'll be waiting for you, Soran.
Isn't there anybody here?
Love?
The pain of thinking about
someone that you can't see
Yes.
What're you doing?!
I thought it might cheer you up.
drags you down and leads
eventually to your death.
Luffy!
Yeah, I'm really cheery now! Thank
you so much! I'm outta here!
Everybody!
The former empresses fell
in love with some men but
Where are you going? It's
impossible, young girl!
because they were empresses,
Here! This is the specialty of Maiden Island!
I don't think that I can make it in time.
they had to bottle up their feelings
and stay on this island.
What? Specialty?
I'm the only one on this island.
In time, the pain was too much for them
Penne gorgonzola with Sea King meat.
What am I gonna do?!
This isn't so bad!
and and in the end,
that's what took their lives.
I'm thirsty and hungry...
I'm okay!
I often eat Sea King meat
but this is different!
But the decision you made to go
with him will save your life.
If only Luffy and everybody else were here,
It really does stretch!
even on a deserted island like this,
It's soft like gum!
If you go to the World Government HQ and
keep your title of Warlord of the Sea,
we'd have a banquet!
Your time's up!
--What? One more time!
--No, then you won't stop!
it will save this country and help
Monkey D. Luffy at the same time.
Wow, this Sea King meat is
very good! It's hard to eat...
Looks like a huge cyclone is on its way!
Banquet, banquet!
W-W-What are you doing - picking
and stretching my body?!
What a weird fate he has brought with him.
We can't help it! You'll
leave tomorrow, right?
Normally, there is only one way for
a pirate to get to the Great Prison
Maybe I'll never see them again...
There are a lot of people who
want to touch you just one time.
Oh, did I wake you?
Oh no, I told you!
and that is to just get caught.
I can't take it!
Soran, you're so dirty!
You're covered in dirt.
Come in and take a shower!
--It's taking too long! I wanna touch him now!
--Me, too!
I'm okay.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring, clank!
Where is everybody?!
What kind of work do you do?
"20 gol per touch"
In the meantime, I will
wash and dry your clothes.
--We are making a bridge.
--A bridge?
--You're so popular!
--Luffy-chan!
It's me.
Luffy... Everybody...
Boa... Hancock?!
This country is on a bridge.
You can't do business using
me without asking me!!
Grandpa.
Oh yeah!
What?
I decided to follow the orders to convene.
There's this!
This is not just a rain!
Come on, Luffy-chan! Tonight is
our only chance to touch a man!
We made a promise to meet up
where this Vivre Card leads us!
An enormous cyclone's approaching!
However, there is one condition.
Luffy and others will be there!
What? What did you say?
The bridge will connect
many islands together.
Hey! S-Stop, you people!
I can't eat! Hey! Hey!
If you can't accept that condition...
I'm telling you that a storm
is coming! A gigantic one!
I know that nothing can stop them!
This construction has been
going on for centuries now.
Oh yeah, this is true.
I will make it!
All right, let me hear it - this
condition that you're talking about.
That's what the officers say.
Maybe somebody else will fall out of the sky.
This is no time to give up!
For centuries?
Tell me. Where are you from?
Where's Margaret?
I'd eat anything to survive
to see everybody again!
God! He's so irritating!
I'm from...
--Where did Luffy-sama go?
--No! He ran away!
Whatever happens, I don't care!
This fruit is bitter!
Luffy!
But it's juicy!
He can't have gotten too far!
Let's find him and touch him!
What? What's this?
My home island no longer exists.
This one's too sour!
But I traveled many islands and oceans.
If you turn the wheel,
hot water will come out.
Gotcha! I need some meat, too!
I thought that he was gonna leave tomorrow.
What's the matter with them?
T-The wheel?
But this doesn't look so appetizing.
I heard that they changed
where they are heading.
Keep hiding!
Soran?
He'll get on a navy ship with Snake Princess.
No, I can't expect too
much on a deserted island.
This is only food that I could bring.
--Luffy!
--You guys! Thank you for everything!
It's great that you can
return to your friends!
What're these?
Wow! You can't run!
They're drawings of islands
all throughout the world.
I'll be back with my friends!
Yeah. Well, I'm sorry that
I got you into some trouble.
I've never left this place so I
drew them out of my imagination.
You can't get away from me!
Your friends?
Yes! I'll have Sanji cook for you.
Clouds raining hot water? What's going on?!
But when I draw an island, it makes
me feel like I'm visiting that island
I worried when you turned into stone!
How's the water temperature?
He's a great cook!
If you push the wheel, hot air comes out.
You'll be surprised!
and I can forget how difficult life is!
And there's a skeleton who's a musician!
These are wonderful!
Who the hell... hit me?
A skeleton?
His name is Brook and when he sees a
girl, he always tries to see her panties!
This is the Sky Island!
But you protected us, right?
Does the island in the sky really exist?!
Ouch!
I made some tea.
--Yes.
--Tell me about your trip there!
Oh, thank you!
Panties?
Why is it so hot?
I heard what happened.
What's so great about them?
All right.
Thank you, Luffy!
And there is a reindeer called Chopper and...
Well... where should I start?
It's good!
Wait! What? Why're we so relaxed?!
I said "a storm is coming"!
Oh, but is it possible?
You should really give a crap!
Nami and Robin are
okay but this country prohibits men...
You have to calm down!
What's wrong with Big Sis?
Am I gonna be dinner?!
They'll make an exception for your friends.
She hasn't eaten anything and while she
said she's tired, she also can't sleep.
Wow, it's so rare to find a raccoon!
We'll cook raccoon hot pot!
Snake Princess seems to favor you.
The forcing assemble thing
is maybe bothering her.
Wow, that's wonderful!
I rather get some birds
and do chicken hot pot.
We'll look forward to seeing them!
It seems like the outside world
is as much fun as I thought!
Are we really gonna be alright?
We would've done it, if it were that easy.
It is about time.
She's here!
We'll just have raccoon for now.
Every day they push us around and
work us until we're exhausted but
I'll be back soon. You wait
here quietly, young girl.
Stop it! I'm a reindeer!
Who put these things here? They're in my way!
Tomorrow morning...
What?! H-Hey!
when I think about it, maybe
making a bridge isn't so bad!
A puppy and...
...a baby seal!
When it links to a distant island someday,
Then it looks like we'll
have reindeer hot pot!
Wait!
anyone can travel freely
by crossing the bridge.
It's Snake Princess!
Big Sis!
Oh wait, did it just say something?
There's no end to her sexual allure!
How can he walk smoothly in this wind?
Then I'll travel all over the world
Do reindeers speak?
I don't know why but her beauty
is even more striking than usual!
Let me go! Just let me go!
and draw pictures of actual islands!
I am deeply sorry! I am
responsible for the animals!
I-It's a crisis! We tried to
sneak into the birds' nest
Please be careful.
That's a great dream!
Hey, sorry to put you on such short notice!
--Granny Nyon!
--What's the matter, Margaret?
but they caught us!
Here it is!
Yes! So, tell me more!
The birds are coming!
Luffy's been chased by girls of the village.
Okay.
Let's shoo them away!
Can we join?
Snake lady, I wanna leave
as soon as possible!
--Let's go, everyone!
--Let's go!
No wonder. They don't see men often.
Don't look at his eyes!
Of course.
H-Hey! Wait! Set me free before you go!
Hey, Granny Bean!
No, Luffy! It's rude to call her that!
This part of the village is
secluded. Stay here for a while.
Call her Snake Princess!
And my name's not Bean!!
The woman is in the loft.
Cool Ball!
Good job. Let's go!
He has something to eat, so just
bring him tea or something.
You can call me Hancock.
Looks like the birds are stronger!
Heat Ball!
Snake Princess!
Hey! Don't forget your promise
to get me out of this country!
Okay.
Granny, you like to read newspapers, huh?
Alright, I got you, Hammock!
Oh no!
Coo News isn't delivered to a Calm Belt
--Don't move!
--W-What is this?!
It's Hancock.
S-Snake Princess is smiling!
--Outta my way!
--We're looking for the stranger!
so it's hard to get it but since our
empress is a Warlord of the Sea,
If you resist us, we'll kill you!
How many karats is that sparkle?!
Here I go!
What's happening?!
It's too dazzling...
I have to know what's going
on in the world at least.
Cyclone Burst!
A woman in love! I was once like that...
Augh! Ow! Ow!
Somebody must've told the
officers! They're here for her!
Ouch! Ouch!
Who's a Warlord of the Sea?
What's wrong, Granny Nyon?!
That face is so creepy.
Snake Princess.
Those birds treated me like a toy
Shut up!
What should we do?!
Wh...
and the humans tried to eat me in a hot pot!
What?!
What's wrong with this island?!
She's a Warlord of the Sea?
Have a good trip, Snake Princess!
Does that mean she's
really strong in a fight?
--We'll see you, Luffy!
--Luffy-chan!
One legend suggests this
island is a treasure island.
You are a pirate.
Didn't you notice it?
See you!
Cut that out!
This is Birdie Kingdom,
where birds reign supreme.
N-No, I didn't.
Don't you read newspapers?
What do you want?
What is Chopper's fate?!
Come see us, really!
No, I don't read them.
I heard that you're hiding a
suspicious woman in this house.
We're all looking forward
to seeing you again!
Oh, what a shock!
These days, people opposed to the
construction of the bridge threaten the order.
Snake Princess became
empress of this country
and a captain of the
Kuja Pirates 11 years ago.
It's done!
Turn her over!
We don't know a woman like that!
She was young but
Whoa...
they put a price of 80 million on
her head after her first expedition.
Behold! A dream island in the Grand Line
It's no use searching here!
We're tired so leave us alone!
I had no obligation to save you!
called Peachy Island.
Just one?
Watch your mouth!
It had to do with the bad reputation
Kuja had even before her.
Oh, I'm so relieved!
Auntie!
If you don't cooperate, we have to arrest
all of you and question you one by one.
I was worried that you were going to die.
The World Government became
cautious about her from the start
Gum-Gum Belly-talk!
and they suggested that she become
one of the Seven Warlords.
You know what we do to get the
information we want, right?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
"Dear Nami-san, Robin-chan,"
But now, that title is about to be revoked.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, young girl!
"how are you both doing?"
Because...
"Right now, I'm... I'm..."
Luffy! I hope you can see your friends!
I heard you the first time.
W-What?!
What?
- A FEW HOURS BEFORE -
The Seven Warlords and Navy Headquarters
Yeah!
are gonna fight
the Whitebeard Pirates?!
Oh, you only saw it the one time
but you already used the Wind Knot.
What's that?! What'll happen?!
W-W-W-W-Wait a minute!
Granny Nyon.
Captain, I found these!
You are impressive!
Snake Princess has no problem but can
Luffy get on a navy ship for sure?
It's easy!
T-This is too much to hear at once!
Okay, I got to go!
What is this crap?
Islands?
Managing to get a 3 hundred million
berries price on his head,
I drew them! Give them back!
What a foolish man!
You don't know anything.
Wh-What is this?
W-Where am I?
and then causing a serious incident
on the Sabaody Archipelago,
You drew islands?
Where... am I?!
I must say, that was just a prediction.
Monkey D. Luffy is a sworn enemy of the navy.
Damn! This is all because of that Warlord!
But the battle will probably happen.
That's amusing! How silly!
Is he planning to hide behind cargo?
This is a small Sky Island - Weatheria,
Don't worry.
Give them back!
The World Government has made a move.
where scientific studies
of the weather are conducted.
I gave Snake Princess a good strategy.
Excuse me! Mister! Mister! Are you all right?
Tell me where the woman is.
S-Sky Island?!
Whitebeard is a man who would never
allow his mates to be killed.
Then you'll get your drawings back.
That cyclone was going to be a good sample
Mister! Mister! Are you all right?!
Even though they know this, they
announced the public execution of...
I don't know!
but it suddenly disappeared.
...Portgaz D. Ace, a great
commander of Whitebeard's.
Once again, where's the woman?
I wonder who did such thing.
I don't know!
Nami was whisked away to
a small island in the sky.
If you cooperate, we'll get
you out of here someday.
Will she able to get back to her friends?
Then you can see the outside world for real.
I can feel something...
and smell something sweet.
I don't know!
One last chance!
I'm in the hands of a beautiful woman!
Where is the woman?!
They announced the public execution of...
Is it... Nami-san?!
...Portgaz D. Ace, a great
commander of Whitebeard's.
No, is it Robin-chan?!
I've been waiting for you, Boa Hancock.
No, I must be dreaming.
"A Winter Island on the Grand Line"
What's wrong?
But it's doesn't matter. I
just wanna be here forever!
I told you about my condition
through the Transponder Snail.
Of who?
Ace. "Fire Fist" Ace.
I managed to get my superior's approval to
stop by at Impel Down, the Great Prison.
I don't know!
Ace... is gonna get executed?
Oh, w-wait a minute!
Is it only you and that snake
who'll get on this ship?
What's this?
You forgot your handkerchief! Oh?
Even though you're a Warlord, pirates
are not allowed in that area.
I heard a pirate called Blackbeard...
So it wasn't a dream?
...became a Warlord by
defeating "Fire Fist" Ace.
We've made an exception for you
You people won't leave this place
for the rest of your life anyway!
but we don't have time,
so we can't stay there that long.
Elizabeth?
I know.
Take all of them in!
Blackbeard...
We're gonna torture them until they speak!
Big Sis, please return safe.
The World Government will take full
advantage of this big fish they've caught,
Please come home alive, Big Sis!
And show no mercy to the kid!
The storm's getting worse. Let's
take a break somewhere, Kitton.
We'll wish your good luck
in battle, Snake Princess!
Come on, move!
--a pirate named Ace...
--Granny...
Anyway, where the hell am I?
Take care, Luf...
Okay.
Lady!
Granny!!
That's my brother!
What's wrong, Taroimo?
I'm going now. I'll leave the country
in your hands while I'm gone.
Ace is my older brother!
Yes!
Clutch!
Don't tell me that I'm in heaven!
--It's big!
--Kitton, back off!
What?!
It was worth the wait.
Her name is Elizabeth...
Is that true?! He's your brother?!
It seems like I can fulfill my duty now.
H-Hey, guys!
I didn't know that he was captured.
And he's gonna be executed?!
Then, there's no chance for him to escape!
Anyway, you were so adamant about not
wanting to assemble, what made you change your...?
If this is heaven,
S-Stay away! P-Put your hands up!
If Whitebeard wins this battle,
there will be a chance for him.
W-Wait! Stop, Taroimo!
is she an angel?
Oh, my heart aches!
What should I do? Where are
they gonna execute him?
People may fear you as a pirate empress
but after all, you're just human.
Why is my heart beating so fast?!
Wait!
This...
It'll take place Marinford's town square,
When you are hungry, your stomach growls.
must be love!
I-I'm sorry! Forgive me!
Please don't hurt me!
He's human!
where Navy Headquarters stands.
I can see that romance is blooming!
Silence! As an empress, I have
better manners than that...
It says "in one week," which
means 6 days from today.
--Then, what was that...
--That was me!
What do we do?!
What?! That's too soon!
Sanji-san!
E-Excuse me! Are you all right?
How long will it take to get to
Sabaody Archipelago from here?
Wait!
Luffy!
I got you!
Sorry. I couldn't eat enough at the banquet
since I was being chased by all those girls.
He thought that you were
something we were hunting.
It will take more than a week.
It's her! I got her cornered!
Oh no no!
Yeah, I'm fine!
Hurry! Someone! I need backup!
If we get caught now, it's all over.
If it takes that long, then Ace will
be finished before I meet my crew!
How is that possible?!
Nami-san and Robin-chan are waiting for me!
I will ask for food later.
Be patient for a while!
No but...
Ah, so you are fine.
What're you doing? Didn't you hear him?!
Alright!
Then how long will it take
to get to where Ace is?
I gotta say thank you to her!
That's good, right? Taroimo.
And it's getting hard to walk like
this. Can you climb up higher?
Isn't she the one that you're looking for?
I'm not the kind of guy
to forget his manners!
Impel Down is where he locked, and
it'll take a week by a pirate ship
But, damn!
Just go and get her!
Like this?
How far did I come?
You're not welcome here!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
and 4 days by a navy ship.
Oh, it's so cold! Is this the arctic?!
Forgive me for being unfaithful!
Captain...
Do you have a fever? You're flushed.
Why?! Navy ships are that fast?
What're you doing?! Go and cover him!
Elizabeth-chan! Oh?
It's nothing.
Franky!
Yes, sir!
There's a current used exclusively
by the World Government.
Oh no! He's only in his
underwear in all this snow.
I'll let you get away for now!
Enies Lobby.
But I won't forget your rebellious behavior!
Then, first of all, can you revert
my crew that you turned to stone?
Have you been robbed?
Impel Down.
Put this fur pelt on.
We don't care!
This house has the same
design as this handkerchief.
Navy Headquarters.
We can't go back to Navy Headquarters
in this ungainly state.
Fur pelts?! You got to be kidding! No thanks!
There's a giant whirlpool which
connects those three facilities.
Well then, maybe this is Elizabeth's...
If I wore crap like that...
Are you all right?
Are they dead?
When you open the Gate of Justice
at any of the three facilities,
Aw! Nah, man, it wouldn't be
fitting for a pervert! Aw!
--What was that? It sounded like a man's...
--I-It was me!
the current runs inside
allowing you to enter.
Hey, follow my lead!
Lady...
Is Lady Elizabeth here?
That means if the gates aren't open,
you'd just keep drifting on the current.
Shake your hip to the right!
The night wind is not good for your
body. I may have caught a cold.
My name is Sanji. You were
looking after me a while ago.
Right hand on your waist!
Stick out your left hand!
I came here to return your handkerchief...
Sorry, your hair tickled my nose!
Pirate ships would rather avoid the current
It seems like he didn't notice.
Slide and left!
by going a long way round.
I'm not so sure but
This is a country of laborers.
What should I do?
Right! Left! Right! Left!
you're not up to something, are you?
Pull! Pull!
Repeat! Aw!
What do you mean by that?
What do you want to do?
Isn't that a bit cruel, Elizabeth-chan?!
The people who work here are
criminals from various countries
One! Two! One! Two!
You seem different than when
I saw you a few hours ago.
Don't tell me that's your
brother's Vivre Card!
No, don't rush it.
Right! Left! Right! Left!
She's a shy, naive girl.
or citizens of countries that refused
to be allied with the World Government.
Did he notice?
Oh, is it the sheet that moves
around that you care about so much?
One! Two! One! Two! One! Two! One! Two!
I got to be cool - have patience.
I swear that both my body and soul are pure.
I'm really sorry about the
way I acted back there!
That's a different one.
Right! Left! Right! Left!
But if you have a doubt, why don't you
search my body with your own hands?
This is the one that Ace gave to me.
Your hand was so attractive
I couldn't help it!
Aw! One! Two! One! Two!
On your feet! Let's go!
That's also known as a paper of life.
I'll allow it.
In other word, slaves.
Ha!
Excuse me for being so forward but
I'll let you.
How long until the bridge is complete?
It tells you a direction in which the
person is and about their vital energy.
Super!
I have no clue.
may I make it up by cooking
something for you?
So, if it's that small, it means...
It's been under construction for 700 years!
Woo-hee! Great!
What're you saying? That's too risky!
You can tell me whatever you want to eat!
When I got it, it was ten times bigger.
700 years? For what purpose?
I may not look it, but I'm a good chef!
You don't need to know that.
You'll become one of laborers,
Ace has his own adventure...
Ah, this isn't working.
I'm still pretty cold! Where
the hell is this place?!
so all you have to worry about
is making the bridge!
Do you like to cook?
No. If you say so, I must believe you.
What?! You don't know where you are?
I wanted you to have it. Here.
Oh yes! I love cooking!
Why the hell would I know this place?!
Take care of my crew.
Then, do you like clothes?
Not only can we not make it to Impel Down,
You're on Mechanical Island,
Future Land Baldimore,
Always hang on to that.
Clothes?
but we can't even run the ship like this.
This islands look like a flower blooming
in the ocean. It's called Bowin Islands.
the birthplace of the genius.
Yes, yes, of course!
Huh? It's just a scrap of paper.
--Degenerate?
--The genius.
Unlike some stupid swordsmen,
I care about how I look!
That scrap of paper will bring you
and me together again sometime.
Wake up!
Let's go Usopp Exploring Party!
The... Degenerate?
Really? You like clothes?
The genius.
Of course, I'm the leader!
Usopp the king of snipers!
Yes!
...cock-sama!
Then what about dresses?
You don't want it?
And here is my crew!
No, I'll keep it.
Dresses?
What happened?
Mister!
It's natural for a big brother to worry...
Geek! I mean, god!
Get underway, you idiots!
I got it!
They couldn't be here due
to unforeseen circumstances.
Y-Yes, sir! Right away!
Let's take him to the hospital, Kitton!
She keeps asking what I like because she...
...about his bungling kid brother.
Where am I?
Okay.
Before we return to Marinford,
we'll stop at Impel Down!
Maybe she has a thing for me!
I wonder whether Luffy and others are alive.
Ace won't like me rescuing him
since he's stronger.
How's this dress? Do you like it?
They can't do anything without me.
I like dresses! I like them! I love them!
I know that they're crying for me!
I'm really fond of it!
But...
"Navy Headquarters"
Yeah, I'm sure!
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
How about flower prints?
I gotta hurry to save them!
I'm sorry, everybody.
We heard from Vice Admiral Momonga!
Flower prints! They're wonderful!
I'm gonna take a little side trip.
They are really cute!
Pirate Empress Boa Hancock finally gave in
Oh, just the wind.
and they are heading here now.
All right...
The crew of Usopp Exploring Party
should always be on the lookout!
Finally!
Finally, the door to
Elizabeth-chan's heart has...
I hope she can make it.
"OPERATION IN PROGRESS"
That woman is strong.
I'm Usopp...
So he is a cyborg.
Six of the Seven Warlords
of the Sea will be here.
I can't believe that his
energy source is cola.
What should we do?
We don't have any cola here.
I wanna go and rescue Ace!
Hawk-Eye Mihawk.
How can I get off this island? And...
You have a good taste, Elizabeth-chan!
Bartholomew Kuma.
There's no time to lose. Let's just begin.
Hey! Is anybody here?
Don Quixote Doflamingo.
Do you know for sure
Okay.
Gecko Moria.
how reckless it would be and how
big this battle is going to be?
Don't be shy! You've already
opened up the door of your heart.
Don't tell me this is a deserted island!
Marshall D. Teech.
And Boa Hancock.
Ugh! It's the My-Heart-Will-Stop-Beating-
If-I-Don't-See-Anybody Syndrome!
You'll be like an ant blown into a storm.
Sanji-san!
What about the last one
who was put in the prison?
Now, don't be afraid and
just come into my arms!
Collapse!
You can just be flicked away
without even having done anything.
Did he cool off?
No, sir. He seems like he is
still rigidly opposing battle.
I don't care what's gonna
happen! I just wanna go!
How sad!
Elizabeth-chan!
I can't just sit by calmly on the
sidelines and let this happen!
I think...
Hey! Isn't anybody here for real?!
Stop being shy and come out!
He said he is ready for his title
of Warlord of the Sea to be revoked!
...this will look good on you!
I assumed that he would be the most
cooperative and fight with us.
I see.
Ah, there you are!
So you're going to rescue the most
infamous prisoner in the world now.
But he caused a commotion at the last minute!
How're you?
Oh, ow, ow, ow...
Damn, Jimbei!
You seem to be doing a little well!
If there is a chance in a million,
Despite your appearance, you're
very strong, Elizabeth-chan!
I have an announcement. Fleet Admiral!
you better go to the Great
Prison where he's being held.
Mister!
The 500 pirates
Admiral Kizaru captured in revenge
for the Sabaody Archipelago incident...
When they move him to the
execution ground in Marinford,
Mister?
they said they can't hold them at Impel Down.
the navy admirals and the Seven
Warlords will be keeping a close eye.
Put them on labor!
Don't bring me any problems other
than ones related to Whitebeard!
Hello! You're the boy from earlier, right?
However, because your brother is now
the most important prisoner they have,
I'm sorry to keep you waiting!
And Saint Roswald, the World Noble, is...
there is no doubt that they're guarding the
prison with the military's full strength.
Let the Admirals handle it!
I-Is this a dream? Then it must be...
S-Something's different about you.
Where's Garp?
Yes! Unfortunately, they don't
have any cola here so...
Vice Admiral Garp headed
to Impel Down while ago.
So it's impossible to enter.
I care more about getting there in
time than what happens after.
...they used tea instead.
What is that man doing?
It's Darjeeling!
...a nightmare!
I got to get there while Ace is there.
Tea?
Coming and going as he wishes
at a time like this!
Just give me a big oar,
and I'll paddle myself...
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
It's an emergency! Whitebeard is moving!
Wait a second! You can't
get there on will alone.
Here they come! Is that from
one of the guard ships?
It has a super flavor!
This is a slim chance, too, but...
Put it through! I wanna hear directly.
I thought that you were one of us!
No, but...
Snake Princess refuses to follow the order to
force the Seven Warlords of the Sea to assemble.
All 23 Navy ships which were guarding
against Whitebeard's main ship Moby Dick,
It makes me super relaxed!
--Are you gonna eat that'n?
--Yeah, right!
You were suffering, weren't you?
You don't have to pretend anymore!
M-Mister!
But you saved me! Thanks,
Mr. Whoever-you-are!
If only she obeys the order,
Yes, this is a free country!
Oops! I'm sorry!
My name is Heracles'n!
we lost contact with them
all a few minutes ago.
we can take advantage of it
and let you on their ship.
Wow! That's a cool name!
Their ship? There's a navy ship here?!
What?! What did you say?
Oh? You think so'n?
Here you go!
Be careful, it's hot.
I'm Usopp! Nice meetin' you!
Now, put this dress on and open
up the door of your heart!
I heard there was some worrying activity
by other pirate ships in New World, too.
Then I'm gonna go and ask her!
Is this good to eat? I've
never seen a fruit like this!
If nothing is done,
I-I-I don't wanna open anything!
we won't have any intel on how many
ships they have or when they're coming!
No no! That's not what I was gonna say!
Wait!
It's fine'n! Usopp'n!
I already made arrangements for guard
ships to move in as replacements.
Mister! You were funnier
before and I miss it!
This island is known as
the second Maiden Island.
And my name is Heracles'n!
Granny Nyon!
What's wrong, Enishida? Why
are you in such a hurry?
Oh yeah? What was I like?
They've caught us off guard!
Everything is pink here.
Thank god. I was going to come get you.
Yeah, OK, fine - that's cool.
I didn't realize that they
were already on the move.
Like this!
All people and animals
who come to this island
What happened?
We don't know where they will strike.
It sure smells delicious...
Super!
have girlish hearts.
Well...
Spread the word:
Let's just lick it and see.
As long as Ace is there, a battle
may break out on Impel Down!
This can't be heaven!
...Snake Princess...
Hey! Wait!
...has come down with an unknown illness.
Yes, sir!
Usopp'n!
--Aren't you one of us?!
--You are one of us!
Kid.
Boy! What was it?! Did
that plant try to eat me?!
--Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
--How can you even say something like that?
--She's sick?!
--Oh my god!
Shut up! Don't come after
me! I told you I'm not!
It's this way, Vice Admiral Garp.
Of course, they're man-eating plants'n!
Franky becomes a gentleman
on Mechanical Island!
Man-eating?!
"Dear Nami-san, Robin-chan,"
Please be careful!
All right.
Will he ever be the same again?!
"how are you both doing?"
And what will happen to
the separated Straw Hats?!
Big Sis!
"Right now, I'm..."
"I'm..."
Oh no... this is a horrible sight.
--Wait!
Where the hell am I?!
Why don't you wait, man?!
Am I...
This is the Swindling Forest - Glinston!
Why should I? Stupid!
H-H-Help me!
Am I...
Welcome to Kamabakka Kingdom!
Are you still breathing?
And my name is Hera...
"Right now, I'm..."
...going to die?
"...in hell!"
Ace?
Chopper awakens on an island
Kuma's power has sent the friends far away.
In a certain land where snow silently falls,
Zoro arrives at an old castle,
Hancock has fallen ill.
to find himself perpetually under attack
by giant birds and brawny natives,
where he runs into Perona.
Granny Nyon tells the whole gang
about this terrifying illness,
the people have been forced to
work day and night for 700 years.
Nami ends up on an island
populated by mysterious old men.
landing him in a nasty crisis.
Zoro wants to return to his friends,
but for some reason, Perona stops him.
Meanwhile, Sanji awakens
What is it that this
island's inhabitants study?
What has Robin seen there?
which has killed previous
empresses of Amazon Lily.
on Peachy Island, the island of dreams,
Around the same time,
Around that time,
Meanwhile, Franky ends up on a different
island, where his body undergoes a change...
Usopp is about to be eaten
by mysterious plants!
where he has an encounter with
someone truly frightening.
What could this illness be?
Brook is being hailed as
Satan, the king of demons!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Friends' Whereabouts! A Princess
Negativity and the King of Demons!"
"The Friends' Whereabouts! Bridging
the Islands and Vicious Vegetations!"
"Love is a Hurricane!
Love-Love Hancock!"
"The Friends' Whereabouts! The Science
of Weather and the Mechanical Island!"
"The Friends' Whereabouts! An Island
of Giant Birds and a Pink Paradise!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!