Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Leaving the female-only island of Amazon Lily
to rescue his brother Ace who
is waiting to be executed,
Luffy stowed away on a navy ship with
the Pirate Empress Boa Hancock's help
and headed to the Great Prison - Impel Down!
Meanwhile, the rest of the Straw Hat crew,
who had been ejected from the Sabaody
Archipelago by Bartholomew Kuma are...
"The Friends' Whereabouts! Bridging
the Islands and Vicious Vegetations!"
Love-Love Beam!
Are we gonna survive this trip?!
They'll never learn!
Luffy, the food is here!
Luffy?
Hey, haven't we reached Ace yet?
Yes, I'm afraid it'll take more time.
I see.
Oh! Yum-yum!
Luffy.
Do you want some tea?
Yeah, please.
Yes, please.
Oh no!
A-All right, I'll make some.
Say, Luffy,
tell me about your friends.
Well, I mean, it's no big deal!
I'm just making conversation!
It's not like I want to know more
about you or something like that!
Well, which one of them should I start with?
Zoro, Sanji, Usopp, Brook,
Franky, Nami, Robin...
Nami? Robin?
There are girls?!
Yeah. You're spilling the tea water.
I'm sorry, but I can't be with you.
Why?! Why, Luffy?!
Because I'm with them!
No, I won't back off!
What're you talking about?
That's a person!
I've never seen clothes like these...
She's from somewhere else.
She's alive!
Are you okay?
Well... I'm not sure.
Where am I?
You're in Tequila Wolf, a
country in the East Blue.
Are you cold? Do you want
to come to our house?
If it won't put you out,
yes, I would like to.
Hey, hustle up!
Soran! Did you go out without asking again?!
You can't do that! You hid
from the officers, right?
Yes.
Who's that?
Seems like she's from somewhere else.
She was lying down in this snow.
A drifter?
Maybe, a wanted person.
Anyway, she wouldn't come to the
place like this if she were sane.
Looks like I'm not welcomed here. I'll go.
I'll look after her.
Don't be selfish!
What would you do if the officers find
out that we're giving a stranger shelter?
I'd take all the responsibility!
She's hopeless!
Where are you gonna hide her?
In my room.
In the loft?
It'll be okay for a while there.
Are you people serious? Shouldn't
we turn her in before it's too late?
It's too late. She's already in our house.
I don't wanna regret it later.
Keep me out of it!
Thank you!
Don't get any ideas. She has to
leave as soon as her wounds heal.
Even if she gets well, there's
nothing for her in this country.
They are kind.
Yes.
Thank you.
Something smells so nice.
I didn't use any perfume.
Maybe, that's the scent of the outside world.
The outside?
I haven't left this country since I was born.
Are you a traveler? Did you
come from a hot climate?
Yes, I've been traveling
around on a ship but...
Is it a big ship? What kind
of island did you come from?
Have you seen any beautiful
flowers or birds? And...
Soran! The break is over!
Hurry and get ready!
It's time to work.
You work this late at night?
We work all day and night.
You can rest.
Tell me about the outside world later.
Okay. I'll be waiting for you, Soran.
Yes.
I don't think that I can make it in time.
Oh, did I wake you?
Soran, you're so dirty!
I'm okay.
What kind of work do you do?
--We are making a bridge.
--A bridge?
This country is on a bridge.
The bridge will connect
many islands together.
This construction has been
going on for centuries now.
That's what the officers say.
For centuries?
Tell me. Where are you from?
I'm from...
My home island no longer exists.
But I traveled many islands and oceans.
Soran?
What're these?
They're drawings of islands
all throughout the world.
I've never left this place so I
drew them out of my imagination.
But when I draw an island, it makes
me feel like I'm visiting that island
and I can forget how difficult life is!
These are wonderful!
This is the Sky Island!
Does the island in the sky really exist?!
--Yes.
--Tell me about your trip there!
All right.
Well... where should I start?
Wow, that's wonderful!
It seems like the outside world
is as much fun as I thought!
Every day they push us around and
work us until we're exhausted but
when I think about it, maybe
making a bridge isn't so bad!
When it links to a distant island someday,
anyone can travel freely
by crossing the bridge.
Then I'll travel all over the world
and draw pictures of actual islands!
That's a great dream!
Yes! So, tell me more!
Okay.
Can we join?
Of course.
The woman is in the loft.
Good job. Let's go!
Hey! Don't forget your promise
to get me out of this country!
--Don't move!
--W-What is this?!
--Outta my way!
--We're looking for the stranger!
If you resist us, we'll kill you!
What's happening?!
Somebody must've told the
officers! They're here for her!
What should we do?!
What do you want?
I heard that you're hiding a
suspicious woman in this house.
These days, people opposed to the
construction of the bridge threaten the order.
Turn her over!
We don't know a woman like that!
It's no use searching here!
We're tired so leave us alone!
Watch your mouth!
Auntie!
If you don't cooperate, we have to arrest
all of you and question you one by one.
You know what we do to get the
information we want, right?
Captain, I found these!
What is this crap?
Islands?
I drew them! Give them back!
You drew islands?
That's amusing! How silly!
Give them back!
Tell me where the woman is.
Then you'll get your drawings back.
I don't know!
Once again, where's the woman?
If you cooperate, we'll get
you out of here someday.
Then you can see the outside world for real.
I don't know!
One last chance!
Where is the woman?!
I don't know!
You people won't leave this place
for the rest of your life anyway!
Take all of them in!
We're gonna torture them until they speak!
And show no mercy to the kid!
Come on, move!
Lady!
Clutch!
H-Hey, guys!
S-Stay away! P-Put your hands up!
I-I'm sorry! Forgive me!
Please don't hurt me!
I got you!
It's her! I got her cornered!
Hurry! Someone! I need backup!
What're you doing? Didn't you hear him?!
Isn't she the one that you're looking for?
Just go and get her!
You're not welcome here!
Captain...
What're you doing?! Go and cover him!
Yes, sir!
I'll let you get away for now!
But I won't forget your rebellious behavior!
We don't care!
Are you all right?
Lady...
This is a country of laborers.
Pull! Pull!
The people who work here are
criminals from various countries
or citizens of countries that refused
to be allied with the World Government.
On your feet! Let's go!
In other word, slaves.
How long until the bridge is complete?
I have no clue.
It's been under construction for 700 years!
700 years? For what purpose?
You don't need to know that.
You'll become one of laborers,
so all you have to worry about
is making the bridge!
This islands look like a flower blooming
in the ocean. It's called Bowin Islands.
Let's go Usopp Exploring Party!
Of course, I'm the leader!
Usopp the king of snipers!
And here is my crew!
They couldn't be here due
to unforeseen circumstances.
Where am I?
I wonder whether Luffy and others are alive.
They can't do anything without me.
I know that they're crying for me!
Yeah, I'm sure!
I gotta hurry to save them!
Oh, just the wind.
The crew of Usopp Exploring Party
should always be on the lookout!
I'm Usopp...
How can I get off this island? And...
Hey! Is anybody here?
Don't tell me this is a deserted island!
Ugh! It's the My-Heart-Will-Stop-Beating-
If-I-Don't-See-Anybody Syndrome!
Collapse!
How sad!
Hey! Isn't anybody here for real?!
Stop being shy and come out!
Ah, there you are!
How're you?
You seem to be doing a little well!
--Are you gonna eat that'n?
--Yeah, right!
But you saved me! Thanks,
Mr. Whoever-you-are!
My name is Heracles'n!
Wow! That's a cool name!
Oh? You think so'n?
I'm Usopp! Nice meetin' you!
Is this good to eat? I've
never seen a fruit like this!
It's fine'n! Usopp'n!
And my name is Heracles'n!
Yeah, OK, fine - that's cool.
It sure smells delicious...
Let's just lick it and see.
Usopp'n!
Boy! What was it?! Did
that plant try to eat me?!
Of course, they're man-eating plants'n!
Man-eating?!
Where the hell am I?!
This is the Swindling Forest - Glinston!
H-H-Help me!
And my name is Hera...
Zoro arrives at an old castle,
where he runs into Perona.
Zoro wants to return to his friends,
but for some reason, Perona stops him.
Around that time,
Brook is being hailed as
Satan, the king of demons!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Friends' Whereabouts! A Princess
Negativity and the King of Demons!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!