Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the
Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way
to the New World,
will speed along the
Grand Line again today!
To rescue his brother Ace who
has been captured by the navy,
After being separated
from his friends,
To rescue his brother Ace who
has been captured by the navy,
After being separated
from his friends,
Luffy comes to the rescue his brother
Ace who has been captured by the Navy
Luffy stowed away on a navy ship with
the Pirate Empress Boa Hancock's help
the Pirate Empress Boa Hancock's help.
by sneaking into Impel Down -
the greatest prison in the world!
and headed to the Great
Prison - Impel Down!
Now, he is racing to level 5 with
a help of Buggy the Clown.
I'm sure that you
heard about Luffy.
He heard from some prisoners that Ace
would most likely be held on level 5
Meanwhile, the rest
of the Straw Hats
He picked a fight with the World
Government at Water Seven
who had been sent to separate
islands by Bartholomew Kuma are...
had been sent to separate
islands by Bartholomew Kuma.
Now I'm free! I finally got the treasure
mark that I always dreamed of!
and ran into an
unexpected acquaintance!
and destroyed the Judgement
Island - Enies Lobby!
This is a country of laborers.
Down to level 3 or level 4 - it doesn't
matter either way you're a goner!
I'll change my plan!
Pull! Pull!
As time ticks down for the
public execution of Ace,
Oh yeah. I told Luffy
about his father.
Now for some chaos!
The people who work here are
criminals from various countries
tensions at Navy
Headquarters are rising
I'm with you!
Stupid Blugori! You can't chop
me because I ate Chop-Chop fruit!
and preparations for
war are underway.
Luffy was surprised to
know about his father.
or citizens of countries that refused to
be allied with the World Government.
It doesn't matter to us at all.
"The Strongest Man in the Prison!
Poison Man Magellan Appears!"
Nobody can stop it now.
In other word, slaves.
We made the
king of the sea...
Because Luffy and
I unfortunately
--How long until the bridge is complete?
--I have no clue.
"Break through the Crimson Hell!
Buggy's Chaos-Inducing Plan!"
have the blood of the world's most
infamous criminal in our veins anyway.
...angry!
You'll become one of laborers so all you
have to worry about is making the bridge!
There was no way for
us to become marines.
"A Deadly Infiltration! The
Underwater Prison Impel Down!"
I took over the name "Portgaz" from
my mother to whom I owe so much
I just finished breaking out of my
cell! I don't wanna fall to another hell!
Gum-Gum...
Is this good to eat? I've
never seen a fruit like this!
Whip!
but I never wanted to have my
good-for-nothing father's blood.
Stop! Stop, stop!
I wanted you and Luffy to
become good marines.
Usopp'n!
Because I don't have any memory of
him and I don't owe anything to him.
Ow, ow, ow...
No!
Boy! What was it?! Did
that plant try to eat me?!
Ah yeah, I understand
but he tried...
Just kidding!
But instead, both of you brothers
have become notorious hoodlums.
Of course, they're
man-eating plants'n!
Chop-Chop
Emergency Escape!
What I want to say is...
Old man...
I'm sure that you
heard about Luffy.
Run as wild as you want
on the sea under my name.
He picked a fight with the World
Government at Water Seven
This is pretty creepy!
But, at least now I have this which means
and destroyed the Judgement
Island - Enies Lobby!
Where the hell am I?!
You are my son from now!
This is the Swindling
Forest - Glinston!
I'm seconds away from finding
Captain John's treasure!
My only father is...
I rushed there and gave him
some tough-love with this fist
Prepare to fall and have
your head crushed!
H-H-Help me!
All I have to do is
find my way out of...
Aerial Tailspin Big Top!
Whitebeard!
Okay, let's go!
Tell me the way!
W-W-Wait a second!
but he didn't
learn even a little.
"The Friends' Whereabouts! A Princess
Negativity and the King of Demons!"
You better just give up.
So he went and made a big
mess at Sabaody Archipelago.
How d'you like that,
you sea gorilla?!
Buggy the Clown's luck
as a pirate has run out.
I'm so proud of
my grandson!
No damage at all?!
That can't be true!
D-Don't! Stop punching me!
I didn't know navy sailors
got to eat grub this good!
This is not the way
Captain Buggy will die!
Oh yeah. I told Luffy
about his father.
But the meals that Sanji
cooks are way better!
This is the world's
greatest prison!
"Hancock & Luffy"
A father? Do I have a father?
Love-Love Beam!
Your father's name is
Monkey D. Dragon!
Welcome to my Impel Down!
It's a dead end!
I can't stop thinking about
those two girls on Luffy's crew.
Oh, I got it wrong! I said
"my" - jumping the gun!
He's a revolutionary!
Luffy was surprised to
know about his father.
I'm still the vice warden,
Hannyabal. Nice to meet you!
So you choose those
two girls over me?!
It doesn't matter to us at all.
Looks like you've gotten
stronger since we last met!
I told you to forget about me.
So this is level 2...
Now, let's just start.
They're tough! What
kind of animal are they?
Because Luffy and
I unfortunately
Let me put these Sea Prism
Stone handcuffs on you.
I didn't know you
were so stubborn.
have the blood of the world's most
infamous criminals in our veins anyway.
Yes!
They're fighters from the sea called
Blue Gorilla known as Blugori!
I'm not a prisoner but you put handcuffs
on me. You couldn't be more careful.
It's worse than the Crimson Hell of
level 1! It's called Wild Beast Hell!
Tell me what you don't
like about me, Luffy!
Stay sharp! There're
still 4 more...
There was no way for
us to become marines.
I'll change myself for you!
Don't leave me, Luffy!
You bastard! You had
me running like an idiot!
Well, then! I see you've
taken care of them already!
I took over the name "Portgaz" from
my mother to whom I owe so much
This floor has all the wild
beasts of hell everywhere!
But I don't have time to
mess around with these!
Public execution of Ace...
I won't back off!
...is in 33 hours!
but I never wanted to have my
good-for-nothing father's blood.
Wild beasts of hell?
Wow! He kicked a
lot of Blugori ass!
Because...
Damn it! Well, until I get
a chance to run away,
--Hey you! Who are you?!
--Let us out!
Because I don't have any memory of
him and I don't owe anything to him.
The love those two have for
Luffy can't compare to mine!
I'll take full advantage
of Straw Hat!
"A Reunion in Hell?! The Man
Who Ate the Chop-Chop Fruit!"
Ah yeah, I understand
but he tried...
Is that one of them?
Whew! Couldn't eat another
bite! That was so good!
They found us already!
What I want to say is...
What's up?
I thought there was
only one escapee.
Luffy!
Old man,
Yes, there's just one.
Don't forget that
you are a stowaway.
I could be wrong
but I saw two guys.
You are too valuable
to let die now, boy.
Sea Prism Stone handcuffs...
Is that how that beautiful,
elegant empress laughs?
Anyway, 5 Blugoris have been beaten
in front of community cell #10!
5 of them? It can't be true!
Run as wild as you want
on the sea under my name.
Well, I kinda find
that attractive, too.
It looks like a hippo to me.
Put out your hands.
We don't have any prisoners on level 1
who stand a chance against Blugoris!
Um, yeah.
But something is not right.
It's smaller than a regular hippo. Is
that what you'd call a "wild beast"?
You are my son from now!
"More investigation
is needed."
Whaaat?!
It's odd! I heard
that level 2 has...
You wanna rescue Ace?!
Meanwhile, the other crew who had been sent
Yeah.
Augh! What's
this thing?! Run!
"Grand Line, Kuraigana Island"
My only father is...
to separate islands by
Bartholomew Kuma are...
Shh! Be quiet!
You're the one
who's screaming!
"Ruins of Shikearu Kingdom"
Whitebeard!
Hey guys? The key? Please...
Wow! He's pretty
fast for a hippo!
Shut up! Keep
your mouth shut!
I'm holding a grudge...
Stop admiring it!
Turn left here!
Do you know Ace?!
I'm holding a grudge...
Yeah. Unlike you, your
brother was very polite...
He crashed into the wall!
I know I said that
He runs pretty fast but can
only run in a straight line!
if I were to travel, I would go to a dark,
damp old castle shrouded in mystery
Please don't hurt me!
W-What's wrong?!
and spend my time
singing dark songs.
So you really don't mind
that your body got eaten?!
You'll see! I'm the Chop-Chop
man - Buggy-sama!
Come out, Luffy!
Is this really a time
to be partying?
That was close!
How can you attack Luffy if you
don't even know where he is?
Damn that Kuma!
I was thinking of taking a risk
and sneaking out very quick but
But I didn't know there
would be no servants!
Vice Admiral Momonga!
I see a pirate ship!
Don't be such a
spoilsport, Alvida!
And I didn't know there wouldn't be bagel sandwiches
and hot chocolate in a comfy bed in the morning!
you can turn
anything to stone!
Whose ship is that?
How did you manage that?
That mark... I've
seen it before...
Let us enjoy ourselves!
It looks like I can't go
any farther with you.
Huh?
Even if my body parts are chopped
to pieces, I can move them as I want!
I didn't know there wouldn't
be any stuffed animals here!
I'll look into it!
Do you wanna see Luffy?
I know where he is!
If you don't remember, they
must not be a big deal.
I can't use my power while
wearing those Sea Prism cuffs.
See? He knows
where Luffy is...
That will learn ya!
You little hippo!
And they'll take my cloak
away so I can't hide you.
Let them go! There is no
time to waste on this trip.
Who the hell are you?!
I wish I could do more but...
Yes, sir!
Hello! Excuse me for
interrupting your banquet.
What're you talking about? I wouldn't
have made it this far without your help!
Ahh! Look over there!
It's a big Sea King!
Where am I? Moria-sama!
I was drawn here by the
smell of all this good food.
Who is that guy with Buggy?
If he targets us, he can eat
this whole ship with one bite.
I was able to get in even though the
building is surrounded. I'll be fine!
My name is Ace.
Nice to meet you!
I miss you, Kumacy!
Oh no no, you don't have to be that
polite. The pleasure is all ours...
I wanna go back
to Thriller Bark...
Please don't notice us!
Luffy.
What is that?
That's not what I asked!
They built this place as a
fort that locks people in.
He's gone.
Isn't there any way I can
just get out of here?!
I don't care about your
name! Don't mess with me!
W-We came all this way but
Don't get in any trouble.
Captain! Captain,
he's the "Fire Fist"!
there is nothing
we can do now.
Once they catch you, you'll
never be able to get out.
What should we do
now, Sister Alvida?!
"Fire Fist" Ace! Whitebeard's
Second Division Commander!
What's wrong?
That's what I thought! Somebody
has been sent here like me!
I think I saw something!
A bat, maybe?
I know that you're strong
Whitebeard?!
Don't ask me what to do!
I hope that
somebody is cute.
but promise me that you
won't get in any trouble.
What?!
Chop-Chop Quick Escape!
Oh! You know my father!
It's you guys who
wanted to come here
I can't expect too much!
That's very...
Anyway, I'm not on
my own anymore!
It's a monster mantis!
Alright! I promise!
and who spent a fortune
on an Eternal Pose.
He's sleeping!
Yeah, it's too big
for a mantis...
Thank you so
much, Hancock!
B-Because we really wanted to save Captain
Buggy who has been taken to Impel Down!
Then we hit it off and
became drinking buddies.
I won't forget what you've
done for me. I owe you!
He cuts like a pro!
So I feel very sorry about
what happened to him.
Did you just call
me Hancock?!
How can you be
so impressed?!
That's the foolishness of the Navy
to mess with Whitebeard's crew.
If I get chopped up much
more, it'll be a big problem!
Look at the sea!
We're about to enter the Calm Belt
where monsters have their nests.
I wanna get to level 5.
That's where Ace is, right?
You're an amazing fighter!
Alright, I got you, Hammock!
You think this ship
can sail there?
I don't know! Go by yourself!
I'm no friend of yours!
How can you be so relaxed?
Can I have more,
Hammock?!
But there is only one other course
and that's exclusively for the Navy.
What're you
doing, Hammock?
I'm not going to that
hell hole! See ya!
H-He is...
They're not gonna open the
Gate of Justice for a pirate ship.
one of Straw Hats!
Hancock!
If you're not willing to
escape, I'll do it on my own!
No way! We can't
even get there?!
There's 10 or more navy ships out
there. Are you sure you can make it?
He must have been
beaten by Kuma.
If nothing is done, Captain
Buggy will be executed!
--Do you think he's stuck?
--Yeah.
He's dead, isn't he?
Now I can die happily!
10 or more?
...Along with his
friend Ace-kun!
What should we do?
Oh, I get it! They must be
preparing for Whitebeard's attack!
Well, maybe we should...
Wanna just go?
Yeah, let's just go.
Hey! You can revert
them now! I'll be fine!
He's still alive with all
those scars and bruises!
Richie! Look at how sad he is
thinking about the Captain!
Now isn't the best time.
Are these really
wild beasts of hell?
Finally, he loves me back!
I'll just kill some time and...
They're not that big deal.
Looks like it's just a matter
of time before he's dead.
Impel Down is the greatest
prison in the world
Hey!
What?!
Yeah, they're not
as bad as I heard.
Oh well, I'll just ask
somebody else!
It's taking too long.
That serves you right!
I think she's being careful about doing it
because Hancock is an important figure.
and it's impossible to
break in or break out.
Level 1 was way more
terrifying than this.
The key!
Well, if you think about it, wild beasts
of hell can only really exist in...
You better just give up.
No no, it can't be!
It's stupid to even think it!
A thorough body search...
Buggy the Clown's luck
as a pirate has run out.
Wow! Do you think that's
what they're doing?!
But maybe...
That can't be true!
What was that?
What are you imagining?!
This is not the way
Captain Buggy will die!
Beep! Beep!
What's the matter?
Vice Warden Hannyabal!
Yeah! Until the day he finds
Captain John's treasure island
Alright then, good
luck with your escape!
We're not getting any visuals from the snail in
that room! Is something going on in there?!
which he has been searching
for with all his heart,
It is a wild beast of hell!
I'm sure it is!
we're gonna stand
by Captain Buggy!
Oh! This guy...
Wait a minute, Straw Hat!
Domino! Something wrong?
Captain Buggy!
--What're you...
--There he is!
Damn it! What I heard was true!
We're gonna get eaten this time for sure!
She's not answering.
--Up there!
--They found me!
What a compassionate
lion you are!
On the pretext of checking what's
going on in the room as a vice warden,
Why did you yell?!
I didn't wanna come to level 2!
H-Hey, that's a beautiful
armlet! Can I have it?
this is a chance for me to
see Hancock's body search!
I was about to make my escape without you!
Why're you so interested all of the
sudden?! This was a gift from Nami!
I'm alive...
Richie!
What? Did you say something?!
What's this creature?!
Hey!
Where am I?
I'll tell you where Ace is!
Alright, have fun!
I think it's the most
rare kind of mutant!
I'll take this Big Top so
you guys take a boat.
Really?
A snake born from a
chicken's egg - a Basilisk!
Yes! If you give it to me.
The body search is done!
Yeah, in that case!
What?!
"Prison Guard
BASILISK"
Beep! Beep!
No way! This is
Captain Buggy's ship!
Yeah!
We're getting visuals
again! Everything is fine!
These things come
from chickens?!
Okay, first, let's
lose our enemies!
I'm sorry. Did I take
too much time?
Are you kidding?
That's why they call it a monster!
But Buggy is not here!
Hold onto my feet!
Your feet?!
If it's allowed to roam
free, it'd eat everybody!
What? No no!
Oh, that's true.
Run, Straw Hat!
Everything is fine here, too!
So they leave it here as a guard!
You are...
I'm not going to march
up to death's doorstep -
I'm not happy with
this. I'm not a prisoner.
Don't drop those, Straw Hat!
Run!
and I won't let you
waste this ship.
Who do you think I am?
Negative Hollow!
Let's see how Buggy the Clown's
Chop-Chop power works!
You guys can chase after
Buggy to your heart's content.
I'm sorry. But that's the
rule here at Impel Down.
He can chop apart his body and
control each part as he wants.
It's strange. Feels like I've
lost a part of my memory...
We'll never stop
following our Captain!
But the pieces are controllable
only in a limited area and to use his power,
What're you doing?!
Lead the way now!
I don't have time for this! Alright, you!
Alright then, let's
take the big elevator.
I don't deserve to walk on the
same earth with everyone.
Whether it's to the great
prison or the end of the world!
his feet must be on the ground.
You're gonna get
your ass kicked!
Yeah!
I'm sorry.
I have a feeling that you're gonna
die before you even see Impel Down.
But that's not so bad! I'll
just make my escape!
Why are you here?
Yes! How lucky I am!
We're gonna go
down to level 4,
What about you?! Don't start
screaming all of sudden!
I'll leave the rest up to you!
Bye, Straw Hat!
the Burning Heat Floor
where Warden Magellan is.
Captain Buggy! Thank
you for everything!
Third Gear!
I can't believe that I found the treasure
I was looking for in hell like this!
Where is my sword?
It's hot there so be prepared.
We won't forget what
you've done for us!
Jailers on level 2!
I'm not gonna
return your weapon!
We identified the guy that
Buggy the Clown is with!
Have a peaceful
execution! Goodbye!
You bitch!
It's Straw Hat Luffy!
Luffy!
--That Straw Hat?!
--He's in Impel Down?!
See you in next life!
Captain! Captain!
Good luck!
Capture them right away!
Dead or alive!
Take this!
I can feel your grief, Richie!
Negative Hollow!
What do you want?
Thank you!
Let's go!
Are you really
sure that this is it?
Gum-Gum...
W-What's the matter?!
...Giant Pistol!
Is this the cave
where Captain John
This is Momonga,
marine code G100660.
I'm such a piece of garbage.
I'm sorry to be alive.
who acted so cruelly to
protect his treasure hid them?
What's this?
What happened?!
"Thank You"
We are about to sail on the current
so prepare to open the Gate!
What's going on on level 2?!
Yes, it is! Proceed carefully!
"I...
The navy ship that Luffy
and Hancock are on
...love...
O-Okay.
...you"!
is approaching
the Tub Current
He said "I love you"!
Yes! I can do anything
if I put my mind to it!
Listen, where there are treasures,
there are usually traps or guards!
which is exclusively
used by the Navy
--Hey!
--Hancock-dono! What's wrong?!
and connects three of the
government's central facilities.
One false move
and you're dead!
It's hot!
"The Great Underwater Prison
Impel Down"
Maybe there will be
some kind of monster
Yes, as Vice Warden
told you before,
Are you alright?!
What happened to
her all of sudden?
or bloody traps like
you'd see in hell!
How dare you!
the Warden's office is on level
4 - the Burning Heat Floor.
Stop talking with your
low voice! It's not cute!
The whole floor except for his
office is a burning inferno.
You serve me from
now on! Understand?
Alright, let's continue with
the tunnel construction!
Okay, we are here.
Yes, boss!
Be cute!
Now, where should I go?
Oh? You guys must
be the new crew!
Where's the Warden?
What the hell
are you doing?!
He said that the elevator was
going down to the basement.
Warden Magellan has terrible digestive
problems so he stays in a bathroom...
Yeah! Boss, I love this job!
And Hancock said that Ace
might be held underwater.
Get off of me!
I'm not alone anymore!
...for about 10
hours every day.
Right! All our sweat turns into a part of
the tunnel that will make people smile!
Oh yeah!
Shit! I can't move!
This Vivre Card would
help at a time like this!
On top of that, he needs 8 hours of sleep
and then there're mealtimes and breaks
And beer tastes so much
better after hard work!
so he usually works for
about 4 hours a day.
It's this way!
Is it enough for a warden?
Enough of this
goody-goody laborer crap!
When the need arises,
he is the right man. Oh!
What the hell?
Sorry to keep you
waiting. He is coming out.
Kumacy!
Just kill me!
What did you do to me!
We kept sailing here and there in the Grand
Line looking for the treasure after that
I forgot to mention but Warden ate
Venom-Venom Fruit so he is a poison man.
Get off of me!
Hey, new guy!
but we couldn't
find it anywhere!
A poison man?
Please be careful.
How come you're eating without first
paying respect to our cell leader?
To top it all, I was caught in a navy
post while I walked in by mistake
I'm sorry that I yelled...
It's okay as long as
you learned a lesson.
You little bitch!
and was shut up
in this prison.
Blugoris are returning!
Should I say hello every
time I eat something?
I'm sorry about my attitude.
They got food!
Open the hatch!
Screw you!
I'll call you "mistress"...
Don't be ridiculous!
But my luck has
not run out yet!
I won't!
There's a rule that a newcomer
should give his food to the boss!
I'm really sorry that
I'm being so rude.
--Thank you for your trouble!
--Thank you for your trouble, Warden!
--Good job!
--Take the meat to the refrigeration room!
Run as fast as you
can, Straw Hat!
That's enough, you idiot!
I'll lead you to the
entrance of level 2!
I don't have any
time to waste.
As always, it was
a tough battle!
Level 2? Aren't you listening?
I wanna go to level 5!
I got to go back.
You must be a guest. I'm
the warden, Magellan.
Are you awake? We'll pass
through level 1 shortly.
The exit is that way.
Listen to me, Straw Hat! You'll be
unable to go straight to level 5!
Yeah?
"The Warden of Impel Down
Magellan
(Venom-Venom Fruit Eater - Poison Man)"
Why did I tell you that?
In Impel Down, this first
basement is what they call level 1
It's too bright!
Why is it so bright in here?
That will learn ya!
Where're you going?! How
can you miss the door?!
I'd prefer to stay closed up in a dark room!
Help me!
If possible, I want to keep
my heart closed in, too!
and as you go down to
level 2, level 3 and so on,
Stop being
ridiculous! Warden,
It's worse than I expected.
you encounter more vicious
criminals who have been captured.
Vice Admiral Momonga and
Boa Hancock-dono are here!
You can't be serious.
This floor only contains
prisoners with light sentences.
I've only ever been to level
4 to be tortured by fire,
Hey!
We're a bit pressed for
time, Warden Magellan!
What? You wanna tell
me where my sword is?
I'm sorry! You see, I've got a
pretty bad case of the runs.
--What?
--She's right.
so I don't know about
the floors below.
Level 1 of Impel Down
is the Crimson Floor.
The poison soup that I had for
breakfast seems to disagree with me..
But level 5 holds the
extraordinary criminals with bounties
of hundreds of millions or more!
Why is it "Crimson"?
What do you
expect? It's poison!
That's a secret!
I'm a poison man
so I love poisons!
Y-y-y...
Next up, level 2 is the Floor
of Wild Beasts from Hell.
...you gonna leave?!
H-Hey, wait a minute! That
was just a little disagreement!
There is a saying -
"Poison quells poison."
It's none of your business!
But I heard from some prisoners
that there are more floors below!
Level 3 in the basement
is the Starvation Floor.
It's just an expression.
That's why you have diarrhea.
We're not on death
row! Get us out of here!
They said that there are heinous
monsters whose existences
You have a venomous
tongue, Hannyabal!
And level 4 that we're heading
to is the Burning Heat Floor.
have been deleted from history!
Hurry up and retire so
I can become warden...
It's just a rumor but maybe
that's where Ace is!
Oh, silly me! I meant, hurry up
and show them "Fire Fist"...
It's gonna take a
while to get to level 4.
That's terrible
mistake you made!
Anyway, I can only
lead you to level 4!
In the meantime, you'll hear the
pleasant screams of prisoners
What a heartless
colleague I have!
Alright! Suddenly you're
not such a bad guy!
so please enjoy it.
Is "Fire Fist" Ace in level 4?
Yeah, because you said
you'll give me the armlet
Put this on!
No, he isn't. We have more levels
than that and "Fire Fist" Ace is...
H-Hey! Be careful
when you exhale!
I'm not gonna let
you go so easily!
that will tell me where
Captain John's treasure is!
Luffy...
Your breath is poison gas!
You've got to deal with
me a little bit longer!
I-I shouldn't have
opened my big mouth!
Ace should be
down these stairs!
Right! That's so funny!
It has been four and half days since they
left the Maiden Island - Amazon Lily.
You're a...
That serves you right,
stupid vice warden!
Yeah?
He spews venom!
...a pretty crappy pirate
to have been caught!
Shut up! Leave me alone!
Vice Admiral Momonga! We
are arriving at Impel Down!
Hey, you cheater!
Hey you! What did you just
breathe in my face?! That's rude!
You didn't tell us that you
had that kind of ability!
H-He wasn't even paying attention!
Thank god he's such an idiot!
Hurry and open the Gate!
Aye-aye, sir!
Shut up!
Wow! What a beautiful
woman! I'm in love!
I didn't know that this armlet
functions as a treasure map!
Being tortured every day and night
here is like dying a thousand deaths!
Oh, he's so lucky...
I had no clue at all!
Vice Warden, that's
Warden's seat.
Are you gonna just
run out on us?!
It'll become mine in time.
Huh?! I don't remember
making friends with you.
"Grand Line, Namakura Island"
You were paying attention!
Damn! Then I have no choice!
We're in a hurry!
This is the Warden's office.
I'm like a free, wild eagle! If you don't
like it, why don't you do what I did!
Alright then, you
can have it now!
What are you doing
answering my phone?
No! Can't take it! Damn!
The Land of Poverty, "Harahettania"
Oh, you can't! Then you
have to die like a dog!
This is the world's
greatest prison!
I wanted to be a warden...
You know that it's a treasure map
but you're still gonna give it to me?
Get an antidote
for Vice Warden!
--Kiss my ass!
--I'll get you someday!
Aye!
Yeah! Rescuing Ace is
more important to me!
Buggy!
What?! Someone's
broken in to Impel Down?!
And don't you think that I may just take
off with it if you give it to me now?!
I already forgot about you!
That's impossible! In this prison's entire
history, no one has ever broken in!
No! Because you gave your
word that you'd lead me to Ace!
We call on you to answer us!
This is a grave error! And
you're responsible, Warden!
We call on you to answer us!
Don't look at me with
those trusting eyes!
Did they notice our plan?!
We call on you to answer us!
Transfer the video!
I'm a sly and worthless man!
We pray that all those hateful
people will be terrorized and killed!
Warden!
Can I see the prisoner now?
You shouldn't
believe a guy like me!
Grant our wish!
Okay, let's go!
I'm ready to go!
W-Warden! Don't you
realize how serious this is?!
We call on you to answer us!
I finally have Captain John's
treasure mark after all this time!
A Surveillance
Transponder Snail?!
We call on you to answer us!
Come, Satan!
Thank you, Straw Hat!
Come, Satan! Come, Satan!
We were delayed a bit
because of head winds
Grant our wish!
Now, how the hell
do I get out of here?
but we have arrived
at Impel Down!
Satan-sama! Satan-sama!
What's going on?!
They haven't replied?!
Oh boy! We have to hurry!
Get Hancock now!
It's odd! We've lost contact
with Warden Magellan!
Oh! Is it faster to break
through the wall? I got it!
Yes, sir!
Hancock-dono! We are here!
Hurry and report to the jailers' room on
each floor and to Navy Headquarters.
No, that's not what I...
I'll be right out.
Good evening!
What the hell?! They have more navy ships
here than when they did the Buster Call!
We found him!
Buggy the Clown who escaped
from community cell #4 of level 1...
I don't know why he's
here and what he's up to
This is the most dangerous
place in the world
but the guy running around with Buggy
on level 2 that we saw just now is
...is in the hallway in
front of solitary cell #22!
Get him now!
so this is necessary.
Damn! They found me!
But - you saw
the Buster Call?
the pirate, Straw Hat Luffy!
You bastard!
We can't reach the
jailers' room on level 2!
Shit!
What?!
I know it only by
what I've heard.
Damn! It's everywhere!
What's going on?!
Surveillance Transponder
Snail #71 has been shut off!
Did you hear
that? It's Buggy!
Just keep trying
until they reply!
It was an all-out attack by five vice
admirals with a fleet of ten ships,
That's what happens when you try to
escape alone! That serves him right!
Yes, sir!
Jailers' room on level
2! What's wrong?!
and the strongest military
operation by the Navy.
He's gonna get the
worst punishment!
Come in, jailers' room!
Here comes Blugoris!
Go for it!
I wonder how Luffy's doing.
Is this where Ace is?
Yes!
Get him!
His fist became huge!
I warned him not to
get into any trouble...
I think he is being
held deep underwater.
Gum-Gum...
They built this place as a
fort that locks people in.
...Giant Pistol!
Now, get into my cloak.
This Vivre Card keeps
leading me down but...
Don't get in any trouble.
And why are you
so small now?!
...it's a dead end.
'Cause it's Third Gear.
Once they catch you, you'll
never be able to get out.
I hardly beat it!
I know that you're strong
Okay, I'm reverted!
It's prisoner #8200!
Is-Is this the Devil?
but promise me that you
won't get in any trouble.
Don't let him get away!
Let's go now!
The black magic
really worked!
Thank you for coming,
Vice Admiral Momonga!
The God of salvation
has descended to hell!
Alright! I promise!
He was hiding the fact that he ate Devil
Fruit! Don't forget a Sea Prism Stone!
Amazing! He
defeated the monster!
What a dreadful figure!
Thank you so
much, Hancock!
He's definitely unearthly!
Hancock...
Hancock ...ncock...
He beat the Basilisk!
Hurry up!
Split into two and get
him from both sides!
You did it! You
guys are awesome!
Our prayer will be answered!
Oh, Luffy! I can hear your
heavenly voice in my heart!
W-Wow! L-L-Look at her!
They have destroyed
the jailers' room, too.
We must have our revenge!
Yes! Made it!
It's unbelievable! They
must be sent from heaven!
--There is nothing left for us!
--The Long-arm Tribe took everything from us!
Hurry up!
That's the pirate empress! She's the
most beautiful woman in the world!
Okay, it's about time!
What happened?
I don't know who you
are but thank you!
Her beauty has no limit!
"Level 1: Crimson Floor"
Satan-sama, the king of
devils! If our wish come true,
How many volts is the power of
her beauty?! 10,000? 1,000,000?
Can you get us keys, too?
For the doors and cuffs!
Mmm! What a
pleasant scream!
we are all prepared to
sell our souls to you!
Are these all cells?
Hey, they're right
there on the ground!
Seems like jailers
doing pretty well.
What's that noise?
It hurts my ears.
Leave them all bloodied!
He is...
Did you like it,
Hancock-dono?
A scream? Forget it
- I gotta get going!
Let's keep going!
The king of devils, Satan-sama!
Can I turn them to stone?
Oh, you didn't hear it?
Don't rush!
I don't have time!
The king of devils,
Satan-sama!
Sorry about that!
...Straw Hat Luffy!
Why is he here?!
But there is one more
chance so please do enjoy it!
Please don't.
The Navy can't take
any more humiliation.
Go away! Jerks!
Well, he's not in a cell - looks
like he's on his way out!
How far have I
been carried away?
I don't care about screams! I can't hear
the voice in my heart because of you!
Are we already inside?
I've gotta take this
chance, it's now or never!
Help me!
Not yet.
I don't know what I did wrong
but she's stepping on me!
Don't rush, Luffy.
What happen to Luffy
and the others?!
Heaven hasn't
forgotten me yet!
Why? I'm a vice warden!
The condition
you named was
Don't do that, Hancock-dono!
to see the key figure of this whole
mess, Portgaz D. Ace, wasn't it?
This way!
But I'm kinda enjoying this!
I must go back to meet them!
Hey, you guys! Is this
what you're looking for?
What?
Oops! Did I say
that out loud?!
Like I told you the other day,
W-Wait a minute! Don't go
back to Hell, Satan-sama!
pirates are not welcomed here
even though you're a Warlord.
--Of course, we want it!
--Give it to me now!
--Try to stop him!
--Maybe we haven't offered him enough!
They're gone!
What? Is that how you ask
somebody for a favor?
So we'll put handcuffs made
of Sea Prism Stone on you
"DANGER"? It's not like
anyone is gonna touch it...
What does
Satan-sama want?!
We're sorry! We're
begging you!
and we'll conduct a strict
body search before you go in.
A sacrifice? Some blood?
There's no excuse!
Please, sir!
What should we do?
What should we offer to
make him grant our wish?!
Who are they?!
What? What d'you
say? I can't hear you!
Because we don't want any ploys
to free any of our prisoners.
That's Buggy the
Clown who escaped...
And who is the other one?!
What're you doing?
This is the jailers' room!
Then we shouldn't go this way!
Please, sir!
What the...?!
What do I want?
Luffy, they'll
search my body.
Alright! I'm giving you this!
It's a favor of Captain
Buggy-sama! Accept it gratefully!
Stop! Straw Fool!
I'll figure out a
way. Just go on.
Wait!
I don't mind.
What?! Buggy the Clown
has vanished from his cell?
That was close!
Yeah! We're free!
What the hell is this?
A forest in the prison?!
He ate a Devil Fruit?
We're out of the cells!
I didn't see that coming!
Vice Warden! Vice Admiral Momonga and
Hancock-dono of the Seven Warlords arrived.
Hey! The traps over
here have gone off!
It's a crimson forest!
Oh no! Somebody's coming!
There are so many people!
Alright, I'll be there.
Stop!
Thank me, you idiots!
They're prisoners!
This is not just a forest!
Wow, c-c-cute! Open
the gate please!
Tell me who has set you free!
Let's go!
Excuse me.
Captain Buggy!
We're indebted to you forever!
Leaves are as sharp as blade
because they're Blade Trees!
Open it fully! Give her space!
Could I look at your panties?
Oh? Looks like they
aren't coming. Oh, well!
Captain Buggy is our savior!
U-Underwear! Hurry and
show him your underwear!
The grass is actually needles
which prick  your body!
Yes, I am! Don't you
ever forget my name!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
It's called Spike Needle Grass!
Now, unlock all the cells!
Chased by loosed venomous
spiders and jailers,
Young man!
What?!
I fell down here by chance, but if I start
chaos, it'll give me a chance to get out!
prisoners run around the forest
Wait a minute! How
did you get out?
Um...
I don't need to see the
guys' underwear. Wow!
and get cut by leaves and
grasses which shed their blood
Here we go, Luffy!
What's the matter?
Get out? I got
in from outside!
Returning to the present, to rescue his
brother Ace from prison,
--Alright, are you happy now? Now, it's my turn!
--Let me go! Let me go! You fool!
Okay, bye!
causing them to agonize!
Take care!
Wait, wait! Quit lying, you!
Luffy speeds steadily over the waves
to the Great Prison - Impel Down!
--Lead me now!
--Hey! Straw Hat!
Hancock-sama!
Have a nice visit!
It's true!
This is level 1 -
the Crimson Hell!
Is there any hole
like the last time?
Who are you? You don't look
like a jailer or something.
Something stinks! It reeks!
Shut up, you idiots!
That is Impel Down!
I don't know the
way to level 3!
Don't be so mean!
And take care!
"The Underwater Prison - Impel Down - Level 1
Crimson Hell"
Why aren't you behind bars?
Help me!
How can I remember all floors
of this maze-like prison?
I can't stand it!
Man, you guys are irritating!
Whew! Couldn't eat another
bite! That was so good!
Oh yeah! Do you
know where Ace is?
This is a real hell! Is this the kind
of thing they're doing to Ace?
Thank you, Captain Buggy!
Luffy!
Ace?
I can smell freedom...
Don't forget that
you are a stowaway.
This Ace that you're
talking about is...
Yes! Let's just keep falling!
Help me!
Why?! We're gonna get cut!
S-S-Somebody!
"Fire Fist" Ace?!
I'm not gonna get cut!
Just shut up and hang on!
Get me out!
Yeah! I'm here to rescue him!
Hancock! Is anybody
else in your room?
What a dark atmosphere!
This must be hell.
Straw Hat! My feet! Throw
them to the ground!
That's impossible!
Oh, damn!
Lieutenant Stalker, did you
really hear someone else?
Yeah, I heard that
he just got in.
Ugh! Stop, Straw Hat!
Yes! I'm sure that I heard "Whew!
Couldn't eat another bite!"
Your feet?
Finally, we got in! But
we're not in the clear yet.
Why should I?! You said
that you'd lead me to level 4!
Ah! Okay!
They must have put him on level
5. You can't get anywhere near it!
I lied, I lied! I wanted the
treasure so I lied to you!
I don't think the
empress would say that.
Impossible!
Welcome to my Impel Down!
That floor holds all the criminals with
bounties of hundreds of millions or more!
Those prisoners are gonna run
rampant on this floor and...
It can't be!
Oh, I got it wrong! I said
"my" - jumping the gun!
If that was her, I'll give
myself a Mohawk!
W-What is that?!
You lied to me?!
I'll do that, too!
Level 5?
Augh! Watch out!
I'm still the vice warden,
Hannyabal. Nice to meet you!
By the way, young man,
can you run to the jailers'
room and bring us some keys?
What's that?
Once I get my feet on the
ground, it's a piece of cake!
We don't need to use stairs
to go down from this floor!
W-Whew! Couldn't
eat another bite!
I'm Momonga.
Yeah! Please, young man!
I knew that you were coming.
It must be fate that brought
us together in this big world!
We don't need a key to
open the door to the stairs!
And you're Empress
Hancock-dono?
She said it!
I just remembered that there's a way to
escape the agony of the Crimson Hell!
You're my Empress
Hancock-dono?
I'm done. Take these plates.
Right?
What're you doing?! It's your
chance to break out in chaos!
Oh no, I'm sorry! That
was over-ambitious!
Don't forget the amount.
I need it five times a day.
There's a way out of hell?
The dumb-ass-warden...
Oh, sorry!
W-What's that?
Isn't that a bit much?!
We just had a dose of reality!
That's Blugori!
The Warden Magellan is in his office on
level 4 and I would like you to meet him.
What about our food?!
Blugori?
There's no way to escape if the
boss of this floor is still here!
Run, young man!
They're gonna get you!
I don't care if you
starve to death!
Yeah, it's safer to be in a cell.
She's terrible!
Look! This is it!
But, beautiful!
Vice Jail Manager Domino
and I will guide you.
It's a hole!
O-Okay, Straw Hat! I'll
guide you to level 3!
6 days left for the public
execution of Portgaz D. Ace!
Wow! It's as dark as night!
Augh! What're those?!
It seems like you are in a rush so
let me ask you to come this way.
You just said that you don't
know the way, Big Nose!
This is the way out but nobody
wants to escape from here.
Vice Admiral-dono, you can go that way.
I'm afraid I have to conduct a body search.
What did you just call me?!
Right side!
After having all their guard
ships destroyed by Whitebeard,
Left side!
If you're having trouble on
this floor, I can help you.
Do you know
why, Straw Hat?
tensions at Navy
Headquarters are rising.
If you were a prisoner, we'd ask you to go inside
of this cell and take off all of your clothes,
Unite!
Because this hole is
connected to level 2
Who is that guy?
Renowned marines started assembling at the
harbor of Marinford from various regions.
You fools! Don't mess with
a Chop-Chop Fruit eater!
then we'd push you into an iron pot filled with
"the warm water of hell" boiling at 200 degrees
which is an even
more terrifying hell!
Long time no see,
Straw Hat Luffy!
You helped me out
without noticing.
There may be people who try to
escape from hell back to earth
I always pay back my debts.
to receive your baptism and get sterilized at
the same time and you would be ready to enter.
Wow! Straw Hat!
but there aren't people stupid
enough to descend deeper into hell!
Who are you?
What're you doing here?!
There are different
classes of prisoners.
Well, this is good for us!
We can just jump down!
Oh, that's 3! That means...
Yow! Look at that weird hair!
Among all recent
newcomers, "Fire Fist" Ace,
Yeah but down below,
there's... No, wait! Hey!
Shut up!
And it's on fire!
Take that! Candle Lock!
Jimbei of the Seven Warlords
and the former Warlord Crocodile
Wow, it's deep! I wonder
what's down there!
In the name of justice, the machines of war were
steadily being built up at Navy Headquarters.
Oh, this is perfect!
Oh, it's just Buggy.
Gum-Gum...
didn't turn a hair while receiving baptism
and entered prison very smoothly.
Ha! What a hotfoot!
Right! Shut up! You asshole!
...Mallet!
He isn't afraid of anything?
You're as annoying as ever!
I didn't know that
they also got you!
But at least now he can't
stop me if I just take off!
Meanwhile, in the
Holyland of Marejois...
Now, can you tell
which is the real me?
Please come in. We search guests
in a private room so don't worry.
I came here on my own
will! No one got me!
You're just a powerful fool who acts
only on instinct. You can't catch me!
Nobody comes to a
prison on his own will!
The Seven Warlords of the Sea
who had already been summoned
were told the locations of their battle positions.
Ah? Don't tell me that you
heard that I was captured
I am Mr. 3! I always get
the job done perfectly!
Now I'm free! I finally got the treasure
mark that I always dreamed of!
But they are all ruffians who
can be tamed by no one.
I'd like you to take
off your cloak.
and that you came
here to rescue me...
Gum-Gum...
Those are well-suited for hide
something inside so I'll take it here.
No way! Stupid!
That's gross!
Find your own way!
Good-bye, Straw Hat!
...Stamp!
One thing is certain:
Cut it out! Bastard!
How did you know
where I was...?
It is impossible for them to
cooperate and fight together.
Down to level 3 or level 4 - it doesn't
matter either way you're a goner!
It's not like I don't trust you but you
better not do anything suspicious.
I promised Hancock that I
wouldn't get into any trouble
but you got me involved!
Surveillance Transponder Snails are
everywhere inside of Impel Down
Instinct.
It's not like I'm
enjoying this situation!
You were on the island with
the Giants! You are San!
Stupid Blugori! You can't chop
me because I ate Chop-Chop fruit!
Let me go!
No, I'm Mr. Three!
and they keep sending video
to the surveillance monitors.
Wow! This is the
pirate empress!
"Prisoner Number D-0464
Former Baroque Works Agent
Mr. 3"
She's as beautiful
as they say!
O-Old man!
Snails! Let me see
Hancock-sama more clearly!
That's...
Fleet Admiral Sengoku! We just got an
emergency report from Impel Down!
...my feet!
Close-up! Zoom
in for a close-up!
How can you still live with
all those terrible wounds?
Hmmm? What happened? Don't
tell me it's about Whitebeard.
Wow! Cute!
No! You got to
be kidding me!
No, Straw Hat Luffy
has infiltrated.
Buggy's Peaceful Escape
Plan is officially ruined!
Ace!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
What?! Straw Hat?
What's going on?
Now, let's just start.
Who gives a shit?
I thought that Bartholomew
Kuma took care of him.
Because of you, the
Navy Headquarters -
Let me put these Sea Prism
Stone handcuffs on you.
Surveillance Room!
There is another guy!
No! All of the World
Government! - is a mess.
Yes, that's what we heard.
They're ahead of us, too!
I'm not a prisoner but
you put handcuffs on me.
They just fell down to level 2!
Can you look for them?
Damn it all!
But why would a pirate
sneak into Impel Down?
You couldn't be more careful.
Hey! Should we just fight?!
I got it!
What're you
thinking, stupid?!
What is he up to?
K-Kill me!
You don't know how painful
all the torture's been!
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
I don't know what he wants but this
time, it's the end of the road for him.
They're so cold-blooded!
You should kill me!
--Doesn't matter if we don't get caught!
--What're you talking about?
Because the place
he finds himself...
"The Underwater Prison - Impel Down - Level 2
Floor of Wild Beasts From Hell"
Kill you?
W-What's going on?
I gotta hurry! My cover's
already been blown!
The beasts unusually agitated!
You idiot! Nothing
can stop it now!
Are they hungry or something?
Even if you die now, that won't
prevent Whitebeard from fighting!
...is a prison that has held hundreds
of thousands of prisoners in the past
That's what I don't like
about you and Red-Haired!
without allowing even a
single breakout or escape.
You guys always stay
positive in a bad sense!
Nobody can stop it now.
It's a truly iron-tight, great
prison - Impel Down!
I have no energy
left to be afraid.
We made the
king of the sea...
Either way we're
gonna be their dinner.
Of course, it's their blunder to
let him enter in the first place
Alright! I'll do it!
I have no choice!
...angry!
but there is absolutely no way that
the kid will walk out of there alive!
I'll change my plan!
Oh no! There was one guy...
There was?
Now for some chaos!
I'm with you!
Twenty years ago, he became the first and
only escapee in the history of Impel Down.
He's a pirate named
Shiki the Golden Lion.
Public execution of Ace...
Shiki the Golden Lion?
...is in 33 hours!
Father!
Twenty years ago, one man
Luffy and Buggy fall down to level 2,
Luffy joins up with Buggy,
Luffy parts ways with Hancock and
infiltrates the prison alone.
Setting aside his concern for his crew,
became the first and only escapee
in the history of Impel Down.
and they use Buggy's Chop-Chop
Fruit power to get through
Luffy heads to Impel Down to save Ace.
where beasts of fearsome strength roam.
He slips through the guard
to search for Ace's floor,
His name was Shiki the Golden Lion.
the prison and find Ace's floor.
This is the floor of the wild beasts of hell.
An inescapable prison for
the most terrible criminals.
but he finds it harder than he
thought to penetrate Impel Down's
But level 1 of the prison, the Crimson Hell,
In the present, the Straw Hats encounter
a giant beetle while sailing the seas
Meanwhile, Hancock reaches
the heart of the prison,
iron-tight security.
shows its terrifying true
form and impedes their path.
Will Luffy be able to reach his brother, Ace?
Just then, that man with
the red nose appears!
where she encounters Warden Magellan.
and find themselves caught
up in Shiki's ambitions.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Strongest Man in the Prison!
Poison Man Magellan Appears!"
"Break through the Crimson Hell!
Buggy's Chaos-Inducing Plan!"
"A Reunion in Hell?! The Man
Who Ate the Chop-Chop Fruit!"
"A Special Presentation Related to the Movie!
A Gold Lion's Ambition on the Move!"
"A Deadly Infiltration! The
Underwater Prison Impel Down!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!