Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the
Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way
to the New World,
will speed along the
Grand Line again today!
After being separated
from his friends,
Luffy comes to the rescue his brother
Ace who has been captured by the Navy
by sneaking into Impel Down -
the greatest prison in the world!
Now, he is racing to level 5 with
a help of Buggy the Clown.
Now I'm free! I finally got the treasure
mark that I always dreamed of!
Down to level 3 or level 4 - it doesn't
matter either way you're a goner!
Stupid Blugori! You can't chop
me because I ate Chop-Chop fruit!
"The Strongest Man in the Prison!
Poison Man Magellan Appears!"
I just finished breaking out of my
cell! I don't wanna fall to another hell!
Ow, ow, ow...
This is pretty creepy!
But, at least now I have this which means
I'm seconds away from finding
Captain John's treasure!
All I have to do is
find my way out of...
Okay, let's go!
Tell me the way!
W-W-Wait a second!
It's a dead end!
So this is level 2...
Yes!
It's worse than the Crimson Hell of
level 1! It's called Wild Beast Hell!
You bastard! You had
me running like an idiot!
This floor has all the wild
beasts of hell everywhere!
Wild beasts of hell?
Damn it! Well, until I get
a chance to run away,
I'll take full advantage
of Straw Hat!
Is that one of them?
They found us already!
It looks like a hippo to me.
Um, yeah.
It's smaller than a regular hippo. Is
that what you'd call a "wild beast"?
It's odd! I heard
that level 2 has...
Augh! What's
this thing?! Run!
Wow! He's pretty
fast for a hippo!
Stop admiring it!
Turn left here!
He crashed into the wall!
He runs pretty fast but can
only run in a straight line!
So you really don't mind
that your body got eaten?!
You'll see! I'm the Chop-Chop
man - Buggy-sama!
How did you manage that?
Even if my body parts are chopped
to pieces, I can move them as I want!
That will learn ya!
You little hippo!
Who is that guy with Buggy?
Isn't there any way I can
just get out of here?!
What's wrong?
I think I saw something!
A bat, maybe?
Chop-Chop Quick Escape!
It's a monster mantis!
Yeah, it's too big
for a mantis...
He cuts like a pro!
How can you be
so impressed?!
If I get chopped up much
more, it'll be a big problem!
You're an amazing fighter!
How can you be so relaxed?
--Do you think he's stuck?
--Yeah.
What should we do?
Well, maybe we should...
Wanna just go?
Yeah, let's just go.
Are these really
wild beasts of hell?
They're not that big deal.
Yeah, they're not
as bad as I heard.
Level 1 was way more
terrifying than this.
Well, if you think about it, wild beasts
of hell can only really exist in...
What was that?
What's the matter?
It is a wild beast of hell!
Oh! This guy...
Damn it! What I heard was true!
We're gonna get eaten this time for sure!
I didn't wanna come to level 2!
I was about to make my escape without you!
What? Did you say something?!
What's this creature?!
I think it's the most
rare kind of mutant!
A snake born from a
chicken's egg - a Basilisk!
"Prison Guard
BASILISK"
These things come
from chickens?!
Are you kidding?
That's why they call it a monster!
If it's allowed to roam
free, it'd eat everybody!
So they leave it here as a guard!
What're you doing?!
I don't have time for this! Alright, you!
You're gonna get
your ass kicked!
But that's not so bad! I'll
just make my escape!
I'll leave the rest up to you!
Bye, Straw Hat!
Third Gear!
Jailers on level 2!
We identified the guy that
Buggy the Clown is with!
It's Straw Hat Luffy!
--That Straw Hat?!
--He's in Impel Down?!
Capture them right away!
Dead or alive!
Let's go!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Pistol!
What's this?
What happened?!
What's going on on level 2?!
It's hot!
Yes, as Vice Warden
told you before,
the Warden's office is on level
4 - the Burning Heat Floor.
The whole floor except for his
office is a burning inferno.
Okay, we are here.
Where's the Warden?
Warden Magellan has terrible digestive
problems so he stays in a bathroom...
...for about 10
hours every day.
On top of that, he needs 8 hours of sleep
and then there're mealtimes and breaks
so he usually works for
about 4 hours a day.
Is it enough for a warden?
When the need arises,
he is the right man. Oh!
Sorry to keep you
waiting. He is coming out.
I forgot to mention but Warden ate
Venom-Venom Fruit so he is a poison man.
A poison man?
Please be careful.
--Thank you for your trouble!
--Thank you for your trouble, Warden!
As always, it was
a tough battle!
You must be a guest. I'm
the warden, Magellan.
"The Warden of Impel Down
Magellan
(Venom-Venom Fruit Eater - Poison Man)"
It's too bright!
Why is it so bright in here?
I'd prefer to stay closed up in a dark room!
If possible, I want to keep
my heart closed in, too!
Stop being
ridiculous! Warden,
Vice Admiral Momonga and
Boa Hancock-dono are here!
We're a bit pressed for
time, Warden Magellan!
I'm sorry! You see, I've got a
pretty bad case of the runs.
The poison soup that I had for
breakfast seems to disagree with me..
What do you
expect? It's poison!
I'm a poison man
so I love poisons!
There is a saying -
"Poison quells poison."
It's just an expression.
That's why you have diarrhea.
You have a venomous
tongue, Hannyabal!
Hurry up and retire so
I can become warden...
Oh, silly me! I meant, hurry up
and show them "Fire Fist"...
That's terrible
mistake you made!
What a heartless
colleague I have!
Put this on!
H-Hey! Be careful
when you exhale!
Your breath is poison gas!
Right! That's so funny!
That serves you right,
stupid vice warden!
He spews venom!
Hey you! What did you just
breathe in my face?! That's rude!
Wow! What a beautiful
woman! I'm in love!
Oh, he's so lucky...
Vice Warden, that's
Warden's seat.
It'll become mine in time.
We're in a hurry!
This is the Warden's office.
What are you doing
answering my phone?
No! Can't take it! Damn!
I wanted to be a warden...
Get an antidote
for Vice Warden!
Aye!
What?! Someone's
broken in to Impel Down?!
That's impossible! In this prison's entire
history, no one has ever broken in!
This is a grave error! And
you're responsible, Warden!
Did they notice our plan?!
Transfer the video!
Warden!
Can I see the prisoner now?
Okay, let's go!
I'm ready to go!
W-Warden! Don't you
realize how serious this is?!
What's going on?!
They haven't replied?!
It's odd! We've lost contact
with Warden Magellan!
Hurry and report to the jailers' room on
each floor and to Navy Headquarters.
I don't know why he's
here and what he's up to
but the guy running around with Buggy
on level 2 that we saw just now is
the pirate, Straw Hat Luffy!
We can't reach the
jailers' room on level 2!
What?!
Damn! It's everywhere!
What's going on?!
Just keep trying
until they reply!
Yes, sir!
Jailers' room on level
2! What's wrong?!
Come in, jailers' room!
Yes!
His fist became huge!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Pistol!
And why are you
so small now?!
'Cause it's Third Gear.
I hardly beat it!
Okay, I'm reverted!
Let's go now!
The God of salvation
has descended to hell!
Amazing! He
defeated the monster!
He beat the Basilisk!
You did it! You
guys are awesome!
They have destroyed
the jailers' room, too.
It's unbelievable! They
must be sent from heaven!
I don't know who you
are but thank you!
Can you get us keys, too?
For the doors and cuffs!
Hey, they're right
there on the ground!
He is...
Let's keep going!
Don't rush!
I don't have time!
...Straw Hat Luffy!
Why is he here?!
Well, he's not in a cell - looks
like he's on his way out!
I've gotta take this
chance, it's now or never!
Heaven hasn't
forgotten me yet!
Hey, you guys! Is this
what you're looking for?
--Of course, we want it!
--Give it to me now!
What? Is that how you ask
somebody for a favor?
We're sorry! We're
begging you!
There's no excuse!
Please, sir!
What? What d'you
say? I can't hear you!
What're you doing?
Please, sir!
Alright! I'm giving you this!
It's a favor of Captain
Buggy-sama! Accept it gratefully!
Yeah! We're free!
We're out of the cells!
Thank me, you idiots!
Tell me who has set you free!
Captain Buggy!
We're indebted to you forever!
Captain Buggy is our savior!
Yes, I am! Don't you
ever forget my name!
Now, unlock all the cells!
I fell down here by chance, but if I start
chaos, it'll give me a chance to get out!
--Alright, are you happy now? Now, it's my turn!
--Let me go! Let me go! You fool!
--Lead me now!
--Hey! Straw Hat!
Is there any hole
like the last time?
I don't know the
way to level 3!
How can I remember all floors
of this maze-like prison?
Thank you, Captain Buggy!
I can smell freedom...
Ugh! Stop, Straw Hat!
Why should I?! You said
that you'd lead me to level 4!
I lied, I lied! I wanted the
treasure so I lied to you!
Those prisoners are gonna run
rampant on this floor and...
You lied to me?!
What's that?
What're you doing?! It's your
chance to break out in chaos!
We just had a dose of reality!
There's no way to escape if the
boss of this floor is still here!
Yeah, it's safer to be in a cell.
O-Okay, Straw Hat! I'll
guide you to level 3!
You just said that you don't
know the way, Big Nose!
What did you just call me?!
If you're having trouble on
this floor, I can help you.
Who is that guy?
Long time no see,
Straw Hat Luffy!
You helped me out
without noticing.
I always pay back my debts.
Who are you?
Oh, that's 3! That means...
Yow! Look at that weird hair!
Shut up!
And it's on fire!
Take that! Candle Lock!
Oh, this is perfect!
Gum-Gum...
...Mallet!
Now, can you tell
which is the real me?
You're just a powerful fool who acts
only on instinct. You can't catch me!
I am Mr. 3! I always get
the job done perfectly!
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp!
How did you know
where I was...?
Instinct.
You were on the island with
the Giants! You are San!
No, I'm Mr. Three!
"Prisoner Number D-0464
Former Baroque Works Agent
Mr. 3"
Fleet Admiral Sengoku! We just got an
emergency report from Impel Down!
Hmmm? What happened? Don't
tell me it's about Whitebeard.
No, Straw Hat Luffy
has infiltrated.
What?! Straw Hat?
What's going on?
I thought that Bartholomew
Kuma took care of him.
Yes, that's what we heard.
But why would a pirate
sneak into Impel Down?
What is he up to?
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
I don't know what he wants but this
time, it's the end of the road for him.
Because the place
he finds himself...
...is a prison that has held hundreds
of thousands of prisoners in the past
without allowing even a
single breakout or escape.
It's a truly iron-tight, great
prison - Impel Down!
Of course, it's their blunder to
let him enter in the first place
but there is absolutely no way that
the kid will walk out of there alive!
Oh no! There was one guy...
There was?
Twenty years ago, he became the first and
only escapee in the history of Impel Down.
He's a pirate named
Shiki the Golden Lion.
Shiki the Golden Lion?
Twenty years ago, one man
became the first and only escapee
in the history of Impel Down.
His name was Shiki the Golden Lion.
In the present, the Straw Hats encounter
a giant beetle while sailing the seas
and find themselves caught
up in Shiki's ambitions.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Special Presentation Related to the Movie!
A Gold Lion's Ambition on the Move!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!