Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the
Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Impel Down - the great prison that holds
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
villainous prisoners from all over the world.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
The world's greatest prison - so heavily
guarded - has just been breached!
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
He has come to rescue his brother "Fire
Fist" Ace who will soon be executed.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
He is Straw Hat Luffy.
The crew, on its way
to the New World,
However...
will speed along the
Grand Line again today!
twenty years ago...
Luffy and his friends
chased after a big beetle
In order to become brothers
of the legendary pirate Shiki,
Luffy and others had been captured by Largo,
After being separated from his friends,
which appeared suddenly during their journey,
there was a man who had broken
out of the iron-tight Impel Down!
Luffy comes to rescue his brother Ace
who has been captured by the Navy
the Amigo Pirates came to the
island to catch the big beetle!
in order to recruit him, and in doing
so they reached an unknown island.
captain of the Amigo Pirates,
with his Net-Net power.
by sneaking into Impel Down - the
greatest prison in the world!
Alright, you giant beetle! Join my...
If you don't wanna get killed,
let us have the beetle!
Even if you are a rubberman, I will
not let you get away with it, senor!
The giant beetle doesn't want to join
a pirate crew! Just give up on him!
My boss...
Luffy is now at level 2 - Wild
Beast Hell with Buggy the Clown.
But Boss, the big beetle, tried to
sacrifice himself to save the island...
...will never become...
This can't be real! He cut off his own legs!
...a pirate!
You got me wrong, stupid!
I'm here to catch him!
It is a wild beast of hell!
With this beetle as their guardian angel,
Wait!
This legendary person is...
Yoko, a girl who hates pirates and...
Can't you hear what I'm saying!
...the people from the same ocean
live on this island called...
Damn it!
Gum-Gum...
"Golden Lion"
...Giant Pistol!
Mucho Needle Net!
This is Kansorn Island where people
from the East Blue live together!
...the captain of the Flying Pirates,
What?! Someone's broken in to Impel Down?!
Ow, ow, ow... Ouch!
Boss, after shedding his skin,
It also known as Little East Blue!
then cut down the nets which
held Luffy and the others.
Shiki the Golden Lion!
That's impossible! No one has ever
broken in all the prison's history!
Luffy!
Meanwhile, the Amigo Pirates, working on
orders from the legendary pirate Shiki...
Even if you are a rubberman, I will
not let you get away with it, senor!
This is a story of what
happened several days ago...
Did they notice our plan?!
...are heading to Kansorn Island as well!
...before Shiki the Golden Lion
faced Luffy and his friends!
Transfer the video!
"A Special Presentation Related to the Movie!
The Fierce Onslaught of the Amigo Pirates!"
Warden!
Can I see the prisoner now?
"A Special Presentation Related to the
Movie! Little East Blue in Danger!"
"A Special Presentation Related to the Movie!
A Gold Lion's Ambition on the Move!"
Okay, let's go! I'm ready to go!
Oh no! It was too soon to
shed his skin as I thought!
W-Warden! Don't you realize
how serious this is?!
Crying or screaming won't help anymore!
I can't believe this!
If you're having trouble on
this floor, I can help you.
There's no way to defeat her!
We got your guardian angel as you see!
You won sixty-nine out of sixty-nine...
Who is that guy?
It's not over yet!
Robin-san, you're so good at it.
Reefs surround the island. It's
too dangerous to speed up.
Long time no see, Straw Hat Luffy!
We won't let his last breath...
Hmm... I don't think that it's
possible to make such a clean sweep!
...be wasted.
You helped me out without noticing.
Thank you, Giant Beetle!
I always pay back my debts.
Ready?
Oh? Are you suspecting that I
cheated? Do you have any proof?
Now, it's showtime!
Nami-sama!
Who are you?
Over here! It's this way!
Well...
Oh, that's 3! That means...
Captain! Colt-san!
What the... hell...
"A Special Presentation Related to the Movie!
Luffy vs. Largo The Battle is on!"
You were on the island with
the Giants! You are San!
Ah? What?
What was that?!
We have word from Big Boss Shiki!
No, I'm Mr.Three!
It must be from behind the mountain.
L-Look at her! Nami-sama in
person is there in front of us!
Do you think Nami-san and others are okay?
Maybe they're having a hard
time catching the beetle.
She's mega cute, way more
than the wanted poster!
I can't help crying! I'm
so happy to be alive!
Let's go help them!
"A Warlord in Prison! Jimbei
the First Son of the Sea!"
Well, finally! We've waited so long!
Yeah, yeah!
W-Who are you people?
What can three burned men
Bring a Transponder Snail here!
To be honest, when I was assigned
to this floor I thought I was dead,
Thank you for asking!
and some weak sea idiots
with pathetic weapons do...
Yes! Right away!
We're members of the unofficial
Nami-sama fan club...
Big Bro, we did it! If we
can join Shiki's party,
but it's surprisingly peaceful.
...at this last moment?!
Known as Orenami Group!
It couldn't be any other way.
Orenami?
it's gonna be our chance
to become successful!
"Big Bro"?
Yes! L...!
What kind of floor did you think it would be?
O...!
V...!
It's obvious! We want the Giant Beetle!
This lowest floor holds the
worst villains with more
E...!
Are they related?
We love you! Nami-sama!
Boss!
than a 100 million berry price...
Give him back!
Stop it! That's so irritating!
...or other infamous menaces.
That's why the security here is so tight
Ow!
and that's why it's called Eternal
Hell -the worst floor for
Thank you!
Take me to see Luffy, already!
prisoners to be held on.
Go ahead, make my day!
Yes, it's our pleasure, Nami-sama!
Augh! What is this?! It's all tangled up!
Zoro! Cut that net!
Well, the only chance for them
to get out from the deep sea...
For God's sake...
Okay.
Damn you!
How stupid are you?
Can you stop calling me Nami-sama?
There's no use in doing that.
You know that your sword
is too dull to cut my net.
Yes, Nami-sama!
and get sunshine is when
they go to their execution.
The more you struggle,
the tighter the net gets.
Ah! Feels great!
B-Big Bro? Why are you crying?
Death is maybe easier...
We'll see about that!
This is awesome!
Choking to death like that at your age...
...than spending the rest
of your life in this hell.
Do you like it?
Amore! My beloved brother Colt!
...makes me think how
cruel this world can be...
Lion Strike!
Maybe!
I am very sad!
You're from Windmill Village so
they must be familiar to you.
Hey! The Warden and Vice Warden
are on their way with Boa Hancock.
No way!
Yeah, but none of ours were this big!
You're the vice captain of
the Amigo Pirates, right?
If the plan of senor
Shiki is put into action,
We gotta fight, too!
I wonder why the pirate empress
wants to see "Fire Fist" Ace.
How would you explain
this shameful situation?
Wait a minute!
the world will be filled with sorrow.
That windmill is like a
symbol for Little East Blue.
Oh, I'm sorry! I heard the big beetle
is the guardian of this island
When I think about hearing
thousands of despairing voices,
Yeah, he is the most dangerous
prisoner in Impel Down,
Second Gear!
Sanji! Shoot me over there!
See? This is the training hall!
I mean, maybe in the whole world now.
it makes me very very sad...
so we tried to give them a scare
and make them bring out the beetle
Hmmm...
Alright!
I don't want any trouble.
Get ready, Net Man!
but then that guy stepped in!
Why should I?
Speaking of dangerous men, that
guy who is a Warlord like Hancock
Here is a Transponder Snail!
A big beetle? Oh, I thought
we're here for a stag beetle.
Armee de L'Air Assault Gum Shoot!
Good! Put him through!
who rebelled against Navy Headquarters
is also pretty dangerous.
Jet Bullet!
Are you the captain of
Amigo Pirates - Mr. Largo?
You never pay attention! How many
times do I have to tell you?!
No, I'm a vice captain Colt.
Tell me what you want.
Get the rest!
It's a beetle! A big beetle!
Alright!
All right.
Big Bro got taken down?
I called to let you know that we have decided
Yeah?
I’m here to challenge you!
No, he was just off-guard! He can't
have been beaten by that kid!
Then maybe the beetle that
I saw on the way here
I am...
to welcome Mr. Largo to Big
Boss Shiki's assembly...
Against me?
was the one you're talking about...
Sure.
...as our 51st pirate captain.
To be recognized by Big Boss Shiki...
...not going to run!
Whaaat?!
Oh, shoot!
--No surprise there!
--However...
You have to keep moving!
...there is a condition to
your attending the assembly
Boss! Can you hear me? Boss!
Did you get hurt, maybe a bit?
and we need to ask you to fulfill that first.
I can't even move to scratch an itch.
Now I remember!
Where did you see it, Big Bro?!
They beat you up, huh?
Conditions?
That straw hat!
Hmmm... I think it was around there.
Captain.
You have a 300 million
berry price on your head...
My 2001st win.
It doesn't hurt me, Ace-san.
Alright then, let's just...
You're Monkey D. Luffy, aren't you?
Yes, I am!
What hurts me is...
Nothing so far...
It's hard for me to take a young man's life
We can catch that crappy beetle any time.
Man... Bad memories.
....the fact that I can't take a stand...
No good at all...
...for my beliefs about humanity and justice!
So...
but the sweet sound of your death
cry will be worth 300 million to me.
Lunch break is over! Let's
start afternoon lessons!
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei
A Warlord of the Sea
(A Whale Shark Fish-man Formerly
With a Bounty of 250 Million Berries)
Let's give them an ultimatum: either let
have the beetle or face extermination.
I'm hungry...
Mucho Burning Net!
Okay!
Jimbei.
That was a good idea which is rare for you.
I can't die without doing something about it!
You look pretty full to me.
Ouch! Please!
Gum-Gum...
Let's just go with it!
...Jet Lance!
I don't give a damn about the title of
Warlord of the Sea! I don't want it!
We've been having banquets
every night these days.
So our stomachs have expanded and
we have to eat more to be satisfied.
I didn't say "extermination"...
Mucho Sticky Net!
If it means I can stop this war...
H-H-H-He wants to challenge us!
Ah, in addition to that,
You're right! It feels like my
bones are bigger these days...
The jungle is a poor place to
fight! I need to get out of here!
we should get rid of those two who're
having been glaring at us so rudely.
I'd be happy to sacrifice my life!
Hey! He's not a challenger!
Yeah, in your dreams.
Bastard! He's running away!
How's it going? Catch something?
No wonder we can't reach them!
Take a good look! He's
"Pirate Hunter" Zoro-san!
Not good! Not even a nibble!
The jailors' room on level
2 was crushed by a Basilisk!
You two! How would you like to
die by my Net-Net Fruit power
Wow! Really? Amazing!
We're totally out of food!
A Basilisk was beaten?!
Where are those two?!
If you can't catch anything,
it'll be no food for you guys!
What?!
which has a capture rate of 120%?
Don't "what?!" me!
What's happening on level 2 now?!
I told you it was a bad idea
Oh no! Really?
Of course!  That's why
they call it "weak sea!"
to have a banquet before
we got to the next island!
Can I have your autograph?!
But you guys were...
People from the East Blue
are quick at running away!
Alright, bring it on, swordsman!
Banquet! Banquet!
Is that how we were?
How pathetic!
No. A smart lady from the
East Blue figured that...
Don't even remember?!
I see them!
Hundred-and-Eight Pound Phoenix!
--Really?--But...
...two of us are enough to beat you all.
You bastard!
...there's three now.
Hey! Why are we running?!
A bite! I've got something!
What?!
This looks just like Kaya's mansion!
"Level 2
Floor of Wild Beasts from Hell"
We're all ready to kick their butt!
Here it comes!
A flying sword attack! Now I'm wide-awake!
Way to go, Brook!
This brings back memories!
Ouch! Don't be stupid!
Mucho Sticky Net!
You can't confront them!
She'd always poke her head
out of the window upstairs...
He's right!
You can only do what you are
capable of at times like these...
--Usopp-san!
--Hey, Kaya!
It's a big one!
I can't cut it!
Not done yet!
Great! We're gonna have
another banquet tonight!
...even if that means using your brain!
Sticky Net Network!
Did I keep you waiting?
Catch that fish even if it kills you!
It seems like all the wild beasts
on this floor are after us now!
So what adventure are you
going to tell me today?
--Banquet!
--Hang on! It's coming!
You! Hurry up!
Hmm, let’s see…
Don't tell me what to do, Pirate!
Looks like they're having fun.
We can't just run forever!
The story of when I fought the
giant goldfish at the South Pole
when I was five!
You're right! As soon as we stop
running, we're gonna become dinner!
Goldfish?
W-What the...?!
Yeah! What first shocked me was
the immense size of its poop!
And while we're busy running,
Do you want them to have
the beetle and the island?!
What's this?! It's so sticky!
jailors from other floors are on
their way here to catch us, too.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
It was so big that I landed on
it, thinking it was solid ground!
If not, you have to do as I say!
I'm tired already...
Oh, shit!
What're you doing, stupid?!
Are you sure...
I don't have time for this!
I wonder how she's doing...
Gum-Gum...
Wow, it's so thin!
Are you sure that I'll get Boss
back if I go along with you?!
Next up, what do you do for living?
Chop-Chop...
It's coming! It's coming!
Candle...
W-What's wrong here?!
--...Pistol!
--...Cannon!
--...Lock!
I'm a good cook, you crappy net geek!
Yes!
Well then, how about something
boiling hot? Colt.
I heard that Luigia who lives here
built this in the style of the
mansion that she used to live in.
Okay!
Augh! That big centipede just exploded!
N-N-No way! It wasn't like this!
Are you ready now?!
You gotta be kidding me!
Yeah!
It was just made of a bunch of Puzzle
Scorpions! They are extremely poisonous!
Aak! Ow, ow, ow...!
We're all in agreement?!
But maybe...
What a fool! You think drinking
hot water will help you?!
What the hell is that?!
Yeah!
if she used to live in the mansion
that means she's a relative of Kaya?
They're multiplying!
Whew, that was hot.
Okay, let's do it!
You two are enough for us?
Million Boiling Net!
What a big mouth!
The only thing they've got going
for them is their numbers.
Do you want me to protect you?
Are you kidding me?  You
just watch your own ass!
D-Don't tell me that you're K-Kaya?
I-It's a...
...Beetle!
Our fish...
...He ate it!
Guys! Let's...
You bastard! Stop messing around
with those stupid attacks!
...Get them!
Awesome!
Who is she?! Who is she! Who is...
Let my friends go!
--Ouch!
--W-What happened?!
That kind of friendship gets me choked up.
Don't mess with us!
It's...
You know that you can't beat me...
Fool! Aw!
Mucho Iron Net!
...a pirate ship!
Get out of here!
I told you!
What are they doing?!
What shameless bastards!
They sure were fooled by my footsteps trick!
What's this?!
Take that!
This is crap!
Boss! Get them!
You're a member of the Straw Hats, right?
They found us, stupid!
Yeah, I cook for them.
Surprised?
Damn it!
Where did you learn to cook?
The caves here are all connected
to different parts of the island.
By the way, I heard that the boss of
beasts on level 2 looks like a lion.
At an on-the-sea restaurant in
the East Blue for several years.
It's a waste to just use them as an
escape route for when an enemy comes!
He got all three! These
guys are the real deal!
Is this them?
No! These are man-eating lions with
human-like faces called Manticores!
The Baratie?!
I told you!
Are you really from the Baratie?!
What the swordsman got was the
basic sticky net and there is...
I-It's coming back!
"Prison Guard on Level 2
MANTICORE"
Once they catch us, they'll
eat us to the bone!
K-Kind of...
Alright! Get down, everybody!
That's great! I'm thrilled!
To the bone!
That's a big beetle!
--Key!--What?
...iron, hot water,
I fell in love with dishes that Zeff cooks
Thunder Bolt...
Give me the key!
I wanna ride on it!
and tried to steal some idea
and then here is fire!
...Tempo!
What?! Are you nuts, Luffy?!
Don't pay attention!
Since they look like humans
they do impressions of people!
s by going there often around
the time when it started.
Hey, Usopp! Let's catch it!
Aak! Ow, ow, ow, ouch!
--Help me!--It's too painful!
Alright!
Oh, really...
Oh no!
Where the hell did you get that net?!
Let's get them all at once!
The building is similar, right?
They just learn what prisoners say!
They don't even know the meaning!
I don't have Zeff's courage so I
couldn't imagine making it on the sea
I can turn everything that I ingest to nets
I'm not gonna let it destroy our ship!
I-It's creepy!
and capture something with a 120%
success rate that is my Net-Net power!
but I still wanted as style similar to his.
--Loincloth! Loincloth!--Strawberry-print
panties!
Coup de Vent!
What's going on here?!
Go ahead and try it.
But you still challenged me...
Who taught them those dumb words?!
Stop it!
Sure-Kill Egg Star!
I'm sorry but I don't have any money...
Beef Steak!
It's so sad to see someone
who doesn't know his limits!
No problem! Come on!
Augh! It stinks!
--What?!--Don't react to it!
Franky's attack didn't work?!
Oh yeah?
Nice!
Hey you!
Alright.
Can't be true!
You said that you're gonna help us, right?
Now, it's your turn!
Leave it to me!
Of course! Let's join forces
to break out of this prison!
I wanna see you do your very worst.
This must be...
You can count on it!
They're great!
Alright, come on, you giant beetle!
Where can we get down to level 3?!
Alright, you guys! I heard that...
...you are all from the East Blue.
Huh? Don't you wanna break out?!
Gum-Gum...
I thought that you wanna go up to level 1!
You think you can make a fool out of me?!
I'm gonna tell you weak
sea idiots once again!
Straw Hat came here to
rescue his brother Ace!
You can't get away with it!
Brother?! "Fire Fist" Ace
is Straw Hat's brother?!
Let us have the beetle!
And you came here to rescue him?!
What the hell?!
...Bazooka!
I'll kill you all!
I'm gonna picking you off
one by one from the end!
I've no time!
If Ace is being held here, I'm
sure that they put him in level 5!
Oh no!
If you don't wanna die,
just tell me where it is!
They blew Boss away!
And he wants to go there?!
No way! That's crazy! I'm not going!
Stop it!
Boss!
Wait! Tell me where the stairs
to go down are, at least!
Screw you!
Yoko! Don't be fool!
Ouch!
That beetle breathes fire!
The stairs to go down? Oh yeah!
Out of bullets?!
I'll fight you!
He's gonna roast our ship!
A Navy coat?! Is she a brand new recruit?!
The stairs are connected
between level 1 to 3.
Luffy! You alright?!
Why don't I use Straw Hat as a bait--to
the beast guarding the stairs!
Oh, senorita!
That beetle isn't just
huge - he breathes fire...
Yes! I figured out how the
damn geezer cooks the dish!
What have you done?!
You stand against us with a
bamboo sword? Are you nuts?
How cool is that?
And then, I can just take off!
As a requiem for my brother,
Huh?
Shut up! This is all I need...
All right, Straw Hat! Let's go together!
I will take your life!
How is it? Does it taste like Zeff's?
He looks just fine.
...to beat you guys!
Okay! I'm gonna make him one of us!
Here on the beach, with an expansive view,
Oh no!
Count on me, Straw Hat!
you'll find it hard to elude me, I'm sure!
--Shoot her!
--Yes!
What?! No! Wait a minute, Luffy!
Yoko!
Follow me...
Oh yeah? But I'm sure you can't beat me!
Yeah. In fact, you're better
than that old geezer!
Alright, you giant beetle! Join my...
Are you sure? I can't tell
you how happy that makes me!
How stupid you are!
Bring it on, senor!
Gee... even the cook seems happy!
Boss!
Oh no. There's something
here. And what the...
Oh? What's going on there?!
I got you!
--It's Luffy!
--Seems like he's fighting.
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
This can't be true!
Jet Pistol!
So that must be the Shiki's big beetle!
It's a guardian of the
stairs called the Sphinx!
Yeah, it is very big!
No shock! Net Body!
"Prison Guard on Level 2
SPHINX
(A Lion with a Human-like Face and Feathers)"
What is he doing there?
So tiny...
Oh no, it was just about to get exciting...
Shut up!
W-What's that?!
So you're from Syrup Village?
They're coming this way...
Is it a lion?! Or a grandpa?
Sorry! Your attack won't hurt me anymore!
Yeah, they seem to be getting bigger...
--Here he comes!
--Go, Boss!
Huh? Yeah.
He's aiming at us!
You must be Yasopp's son.
Beat them up, Boss!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
Yes! Get them!
You know him?!
Sort of. We had a lot of
troubles with his lying.
Giant Beetle!
--Omelet rice!--Steak!
--Underpants!--Strawberry-print panties!
Help... Help...
It's not working! How long
are you going to do that?!
Dad? Oh, by the way,
Help me!
did you really live in the mansion there?
--Oh no, Usopp!
--Damn it! You idiot!
Until you get blown away!
Luffy's attack isn't working!
He must be a Devil Fruit eater!
You must know if you're from there!
That's not good.
That mansion is not only
the symbol of the village
Thin noodle.
T-Thin noodle?!
but it's everybody's dream house!
Shoot it! Shoot it!
Y-Yeah!
I always wanted to live in a mansion
like that since I was a kid.
Chinese Noodle!
He's flying away!
Alright, let's finish it up.
This is for my brother!
A requiem of a death cry!
I finally made my dream come after
I ended up being on this island.
Vegetable noodle!
What were they thinking?!
Nice!
They taught him mainly names of noodles?!
Mucho-Mucho...
Hey, look! An island!
So that means you're not
related to Kaya at all.
BBQ pork noodle!
...Full Net Body!
Boss!
Big Bro, the nets! Please!
Is that where the beetle came from?
Spicy Szechuan noodle!
I'm known as a cranky princess here so don't
No fun... This is no fun at all...
tell anybody if you don't wanna die!
Cool dude!
Boss!
--Luffy!
--Luffy-san!
I was about to see a mucho mucho beautiful
Watch out, Boss!
Yes, Ma'am!
--Who, me?!--Who, me?!
H-Hey! We're gonna hit the wall!
Damn, even the granny is bonding with them?!
inferno colored by despair and screams...
He's very tough!
T-That's gotta be...
Big Bro, hurry!
Oh, please watch your step there!
Now, you're captured!
The Sphinx is going nuts somewhere!
It's a strange place to walk through.
Oh, he's so annoying. Doesn't
he know that he's just a pest?
You will never break this net!
I knew it! We'll be stuck here forever!
This is a maze made by nature!
Hmm.
Mucho Burning Net!
Ground pork noodle!
It connected to different
parts of the island!
Hot-pot noodle!
That's nice but, are we there yet?
What now?!
Canton noodle!
Ah, we're almost there!
Now, shoot!
I wanna eat Sanji's food! I
haven't had it for long time!
It's a submarine, isn't it?
It's being used as a pirate ship?!
W-W-What the hell is this?!
Wonton noodle!
Looks like it.
You can't get away now, you giant beetle!
Now, I have a prize worth
300 million berries!
It's the symbol of Orenami!
Just give up and become one of my crew!
Wonton noodle!
It was hard because we only
had the poster to draw from!
Third Gear!
I don't take "no" for an answer!
Bone Balloon!
Damn! He's pretty strong!
W-Well... I mean... Why is it naked?!
My boss...
W-What are you...?!
You know, I don't wanna go
down to the lower levels!
That was decided by consensus!
...will never become...
Don't worry! We made sure
to get the front, too!
...a pirate!
I'm totally with you!
Stop it!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow!
All right! Now, let's form
an alliance to breakout!
That's enough!
I'm so glad that you are a real escapee!
Sorry...
Boss!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow!
Alright, let's execute the
"Straw Hat for dinner" plan!
Ow, ow, ow! What is this place?
Oh yeah!
I didn't know there was an island like this.
Boss...
They're all stupid!
And for that matter...
They let pirates on to the
island which you and my father
...What the hell is going on?
have always been protected!
We got it!
Yoko! What happened?!
I hate them! I hate them!
Gum-Gum...
Be careful! He's a pirate!
...Giant Pistol!
Miso flavored noodle!
A pirate?! No!
Boss!
Salt flavored noodle!
Soy sauce flavored noodle!
Show us mercy!
I can't believe that Boss got beat!
Stop doing that!
Hey, what're you guys doing?
Fabre-san, there is no other way!
Oops!
You people are Straw Hats, aren't you?
H-Here he comes, Straw Hat!
To save this island, we
should let them have Boss!
That tickles! Boss!
Make a decision! You're the mayor!
Stop it! Hey!
Yes, we are.
Gum-Gum...
Oh yeah! He's a Straw Hat!
Yoko, I...
...Bazooka!
Ah! He's "Pirate Hunter" Zoro!
And he's "Black Foot" Sanji!
Oh no!
Dad, what should I do?!
Augh! Luffy!
Why did you want to make him angry?!
And then he's...
I got it!
To save this island...
Who are you?
Oh no!
I'm coming to save you, Luffy-san!
Let me go! He tried to steal Boss from me!
It's not fair! I wanna go
up higher like you two!
What?
I'm gonna bite you to death!
Boss?
Oh, wait--I seem to have
forgotten I can't swim!
Yoko! Stop!
Shut up and just let me go!
Boss?! Where are you going?!
Cold noodle!
Who are these people?
Oh, you...
Ouch! You are the owner of this beetle?
I thought I'd die here!
No, it's not like that, Boss!
Even though I'm already dead!
The owner?! No way! Boss is my friend!
Thank you, Giant Beetle!
Friend?
No!
Oh, you're already on someone else's team?
Ow, ow, ouch! What do
you think you're doing?!
Is there any way that you'd let me have him?
I got you, naive animal!
Boss!
That's just a wax figure that
I made with my Wax-Wax power!
Of course not! Over my dead body!
Hey, Fabre! What is Boss doing?!
You bastard! A few minutes ago,
you could barely breathe fire!
Hot thin noodle.
He heard everyone's inner voices and
I can't take it! Let's fight right now!
It's better with Miss Goldenweek's coloring,
Alright, guys! Let's take this
thing to the legendary pirate Shiki
No! Wait until I get down!
Alright! I give him up!
he's trying to save this island
by sacrificing himself!
but it's enough to fool an animal like you!
Ah no!
Huh?!
and become his brothers!
Remember, we're after the big beetle
that took off from Shiki's hide-out!
Here we go!
Do you understand?! Failure is not an option!
Hey! What're you doing?!
Ow, ow, ow... You bastard!
Here we go!
Be ready for anything!
--Those two...
--Ow, nice one!
Yeah!
Boss!
are they gonna fight forever?
Can you tell which is the real me?
Uh, sorry, Big Bro,
Dunno.
but you're the captain so you
better say something about...
You haven't won yet!
Noodle!
Boss!
You missed it!
Oh no, he's in the middle of a siesta now!
Noodle!
You missed it!
I'm sorry if I hurt you.
Noodle!
You missed it!
Uh-oh! He's not gonna wake up for a while!
You think that you defeated him?!
Wow, that's fun! It's like Whack-A-Mole!
No, I didn't mean it like that.
--You bastard!
--Don't do it, Colt-san!
Dad...
--Noodle!--Missed it!
You know what's gonna happen if you
wake him when he's having a siesta!
There you are.
Boss!
--Noodle!--Missed it!
--Hey!
--Stay away!
That's him!
Can I join?
--Noodle!--Missed it!
These wounds mean nothing to him!
He's right! We don't wanna die yet!
Oh, it's not! This one?!
Why are you here?
They'll heal up overnight while
he's sleeping underground.
How the hell could he take a nap at this
crucial moment for us Amigo Pirates!
--Noodle!--Missed it!
I heard there was an orange plantation so...
Wow! That's amazing!
--Noodle! Noodle! Noodle!
Noodle! Noodle!--Go get him!
We gotta do it without him
then! Are you ready, guys?!
Not only that! Tomorrow he will molt!
What a view!
He's playing with Sphinx!
He'll become bigger and stronger!
How simple-minded are you, Straw Hat?!
Órale!
Huh? Do they continue doing that
even as full grown beetles?
Noodle! Noodle! Noodle!
My dad used to love this place.
Okay, it's done! We have a
steel cage for the beetle!
Boss is different. He sheds
his skin once a month.
Noodle!
You're starting to enjoy this!
Amazing! It only took you a minute!
And so did I.
That's why he's so big.
They're having more fun than I
expected. I gotta make a break now!
Huh! It's a piece of cake for me!
Look, Yoko! This is my favorite
place in the whole world!
You're gonna be stronger than you are now?
Yes, he is! What do you say to that?!
You're good!
Hey, what are these unusual tremors?!
We're ready for the beetle at any minute now!
Yeah! I love this place, too!
That's cool!
They must be making Sphinx mad!
Yeah! They might be back
with it at any minute!
Alright! Then, let's have
this fight again tomorrow!
I really really love it!
Noodle! Noodle! Noodle!
Yeah? You really love it?
Let's make it clear which
one of us is stronger!
It's okay. Don't be afraid.
Noodle!
Burn everything up!
Awesome!
That's so silly... Oh?
Take all the treasure and food!
You're covered with cuts and bruises.
Kill all who resist!
It's a welcome party for you.
Don't worry.
Dad! Dad!
Mitsuboshi really wanted this to happen.
What?! What happened?!
Is it safe to be on this floor?!
Stay still.
Yoko!
Everybody, dig in!
Alright! So I have your word, then!
Hurry and escape from this island!
Level 3 to monitoring room!
I'll fix you up.
Cheers!
We're hearing big noises from upstairs!
No I won't! Because I love this island!
So good!
Mr. 3! This is our chance!
He is an interesting young man as they say!
I love the view from the orange plantation!
Having a party for pirates?
What're they thinking?!
The plan is a success!
Boss?
Trust me.
You said that you love it, too!
This wasn't our plan! But let's just run!
--We're here!
--The town square is right there!
Oh?! That must be the door to the stairs!
This way!
You kept saying we were "almost"
there but you made me walk for hours!
I'll make a key out of wax!
What a big cave! What is it for?!
You're right.
This is the monitoring room!
We can't get in touch with level 2 yet!
We wanted you to enjoy our
island to the full extent!
No!
This is an escape route.
So we don't know what's going on!
Escape route?
Saying goodbye is always hard to do.
This cave is like a maze.
Noodle!
I understand you, senorita!
You're a pirate, too, right?
We can escape through this
cave when pirates come.
You save...
Even women are into pirates?
These are crazy times!
Oh no! You stupid beast! You
battered down the floor!
We are world champions at
running away and groveling!
That was too easy but it's okay.
...t-this island from now on.
Y-You're proud of it?
Humph! Everybody's into pirates!
These are crazy times!
Now, come in and make yourself at home!
Dad!
This is level 3! Augh! The ceiling is
crumbling and the beast is about to...
That's how we survive in the Grand Line.
We don't have a military
and it's a remote island
Yoko! You can't talk to
Nami-sama like that...
Together with the island...
With this beetle in our hands,
so the Navy always leaves
us on a back burner.
Augh! Ouch! Stop it!
we can finally become members
of the Big Boss' crew!
...live strongly!
Oh, hey!
Speaking about the Navy, that
girl was wearing a Navy coat.
Hey, you!
This is not good!
I'm sorry, Nami-sama! Her father
was killed by pirates...
I was like you.
No no! This is the way to level 3!
Is there any reason for that?
I really hated pirates.
Sorry, noodles!
She wears it in memory of her father.
What?
Oh...
Then, why did you become one?
He was a good man.
Well... I'm not sure why.
He couldn't stand by and see us
repeatedly attacked by pirates
What happened?!
so he stayed on this island separated from
Wait!
other marines in order to protect us.
I said "wait!"
You said "in memory of" so I assume...
I'm known by the government
as a pirate who hates pirates
It was exactly five years ago...
Can't you hear what I'm saying!
he was fighting against some
pirates alone and died.
except for you people.
Hey, everybody, I need your
attention! Yes, look at me!
You hates pirates?
We're Amigo Pirates! This
island is under siege!
Must be surprising for you, Ace-san.
Three years later,
I visited Whitebeard's ship frequently
If you don't wanna get killed,
Boss came to us out of nowhere.
let us have the beetle!
Nami!
but because of my status, I always
traveled under the sea to get there.
He bonded with Yoko right away and became
I'm not gonna let you go with...
The beetle?! Why does he know about Boss?!
You're one of us now!
the guardian angel of this island.
...these bastards!
Because I like you people.
Maybe, Boss reminds her of her
late father who was strong.
Giant Beetle! You still
haven't fought with me!
Ho-hum.
Uh-huh!
We promised and I know that you remember!
I remember that you almost killed me once.
Couldn't you hear what I said?
But Luffy is not the kind of
pirate that you think he is.
Is it okay for us to be here?
I can say the same for you.
How about these?
Pirate!
W-What're you doing?!
We're pirates.
You people are different! Now, we are here!
I just wanted to do something for him.
Can't you see that Boss was trying
to sacrifice himself for the island?
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow!
Fish-Man Island is peaceful now and it's
all because of the old man Whitebeard.
Shut up! I don't care!
Wow! A windmill! It's gigantic!
Let's make it clear which
one of us is stronger!
I just wanna fight him!
When pirates go along the Grand Line,
they always pass Fish-Man Island.
Is that it?!
Shut up! I don't care!
He's so hopeless!
W-What's this?! What's going on here?!
Do you have something to say?!
Right after the dawn of Great Pirate
Era, Fish-Man Island was in trouble.
I just wanna fight him!
It's so high!
I don't know!
No! Don't go to them!
Is that it?!
I want to...
Countless human pirates and Navy
who were chasing after them...
Yeah, I think I see what you mean.
I want to...
Oh! I thought that it was just a
crag but it's beautiful in the back!
Yeah?
...be with Boss forever!
Uh-huh.
W-What's going on?!
...were wreaking havoc.
He's too stupid and naive to be a pirate.
I heard that the big beetle
is protecting this island!
A large number of Fish-men and mermaids
were kidnapped and sold as slaves.
But then...
Yoko!
How can I say this? The buildings
here are all different in style...
But if he has nobody to protect, there'll
be no reason for him to stay here!
I want to...
I agree.
And just when everyone gave
themselves up to despair,
...be with Boss...
It's a strange town!
It's quiet. Did they finish fighting?
Don't you think so?
Whitebeard came.
...on this island!
Can't you see?
Oh yeah.
It was a deserted island when we first
They want Boss!
I wonder how Boss did.
"I declare that this island
is my territory now!"
Hearing that makes me realize
something. Let me down!
got here and that was just the beginning.
No, Boss! Stay there! Don't show yourself!
Since then, for some reason, people
are coming here from the same ocean.
With just those few words, no one
bothers Fish-Man Island anymore.
You're completely right!
What do you say? Do you give up?
I'm sorry that I gave you a hard time, Yoko!
That's what made this town.
He says "No, I won!"
Welcome, Straw Hats!
Before I thought that we
better let them have Boss...
What power!
My restaurant...
This is Kansorn Island where people
from the East Blue live together!
What?!
How could I ever forget that day?
...And I'm ashamed of myself!
They destroyed it!
Alright, that's it!
We love Boss...
And he's protecting other islands
with his name in the same way, too.
It also known as Little East Blue!
It's time to go back to the sea!
...As well as this island!
What're you talking about, Nami?!
We're not through yet!
It's not right to knock somebody down
just because he's the head pirate!
Yeah! I didn't expect to see the rookie
of great promise in the East Blue!
W-W-We won't let...
It seems like it only takes a half day to
record the magnetic wave of this island.
Old man!
...People like you...
If he ever got killed, what
will happen to the sea?!
Zoro-san! You're from
Frost Moon Village, right?
...Have him!
So we better go now before it resets.
Are you okay?
--Yeah!
Y-Yeah.
We have a training hall for
people who came from there!
It's clear to everyone that that
time of confusion would come again!
Come and see it!
A training hall?!
Sanji-san, you grew up on The Baratie, right?
You people are really manipulated
by what that stupid kid said!
I represent this island's inhabitants.
The government must know it, too!
Try the food at the local Baratie!
Is that so? Then where's the beetle?
It's pretty good!
It's like a sappy drama! It makes me sick!
You have The Baratie here?!
I'm sorry but you can't have him!
I wanted to stop the war even if it kills me.
Nami-sama!
Anyone from Syrup Village?!
They choose to be exterminated.
Instead, you can have all
our money and food and
I think Luigia is from there.
Underdogs will always perish.
That's the way of the world.
I wanted to rescue you, Ace-san.
everything on this island!
Luigia?!
Just take it all and go away!
Yeah. She's living in the most
luxurious mansion in this town!
Oh, believe me, we intend to do
so! We intend to take everything!
Oh, that's...
Mansion? The only mansion in
Syrup Village is Kaya's mansion.
Jimbei, that's enough.
Money, food, and the beetle as well!
It's too painful.
I haven't given up hope yet.
Whew! Couldn't eat another bite!
Humph! Everybody's so caught up in them!
Oh, he starts to shed his skin!
W-Who the heck are you? What're you doing?!
I believe that a miracle will
happen and a chance will come.
Pirates are all the same!
Luffy!
Hey, you, Fancy Hat! Go home!
I wonder how they're doing...
W-What?!
Thank you for saving our island!
The giant beetle doesn't
want to join a pirate crew!
Don't worry, Chopper! They'll call us soon!
It looks like there's a lot of fun
going on in the outside world!
Just give up on him!
No problem!
You think?
What?! Join the crew?!
You got me wrong, stupid!
We better get an insect cage fixed for them.
It's a now-or-never chance
to defeat Whitebeard.
Giant Beetle! I'll be back someday so,
You're right. If the beetle
joins us, we will need it.
Awesome!
I'm here to catch him!
let's continue where we left off!
I can't help getting excited.
See? It's them!
Oh no!
Hey, it's me! Is Nami there?
Promise me!
You bastard!
Usopp? It's me! What's
wrong? Did you catch it?
You think that you can fell my old man?!
No no no, it's...
That's not gonna work on me.
Shut up! Calm down!
It's not just me.
I got it!
I'm a rubberman!
Um... I'm wondering - can you come over here?
A Devil Fruit eater?!
Kill Whitebeard!
Gum-Gum...
How funny! Now they're starting
to fight amongst themselves!
Huh?
That guy's gonna die? Yee-ha!
There's a town on the
other side of the island!
...Whip!
That'll be great!
They say that they really wanna see you!
Zoro! Sanji!
Get me out to the sea!
I'm the one who will kill him!
--Alright!
--We got it!
Call her "Nami-sama"!
They're coming!
Let me have a chance, too! I'm
gonna put an end to his era!
Boss!
What's going on?
Anyway, just come over here! I beg you!
Huh? Wait, Usopp!
Do you wanna fight more, Fancy Hat?!
He hung up!
Why do they want just Nami?
I don't know.
That beetle's gonna fight me again tomorrow!
Boss!
I thought that they were
specialists in trapping.
Okay! Let's just go!
I'm not gonna let you ruin that!
Mucho Needle Net!
--Boss!
But I'm afraid we've lost
touch with the Amigo Pirates.
Oh no! It was too soon to
shed his skin as I thought!
I'll leave the ship to you!
Shut up, you assholes!
Yeah! Count on us!
It seems as though it was
impossible for them to defeat
I don't know about the structure of your body
Jimbei, "Fire Fist," just so you know,
Ow, ow, ow... Ouch!
There she goes...
the monster that you created.
but it seems like that was
an incomplete transformation.
Luffy!
there are dozens and dozens
of silver medalists
You should be disappointed.
I feel sorry for you!
However, one escapee doesn't affect
the execution of my plan at all.
in the world who in the end didn't win...
Is this it?!
Crying or screaming won't help anymore!
It's a rockbound and there
are reefs all around it
Amore! My beloved brother Colt!
...against Whitebeard and Roger
all holding back their tears.
We got your guardian angel as you see!
so regular ships can't approach the island.
These monsters will help
me to conquer the world!
What a shame!
It's not over yet!
Well, reefs are no problem with this ship.
Even if you are a rubberman,
We won't let his last breath...
I will not let you get away with it, senor!
...be wasted.
Let's declare war against the whole world!
Thank you, Giant Beetle!
Yeah! That's my Big Bro!
Straw Hat! You're the worst
troublemaker in the world!
Alright! Let's go hunting!
Shiki the Golden Lion's
supreme plan will begin!
Boo-hoo-hoo, so melancholy!
We're gonna get the big beetle that
took off from Shiki's hide-out!
What's this?!
Sorry, noodles!
Now, it's showtime!
Let's go, guys!
Yeah!
To recover the beetle and
protect Little East Blue,
Level 3!
The Straw Hats arrive at the island
Luffy and the others defeat the
Basilisk and press on through level 2,
Luffy is captured by Largo.
This is Starvation Hell, where
prisoners are given no food or water
where immigrants from East Blue live.
Zoro and Sanji also struggle against
the powers of the Net-Net Fruit.
the islanders travel through
the caves according
but more wild beasts impede
their path one after another.
The scenery looks so much like
and are tormented by extreme heat.
to Nami's secret plan.
their homeland that they
can't help but reminisce.
And when the beetle learns that
it is the pirates' target,
Meanwhile, another pirate is being
held in the same prison cell as Ace.
Meanwhile, Luffy pursues
Largo, but the power of the
As Luffy and the others roam
this desert-like floor,
But the Amigo Pirates are also heading
toward the island in pursuit
it makes a grave decision in
order to protect the island.
they fall into a trap set by a chief guard.
His name is...
of the giant beetle!
Net-Net Fruit traps him inside Largo's body.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Chief Guard Saldeath's Trap!
Level 3 - Starvation Hell!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Special Presentation Related to the Movie!
Little East Blue in Danger!"
"A Warlord in Prison!
Jimbei the First Son of the Sea!"
"A Special Presentation Related to the Movie!
The Fierce Onslaught of the Amigo Pirates!"
Luffy vs. Largo The Battle is on!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!