Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight--
desperately for the One Piece,
Countless pirates fight
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
also takes to the sea to-- become
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After being separated from his friends,
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Separated from Buggy and Mr. 3 on level 3,
Luffy comes to rescue his brother Ace--
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
Luffy headed to the lower
levels with Bon Clay!
Luffy comes to rescue his brother Ace
who has been captured by the Navy
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy
by sneaking into Impel Down - the
greatest prison in the world!
who has been captured by the Navy.
Summon all the other forces
of Impel Down to level 4!
who has been captured by the Navy.
He ran into Buggy and a former
Baroque Works agent - Mr. 3,
After running into Buggy on level 1,
Roger that!
Luffy went on to level 2 - The
Floor of Wild Beasts from Hell,
Luffy met Buggy, former
Baroque Works agents Mr. 3
Ace-san.
If they manage to get away from Minotaurus
and come down here to the Burning Heat Hell,
where he joined up with Mr. 3
- a former Baroque Works agent,
and together, they have reached level 3!
What did she just tell you?
and Mr. 2 Bon Clay in the prison
and they all fell into level 4!
This is level 3 - the Starvation Hell!
I'll execute them with my own hands!
and together, they all
headed to the lower floors!
We have to get away from here while
we still have sweat to spare.
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
She said that my brother's here!
There's a huge amount of hot air and smoke!
Smells good...
It looks like there's a lot of fun
going on in the outside world!
Let's go to level 4 in hurry!
Ouch, ouch... Smells good...
Swan Arabesque!
It's hard to even stand here!
Seriously?!
Soup spaghetti!
Right! But...
Jimbei, "Fire Fist," just so you know,
The Sphinx is awake!
It's been a long time! Straw-chan, it's me!
...this is level 4--the Burning
Heat Hell where you wanna go!
Deep-fried noodle!
I've had enough of you running
around and playing by your rules!
there are dozens and dozens of silver
medalists in the world who in the end didn't win...
Gum-Gum...
Burning Heat? Is it down there?
"Warden Magellan's Strategy!
Straw Hat Entrapment Completed!"
...Gatling!
Who're you?!
...against Whitebeard and Roger
all holding back their tears.
Meanwhile, Hancock who helped
Luffy to sneak into the prison...
M-Magellan!
You said you were gonna break out!
Gum-Gum...
Straw Hat!
You're dead, you vermin!
...is about to reach the floor
where Ace is being held.
...Whip!
I knew you'd want to come with me!
No one wants to follow you to hell!
Un, deux, come on!
Anyway, you take this! The
special weapon--Muggy Ball!
Gum-Gum...
--Un, deux, faint!
--Who's singing?
"Mighty Magellan! Bon Clay Bugs Out!"
...Gatling!
Un, deux, come on!
"Chief Guard Saldeath's Trap!
Level 3 - Starvation Hell!"
Alright! Gum-Gum...
Spin, spin!
Un, deux, faint!
The following prisoners seem to be
helping the invader - Straw Hat Luffy:
...Mallet Rifle!
Un, deux, come on!
Monitor room! We are at the scene on level 2.
Prisoner number E-8200:
Pirate - Buggy the Clown.
Can you see the image?
"The Unleashed Swan! A
reunion with Bon Clay!"
Yeah! Keep us updated!
We did it!
Roger that!
We beat the monster of hell!
IMPEL DOWN LEVEL 2 FLOOR
OF WILD BEASTS FROM HELL
Uh oh! I gotta get out of here!
Prisoner number D-0464:
Former Baroque Works agent -
The Burning Heat Floor is too hot!
Oh Come My Way!
Galdino, A.K.A. Mr. 3.
What happened here?!
"All Forces Have Gathered! The Battle
on Level 4 The Burning Heat Hell!"
Oh, oh! Oh Come My Way!
This hole is big enough for even
the Sphinx to fall through!
W-Warden! W-Wait for just a second!
Prisoner number C-9915:
Former Baroque Works agent -
Yeah, yeah! Oh Come My Way!
Don't start fighting yet!
What does Straw Hat Luffy want?
Get away from here! Warden's
poison will get us, too!
I can barely stand in this Starvation
Hell but that guy's singing so happily.
Bentham, A.K.A. Mr. 2 Bon Clay.
How much time left until Ace's execution?
Straw Hat Luffy and Mr. 2 Bon Clay
are now in district N on level 3.
If he's a prisoner, he sure is something!
29 hours. Everything's gonna
be over at 3 p.m. tomorrow.
The Blugoris are having
trouble subduing them!
Spin, spin! Oh Come My Way!
Damn you! I was about to find
all of that good smelling food!
But only if everything
goes according to plan.
Hey, Bon-chan! How can we
get to the lower levels?
It sounds familiar! This must be...
Hey, partner! I think this guy can help us!
There are stairs at the opposite side!
I'm hungry! You need to get out of my way!
We'll transfer Portgaz
D. Ace tomorrow morning.
Nice! I'm so glad to see
you, Bon-chan! Thank you!
H-Hey! W-Wait a minute!
You're so high-spirited. Don't worry.
Look! This is bad!
You won't need to think
about eating ever again!
You needn't thank me!
Yeah, yeah! Oh Come My Way!
The prisoners on level 2 are all
free! How did they get the keys?!
What do you mean?
We were destined to see each other again!
Luffy!
Spin, spin! Oh Come My Way!
S-Straw-chan! Don't fight him!
Are they responsible for this, too?!
If I could only know you
were safe, I'd want nothing else!
Those guards are in trouble!
You guys are doing great!
IMPEL DOWN LEVEL 3 INSIDE OF THE WELL TOWER
He's the warden of Impel Down--Magellan!
I spin and spin like I'm caught
up in the tide of the times!
Let's hear it for Captain Buggy!
He ate the Venom-Venom Fruit!
It seems like they're heading
to the staircase to level 4.
This way!
Alright, let me ask you once again.
He's our savior!
You gotta run away! He's the last
person that you wanna fight!
Wait! Listen to me! That's...
Meanwhile, we lost track of the other
two, Buggy the Clown and Galdino - Mr. 3.
Okay!
Venom-Venom? He's poisonous?
You still wanna go down to level 4?
L-Level 2 reporting! We need backup, pronto!
Yes, I am.
Yeah! I knew you'd want to come with me!
Guys! You can't be that tired!
Straw Hat Luffy! You're a rookie pirate
The prisoners are...
There is a riot going on level 2 and
the invader is still on the loose!
I'm not going at any cost!
with a 300 million berry price
whose caused far too many problems
It's not that hot!
My body will melt away completely!
I can make more people suffocate!
by rebelling against the Navy
and the World Government!
This is getting interesting!
How many times do we have
to tell you, bonehead?!
Send Blugoris to level 2!
This is a good way to kill time!
We've just received word of
Straw Hat Luffy's intent!
And now, you've snuck into this great,
Can't you see the plumes?!
It's the Burning Heat Hell!
They'll get caught and it'll be over soon!
historic prison with iron-tight security!
You did?! From whom?!
Oh! What's up, Mr. 3!
We're not gonna go to level 4!
Fleet Admiral Sengoku at
the Headquarters sent word!
I have to thank you for ruining
my reputation as a warden!
Why not?!
The invader - Monkey D. Luffy and...
It's obvious!
Just as I thought. It's you...
I know why you're here!
We wanna escape! E-S-C-A-P-E!
...the condemned prisoner - Portgaz D. Ace,
You came to rescue your
brother Portgaz D. Ace,
That's right! We wanna go up! Understand, up?
those two are brothers!
the second division commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates!
What?! Mr. 3?!
What?!
Wow! I got a really big, bloody booger here!
But I assure you that there's no way that
you can save him and get out of Impel Down!
Then, he came here to rescue "Fire
Fist" Ace before the public execution?!
Hey, wait a minute! Why're you here?!
--Thank you for being understanding.
--No problem.
You're not listening!
You're behind bars, so you've been caught?!
Yeah, that's exactly it!
Here is your cloak.
Straw Hat Luffy! This is where
you will meet your fate!
That explains why he keeps going down!
Whew! Straw-chan, let them go!
We were focused on Whitebeard's attack!
They don't have the balls to go further!
I'll find out all about when
and how you broke in...
--Thank you for everything.
--M-My pleasure!
If he pulls this off, the
tide will turn against us!
No, no. It's me who has been caught!
Whose nose looks like a ball?!
What's that?! How did you hear me?! Ha-ha!
I was so surprised I had to do a double take
with an "Oh Come My Way" Kenpo called...
...after I pass down your sentence!
Inform Warden Magellan at once!
And get the riot on level 2 under control!
...Looking Back on that Autumn Night's Dream!
By the way...
I made up my mind! I'll just spin!
Y-Yes?
Come out, Luffy!
Ha-ha-ha! Gimme a break!
Hey! What kind of animal is this?!
Earlier, there was a report of an intruder.
That was close!
Let's be sure to not let him out.
Yes, it seems so.
It looks like I can't
go any farther with you.
NAVY
But Impel Down is truly iron-tight.
What're you saying?! Let me out!
What's so funny, Garp?!
Hey! It looks like ceiling is rising!
I can't use my power while
wearing those Sea Prism cuffs.
Now that we have Warden Magellan in command,
Ah! You're right!
I assume that it'll be over soon.
And they'll take my cloak
away so I can't hide you.
That's good.
I wish I could do more but...
I hear a rattling, too. I
think if I'm not mistaken...
We're standing at a crossroads that
could change the whole world of the sea,
Why would you want to sneak into hell?
How much hotter can it get?!
What're you talking about?
But if I keep going down these stairs,
I think I can get to where Ace is!
That guy must be crazy.
but he keeps causing problems,
one after another!
I wouldn't have made it this
far without your help!
...that we are falling!
At Enies Lobby...
Luffy.
Magellan has a deadly power.
That symbol represents...
I'm not gonna tell you
even if it means death!
Oh no!
...the unity of over 170 member nations
in the four seas and the Grand Line
My Muggy ball was so powerful,
it caused the floor to collapse!
Don't get caught, Luffy!
Every prisoner says that
before they are tortured!
No way, it's because of my heavy kick!
What's Saldeath doing?
He headed down?!
which is to say - the whole world!
However, Straw Hat, what you're about
to go through is far worse than torture!
You're wrong! It's because
my punch was so strong!
The Blugoris can't beat
Straw Hat and Mr. 2 so...
Is that true?! You're not
fooling with me, are you?!
Now, do you realize how big the
organization that is after her is?!
No no! My Wax-Wax power was...
...he went to level 2 to break up the riot.
--No!
--Certainly not!
Oh! I didn't do that much...
Now I know the enemies Robin has.
Straw-chan!
Okay! Thank you for letting me out, Mr. 3!
Magellan's whole body is poisonous
so you can't even touch him!
Then, shut up!
Sogeking!
Shoot the flag.
We're gonna get burned by hellfire!
I owe you!
Do you think you can beat a guy like that?!
Understood.
--Ah?
--Alright then...
My new weapon - The giant
slingshot called "Kabuto"!
Help us!
I will!
I'm on my way, my friend!
Let me show its power!
Let's go back to the Pool
of Blood and turn right!
Oh Come My Way! It's the way to hell!
Why was there no report before
things got this out of hand?!
Sure-Kill! Fire Bird Star!
Straw-chan! Give up on that
food and let's get to level 5!
You weren't paying attention because
you were crazy about Hancock-dono.
This is the best for all of us.
That's no use!
Yeah, for sure...
I didn't pay attention?
LEVEL 4--THE BURNING HEAT HELL
Three demon guards and their commander
are guarding the staircase to level 5!
How did he slip through our tight security?!
Agh! No!
No, you didn't. As Warden, you
need to take responsibility.
There's just one invader.
What?!
Warden!
And the time with the Celestial Dragons...
All exits on this floor
have already been covered!
But if we let him rescue Ace,
Can I see the prisoner now?
Hey, don't do it! You can't kill us!
There's no way for you to...
not only Impel Down but the World
Government will be humiliated!
Okay, let's go! I'm ready to go!
I'll let them get away and
lay the blame on Warden!
Whatever happens, you deserve it!
W-Warden! Don't you realize
how serious this is?!
How many people have you killed?
We're gonna get into that prison
You annoy me, too!
...get out of here!
No! I don't wanna believe it!
You're stupid.
and in the name of Navy Headquarters,
we must catch Straw Hat Luffy!
Get them!
If only you had checked on it at the time...
--We deeply regret what we've done!
--Yeah, we're really sorry!
Warden! Stop sighing!
Don't!
Hydra!
I didn't pay attention?!
Wait a minute!
Or - maybe you did pay attention!
W-Who are you?!
W-What's that?!
Made out of poison?!
A body of pure poison?!
I'm Sadie-chan who loves torturing people!
Have the guests left, Warden?
I'm burning!
Help me!
Oh, Sadie-chan!
After being breached by an
intruder, taking Navy help
Salute the commander!
Keep lugging firewood! Hustle!
Gum-Gum...
would only further
disgrace Impel Down's name!
All of this has been unprecedented!
We're ready to go hunting...
...Pistol!
It's too hot.
My whole body...
even my guts are gonna get burned!
No!
And this time,
What do you say?
he's meddling with a prison where
no-one's escaped for 20 years!
I'd rather die than stay on this floor!
She can't be serious using
"chan" to refer to herself...
I can't take it anymore!
Ever since the abhorrent Golden Lion,
--Straw-chan!
--Bon-chan!
Shut up!
Get out of my way! Move it!
You're just the person! Do
you have somebody on level 3?
You better call me "Sadie-chan!"
a prison which has never been breached,
A prisoner is escaping!
--Why did you do that?!
--I told you that you can't fight!
Minotaurus... happens to be there!
known for so long as a robust  and
iron-tight great fortress - Impel Down!
The poison will harm you
if you get it all over you
Hey! Outta my way!
He has disgraced its name by being
the first to penetrate its walls!
I can't resist those screams!
but even one touch will be lethal!
Do you want me to throw
you into the sea of fire?!
How could he be your grandson, Garp?!
You bitch!
Hold it! Are you saying that
you don't need our help?
I can't fight without touching it!
He sure has accomplished a
lot! I'm proud of my grandson!
Yes. This prison is a labyrinthine hell.
That's why you can't fight him!
That's good but there are many
places to hide on level 3.
Damn Bartholomew Kuma!
Can't you say anything
other than "you can't"?
If you don't know it well, you can't help us!
I'm gonna fall!
He said that he took care of the
Straw Hats at Sabaody Archipelago!
It's hard to corner them.
Magellan's target is Straw-chan!
We'd appreciate your help if
you just guard the outside.
Let's leave the riot to Saldeath and...
I knew that he was lying!
Un, deux, trois!
Hey! You're not allowed
to beat other prisoners!
...summon all the other forces
of Impel Down to level 4!
You weren't going to trust the
word of a Warlord, were you?
We'll raise this drawbridge which is
the only entrance to the prison...
Do you wanna get executed right here?!
Gum-Gum...
Roger that!
Anyway, I wonder how he got through
the Navy's impregnable defenses...
Gum-Gum...
If they manage to escape from Minotaurus
and come down here to the Burning Heat Hell,
...and seal off Impel Down completely!
...Queer Pistol!
Maybe he just flew in!
Don't worry. There is no way out...
I'll execute them with my own hands!
...Queer Gatling!
Cut the crap! If you weren't
known as the hero of the Navy,
FORMER BAROQUE WORKS ASSASSIN--
DAZ BONEZ A.K.A. Mr. 1
...Queer Giant Scythe!
...of this underwater prison!
This great prison Impel Down
is not to be trifled with!
I would have made you take full
responsibility for your family, Garp!
Now, can you tell which
is the real Straw-chan?
Alright then, we'll guard the outside.
I'm sure it's very hard to tell!
Your condition has been granted. Now, you...
You're a good boy.
You can take this old man's life but the
situation is far more serious than that!
It's hot!
I'm well aware!
Bon-chan, your clothes...
I'll follow the orders
to convene as I promised.
A koala?
You gotta get away while I draw the
Hydra's attention to me, Straw-chan!
The air is so hot up here.
It's not funny!
You're kidding me!
Welcome back!
This has all been
the Navy's blundering!
A koala.
It's unbelievably hot!
Thank you. Escort the Snake
Princess to her quarters.
Huh?
Here, here! I'm here, Hydra-chan!
Come on, come on! Oh come on!
We have no choice.
Do you realize how much Tsuru and I
worked to deal with the aftermath?!
A koala?
Yes, sir. This way.
A koala.
This is the safest place to be.
Hey, that's mine! Give it back!
I got you!
I'll bring you a meal right away.
But we gotta figure out how to get to level 1
I said "that's no use!"
Shut up!
I don't want it. Reduce
the amount from now on.
Really?
because we don't have much time!
--There are more?!
--No!
Don't question me! Such insolence!
Oh Come My Surprise!
Oh... I'm totally out of spit!
We're completely sealed off!
I-I'm sorry, Madam.
Are we gonna die like this?
Vice-Admiral Momonga!
Please wait, Warden Magellan!
We're still evacuating...
What's wrong?
We got a report that Red-Haired
had a run-in in the New World!
Augh! Why is he poisoning his own people?!
Ouch!
Impossible! It must be a mistake!
A koala?
No! Hydra's poison is a paralytic neurotoxin!
Ow, ow, ow...
Why now? Who did he fight against?!
Ow, ow, ow!  This floor is like a frying pan!
It's gonna run through your body causing
horrible pain and eventually it will kill you!
It's hard to believe but it's
Kaido of The Four Emperors!
What happened here?
I don't see any of the guards
who were here a while ago.
Kaido?!
Headquarters believes that
Red-Haired intercepted Kaido...
It hurts! Get me an antidote now!
Hannyabal?!
It's so quiet. Maybe we're dead already.
...and stopped him from attacking Whitebeard!
Magellan's here, too. What's going on?
Augh! Stay away!
Get away when I'm fighting! Fools!
I have a bad feeling about this!
But it wasn't a large battle.
That kind of thing is bound to happen!
I-I'm very sorry, sir!
Are we in the desert?! It's so hot!
I'm hungry, hungry, hungry!
That's how insecure the sea is now!
He still has an appetite
under these circumstances!
A brush with The Four Emperors is...
Why is it so quiet?
Straw-chan is quite a guy!
a serious matter that's beyond our
control in these circumstances.
You have a special visitor, Ace!
Level 3! Oh, I never wanted to come here!
But it seems impossible
to get away from Magellan!
Maybe, there's absolutely no way that
we can avoid the war against Whitebeard!
Guess who's here!
Straw Hat! I'm doomed along with you, again!
Jimbei! Even you have never met her before,
Oh! Looks like the lion's taking a cat nap!
I was talking!
Follow me if you can!
so there's no way that
Ace can guess who it is.
Do you think that it'll be an all-out battle?
Ouch, ouch, ouch! Ouch!
She's well-known but never shows herself!
She leads the Kuja - the tribe of warriors!
This is especially difficult
for me and my wax powers.
I-I-It's burning!
One side is Whitebeard Pirates - the
strongest pirate crew in the world.
She's a Warlord of the Sea!
Yes! One head's gone!
The other side is all the forces of
the Navy including three Admirals
That's what I'd expect from Ace's brother.
Strong, noble, and the most
beautiful woman in the world!
S-Straw-chan! This is not good!
and The Seven Warlords of the Sea!
But it's over now!
She is the Pirate Empress Boa Hancock!
Oh no! Warden Magellan's gonna do it!
No matter who wins, the
war will become history!
Yeah, yeah, Hancock! Hancock-sama!
It's really big!
Where are the stairs?
Yo, goddess! When I become
warden, will you marry me?!
--Let's hurry to Marineford!
--Yes, sir!
Chloroform Ball!
I don't know.
Please!
He can't stand here for much longer.
What's going on?
Ouch! I really wanna become the warden!
That was close!
Magellan, Hannyabal, and the
demon guards are all here!
Alright, let's just go.
I mean, it really hurts
to be hit by the warden!
Put your gas masks on! Stay clear!
Warden's in the midst of a battle!
What's gonna happen on this floor?
What are you doing?!
Wow! Is she it?! She is so beautiful!
LEVEL 4 IN FRONT OF THE STAIRCASE
THAT LEADS TO LEVEL 3
It's really hot here!
--Tear and sneeze gas?!
--Damn! It's Magellan's poison gas!
Fasten your fireproof coat!
Straw Hat Luffy and others
should come out from this door!
So she's the Snake Princess
of the Kuja? Hey, turn around!
--Go somewhere else to fight!
--Atchoo! Who's the opponent?
What's this creature?!
I've never seen moves like those before!
How long do we have to walk
until we get somewhere?!
No information yet?
Hancock-chan!
Atchoo! Maybe the intruder
that they were talking about?
Maybe they got beaten by Minotaurus.
Look how sexy she is!
Chatting won't do anything but waste energy.
It's Minotaurus!
Now it's poison gas in addition to
the heat of hell?! Give me a break!
Young lady! Come to our cell!
Minotaurus?!
Wardens should not hide!
We will love you tenderly!
Atchoo! What the... Atchoo! Atchoo!
Come out of there right now!
A cold-blooded demon guard!
Wow! Grilled chicken is served!
What a good smell! I wanna
visit the Maiden Island!
My eyes itch and they're tearing up!
A monster that tosses people
around like garbage!
Don't be ridiculous!
Don't open it without
notice! It's too bright!
That's a hummingbird that fluttered down
from upstairs and got grilled in the air.
There's only women and
everybody's naked there, right?
When you pass the seat on to
me, I want it to be more open.
What happened to me?! I
can't fight... Atchoo!
How hot is it in here?!
...Like this! Atchoo!
Shut up! This was custom-made for me.
It's cooked perfectly! Yum-yum!
That's who it is!
What's happening now?!
The Hydra stopped moving!
I prefer to stay closed up in a dark room!
DEMON GUARD - MINOTAURUS
How can he...?!
I want to keep my heart closed from you, too!
I'd prefer the lion from
upstairs be barbecued.
A monster?! A Devil Fruit eater?!
What do you want from me?
How do I know?!
Who wants to eat an animal
that speaks like a human?
It's coming!
Venom Road!
Nothing. I just wanted to take a look at you.
How can you have an appetite
at a time like this?
No matter how hard you try...
Because you will become the cause
of the war that I will take part in.
No way!
...you can't get away from me!
Bon-chan!
So I'm worth a look, then?
Oh! There are some cells!
Ouch!
Can't see a thing!
What?! It's a toilet as well?!
So what? It's a prison!
What speed!
Did you want to touch these?!
That's why you're an idiot!
Boa Hancock! Are you ignoring us?!
That's so gross!
We can hide from the sun in there
and it's definitely cooler than outside!
I can hear you!
Come here!
Oh yeah! You're so smart!
You've always been an empress with a strong
will who never obeyed any summonses,
Of course I am!
If I knew that we'd have to wait this
long, we would've gone to level 3...
Mr. 3, you better make some keys!
Straw-chan, watch out!
Yeah!
but you're taking part in this war?
...directly!
Wait just a Fouett!
Suddenly, you value your
title of Warlord of the Sea?!
No need to rush, Sadie-chan!
There's no place to hide...
I'm fine but these kids are
always lusting for blood, so...
So you're Jimbei. Don't snarl at me.
Hey, can we just get in...
Yo, yo, young lady! Young lady!
...they're losing their patience.
They're talking! Shut your mouths!
Isn't it a miserable sight?
Shut up, Magellan! Go have a shit as always!
Prisoners on this floor
I-I can't breathe!
Yeah, he's right!
DEMON GUARD MINOKOALA (HAWKISH)
were once all tough
criminals with more than 50 million berry bounties.
Hey, Snake Princess!
I bet the girls on the Maiden
Island are hungry for us guys!
Second Gear!
One touch and it's all over.
Hey you! Give me your post as warden!
Gum-Gum...
The heat from the Burning
Heat Hell underneath...
DEMON GUARD MINORHINOCEROS (BASHFUL)
...Jet...
Vice Warden!
Augh! The rock wall is melting!
...along with depriving them of food
and water has made them half dead.
Hey girl! I said "get your
ass over to our cell!"
...Bazooka!
Now, it's your turn to melt!
You guys!
She turned!
I need to rescue Ace...
DEMON GUARD MINOZEBRA (SHY)
You keep taunting me with
those coarse voices...
In the end, brothers like you and Ace...
I'm scared!
Oh, god! I can't resist!
This is level 3 - the Starvation Hell!
There's been an update!
How cute she is! Let us have her, Shit Man!
Straw Hat Luffy is now inside
of the Well Tower on level 3
Now you know why this floor
is covered with sand.
This is the vilest place in
the world! It makes me sick!
so they can't monitor him!
...share the same fate!
Don't tell me it's...
What?!
If they make it out of there, I'll
lay the blame on Warden and...
The prisoners call you "Shit Man."
How can you stand it, Warden?
They must've crushed any
pride you take in your job...
Ouch! I really wanna become the warden!
Chances are the sand that
you're stepping on now
Wow! She's irresistible!
I mean, it really hurts
to be hit by the warden!
Shame on you, Shit Man!
is the remains of a
prisoner who has dried up.
It'll be easier for us if they
would just fall from there.
However...
Please! Give me the antidote now!
Let me have her, Shit Man!
They were poisoned by Warden?
If we stay here too long,
Shit Man! Let me have Hancock!
There's the boiling Pool of Blood under
there and they're all Devil Fruit eaters so...
Yeah, I heard that he's fighting
with Straw Hat Luffy right now!
we will become like them before we know it.
I'm infuriated at their rudeness!
If it goes bad, we're gonna get poisoned too!
...once they fall into it, they'll be dead!
I don't deserve this!
I hope we don't!
We have to get away from here while
we still have sweat to spare.
Looks like Straw Hat's in a tough battle!
I don't wanna go to level 4!
It's good for us!
Oh no! We're gonna fall straight
into the Pool of Blood!
Let's go to level 4 in hurry!
You alright, Bon-chan?
Why?
I'm falling!
Seriously?!
Warden Magellan is the
strongest one in Impel Down
I almost died!
Hey, not that way! We gotta
take the stairs on the left.
Oh yeah?
I saw the great heavenly
garden of Oh Come My Way!
--No, we should take the pass on the right.
--Stop confusing me!
and he's focusing on Straw Hat now!
I'm sure that they are guarding
the staircase to level 3, too
The targets are proceeding to the back.
Wow! Warden, w-w-wait!
I see. Just keep watching.
You're very strong, indeed!
but at least, we know that we
won't face the worst terror!
That's gonna harm us, too! No!
Let's do it as we planned.
That means that this is our chance!
I'm sure that the monster's still alive
but I think he must be pretty hurt. Oh?
Oh no no! Fume, fume, fume!
My make-up's been ruined!
Warden Magellan! An update!
Straw-chan's in trouble!
You've gotten carried away!
Cosmetics, cosmetics! I need some cosmetics!
But I can't do anything for my dear friend!
Ugh! Oh man!
Plus, pointe shoes and
clothes and weapons and...
The invader--Straw Hat Luffy
- is already on this floor!
This is the least I can do!
I have to show you...
...drinks and tears and Oh Come My Way!
What?! What do you mean by that?!
I wanna get going now!
I'm thirsty and hungry!
Straw-chan!
Haven't you been able to
contact Warden Magellan yet?!
It seems like he fell into the well!
Hang in there!
Don't rush, Straw-chan!
I'm just...
--Not yet!
--What about the Blugoris?!
It's too-too easy to go down
to level 4 from here, actually!
...spinning for you!
There's the Pool of Blood underneath!
They headed off to catch the
invaders with their commander!
...who is boss in this prison!
How are they still alive?!
Damn! The security of Impel Down
shouldn't fall to pieces this easily!
Oh, really?!
I think the giant piece of the floor
that they were on enabled them...
Yes! It's too-too easy! Much too-too!
It's not gonna help him!
Why...
...to avoid falling into the pool.
--There it is, Straw-chan!
--Heh?
How stupid am I?!
...are we back where we started from?!
How lucky they are!
Climb this big wall!
--There's another thing!
--What?!
Looks like we went in a circle.
My life will be worth something
if I can die for my friend!
All the way to the top?
Quit being so relaxed!
Warden, it stinks!
Yes! But don't just barge
in! Watch your step!
I mean, wow, this situation really stinks!
You gotta get up and fight in the
name of Oh Come My Way, Bon Clay!
I told you that we should go right.
Alright!
I hope we make it to level 4 soon.
Minotaurus the demon guard fell into
the well also and he's not moving!
Ow, ow, ow, ouch!
Oh man!
--I told you "I'm not going!"
Having said that...
No way! They defeated him?!
What the hell?! It's hot
like a heated iron pot!
You have to guide me!
I can't move my legs!
You said that we were
gonna save Ace together!
His Hydra appears!
A heated iron pot?
I think so.
It's something like that,
Straw-chan! Your hand alright?
We never said that!
That can't be true! I can't believe it!
Ouch!
Stop imagining things as you want them to be!
Here we go!
Calm down!
Didn't you say you would?
They are in!
Ouch!
Ow, ow, ow... Ouch!
Straw-chan!
Alright, draw the net!
Follow these orders!
Yes, sir!
--What're you doing?!
--Stop, Magellan!
I can't even help my friend?
Here, Straw-chan! You should
take a look at this!
There are only two ways
to get out from level 4 -
You fool! We were just joking! Don't!
Can't I do something?!
two staircases that they can take without
authorization by security guards.
I'm going on my own then!
Calm down and think!
Ah?
Split our forces here into three.
Hannyabal, you take this staircase
which leads to level 3!
Swan...
...Arabesque!
Sadie-chan, you defend the stairway
to level 5 with the demon guards!
Swan is dead...
There's a huge amount of hot air and smoke!
What's this?!
Oh no! It's a trap! They got us already!
Gimme a break!
It's not gonna work!
It's hard to even stand here!
No, I don't wanna defend...
Right! But...
I wanna attack!
...this is level 4 - the Burning
Heat Hell where you wanna go!
Being on the attack
is my true calling, Warden!
Wait just a Fouett?!
You bastard! You can't do this to me!
I'll let them get away and
lay the blame on Warden!
It's made of iron!
I can't use my Chop-Chop Fruit power!
Burning Heat? Is it down there?
The rose wilts...
Do you have any objections?
Oh no! You're gonna die!
Yes! As you mentioned before, level
4 is exactly like a giant iron pot!
Of course, it contains Sea Prism Stone!
Gimme a break! That won't work either!
Please stop... sighing!
They're gonna torture us for
attempting to break out.
I need... I need an antidote! Shit!
I didn't complain!
Once you go down there,
We're goners.
you'll see a boiling pool of blood
and the blazing sea of fire!
I can feel your evil intentions towards me!
Memoirs of a Winter's Sky!
We got the invader - Straw
Hat Luffy and two others!
Once you catch them, you can
do whatever you want to them!
I did it!
--What do you mean "two others?!"
--Don't antagonize them, Buggy-kun!
I have the authority and the ability...
The heat on this level is
nothing compared to down there!
The garden of Oh Come My Way is calling me...
...to execute any of you at
my whim! Don't forget it!
Yes! That sounds irresistible!
It's over.
We can just jump down from here...
Absolutely not! I've run out of ideas!
All the rest of you, just go after them!
Damnit! I gotta rip this net!
...but if you land on the
wrong spot, you'll be fried.
I can't think of anything!
There are guards and Blugoris here!
You're gonna have to risk your life
just to go further from now on!
I don't care if they're dead or alive!
--Put the Sea Prism Stone handcuffs on them!
--Roger!
Yes, sir!
I can't... No matter what
I do, I can't help him!
"Almost dead" would do for me!
Damn! Damn! Damn!
I won't let Straw Hat Luffy and
the others toy with me any longer!
All right, Hancock-dono.
You can talk freely now.
They'll meet their doom
in this Burning Heat Hell!
I'm done.
Hey! Is what you just told me true?!
Who're you?
Why would I lie to you?
I'm Saldeath.
But first...
Gum-Gum...
The Warden is finally going to make his move!
Bon-chan!
Saru-desu!? But you don't
look like a saru (monkey).
Oh yeah!
...Stamp!
He was worried that you might get mad.
You said that there's
someone that you wanna see.
No! You're not listening.
Who is it that you wanna see
at the risk of your life?
Are you done already?
I'm Saldeath.
What were they talking about?
So, you're a monkey, right?
People call him a miracle.
I dunno. I was trying really
hard to get away from you.
No! Get it right! It's my name!
Magellan guards the worst prisoners
in the worst prison in the world!
He was imprisoned on a baseless
charge. He's known as Ivan-san!
Give up.
You have to take another dump?!
Ace-san.
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow... It's
insanely hot in this passage!
CHIEF GUARD - SALDEATH--
A COMMANDER OF BLUGORIS
It's no use holding out.
What did she just tell you?
He's the queen of Kamabakka Kingdom,
the pink paradise of the Grand Line!
He's the master of hell!
There's no place to get away...
Even my lungs are burning!
NEAR THE "POOL OF BLOOD"
...in this closed underwater prison!
Make up your mind, Bon Clay!
Every queer looks up to this world's
greatest queen of all queers!
Hurry! I wanna get through this level!
She said that my brother's here!
It's lucky you were caught by me.
Which way should we go?!
What?! The one with a straw hat
that you always talk about?!
The queen of all queers?!
Because there are four demon guards
prowling around on the floors beyond this.
You guys are so pathetic!
I'm sorry!
There's a queen for queers?! Wow!
That's insane!
There's no way to beat Magellan!
If you just keep your cool, the fire
is like your queer little friend!
Yes, there is!
I wanna see him even just for a
little bit and rescue him if I can!
What?!
But I know how you feel!
This floor is a little bit
hotter than the upper level!
Oh? Yeah, it's a little too hot!
Ah? I didn't notice but I'm
climbing now! I wanna go down!
We have no chance to win!
I'm sorry but I gotta run!
He's right! I don't wanna
face them and the warden!
Hmmm... I can feel that my body's burning!
But I guess If I keep going, it's
gonna go downwards at some point!
I'm sorry, Straw-chan! I'm sorry!
If only we have gone the right way there...
Oh? Ouch!
Oh no. We were watching you
We can't handle any more of that!
I'm hungry!
We got an image! He's
about to enter district C!
but no matter which way you choose,
you would have ended up here.
This is our only chance to get away
while Magellan is fighting Straw Hat!
Hey! What're you, nuts?! Why're
you bringing him back again?!
It's that way! Let's go!
Alright, I see him!
Oh, is that how it was?!
H-Hey! Where're you going?!
Are you out of your mind, you idiot?!
You said you were gonna break out!
Vongole bianco!
--It's too hot!
--Shut up!
Look how many there are!
Oh, Chief!
Straw Hat!
It doesn't matter! Think about it!
Pasta?!
I knew you'd want to come with me!
Hmm... What must be there that
Straw-chan's running towards?
Soup spaghetti!
They put demon guards at
the staircase to level 5
No one wants to follow you to hell!
He's onto pasta now!
Sea Prism Stone nets, again!
because they don't want to let
Straw Hat get to the lower levels!
BON-CHAN'S ROUGH MAP OF LEVEL 4
He smashed into us while we were hiding!
We're gonna get squashed!
--Spaghetti!
--The Sphinx is awake!
The security here is the poorest!
I dunno why!
It's the kitchen!
Oh no, he's gonna break the net!
--Oh, I knocked him your way.
--Oh, okay... No, it's not okay!
That was close!
I'm hungry, too! Wait for me, Straw-chan!
If we miss this chance, they'll
tighten their defenses!
Don't let those three,
especially Straw Hat get away!
I don't wanna run anymore!
Wow! That'd be nice!
I should've...
This is our best chance! Because
eventually Straw Hat's gonna lose!
I should've let myself
get caught rather than run away!
It'll be even better if
they have drinks, too!
Deep-fried noodle!
We gotta get to level 3 before that!
Oh no! The lion!
Wait a minute, Buggy!
Stupid monster!
Damnit!
Noodles, again!
Minotaurus! I'm gonna die!
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
He must've been going through a phase!
Maybe you're right!
Smells good...
Yeah!
Wait a minute, you lion!
That leaves me one choice!
Ouch, ouch... Smells good...
I never heard anything about Vice Warden
Hannyabal eating any Devil Fruit!
There he is!
That's Straw Hat Luffy!
This is great! Now, we can run!
Hey, Straw Hat!
If I can blow the others
up with my Muggy Ball,
Do you remember the Buggy Ball?!
Get them!
Oh! There are a lot of them!
The powerful and special weapon that
I used to make you scared as hell?!
all we have to deal with is Hannyabal!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
This floor is really hot but once I
eat, I'll be filled with energy again!
That's right! Let's do it!
No.
I'm here to help you!
I don't want to stay in this heat anymore!
Stop!
You don't? You can't be serious...
Zoro!
Ready?!
I'm sure that you remember the Buggy Ball!
Gum-Gum...
You were there when I blew up the
whole town with just one shot!
I fooled you!
--We're gonna fight our way through!
--Right!
Ka-boom! Remember the ka-boom?!
...Fireworks!
Oh? Where'd they go?
Hannyabal-sama! Here come
Buggy the Clown and Mr. 3!
Swan Arabesque!
I think it's hard to forget
something that was so shocking!
Hurry up, Mr. 3!
They're trying to get to
level 3! Don't let them!
I can't move quickly due to this heat...
No.
We found Straw Hat Luffy!
Muggy...
Ah! They climbed up the net!
Candle...
Team A is fighting against him right now!
Wait!
--Swan, swan!
--Oh?
Team B has arrived on the scene!
Um... Well...
Straw Hat!
Stand down, everyone!
They're closing in on him
together with Team A!
If you see Ace, tell him
that I said "hello" and...
I mean...
"let's have a drink if I
ever see you again alive!"
Spin, spin! I'm spinning!
But they've taken heavy casualties!
There is this big and powerful
cannonball called Buggy Ball...
Hannyabal-sama!
Be a good little live bait for us, stupid!
They're requesting backup! What shall we do?!
I'm the vice warden and I'm in charge here!
He's not Zoro but he sounds familiar...
It's kinda like my special weapon...
Yes! Here comes my chance!
I was happy to see you were
alright but... Alright! See ya!
Buggy Ball?!
It's been a long time!
Straw-chan, it's me!
Gum-Gum...
Heaven is on my side!
I assume that you have a lot of confidence
in it because you put your name on it!
Thanks for helping me!
...Whip!
On top of the invasion of Straw Hat Luffy,
if these two are allowed to pass through,
Ugh! How sweet!
Spin, spin! I'm spinning!
Ouch! It's heartbreaking!
Yes, I have!
"Oh Come My Way" Kenpo -
Memoirs of a Summer's Day!
Stay sharp! He is a pirate with
a 300 million berry price!
I'm sure that the top
officials won't be happy!
And I made it smaller without reducing
its power so I can carry it around!
So how was my secret talent?!
And they're gonna blame Warden
Magellan for all of this!
--It's called Muggy Ball!
--You changed the name!
Cool!
Gimme a break!
--Team A and B have been wiped out!
--C, D, and E have major losses!
Anyway, you take this! The
special weapon - Muggy Ball!
And then...
Now is our chance to run!
--Running now wouldn't be like Bon Clay...
--Huh?!
Alright!
Backup from upstairs won't do!
If we abandon pals who would risk
their lives to pick up their pal,
I will become the warden!
I don't have time to fight you all!
We can't compete with them!
We can't hold that
position any longer!
will we... be able to
enjoy our food tomorrow?!
Hannyabal-sama! Shouldn't we catch them?!
Buckwheat noodle!
Oh no! He's still around!
Miss Hina! The sheep ship
is heading to the east!
What shall we do?! Give us an order!
What?!
You were tricked, weren't you!
The position that I worked
so hard to gain is at risk!
Wow! Cool!
You bastard!
Alright, clear the way!
Were experts at disguising
ourselves! And...
You did it!
What?!
He's gonna run! Chase him!
We were expecting you! Please come this way!
It was a piece of cake!
Where are the stairs to go down?!
were the Straw Hats friends...!
Now, you remember it, Straw Hat?!
Hurry and make way!
Bring it on!
Don't be rude to our guests!
We'll never forget you!
Is it okay to do this?
We'll soon arrive at "Fire Fist" Ace's floor.
Maybe this is a part of
the Vice Warden's plan!
Finally. It took a long time.
Please! Go right ahead!
Bon-chan!
I'm so disappointed that you're not
Zoro but at least you're alive!
It couldn't be helped.
That floor is filled with notorious criminals from
all over,
What's up, partner?!
Screw you!
Take a good look!
We see through your plan, you fool!
Damn! He's still alive!
It's our chance! Get Straw Hat!
There is a sea of guards down there!
not just "Fire Fist."
Go away!
It can't be this easy!
We can beat him, Straw-chan!
It is not the place one can enter casually.
And level 4 is about screams and cries but
there's not a single guard at the fire torture pit!
We know that this is a trap!
Hey, 3! You sure that you can't
use your Wax-Wax powers?!
You assholes! What do you think
you're doing to my friend?!
We're doing this as a favor for a Warlord.
Special weapon--Muggy Ball!
--It'll melt in 3 seconds!
--That means you can use it!
Candle Lock!
It's my request.
Fly, fly, I'm flying! "Oh
Come My Way" Kenpo...
You have to grant it, right?
Yeah, Sphinx! Fight back!
Yes, I have to!
...Memoirs of a Winter's Sky!
Let's go! It's up there!
We ought to check the staircases right away!
Maybe they ambushed us and
boxed us in on this floor!
Why didn't you just go?!
By the way, there is a prisoner
who was once a Warlord like you.
Okay! He's not gonna attack us
after getting busted up like this!
You stupid bastards!
Ready, Straw Hat?!
You don't have to worry. I
just want to see "Fire Fist."
You gotta get rough to teach
a wild animal a lesson!
--Candle Lock!
--Alright!
If they've been waiting on level 4,
that means they only want Straw Hat!
--Oh no!
--Oh yeah!
Gum-Gum...
I won't do anything improper.
Because we only came here by accident!
You better keep it that way.
...Mallet Rifle!
Fried noodle bun...
They all know our names and
faces as escapees anyway!
Hey, Bon-chan! I thought
that you were dead...
Don't you wanna give up now?
What I am concerned about is
that it is very likely that...
...after sacrificing yourself for us!
Gimme a break! Queers never die!
I'm gonna rescue Ace
...they have the all-stars of Impel Down
on this floor to put an end to this fuss!
It's hot...
and we're gonna get out of here!
We'll be safe here! They're
after Straw Hat as we wished.
Oh, is that right?!
That means, on top of the
three other demon guards,
They closed up the staircase going up.
I'm not gonna die without even seeing him!
It's already too much for me to stay here.
Warden Magellan might be here, too!
Let's see how Mr. 2 Bon Clay's power works!
I'm not gonna let you execute Ace!
Un, deux, faint!
Then, we're through!
He ate the Clone-Clone Fruit
and he can turn into anyone whose face
has been touched by his right hand.
Un, deux, come on!
What's that smoke?!
Get out of my way!
I don't wanna lose to you by not
touching you because you're poisonous!
--Un, deux, faint!
--Who's singing?
He turned into Zoro because
he touched him before.
Stop!
Un, deux, come on!
Don't stand in my way!
I'd rather touch you and...
Un, deux, faint!
We did it!
Here's another escapee!
We beat the monster of hell!
...give you my arms!
Un, deux, come on!
He keeps gaining friends as
he descends deeper and deeper!
Oh, that scared me!
I thought that it was a spear or something!
Alright, let's keep it
up and go on to level 4!
W-What's this?
You know, this world is
about a man and a woman!
I don't want your arms!
Blugoris! Don't let them get away!
But if you want me to have
them, I'll take them!
Ow, ow, ouch! Is it jelly?! Or crap?!
But when you're queer,
you're a little of both!
Gum-Gum...
Straw-chan, look up!
That's why we're the greatest!
...Jet Bazooka!
By the way, Straw-chan, I heard
that you wanna get to level 5!
The greatest!
The queer way is the greatest!
This is level 4.
Yes, indeed! Can you show me the way?
I've had enough of you running
around and playing by your rules!
All of our forces are rallied
under Warden Magellan!
The greatest!
Alright, I'll go with you!
The queer way!
Actually, there's someone
that I wanna see on level 5!
Who're you?!
The queer way!
M-Magellan!
You sure?!
The queer waaay!
Okay then, let's do it together!
Stay away!
You're dead, you vermin!
Uh-huh!
Let's go!
Luffy!
Yeah!
Luffy teams up with Mr. 2 Bon Clay again,
Warden Magellan has finally
made his appearance!
Impel Down beefs up security
after its series of incidents,
Luffy, after attacking Magellan,
whom was unscathed,
Buggy and the others want to escape,
while Luffy wants to proceed to level 4.
sealing the only way in and out.
and they blast through level 3, taking
out armies of Blugoris along the way.
The power of the Venom-Venom
Fruit makes him untouchable,
In a stroke of good (or bad) luck, an
accident drops all of them into level 4.
ends up trapped by the Venom-Venom Fruit.
Luffy and the others are
completely trapped inside.
but Luffy risks it all to take him on.
At last, they're close to level 4!
But waiting for them there is
Warden Magellan, who has amassed
In order to save Ace, Luffy brashly
releases a self-destructive attack!
Unaware of the dilemma he's in,
Luffy continues toward Ace's floor,
But before they get there, an
immensely powerful demon guard,
However, faced with the might of
the Hydra produced by Magellan,
all the forces in Impel
Down together to stop them!
What will the battle's outcome be?
and unexpectedly encounters
an old friend along the way...
Bon Clay makes a surprising move!
Minotaurus, stands before them.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"All Forces Have Gathered! The Battle
on Level 4 The Burning Heat Hell!"
"Warden Magellan's Strategy!
Straw Hat Entrapment Completed!"
"The Showdown Has Come!
Luffy's Desperate Last Attack!"
"The Unleashed Swan!
A reunion with Bon Clay!"
"Mighty Magellan! Bon Clay Bugs Out!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!