Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
Luffy met Buggy, former
Baroque Works agents Mr. 3
and Mr. 2 Bon Clay in the prison
and they all fell into level 4!
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
Smells good...
Ouch, ouch... Smells good...
I've had enough of you running
around and playing by your rules!
Who're you?!
M-Magellan!
You're dead, you vermin!
"Mighty Magellan! Bon Clay Bugs Out!"
Uh oh! I gotta get out of here!
The Burning Heat Floor is too hot!
W-Warden! W-Wait for just a second!
Don't start fighting yet!
Get away from here! Warden's
poison will get us, too!
Damn you! I was about to find
all of that good smelling food!
I'm hungry! You need to get out of my way!
You're so high-spirited. Don't worry.
You won't need to think
about eating ever again!
What do you mean?
S-Straw-chan! Don't fight him!
He's the warden of Impel Down--Magellan!
He ate the Venom-Venom Fruit!
You gotta run away! He's the last
person that you wanna fight!
Venom-Venom? He's poisonous?
Yes, I am.
Straw Hat Luffy! You're a rookie pirate
with a 300 million berry price
whose caused far too many problems
by rebelling against the Navy
and the World Government!
And now, you've snuck into this great,
historic prison with iron-tight security!
I have to thank you for ruining
my reputation as a warden!
I know why you're here!
You came to rescue your
brother Portgaz D. Ace,
the second division commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates!
But I assure you that there's no way that
you can save him and get out of Impel Down!
Straw Hat Luffy! This is where
you will meet your fate!
I'll find out all about when
and how you broke in...
...after I pass down your sentence!
Come out, Luffy!
That was close!
It looks like I can't
go any farther with you.
I can't use my power while
wearing those Sea Prism cuffs.
And they'll take my cloak
away so I can't hide you.
I wish I could do more but...
What're you talking about?
I wouldn't have made it this
far without your help!
Luffy.
I'm not gonna tell you
even if it means death!
Every prisoner says that
before they are tortured!
However, Straw Hat, what you're about
to go through is far worse than torture!
Straw-chan!
Magellan's whole body is poisonous
so you can't even touch him!
Do you think you can beat a guy like that?!
I will!
Let's go back to the Pool
of Blood and turn right!
Straw-chan! Give up on that
food and let's get to level 5!
That's no use!
Three demon guards and their commander
are guarding the staircase to level 5!
What?!
All exits on this floor
have already been covered!
There's no way for you to...
I'll let them get away and
lay the blame on Warden!
...get out of here!
No! I don't wanna believe it!
Hydra!
W-What's that?!
Made out of poison?!
A body of pure poison?!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
No!
--Straw-chan!
--Bon-chan!
--Why did you do that?!
--I told you that you can't fight!
The poison will harm you
if you get it all over you
but even one touch will be lethal!
I can't fight without touching it!
That's why you can't fight him!
Can't you say anything
other than "you can't"?
Magellan's target is Straw-chan!
Un, deux, trois!
Gum-Gum...
...Queer Pistol!
...Queer Gatling!
...Queer Giant Scythe!
Now, can you tell which
is the real Straw-chan?
I'm sure it's very hard to tell!
Bon-chan, your clothes...
You gotta get away while I draw the
Hydra's attention to me, Straw-chan!
Huh?
Here, here! I'm here, Hydra-chan!
Come on, come on! Oh come on!
I got you!
I said "that's no use!"
--There are more?!
--No!
Oh Come My Surprise!
Please wait, Warden Magellan!
We're still evacuating...
Augh! Why is he poisoning his own people?!
No! Hydra's poison is a paralytic neurotoxin!
It's gonna run through your body causing
horrible pain and eventually it will kill you!
It hurts! Get me an antidote now!
Augh! Stay away!
Get away when I'm fighting! Fools!
I-I'm very sorry, sir!
I'm hungry, hungry, hungry!
He still has an appetite
under these circumstances!
Straw-chan is quite a guy!
But it seems impossible
to get away from Magellan!
Follow me if you can!
Ouch, ouch, ouch! Ouch!
I-I-It's burning!
Yes! One head's gone!
That's what I'd expect from Ace's brother.
But it's over now!
Oh no! Warden Magellan's gonna do it!
Chloroform Ball!
That was close!
Put your gas masks on! Stay clear!
Warden's in the midst of a battle!
--Tear and sneeze gas?!
--Damn! It's Magellan's poison gas!
--Go somewhere else to fight!
--Atchoo! Who's the opponent?
Atchoo! Maybe the intruder
that they were talking about?
Now it's poison gas in addition to
the heat of hell?! Give me a break!
Atchoo! What the... Atchoo! Atchoo!
My eyes itch and they're tearing up!
What happened to me?! I
can't fight... Atchoo!
...Like this! Atchoo!
What's happening now?!
The Hydra stopped moving!
Venom Road!
No matter how hard you try...
...you can't get away from me!
Can't see a thing!
Did you want to touch these?!
One touch and it's all over.
Augh! The rock wall is melting!
Now, it's your turn to melt!
I need to rescue Ace...
In the end, brothers like you and Ace...
...share the same fate!
Please! Give me the antidote now!
They were poisoned by Warden?
Yeah, I heard that he's fighting
with Straw Hat Luffy right now!
If it goes bad, we're gonna get poisoned too!
I hope we don't!
Looks like Straw Hat's in a tough battle!
It's good for us!
Why?
Warden Magellan is the
strongest one in Impel Down
and he's focusing on Straw Hat now!
I'm sure that they are guarding
the staircase to level 3, too
but at least, we know that we
won't face the worst terror!
That means that this is our chance!
Straw-chan's in trouble!
But I can't do anything for my dear friend!
This is the least I can do!
Straw-chan!
Hang in there!
I'm just...
...spinning for you!
It's not gonna help him!
How stupid am I?!
My life will be worth something
if I can die for my friend!
You gotta get up and fight in the
name of Oh Come My Way, Bon Clay!
Having said that...
I can't move my legs!
Ouch!
Straw-chan!
I can't even help my friend?
Can't I do something?!
Calm down and think!
Swan...
...Arabesque!
Swan is dead...
Gimme a break!
It's not gonna work!
Wait just a Fouett?!
The rose wilts...
Gimme a break! That won't work either!
Memoirs of a Winter's Sky!
I did it!
The garden of Oh Come My Way is calling me...
Absolutely not! I've run out of ideas!
I can't think of anything!
I can't... No matter what
I do, I can't help him!
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp!
Magellan guards the worst prisoners
in the worst prison in the world!
He's the master of hell!
Make up your mind, Bon Clay!
I'm sorry!
There's no way to beat Magellan!
We have no chance to win!
I'm sorry but I gotta run!
I'm sorry, Straw-chan! I'm sorry!
This is our only chance to get away
while Magellan is fighting Straw Hat!
Are you out of your mind, you idiot?!
Look how many there are!
It doesn't matter! Think about it!
They put demon guards at
the staircase to level 5
because they don't want to let
Straw Hat get to the lower levels!
The security here is the poorest!
If we miss this chance, they'll
tighten their defenses!
This is our best chance! Because
eventually Straw Hat's gonna lose!
We gotta get to level 3 before that!
Maybe you're right!
I never heard anything about Vice Warden
Hannyabal eating any Devil Fruit!
If I can blow the others
up with my Muggy Ball,
all we have to deal with is Hannyabal!
That's right! Let's do it!
I don't want to stay in this heat anymore!
Ready?!
--We're gonna fight our way through!
--Right!
Hannyabal-sama! Here come
Buggy the Clown and Mr. 3!
They're trying to get to
level 3! Don't let them!
Muggy...
Candle...
Wait!
Stand down, everyone!
Hannyabal-sama!
I'm the vice warden and I'm in charge here!
Yes! Here comes my chance!
Heaven is on my side!
On top of the invasion of Straw Hat Luffy,
if these two are allowed to pass through,
I'm sure that the top
officials won't be happy!
And they're gonna blame Warden
Magellan for all of this!
And then...
I will become the warden!
Hannyabal-sama! Shouldn't we catch them?!
What shall we do?! Give us an order!
Alright, clear the way!
What?!
We were expecting you! Please come this way!
Hurry and make way!
Don't be rude to our guests!
Is it okay to do this?
Maybe this is a part of
the Vice Warden's plan!
Please! Go right ahead!
Screw you!
We see through your plan, you fool!
It can't be this easy!
We know that this is a trap!
Special weapon--Muggy Ball!
Candle Lock!
Why didn't you just go?!
You stupid bastards!
--Oh no!
--Oh yeah!
Don't you wanna give up now?
I'm gonna rescue Ace
and we're gonna get out of here!
I'm not gonna die without even seeing him!
I'm not gonna let you execute Ace!
What's that smoke?!
I don't wanna lose to you by not
touching you because you're poisonous!
I'd rather touch you and...
...give you my arms!
I don't want your arms!
But if you want me to have
them, I'll take them!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Bazooka!
Luffy, after attacking Magellan,
whom was unscathed,
ends up trapped by the Venom-Venom Fruit.
In order to save Ace, Luffy brashly
releases a self-destructive attack!
What will the battle's outcome be?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Showdown Has Come!
Luffy's Desperate Last Attack!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!