Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
"THANK YOU"
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
Now at level 4 the Burning Heat Floor,
Bon Clay who was saved by
Ivankov of New Kama Land...
This is your punishment.
Buggy and Mr. 3 who were
trying to get to level 3...
Together with Red-nosed Buggy
Warden Magellan has ambushed him!
...has just learned that Luffy's
treatment has already begun!
and former Baroque Works
agents Mr. 3 and Bon clay,
There is no way to neutralize the
amount of poison you have absorbed!
...have been captured by
Vice Warden Hannyabal, but...
I'll find out all about when
and how you broke in...
Don't underestimate miracles!
he reached level 4 the Burning Heat Hell...
Meanwhile, Luffy's battle
against Warden Magellan is...
...after I pass down your sentence!
"Believe in Miracles!
Bon Clay's Cries from the Heart!"
...but was poisoned by Magellan,
the warden of Impel Down
What do you think you're doing to...
This is your punishment.
I'm not gonna tell you
even if it means death!
...Bon-chan?!
and taken into custody!
Leave Bon-chan...
There is no way to neutralize the
amount of poison you have absorbed!
...alone!
No!
You will agonize for 24 hours
As Luffy was taken into custody
on level 5--the Freezing Hell,
M-Miracles?
After fighting the Army Wolves,
Luffy and Bon Clay lost consciousness
and then pass...
Straw-chan!
Bon-chan!
Yeah!
Bon Clay tried his hardest
to find a way to save him!
...to the real hell!
But it will take a tremendous miracle
for Straw boy to survive!
and a mysterious man named Inazuma
rescued them and took them to...
No way?!
Why did you do that?!
I mean, what do you mean that
you can't make an antidote!
I told you that you can't fight!
I believe in Straw-chan's spirit!
Welcome to...
"For his friend!
Bon Clay Goes to the Deadly Rescue!"
The poison will harm you
if you get it all over you
I believe that miracles can happen!
but even one touch will be lethal!
A miracle?
Oh yeah! He is in Impel Down!
...Impel Down--Level 5.5!
B-Because it's Straw-chan!
Venom Road!
It's a secret garden for prisoners!
I believe that he can do it!
The queen of queers--
Warden Magellan! Great fight!
Ivan-san!
Then, stop panicking!
No matter how hard you try...
What should we do with the fallen Luffy?
We better find him now!
New Kama Land!
We have to trust him and wait!
He'll die soon but we don't
want him lying there.
Heehaw!
...you can't get away from me!
"A Paradise in Hell!
Impel Down Level 5.5!"
Throw him into the Central Tower on level 5.
"Luffy's Treatment Begins!
Ivan-san's Miraculous Power!"
Yes, sir!
So I ate the Horm-Horm Fruit
W-Warden Magellan!
Yeah! Yo! Wow!
T-This is no good!
We had a problem at the staircase to level 3!
and now I can control people's hormones
Magellan guards the worst prisoners
in the worst prison in the world!
and change their sex, body temperatures,
That's Hannyabal's post! What happened?
Ah hey! Hey!
skin colors, growth and emotions!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
I don't know the details!
I can remodel people from the inside,
He's the master of hell!
I'm like an engineer of the human body!
Third district, third district, wow!
Make up your mind, Bon Clay!
We have no choice!
We should lock ourselves up!
Hey. Hey!
Fourth district, fourth district, wow!
I can feel that you're
like the candies here...
There's no way to beat Magellan!
He's gone.
Gay district, gay district, wow!
Alright! I'll draw their attention!
...except they've all
transcended sex completely!
He's either dead or preserved for the future.
I'm sorry!
Open it quick!
We have no chance to win!
Dammit! Chew on this,
my special weapon--Muggy Ball!
Some men you see could have been women...
That's ridiculous!
I'm sorry but I gotta run!
My f-fingers!
Ha! How's that?!
...and some women could have been men!
I'm sorry, Straw-chan!
I can't move them! I can't even feel them!
That's some kind of miracle!
I'm sorry!
What?!
That's some kind of miracle-able!
That's frostbite! You're history!
Don't you wanna give up now?
I did it!
That's right!
Did you?!
I'm not gonna let you execute Ace!
He changed that man to a
woman by injecting hormones!
Damn, this is aggravating!
I did it... I broke the key!
I can't even bite this bread!
I don't wanna lose to you by not
touching you because you're poisonous!
What're you doing?!
It's too late!
I'd rather touch you and...
Umm... But I still can't believe
there's a place like this in a prison!
You're wonderful!
Candle Shield!
...give you my arms!
Gum-Gum...
I must be dreaming!
Hey, look! Here's a newcomer!
It's not a dream!
It's a dream land!
...Jet Bazooka!
Hey! What's your name?!
How much is your bounty?! Talk to us!
Heehaw!
All of these candies were lost
prisoners who made it here by luck!
That was close!
You better get into the cell now!
He's nearly dead!
Heehaw!
We don't need to!
He already got the poison punishment!
You see--there are entrances to
this New Kama Land on every floor!
I have an idea!
Is he...
What's the meaning of all this?!
Heehaw! Haw!
Stupid wolves! You can't get us now!
There's one at the bloody mountain of needles,
...Ivan-san?!
and in the lair of wild beasts!
It's no use biting it!
Or in the burning hellfire!
Hannyabal! I counted on you but all
of your guards have been beaten!
Even in the mortuary.
This Candle House is as hard as iron!
"The Showdown Has Come!
Luffy's Desperate Last Attack!"
We use those passages to
get everything we need!
Even with your big fangs, you can't break it!
Wake up, Hannyabal! What happened here?!
Let's go!
Oh yes!
W-Warden! Please let go of me!
Jailers would never think that
there was a paradise like this in hell.
1, 2! 1, 2!
Wow! This is nice!
They can't even touch us!
But we always know what's going on out there!
I-I am very sorry! I was off-guard!
I got a little too excited...
I-I don't want gomon (torture)!
Because we've got a Transponder Snail
I'm starting to get a little dizzy...
How thoughtless you guys are!
Ivan-sama, are you alright?
Komon (anus) stinks!
which is the same as the ones the jailers use.
I'm gonna... collapse...
Damn that queer! He abandoned us!
It's heavier than I thought!
So we can get all information
inside the prison!
If you'd have just shut up and gotten away,
I made it thicker than usual to protect us!
...Or not!
And we steal newspapers from garbage cans
I could have laid the blame on Warden!
A queer who uses martial arts did all this!
That was a joke?!
so we know what's going on outside, too!
Yeah? Well, good job!
You sure fooled me!
How can I put this...
He caught us by surprise!
I'm at the staircase to level 3!
We enjoyed watching the adventures
of the first invader--Straw boy...
No excuse!
Even if it's a tortoise's pace,
as long as we can get to the stairs,
You're Ivan-san, aren't you?!
We have some casualties
caused by the escapees' raid!
You let him get away and
he escaped to the upper levels, right?
then we can get out of here!
...as well as you and the others!
Oh dear!
Yes, we have Buggy the Clown
and Mr. 3 in custody!
That prisoner used to work for
Crocodile's Baroque Works.
That's right!
We had so much fun!
And as long as we're in here,
we can avoid the cold wind!
Do you know about me?!
Where are we in the prison?!
How did you find a space like this?!
Hey! Calling him Ivan-san
is so disrespectful!
He's the guy who used to call himself Mr. 2.
I told you to just be on your way
but you just had to fight me!
Alright!
I mean, that queer!
She's right!
Oh, this place wasn't always here.
1, 2! 1, 2!
He's the king of New Kama Ivan-sama!
That doesn't matter!
You stupid bastards!
He was captured in level 3.
I heard that there was a prisoner
with a hole-digging ability
Wait! Let's go back a little!
H-H-He's strong!
Ivan-sama! Ivan-sama!
I'm sure that we'll catch him in time.
Surprisingly strong!
Ivan-sama! Ivan-sama!
What happened to the riot on level 2?!
and with that candy in the lead,
Damn Hannyabal!
they built this prisoners' paradise long ago!
What's the matter?
Ivan-sama! Ivan-sama...
It's almost under control.
I don't wanna be tortured!
Something is wrong.
Hush, now, candies!
What happened to the wolves?
If I'm going to get tortured, I will...
I want all guards gathered
on level 4 to go to level 3!
This place is like an ant farm that's been
created by digging tunnels in the rock.
Don't sweat the small stuff!
Yeah, where the hell do they go?!
...bite off my tongue right here!
It's just a little thing!
All of them are gone!
Unleash all demon guards
under Sadie-chan's command!
It's right in the middle of level 5 and level 6!
Okay... I'm gonna bite... now!
They can call me whatever they want!
Even "Dooky" is fine!
I'm really gonna do it!
I'll leave the rest to you!
What's that noise?
Wait a minute! Level 6?!
There is such a floor?!
Okay! What about these two?
No, don't call me "Dooky!"
Do whatever you like!
Then why did you say it?!
You got me again!
Well, it's not widely known but...
Clean up all the mess now
and get things in order!
H-He is the miracle-worker?!
...there is level 6 where true villains are kept!
I'm going to head to my "private place."
The one that I worshipped for so long?!
T-This must be...
Every one of them is condemned
to a lifetime without parole!
Not "Dooky!"
That was pretty clever of them!
That's level 6--Eternal Hell!
Emporio Ivankov!
Ouch!
Exceedingly cruel crimes are often
covered up by the government.
"The runs"... as usual?
Hey you guys, get up and
look for the last escapee!
As are incidents that'd harm
the reputation of the government.
For example, you guys
rampaged all the way to level 4
Yes, in a second!
E-Excuse me!
What do you wanna do with these two?
but if you'd tried that a little while ago,
it wouldn't have been so easy.
You were the queen of
Kamabakka Kingdom, weren't you?!
Oh! I want to ask them about something.
Get us an interview room.
Because there was another
threat in this prison!
Who the hell is this guy
all covered in blood?!
15 years ago, my father who was
once king of a country himself...
I'll take charge of them.
H-He's coming!
Understood, sir.
He was the Jail Manager of Impel Down -
Hey! Get out of my way!
...went to Kamabakka Kingdom and...
Shiryu of the Rain!
Outta my way, you fools!
He's as strong as Warden Magellan.
...came back as a queer!
Earlier, I was...
Aak!
Alright then, Vice Warden!
If you think about how little
Magellan actually works,
Yeah.
We have no chance to win!
Shiryu was twice as troublesome.
I'm sorry but I gotta run!
Because the king became a queer,
Straw-chan! I'm sorry!
S-Strong as Warden Magellan?!
If you don't wanna get hurt,
both his country and family were ruined
just let me go through!
I'm sorry that I ran!
Impel Down was iron-tight with those two!
Now, what we'll do is...
and I fell from my princely status
to become a lowly pirate!
Let's get Mr. 2!
How do you know this guy?
Damn! Don't stand in my way!
I'm glad to have found you!
We're safe now!
Jail Manager Shiryu of the Rain...
You'll pay the price for ruining my life!
W-We escaped torture!
Drunken Swan Soiree!
Okay, what should we do now?
You know what we're gonna do!
I'm his friend!
We better hurry and...
No! No!
Straw-chan! I'm not gonna let you die!
Don't do that! Where did you get that thing?!
...rescue Straw-chan!
R-Rescue him?!
Watch it!
There's no way we can beat him!
We better go now!
I said "watch it!"
Did you hear them saying
that he's been poisoned
by Magellan and is on level 5?!
I'm not gonna dream an impossible dream!
I'm gonna die! I'm gonna die!
There's no hope for him to survive
If I'd stayed there any longer,
I'm 200% sure that I'd be killed!
If I get shot, I'm gonna...
What do you think you're doing, Shiryu?!
I'm gonna die...
and we'd die like dogs!
...Or not!
What do you mean?
He's right! Why should we even try?!
You're such a character!
I've gotta run!
The prisoners are not here
for your amusement!
He left the keys!
You were pulling my leg?!
I don't care if we die like dogs--or queers!
Don't look back!
I never thought about breaking out.
When I turned my back on
Straw-chan and Magellan,
No one cares whether or not these vermin die!
All I can do is run!
I had already died!
I gotta find Ivan-san as soon as possible!
I can't overlook your actions any longer!
Death Wink!
If anyone finds out what you've done here,
I thought that I better run
than suffer the same fate.
Ivan-san?!
How should I know
where that queer went?!
it will disgrace Impel Down!
Straw-chan!
And if there's a chance he'll survive,
Now I must exercise my authority
and put you under arrest!
Who the hell are you?!
then I'll be back to put my life
on the line and rescue him!
Emporio Ivancov?
That's what I swore!
And I ran!
Oh yeah, I remember him!
That's a very nice story,
but now you're free!
Yes! That's how Ivan-sama blinks!
He must be dead!
What are you looking at?!
Death Wink!
Why would you wanna go back
and risk your life again?!
He put prisoners to the sword as he wanted
and was out of control
He was able to turn back that
bullet with only a wink?!
Why are you looking for a missing person?!
so they hold him in level 6
now as a security risk.
Because I'm his friend!
I don't need any other reasons!
How did you get out of your cell?!
You seem to have brought me to my knees!
Friends?
Why don't you set me free?!
I've never heard of this!
We gotta deal with the poison
to save Straw-chan!
Even though it happened before I got here...
We never know what a cornered rat will do!
Do you know where the man named Ivan-san is?!
There are also pirates like
We need an antidote!
the world's most dangerous woman--
Catalina Devon,
Emporio Female Hormone!
Hello?! Can you hear me?!
You think that we can get it?
Hey, why don't you say something?!
"Great Battleship" San Juan Wolf,
But now you got enough poison on your hand...
It's too late anyway!
It's no use!
"Heavy Drinker" Vasco Shot!
Shut up!
They're all frozen in that cell!
I must... I must do this!
These are names that'd make
anyone shiver with fright!
...to affect your whole body!
I wanna know...
Wait for me!
Don't die on me yet, Straw-chan!
Yeah, I heard you.
What did you do?!
You're looking for that fairy, Ivancov, right?
No way?!
There are wretched criminals,
whose crimes were so cruel
I mean, what do you mean that
you can't make an antidote!
Do you know something?
Look! Do you see the forest?
even papers refused to mention them...
It must really hurt, poor boy!
You bastard! Don't tell me it's...
No one ever survives after...
Yeah.
...all down there in level 6.
There's an abandoned jailer's room in there.
Your father wanted to become a woman!
Your former boss is there, too!
...challenging Warden Magellan and
receiving a heavy dose of his poison!
He's just as crazy as the others!
I once saw a strange guy moving around there.
What's wrong with that?!
If it's just one kind, maybe we could
but we can't make an antidote...
What?! 0-chan?! Crocodile?!
Oh no!
Really?!
I'm gonna lose it!
...that works for various poisons!
Why don't you go and check?
You guys were enemies of
Straw boy at Alabasta, right?
Two mothers and one daughter!
And you people call yourselves
a medical team?!
Gimme a break!
Thank you!
What's wrong with that?!
You still don't give up?!
It's interesting!
No problem!
Huh?
It's your family!
I mean... give me a break and do something!
No! Please don't...
Gum-Gum...
It goes to show that anyone
can become friends!
I thought that's where the wolves live.
...Twin Jet Pistol!
We have to turn Straw Hat Luffy
over to the Navy!
...do it!
Oh? Is that so?
You're right!
But if we administer the medication
incorrectly, he'll die sooner!
There is also a Warlord of the Sea
- "First Son of the Sea" Jimbei!
What?!
Venom Blowfish!
I'm sorry to say this but
there's no way to keep him alive.
And the guy that Straw boy snuck in here for.
People have disappeared
occasionally in Impel Down.
What happened?
I told you! It's too late to save Straw Hat!
He's the second division commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates--
Portgaz D. Ace!
They didn't break out because
some of them could barely move.
There is no antidote.
That means we can't do anything for him!
I heard it over the radio!
They are brothers, right?!
They just disappeared without a trace.
We call it "Demoning away!"
Now, give up on Straw Hat
Yes, Straw-chan said that the only reason
he came here was to rescue him!
We all fear these unnatural disappearances,
and let's get out of this prison together!
Gum-Gum...
Way to go!
and assume that they're pulled
into the gate of hell.
He's right!
...Jet...
It's miraculous that he snuck in.
Hydra!
You need to know when to give up!
That's why we call it "Demoning away!"
If we stay here any longer, we'll melt away!
But he's going to have to give it up!
You can become a woman or a man,
...Pistol!
heehaw!
To be honest with you,
no matter how hard you try,
"The gate of hell?" "Demoning away?"
Even a fairy!
He has to save himself first!
Straw Hat is maybe already...
Yeah, right!
You can become whoever you want!
I don't think that's the reason
that Ivan-san disappeared!
Today's the day that Ace boy
will be executed--at 3pm!
It was reckless to fight against
Magellan in the first place.
Don't you think so?!
I've never met him but he's a miracle-worker!
I think that they're gonna take him
to Navy Headquarters in the morning.
You can't survive a battle with him.
He must be able to work miracles
in a place like this, too!
It'd take a miracle!
That means Ace boy will be taken
out of Impel Down in 7 or 8 hours!
The border called gender!
A miracle?
I... No, everyone here,
Ivan-san is the God of all queers!
It didn't hurt him at all?!
Oh yeah! He is in Impel Down!
Straw boy's treatment will take 2 more days!
heehaw!
We've all crossed that border!
The queen of queers--
Ivan-san!
So we're the new human race!
Even if he survives,
Please!
He once saved both a patient
who was given up on by his doctor,
Save Straw-chan!
he'd need 3 days of sleep
to restore his strength!
New Kama!
and a half-broken country!
So when he wakes up, everything will be over!
If antidotes won't help him...
There are a lot of legends about him!
This is the garden of freedom -
But can he even take 2 more days of that?!
He's the greatest star of all queers--Ivan-san!
New Kama Land!
...you're his only hope!
I told you that the possibility is low
and that he needs a miracle to make it!
Heehaw!
We better find him now!
Who's... Ivan-san?
Ivan-sama! Ivan-sama!
And I won't give up on hoping!
LEVEL 4--STAFF STAIRCASE
Fog?
Ivan-sama! Ivan-sama! Ivan-sama!
You need to rest, too!
You wanna go to level 5?
Yes, I do.
Eat something nutritious and go back to bed!
He transformed a man into a woman!
These two have been
sentenced to freeze to death!
I'll offer you a quiet room to sleep in.
He is a miracle-worker! What great power!
Why are we going to level 5?
We have no choice.
We can try to escape
but the security on level 3
Welcome to our New Kama Land!
I'll stay with Straw-chan!
must be tightened by Magellan's order.
Hey, don't bother! He's...
Heehaw!
There's little hope!
We're safe for now as long as
we stay with the "Vice Warden."
What are you gonna do?!
I'm so embarrassed!
Venom Cloud!
I know that!
But his obsession with saving Straw Hat -
Heehaw! She's embarrassed!
I don't know how long we're gonna be safe!
She's still got a long way to go
to become a New Kama!
Yeah, but at least we are for now!
S-Straw-chan!
Aak! No!
Bon boy?
The miracle-worker, Emporio Ivankov!
Damn it!
It's my honor to meet you!
Hang in there!
Keep walking!
I'm glad to see you! I'm so glad!
It's no use!
Hang in there!
I got to do this!
That poison fog is a part of me!
Hang in there!
Wait for me, Straw-chan!
If you don't mind, I have a favor to ask you!
Straw-chan!
But this list of prisoners is confusing.
A favor?
It's alive!
Can you save my friend's life?!
He was poisoned by Magellan!
What is this about?
I wonder how he's doing.
Emporio Ivancov--the real name
of Ivan-san has been crossed off!
No antidote can help him and he's just dying!
All he can do is wait.
Has he been released already?
Or has he been executed?!
I'll do anything for you if you'll save him!
Hang in there!
Hang in there! Straw-chan!
Straw-chan!
Are you talking about Straw boy?
Did we let this prisoner go free?
What do you think you're doing to...
What?! Oh, Ivancov...
Hang in there! Hang...
...Bon-chan?!
You-know-what happened
to him a few years ago...
Leave Bon-chan...
Hang in there! Hang in there!
...alone!
You-know-what?
He's been doing it all this time?!
Don't you remember it, Vice Warden?
Bon boy?
Huh?
Your vision's blurry?
Do you know why you've been treated already?
That's so stupid! That won't do anything!
Oh!
Oh yeah! That! Yeah!
Your ears are ringing?
You're right! Let's go!
Oh yeah! When did you do it?!
Do you know about That?! Explain it to me!
Hang... Hang in...
Gum-Gum...
We're just prisoners!
But there are prisoners here.
I don't care!
We don't just take in and
care for anyone who we find injured.
...Balloon!
People have disappeared
occasionally in Impel Down.
Hang... Hang in there!
We're just not that nice!
They didn't break out because
some of them could barely move.
I treated you because Straw boy begged me to.
They just disappeared without a trace.
I said "it's no use!"
Can't you find...
Why can't you see that?!
We call it "Demoning away!"
Straw-chan begged you?!
We all fear these unnatural
disappearances and assume...
...even one queer?!
Look for him again!
...that they're pulled into the gate of hell.
S-Straw-chan! What did you do...
No matter how hard you try,
there's no way out for you!
He's not back yet.
That's why we call it "Demoning away!"
Is he still doing it?
...to them...?
People disappear...?
He must have given up already
and probably went to sleep!
I assume that you can't use your hands now!
I'll go check!
I wish that I hadn't heard that.
I'll go!
Me, too!
My poison will take...
Me, too.
Wow, it's cold already!
The door isn't even open yet!
...everything from you in time!
We've been watching you guys on the monitor.
I can't hear it anymore.
And we're wearing heavy clothes!
See, I told you!
We're here!
Straw boy,
Be careful of the severe coldness
and Army Wolves!
He gave up and...
I can't believe that you made it this far.
Hang... Hang in there!
I've never seen people as lucky as you guys!
Now, I'll take them as usual.
Huh? You take what?
Well, your weapons and coat.
Hang in there!
Bon...
What?!
Hang... in... there!
Bon...
We really can't imagine how you can do it!
Bon-chan tried to help me
Hang in there!
How you always say
The public execution of Ace is in...
"I'll show the prisoners
the dignity of the Vice Warden!"
How long will he keep wasting time like that?!
and got bitten by the wolves!
...26 hours!
and go into the Freezing Hell
naked without any weapons.
Take care of him!
Hang... Hang in...
We all admire you for doing so!
I beg you! He's my friend!
What?!
S-Straw-chan...
You wouldn't say something
like that when you're dying.
It's not appropriate to let prisoners wear coats
so we'll take them, naturally!
So some friendships can't
be ruined even in a prison.
They'll take our coats, too!
When someone begs you like that,
What?!
Damn!
you gotta do it unless you're
a demon in human skin.
Straw-chan!
Where are you?!
S-Straw-chan...
Be careful!
I already began the treatment
of Straw boy 10 hours ago!
Due to the temperature,
Transponder Snails don't work here!
This place is too hot! It's like hell!
That fool!
Hey, you alright?!
Really?!
Take care!
Take care of yourself first!
Wow! Nice! She's exactly my type!
We gotta treat him!
Keep your hands to yourselves!
Healthy, young and beautiful!
LEVEL 4--IN FRONT OF THE STAIRCASE
Let him do what he wants!
Wait a minute! But...
But...
I'm going to bite off my tongue now!
...where's that quick pansy prisoner
who beat all of these guards?!
What?!
Bon boy wants to struggle
and fight alongside Straw boy!
But, in a rough way...
I am really doing it!
Who are you?!
You can't stop me!
Even if there's only a ghost of a chance,
he believes in Straw boy
That doesn't matter, sweetie!
Why don't you come here?
Huh?
and puts his life on the line
and shouts himself hoarse!
I'm all sweaty!
Can you help me undress?
S-Straw-chan!
It's so... ugh!
I can't do it!
Please!
Puff-puff!
Dammit!
Why don't you unlock this door?
They're both beyond their
capacities already but...
Take them away!
U-Unlock my handcuffs now!
Yeah, alright!
Yes, sir!
Hey! Those of you born after the 90's!
Smash!
Fools!
I-I can barely use my hand in this coldness!
Here you go!
Wait... D-D-Don't do this to me!
...they're trying to create a miracle!
It's too cold! The air hurts!
Please don't!
I-I don't want gomon (torture)!
I-I almost got it!
These are old-fashioned bamboo stilts!
Alright, how can I help you?
Komon (anus) stinks!
It's unlocked!
Yes! You did it!
Ha ha! Do you have extra clothes?
Yes, it does!
Wait right there!
I got you!
1, 2, 3... there're 4 of them!
You gotta try these! It's fun!
W-Who is it?!
He sounds familiar!
Hey, don't tell me that they're Army Wolves!
I can't take this!
For more than 10 hours,
Isn't he...?!
That queer! I'm coming after you!
I mean, I made these with wax,
S-Straw-chan has been fighting against
his own destiny for his life in this way!
Do you know why they're here instead
of the Floor of Wild Beasts from Hell?!
It's nice to be able to
lay the blame on Warden
Swan Arabesque!
but I don't like the fact he outsmarted me!
so we should call them wax stilts!
No. Why?
Oh, I know!
Then I... I...
Because they would eat the
other beasts like the Basilisk or Sphinx!
How much longer can they keep this up?!
Go away now!
And I wanna become the warden!
W-Who are you?!
It's not good!
Are you kidding me?!
So they're extra special savage!
We gotta get off of this floor
in order to lose them!
Just keep running!
You!
Severe cold was enough
but now we got Army Wolves, too!
Mr. 2!
Tell me somebody! Where's the exit?!
I shouldn't give in, either!
The third escapee?!
I used too much poison!
Another reason for my teeth to chatter!
Damn!
My stomach! Oh, my stomach!
Alright, let's just do this!
We're gonna rescue Straw-chan!
Yes, the riot is completely
under control now!
Hang... Hang in there!
We put all the prisoners back in their
cells and got the keys back but...
That's enough!
Hang in there!
I don't wanna become their dinner!
Hang in there, Straw-chan!
You're running already?!
...I think some keys are missing.
Straw-chan!
What a pain in the butt!
You have to live!
You got to... mmm... find him!
Hang in there!
Take this! And this! And this!...
Un, deux, trois! Un, deux, trois!
Catch him alive now!
Hang in there!
S-So strong!
Un, deux, trois! Un, deux...
--Straw-chan!
--Hang in there!
This queer must be... mmm... on this floor!
Now I know why they're
demon guards on level 5!
Take this 'n this 'n this!...
Un, deux, trois! Un, deux, trois! Un...
Hang in there!
But I can't die here like a dog or a queer!
Yes, Madam!
Hang in there!
Several hours later, Mr. 2 Bon Clay is...
Hang in there-able!
I gotta save Straw-chan!
I'll show them my queer guts!
What's going on here?!
Is this the treatment?!
Straw-chan!
Where... is this?
You're quite a fighter!
But you can't get away!
Hang in there!
Oh yeah!
He's been screaming for 10 hours
since we put him in this chamber.
"Oh Come My Way" Kenpo...
Ack?
Hang in there!
Ha!
Who are you?
Straw-chan!
So cute!
It'll be two more days before he is treated.
Straw-chan?!
W-W-What are you doing?
Hang in there!
I-I can't move my body!
Where did Straw-chan go?!
What?!
Straw-chan!
I hear people talking...
WARDEN'S OFFICE
I told you!
It's not good for us to stay with that guy!
Warden!
I just heard from the canteen staff on level 5
The situation is far worse than I expected!
10 years of your life.
and they said that Straw Hat Luffy has...
We gotta find a way out, quick!
I'll have to use 10 years of
your future for this treatment,
...disappeared!
If we fool around here any longer,
The Army Wolves will find us!
What?!
Straw boy.
The Burning Heat Hell to the Freezing Hell!
Alright!
V-Vice Warden Hannyabal!
What are you doing here?!
What a difference!
But there's no guarantee
that it's gonna save your life.
But this coldness is unusual...
Hey, don't stop running!
Now you have no chance of survival
This is it!
and all I can do is give you
a 2 to 3% chance for survival.
But I can feel that instead of
keeping myself warm by running,
You really don't know when to give up!
it's drawing all my energy!
It's so bright!
You want to rescue your brother that much?
And then it's up to your spirit,
if it's possible or impossible
for you to survive.
How cold can it get?!
Yeah!
If the poison takes over, you will die.
Hang in there!
Oh, I think that we can
avoid the wind over there!
What?!
Oh! So you finally woke up, young man!
But if spirit wins out
W-W-Wait!
Hang in there! Straw-chan!
you will survive!
You've been sleeping quite
a while! Want a drink?
Alright now, have a nice trip to...
Hang in there! Straw-chan!
...the valley of the shadow of death!
Cheers to the newcomer!
Emporio...
...Healing Hormone!
Cheers!
D-Dammit!
We've been watching you guys on the monitor!
The wind isn't blowing here but
the floor froze my butt and my entire body!
I really enjoyed it!
Ace-san, I don't know anything
about that woman but...
If we stay here,
both of us will be frozen for real!
What is this place?
I'll take you to your seat!
What floor did you come from?
...I think that you better
assume she's lying.
Alright, let's do it!
We got plenty to eat! You must be hungry!
You got a plan?!
It'd be easier if you just stop fighting.
Just close your eyes!
So you're saying that she came
all the way to here just to lie to me?!
Do you remember that we formed
an alliance to breakout?!
Wait! Where am I?! Where's Straw-chan?!
Gum-Gum...
Yeah, we huddled and decided to join forces...
...Pistol!
Do you think that you're outside the prison?!
We should huddle together now!
Well, I'm sorry.
Don't worry! You're still in Impel Down.
Good idea!
Alright, let's snuggle up and get warm!
But, to tell you the truth, Jimbei.
No way! No one's wearing
their jail clothes here!
My brother would do something like that!
Rub, rub, rub...
He does stupid things!
And you're eating and drinking as you want!
Rub, rub, rub...
Since we were kids,
he always made me worry, that fool!
Hmm...
Is this some kind of paradise?!
Oh yeah, I remember!
Hey, jailer!
I'm not getting warm at all and...
Tell me the truth!
I was chased by the wolves
and Straw-chan helped me!
Finally, the day has come!
Um. I feel kinda sick!
I feel sick, too!
I hope that we can get
rid of him successfully!
Is there something going on the upper levels?
And I just passed out!
I don't want any wars in Impel Down!
They followed us!
Then, am I dreaming?!
Warden Magellan will be here any minute.
No, there isn't.
No! I think I died from the cold
They followed us!
so I'm in heaven now!
10... 10 hours?!
They followed us!
Did you wake up?
And there's more now!
Straw-chan has been screaming
like this for 10 hours?!
You've been sleeping like a
baby for about 10 hours now.
He tastes better than me! I guarantee!
Spirits and hormones,
10 hours?!
these are the vital forces of the human body.
What're you saying?!
Are you kidding me?! Who are you?!
I'm a wax man so I taste awful!
They bring out the power to heal oneself!
My name is Inazuma.
I-It's blood!
--He tastes better than me!
You're being rude!
No more screams...
I'm the one who moved the two of you.
But the treatment is excruciating!
I have drawn out his latent
immunity and changed his body...
You were nearly dying of exposure!
Are you out of your mind?
So the fact that we can't
hear him anymore means...
What? Did you say "two?"
Why are you so determined?
...to enable him to battle
with the deadly poison.
Straw-chan is here, too?
Portgaz D. Ace is a major criminal
who is soon to be executed!
Where is he? Is he alright?
What a mess this is.
There is a lot of destruction and recovery
Are you people jailers?
Do we have to see him dying?
What is this place?!
It's too bad!
raging at an extraordinary
speed inside of his body.
And you're an intruder who
wants to help a criminal like him!
But he did his best for 20 hours!
Now, now, calm down.
He will survive only if he can
make it through the pain!
Ouch!
I won't forgive any of those offenses!
He is going to tell you!
Straw-chan...
W-Who is He?
W-What?!
Ace's execution in Marineford is...
Oh! The lights are going down!
I wanna go and rescue Ace!
...the absolutely final decision
provided for under the law!
The shows starting!
You can take a look inside if you want.
You'll be like an ant blown into a storm.
Let's go to the front.
There is nothing you can do about it!
You can just be flicked away
without even having done anything.
Shut up!
Where... Where is it?!
What is this?
Did you sleep alright, candy boy?
Stay away...
What... What?!
Stay away!
Luffy!
Straw-chan...?
No, you're Mr. 2 Bon boy.
Food!
Who are you? Why do you know my name?!
H-He's gonna die!
Thank you for coming.
It's gonna tear up his body and
it's gonna be all messed up and...
This is...
No, he's already dead!
You're great! Very sexy!
How could you?!
Help Straw-chan! Please! Help him!
This is pathetic.
S... Straw-chan!
This is...
Yeah!
Down the sewage line of Impel Down
Untie the chains and stop him bleeding!
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp!
and just take the route that shouldn't be there,
T-That's horrible! Please!
Straw boy! I...
A... Ace!
then, you'll get here!
I can't believe this!
Please do something!
It's a paradise for prisoners!
How can this be true?!
Shut up!
Have you had enough now?
It didn't even take a day!
I'm helping him now!
You've got everything here, so enjoy!
Don't underestimate human life!
Warden! Warden Magellan!
Huh?!
Drinks!
Don't you know what it takes to
strive against one's own mortality?!
Good morning!
I've got very bad diarrhea...
"Weapons!"
Please hurry.
Games!
Second Gear!
It's time to move the
condemned prisoner - Portgaz D. Ace
Stop resisting!
And most of all, we have freedom!
I'm not the God or Buddha!
You can't survive after
taking that much poison!
Yes, that's right! We're all free!
Bring more food here!
A miracle-worker?!
You've lost your sight, huh?
Keep it coming! Cooked or not!
The amount is what matters!
You can call me whatever you want, but...
Can you hear me?
Hydra!
Be quiet and accept death!
Yes! The jailers are
panicking today as usual!
...I could never save a fool who
only depends on other people.
No! I don't wanna die!
Hurry up! Just leave it close to him!
"Prisoners have disappeared!"
I'm not gonna die until I rescue Ace!
Wow! He's taking in food like a sand pit trap!
"They've been pulled into hell!"
I saved an impoverished country
Just like that!
and a country that was defeated in war
How long will he keep eating?!
I'm sorry but they're all here!
Do you wanna rescue somebody?
but all I did was draw
out their spirit to live.
He's been eating for
30 minutes at a steady pace!
Even you have no hope for yourself?
Is it your friend?
Miracles only happen to
people who don't give up!
How stupid!
He ate several days worth of
the food supply for Kama Land!
You gotta save your own ass in a prison!
Do you say that this is hell?!
Don't underestimate miracles!
No one's gonna come to save you!
What an amazing vital force!
Maybe you're right,
but at least it's a gay one!
We're all alone!
In the sea of fire,
you'd step on someone
beside you in order to survive!
He's coming out!
The underground that nobody knows!
When you face the beasts,
Ace!
you'd sacrifice someone near you to survive!
Welcome to...
Give me...
What kind of creature is that?!
You'll die if you care about others!
That's not the form of human being!
...Ace!
So, cut the you-wanna-rescue-someone crap!
...Impel Down--Level 5.5!
It makes me sick!
It's a secret garden for prisoners!
New Kama Land!
Heehaw!
Look! Somebody's coming!
This is your punishment.
He's not a jailer or one of the staff!
Who are these perverts?!
There is no way to neutralize the
amount of poison you have absorbed!
What's wrong with him?
Yeah! Ivan-sama!
Is he naked!
What?!
Ivan-sama!
You will agonize for 24 hours
and then pass...
Ivan-sama?! No way!
...to the real hell!
I'm...
He is the legendary...
...recovered!
THE PUBLIC EXECUTION OF ACE IS IN...
...Queen of Kamabakka Kingdom.
Straw-chan, I come to rescue you!
Heehaw!
In the name of friendship!
...16 HOURS!
Emporio Ivancov?!
A... A...
Heehaw!
Ace!
Bon Clay searches level 5 for the queen of queers--Iva-san.
Thanks to Ivankov's treatment, Luffy has miraculously recovered
Luffy fights the poison treatment himself.
After being defeated by Magellan,
Luffy is tossed into level 5.
Bon Clay implores the miracle-worker,
Iva-san, to cure Luffy's poisoning.
The chance of survival is so slim,
it would be a miracle for him to survive.
and intends to save Ace by himself.
However, under repeated attacks
from the Army Wolves and
Despite knowing there's no antidote for the poison,
However, Iva-san's remedy is
fighting to withstand the
cold of the Freezing Hell,
Trusting his friend,
Bon Clay continues to cheer for his survival.
Bon Clay makes a stand to save his friend.
Once Ivan-san learns that Luffy is the son of the revolutionary--Dragon,
a cruel procedure that will
leave Luffy battered and torn.
he loses his strength and collapses.
However, standing in his way
is a pack of Army Wolves!
Where is this queen of queers, exactly?
And then, the time of Ace's
execution is finally at hand.
A fierce battle commences against the poison.
he decides to lend Luffy his strength.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Paradise in Hell!
Impel Down Level 5.5!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy's Treatment Begins!
Ivan-san's Miraculous Power!"
"For his friend!
Bon Clay Goes to the Deadly Rescue!"
"Luffy's Back!
Ivan-san Begins the Breakout Plan!!"
"Believe in Miracles!
Bon Clay's Cries from the Heart!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!