Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
Countless pirates fight desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become the next King of the Pirates.
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
As Luffy and his friends overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less able to ignore their existence.
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
What kind of adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
While Buggy and Mr. 3 ascended to level 4 in order to break out,
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
the moribund Luffy was injected with a Healing Hormone by Ivankov,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
Luffy got to level 6 along with
the queen of New Kama Land Ivankov
Now with Jimbei and Crocodile,
they're battling on level 4!
which will cure him, but rob him of 10 years of life!
With the help of the queen
of New Kama Land Ivankov,
While Buggy and Mr. 3 got out of level 4,
Food!
Luffy got to level 6 where Ace was held!
but Ace was already gone!
moribund Luffy had been treated by
Ivankov, the queen of New Kama Land...
We transfer custody of the criminal
- Portgaz D. Ace to the Navy!
You better not resist because it's useless!
There's no need to hesitate!
...the land of vanished prisoners
and recovered miraculously!
I'm...
Luffy!
But it was too late! Ace was already on
a ship heading to the Navy Headquarters!
...on the Government side!
I know what's going on in the world now.
...recovered!
Your brother is also a pirate! There's
no way that he'll walk out of here alive.
The world is about to change with the Navy
and the Whitebeard Pirates as major players!
I'm gonna go to Navy Headquarters!
I'm on level 2.
I wished that she was lying!
Why did you come, Luffy?!
I've just taken care of the
fools running wild here.
"Luffy's Back! Ivan-san Begins the Breakout Plan!!"
After letting Jimbei and Luffy's former enemy
--- Crocodile out of their cells,
But he's not gonna make a move yet!
It's simple but their plan defeated us!
I blocked all the exits on this floor!
they are about to reach level 4!
We're confined to level 6! There's
no way for us to get out!
He's the mastermind of all revolutionaries
in the world and my comrade!
I don't know why Blackbeard
is attacking us...
"Even More Chaos! Here
Comes Blackbeard Teech!"
--...but I already did something about it.
--Nice!
They'll hand over Ace boy to the
Navy Headquarters at any cost!
The revolutionary--Dragon!
It's not something that I wanted to do but
I have no option under the circumstances!
Oh, you're talking about my dad.
You need to give up on him!
What?!
LEVEL 2 WILD BEAST HELL
I mean, you need to trust Whitebeard.
I decided to release Shiryu against my will!
Hurry up!
He's not gonna give up on one of his
own! He'll definitely do something!
Dragon is...
What's going on out there?
You did?!
...your dad?!
Wow! He absorbed all the energy!
--Camisole!
--Long johns!
--I'm going!
--Huh?!
Everyone, get down to level 4!
After finding out that Luffy is Dragon's son,
Ivankov decided to accompany him in rescuing Ace!
I'm gonna go to Navy Headquarters!
What a guy! You must be superhuman!
Shiryu, how do you like
being out of the cell?
Everyone, get down to level 4!
He has overcome Magellan's poison! I can't believe it!
If I give up now...
...I'm gonna regret it!
Yeah, I really learned a lesson.
The Vivre Card was pointing down
which means that he's still here!
He recovered after only 20 hours!
I heard some kind of announcement too.
The eternal boredom makes you long for death.
But first of all, how can
you get off of this floor?!
Maybe something has happened in the prison.
This must be a miracle!
Alright, Portgaz D. Ace!
Miracle? It's something far greater than that!
Hey, Buggy! Look!
But you're not gonna use me as a pawn
All the jailers and Blugoris are leaving!
and then ask me to go back into
the cell, are you, Magellan?
We will take you to Marineford...
Everyone, get down to level 4 now!
If you wanna get out of here, set me free!
...where the execution ground is!
You did it! You did it! You did it! You did it!
Wow! All the beasts are going away!
You're a condemned prisoner!
And this is a deferred sentence!
I can create a hole on the ceiling!
--Go away, you fools!
--Don't ever come back!
You did it! You did it!
This is your only chance!
What do you think?
"Ace's Convoy Begins! Battle
on the Lowest Floor Level 6!"
Yeah, I bet.
Seems like they've got a problem
somewhere else, partner!
I'm so glad!
I'll keep that in mind!
Oh, Bon-chan! I'm so happy you survived!
This is our big chance!
You're right!
What?! Are you kidding?! Gimme a break!
Ace!
I have the right...
You're the one that made me worry....
When I look back, we've been chased
by the Army Wolves in level 5...
Crocodile!
...to cut you down!
That was pretty clever of them!
Hurry up!
It's been a while!
"The Dangerous Encounter! Blackbeard
and Shiryu of the Rain!"
Bon-chan! Hey!
We've suffered the remnants of
Magellan's poison gas in level 4...
Don't let them pass!
Straw Hat!
You alright?! Hey!
What happened to you? Hey!
He's just exhausted! But it's not because of his wounds!
They broke into the jailers'
room and took the keys!
This must be Magellan's poison!
--They're coming!
--Move it! Move it! Move it!
"The Ultimate Team Has
Formed! Shaking Impel Down!"
Let's set more prisoners free and
let chaos free in the prison!
Ready!
Oh, Ivan-chan!
Gum-Gum...
Ivan-chan?!
Then we faced the Sphinx again in level 3!
...Pistol!
I made it! Thank you for helping both of us!
Then, we can divide our opponents forces and
we will have a higher chance of survival!
Gnocchi!
Dammit! Take this!
If you wanna thank someone, you better thank Mr. 2 Bon boy, not me!
You're still here?!
Penne! Buckwheat noodle with an egg!
I thought that there was no
reason to get back on the street
What an annoying trap! Ha!
Camisole!
I only nudged you along with my powers.
Death Wink!
Long johns!
If you wanna run, come on and get out!
but Whitebeard and the Navy
are gonna start a war?
T-back!
It's your chance to break out! Come with us!
--Pantyhose!
--Briefs!
But him,
Heehaw!
It's my chance to finally
bring down that old man!
Wow! Are you gonna release us?!
he was struggling alongside you for hours and hours and hours here!
And we pretended to be a part of the
floor to trick the wild beasts just now!
We better hurry!
Oh! You're right! Hmmm?
He lost his voice and spewed up blood but he didn't stop!
This war has piqued my interest.
Go Blugoris!
We were pretty much the comic relief
but now we've made it all the way here!
And with my power, you and
I could get out of here.
W-Who are you people?!
Go wild!
He kept shouting "Hang in there!" "You have to live!" to you!
To level 2!
Hey, you! Could you come
with us for a minute?
It's not bad, huh? We both get what we want.
Damn, the Blugoris!
Just a little more to go to get out of here!
Chief Guard Saldeath,
we'll leave them to you!
--No, wait! Let me go!
--Don't worry! You won't regret it!
Blugoris! Get that queer
king with a gigantic face!
Let's go! We can't spare even a second.
I think it somehow affected your recovery!
It's not a "gigantic face,"
it's Face Growth Synthesis!
Don't hesitate! Attack him!
Clear the way! Gum-Gum...
Are you guys ready?!
Blugoris! Get him!
Anytime!
...Ricochet!
Hell...
...Wink!
These copies of keys that
Brother 3 made by wax,
Screw you!
I see.
--You're the man who messed up Vivi's country!
--That was a long time ago.
they're fine pieces of work!
The trap didn't work! And
the jailers are out cold!
--Go to level 4!
--What's wrong, A team?
--What's wrong with him?
--Is he naked?!
I lost interest in that country.
--Get B team!
--We lost touch with C team!
Straw Hat Luffy! Ivankov--the king of queers!
--Hurry up! What're you doing?
--Answer me!
Heehaw!
Inazuma--the revolutionary!
What?! Vice Warden, this is
the monitoring room!
He finished off the Blugoris
with a single blow!
The three criminals are
now entering... level 6!
Straw-chan, I come to rescue you!
Let's release him, Straw boy.
N-No way!
What's wrong?!
I don't get it! What was that?!
It's weird...
Ace!
What?!
In the name of friendship!
His power will aid us greatly.
Straw boy! You can't stop running!
No, no, this cool headdress is...
What?! Ivan-chan! If you
knew what he's done...
Who the hell is this guy all covered in blood?!
...something that I ordered secretly
to wear when I became the warden....
Leave them to us and...
Earlier, I was...
You wanna keep going, right?!
If you wanna make it to
Navy HQ,  you need him!
...you better keep going
forward and up! Now, go!
So this is level 6!
I'm not talking about that!
I'm sorry that I ran!
Ivankov!
I got it!
I see somebody sneaking around level 2!
Long time no see, Croco boy!
How do you know this guy?
Thanks!
They look like prisoners!
Y-You know him?
Only legendary criminals have been
held here in the Eternal Hell!
Just a passing acquaintance! I met
him when he was just a rookie!
What did you just say?!
--It's the demon guards!
--There're three of them!
Don't worry!
I can bring him under control
in case he tries to betray us.
I'm his friend!
Finally! We got our backup!
Sadie-chan's are here!
Thanks!
Straw-chan! I'm not gonna let you die!
You gotta thank Captain Buggy for this!
They aren't gonna let you...
I can't trust him at all!
...go any further beyond this point!
But I know one of his weaknesses!
Let's go, Luffy-kun! I'll assist you!
Bon-chan, thank you! I'm really grateful!
Send the remaining guards there to check!
Where are you, Ace?!
Hey, if you so much as say it...
I'm not good at fighting on the land though!
Yes, sir!
Oh? Do you wanna take that tone?
I'm here to save you!
Are there any jailers on level 2?!
Yeah? You're strong enough!
Ace, where are you?!
Answer me if you're still there!
Alright, let's get them, demon guards!
If you like, I can just
reveal your past here.
Ace!
--Yes?!
--What are you guys doing?!
Gum-Gum...
You can't just yell blindly!
But, if you just shut up and help
us, I keep the secret for Y-O-U!
Wait a minute!
We were gonna go down to level 4 as ordered.
Would you like to tell us where he is?!
No, inspect that floor!
Heehaw!
This floor?
N-No, I would not!
You bastard!
We'll save you two the trouble!
Why don't you release me, too?!
Oh no, what should I do then?!
Here are your hat and clothes. But you're not ready yet.
Like Ivan-san said, you need
to keep going, Straw-san!
You have to be true to yourself!
Me, too! I have something against Whitebeard!
You need to rest for several days to be fully recovered.
We'll take care of the demon guards!
W-What're you gonna do to me?!
Let me out, too!
Emporio...
I don't have time! I've already wasted too much!
You guys?!
...Female Hormone!
People call us...
This is our time, partner!
Sorry, but can you look after Bon-chan? I'll be back for him later!
While they're having a riot here again,
we're gonna stow away on a Navy ship!
...The New Kama's Six Forces!
Shut up!
Death Wink!
Oh! Are they formidable?!
Yeah, then our prison break will be complete!
These babies have a lot of friends...
--Hey, hey!
--See? You're not completely well yet!
Have mercy on me!
I think that Straw Hat and
Mr. 2 are already dead...
...who got killed in the fire
and brimstone of Impel Down!
W-What happened?
Wow! He turned into a woman!
...or they will spend the
rest of their life in prison!
They hold grudges against especially
the merciless demon guards and...
How do you like being your true self?
But my own life is the one I saved!
-- I feel very sorry for them!
their commander and the chief guard!
The paper is still pointing down! Ace must be downstairs!
What?! Is that me?!
Take me with you! I can help you for sure!
You're reborn!
I have known Ace-san ever since
he joined the Whitebeards!
That's Buggy the Clown!
Humph! Take care of them already!
By the way, where am I now?
You're not a jailer anymore,
you're a New Kama now!
What's that?
Look! There's Mr. 3, too!
Take this!
It's a Vivre Card, isn't it?
He always told me about his brother!
Oh! How fabulous!
Even a demon guard is just a big
oaf without his eyesight! Get them!
Look up!
You're on a floor between level 5 and 6.
Up?
Thank you very much, Ivan-sama!
I found my true identity!
I was arrested because I objected to the war!
I bet that since you've recovered,
It was an eye-crusher!
Attack them at once!
you wanna go to rescue your brother no matter what.
Oh, don't mention it!
--By the way...
--Where's Ace?!
I wanna save Ace-san, too! So please!
All right, guys! This is our big chance!
Well, it's your life! You can do whatever you want!
That way!
Don't underestimate... mmm... these kids!
Let me die for him!
If you wanna get back on the
street, go berserk for your life!
Such a strong bond between a Warlord
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei and...
What about you, Ivan-chan? Are you gonna break out?
Even if they can't see you, they
still can smell you and feel you!
Now let's kick it off!
Bon-chan thought he'd help your butt get out of here.
--He's our savior!
--Captain Buggy!
That's how Impel Down's...
mmm... demon guards are!
...the second division commander
of the Whitebeards--Portgaz D. Ace!
Your butt?!
T-This is level 2!
Can you guide me to Ace on your way out?
I never would have guessed!
How about this?!
The prisoners are out of their
cells and rampaging again!
What did you just say? Bon boy came here to save me?
Send the Blugoris back! It's out of control!
Ace!
Oh, I didn't know that. That's really sweet of him.
Snap!
Is this it?!
Ace?!
You can't fight back this time!
But I don't need to be saved.
This is level 4!
--What now?!
--The queen of queers Ivankov and Inazuma...
-- Alright.
-- Are you sure?!
Okay, everybody, pull!
It's not time to break out yet!
We don't know about him
and how dangerous he is!
...and Mr. 2 who tricked you earlier are...
He's not here!
It's okay! Let him out!
I know what's going on in the world now.
Are you sure that this is the right cell?!
Heehaw!
The world is about to change with the Navy and the Whitebeard Pirates as major players!
Yes, I am! I'm not lying...
Gimme a break!
Thank you!
--They're here with a mob!
--A mob?!
How dinky they are!
We're a bit too late.
--Hey, I'll thank you, too!
--Have mercy on me, too!
But he's not gonna make a move yet!
Everyone, get down to level 4
now! Everyone, get down to...
Shut up! Death Wink!
--No! They're too strong!
--Guns and cannons won't do!
He's the mastermind of all revolutionaries in the world and my comrade!
--Help me!
--It's impossible! Don't fight! Get back!
I can't believe this but the
people that they're with...
--We're all gonna die!
--They're way stronger than Blugoris! Run!
...are the prisoners who had disappeared
by "Demoning Away" over the years!
It's a straw hat! So he must be... Yes!
The revolutionary--Dragon!
Oh, you're talking about my dad.
She said that my brother's here!
I can't resist! Those screams!
Yes. When your father makes a move with his army,
A Warlord and a former
Warlord both on our team.
--Help me!
--Those demon guards are formidable!
What?! What's really going on here?!
He's really here! He broke into
the impregnable Impel Down
Two of them? Who is the other one?
then I'll reappear and enter the world again!
It's for sure!
I appreciate this! Now I can be of some help.
and made it all the way down to level 6!
Third Gear!
Somebody tell me if I can
still become the warden!
Fish-Man Karate!
If I escaped now, I'd just end up on countless wanted lists around the world!
You're Straw Hat Luffy, aren't you?
Maybe you can stop the war between
the Whitebeards and the Navy
Yeah.
Get them all, demon guards!
They took him just now!
Heehaw! Finally, I caught up with you!
Go! They've taken Ace-san to the elevator!
Gum-Gum...
but it's a waste of time.
...Giant...
Go! You can still catch them!
Straw-chan!
D-D-D-D... Dad?!
Because I'm gonna get that old man anyway.
5000 Brick...
Bon-chan! Looks like you
got your juice flowing now!
Who're you, old man?
I won't let you even touch good
old Whitebeard, Crocodile!
He's a big deal!
Did he say "my dad?!"
Yeah, I'm more than fine now!
What?!
Sables!
Then, do you wanna just fight me here?
...Fist!
Dragon is...
No! Why are you here, Mr. 1?!
...Pistol!
Croco boy--your secret past?
...your dad?!
Who is it?
He's the guy who was defeated
by Sash-chan in Alabasta!
Alright, we don't have much time!
D-D-D-Don't be ridiculous!
ONE
You're a son of Dragon?! He has a son?!
We're gonna just break out by force!
Okay, I got it!
Heehaw!
Oh! I shouldn't have said anything.
Thank you! Whoever you are!
Oh, then I don't know him.
Straw Hat, Ivankov, Inazuma,
they're all Devil Fruit eaters!
I guess it's okay. Grandpa didn't keep it a secret.
Vice Warden, we need backup on level 4 now!
Don't forget the Prison Bullets!
We need it on level 2, too!
Your father's name is...
We've reached level 6!
I can't believe it!--
Even after risking your life, it's almost
impossible to get all the way here!
...Monkey D. Dragon! He's a revolutionary!
Move in!
What should I do?
--Please hurry!
--Hannyabal-sama, give us an order!
--We need it on level 4!
--No, the poison is...
--Damn! Get back!
Did he really get through all five hells?!
I don't really know about him. I've never even seen his face.
--No, on level 2!
--Vice Warden, give us an order now!
Dammit! We can't even get closer to it!
What?!
My brother would do something
like that! He does stupid things!
That turd, Magellan, he's no fool!
This seems legitimate!
What's this stone thing?
Emporio...
He doesn't seem to be the kind to lie and he's a new star in the world of pirates!
...Face Growth Synthesis!
What should we do?!
N-No way!
Since we were kids, he always
made me worry, that fool!
As long as this block of poison
is here, we can't get to level 1.
Are they still here?! Go look!
And I've just seen his extraordinary vital force!
Heehaw!
Do you really think that they stayed
here after making that hole, stupid?
No way! Nothing will counteract
Magellan's poison!
So annoying!
He's not a normal man! So it's believable!
It's impossible to break out
of Impel Down as I thought!
Hell Wink!
Where did you come from?!
I'm from the East Blue!
Shut up! We can't give
up after coming this far!
We can't stop them!
That's exactly what Magellan wants!
S-Shiryu, the Jail Manager!
Dragon.
They were all vicious
before they disappeared...
Have you got any insights?
Whenever you go for some air,
See, you guys? You can't do
anything right without me.
you always face towards the same direction no matter where you are!
Oh! Um...
They took that to the upper floors!
Do I? Why would you be so curious about such a thing?
You're doing your job so poorly!
Mr. 3! When we're in trouble,
we can depend on your wax!
...but now they're very bizarre!
Let's go!
This is a huge mess and the
embarrassment of Impel Down!
Use your power and...
They've left the iron door
to the elevator open!
W-Wait a minute!
I've never noticed.
Nice!
It's not as easy as
fooling Transponder Snails or Manticores!
The three that you're looking for
released Crocodile and Jimbei and...
The operation system is locked! It's no good!
Then, it must be a homing instinct like animals have.
Oh wait! I see!
Is your home in that direction?
Fish-Man Karate!
...climbed up through the hole to level 5!
It doesn't work?!
Candle Coating!
Arabesque Brick Fist!
But we can just climb!
You're thinking about your family in the east,
Tell Magellan now  that I
can help him if he wants!
Do it!
aren't you?
Memoirs of a Winter's Sky!
Okay!
No, that's...
Don't be so inquisitive about my past, Ivan!
I can cover the poison up with
wax! What was I thinking?!
W-What?!
I'm sorry.
T-That was close!
You're good, Buggy! It was a great idea!
They took Crocodile and Jimbei?!
Oh no! If Straw boy is a son of Dragon for real, that means...
Yes, they're not in their cells!
For lots of reasons--we can't stop them!
I wasn't thinking about anything!
No! Does it mean that I thought
that I confined them to level 6
You came up with the great idea so quickly!
Of course, they wouldn't
allow us to climb it!
but that I've been outsmarted?
You're a tower of strength!
Let's get to the Navy Headquarters!
Inazuma, check to see when they'll take Ace boy away!
It's not usable! They're
already keeping an eye on it!
There're now five of them and
they're on level 5, right?
I almost fell in love with you!
Yes, right away!
That's right!
We've had word of an unprecedented
riot going on in Impel Down.
There isn't much time!
Let's go back up the stairs!
Of course! I'm not just a flashy guy!
But the Vivre Card was pointing down which means that he's still here!
Do you think that  I'm
responsible for any of this?
You need to think carefully sometimes!
I'm gonna go to level 6 with Straw boy now!
Warden Magellan is
convoying Portgaz D. Ace
The ringleader is Monkey D. Luffy.
Do you get it, you fools?!
You can't get away!
so I think that you're
responsible for all of this!
What? Are you gonna show me the way?!
I'm responsible for all of this?!
This is your last chance to see the sky.
But, did you just say "level 6?" Isn't it 5?
Now we're safe from the poison but
it's still blocking our way out!
Hey, they blocked the staircase!
Alright, I'm gonna fight, too!
It can't be! You're on level 5.5!
They're trying to trap us!
All jailers must go back to level 4!
That's true. It's not time to celebrate yet.
We gotta break through! There's no other way!
Sadie-chan, Saldeath!
Whatever. Alright, let's go!
Don't worry! We got Captain Buggy with us!
Alright!
Go to level 4 with all of your people now!
I'd risk my own life to become Warden!
I wasn't paying attention! It didn't even occur to me!
He definitely has our next move planned!
That's a lot of gas! Is it poisonous?!
I mean, risk your own lives to stop them!
If Straw boy is Dragon's son, so is Ace!
Once you've been shackled on the
scaffold, you will never again...
What?!
Poison gas, again?!
You're right! There's no doubt about it!
Hey, you guys!
What?! What?!
I don't know who you
are but don't make us suffer with you!
Is this why the Navy captured Ace?!
I mean...
Tell us!
No, it can't be! There would be no point in it!
Shut up, you level 6 people!
W-Well...
They don't wanna fight Whitebeard and Dragon at the same time!
--I'd do anything!
--What's next?!
-- I don't care if it's poisonous or not!
-- Wait!
Are you ready, Bon boy?
--D-Don't ask me what t'do...
--"Wax'd do?"
What does the government truly want?!
Y-Yes, Ivan-san!
It's sleeping gas!
Wax would do!
You sure?
How reckless you are, Straw boy!
Emporio Energy Hormone is just
for you to recover for today.
Let's use my wax power again!
In any case, it's time to make a move!
You really need to stop...
We're gonna do it like when
Straw Hat beat Minotaurus!
There'll be after effects!
We don't want to...
Okay, Bon-chan! I'll be back!
I know! Go ahead!
They wanna make us sleep
to stop us in our tracks!
"It?"
I mean if you don't, I can barely move!
Ready, Straw Hat?! Candle Lock!
Straw boy!
Vice Warden, we've blocked
off level 6 completely!
Don't tell anyone casually about your birth!
Alright! Gum-Gum...
Oh yeah! You're right!
The sleeping gas is potent
and there's no place to run!
...Mallet Rifle!
...see the sky.
You got me there!
Keep the guards armed and
on standby just in case!
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Emporio Energy...
I'm a friend of your dad and one of the commanders of the Revolutionaries army!
...Hormone!
That was when we were in level
3 - the Starvation Hell!
Did you report to Warden Magellan?!
Just now!
Oh! I injected it into
your crotch by mistake!
I wanted to go up but I had to go
down to level 5 because of Straw Hat!
Good!
That's why I was arrested!
New Kama Land!
So it's my duty to support you whether you like it or not!
My job is safe now!
After that, it was a pain to
get back to level 2 again!
Bon-chan! Don't die!
Now I'll lay the blame on
Magellan for all of this mess
I can't let my friend's son die before my eyes!
Are you ready?
and then I'll become the warden...
Are you ready, Buggy? Candle Lock!
Even if we manage to get to
the  front door of the prison,
The microphone's still on!
Tell all the people in the New Kama Land!
I-I gotta do what he did?!
we'll still be in for a fight!
Whaaat?!
This is Onigumo.
We're going to rescue Ace boy and try to break out of the prison!
I'm not ready yet...
There's the Calm Belt all
around us which is impassable!
What unfortunate timing!
Prepare to open the gate of Marineford!
Damn! There's no option!
Straw Hat made it to level
6 just after we left!
We have to steal a Navy ship
to go to the Navy Headquarters!
--What are you saying all of the sudden?
--Isn't this a bit hasty?
L-Luffy!
Chop-Chop...
We just need to get more
people to fight with us!
Go, Captain Buggy!
Release Wax-Wax and Candle Lock!
Decisions must always be sudden!
To be honest, we already have a lot but...
We're completely trapped!
If you wanna come with me, get ready to die,
...only a few of you can
make it  to the top floor!
prepare for action and wait for us here!
...Flashy Mallet!
If you are captured, you'll
be tortured to death!
Alright! Let's do it!
So if you wanna survive,
I'll follow you, Ivan-sama, to the end!
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
you need to set free as many prisoners
as you can from levels 1 through 5!
It's a new beginning for New Kama!
How did it go?
NAVY
We still can't find him! Ace's
execution is in 5 hours...
--That's Magellan's infamous poison!
--It's like a creature!
If we can start a riot,
we'll keep our foes busy!
Alright! Wait for me, Ace!
Hey, wait! Gimme back my hand!
...so time is of the essence because
Whitebeard could appear at anytime!
I'm coming for you!
We have to steal the keys and set
as many as we can free on our way!
But we can't find the Warlord of the Sea,
\ Blackbeard, anywhere on this island!
What?!
The emergency sleeping gas
has just been released!
Let's unleash mayhem in Impel Down
such as has never been seen before!
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
It's only a matter of time
before they catch Straw Hat!
Oh my butt!
Heehaw!
And maybe this is unrelated but
a Navy ship without clearance...
It didn't go like it did with
Straw Hat. That's all we had!
The Freezing Hell wasn't
punishment enough for him!
Since the cell that you were in is open now,
Let's go, Straw boy!
Damn! Magellan the turd!
...has just arrived at Impel Down!
Maybe you're the warden of Impel Down
- the greatest prison in the world!
this time he'll be held on level
6 and will suffer greatly!
What?!
Oh?
His pulse...
What?!
I don't think that it's him but...
He went ahead.
But you're just a turd with the runs!
What a free spirit! Heehaw!
You've got no friends other
than the toilet seat!
Let's catch up with him, candies!
-- Luffy...
-- Don't stop! Keep walking!
Wait! Please somebody stop me!
--Buggy-san lost it at last!
--Magellan-chan, how's your seat doing?
I'm going way too fast!
It's faster than usual!
We're stuck. No wonder!
You fools! Why can't you see it?!
Why did he come here?!
You!
The hormone is working overtime!
Search the ship they arrived on!
Captain Buggy's not giving
up yet! He's still fighting!
His pulse...
Yeah, but it must be  nice to move like that.
It's not always nice!
Yes, sir!
Here's your bowels forecast!
Please wait! We didn't ask
for reinforcements and...
He tries to fight the venom
with his venomous tongue!
...is fine!
That was a joke?!
...there's a state of emergency here
so we can't assure your safety!
As they say "Poison quells poison!"
Because the treatment has just shortened his life,
You're gonna have loose
bowels all night long!
We're waiting to hear from
the Headquarters now so...
he must be exhausted still on some level!
It doesn't matter! We're on the same side!
--What a man!
--That's the indomitable pirate spirit!
You better not resist because it's useless!
Emporio...
But even so, pirates are not
allowed to enter the prison...
...Energy Hormone!
--He's a natural born captain!
--I will follow him forever!
Luffy!
Your brother is also a pirate! There's
no way that he'll walk out of here alive.
Alright, Captain Buggy! We'll fight with you!
Poop, poop, diarrhean Magellan!
I wished that she was lying!
Why did you come, Luffy?!
It's a matter of adrenaline!
Anyway, no one can live after that much
poison no matter how strong he is!
Now you have enough energy for a day!
How did you recover,
Straw Hat?!
There's no need to hesitate!
You'll feel the after effects in several days but I guess it won't matter much at that point!
Raise the drawbridge!
Don't let them cross it!
Hurry up!
THE UNDERWATER PRISON IMPEL
DOWN LEVEL 1 CRIMSON HELL
We made it back to level 3!
I'm...
Only five of them! Stop the Blackbeards!
...on the Government side!
Vice Warden! Warden won't like it if he hears that you've been sitting there!
We still got another half to go!
What a gloomy place!
S-Shoot!
It was faster on our way down because
we often fell down accidentally!
We'll be sure to tell him later!
I can't walk another step!
You guys are so mean!
I'm thirsty!
Sir! All crew members of the ship--
that Blackbeard was on are wiped out!
Shoot! He's a Warlord but we're
pretty sure that he betrayed us!
Mr. 2, Mr. 3, Buggy the Clown...
What?!
Blackbeard is not on our side!
Are you sure that they got onto level 5?
What?! Let me take a break for a minute!
Hey!
Yes, sir!
The biggest trouble in the history
of Impel Down is now gone!
Yes, his disguise was perfect!
What are you...?!
Stop there!
But the only thing that they found on level 5 was the headdress covered in blood.
Pirates can't be on our
side in the first place.
Back to your posts and
clean up the mess inside!
Jail Manager Shiryu! When
did they let you out?
Hello!
Gnocchi!
We assume that they took Straw Hat out of the cell
but ended up being eaten by the wolves.
You're still here?!
Liberation!
Penne! Buckwheat noodle with an egg!
It's before 10 in the morning!
There are five of them...
I see.
--Let us go!
I never thought that I'd wear this special order thing before I became the warden.
The execution is at 3 in the afternoon.
Buckwheat noodle with fried tofu!
They'll definitely do it on time!
Wheat-flour noodle in curry soup!
Wheat-flour noodle?!
If Whitebeard is going to do something,
he'll do it hours before that!
I still haven't brought down Magellan!
Don't say it so plainly!
Who's that? Here comes trouble!
If we get duped or beaten again,
Ace should already be on the ship!
Do something!
The war could begin anytime now!
Is he Magellan?!
both yours and the Warden's jobs are on the line!
We have an intruder! The Warlord
of the Sea - Marshall D. Teech!
The floor's gonna be filled with gas!
I'm Marshall D. Teech.
You're Blackbeard, right?
But he's not gonna get killed until 3!
Help me!
My position, too?!
Which means that we still have a chance!
Hey, you alright?!
--Of course!
They're the ones who vanished a while back!
Yes, I am! Who the hell are you?!
The Staircase to level 3 must be close!
Darkness...
Blackbeard and his clan are breaking
into the prison! This doesn't look good!
Doors can't stop me!
Level 4 is a breeze!
I haven't seen any jailers at all! They're totally gone!
I'll turn it into sand with my right hand.
I blocked the exits on level 2.
Who is he?!
Buggy the Clown and the others are trapped.
Let's see how Crocodile's
Sand-Sand Fruit power works!
He's cutting the floor like paper!
Let's make a game of it! It's the Buggy and 3 Adventures!
I was dragged into the darkness!
And I know that Shiryu can
handle Blackbeard on level 1.
His motive is unknown!
He can turn into sand and control it.
Don't stop suddenly!
Give us an order! H-Hurry!
Wait a minute!
With his right hand, he can
suck any type of moisture
That leaves us Straw Hat
and the others on level 4.
so people and plants will wither
and rocks and land turn to sand!
They've got Crocodile and Jimbei with
them and have become quite a force!
It's a Surveillance Transponder Snail!
If it finds us, all our efforts will go to waste!
In Impel Down, we won't tolerate a riot...
It's over! My life is over now!
Thank you for noticing it, partner!
...let alone a break out!
Let's go carefully from now on!
I'll be there soon!
No, this is just a beginning!
Now he's flipping the floor like paper!
You must hold Straw Hat and others
back until I get there, Hannyabal!
A sad and long life in which I
will never become the warden...
T-They're coming!
...has just begun!
He blocked the gas with the floor!
Vice Warden, we have a problem!
Vice Warden! Are you okay?!
T-This is level 4!
That's amazing!
What's wrong?
According to the report from level 4,
The prisoner who escaped from
level 6 - is a Warlord Jimbei!
Inazuma ate the Snip-Snip Fruit
and now he's a scissor-man!
the demon guards got beaten
in the blink of an eye!
This is the Burning Heat Hell!
T-That can't be true! The
demon guards can't be beaten!
The intruder--Monkey D. Luffy!
What is this?!
M-My eyes are itchy!
He can manipulate whatever
he cuts as though it's paper!
Don't panic, stupid! Tell
them that I'll be there soon!
It's hot!
This must be Magellan's poison!
A former Warlord Crocodile!
They're here! So we will fight!
Oh, really?
I'm gonna hold them back at any
cost until the Warden gets there!
That poison that he used against Straw Hat is still in the air here!
Wake up! I'm fighting off
the urge to sleep but I...
Shoot!
Straw Hat on level 4!
I'll definitely fulfill this
duty that the Warden left to me!
I...
Oh no!
...Don't sleep!
Warden!
The guards will see us through it!
Were you kidding just now?!
You're awake!
I wanna keep going! Crab-chan!
Buggy the Clown on level 2!
You've blocked the staircase but
now I can't catch up with Ace!
Hey, hey, Warden! Yes, yes, Warden!
MAIN ENTRANCE
--That was close.
That was the only way to stop the gas!
Hey, Warden! Our great Warden!
Go for it, go for it, Warden!
THE ELEVATOR TO LEVEL 6
If you fall unconscious, you can't save him!
You were too late!
Hey, Warden! It for go, it for go, Warden!
I'm gonna save him even if I'm
unconscious! I don't want him die!
Vice Warden! The crisis on
level 4! Can we go now?!
You're so strict, Domino.
The Warlord of the Sea--Blackbeard
at the main entrance!
Stupid! Use the Prison Bullets!
You need to do your business quickly from now on!
Don't be ridiculous!
Crescent Cutlass!
It's simple but their plan defeated us!
That's impossible!
We're confined to level 6! There's
no way for us to get out!
I don't know...
Here it comes again!
...how to begin to deal with this mess!
Just hold it!
This is it! We can't fight
them without the demon guards!
No way!
I'm sorry but this is all I can do now!
IMPEL DOWN'S EXCLUSIVE PREMIUM
"FRIED RICE CRACKERS"
We need to hand them the prisoner 9 am sharp at the front gate!
Break away! There's nothing to fear anymore!
Shoot the Prison Bullets!
Anybody want snacks?
That's our mission!
Damn! They're multiplying, too!
If we can't make it, we'll ruin the honor of Impel Down!
Are you nuts?! We gotta save Impel Down!
Dammit!
They can't see us anymore!
Ring, ring, ring...
Gum-Gum...
You have to realize--we're too late!
That's easy for you to
say! You're not in charge!
THE FRONT GATE OF IMPEL DOWN
...Rain!
They must've gotten to the top
floor with Ace boy by now!
--That's Chief Guard Sadie!
--Who cares! Push her away!
--I see! You wanna become a vice warden!
--Hannyabal!
Listen! We'll take Portgaz D. Ace from here and get to...
Fish-Man Karate!
Can you hear me?!
Shut up! You better call me Sadie-chan!
On the other hand, we have a lot
of obstacles standing in our way!
Manifesto of Excitement--Red Viper Whip!
W-Warden Magellan?! Where are you now?!
...the Marineford--Navy Headquarters.
The Navy's convoy is pretty
quick! Look at the Vivre Card!
How dare you...
Until the very moment that we hand over the prisoner,
I'm on level 2.
W-What was it?!
I've just taken care of the
fools running wild here.
...beat my sweet...
--I need you to pay full attention!
--Yes, sir!
It's not pointing straight up, is it?
To be prepared for any possibility, we'll convey him strictly with 5 ships...
Huh?!
...minions!
I think that Ace has already
been handed over to the Navy!
Help me!
...under the direction of 5 vice admirals! Do not fail!
I blocked all the exits on this floor!
Damn you!
All of them will stop moving soon!
Yes, sir!
Wait!
I told you to keep moving!
We're blocked up!
Heehaw!
I dunno why but I'm full of energy!
Captain Buggy! There is a
block of poison in our way!
I'm gonna be your match!
We gotta hurry! We don't wanna waste even a second!
Damn Magellan! How annoying!
Don't call me "you!" Mmm... I
told you to call me Sadie-chan!
There's no security here! So we can just run out in the open!
We can't stay here!
What's happening?!
I don't know why Blackbeard
is attacking us...
Emporio Female Hormone!
Nothing can stop us now!
--...but I already did something about it.
--Nice!
It's not something that I wanted to do but
I have no option under the circumstances!
Get out of our way! Eccentric girl!
What's that?!
It's not something that you wanted to do?!
Shut up! Now you became a woman, Ivankov?!
Who are they?!
T-That looks like Ivankov! I thought that he was dead!
You're just a confused anarchist!
I decided to release Shiryu against my will!
No way!
You did?!
For now, I...
Anyway, we can't ask the Navy
Headquarters for reinforcements.
...really feel like a woman!
Arabesque Brick Fist!
Outta my way!
You're right on time!
We have to handle this ourselves!
Don't mess with me!
We transfer custody of the criminal
- Portgaz D. Ace to the Navy!
You focus on bringing the situation
on level 4 under control!
Level 1! What's going on?
Have you gotten Blackbeard?
Death...
...Wink!
I'm gonna head down to level 4 soon!
Answer me! What's wrong? Answer me!
We're no match for them - an
infamous rookie and two Warlords!
Inazuma, open it!
It seems like fortune favors us now!
Hold out until I'll get there!
Okay!
D-Don't stop!
Hold out until backups will get
here! We're outnumbering them!
There's no response from level
1! Maybe they got wiped out!
They'll be monitoring us from now on!
Come and get me if you want!
Get out of our way! We're in hurry!
Warden!
That's ridiculous! Vice
Warden told me that...
Warden!
...Warden Magellan has released Jail Manager
Shiryu and let him fight Blackbeard!
Let's just go!
Hey, Warden! Hey, Warden! Hey, Warden!...
Here.
We have an intruder!
You fools! Shoot them up!
It's just a paper.
Can we go now?
They're at the staircase between level 5 and 6!
Yes, but that paper will
lead us to one another.
Even if the enemy is one of
The Seven Warlords of the Sea,
Fever!
Oh! I know this big guy!
Heehaw!
He was the king of queers--Ivankov who went missing years ago!
it's not so easy to beat Jail Manager Shiryu!
You don't want it?
No, I want it!
Humph! Maybe it's interesting to hear
the scream... mmm... of the queer king!
How could this be possible?!
Luffy!
How did he survive all these years?!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring,
ring, ring... Clank!
And this is the invader from yesterday
Women's weapons are not just their beauty!
What's up?!
--Vice Warden, this is level 4!
--You did it?!
These...
I thought that he was killed by the Warden!
...lithe and soft movements are weapons, too!
No, actually...
And he's another missing prisoner!
A revolutionary from South Blue--Inazuma!
We need to move on now!
Please come help us!
And maybe you don't understand it because
all you do is snap a whip but...
What's going on here?!
I'll do my best to help you break
out of this great prison safely!
H-Hurry up! Damn it! Dash!
Crab-chan! Where is the
staircase to level 3?!
They're heading straight to level 6!
They want to save "Fire Fist" Ace!
Go left! And across that bridge!
...women care for others tenderly!
They'll hand over Ace boy to the
Navy Headquarters at any cost!
Domino-san and Warden Magellan are also heading to level 6 now!
Camisole!
May his spirit rest in peace!
Long johns!
Got it!
T-back!
Get out of my way!
Ivan-sama! Stop mourning! I'm not dead yet!
You need to give up on him!
They'll bump into each other!
I mean, you need to trust Whitebeard.
--Pantyhose!
--Briefs!
They are all alive?!
Oh no!
He's not gonna give up on one of his
own! He'll definitely do something!
--Leggings!
--Briefs!
Vice Warden!
In addition to that, women are
sometimes far stronger than any man!
Bra!
Activate passageway traps now!
Bloomers!
Call jailers on level 6 and have them clear for action!
Bloomers! Briefs!
Shut up! Red Viper Whip!
--I'm going!
--Huh?!
They need to hold on until Sadie-chan and the demon guards get there!
I'm gonna go to Navy headquarters!
Briefs!
And report this to Warden Magellan and all floors!
I will get you!
Briefs!
PRISON
Don't be stupid!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
I can just pluck your head away
There's a battle brewing between
the world's two leading forces!
--That's all! Hurry up!
--Yes, sir!
Here comes the funny part!
What can you do?!
but then I don't get a chance to
hear your whimper so I'll wait!
Damn! Why're they hanging out
here? Those underwear fetishists!
I've never seen Vice Warden getting so serious!
Do you know how strong Whitebeard is?!
Light.
I'm gonna take time and make you
suffer so let me hear you scream!
Yes, sir!
They're so relaxed!
Maybe it's an imposter again!
What about the admirals, vice-admirals,
and Warlords on the Navy side?!
Finally we got to level 2!
We have to get them!
A JAIL MANAGER OF IMPEL
DOWN SHIRYU OF THE RAIN
Now!
If they find us, all of our efforts will come to nothing!
My job is on the line!
Don't you remember that you fought
just Magellan and almost died?!
But their farts really stink!
How stubborn you are! Let me hear it!
No, he's the real one!
Oh yeah!
Let me hear the queer king
- Ivankov's final scream!
Do you have that many lives to spare?!
Shiryu, how do you like it out of the cell?
We can make it! We can make it!
What?
Yeah, I really learned a lesson.
If I give up now...
The eternal boredom makes you long for death.
...I'm gonna regret it!
All of my bones shattered...
I'll be there right away, Ace!
But you're not gonna use me as a pawn
I-Ivan-sama!
You!
I've seen this face so many times before!
and then ask me to go back into
the cell, are you, Magellan?
Oh! I can't resist this!
I'm sorry.
--S-Smells like burdock...
--Sorry...
...Or not!
It's exactly like looking at Dragon!
Then why did you say it?!
No way! How come?!
But first of all, how can
you get off of this floor?!
You're a condemned prisoner! And
this is a deferred sentence!
By injecting Emporio Female Hormone,
my body got very lithe and soft!
This is your only chance!
Yeah, I bet.
So it absorbs any kind of shock!
If you wanna get out of here, set me free!
I'll keep that in mind!
How dare you!
Wow, the key! We can get out!
Here's your sword, Jail Manager Shiryu.
I can create a hole on the ceiling!
Hey! That was too hard!
Thank you very much!
Oh, you're C-Crocodile!
I'll leave Blackbeard to you!
Heehaw!
What do you think?
Who is it?! She talks like Ivan-chan!
I'm thinking about breaking out
but I need some assistants.
Hurry up! We're close to
the staircase to level 3!
Yes, sir!
Do you wanna come with me?
I'm gonna open the door!
Clank!
Alright, let's go!
Mr. 1!
Oh my sword!
Why's that?! The door's opening by itself!
Who cares? It's our luck!
Let's go up to level 3!
I haven't seen it for a while!
Alright, Portgaz D. Ace!
This is the great fort
of hell! No one may pass!
We will take you to Marineford...
You're being held here?!
...where the execution ground is!
Crocodile!
I'll come with you because you asked me.
I have the right...
The public execution of Ace is in...
It's been a while!
I was just starting to get bored.
...6 hours!
...to cut you down!
Straw Hat!
Who are you?!
Luffy finally makes it to the
lowest level of Impel Down, level 6.
With the Blackbeard pirates having invaded,
Impel Down spirals further into chaos.
Joining forces with Crocodile and Jimbei, Luffy and the others plan their escape.
Trying to break through level 4, Luffy and the others rush forward.
And the prisoners on level 2 begin to riot.
Meanwhile, Hannyabal takes note of their actions
However, Ace has already been taken away,
and the cell is empty.
Magellan arrives on level 4, and makes his way to Luffy and the others.
Blackbeard and the others manage
to evade the traps set out for them.
and is determined to settle things for his
own gain, so he turns his gaze to level 4.
Impel Down is engulfed in chaos.
Meanwhile, the man freed
by Magellan stands in their way.
Luffy tries to follow Ace but he's held up by Hannyabal's traps!
And to make things even more crazy,
Having eliminated the forces,
Luffy and the others attempt to reach level 3,
The final showdown between the Straw Hats
and Impel Down is about begin!
an unknown ship shows up.
but Hannyabal stands before them
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Ace's Convoy Begins!
Battle on the Lowest Floor Level 6!"
"The Dangerous Encounter! Blackbeard
and Shiryu of the Rain!"
and finally reveals his true power.
"The Ultimate Team Has Formed! Shaking Impel Down!"
"Even More Chaos! Here Comes Blackbeard Teech!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"No Price Too High! Serious Hannyabal!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!