Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
The public execution of Ace is in 4 and a
half hours and Luffy has gotten to level 1
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
and was about to get out of Impel Down
but Warden Magellan caught up with him,
who has been captured by the Navy.
Now with Jimbei and Crocodile,
they're battling on level 4!
who has been captured by the Navy.
While breaking out, Luffy and others
ran into the Warlord--Blackbeard...
But Ace has already been taken
away to the Navy Headquarters!
They are trying to break out!
so he has been held up!
He is pursuing his brother
who has been taken away!
--I'm going!
--Huh?!
...at the staircase in level 4!
This is the great fort
of hell! No one may pass!
And he is chasing them!
I'm gonna go to Navy Headquarters!
This unprecedented jailbreak
taking place in hell itself...
Now Luffy and others are trying to
break out and have gotten to level 4
What is going on here?!
"No Price Too High! Serious Hannyabal!"
...continues to unfold under the sea!
There's no Navy ship at all!
Ace's public execution is in...
I'm gonna save Ace at any cost!
Take a good look!
but at the staircase to level 3, they
face the furious Vice Warden Hannyabal!
...4 and a half hours!
You can see shadows of
sails slightly in the fog!
New Kama Kempo: 44--Aesthetic Technique!
This is the great fort of hell!
Yeah, I'm not gonna say that it's a waste!
There they are! Crowds of Navy ships!
Who is that?! Why did he
open the door so wide?!
If we let prisoners out of here, the
world will be filled with terror!
Anything is possible in this world!
I'm going to launch you
onto the deck! Hold tight!
He is Hannyabal - the vice
warden of this prison!
Hair Removal Fist!
Huh? W-What?! What did
you just say, fish face?!
So as I said, I won't let you take...
The 4 demon guards all
together after all this time!
I told you that the Sky Island exists!
...even a single step!
Shoot!
And so does the One Piece!
It certainly exists!
Oh? That bastard's gone!
B-B-B-B-Boss!
The only thing I care about
is saving Ace! So just move!
Ugh! What's going on here?!
--S-S-Straw Hat?!
--T-That's the Warlord--Jimbei!
Hydra!
You all should look forward to this!
Cut it out!
Ocean Current...
...Shoulder Throw!
All this arguing about right and wrong!
In a few hours, we're going to...
Look!
...put on a show that's
gonna shake the whole world!
Search the ends of the earth,
"Magellan's Tricky Move!
A Foiled Escape Plan!"
We have a thousand Cage Shot bazooka
troops on the stairway to level 3!
and you'd find no answer!
They're trying to hijack the
ship! Stop them at any cost!
Don't stop, Luffy-kun!
So, cut the crap!
We can just throw those Devil
Fruit eaters off into the water!
Looks like you were in middle of something!
After that king of the pervs and his crony,
There's no way out for you guys!
Keep going!
To level 3!
Teech! Why the hell are you here?!
it's your turn now!
Magellan...
"The Escapee Team in Trouble! The
Forbidden Move: Venom Demon!"
No way! Ivan-san and Inazuma got...
Or should I call you Blackbeard now?
--Vice Warden got all fired up!
--Maybe somebody's posing as him again!
Blackbeard!
Are you Magellan?!
Crab-chan!
So you're... Blackbeard?!
So you're Blackbeard?!
Ivan-chan!
Yes, indeed!
Pay your respects at Ace's grave!
Damn you!
Hydra!
If it weren't for him,
you'd be the one who...
No, Straw-chan!
Running is the only option
we have with Magellan!
...would've been killed, Straw Hat!
Let me go, Bon-chan! I got to kick his butt!
Ouch! What is this?!
Then why don't you try to kill me now?!
Are you sure?!
Gum-Gum...
This is for the bright future
of all innocent people!
--I understand--but you really want us to...
--Yes.
...Jet...
Straw Hat! How did you survive
after I poisoned you?!
--Set it all up as I said quick!
--Yes, sir!
...Pistol!
You, the worst pirate in
the history, Straw Hat!
He's probably the one who
caused this situation!
I impose the death penalty on
you on the Warden's behalf!
Alright! We have orders from Warden
Magellan! Get backup security to help us!
Hey.
You're gonna throw who into the water?
"Jet Pistol of Anger! Luffy vs. Blackbeard!"
I must take his life for sure this time!
You don't know your limits.
Yes, sir!
Dammit! So that's what he's planning?!
Straw Hat!
He's really out of character!
Don't be scared! Throw them overboard!
Outta my way!
Captain!
Don't forget that you
nearly died fighting him!
No way!
That poison bastard!
Outta my way!
I will never let you get out of this prison!
But I'm alive now!
I won't let Ace die!
Miracles don't come often, that's
why they are called miracles!
What the...
I can't believe it!
Hey! Look at that halberd!
Both of you, let's get to the upper level!
That's the Bloodsucker!
Jimbei!
Luffy-kun!
"Stop Magellan! Ivan-san's
Esoteric Technique Explodes!"
Gum-Gum...
Fish-Man Karate!
...Jet...
Get to the main entrance quickly!
You bastard!
Vortex!
Don't underestimate me!
It's not looking good!
Spear Wave!
We were paying
too much attention to Magellan!
--Looks like he's serious!
--Then we can depend on him because he's strong!
Straw-chan!
Hannya! Hannya! Hannya! Hannya!
Okay, I got it!
--We're gonna proceed with the plan now!
--Clank!
Straw-chan! Don't look back! Keep running!
Blood? I thought his body was rubber!
W-What's going on here?
Everybody, get ready! Get to your positions!
Yes, sir!
Hey, man...
Oops, I shouldn't have done that.
Those of you with guns,
shoot to stop Magellan!
We were gonna use that boat!
As you may know, it's the Hannya
Hustle Dance: Inferno Hell Wheel!
Blood?
Dammit!
Seems like you don't have
any idea of what happened!
You better go now, Straw-chan!
Gum-Gum...
You brother Ace looked like that!
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
I won't let you get away!
Hydra!
That's not enough to stop him!
Hurry up!
If you don't move, I'll move
you myself! I gotta save Ace!
Hurry! Magellan's right there!
Oh no! He's coming!
Let's go all the way to level 2!
Hurry up, Luffy-kun!
That's hilarious!
...Champion...
If I moved away that easily,
I wouldn't be the vice warden!
...Gatling!
Hydra!
Heads up, everybody!
I think that you got it when I grabbed you!
Another thing that my darkness drags in is...
Second Gear!
This is the last group!
...Devil Fruit powers!
Gum-Gum...
Behind these ones, no one is...
That means as long as I touch them,
...Jet...
...Gatling!
Devil Fruit eaters can't
use all of their powers!
...left standing!
And that's how I beat Ace! Don't you get it?
Candle Wall!
Devil Fruit powers are ineffective before me!
San!
How's that?!
He stopped Magellan's Hydra!
Your naiveness sickens me!
So what?!
Don't think me letting my guard down
means I want to be your friend!
We've been waiting for you!
Warden Magellan, please hurry!
Stupid!
Yes! Just one more push!
I just don't want to owe you any more favors!
Take this, bastard!
Wait, Luffy-kun! Enough already!
I admire you even more, brother 3!
Let me go!
Not now! Hold your anger!
I see. You use wax!
Let me go!
Where are the ringleaders?!
No, Luffy-kun! What is your priority?!
That's right! I ate the Wax-Wax
Fruit and became the wax man!
In front of the staircase to level 3!
Think about it! Luffy-kun!
That's the opposite side of
this floor! We have to hurry!
This wall is as tough as iron!
It won't let your venom through!
Vice Warden Hannyabal and the others are
managing to keep them there for now!
Ever since he was on good old
Whitebeard's ship, he was so strange!
Inazuma!
That pile of garbage found his use.
It's no use stalling for time!
Alright!
Vice Warden!
You never know what powers may come in handy.
Great Scissors!
I don't know how he got it
I've told all ships to
take off from Impel Down!
You better go now! I don't
intend to do this forever!
but he has this power that enabled him
to defeat even the unbeatable Ace-san!
There are no ships left for you to steal!
San!
That was too easy! I'm not
a very good vice warden!
How annoying!
You can't waste your time and energy here!
The old Fish-Man and others went to get
one!
If he were here...
I know that they will find a way!
Fighting with him out of anger now
doesn't help you to save Ace-san!
Don't just stand there! It
won't hold out that long!
THE WARDEN'S OFFICE
20 YEARS AGO
You're talking about Jimbei?
Then
I should end this all the faster!
Okay, I'm gonna go!
T-This is my first day as a jailer!
Let's go, you guys!
Inazuma-san!
My name is Hannyabal!
--You've got quite a power!
--It works well if it's not the fiery floor!
Why did you cut the staircase?!
You're stronger than I thought!
You look like a viper as they say.
Ivan-sama hasn't come up yet!
You got more Haki than you did before!
What?! No! That hurts!
Keep going, you guys! I wanna
follow right behind you!
Don't worry! Just keep moving!
Your name is Blackbeard?
You're the only person who can
look out for him as I thought.
Luffy-kun, we have to go now!
I heard that a nameless pirate...
Magellan!
Didn't you say we need to steal a Navy ship?
I got it, sir!
...who was on Whitebeard's ship
had taken my place as a Warlord.
Ivan-san!
Yes.
Then, why don't you go ahead with
everyone else? I'll try to stop him!
But it's odd.
You should've been summoned
by Navy Headquarters already.
It'll be hard to steal it
with him chasing us anyway.
Why are you here?
Damn Magellan!
That's true but...
Gum-Gum...
You're risking your title of Warlord
that you really wanted by being here.
Why should I be assigned to level 1?
I have an idea!
No no! Run, Straw Hat!
Do you think it's gonna work?
On top of that,
Yeah! You can count on me!
I'm only in charge of
the security check for new prisoners!
...Champion...
Alright! But don't push it too far!
...Stamp!
It's all part of my plan!
--The next one has come!
--Oh, okay!
Please be safe!
Do I have to tell you everything about it?
She has a 50 million berry
bounty. A pirate--Ms. Olive!
You pushed it too far! The
wax won't work anymore!
Okay, San! Let's fight him!
Mr. Crocodile!
No no! I wasn't gonna fight! I
was doing it so we can run...
She's a vicious criminal!
Take extra care with her!
No, you don't. Actually
I'm not interested at all.
She's so my type! Oops, I
shouldn't have said that!
Brother 3! We aren't so
strong but let us help you!
Wax-Wax...
...Release!
Oh, how cold of you!
Like I said, I wasn't gonna go that far...
He was so easy! Like all other men!
H-Hey! What's going on?!
Hey, can you do me a favor?
I gotta strip all my clothes off, right?
That was close!
Listen to me!
Magellan's here!
It's embarrassing,
so can you turn away?
Here comes Hydra again!
S-Sure!
It's not good.
--Can you do that?
--Yes, that's possible.
Straw boy, you better go now!
Are you ready yet?
Not yet!
If you get poisoned by Magellan again,
there's no way for you to survive this time!
--Okay, I'm counting on you!
--All right!
How foolish is he?
Quite.
Wax-Wax Candle Armor!
It's Warden Magellan!
Dammit! Everyone, run!
Warden Magellan...
L-Let me go!
Thank god! Warden's here!
Don't let your guard down!
Ouch!
It doesn't matter if it's level 1 or
6! All duties are equally important!
Magellan... I get to meet him finally!
Climb up the stairs!
The bazooka troops are gone!
Nothing's in our way now!
You gotta keep in mind what's going
to happen if any one person fails!
Venom...
...Demon!
Ivankov! Mmm... I won't let you go!
Let me hear the scream of a queer!
What are you trying to do here?
Alright! With these on, I'm...
P-P-Princess! P-P-Please don't!
Let me go!
...so cool!
S-S-Striking me with your
whip? It's gonna hurt!
What am I trying to do?
It's perfect!
It's not over yet!
If you really can't tell
what I'm trying to do...
What happened to you?
Face forward! What're you
saying at a time like this?!
But I like how you're freaking out!
Don't know why... but tears
keep filling my eyes...
Now stop fighting me!
I-I-I got it! I'm coming to you now!
Thank you for making me this cool!
Catch me if you can!
Shut up and just fight!
You can't go through here!
Straw Hat, I admire you
just for your tenacity!
Mmm... My whip!
What did you do to Ivan-chan?!
Give it back to me, Ivankov!
You're talking about Ivankov?
If you're so into screaming,
Of course, I executed him!
Follow the Vice Warden! Don't hold back!
why don't you scream yourself?!
Don't worry! You will soon follow!
...you must be very...
Bring it on!
I'm the queen of queers--Ivankov!
Outta my way!
...stupid!
I-It's coming!
Death Wink!
Why don't you call me Mistress?!
I'm gonna save Ace!
Hydra!
--San!
--All right!
Heehaw!
Candle Wall!
Ivankov!
Straw Hat! You better hurry and
climb up the stairs to level 3!
It's not gonna work no matter
how many times you try!
--We better run!
--Hurry up!
Heehaw!
Gum-Gum...
Hell's Judgement!
It's fortunate for us that you broke
their defense on the staircase!
...Champion...
So what?! It's not over yet!
...Rifle!
Outta my way!
You helped us, too.
Yes! I can touch him!
We took advantage of the
panic that you caused!
Damn!
--We found cannons!
--With candle shields!
You...
Guys, help me! Let me go with you!
Now things are getting serious!
You can't go through here!
Yes! We can get to level 3!
Hey!
Even if you buy yourself some time,
Gum-Gum...
Stupid! You can't touch me!
Let's go at once!
...Jet Stamp!
Straw Hat and others can't get out of here!
Yeah! We got him!
The poison's spreading!
We can beat him!
"Buy some time?"
Alright!
Stop!
So you think that you can beat me?
Quit bothering me!
Listen! We gotta buy some time here!
Dammit! I have to hurry to make it on time!
Kamabakka style - New Kama Kempo!
Here they come! Shoot!
You can't go through here!
Feast your eyes on this!
Don't hesitate! You guys, break away!
It doesn't matter if it's wax or rock,
Kama!
It's a demon guard again!
the poison is spreading like an infection!
You're the King of Diarrhea!
This time, it's Minotaurus!
Why don't you wear a toilet
seat instead of your hat?!
We're close! Keep going up!
Dammit! No wonder the
Wax-Wax Armor didn't work!
What?! Minotaurus?!
--Almost there!
--We can get out!
He's been cussing for more than 30 minutes!
Heehaw!
"Oh Come My Way" Kenpo:
That's our Captain Buggy!
Memoirs of a Winter's Sky!
Your mom's got an outie belly button!
IMPEL DOWN--LEVEL 1 ABOVE WATER
"MAIN ENTRANCE"
Ready, Straw Hat?!
I don't have anything more to say!
I wonder how Straw-chan and others are doing!
It didn't work?!
--Candle Lock!
--Alright!
I can't ad-lib anything else!
Magellan is unbeatable! Let's go all the way!
Hey hey! Come on now!
Gum-Gum...
--What about the ships?!
--I can hear the sound of gunfire...
A-Are you alright?
Heehaw!
...Mallet Rifle!
...but can't figure out
what's going on in the fog!
What?!
Magellan's kind of tough, huh?
Let me just go to the bathroom!
I know that they're capable of
stealing a ship for sure but...
I thought that we already
beat him on level 3!
D-Don't tell us...
...that you got diarrhea, Captain Buggy?!
It's inevitable.
But it's too far!
They're all awakened Zoan
type Devil Fruit eaters!
No, I just wanna pee! Ha!
They have to steal it and bring
it all the way back here!
Long underpants!
Chemise!
That's why they're extremely
tough and resilient!
Then, we'll go with you!
You mean they can't make
it here before Magellan?!
There are no more formidable enemies here!
It's odd! The poison bastard
was right behind us while ago!
So you're saying that he
ate the Devil Fruit, too?!
You're letting your guard
down. What are you an amateur?
I saw Ivan-san and Inazuma
stopped in the lower level!
I know that Straw Hat Luffy is strong...
If we don't hurry up, the
other three will recover soon.
What?!
...but I don't think that he can stall
the unbeatable Magellan for that long!
What?!
There are at least 10 Navy ships out there.
So they're fighting the poison
bastard! Let's go back!
What should I do?!
But we shouldn't be afraid of them now.
Straw-chan!
If nothing happens,
Gimme a break!
And each one has 800 marines on board.
Damn! Please hurry, Jimbei!
Because the boss of hell
will be here any minute!
we can't break out and
my reputation will be ruined!
If they're fighting, we gotta keep moving!
I don't know their configuration but...
I gotta come up with something!
You have to believe in the
power of the miracle-worker!
...stealing a Navy ship means that we
will have to face the remaining ships.
Warden Magellan!
Spin, spin!
I got a report that Blackbeard is already
on this floor at the staircase to level 3!
Can you still be relaxed?
What's wrong with this floor?
They can't be this lax.
Y-You've got a point.
Throw them off! Don't
let them have this ship!
It's strange! I don't see
any prisoners in the cells!
I ordered Shiryu to handle
them! Was he defeated?!
That's not the only problem we have!
--This is the monitoring room!
--What now?!
And all the doors are open!
There's no more guards here!
All that is left is this door!
We've got a problem!
Damn you!
I wonder who released them!
Somebody broke the Vision
Receiver Transponder Snail...
...and none of monitors are working now!
What shitty fortifications!
Come on, get out! Let's
get back on the street!
Plus, all communication channels to the Navy
HQ and government agencies are cut off!
Finally!
That didn't help them avoid their destiny!
I've never forgotten the
entrance of Impel Down!
Thank you, Captain Buggy!
What's wrong with his body?!
The whole body's like a knife!
Yes! I'm so glad!
We all came through here
and entered into hell!
I'm out!
Liberation!
You gotta do your part!
I ate the Dice-Dice Fruit.
--Here you go!
--Thanks!
It's been how many years?
So we can't contact...
Take this!
Are we really here?! I
still can't believe it!
W-What's going on here?
I remember him! He's an
assassin from the West Blue...
Shoot! Shoot!
...named Daz!
What's the matter?! What happened?!
I never thought that I'd break out like this.
--Who did all that?!
--Clank!
Alright! Everybody, train your
weapons! Let's open the door!
Keep going! Keep it up!
Don't blow my cover!
I don't want Magellan clued in!
Ready? Here we go!
That's a long leak!
I'm gonna get out finally!
You gotta hear this, Captain Buggy!
You fool! This doesn't mean
that we've succeeded yet!
What's wrong?
The Navy is waiting for us out there
and we don't know if we can make it!
Come on, get out! Let's
get back on the street!
The wall...
...is gone!
Thank you, Captain Buggy!
Yes! I'm so glad!
The communication has been cut!
What did you just say?!
Sables!
I'm out!
--Send someone to check!
--Yes, sir!
You're right.
You gotta do your part!
W-What happened?!
Now that you put
it that way I agree with you.
--Here you go!
--Thanks!
This is bad.
Take this!
If Blackbeard got
to this floor, it means that...
The block of poison's really gone!
Yeah. But we can't stop
after coming this far.
It's only a matter of time
before they steal that ship!
...he has broken the block that I set
on level 2 and made his way there!
We should just go as far as we can!
My attack finally worked!
It'll be a dishonor to the Navy!
--Sink it right away!
--Yes, sir!
Keep going! Keep it up!
Nothing is going as planned!
What a pain in the butt!
Get ready to fire!
We allowed just this one rat to
sneak in and now look at this mess!
So you were really fighting the
venom with your venomous tongue!
Luckily getting out of level 2
blocked by Magellan's poison,
Was the peeing part of it?!
--Buggy!
--Mr. 3!
There's the column again!
Captain Buggy and merry prisoners
are heading to the main entrance.
Cool! I knew that you were in another league!
--Buggy!
--Mr. 3!
--It's sunlight!
--I'm free!
Oh no. This doesn't make sense at all.
They're on level 1.
We are flashy lucky men!
Everybody, get ready!
--Dammit! The gunpowder got wet!
--That must be Jimbei!
Running through level 4--the Burning Heat
Hell and level 3--the Starving Hell,
Alright! The block is gone now!
Guys! We're finally here! It's level 1!
Even if thousands of marines
are waiting for us,
we're gonna break through
and go back to the sea!
the mob of New Kamas led by Straw Hat
Luffy and the assembled freed prisoners...
Come and follow my lead, you guys!
Shoot him from the other batteries!
Everyone! We're gonna go
out on the sunny street!
...are now running through
level 2 - the Wild Beast Hell.
Hurry up! Hurry! He's right behind us!
Our very lucky savior!
Captain Buggy!
Stop bothering me!
Get out of my way!
And Warden Magellan who was on their tail...
--Jimbei!
--Crocodile!
No, I won't!
Alright! Let's go, you guys!
...is fighting with the queen
of queers Ivankov in level 3!
--I said "Outta my way!"
--I won't let you go a single step!
Captain Buggy!
I can't believe that the poison
block had gone on its own!
There's no time!
I said "Outta my way!"
M-My spine has... mmm... got hurt!
Yeah, me too!
We're so lucky!
D-Damn Ivankov!
Hey! Is everybody there?!
I... I gotta save Ace!
Heehaw!
I hear Straw-chan!
I'm gonna save Ace at any cost!
That's unforgivable!
You gotta run!
"Wanna save my brother?"
Yeah, I'm not gonna say that it's a waste!
Alright! Let's go, you guys!
You're the dreg of society
so just cut the crap!
Anything is possible in this world!
They're being chased by something horrible!
Follow me!
Get them right now!
It's Magellan! We have nowhere to go!
How long... mmm... are
you gonna keep sleeping?!
You guys are all pirates and
rebels who earn only infamy!
I told you that the Sky Island exists!
Did you get a ship?!
Straw-chan! I'm afraid that
we don't have a ship yet!
--Vice Warden Hannyabal!
--Don't stand up! You're gonna die!
And the 4 demon guards who have been
beaten but come back repeatedly...
What?!
What is going on here?!
With you on the seas,
...are heading to level 1 by elevator.
She said "Sky Island!"
There's no Navy ship at all!
people can't even sleep at night from
fear of losing their loved ones!
Give me a break!
Jail Manager Shiryu who switched
sides cut all communication lines
I've injected some hormones and
managed to walk a little bit...
That's why we lock up all the vicious
criminals to make them feel safe!
Not even a single ship to steal!
Hey, you got me there.
so no one would find out the
situation inside the prison.
You guys believe in such an ancient legend...
Not even a single marine!
This is the great fort of hell!
that there's an island in the sky?
Those unprecedented dramatic events keep
expanding literally behind closed doors.
No way! Then...
If we let prisoners out of here, the
world will be filled with terror!
Listen. The era where pirates
dream about things is over!
...we can't do anything!
But I have had it...
So as I said, I won't let you take...
Navy ships and prison ships are
anchored around the prison!
When I see idiots chasing after
dreams like that, I get disgusted!
...even a single step!
What should we do?!
If we're able to steal one of them, we can
get to Marineford before Ace-san's execution!
Vice Warden!
All we can do is just wait for
Magellan to come and kill us here?!
Luffy!
The Sky Island exists.
Hell Wink!
Great! Wait for me, Ace!
Dammit! You gotta be kidding!
You're that guy...
Ace's imminent public execution is...
The new era they're talking about is crap!
I see. They're not as stupid as I thought.
...in 4 and a half hours!
The era where pirates have dreams
will be over, they say?! Huh?!
There are large Sea Kings in the water.
The only thing I care about
is saving Ace! So just move!
As is said, the Calm Belt is the
greatest barrier protecting Impel Down.
My face... My face is gonna melt!
You're too stupid to understand...
We barely made it this far
from the bottom of hell!
People's dreams... have no end!!
V-Vice Warden, help me!
Damn! We'll be dragged back to hell!
My face... My face...
We don't have time to complain!
Isn't that right?!
Ivan-chan?!
My face... My face... My face is...
Hey, what's the matter, you guys?!
They cleared out because Magellan
told them to do so--but not long ago!
Cut it out!
And so does the One Piece!
It certainly exists!
You scared us!
...gonna melt... melt... melt...
I-It seems like I made it in time! Thud!
Take a good look!
...Or not! Because I've
got so much make up on!
All this arguing about right and wrong!
You can see shadows of
sails slightly in the fog!
He passed out from hitting his head!
You all should look forward to this!
Oh yeah, he's right!
Search the ends of the earth,
Ivan-san! Inazuma! You both are alive!
"It's not gonna melt?!" Heehaw!
But it's too far! We still can't reach them!
In a few hours, we're going to...
and you'd find no answer!
"You got me there!" Heehaw!
--I'm so glad!
--Ivan-sama!
Yeah, it's too late for us to...
So, cut the crap!
...put on a show that's
gonna shake the whole world!
Don't worry!
Those two!
Heehaw!
Don't stop, Luffy-kun!
Straw Hat! It's from Jimbei!
You have me here! Let me handle this!
Death Wink!
Wink! Wink!
The Baby Transponder Snail?!
I met him at Jaya!
Good job, you guys!
Death Wink! Wink! Wink!
Why did you even come?
Heehaw!
--Clank!
--Luffy-kun, you got out?!
Wink! Wink! Wink!
Keep going!
Yeah, but he's still chasing us!
To level 3!
And we're running out of places to run!
Wink! Wink! Wink!
Holy cow!
Sorry! We got a ship but...
How strong!
Wink! Wink!
Wow! Wow!
Venom Blowfish!
...it'll take some time to get there!
There's no way that we can beat
him! We can't get through!
How interesting to see
all these faces at once!
Don't stop! Just jump into the water!
He's carrying the gigantic door by himself?!
Throw everyone off into the water as well!
I can't carry that many
Looks like you were in middle of something!
What're you saying, Jimbei?!
This is the Calm Belt!
but let's sail out with this
to take one of those ships!
He's pushing us backward on
his way down the staircase!
Those of you who are determined, get on!
Teech! Why the hell are you here?!
The lace... My bootlace...
You can leave the rest up to me!
Damn! We're helpless! What should we do?!
...came loose... loose...
Is it possible to steal a ship with that?
Or should I call you Blackbeard now?
--Let's do as he says!
--What?!
Hey, Straw Hat! Be careful!
...loose... loose... loose...
San, help me again!
Are you nuts?! If we dive into
the water, we're gonna die!
C-Crocodile!
Jimbei!
...Or not! Because they're laceless!
That's it? Alright then...
Hey, that's not nice! Why
don't you loosen your fist?!
He's a minion of the Government
Heehaw!
and we can't trust him! Damn Fish-Man!
Wait a minute!
"There's no lace?!" Heehaw!
Oh yeah! You're close to Ace, aren't you?
Aren't you forgetting about me?
He's a friend of Ace! I trust him!
"You got me there!" Heehaw!
I know you need me so I'm coming with you!
But you're barking up the wrong tree!
--Straw-chan! Let me help...
--Wait!
This is foolish.
What?
Why?
It's foolish of you trying to gain some time!
We better not bother him now!
--You have a lot of guts!
--That's our Captain Buggy!
Into the water?! Go ahead and dive if you
want!
Hey! What do you mean
"bother?!" I just wanna...
You think so? I'm having so much fun!
Take this Baby Transponder
Snail I found just in case!
Blackbeard!
There are Sea Kings' nests everywhere!
I'm chasing a certain man.
Alright then, let's get it over with.
Be careful! You can't touch
even a drop of his poison!
Hey, can we just go now?
Outta my way!
His name is Blackbeard.
Alright! Let's do it!
Between you...
People's dreams...
--That's impossible!
--We're gonna die!
...and me!
You all ready? We got to hurry!
...have no end!
What should we do?!
I heard a pirate called Blackbeard...
New Kama Kempo: 44 - Aesthetic Technique!
...became a Warlord by
defeating "Fire Fist" Ace.
Hell's Judgement!
He's swimming with that
heavy door on his back!
Straw-chan!
Only the captain of the Fish-Man
Pirates could do that!
Third Gear!
Hair Removal Fist!
Blackbeard...
I can't wait to see how
the Warlord's gonna fight!
Here's an oversized treat! Candle Wall!
Second Gear!
So you're...
Gum-Gum...
And our savior Captain Buggy is with him!
...Jet...
It's no use!
...Pistol!
It's looking hopeful!
You're...
...Blackbeard?!
Straw Hat! Hurry up!
Huh? Oh yeah, I never gave you my name.
How stupid they are! It's much
safer to be with a Warlord...
Ace!
...rather than staying there and
being scared of Magellan, fools!
Long time no see, Straw Hat!
I can't hold it any longer!
I was surprised, too, when I heard
you were my commander's brother!
A-Amazing!
Gum-Gum...
He finished the demon
guard with a single blow!
They're shooting at us!
He's quite a guy as I thought!
...Giant Stamp!
Are you sure you want to be
here? You're gonna miss it!
They found us.
Straw-chan!
Ivan-san!
He avoided it! He's so fast!
Okay, guys! The lid of the
pot of hell is off now!
Your brother's public execution!
He's not just a Fish-Man! He's the
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei!
Venom Road!
Let's go!
All forces! Open fire!
If we can sink Jimbei, they are finished!
I found out later that the
former Warlord right there...
Warden!
There they are! Crowds of Navy ships!
...Crocodile was defeated
by you, Straw Hat Luffy!
Can you just help me, Warden?!
Wow! He pushed it back!
Sadie-chan! What happened to you?!
Ivan-san!
At that time, I was trying to
take his place as a Warlord so...
Okama-kov... has beaten me!
Oh no...
I'm going to launch you
onto the deck! Hold tight!
...killing you was the most effective way
to show my ability to the Government!
It's humiliating! My life
is about dominating others!
Keep Out!
Huh? W-What?! What did
you just say, fish face?!
Help her get down! I gotta run!
Are you here to stall me, too?
Oh? That bastard's gone!
Oh, yes! Right away!
The poison keeps spreading!
Ugh! What's going on here?!
Should we dive into the water?!
Teech, let's cut the idle talk!
I know! He left us here
and got away by himself!
Here they are!
You should know the rules, having
lived through twice as much as others.
Here it comes!
Traitor, traitor, traitor...
Ivan-chan! Ivan-chan, wake up!
Why did you come with us?
The 4 demon guards all
together after all this time!
Whitebeard's reign is over! I'll
become the next Pirate King!
We're in trouble! Ivan-chan! Wake up!
Hey, you gotta wake up now!
For starters, I'm gonna kill Straw Hat
Luffy who is in the Water Seven...
Run!
Are you Magellan?!
--What do you want?
--We got to hurry!
It's over! Let's go back!
We can't fight them!
Jimbei! Where's that bastard gone?!
So you're Blackbeard?!
...as a gift to the Government!
--Who are you? Straw boy's son?
--Can you do the wink?!
Yes, indeed!
Let's just forget about breaking out!
Luffy? What did you just say?
We're gonna get hit!
Okay!
Hydra!
What?!
No way! If you do that, we're gonna...
Oh! You know him?!
Can't you just be quiet?
Here you go!
Wait a minute, Ivan-sama!
Hey, are you okay?
Another reason I can't let you go free!
Fish-Man Jiu-Jitsu!
You bastard! What are you...
That's unthinkable to me!
He's my brother!
There's no way to survive by diving
into the water without a ship!
...dile?!
But fate has saved you instead!
B-B-B-B-Boss!
Water Heart!
Huh?
--Everybody, hold onto the face!
--The face?!
Oh, it's you, Mr. 3.
I don't have time to ask
what brought you guys here!
Ace who has been chasing after me for
the crime on Whitebeard's ship...
But I'm not gonna let you get away!
What are you doing here, you useless trash?
...happens to be your brother!
W-Who released this pain in the butt?!
--Hurry up!
--Hold onto Ivan-sama!
It's coming towards us!
When he faced us - we, who were
going to kill his brother -
I won't allow anyone to
escape from Impel Down!
Ouch! What is this?!
C-Captain Buggy!
he had his retreat cut off!
Ocean Current...
Hell...
They KO'd the demon guards!
It should be poison! Dammit! That bastard!
If I yield to power, there's
no point in being born a man.
...Shoulder Throw!
What?!
...Wink!
S-S-Straw Hat?!
T-That's the Warlord Jimbei!
I'll never leave anything to
be regretted later in my life!
I won't!
Good! You guys are okay!
Do you understand, stupid?
Hannyabal!
GOOD! YOU GUYS ARE OKAY!
We're flying!
I'm surprised that you held out this long!
The sun or the darkness -
there'll be only one winner!
It breaks...
What's that water column?!
It looks like a living thing!
...My heart!
Let me handle the rest!
I'm gonna make Whitebeard the king!
Captain Buggy!
Vice Warden!
A bunch of prisoners and perverts
Do you have any idea of what it is?
are
coming up one after another from level 2!
You look horrible!
No, I don't.
We're gonna fall!
--Give him the treatment now!
--Yes, sir!
Perverts, too?! What the hell?!
But I can see people on it! One is Crocodile!
Who are you calling perverts?!
You two! This is for walking
out on us back there!
Vice Warden! Stay with me! Vice Warden!
You can't die! Because you're the only one...
You're here, too, Mr. 2!
Do you get it?
If he let us get away, not only
would it disgrace Whitebeard's name
What're you doing to Captain Buggy?!
Something's under the ship!
...who can take my place!
What are they?!
It's coming!
but he'd allow his brother's death!
This is no good!
These level 4 prisoners
came all the way up here at last!
Fly, Ivankov!
They're trying to hijack the
ship! Stop them at any cost!
There's no coincidence in fate! That means...
It's impossible! He's losing consciousness!
They managed to get away
from Warden Magellan?!
We can just throw those Devil
Fruit eaters off into the water!
Jeez! We allowed two riots at the same time!
Yeah! You're so lucky! Burp...
Where's Warden now?!
Straw Hat! How did you survive
after I poisoned you?!
What's this?!
Hydra!
We landed on something!
Our captain became the
Warlord and made his name
Hey, look!
He's probably the one who
caused this situation!
so you're useless to us now!
What's this?!
I must take his life for sure this time!
You made it!
You didn't learn anything
after I beat you so soundly?!
I'm sorry that I should ask you
to come to this dangerous area!
Your brother fought bravely!
I forgot it all!
Pay your respects at his grave!
Gum-Gum...
Magellan's here, too!
Straw Hat!
...Champion...
If it weren't for him,
you'd be the one who...
What's going on on this floor?!
...Bazooka!
What?! Then Ivan-chan and Crab-chan are...
...would've been killed, Straw Hat!
Is that Magellan?!
That was from the bottom of the stairs!
Once he catches us, we're dead!
Then why don't you...
...try to kill me now?!
That poison bastard!
Then this time, I'll make sure
that you'll never forget...
Gum-Gum...
--It's a school of whale sharks!
--Jimbei must have called them!
I will never let you get out of this prison!
...by burying you with it!
...Jet...
...Pistol!
Cool!
Luffy and the others have finally reached level 3.
To buy Jimbei the timed needed to steal a ship,
Finally, Magellan catches up to Luffy and the others.
While attempting to escape during the choas,
Luffy is confronted by Blackbeard.
Luffy and the others have at last escaped Impel Down.
In order to hold off Magellan,
who continues to gain on them,
Luffy, in order to help the others off level 1,
Luffy makes a stand against Magellan.
However, there isn't any time for celebration.
The Gate of Justice stands in their way,
and the Navy is hot on their tails.
Blackbeard tells of his involvement
in arranging Ace's execution.
holds Magellan at bay with the aid of Mr. 3.
Ivan-san orders Inazuma to seal off
the stairway leading to level 2
Magellan, now at bay,
unleashes his strongest technique, capable of destroying Impel Down itself.
Meanwhile, Jinbei makes it to the entrance with the prisoners,
and remains behind on level 3 alone
Just when it seems like all hope is lost,
After hearing this, Luffy fights him out of anger.
a friend makes the ultimate sacrifice!
where he unleashes his secret technique,
New Kama Kempo, on Magellan!
but Magellan has one more thing up his sleeve!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Escapee Team in Trouble! The
Forbidden Move: Venom Demon!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Jet Pistol of Anger! Luffy vs. Blackbeard!"
"Come, Final Miracle! Break
Through the Gate of Justice!"
"Stop Magellan! Ivan-san's
Esoteric Technique Explodes!"
"Magellan's Tricky Move!
A Foiled Escape Plan!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!