Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
But Ace has already been taken
away to the Navy Headquarters!
--I'm going!
--Huh?!
I'm gonna go to Navy Headquarters!
Now Luffy and others are trying to
break out and have gotten to level 4
but at the staircase to level 3, they
face the furious Vice Warden Hannyabal!
This is the great fort of hell!
If we let prisoners out of here, the
world will be filled with terror!
So as I said, I won't let you take...
...even a single step!
The only thing I care about
is saving Ace! So just move!
Cut it out!
All this arguing about right and wrong!
Search the ends of the earth,
and you'd find no answer!
So, cut the crap!
Looks like you were in middle of something!
Teech! Why the hell are you here?!
Or should I call you Blackbeard now?
Blackbeard!
So you're... Blackbeard?!
Pay your respects at Ace's grave!
If it weren't for him,
you'd be the one who...
...would've been killed, Straw Hat!
Then why don't you try to kill me now?!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
...Pistol!
"Jet Pistol of Anger! Luffy vs. Blackbeard!"
Captain!
I won't let Ace die!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
Vortex!
Straw-chan!
Blood? I thought his body was rubber!
Blood?
Seems like you don't have
any idea of what happened!
You brother Ace looked like that!
I think that you got it when I grabbed you!
Another thing that my darkness drags in is...
...Devil Fruit powers!
That means as long as I touch them,
Devil Fruit eaters can't
use all of their powers!
And that's how I beat Ace! Don't you get it?
Devil Fruit powers are ineffective before me!
So what?!
Wait, Luffy-kun! Enough already!
Let me go!
Not now! Hold your anger!
No, Luffy-kun! What is your priority?!
Think about it! Luffy-kun!
Ever since he was on good old
Whitebeard's ship, he was so strange!
I don't know how he got it
but he has this power that enabled him
to defeat even the unbeatable Ace-san!
You can't waste your time and energy here!
Fighting with him out of anger now
doesn't help you to save Ace-san!
You're stronger than I thought!
You got more Haki than you did before!
Your name is Blackbeard?
I heard that a nameless pirate...
...who was on Whitebeard's ship
had taken my place as a Warlord.
But it's odd.
You should've been summoned
by Navy Headquarters already.
Why are you here?
You're risking your title of Warlord
that you really wanted by being here.
It's all part of my plan!
Do I have to tell you everything about it?
Mr. Crocodile!
No, you don't. Actually
I'm not interested at all.
Oh, how cold of you!
H-Hey! What's going on?!
Magellan's here!
It's not good.
Straw boy, you better go now!
If you get poisoned by Magellan again,
there's no way for you to survive this time!
It's Warden Magellan!
Dammit! Everyone, run!
Warden Magellan...
Thank god! Warden's here!
Magellan... I get to meet him finally!
Climb up the stairs!
The bazooka troops are gone!
Nothing's in our way now!
Ivankov! Mmm... I won't let you go!
Let me hear the scream of a queer!
P-P-Princess! P-P-Please don't!
S-S-Striking me with your
whip? It's gonna hurt!
What happened to you?
But I like how you're freaking out!
Now stop fighting me!
I-I-I got it! I'm coming to you now!
Catch me if you can!
Mmm... My whip!
Give it back to me, Ivankov!
If you're so into screaming,
why don't you scream yourself?!
I'm the queen of queers--Ivankov!
Why don't you call me Mistress?!
Heehaw!
Ivankov!
Straw Hat! You better hurry and
climb up the stairs to level 3!
It's fortunate for us that you broke
their defense on the staircase!
You helped us, too.
We took advantage of the
panic that you caused!
Yes! We can get to level 3!
Let's go at once!
It's a demon guard again!
This time, it's Minotaurus!
What?! Minotaurus?!
"Oh Come My Way" Kenpo:
Memoirs of a Winter's Sky!
Ready, Straw Hat?!
--Candle Lock!
--Alright!
Gum-Gum...
...Mallet Rifle!
I thought that we already
beat him on level 3!
It's inevitable.
They're all awakened Zoan
type Devil Fruit eaters!
That's why they're extremely
tough and resilient!
So you're saying that he
ate the Devil Fruit, too?!
If we don't hurry up, the
other three will recover soon.
But we shouldn't be afraid of them now.
Because the boss of hell
will be here any minute!
Warden Magellan!
I got a report that Blackbeard is already
on this floor at the staircase to level 3!
I ordered Shiryu to handle
them! Was he defeated?!
--This is the monitoring room!
--What now?!
We've got a problem!
Somebody broke the Vision
Receiver Transponder Snail...
...and none of monitors are working now!
Plus, all communication channels to the Navy
HQ and government agencies are cut off!
So we can't contact...
W-What's going on here?
What's the matter?! What happened?!
--Who did all that?!
--Clank!
Don't blow my cover!
I don't want Magellan clued in!
The communication has been cut!
--Send someone to check!
--Yes, sir!
This is bad.
If Blackbeard got
to this floor, it means that...
...he has broken the block that I set
on level 2 and made his way there!
Nothing is going as planned!
We allowed just this one rat to
sneak in and now look at this mess!
--Buggy!
--Mr. 3!
We are flashy lucky men!
Guys! We're finally here! It's level 1!
Everyone! We're gonna go
out on the sunny street!
Our very lucky savior!
Captain Buggy!
I can't believe that the poison
block had gone on its own!
Yeah, me too!
We're so lucky!
I'm gonna save Ace at any cost!
Yeah, I'm not gonna say that it's a waste!
Anything is possible in this world!
I told you that the Sky Island exists!
She said "Sky Island!"
Give me a break!
Hey, you got me there.
You guys believe in such an ancient legend...
that there's an island in the sky?
Listen. The era where pirates
dream about things is over!
When I see idiots chasing after
dreams like that, I get disgusted!
Luffy!
The Sky Island exists.
You're that guy...
The new era they're talking about is crap!
The era where pirates have dreams
will be over, they say?! Huh?!
People's dreams... have no end!!
Isn't that right?!
And so does the One Piece!
It certainly exists!
You all should look forward to this!
In a few hours, we're going to...
...put on a show that's
gonna shake the whole world!
Don't stop, Luffy-kun!
Heehaw!
Keep going!
To level 3!
There's no way that we can beat
him! We can't get through!
He's pushing us backward on
his way down the staircase!
Damn! We're helpless! What should we do?!
Hey, Straw Hat! Be careful!
--Straw-chan! Let me help...
--Wait!
Why?
We better not bother him now!
Hey! What do you mean
"bother?!" I just wanna...
Outta my way!
Straw-chan!
Second Gear!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
...Pistol!
Ace!
A-Amazing!
He finished the demon
guard with a single blow!
He's quite a guy as I thought!
Straw-chan!
Okay, guys! The lid of the
pot of hell is off now!
Let's go!
Warden!
Can you just help me, Warden?!
Sadie-chan! What happened to you?!
Okama-kov... has beaten me!
It's humiliating! My life
is about dominating others!
Help her get down! I gotta run!
Oh, yes! Right away!
Are you Magellan?!
So you're Blackbeard?!
Yes, indeed!
Hydra!
I don't have time to ask
what brought you guys here!
Ouch! What is this?!
It should be poison! Dammit! That bastard!
Hannyabal!
I'm surprised that you held out this long!
Let me handle the rest!
Vice Warden!
You look horrible!
--Give him the treatment now!
--Yes, sir!
Vice Warden! Stay with me! Vice Warden!
You can't die! Because you're the only one...
...who can take my place!
Straw Hat! How did you survive
after I poisoned you?!
He's probably the one who
caused this situation!
I must take his life for sure this time!
Straw Hat!
Is that Magellan?!
That was from the bottom of the stairs!
Once he catches us, we're dead!
That poison bastard!
I will never let you get out of this prison!
Luffy and the others have finally reached level 3.
In order to hold off Magellan,
who continues to gain on them,
Ivan-san orders Inazuma to seal off
the stairway leading to level 2
and remains behind on level 3 alone
where he unleashes his secret technique,
New Kama Kempo, on Magellan!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Stop Magellan! Ivan-san's
Esoteric Technique Explodes!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!