Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
They are trying to break out!
He is pursuing his brother
who has been taken away!
And he is chasing them!
This unprecedented jailbreak
taking place in hell itself...
...continues to unfold under the sea!
Ace's public execution is in...
...4 and a half hours!
New Kama Kempo: 44--Aesthetic Technique!
Hair Removal Fist!
The 4 demon guards all
together after all this time!
B-B-B-B-Boss!
--S-S-Straw Hat?!
--T-That's the Warlord--Jimbei!
Hydra!
"Magellan's Tricky Move!
A Foiled Escape Plan!"
After that king of the pervs and his crony,
it's your turn now!
Magellan...
No way! Ivan-san and Inazuma got...
Crab-chan!
Ivan-chan!
Damn you!
No, Straw-chan!
Running is the only option
we have with Magellan!
Let me go, Bon-chan! I got to kick his butt!
Are you sure?!
--I understand--but you really want us to...
--Yes.
--Set it all up as I said quick!
--Yes, sir!
Alright! We have orders from Warden
Magellan! Get backup security to help us!
Yes, sir!
Dammit! So that's what he's planning?!
Don't forget that you
nearly died fighting him!
But I'm alive now!
Miracles don't come often, that's
why they are called miracles!
Both of you, let's get to the upper level!
Luffy-kun!
Get to the main entrance quickly!
It's not looking good!
We were paying
too much attention to Magellan!
Okay, I got it!
--We're gonna proceed with the plan now!
--Clank!
Everybody, get ready! Get to your positions!
Yes, sir!
Those of you with guns,
shoot to stop Magellan!
Dammit!
You better go now, Straw-chan!
That's not enough to stop him!
Oh no! He's coming!
Hurry up, Luffy-kun!
Hydra!
Heads up, everybody!
Candle Wall!
San!
He stopped Magellan's Hydra!
Your naiveness sickens me!
Don't think me letting my guard down
means I want to be your friend!
Stupid!
I just don't want to owe you any more favors!
I admire you even more, brother 3!
I see. You use wax!
That's right! I ate the Wax-Wax
Fruit and became the wax man!
This wall is as tough as iron!
It won't let your venom through!
That pile of garbage found his use.
You never know what powers may come in handy.
You better go now! I don't
intend to do this forever!
San!
How annoying!
Don't just stand there! It
won't hold out that long!
Okay, I'm gonna go!
Let's go, you guys!
--You've got quite a power!
--It works well if it's not the fiery floor!
Keep going, you guys! I wanna
follow right behind you!
Luffy-kun, we have to go now!
Didn't you say we need to steal a Navy ship?
Yes.
Then, why don't you go ahead with
everyone else? I'll try to stop him!
It'll be hard to steal it
with him chasing us anyway.
That's true but...
I have an idea!
Do you think it's gonna work?
Yeah! You can count on me!
Alright! But don't push it too far!
Okay, San! Let's fight him!
No no! I wasn't gonna fight! I
was doing it so we can run...
Brother 3! We aren't so
strong but let us help you!
Like I said, I wasn't gonna go that far...
Hey, can you do me a favor?
Listen to me!
Here comes Hydra again!
--Can you do that?
--Yes, that's possible.
--Okay, I'm counting on you!
--All right!
Wax-Wax Candle Armor!
Alright! With these on, I'm...
...so cool!
It's perfect!
Face forward! What're you
saying at a time like this?!
Don't know why... but tears
keep filling my eyes...
Thank you for making me this cool!
Shut up and just fight!
Straw Hat, I admire you
just for your tenacity!
What did you do to Ivan-chan?!
You're talking about Ivankov?
Of course, I executed him!
Don't worry! You will soon follow!
I-It's coming!
Hydra!
--San!
--All right!
Candle Wall!
It's not gonna work no matter
how many times you try!
Gum-Gum...
...Champion...
...Rifle!
Yes! I can touch him!
--We found cannons!
--With candle shields!
Yeah! We got him!
We can beat him!
Alright!
Listen! We gotta buy some time here!
Here they come! Shoot!
Don't hesitate! You guys, break away!
We're close! Keep going up!
--Almost there!
--We can get out!
It didn't work?!
Magellan is unbeatable! Let's go all the way!
What?!
There are no more formidable enemies here!
You're letting your guard
down. What are you an amateur?
What?!
There are at least 10 Navy ships out there.
And each one has 800 marines on board.
I don't know their configuration but...
...stealing a Navy ship means that we
will have to face the remaining ships.
Can you still be relaxed?
Y-You've got a point.
That's not the only problem we have!
There's no more guards here!
All that is left is this door!
Finally!
I've never forgotten the
entrance of Impel Down!
We all came through here
and entered into hell!
It's been how many years?
Are we really here?! I
still can't believe it!
I never thought that I'd break out like this.
Alright! Everybody, train your
weapons! Let's open the door!
Ready? Here we go!
I'm gonna get out finally!
You fool! This doesn't mean
that we've succeeded yet!
The Navy is waiting for us out there
and we don't know if we can make it!
You're right.
Now that you put
it that way I agree with you.
Yeah. But we can't stop
after coming this far.
We should just go as far as we can!
--It's sunlight!
--I'm free!
Everybody, get ready!
Even if thousands of marines
are waiting for us,
we're gonna break through
and go back to the sea!
Alright! Let's go, you guys!
Follow me!
What is going on here?!
There's no Navy ship at all!
Not even a single ship to steal!
Not even a single marine!
No way! Then...
...we can't do anything!
What should we do?!
All we can do is just wait for
Magellan to come and kill us here?!
Dammit! You gotta be kidding!
I see. They're not as stupid as I thought.
There are large Sea Kings in the water.
As is said, the Calm Belt is the
greatest barrier protecting Impel Down.
We barely made it this far
from the bottom of hell!
Damn! We'll be dragged back to hell!
We don't have time to complain!
They cleared out because Magellan
told them to do so--but not long ago!
Take a good look!
You can see shadows of
sails slightly in the fog!
Oh yeah, he's right!
But it's too far! We still can't reach them!
Yeah, it's too late for us to...
Don't worry!
You have me here! Let me handle this!
Holy cow!
How strong!
He's carrying the gigantic door by himself?!
I can't carry that many
but let's sail out with this
to take one of those ships!
Those of you who are determined, get on!
Is it possible to steal a ship with that?
C-Crocodile!
That's it? Alright then...
Wait a minute!
Aren't you forgetting about me?
I know you need me so I'm coming with you!
--You have a lot of guts!
--That's our Captain Buggy!
Take this Baby Transponder
Snail I found just in case!
Hey, can we just go now?
Alright! Let's do it!
You all ready? We got to hurry!
He's swimming with that
heavy door on his back!
Only the captain of the Fish-Man
Pirates could do that!
I can't wait to see how
the Warlord's gonna fight!
And our savior Captain Buggy is with him!
It's looking hopeful!
How stupid they are! It's much
safer to be with a Warlord...
...rather than staying there and
being scared of Magellan, fools!
They're shooting at us!
They found us.
He avoided it! He's so fast!
He's not just a Fish-Man! He's the
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei!
All forces! Open fire!
If we can sink Jimbei, they are finished!
There they are! Crowds of Navy ships!
I'm going to launch you
onto the deck! Hold tight!
Huh? W-What?! What did
you just say, fish face?!
Oh? That bastard's gone!
Ugh! What's going on here?!
I know! He left us here
and got away by himself!
Traitor, traitor, traitor...
Why did you come with us?
Jimbei! Where's that bastard gone?!
We're gonna get hit!
Can't you just be quiet?
Fish-Man Jiu-Jitsu!
Water Heart!
It's coming towards us!
Ocean Current...
...Shoulder Throw!
We're flying!
What's that water column?!
It looks like a living thing!
Do you have any idea of what it is?
No, I don't.
But I can see people on it! One is Crocodile!
It's coming!
They're trying to hijack the
ship! Stop them at any cost!
We can just throw those Devil
Fruit eaters off into the water!
You didn't learn anything
after I beat you so soundly?!
I forgot it all!
Gum-Gum...
...Champion...
...Bazooka!
Then this time, I'll make sure
that you'll never forget...
...by burying you with it!
To buy Jimbei the timed needed to steal a ship,
Luffy makes a stand against Magellan.
Magellan, now at bay,
unleashes his strongest technique, capable of destroying Impel Down itself.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Escapee Team in Trouble! The
Forbidden Move: Venom Demon!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!