Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
You raised your price again?!
Don't you think your
place charges a bit much?!
Raise it again and I'll stop buying it!
What's the big deal?
It's just a paper or two.
Not when you're buying it everyday!
There's no need for
you to save up money
to buy your village back
from Arlong now, you know.
Or to be so obsessive about money.
You're so dumb!
Now that everything's over,
I'm going to earn money for me now!
I don't wanna be some poor
pirate who can't even dress up!
Whoa, calm down!
I'm in the middle of developing
my special Tabasco Star!
An eyeful of this
will make any bad guy--
--C'mon! Just one!
--Water! Water! Water!
No!
This is Nami-san's tangerine orchard!
I won't let anyone lay a finger on it!
Nami-san! Your love
security is infallible!
Yeah. Thanks, Sanji-kun.
Ol' Sanji's letting himself be used...
C'mon! Just one tangerine!
You're such a cheapskate, Sanji!
No!
Well, oh, well! I'm happy now, anyways!
The world sure is a turbulent place.
Another coup in Villa...
A flyer?
"Bounty! Straw Hat Luffy
Becomes Known to the World"
"Navy"
So, at the very least, they're now
too much for our branches to handle?
Yes. Even before
forming his pirate group,
he defeated Navy Branch
Captain Axe-Hand Morgan,
and he's showed no signs
of slowing down since.
Buggy the Clown, 15 million.
Pirate Fleet Commodore,
Don Krieg. 17 million.
Fishman Pirate,
Saw-Tooth Arlong. 20 million.
These major pirates have all crossed
the big 10 million Berry mark
in the East Blue, where the average
bounty is 3 million Berries...
...but they've all been taken down.
30 million Berries as a starting
bounty is globally unprecedented,
but it is not an
excessively high amount.
It may be best to nip such
seeds of villainy early on,
before they have a
chance to get out of hand.
Absolutely.
Everyone who wants
to run away, do so now!
This bastion of peace will not tolerate
any weakness in this pirate age!
The public's weakness and feebleness
is not a sin! We have justice!
If there is tenacious evil on the seas,
then we, the Navy, must drive
it away with utmost force!
In the name of absolute justice!
"Justice"
Yes, sir!
Miss!
Miss Kaya!
What's wrong, Merry?!
Have a look at this!
Usopp-san!
That's definitely Usopp-san
facing the other way!
Now that you
mention it, you're right...
Heya! You're looking
a lot better, Kaya!
What sort of story
shall I tell you today?
Usopp-san is moving toward his dreams!
I'm moving toward my dream of being
a doctor to help everyone, too!
I'm sure that someday, somewhere,
my dream and Usopp-san's
dream will come together!
"Chore Boy"
Finally... Finally... Finally!
Luffy-san! You've finally
set foot into your dream!
I'm Luffy! The man who's
gonna be King of the Pirates!
See ya!
But the next time we meet,
we may be enemies!
Captain!
I'm the one who's gonna
be King of the Pirates!
We both have foolish dreams.
I'm doing it so I can
achieve my own goal.
Say... do you know the All Blue?
Thank you for all the damn things
you've done for me all these years!
We're wanted criminals now!
"Dead or alive"...
"30 million Berries"...?!
It says I'm 30 million Berries!
Look! I'm gonna be seen around
the world! Girls might fall for me!
What?! They put Long-nose
in but left me out?!
Where are you?!
I don't see you anywhere!
See!
It's just the back of your head.
That's nothing to brag about.
Don't be so glum!
You can get on these without being
captain if you get more important!
Seriously?!
Just keep on tryin' hard!
Let's rush into the Grand Line, men!
Yet again, you guys don't understand
the seriousness of the situation!
This means our lives are in danger now!
This is no time to be taking it easy
and relaxing in the East Blue...
30 million Berries...
At that amount, I bet
Headquarters will take action,
and strong bounty hunters
won't leave us alone...
They're gonna be on a completely
different level than everyone so far!
Let's go! Let's go! Grand Line!
Damn... Cheap booze
makes me feel sick...
How I long for the old days
when I was surrounded by
beautiful women and fine wine...
My one encounter with that
horrible waiter changed my fate...
Tarnishing the Navy's name lost
me my rank of Navy HQ Lieutenant
and put me in charge of this hunk
of junk in the middle of nowhere...
Former Lieutenant Fullbody!
Whadya want?! You're annoying!
I-I have a new wanted poster!
Oh. Just leave it there.
I doubt it means anything to us,
seeing as we're all the way out--
This face... I've seen it
somewhere before...
I've never seen that pirate flag before.
I'm Iron Fist Fullbody,
Lieutenant at Navy Headquarters!
Who's your captain?! State your name!
I'm Luffy!
I'm Usopp!
We just made our pirate flag
the day before yesterday!
Yes! It's him!
Thank you!
God has given me a chance to climb
out of this hellish pit of boredom!
I can catch that brat easily!
And I'll use that feat to get my
rank of Navy HQ Lieutenant back!
Fall in!
Men! We're going into battle!
Battle? Where are we gonna do that?
W-Well... The sea restaurant, I suppose?
--Oh! A restaurant!
--Awesome! A big feast!
--It's the captain's treat!
--Oh, really?!
--No, you got it all wrong!
--Hurray! Hurray!
That was...
Hard to port! Our target's
right in front of us!
Do you think some pirates
attacked it? That warship is scrapped...
It's not nice of the Navy to toss
its scrapped ships into the ocean...
This is not a scrapped ship!
Do you guys got knotholes for eyes?!
Have you forgotten what
Iron Fist Fullbody looks like?!
Oh! You're that navy
guy from sometime!
Are you stranded? Want us to help you?
Quit fooling around! Our meeting
here spells the end of your luck!
Monkey D. Luffy! You're under arrest!
Yeah! That's a good
picture of me, huh?!
And of the back of my head!
It says, "Dead or alive"...
Aim the turret!
What's all the noise? What's going on?
Oh? You're gonna shoot?
They're aiming right at us! This is bad!
Alright! Leave it to me!
I'll bounce it back again!
Luffy. Let me handle this one.
--Yeah, yeah! You stay back here!
--H-How come?
'Cause you mess things up.
C'mon! Over here!
Tremble and sleep!
Awesome!
That's impossible!
Huh? What's all this damn noise?
Don't bother people
when they're napping.
There's plenty more
where that came from! Fire!
--Huh? This is bad.
--It is?!
See? There were cracks in the cannon.
Yeah, that's definitely bad.
You damn brats!
Don't you dare mock the power
of a former Navy HQ Lieutenant!
We'll just have to
fight you hand-to-hand!
Men! Follow me!
Your head is mine!
Gum-Gum...
...Bell!
You got some real balls, pickin'
a fight during mealtime, tough guy.
Don't got any soup bowls today.
You plannin' to lick
the deck or somethin'?
W-What's that waiter doing here?!
Huh? He's done already?
He was nothing but talk!
He's as damn wimpy as ever.
C'mon, you guys! Keep it down!
Honestly! I can't even relax
and read a newspaper here!
Nami-san! I'm finished
preparing your meal!
Ooh! I'm starving!
Let's eat! Food! Food!
What's that?
Lemme see.
Hawk-Eye! Why the hell are you here?!
Calm down. I have no business with you.
Where is your leader?
Camping on an island like this...
What a carefree man.
B-B-Boss!
H-H-Hawk-Eye!
Hey there, Hawk-Eye.
What a rare visitor...
I'm not feelin' so good at the moment...
Have you come to fight me?
I don't have any intention
of settling things with you
now that you've lost your left arm.
I found an interesting pirate,
and was suddenly reminded
of a story you used to tell.
A story about an interesting boy
from a certain small village...
You don't mean...!
So you've made it, Luffy!
In that case, Hawk-Eye...
...I can't just let you leave now.
That so, Hawk-Eye?!
Okay! Drink up! Drink up!
Today's a celebration!
I thought you had a hangover?
Don't sweat it!
It's a celebratory drink!
C'mon, now! C'mon, now!
Just drink it straight down!
I like ya!
Let's drink! Let's drink!
Yeah!
But, wait! Boss! You said you felt
sick 'cause you drank too much!
You idiot! I can't not drink
on a joyous day like today!
The sun is still high.
Don't sweat it!
Let's party hard!
Hey! Luffy's a wanted man now!
Good for him!
Who knows, maybe a great pirate
will've come from this village!
That'd be great!
Quiet, you fools!
Mayor!
What's so good about a criminal
coming from our village?!
A toast!
Honestly! Every last one of them...!
Look, Mayor! Luffy looks so happy!
A pirate's a pirate!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
But it is his dream. Are you worried?
Dreams... Fate...
We're finally nearing the Grand Line...
It looks like the only way into it
is through Reverse Mountain here.
What a pain.
Can't we just sail straight into it?
Nope.
From what the geezer told me,
that's the only way boats can enter.
How come?
'Cause it's supposedly dangerous.
But how come?!
I don't know any more than that!
The reason for that is...
Alright! I got it!
Then let's head straight into it!
Are you even paying attention?!
But it sounds fun!
Plus it'd feel way better
going straight into it!
Talking to you makes me
feel like I'm gonna go crazy...
Anyways, let's stop at
an island first and get meat!
Meat! Meat!
There's a famous city on
this island... Loguetown.
Loguetown?
What? Is it famous for its meat?
Also known as the city
of the beginning and the end...
I'm pretty sure I've heard that before.
It's the town where Gold Roger,
the old King of the Pirates,
was born... and executed.
The town where the
King of the Pirates died...
Wanna go?
Yeah! I wanna see it!
I wanna see the town where
the man who got the One Piece--
everything this world has to offer--
was born and then died!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Hey! What's that
red-nosed thing called again?
A reindeer?
--No, that guy with the big nose!
--Oh, him.
His name was Boogey or Baggy
the Brown or something like that!
No! Buggy the Clown! Buggy!
Yeah! That!
I wonder what
happened to him after that...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Chase Straw Hat!
Little Buggy's Big Adventure"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!