Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy is trying to break free
in order to go after Ace
Luffy has broken out of the
great prison Impel Down
Luffy has made it aboard a Navy ship
in order to rescue his brother, Ace,
Luffy is headed to the Navy Headquarters...
Luffy has broken out of the
great prison - Impel Down
but Warden Magellan is in his way!
...with Ivankov, Jimbei,
Buggy, Crocodile and others,
and is headed to the Navy Headquarters
in order to rescue his brother, Ace!
in order to rescue his brother, Ace!--
who has been taken to the Navy HQ!
in order to rescue his brother,
Ace who is about to be executed!
There is nothing but despair ahead for you!
No! I know that you guys know about the
war between Whitebeard and the Navy!
Into the water?! Go ahead
and dive if you want!
Meanwhile, the rest of the Straw Hats...
You can't get away no
matter how you struggle!
There are Sea Kings' nests everywhere!
Meanwhile, the rest of the Straw Hats are...
...who had been ejected from the Sabaody
Archipelago by Bartholomew Kuma are...
Can't you see that it's no
use? For pirates like you...
--What'd you say?
--The Navy HQ?
Is this the fighting costume...
Hell's Judgement!
We passed through the Gate of Justice.
...The Gate of Justice won't open!
...that you were talking about?!
That means our destination must be
either the Navy HQ or Enies Lobby.
Gum-Gum...
"The Friends' Whereabouts! A Cheeper
of Giant Birds and a Pink Showdown!"
Cute!
Are you sure about opening the gate?
...Giant Stamp!
The Tub Current that we're on
is exclusive to the Government.
Quit it! Shut up!
Warden Magellan!
How odd! Why can't I land a single blow?!
It's a giant whirlpool that connects
the Government's 3 major facilities
Bon-chan is...
I see.
That's because you have doubt in your heart!
It's me!
We didn't know about this!
Sounds like the Navy HQ is harder
to break into than Impel Down.
That can't be it!
Buggy! Buggy!
Bon-chan!　Bon-chan!
Be quiet, you flashy fools!
Hell...
They are expecting a fight
with good old Whitebeard now.
Are you sure?!
...Wink!
What?!
You guys are all full of whim and fancy!
Bon-chan, the gate's closing.
"Dear Nami-san, Robin-chan,
how are you both doing?"
If you guys are real men, why don't
you live out a dream with me?!
I won't allow!
We...
So the place must be filled with
the most formidable forces...
...have to go.
Today...
"I'm looking forward to seeing you two!"
...that you can think of in the world today!
I'll beat Whitebeard which means
that I'll conquer the world!
Thank you!
"When the time comes, I'm sure
that we'll become good friends!"
--The gate is closing!
--We gotta sink them!
We want to avoid an all-out war but
I don't think that it's possible.
Do you wanna say something before you die?!
There it is! Right there!
--I will follow you!
--I don't want a peaceful life!
This is what I wanted!
What's this?!
Luffy has broken out of the world's
greatest prison Impel Down!
Damn! We're on a cliff!
You made it!
That's right!
I'm sorry that I should ask you
to come to this dangerous area!
Let's go, guys! To Navy Headquarters!
Meanwhile, a short time ago...
But the end is nowhere in sight...
Are you guys here to save us?!
...at Peachy Island in the Grand Line -
GRAND LINE
Looks like it's over.
Kamabakka Kingdom...
--It's a school of whale sharks!
--Jimbei must have called them!
I hope they are having fun.
I didn't know that she was her baby!
"To the Navy Headquarters!
Off to Rescue Ace!"
Cool!
I'm sick of this place!
"The Friends' Whereabouts! The Weatheria
Report and the Cyborg Animals!"
"Come, Final Miracle! Break
Through the Gate of Justice!"
"The Friends' Whereabouts! Revolutionaries
and the Gorging Forest's Trap!"
Dammit! All the queers on this island are...
Why do you want to live so dangerously?
If I hadn't come here with an antidote,
You are one of us, aren't you?!
LEVEL 4 BURNING HEAT HELL
you guys would be dead.
Wait!
EAST BLUE TEQUILA WOLF
You can't underestimate Magellan.
Carry them here!
But we're alive!
Dammit!
Stay away from me!
The fact that you came down
here is a part of our fate.
MAXIMUM SECURITY PRISON TOWER
How do you like the Sea Prism Stone armlet?
But you're right! I thought
I was going to die!
What?!
That guy's so cool!
We are...
Those queers...
It just goes to show there are men...
...lucky.
Why are they so strong?!
...who don't have any taste
when it comes to presents.
They are...
...not ordinary queers!
Out with it! Where are the Straw Hats now?!
Whether you die or not--it's up to God!
If you're trying to seduce me,
you need to create a better mood.
Those who harbor fear will lose!
--Cool!
--Heehaw!
You bitch!
We just need to live in the moment!
Nico Robin...
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
Don't we, Shiryu?!
We didn't want that troublemaker here!
When can I see them again?!
I heard that she sank
6 ships when she was only 8.
And I don't think somebody like
her could adjust well to prison.
Yo-ho!
I know that you are worried about Ace-san
I'm grateful for your
help! You have my thanks!
And if she broke out, she'd
turn this country on its side!
but you need to take some rest.
And again, welcome to our gang! I think
that we're gonna make a great team!
I have to make sure that no one
outside knows who she is...
My future here is predictable.
I see.
There've been some candies
I've been waiting to meet someone like you.
Yeah! We made it to the Navy ship!
May I come in?
The war that we are about to get involved in
is literally the decisive battle of our times!
who have had trouble
accepting themselves after coming to this island.
What's the matter?
It's about the construction delays...
We broke out!
It's about time for us to put
out a helping hand to him!
Double the work hours of the laborers!
I can't believe that we
escaped from Impel Down!
Just as Impel Down is the
greatest prison in the world,
One meal a day is enough for them!
But they say that there are people
who are opposed to the construction.
It's not time to celebrate yet!
We have to get going!
By the way, is he strong?
THE SHIP ROUTES OF THE WORLD
GOVERNMENT TUB CURRENT
the Navy Headquarters is the
greatest fortress in the world!
Not that much--but his kicks aren't too bad!
We shouldn't be too strict.
All right, everyone!
Then, let's use the traditional
method of Kamabakka Kingdom...
There aren't that many of them
and they can't do anything.
Let's toast to our unprecedented
unheard-of breakout of Impel Down!
Yeah!
Thank you, whale sharks!
The only threat we have is Nico Ro...
...for first time in a long while!
--Cheers!
I appreciate it!
Well, anyway...
--See you!
--Thank you so much!
You need to see the laborers as expendable!
Get home safely!
You guys are so persistent! Why?!
Hey, don't stop! Pull harder!
Why are you...
I'll start treating Inazuma.
...chasing me?!
Bring all the medicines
from the clinic!
Wait!
Oh, that's good!
Alright!
Why should I?! Stupid!
Meanwhile, a short time ago at
the small Sky Island - Weatheria,
I'm never going back into that hell again!
We'll have to do it without
Inazuma from here.
Me, neither! I'm gonna reform my
ways and go back to my family!
home to scientists who study the weather.
What?! The infection is really that bad?!
Hurry up! We're hungry!
We're free now!
I was infected with just
one kind of poison and...
Thanks to who?
...got it out of my system using my
Healing Hormone and Energy Hormone.
What's this building?!
But before that...
Say it!
Captain Buggy!
What's wrong with them?!
Heehaw!
I can't believe that they made it that far.
Old man! Are you okay?!
But it's complicated because...
Is this the Navy? Bring me a ship!
...one will take years off my life but
the other causes severe side effects!
Why are you goofing around?!
He's dying! Just leave him!
I'll ride it and bring them down myself!
It's better if he can rest
and recover naturally.
Yes, sir!
What are you looking at?!
They don't realize that after
all they are still trapped.
W-What're you guys doing?
Hey, hey, hey, young girl!
Nothing can help you to regain
years lost by using the hormone!
H-Hey!
There is nothing but despair ahead for you!
Damn!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey! Hey, young girl!
I've been waiting for you!
Inazuma is an indispensable New
Kama of the revolutionary army!
You fools, don't leave your posts!
You can't get away no
matter how you struggle!
If you don't wanna work, I can
send you to the prison tower!
We shouldn't allow him
to push himself too hard!
Hey! Hey!
Rear Admiral! We fixed the battery
that was damaged by Jimbei!
Alright! What do you want?!
The prison tower?
H-Hey, what's this?!
W-W-Who are you, you bastard?!
Good.
All ships, open fire!
That lady...
It's so rude to call her
"bastard!" Call her Caro-sama!
Do you like the taste of my cloud
candy? I've been working on it.
When I think about it, he
wasn't a bad guy after all.
It was so hard to make it
taste like cotton candy.
It's seawater just like you like!
Taste it to your heart's content!
Are you queen of this country?
I was looking forward to seeing him again...
What do you think?
Queen?! Please!
But once more, he rushed to our aid!
It's lukewarm.
Buggy!
If we hand you over to a Navy
ship, it'll bring us a fortune!
To be exact,
Are you trying to kill me?!
Bon-chan!
I'm the queen...
Even if you're dead!
--Brother Bon!
--Bon-chan!
Wait a minute, young girl! Violence won't do!
...stand-in!
Bon-chan!
Caroline!
Range correction!
What crude pleasure!
Honestly!
SUB
Bitch!
Oh boy, the potato skin soup again?
Oh, it's sweet! It does
taste like cotton candy!
Caro-sama!
We can't get any energy out of this!
That's what I thought!
A stand-in?!
You're cooperative. Have a chocolate, too.
Hey, how long are you gonna
mourn like that, guys?!
Hm... So I guess that this island
is really full of wonder!
Kamabakka Kingdom is ruled
by the legendary queen -
Thank you, mister!
They started firing!
Humph! Informant!
He was great but he's dead
and nothing can't change it!
Ivan-sama!
--This is no good!
--How many ships are there?!
It'd be presumptuous of
me to call myself queen!
I did it to survive! You're not getting any!
Let's just party!
Oh, by the way, are you sure that we're
heading to the Sabaody Archipelago?!
I don't care if you're a sub or
not, let me get this straight now!
The fleet is coming after us!
It's a breakout party!
Old lady!
You can't have this!
Leave her alone!
They got us!
Yes, I'm doing it for you as a special favor!
Oh yeah, let's celebrate it
as a funeral for Mr. 2...
The lady that you took the trouble to save...
I'm sick of this island!
Get me out of this place!
Even though everybody ranked higher than
Vice Admiral has been summoned to Marineford,
But it's been a while since I asked you.
...was sent to the tower
because she snitched!
the Navy ships are still
formidable without them!
--Alright, I got it!
--Huh?
I knew I'd fall into the red!
When are we gonna get there?
That young lady gave herself
up in order to save us.
However, you need to fight the
strongest one of us and win!
We don't know if Bon-chan's
dead yet, you, big nose!
What do you mean?
She's a strong woman. She'll
forgive the old lady!
Huh?
What did you just say?!
How's that sound?
Wasn't I clear enough?!
Can't you see that it's no
use? For pirates like you...
It's a deal! I'll take it!
Weatheria travels on the wind.
Your nose is red, round and stupid!
...The Gate of Justice won't open!
If a
typhoon comes, it's gonna be really fast.
Well, your face is rubbery,
stretchy and stupid!
Why are you here?!
Okay!
How far did we get yesterday?
This is mine!
Then you need to change into our
traditional fighting costume!
What'd you say?!
Probably about 200 meters.
I couldn't care less about them...
W-What?! Fighting... costume?
Oh no! I forgot about this!
I-I wanted to get out of here!
I don't feel sorry at all!
Oh my God! We can't open it!
Honestly, if this weren't a Sky
Island, I would've left already!
I thought that talking to fish was
the special ability of Mermaids only.
Damn! It's a dead end after coming this far!
Uh-huh.
But we're still too far away from the
Sabaody if you were to go down on the ground now.
You're talking like me!
--What're we gonna do, you shark?!
--Sail through it!
If you stay here, we'll get there someday.
But you can call out to sharks, too.
That's impossible! This is a disaster!
Look, I don't have that much time to spare.
Is it so weird for a Fish-Man
to be a friend of fish?
You can have this.
How can you be so relaxed?!
Is this the fighting costume...
Thank you!
Well, I can say that it's not normal.
Old lady, you're kind!
Then, shall we go down?
Say something!
...that you were talking about?!
I guess that you're a misfit...
I'm running out of research funds anyway.
Cute!
...of the violent species.
Huh?
Quit it! Shut up!
I take it as a compliment.
I'm sorry! But I couldn't help it!
What do you mean "go down?"
I can't stand this much longer!
I mean, on the ground.
I can't deny the fact that
Fish-Men are violent.
I'll finish this with a
single blow in a jiffy!
We're all helpless!
Is that possible?!
Protect the ship first! That's our priority!
Bon-chan's not dead!
We have to stay here and suffer
for the rest of our lives!
And I'll finally leave this stupid island!
Oh! Captain Buggy grew another red nose!
You know, it takes a lot of
money to do this research.
Why are we just taking their
fire?! This is a Navy ship, too!
I haven't say "thank you" to that lady.
Gorgeous!
So I go down from time to time to do some
business with my knowledge of the weather.
--Fire back, you dumb-asses!
--That was my idea!
Luffy-kun.
I want to give this chocolate to her.
What?!
You gave me an opportunity to save Ace-san.
We have to fire back, guys!
I'm gonna fight you?!
What is this?!
What are you doing?! Get back to work!
I'm the stand-in queen of Kamabakka Kingdom
We see, Captain Buggy!
I owe you a great debt.
Here's your meal!
Don't think of it in terms like
that. There'd be no end to it!
and at the same time, the grand master
of Kamabakka style--New Kama Kempo!
Finish it then we'll start questioning again!
Can't wait.
For me, it's just encouraging to
have you along! You're so strong!
--...Stand-in!
--Are you standing in for everything?!
Sables!
I want to thank you and apologize
to you for the other case before this.
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Sounds like you have been
hurt bad, young girl.
How's that?!
Fire!
But, not today. There is
something more important now.
Who are you?
Young girl!
Alright! Let's just do this!
I'm just an old man. I was
sent to this country today
It's this way!
I'll show you my technique!
A ship?!
You can call me Jimbei!
but they said that the elderly
are useless and put me in here.
I don't intend to give you a chance!
I'm a Warlord but I'm sure
they'll revoke my title!
Wow, this ship... floats in the sky?!
Because I'm gonna finish
you with this attack!
I'm sorry about that.
I...
So let's run wild at the Navy Headquarters!
No!
Concasse!
We have to live up to the expectations of...
It's impossible for us to outrun them!
...that Queer-kun and rescue
Ace-san at any cost!
It's over!
--A Warlord?
--The Navy Headquarters?
Dammit! If nothing is done, the
Navy will get us eventually!
Let's go!
Where is he?
What?!
I'm here, candy-chan!
Damn prisoners!
Hey you! You're a Warlord?!
Why are they still heading to the
gate knowing that they're cornered?
No wonder you're so strong!
The gate can only be controlled
from inside of Impel Down.
I have no time to waste!
Sorry that I hadn't introduced myself yet!
There is no other way to open it!
Everyone else knows that.
That's just the island
that I was looking for!
I've got to get out of here!
Damn you!
Hey! What's that about
the Navy Headquarters?!
Even it means that I have to cut my arms off!
Keep firing! Sink them...
Don't tell me that we're heading
to the Navy Headquarters!
How odd! Why can't I land a single blow?!
Young girl, don't feel so pressed!
And what's up with his eyes?
--Yes, we are!
--No!
This island is...
The Gate of Justice is opening!
And that weird movement?
Listen carefully.
I know that you guys know about the
war between Whitebeard and the Navy!
Why?! What's going on?! Why
are they opening the gate?!
Augh! Don't tell me that he's...
Don't you hear something?!
...terrible!
--What'd you say?
--The Navy HQ?
You look good!
Did you say that you can save this island?!
It's obvious. It's your faults
for being so clueless.
Hey, hey, don't look at it!
It's open!
Yes.
What?!
It seems like you people are
in need of blessed rain.
We passed through the Gate of Justice.
W-Why is this happening?
That means our destination must be
either the Navy HQ or Enies Lobby.
Is this a trap?!
I can make it rain with my
knowledge of the weather!
I mean, why should I be embarrassed
by showing my underwear?!
Yes! I don't know why
but the gate is opening!
The Tub Current that we're on
is exclusive to the Government.
What did you just say?!
It's a giant whirlpool that connects
the Government's 3 major facilities
That's your maiden-like modesty
that you can't disguise!
It's open! It's open!
I can do this now for a special price...
We wanted to break out because
we have a role in the war.
Shut up! That's so stupid! I'm a man!
...of 100 million berries!
What?!
I don't care if you see my underwear!
100 million?!
Oh no!
Warden Magellan! Please hurry!
Yeah! The real fight is on its way!
Your kicks are lower than before!
I'm afraid we don't have that much money.
No! Wait!
"The real fight is on its way?!"
You're embarrassed as I thought!
W-We didn't know about this!
Is it too much?!
See?
That's way too much!
No one can afford that!
--Stop the ship right now, you bastard!
--Stop!
What's the matter?
Don't measure it!
No way!
What's that?!
Why is the gate opening?!
That's because you have doubt in your heart!
We can't stop because we are on the current!
Well...
That can't be it!
--Then, 100 berries!
--Huh?!
Dissidents are running wild!
Why don't you guys get off?!
Are you sure about opening the gate?
What a deal!
--Okay, bye!
--Yeah, bye!
Are you sure?!
N-No, don't!
The warden ordered all of
us to go and break it up!
No, we can't!
Warden Magellan!
You came down too much! You
have no sense for business!
Devil Fruit eaters
like us will definitely be killed!
I'm sure! Have I ever been wrong?!
It looks like you're deceiving
yourself just as I thought!
Relax!
The Navy HQ and The Seven Warlords
versus the Whitebeard Pirates?!
No, it's not like I don't believe you!
That aside, can you really do it?
Weren't you being too optimistic?
What?!
After the prisoners' ship passes through,
Be true to yourself!
That's more horrifying than hell!
Believe in my knowledge of
the weather! Okay, ready?
close the gate right away, understood?
Lady!
I got it, sir!
So, why did you stop kicking?!
Lady, where are you?
Do you want me to attack you now?
New Kama Kempo Technique:
Awakening of the Inner Maiden!
Don't let them get away!
They aren't allowed to! Fire!
--Lady!
--Soran!
Those are..
Lady! I just wanted to thank you...
...soap bubbles!
Is it Magellan's order?!
What is he thinking?!
What are you doing there?!
There's something inside.
Why is he doing this?!
What happened to Warden?!
I wanna go back to the prison
rather than entering this war!
Dissidents?
Yes, but as you ordered,
Young girl, could you generate
some wind with this?!
Yes, um, but it doesn't
look like his will to me!
all teams went to break it up
so it didn't become serious!
Why? Why? It's just my underwear! But yet...
Us from the Kama Land knew it.
Oh, this is...
Why didn't you tell us then?!
He was at the pier near the
main entrance just while ago!
I didn't give that order.
...it's so embarrassing!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Do you want it full power?!
Whoa! No!
Yes!
Don't tell me that you even sent the
security soldiers stationed at the tower!
We can't escape death this time!
Huh? Did I just scream like a girl?
Why is this? What's happening here?!
Mom!
N-No way!
Lady!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Soran! How did you get here?
Control room! What are you doing?!
But what is this feeling?!
Who told you to open the gate?!
I don't understand!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
W-Warden!
I'm...
I'm an agent of the revolutionary army!
Hey, do you hear something?
I'm...
Are you alright? The diversion went well!
Oh no!
...about lose myself...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
...myself...
...and become somebody else!
Good job!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
With your command, we can win!
Yeah, you can count on me!
Is that true?
Oh my god! I can't believe this!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Oh yeah!
Bon-chan is...
While you're at it, free
that young girl, too.
--It's a Transponder Snail!
--Who's calling?
You bastard!
Hey lady, you're in luck!
"Dear Nami-san, Robin-chan,
how are you both doing?"
That's right!
Don't you get it? This is a Navy ship!
Thanks.
It's me!
You fool! I don't care about the dissidents!
"I'm looking forward to seeing you two!"
I got you again!
Look out for Nico Robin!
He's an imposter!
This doesn't fit, either.
"When the time comes, I'm sure
that we'll become good friends!"
Warden, I just heard from the lookout!
Young girl, it's gonna be messy for awhile.
The stolen ship will pass the gate soon!
--It's raining!
--Yeah!
Why don't you hide somewhere safe?
--Even if they get through the gate...
--Spin, spin!
I don't want you to slow us down.
--they can't outrun that many ships!
--Spin, spin!
--It's impossible!
What?!
Then, close the gate now! Push the button!
Oh no!
Nico Robin! Shoot her to death!
W-What?!
We did it!
Oh, yes, sir! Um...
This is Birdie Kingdom in the South Blue
No, don't push it!
Okay!
SOUTH BLUE "BIRDIE KINGDOM"
They're so pleased!
--No, push it!
--Don't push it!
where birds reign supreme.
Yeah! Now, don't you think the
science of weather is useful?
--Push it!
--Don't!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
--Push it!
--Don't!
Clutch!
--Push it!
--Don't!
Okay. So I guess this is
goodbye, right? Young girl.
--Push it now!
--Yes, sir!
Memoirs of a Desert Kingdom!
I already asked the mayor
I really wanna get off this island.
You are Nico Robin?!
so he'll provide
you with what you need for your journey.
This place is the worst.
Heehaw! I win!
--I'm not going!
--What?
Why don't we just pretend we're not here?
Y-You bastard!
I'll stay with you.
I owe the people here!
Birds treating me like a toy.
I've become interested
in the science of weather a bit.
I'm not gonna let you go after Straw-chan!
--Clank!
--Hello?
And humans trying to eat me in a hot pot.
I have to pay them back!
Really?
The woman in the tower has broken
out and is coming after us!
He picked up!
Can you teach me about it on our
way to the Sabaody Archipelago?
This is the Navy HQ.
Help me!
And the birds and the humans are...
Oh, this is Luffy.
--W-Warden!
--Robin... Robin is coming!
Don't give your name like that!
Of course!
We know that the ship has
been taken by escapees.
It's over! Everything's over!
You sure? Thank you!
...always fighting.
Nico Robin!
Anyone who loves the weather is welcomed!
We received a report from the
Fleet Escort Force at Impel Down.
You have a nice name!
We determined who the two main suspects
of this great escape case were...
What should I do?
Is this from before? This is perfect!
...from the insider information
before contact was lost.
Let me tell you about this soap
bubble with the thundercloud inside.
Look! The gate is closing!
Here, I got you something to eat!
Two?
Yes! If we can get through it,
the Navy will be stopped by it!
A pirate--Straw Hat Luffy!
Oh no, this is not good!
And another pirate Buggy the Clown!
I was with him at the entrance a while ago!
Huh?
He stayed alone at Impel Down?!
How are your legs?
-- What?!
-- W-What?!
Did they get any better? Let me see.
No way!
Captain Buggy is the main suspect
although there're Warlords here?!
We made it this far at
last! We're almost there!
Stay still!
You...
Who the hell are you?!
What're you doing?!
Oh! They look okay now!
Why me?!
S-S-Science exacts a price!
Because of Bon-chan, we met Ivan-chan
and broke out successfully!
--Let me see the documents.
--Here you go.
Here, go ahead and eat these.
Am I the price?!
Help... Help me!
We thought that you were
just a nameless pirate.
And we're gonna go on without him?!
We don't have time!
You were lucky.
Buggy the Clown, I can't believe that...
Are we gonna leave him there?!
I was just searching for various
kinds of herbs at the time...
...you were a crew member under
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
We already left hundreds
of friends who were beaten!
Luffy-kun, you need to rest if only a little.
How'd you know that?
Do you want to go back and fight Magellan?!
Yeah. Thank you.
What?!
--"The ship" - that means Oro Jackson?!
--He's kick-ass!
And lose more friends and time?!
But I'm okay.
This is for stomach trouble.
He's a star! A star among pirates!
Meanwhile, on the Mechanical Island -
To be able to open this gate, we
needed somebody to stay there!
Future Land Baldimore, the
birthplace of the Genius.
We also know that you're a sworn
brother of "Red-Haired" Shanks,
The wind has died down.
What was that?!
Even though we are moving
forward with the current,
one of the Four Emperors.
I can do it better than anyone! I'm
gonna open the Gate of Justice!
The humans are after me again?!
What?!
we may not arrive in time.
How could someone like this
have laid low until now...
Oh no! They're gonna eat me in a hot pot!
...without raising any alarms.
Luffy-kun!
What are you gonna do after that?!
But now, you've made yourself known.
What a pointless question!
No. I should not give him needless anxiety.
Well...
We can't see clearly your
connection with "Fire Fist" Ace
A cheeper of the birds?
When we get to Navy Headquarters, he will
get involved in an unimaginable war!
Don't tell Straw-chan until
communications are cut off!
It makes me super relaxed!
but we're sure that your goal is
the same as Straw Hat Ace's rescue!
Oh no!
Us queers...
He was way funnier before!
...we don't say goodbye!
She must have fallen out of the nest.
Well... I don't really...
We know that you have
Jimbei, Crocodile, Ivankov,
Oh! What do you think we can
do to turn Franky back?!
I don't understand what she's
saying since she's a baby
It's still connected.
and more than 200 ruffians who
are also escapees on board.
The cola hasn't arrived yet so
we can't conduct an operation.
but sounds like she's been hurt.
A Baby Transponder Snail's
coverage is limited.
I warn you.
You are injured!
Ace!
It won't work after the gate closes.
He has to take back his perversion...
As long as we don't open the Gate of
Justice, you guys can't get to Marineford
No wonder! She fell from such a height!
I mean, wildness, in order to
get back to being himself again.
GRAND LINE BOWIN ISLANDS
Don't move! Stop, it's gonna get worse!
or even get out of the Tub Current!
No, I can't control the
switching device of the gate!
Wildness?
It's a man-eating sunflower!
Calm down!
And my name is Heracles'n!
There is no sea for you all
to get away to or to live on!
It's impossible to fix it in time, Warden!
I'm a doctor!
Heracles'n!
Better make yourselves
comfortable! That's it.
Help me!
You dared to turn into
the Warden, of all men?
Hera...
I said "help!" I'm sick of this!
Hey wait, Navy!
I'm glad that I memorized
your face at that time!
You really eat a lot!
Why?! Why are you depressed?
Wake up, Hannyabal! What happened here?!
I'm gonna rescue Ace at any cost!
You know, it takes a lot of energy
just to get enough food for you!
Sleeping sulkily?!
W-Warden! Please let go of me!
"Wash your potatoes" and be ready for us!
Help me, Heracles! You're
the hero of the forest!
But she will grow up someday
and be able to fly!
Touch!
Potatoes?
Damn you!
The hero... of the forest?
Then she can fly back to the nest. Oh yeah!
Clank!
Bon-chan!
Yes, you're the strong, cool hero!
It's cold!
Straw-chan!
The expression should be "watch your neck!"
I'm the hero of the forest--Heracles'n!
How did I get here?
Hey, can you hear me, Bon-chan?!
You don't wash your potatoes and
boil them at a time like this!
Why are you doing this?!
Here is a scarf!
Wow! Cool!
First of all, why did he try to
pick a fight with the Navy HQ?!
When you learn how to fly,
Usopp'n! I'm coming for you'n!
you gotta take me to Sabaody Archipelago!
Just like you did in the past!
Oh?
Wait, before that... Captain Buggy!
Heracles!
Were you really a member of the crew?!
Luffy!
And a sworn brother of "Red-Haired?!"
Everybody!
Bon Clay-sama!
Our savior is a hell of
a pirate as we thought!
Look out!
Running now wouldn't be like a queer...
What is going on here?!
Heracles! Heracles! Heracle...
Oh, well...
If we abandon pals who would risk
their lives to pick up their pal,
Yeah! Then I can see Luffy and the others!
Damn! If word gets around, the
Government will keep an eye on me!
"Keep Out?"
will we... be able to
enjoy our food tomorrow?!
Promise me! And don't forget about it!
"This is an enclosed forest
of mechanical animals?"
So that's his background!
What... are... you... doing?!
And yet, he's so weak.
Hey! Stop! That tickles, you little monster!
Listen, guys... Straw Hats too!
With such a pedigree, how
could you be so dirty?!
Listen to what I have to say carefully!
So every ship has at least one blemish!
No!
So you're gonna treat me like a toy too?!
Shut up!
Am I the Straw Hat you guys're looking for?!
I didn't know that. But I remember...
Have you also heard of the East
Blue pirate known as Buggy?
Just kidding!
Miss Hina! The sheep ship
is heading to the east!
The Vice Captain old man was saying that.
--Whiz!
Huh? The Vice Captain?
You were tricked, weren't you!
The old man called Rayleigh,
I bet you know him.
We're experts at disguising ourselves! And...
--Zunk!
What?! Have you seen Rayleigh-san?!
we're the Straw Hats' friends...!
Mission: The surprising
wake-up in the jungle!
It's warm!
I miss Vice Captain! Where'd you see him?
They're talking about "Dark King"
Rayleigh! What a conversation!
Take back your wildness
through surviving, old man!
Bring it on!
Captain Buggy! I knew you were something!
Don't try this at home, kids!
Hey guys, you better relax!
Why are you doing this?!
I'm alive!
No no, wait a second! It's all true but...
Like you did in the past!
You all seem very frustrated.
Have you eaten breakfast?
But why're they attacking just me?
Jimbei, you promised me
that you wouldn't tell him!
...if you spread this around, it'll
be bad for my future as a pirate!
It's great to see you guys again finally!
To survive on this island, you need
to look sharp and have stamina'n!
It is not good for your mental health
if you don't eat it every day!
Not until communications were cut off!
But I wasn't sad at all!
It's amazing that you were the
member of the legendary pirates!
You're the weakest one on this island
now! Ants and worms are better than you!
We were gonna break out
together, weren't we?!
Oh I see! This is breakfast time!
Buggy! Buggy!
Screw you! I'm stronger
than ants and worms...
How many times have I been saved by you?!
H-Hey, you fools...
What was I thinking?
Oh? Where did she go?
Stop it! I was an apprentice to be exact!
If you are there, say something, Bon-chan!
Huge!
I don't want you to make
a lion of me with that...
Huge!
Oh okay, since she can walk now,
Delicious! There is nothing like the
first cup of tea in the morning!
That was it?! That queer...
Hey, you got the wrong idea!
she must be walking around a bit...
...stayed there alone to save us!
--Wanna eat this'n?
--Yeah, right'n!
Do you guys want some?
You need to build up stamina if
you don't wanna get beat up'n!
--Bon-chan!
--Brother Bon, say something!
Well, I don't feel so bad...
What?!
I know! But there's nothing
here that I really wanna eat!
Why aren't you answering?!
Oh yeah, wait a minute!
The Navy has overestimated me for
sure but it's not such a bad thing!
Bon-chan!
Something's wrong! From the
looks of her footsteps,
It feels great to be alive!
Oh, I'm hungry!
It's not working!
Yeah! Because it's all true!
she must be somewhere around here.
Oh well'n.
Mr. 2!
I'm hungry!
I'm developing a reputation here!
Mr. 2! How dare you!
Are you sure that there are
things to eat beyond this?
That raccoon that we tried to cook in
a hot pot must still be here somewhere!
I'm sorry about everything!
If by some chance, I could...
Yes, those are too good so be careful'n!
That was not a raccoon, that was a reindeer!
If I could beat Whitebeard,
then I'd become the one of...
-- Bon boy!
-- Fire!
Wow!
What the hell is this place?!
Let's catch it again and
cook reindeer hot pot!
Don't let them get away!
...the Four Emperors!
Break them into pieces!
--Yeah, let's do it!
--Let's do it!
Oh no no no... I'd go way
beyond that and become...
Bon-chan!
Smells so good! Yeah, I
think I can eat these!
Bon-chan!
T-This is bad!
...the King of the Pirates!
Really bad!
Ramen Falls! Spaghetti Patches!
Yeah! These guys might have
higher bounties than me!
Bon-chan, the gate's closing.
Ham Fruits! Chocolat Rocks for dessert!
Help us!
If I play my cards right...
We...
You can eat whatever you see!
...have to go.
...I can do this!
Captain Buggy! We'll follow
you the rest of our lives!
Oh, can I eat these?!
Good morning, boys!
Oh, it's you!
--Go ahead'n.
--Yum-yum!
Thank you!
Give us an order!
Old man!
Eat a lot and build your stamina, then
the man-eating plants won't attack you'n!
Let's steal this ship from the ones
who want to go to the Navy HQ!
I'm glad that you're okay!
I'm not an old man! Call me Mr. Frank!
It's not over here!
And then, we're gonna be free!
Yeah? That's great!
Let's go somewhere else!
Well, Straw Hat! You need to
give over this ship to us!
These are really good,
I can eat these forever!
Violence is not...
Yeah, good idea!
Brother Bon, thank you!
Don't just eat'n! You need to work out, too!
After breaking out, we don't
wanna go to the Navy HQ!
I know you are at an age
when you want to be naughty...
They didn't see us! So you were lost?
--Thank you!
I know! But I need to eat a lot...
We got Captain Buggy on our side!
If you let me talk...
...to become a cool hero of
the forest like you, right?
You'll see...
Go ahead, Captain Buggy!
Let's sort this out...
You're fully recovered!
...in a gentlemanly manner!
But you gotta be quiet!
Straw-chan!
You wanna become a hero, too?
--Buggy! Buggy!
--This is no good.
Stop... Nothing good... comes... from war!
If you're
not, they're gonna find us!
--Bon-chan!
--Straw-chan!
We're the heroes of the forest Heracles'n!
It's better to just kill them all.
Oh no! Be quiet!
You gotta save your brother at any cost!
Mr. Frank!
And Usopp'n!
Oh no, it's not working at all!
Oh, dammit!
Yeah, I feel like I can do it!
Relax...
--There it is! Right there!
--There's a bird, too!
Listen to what I say... Listen to what...
I know that you can save
your brother for sure!
U-Usopp'n! Oh?
Listen to... Listen...
Usopp'n! Where'd you go'n?!
Bon-chan!
We're gonna have a big feast today!
Chicken hot pot and reindeer hot pot!
Lis...
Wow! This is good, too!
To...
--The gate is closing!
--We gotta sink them!
I can eat this even if I'm full!
Listen... Lis... L...
That way'n?
Be quiet, you flashy fools!
This is too good! I can't stop!
You guys are all full of whim and fancy!
Lis...
Usopp'n! Where are you'n?
This ship won't stop!
If you eat too much, you're
gonna be in big trouble'n!
It's been a long time!
We're
heading to the center of the war!
I can't control my hands! I can't stop!
I'm more than fine now!
And you guys are already on board!
Damn! We're on a cliff!
Brace yourselves and think about it!
Gimme a break!
Soon, the man at the top of the
world is gonna show up in our midst!
You can't run anymore!
There you are, finally!
Give up now!
Straw-chan!
This is a once-in-a-lifetime chance.
What do you think, Heracles'n?
I come to rescue you!
Now I can become the hero of the forest!
If you guys are real men, why don't
you live out a dream with me?!
The birds are coming!
Super!
In the name of friendship!
Usopp'n! You're way too big!
Let's shoo them away!
Today...
I'll beat Whitebeard which means
that I'll conquer the world!
Hang in there!
You'd better work off some calories
or you're gonna be in big trouble!
Straw-chan! Hang in there!
Are you guys here to save us?!
Yeah! Captain Buggy!
Who do you think I am?!
I am Franky-sama!
I've been taking care of your baby but...
Us queers...
Yeah! You're back, old man!
...we don't say goodbye!
...you don't need to thank me, you bastard!
Captain Buggy!
Per... vert!
What's this? An earthquake?
--Bon-chan!
--Brother Bon!
We were devastated by the darkness of hell...
It's beginning!
Huh?
What's the matter?
...And we almost lost the
most important thing!
I got cooled down a little
so I'm running out of steam!
I saw this coming!
Losing the jewels of our hearts
that we once had - called dream!
I can't believe this!
Oh, geek! I mean, god!
Whoa, w-what a huge mouth!
We let them get away!
Um... Um...
I will follow you!
If it weren't for him, we would...
Don't wanna fall! Don't wanna fall!
Oh yeah! We gotta go there!
I don't want a peaceful life!
Guard Boost!
We would've sunk in the
water inside the gate!
Where are we going?
That's right!
The house of Dr. Vegapunk!
Let's go, guys! To Navy Headquarters!
The flower of friendship blooms even in hell.
Maybe we can find a machine
to make some cola!
--Usopp'n!
--Heracles!
Dr. Vegapunk?!
--Wow!
--Too heavy!
Looks like it's over.
On the sand where waves come and go,
He's the standout genius
He has this kind of ability at least.
of Future Land
Baldimore known for its advanced technology!
it leaves its petal as a memento.
Hey!
Captain Buggy! You should lead the world!
So they're fighting again...
The mechanical animals that you just
saw are all cyborgs that he created!
I'll follow you to the end!
Hera!
We will make it bloom again
someday, the Oh Come My Way!
Yeah, follow me!
I didn't know that she was her baby!
Goodbye, Usopp'n.
I heard that he was a weirdo and he
left the island with cyborgs running wild
I'm happy for you!
So this is goodbye?!
Hey, don't forget the promise!
I hope they are having fun.
--Bon-chan!
--Brother Bon!
Oh, ramen!
but that he was also amazing!
When you grow up and learn how to fly,
Bon boy!
The ship that carries Portgaz D. Ace
will arrive at Marineford shortly!
you gotta take me to Sabaody Archipelago!
Mr. 2!
Here he comes, finally!
Grandpa told me to keep away from here
I'm counting on you!
because there are a lot of
dangerous creations inside!
Do you wanna say something before you die?!
Relax and go on board!
This is what I wanted!
But when it will be?!
There's room for everybody so don't worry!
We'll meet again in the
garden of Oh Come My Way...
I can't wait that long!
Usopp'n!
At this time,
Sup!
Be prepared for the arrival!
the number of prisoners who escaped from the
greatest underwater prison, Impel Down...
I can't eat anymore!
Alright!
Usopp'n!
...has increased to 241 in total!
Fat things will surely be
eaten on this island'n!
I'm sick of this place!
Surely be eaten?!
This is the biggest gaffe in the history of
Impel Down
NAVY
Why can't the humans and the
birds on this island get along?!
It's impossible to escape
from here - Bowin Islands!
but the ordeal is not over yet.
Impossible to escape?!
Luffy! Everybody!
The public execution of
Portgaz D. Ace is in...
And I'm the hero of the forest H...
Help me!
What the hell is this?!
...4 hours!
Zoro wanders the island with Perona
Luffy and the others say farewell
to Bon Clay and set sail.
Robin is held prisoner in Tequila Wolf.
Sanji is on the run from countless
pursuers of ambiguous gender.
The sky island, Weatheria, still carrying
Nami, continues toward the Grand Line,
in hopes of reuniting with their friends.
Despite the tight security,
After running and running to escape them,
But when Buggy learns that they're
headed for the Navy Headquarters,
the young girl Soran takes action to save
but it's traveling far too slowly.
When Zoro gets lost as always,
a mysterious shadow attacks!
he's met by a mysterious
queen, and a frilly dress.
Robin without concern for
the danger it puts her in.
he and the other prisoners plan a
mutiny to commandeer the Navy ship.
Will Nami make it back to her friends?
Around that time,
Meanwhile, Usopp chows down to
become the hero of the forest!
Then, still more shocking news from
the Navy Headquarters reaches them...
And will Franky, now a gentleman,
ever return to his old self?!
a huge, round creature falls
to the ground behind Chopper!
Brook is trying to repay his panty debt!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Friends' Whereabouts! The Weatheria
Report and the Cyborg Animals!"
"The Friends' Whereabouts! A
Huge Tomb and the Panty Debt!"
"The Friends' Whereabouts! Revolutionaries
and the Gorging Forest's Trap!"
"The Friends' Whereabouts! A Cheeper
of Giant Birds and a Pink Showdown!"
"To the Navy Headquarters!
Off to Rescue Ace!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!