Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy is trying to break free
in order to go after Ace
but Warden Magellan is in his way!
Into the water?! Go ahead
and dive if you want!
There are Sea Kings' nests everywhere!
Hell's Judgement!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Stamp!
Hell...
...Wink!
I won't allow!
What's this?!
You made it!
I'm sorry that I should ask you
to come to this dangerous area!
--It's a school of whale sharks!
--Jimbei must have called them!
Cool!
"Come, Final Miracle! Break
Through the Gate of Justice!"
Carry them here!
That guy's so cool!
--Cool!
--Heehaw!
Yo-ho!
Yeah! We made it to the Navy ship!
We broke out!
I can't believe that we
escaped from Impel Down!
It's not time to celebrate yet!
We have to get going!
Yeah!
Thank you, whale sharks!
I appreciate it!
--See you!
--Thank you so much!
Get home safely!
I'll start treating Inazuma.
Bring all the medicines
from the clinic!
Alright!
I'm never going back into that hell again!
Me, neither! I'm gonna reform my
ways and go back to my family!
We're free now!
Thanks to who?
Say it!
Captain Buggy!
I can't believe that they made it that far.
Is this the Navy? Bring me a ship!
I'll ride it and bring them down myself!
Yes, sir!
They don't realize that after
all they are still trapped.
There is nothing but despair ahead for you!
You can't get away no
matter how you struggle!
Rear Admiral! We fixed the battery
that was damaged by Jimbei!
Good.
All ships, open fire!
Buggy!
Range correction!
They started firing!
--This is no good!
--How many ships are there?!
The fleet is coming after us!
They got us!
Even though everybody ranked higher than
Vice Admiral has been summoned to Marineford,
the Navy ships are still
formidable without them!
Can't you see that it's no
use? For pirates like you...
...The Gate of Justice won't open!
Oh no! I forgot about this!
Oh my God! We can't open it!
Damn! It's a dead end after coming this far!
You're talking like me!
--What're we gonna do, you shark?!
--Sail through it!
That's impossible! This is a disaster!
How can you be so relaxed?!
Say something!
Protect the ship first! That's our priority!
Why are we just taking their
fire?! This is a Navy ship, too!
--Fire back, you dumb-asses!
--That was my idea!
We have to fire back, guys!
We see, Captain Buggy!
Sables!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
How's that?!
Fire!
It's impossible for us to outrun them!
Dammit! If nothing is done, the
Navy will get us eventually!
Damn prisoners!
Why are they still heading to the
gate knowing that they're cornered?
The gate can only be controlled
from inside of Impel Down.
There is no other way to open it!
Keep firing! Sink them...
The Gate of Justice is opening!
Why?! What's going on?! Why
are they opening the gate?!
It's open!
W-Why is this happening?
Is this a trap?!
Yes! I don't know why
but the gate is opening!
It's open! It's open!
What?!
Warden Magellan! Please hurry!
No! Wait!
No way!
Why is the gate opening?!
Are you sure about opening the gate?
Warden Magellan!
I'm sure! Have I ever been wrong?!
No, it's not like I don't believe you!
After the prisoners' ship passes through,
close the gate right away, understood?
I got it, sir!
Don't let them get away!
They aren't allowed to! Fire!
Is it Magellan's order?!
What is he thinking?!
Why is he doing this?!
What happened to Warden?!
Yes, um, but it doesn't
look like his will to me!
He was at the pier near the
main entrance just while ago!
Why is this? What's happening here?!
Control room! What are you doing?!
Who told you to open the gate?!
W-Warden!
Oh no!
Is that true?
Bon-chan is...
You bastard!
That's right!
It's me!
I got you again!
He's an imposter!
Warden, I just heard from the lookout!
The stolen ship will pass the gate soon!
--Even if they get through the gate...
--Spin, spin!
--they can't outrun that many ships!
--It's impossible!
--Spin, spin!
Then, close the gate now! Push the button!
W-What?!
Oh, yes, sir! Um...
No, don't push it!
Okay!
--No, push it!
--Don't push it!
--Push it!
--Don't!
--Push it now!
--Yes, sir!
Memoirs of a Desert Kingdom!
Heehaw! I win!
Y-You bastard!
I'm not gonna let you go after Straw-chan!
Look! The gate is closing!
Yes! If we can get through it,
the Navy will be stopped by it!
I was with him at the entrance a while ago!
He stayed alone at Impel Down?!
We made it this far at
last! We're almost there!
Because of Bon-chan, we met Ivan-chan
and broke out successfully!
And we're gonna go on without him?!
We don't have time!
Are we gonna leave him there?!
We already left hundreds
of friends who were beaten!
Do you want to go back and fight Magellan?!
And lose more friends and time?!
To be able to open this gate, we
needed somebody to stay there!
I can do it better than anyone! I'm
gonna open the Gate of Justice!
What are you gonna do after that?!
What a pointless question!
Don't tell Straw-chan until
communications are cut off!
Us queers...
...we don't say goodbye!
It's still connected.
A Baby Transponder Snail's
coverage is limited.
It won't work after the gate closes.
No, I can't control the
switching device of the gate!
It's impossible to fix it in time, Warden!
You dared to turn into
the Warden, of all men?
I'm glad that I memorized
your face at that time!
Wake up, Hannyabal! What happened here?!
W-Warden! Please let go of me!
Touch!
Damn you!
Bon-chan!
Straw-chan!
Hey, can you hear me, Bon-chan?!
Why are you doing this?!
Just like you did in the past!
Bon Clay-sama!
Running now wouldn't be like a queer...
If we abandon pals who would risk
their lives to pick up their pal,
will we... be able to
enjoy our food tomorrow?!
Listen, guys... Straw Hats too!
Listen to what I have to say carefully!
Am I the Straw Hat you guys're looking for?!
Just kidding!
Miss Hina! The sheep ship
is heading to the east!
You were tricked, weren't you!
We're experts at disguising ourselves! And...
we're the Straw Hats' friends...!
Bring it on!
Why are you doing this?!
Like you did in the past!
Jimbei, you promised me
that you wouldn't tell him!
Not until communications were cut off!
We were gonna break out
together, weren't we?!
How many times have I been saved by you?!
If you are there, say something, Bon-chan!
That was it?! That queer...
...stayed there alone to save us!
--Bon-chan!
--Brother Bon, say something!
Why aren't you answering?!
Bon-chan!
Mr. 2!
Mr. 2! How dare you!
I'm sorry about everything!
-- Bon boy!
-- Fire!
Don't let them get away!
Break them into pieces!
Bon-chan!
Bon-chan, the gate's closing.
We...
...have to go.
Thank you!
Brother Bon, thank you!
--Thank you!
Straw-chan!
--Bon-chan!
--Straw-chan!
You gotta save your brother at any cost!
I know that you can save
your brother for sure!
Bon-chan!
--The gate is closing!
--We gotta sink them!
It's been a long time!
I'm more than fine now!
Gimme a break!
Straw-chan!
I come to rescue you!
In the name of friendship!
Hang in there!
Straw-chan! Hang in there!
Us queers...
...we don't say goodbye!
--Bon-chan!
--Brother Bon!
I can't believe this!
We let them get away!
If it weren't for him, we would...
We would've sunk in the
water inside the gate!
The flower of friendship blooms even in hell.
On the sand where waves come and go,
it leaves its petal as a memento.
We will make it bloom again
someday, the Oh Come My Way!
--Bon-chan!
--Brother Bon!
Bon boy!
Mr. 2!
Do you wanna say something before you die?!
This is what I wanted!
We'll meet again in the
garden of Oh Come My Way...
At this time,
the number of prisoners who escaped from the
greatest underwater prison, Impel Down...
...has increased to 241 in total!
This is the biggest gaffe in the history of
Impel Down
but the ordeal is not over yet.
The public execution of
Portgaz D. Ace is in...
...4 hours!
Luffy and the others say farewell
to Bon Clay and set sail.
But when Buggy learns that they're
headed for the Navy Headquarters,
he and the other prisoners plan a
mutiny to commandeer the Navy ship.
Then, still more shocking news from
the Navy Headquarters reaches them...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To the Navy Headquarters!
Off to Rescue Ace!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!