Horo-horo-horo-horo-horo...
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
The word "thank you" has faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Am I getting stronger?
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
I don't know the answer yet
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
"That feeling" I get when embarking
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
Is something I hope to remember always
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to lose something precious
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
Snatch up the treasure here and there
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
Make some waves...
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
saa yukou
So let's go
To the West, To the East
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to lose something precious
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
To the future I believe in...
shinjita sono saki e to...
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the
Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way
to the New World,
will speed along the
Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy is rushing to Navy HQ to rescue his brother, Ace,
Luffy is headed to the Navy Headquarters in order to rescue his brother, Ace!
Luffy has broken out of the great prison Impel Down
who is waiting to be executed.
and is headed to the Navy Headquarters in order to rescue his brother, Ace!
Ace.
Now, there are only 3 hours left before the public execution of Portgaz D. Ace...
Meanwhile,  the rest of the Straw Hats are...
The execution is in 3 hours.
All forces of the Navy are expecting an attack by the Whitebeard Pirates at Marineford.
Couldn't eat another bite!
"The Friends' Whereabouts! A Huge Tomb and the Panty Debt!"
"A Special Retrospective Before Marineford! The Vow of the Brotherhood!"
--Look, my stomach is bulging!
--It's the Navy's food and drinks!
Ace, tell them the name of your father.
I can't believe that I was thinking "I'll never get out!"
"Gloom Island
Ruins of the Muggy Kingdom"
Meanwhile, a short time ago,
"Ticking Down to the Time of Battle! The Navy's Strongest Lineup in Position!"
All thanks to...
Zoro who was forced to stay with Perona was...
...Captain Buggy! Thank you!
My father is Whitebeard.
No!
Your mother's name is Portgaz D. Rouge.
No problem! No problem!
This is no good! I got to hurry!
That must be Ace-san's Vivre Card.
So, how's it going, Jimbei?
A year and 3 months after the father's death,
Stand up.
Hm?
Yeah.
Don't hm me, you jerk!
the child was born with the blood of the world's most heinous man in his veins.
Where did he go?! That stupid swordsman!
I'm asking you when we will get to Navy HQ so I can conquer the world!
I heard a lot about you from Ace.
That was you!
That attitude really gets me!
He told me that you two always used to run through the fields together.
I can't stop shaking!
The Seven Warlords who sold their souls to the Government
Your father is...
Yeah! Ace and I were always together!
"A Few Hours Ago"
...the King of the Pirates -
and the 3 navy admirals are no match for us!
Gold Roger!
Wait! Ace!
That's right!
Dammit!
I'm gonna beat you this time!
You should be the next King of the Pirates because you're following in the wake of Roger!
Where's the room that I was sleeping in?!
Does it continue?
Eating together...
Sleeping together...
Still?
"A Special Retrospective Before Marineford! The Three Navy Admirals Come Together!"
Spending all your spare time honing your skills...
Is this building a maze?!
The bloodline of the King of the Pirates?!
This way?!
"A Vast Fleet Appears! Here Come the Whitebeard Pirates!"
Meanwhile, at Navy Headquarters in Marineford...
May I come in?
What am I doing?
Everybody, it's time. We need you to come to the harbor with us.
You're still far from defeating me.
Without "First Son of the Sea" Jimbei who is with Luffy
I thought that it'd be fun to use Negative Hollow
I can't believe that the arch villain had a kid!
and Marshall D. Teech who has burst into Impel Down,
That's how it used to be -
to make him depressed when he finds his sword
4 of The Seven Warlords are about to leave Marie Jois.
The legend of Gold Roger continues!
so I told him where his sword was but that was 2 days ago already...
Ace-san told me nostalgically.
In addition, Boa Hancock is here waiting as well
Ace went out to sea 3 years before me.
I'm so relieved that they got him!
If he's a son of the King of the Pirates, he must be atrocious!
He hadn't even eaten the devil fruit at that time but I couldn't beat him even once.
after her stopover at Impel Down.
He can't find it no matter how many hints I give!
4 of these 5 have had dealings with the Straw Hats in the past.
If I'd caught him and put him up for auction, I would have made a fortune!
You hadn't seen him after he left?
Whitebeard is just a man but you people are beside yourselves with fear.
No, I saw him in Alabasta once.
Why're you here?! You use your Devil Fruit power again?!
This execution is turning into quite a show!
Climb.
What are you saying?! Don't accuse me!
We still have 3 hours before the execution.
So the strength of "Fire Fist" is in his blood.
Sheesh! I guess my letting you escape was pretty much pointless.
You're the one who kept losing your way!
Then, he has the One Piece, too?
Yes, that's true but we need to be prepared for any contingency.
If you climb the stairs behind us, all the hallways lead directly to the room!
"Fire Fist" is as good as dead anyway.
Yo!
Ace!
Haven't seen you in a while, Luffy!
He will be wiped off the face of the earth soon.
Bartholomew Kuma!
How can you get lost?!
This brings back memories!
Shut up! You're not clear enough!
I'm just in these waters on minor business,
It's not my fault at all!
Ursus Shock!
You're a fantasista, huh?
so I thought I might look you up.
It's that way!
Minor business?
How can you mishear me so badly?!
"South Blue"
I'm a member of the Whitebeard Pirates now.
I didn't realize you were that pathetic without your sword!
"Navy"
It's in 3 hours now! I wonder if Whitebeard has arrived yet.
Whitebeard Pirates?
This is the mark of the Whitebeard Pirates. It's my pride.
It's so heartbreaking just to look at you now!
I don't know. Do you think he's really gonna be there?
Oh?
He's a big deal but isn't he too old?
So, you're still alive, Roronoa...
Luffy. Won't you join the Whitebeard Pirates?
How sad!
You think so?
If you were to take a trip, where would you want to go?
You put me in this situation!
Your friends can come too, of course.
He is not the biological brother of Luffy, then?
He was around before the Great Pirate Era. He must be senile by now.
No.
Good things will happen to you someday!
I will protect you, even if it costs me my life!
I figured not. Just thought I'd ask.
We haven't heard his name in any big news for years.
Fight!
Whitebeard is the greatest pirate I know.
Leave me alone!
How can you guys take this so lightly?
Damn it!
Roger's...
Because he's unignorable, the Navy HQ has called up its elites and...
I wanna help him to be King of the Pirates...
You can have it back.
...Son?
Why're you doing this?
...And not you, Luffy.
...is expecting him with all their forces.
Luffy... Help m--
It doesn't mean anything.
That's fine! Then we'll just have to fight!
Even if you have your sword, you can't attack me because I'm a replica.
I'm almost certain that Whitebeard is going to appear.
His biological son alive! This must be a miracle!
Cheers!
Who said I was joining you?
Robin!
Nothing can harm this body.
All people connected to Roger should have been executed at that time!
And then what's gonna happen?
So a swordsman like you poses no threat to me!
Luffy!
I don't know. How am I supposed to know?
Ace! Are you sure you won't join us?
Plus, I don't want any servants who are not cute!
Since his brother is Luffy-san, I thought that his father was Dragon, too!
"East Blue"
I'm chasing a certain man.
We will never meet again.
He's a pirate of a different era.
I thought so, too! What's the deal here? They're not biological brothers?
His name's Blackbeard.
He used to be a member of the 2nd Division of the Whitebeard Pirates,
I'm not giving it back for no reason!
Is it possible for him to beat the Navy HQ?
one of my men.
It's not possible for any pirates to attack Marineford.
If I use him, I can go back to Thriller Bark!
But he committed the worst possible sin on a pirate ship:
Farewell...
Seems like he's empty-headed so I can easily handle him!
he killed a crewmember and jumped ship.
That's not true. I think it was 20 years ago,
So, as the commander, I gotta find and get rid of him.
I'll use him as I please,
a pirate called Shiki the Golden Lion invaded Marineford
toy with him and leave him on this island at the end!
and left the Navy HQ half destroyed.
You look so eager to do it.
That's not so bad!
This time it's going to be worse.
I wanted to give this to you. Here.
What?!
You're so uncouth.
No matter who wins, a lot of people will die.
Oh no! I let him get away!
Dracule Mihawk AKA "Hawk-Eye" Mihawk!
Hold onto it, always.
Where did he go?! That stupid swordsman!
It's just a paper.
It'd be better if he didn't appear.
Yes, but that paper will lead us to one another.
Garp.
If nothing besides the execution happens, that'd be for the best.
I wonder how Luffy and the others are doing!
"North Blue"
You don't want it?
Garp.
I gotta go back to Sabaody Archipelago!
No, I want it!
Older brothers can't help worrying...
Can you believe this, Garp?
I hope that they're okay!
I'm expecting a baby.
Hey, we want drinks, old guy!
Everyone focus on escaping!
...if their younger brother is weak.
Are you asking me to open the bar on a day like this? We're expecting a big war in any minute!
I know that he'll be a handful
As we are now, we can't beat these guys!
Unfortunately, I won't be around by the time of the child's birth.
but please look after him.
Go home! If the world's still here tomorrow, I'll open it!
Huh? Are you leaving already?
Then just sell us some drinks! It feels like we're the ones who're on the scaffold!
Why're you telling that to me a Navy officer, Roger?
Luffy! I'll see you at the top of the pirates' world!
Is it possible... that's...
The mother of the child--a woman related to you will be executed for sure!
We can't do without drinking!
I can't just stay here doing nothing!
...Hawk-Eye...!
He's not just another old man.
"West Blue"
He hasn't lost it at all!
I came out to sea to meet you.
Blackbeard...
It was just a year ago, when we saw him sitting right there...
I met him before in Mock Town.
That's why I'm telling you.
What's your goal?
To become the strongest!
How foolish...
--Hey, pops!
--Hey, buddy!
The Government will definitely dig up my whereabouts for the last year
There he is!
Hm? What's wrong?
I think I know that castle... or not...
--This cherry pie tastes extremely bad! Hm?
--This cherry pie tastes extremely good! Hm?
Tiger...
...Trap!
...we thought we were dead.
and find and kill her.
You bastard! Wanna fight?!
"Grand Line"
Is Whitebeard that outrageous?
I know!
What the hell are you fighting about?!
Kid! State your name.
But they can't blame a child whose not born.
It looks like the other castle! How confusing!
Even those kids know it. They're singing as they jump rope.
Are you a pirate?
Yeah, that's right.
Garp!
Do you really think so?! I'm sick of your sense of direction!
The pirate Whitebeard is scarier than a devil!
What's the bounty for you?
Roronoa Zoro.
We've tried to kill each other dozens of times.
30 million!
30 million? For you?
I'll remember it, strong one. I haven't seen any one like you in a while...
Oh, God!
That's why I can trust you as I trust my friends.
I can't believe how nice I am!
Can't be true! It's gotta be a lie!
Where is this world headed?
I don't have to guide him to the sea.
I'm not lying! That's the truth!
As a swordsman's courtesy, I'll sink you using the world's strongest black sword.
Stop it!
But it's okay! I'll take advantage of him wisely!
Whoa! They're gonna take Bellamy on!
Three Swords Style Secret Technique!
Is this the right way?
Go for it!
You have no right to ask me that!
Luffy, wait!
I checked it!
Fall!
Hey, Mister! We want to go to the sky island!
Three Thousand Worlds!
Just shut up and follow me!
On the island of Marineford home of the Navy Headquarters,
You must protect my baby.
Do you know anything about it?
lies a huge city mainly populated by families of the Navy.
Alright.
Stop being so selfish!
Augh! What did I just say?!
No, I'm sure that you'll do it!
Huh? Oh, it's that way.
It's this way, you stupid swordsman!
She said "sky island!"
Huh?!
What are you...?
Give me a break!
Why can't you even follow me?!
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame...
Look after my child!
You have to lead the way properly!
An evacuation order has been issued to all residents at this time.
Admirable!
Hey, you got me there.
Is it my fault?!
You guys believe in such an ancient legend... that there's an island in the sky?
Zoro!!
It's exhausting just staying with him.
And at Sabaody Archipelago at the evacuation site,
Just which era are you from?
residents are watching the proceedings of the execution on monitors.
Listen. The era where pirates dream about things is over
What's the matter?
Don't live so hastily, young man.
You got tired even though you're flying?
Don't worry. I didn't kill that man.
Huh?! It's your fault!
When I see idiots chasing after dreams like that, I get disgusted!
Why?
Never mind! I'll get sick just by talking to you.
It's still too early for you to die. My name is Dracule Mihawk!
Reporters and cameramen from various places are...
Luffy!
...standing by here to break the news quickly to the world.
Zoro...
This tree looks familiar!
Learn about yourself! Learn about the world! And become strong!
Shut up!
Don't take them on, no matter what happens.
No matter how many years it takes,
That's really the best of Navy HQ.
I will hold this seat of the strongest and wait for you.
I assume that Whitebeard knows about this.
What was that?!
Surpass this sword! Try to surpass me! Roronoa Zoro!
Maybe somebody else has been sent here!
But still, will he venture to be there?
You sure that it's this island?
I gotta go and check!
Every look-out ship that the Navy sent has been swiftly sunk
People saw Roger acting like he wasn't a pirate here.
Hey, what're you going?
I don't need a toy like you that is just annoying and boring!
I don't want to get behind!
The sky island exists.
and there has been no report of a sighting of Whitebeard.
As if he were a father.
Roger's era has ended. We have to cut the bloodline.
Being able to steal shadows and corpses of strong men in the world as I please,
So the tension at Marineford continues to rise.
Wander on this island forever!
You're that guy...
The new era they're talking about is crap!
it'll be a great war for me!
Find all the babies who are due within 10 months of his going to jail.
Who is it? I want somebody cute this time!
And there is less than 3 hours left until the looming execution.
The era where pirates have dreams will be over, they say?! Huh?!
Gecko Moria!
"Navy"
Hey, what took you so long?
What?!
All pregnant women, too.
Now, all the shadows in Thriller Bark,
W-W-Why are you here?!
Why? I thought that the sea was this way.
People's dreams... have no end!!
Kill all mothers who are suspicious.
empower me!
Y-You're really a fantasista!
Shadows Asgard!
I can't believe this!
I have problem with that. Is that really necessary?
Isn't that right?!
This guy's really something... probably?
I still can't believe that somebody was able to beat Ace.
This public execution is not just an execution of a pirate.
Gum-Gum...
It has great significance for the future of the world.
...Jet Rocket!
W-What?!
The Warlords and the Navy are gonna fight against the Whitebeards?!
That's why it's necessary to...
Gum-Gum...
What's that?! What's gonna happen?! W-W-W-W-Wait a minute!
Brick Bat!
You are responsible for this matter since you are one of the parties involved.
T-This is too much to hear at once!
That tree must've been cut down recently!
How disappointing! It was just a tree falling down?
Black Box!
Don't forget that, Garp.
What a foolish man! You don't know anything.
He got me!
Nobody has been sent so that means...
Break into pieces!
...I have to settle for him for now?!
I must say, that was just a prediction.
But I love the depressing atmosphere after a war!
But the battle will probably happen.
It's so enchanting!
5 were born in this month.
The World Government has made a move.
"Marineford Navy Headquarters"
Maybe some restless evil spirits did that!
This is...
Whitebeard is a man who would never allow his mates to be killed.
...a baptism for you!
Even though they know this, they announced the public execution of...
I doubt it.
Ones who are due next month are...
...Portgaz D. Ace, a great commander of Whitebeard's.
Doflamingo-dono and Hancock-dono, please hurry.
Hey, where are you going? Hey!
I know. Don't call my name so casually!
What's wrong?
Ace... is gonna get executed?
Not yet.
Hurry and get ready!
Boa Hancock!
Hey you, don't lag behind!
For being charmed by me, your guilty consciences...
I heard a pirate called Blackbeard...
Look into the ones with husbands, too. They could be fake.
...became a Warlord by defeating "Fire Fist" Ace.
...will turn your bodies solid!
Don't slacken your pace!
No matter what happens, it'll last only 3 hours!
She'll come back when she is cleared.
Love-Love Beam!
That's my brother!
Ace is my older brother!
Then it's all finished!
Hanco--!
What?!
I wanna go and rescue Ace!
No. Not yet.
Elite soldiers are summoned from all over the world--totaling almost one hundred thousand.
Is this a...
When I heard the news, I couldn't believe it either.
...Tomb?
Who made this?!
You piss me off!
You can't come out yet.
But... I didn't know that you already met Teech.
It has carved out from a big tree. It took great skill!
Big Sis! Stay strong!
The crescent-shaped bay area and the whole island are surrounded by 50 Navy ships
This can't be! No man exists that won't be my slave!
It's very big!
I remember that that's the way he talks.
I'm sorry.
and numerous cannons have been set at the bay area.
Blackbeard!
Not yet.
Again! Somebody is here as I thought!
So you're...
And in front of all the marshaled forces that can be seen from sea...
I cannot stand that man's existence!
Not yet.
You're...
...stand 5 ruffians who hold the key to the war. Pirates--The Seven Warlords!
Medusa Hair...
Not yet.
...Blackbeard?!
Huh? Oh yeah, I never gave you my name.
Not yet. Not yet.
...Eight-Headed Serpent!
Medusa Hair...
"Bartholomew Kuma"
Not yet.
...Salamander!
Long time no see, Straw Hat!
So fast!
Gum-Gum...
"Gecko Moria"
I was surprised, too, when I heard that you were the brother of my commander!
...Jet...
There're no more pregnant women.
...Gatling!
"Don Quixote Doflamingo"
It's been 10 months since Roger went to jail. I think he has not child.
"Dracule Mihawk"
Are you sure you want to be here? You're gonna miss it!
So Roger's time is really over, huh?
Your brother's public execution!
"Boa Hancock"
Ouch! Hot!
What?! It bounced off!
That man!
It's...
You'd rather die than let people see this, right?!
Hey! Look at that!
...the admirals!
I found out later that the former Warlord right there...
I don't know why but I find them so intimidating!
Stop!
So don't move!
...Crocodile was defeated by you, Straw Hat Luffy!
Guarding closely below the scaffold are...
...the Navy's greatest powers...
At that time, I was trying to take his place as a Warlord so...
You're Portgaz D. Rouge, aren't you?
...the three admirals!
Luffy! Please be safe!
...killing you was the most effective way to show my ability to the Government!
"Navy Admiral
Aokiji Kuzan"
But fate has saved you instead!
You bastards!
This is the only one who has never met Luffy or the others.
"Navy Admiral
Akainu Sakazuki"
Pay your respects at his grave!
If it's a girl--Ann.
Don Quixote Doflamingo!
"Navy Admiral
Kizaru Borsalino"
If it's a boy--Ace.
If it weren't for him, you'd be the one who...
Those are the names that he picked.
Please! Don't do this anymore! Why're you doing this?!
Every force of justice imaginable is...
...would've been killed, Straw Hat!
...now waiting for the Whitebeard Pirates to stop them from rescuing Ace!
Because I don't need any punks to work under me, kids.
So his name is Gol D. Ace.
The guy that he killed was...
...called Thatch--the commander of the 4th Division of the Whitebeards.
Augh! Damn! My body is hardening!
"Lazy Bones Island
The Land of Poverty - Hungeria"
This is Lazy Bones Island
the land of poverty "Hungeria."
Don't do this! Have mercy on me!
He was a good-hearted man.
Brook was mistaken as Satan, the king of devils-- by its residents.
No!
I wanted to help good old Whitebeard whom I owe so much
Our son.
so I often visited the ship at that time,
O-One more chance...
but I didn't notice what Teech was up to!
Give me just one more chance.
And then,
What a clear morning!
Ace.
Ace-san sailed out to sea alone.
I... We will follow you!
As the commander of the 2nd Division of the Whitebeards,
Luffy-san...
Listen, Luffy.
Such an eager underling! Don't make me cry.
he needed to get rid of Teech!
We have to live without leaving any regrets.
I wonder if they are all looking at the sun like this...
--Rouge!
--Rouge! Stay with us!
However, I don't need you to follow me.
Uh-huh.
Yes, I'm sure they are!
Doflamingo!
Because whatever happens, the sun will always rise!
And if I can stay alive,
The day is coming! So hurry and prepare!
You must raise him, Dadan!
I will see them again!
For a world where only true pirates can survive!
No way!
To all soldiers!
The powerless should flee!
Whose baby is this?
Report to the gulf!
The unstoppable swell of the new era of daring men is coming!
Well, come to think of it, this island is very deserted!
Get ready for the public execution of Portgaz D. Ace!
We gotta go out to sea someday...
...and live as we like.
I repeat!
And I didn't notice yesterday but inside that building,
All soldiers, report to the gulf!
His capability is still unknown.
Freer than anyone else.
there was an altar and dolls for some kind of rituals,
uncanny tapestries and posters on the wall,
Dadan?!
and macabre-looking mural decorations.
Yes. You're gonna live with them from today.
And those things on the floor - are they tools for voodoo or something?
No!
You gotta live with them! Be nice to them!
When I think about it, it's kind of weird!
Also, at the Navy Headquarters,
Have you awoken?
Get ready to set sail! We've got a lot to do!
We were just going to visit your room bringing breakfast.
Because Luffy and I unfortunately have the blood of...
under the command of Fleet Admiral Sengoku...
...the world's most infamous criminals in our veins anyway.
Hey! Wait, Teech!
You're here! It's time, Aokiji-san!
I've been looking for you.
Is that for me?
I took over the name "Portgaz" from my mother to whom I owe so much
Yes, of course!
but I never wanted to have my good-for-nothing father's blood.
Oh, it's time for lunch already?
How generous you people are! You don't even know me!
Old man...
Admiral Aokiji!
Oops! I haven't introduced myself yet.
My only father is...
I'm the head of this country Pekkori.
Ace! Commander!
Ice Age!
Whitebeard!
Pekkori-san! Well then, I gratefully accept the food.
I see it!
Quit calling me "commander."
Hey! Jimbei!
People who use that term usually respect others.
I see the Gate of Justice already! That was fast!
Garp.
You can't fool me.
It was 2 years ago.
No, it wasn't! If the wind were right, we could have gotten here faster.
You took over your mother's name and rose up in the world of the sea...
Young lady.
The ocean turns... to ice!
...as the captain of the Spade Pirates with your exquisite speed and power.
However...
Could I look at your panties?
I warn you.
I got it. But let me say just one thing.
As long as we don't open the Gate of Justice, you guys can't get to Marineford
This is what a navy admiral can do.
And that's when we noticed...
Panties! Hurry and show him your underwear!
Ace! Why don't you join my crew?!
...that Roger's blood still flowed!
You got good friends! But you can't change yourself, Nico Robin!
or even get out of the Tub Current!
There is no sea for you all to get away to or to live on!
Oh no no, um... I don't need to see the guys' underwear!
You're wrong! I'm not...
Let's dominate the world together! The way is all planned out
You don't need to hesitate! Enjoy it as much as you want!
But Whitebeard also noticed that at the same time.
Robin! Look out! Run!
Whitebeard's reign is over! I'll become the next Pirate King!
So now, how can we get through the gate?
You guys! It's almost time for...
What is that?! Augh!
And to make you the next King of the Pirates,
For starters, I'm gonna kill Straw Hat Luffy who is in the Water Seven...
Thank you for the big meal!
Huh? What is it?
he let the son of his old rival onto his ship.
I'm so full that I can barely move!
Time for Captain Buggy to conquer the world!
...as a gift to the Government!
Luffy? What did you just say?
Actually, I don't have a stomach to be full!
That's right!
No!
The Navy HQ is nothing!
I got on the ship to make my dad the next King!
You!
Oh! You know him?!
Whitebeard is nothing!
No one believes that except you.
Stop screaming. If you defrost her right, she'll live.
Another reason I can't let you go free!
That's our one-week-worth of food!
Who is the next King of the Pirates?
In fact, it made it harder for us to catch you.
He's my brother!
Be patient for now!
Captain Buggy!
But her body's fragile now so be careful.
You were protected by Whitebeard.
Well, Satan-sama, did you say that you wanted to ask us a favor?
And of course...
If you break her, she'll die. For example...
...I'm not gonna become one of...
If we let you go free, we know you'll use
your abilities to become the next King.
That's right!
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
...if you crush her like this!
I want to set sail right away! So I need a ship!
...your crew.
That's why it means a great deal to execute you here today.
N-No! Have we done something that made you upset?
No!
No.
Hey, everybody! Show your underwear for his dessert!
Ace!
Fire Fist!
Even if it means risking an all-out war with Whitebeard!
Enough with the underwear! Wow!
T-That was close!
You don't like underwear anymore?
No, that's not the point.
--Yeah!
--You did it, Usopp!
I have to get back to my friends at any cost!
What's going on here?
Fleet Admiral Sengoku! I have report!
Usopp! Chopper! Just run to the ship!
The Gate of Justice is opening without any order.
Get back?
Treat her and help her!
Yes.
A-At any cost?!
G-Got it!
And we can't make contact with the control room!
Yes, I feel bad because I've been treated so nicely.
We won't let you...
What?!
Wait, guys!
We're over!
I know what you want, Ace. You want to kill me.
Stand aside. I wanna fight him man-to-man.
If underwear won't do it, there's nothing we can do to keep you here!
Hey, look! "Fire Fist" Ace has come out!
No wonder. Killing a crewmember is the worst crime.
--It'd be nice if it opened with a hit!
--Oh, like "knock knock"...
It's the end of this country!
Yes, I killed Thatch - the commander of the 4th Division!
Let's sort this out--me and you!
It's come to this, we have no choice but to take our lives...
You think that's all it'd take?!
This is the man...
...who may trigger a war that will shake the world!
According to the ship's rules, the one who finds it can eat it.
No problem but since there's no ship to take you into custody,
W-W-Wait a minute! Please relax!
I remembered how they looked from seeing all the fruit in a book.
What?!
I'll kill you all one by one.
Well, it seems like you have a story there.
I noticed this was the one I'd been looking for.
And he is the one who holds the fate of the world now!
That's why you call me Satan and...
...you said something about Longarm Tribe last night.
It's opening!
That's why you killed Thatch? To steal it?
What is going on?
Why don't you tell me about it?
The Gate of Justice opens on its own!
Well, it wasn't for no reason.
The Navy guy told us that they weren't gonna open the gate!
The power chose me, Ace!
This country has been overrun by the Longarm Tribe for too long.
The control room must be in Marineford. Who is doing this?
With that fruit, I've become the world's strongest man, Ace.
Not only money and goods and food...
Gum-Gum...
...but they also take men and women in their prime from us.
...Storm!
Look! This one is different from all the other Logia type.
There we go! A little more!
And as you see, our country is devastated
I know it because...
and suffering extreme poverty!
Ace, your body is made out of fire, right?
...out of joy, my blade bones are dancing the lambada!
Okay, Garp? I'll tell them everything!
Then, those meal were...
So be it. I'll be downstairs.
I'm ashamed to say this but we made them from what little food we had.
Ice Time!
There! There! There we go, there we go, there we go!
No way!
Mine's made out of darkness!
In order to get out of the situation,
Ca-Captain Buggy, don't tell me...
Firefly! Fiery Doll!
we kept praying to all the gods and goddesses.
There we go!
--Step aside for a minute.
--Yes, sir!
Don't tell me that you're opening it!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow...
--Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
--What's going on?
Are you a messenger of God?!
Not only that but we have invited famous psychics from around the world...
Is it true, Buggy?!
Not lunch! What are you talking about?!
Ouch!
No, it's not! What kind of role play is this?!
--Give me a Transponder Snail.
--Yes, sir.
...to curse our enemies to death!
It's the execution of Portgaz D. Ace...
But it's odd.
But seriously. Who is opening it?
Yeah, I know. Don't get so uptight.
If it was a Logia type fruit, you could fend off these attacks.
But when it didn't work, we resorted to black magic
Well, maybe God really wants me to become the King of the Pirates!
and finally, we got you, Satan-sama - the king of devils, to be summoned here!
Please hurry!
Summoning us at lunchtime? So you guys really want to boss us around, huh?
I have something to tell you all.
Satan-sama! You're our one and only hope!
Admiral Kizaru!
Who cares! In any case...
I told you. Darkness will drag in everything.
Please deal the Longarm Tribe a bloody blow!
...let's go!
Portgaz D. Ace...
--We beg you!
Bullets, blades, blows, fire, even thunder!
It's about the great significance of his death today.
Zoro!
M-Me?!
So I can't fend off attacks like you do.
Yes! Will you please curse them to death for us?!
My body will absorb even pain more than a normal person's.
It's not your fault.
--Satan-sama!
Wh-What?! Who are you?!
But, in return for these risks, there's another thing that my darkness drags in!
Women are very sweet at times like this, Tsuru-chan.
Well, I mean...
It's quiet.
Get away! Get away from Zoro, you dumbass!
Ace, tell them the name of your father.
But it's almost unnatural.
It's Longarm Tribe!
Z-Z-Zoro-san! Zoro-san's been hit by a beam!
Vortex!
What?!
The gravity of the darkness will pull in Devil Fruit eaters...
Kizaru?!
Be careful! That man is a navy admiral!
Father? Why is that important now?
No! Help me!
Admiral?!
The gravity?!
Now you can have a nice, long rest...
Alright, let's do it!
Do you wanna get hurt?!
My father is Whitebeard.
Give us back the girl!
No!
...And my body will...
Yes, he is! Whitebeard is my only father!
Zoro!
Quit messing with us, jerks!
Let my daughter go!
We'll give you hell!
We looked for you with our eyes wide open at that time.
Hey! He shoots beams, too! This ain't good! Do something!
There they come!
How's this? You get it already, don't you?
Everyone, battle stations!
At that distance, the beams'll kill him!
Because we heard that there might be a child of that man on some island.
Ace!
Huh?!
Oh no! Zoro's in trouble!
No way!
Based on a small amount of reliable information from Cipher Pol,
No! Help me!
H-Hey, you! Stop that!
Take this!
Um, do you see that they're taking the young lady?
They appeared so suddenly! Where did they get in?
we checked all newborns...
Yes!
Take this!
Put a curse on them now!
...and preborn children...
Damn! What's going on?! Why can't I hit him!
I beg you!
...and their mothers but we couldn't find you.
Huh? I mean, we got to help her now!
Satan-sama!
I-I can't even stab him! Hold on! What should we do?!
No wonder.
Your mother risked her life to bear you.
Take this! Dammit!
Move your foot!
It's the vast fleet of pirate ships!
T-They took her!
She used a trick that can be called mother's pride.
But why weren't they doing anything...
Where's Whitebeard? Look for him!
You haven't been hit by somebody for long time, have you?
Move it aside!
...though someone was taking their friend or family?!
Bohemian Knight Doma!
It's no use; I ate the Glint-Glint Fruit, you see.
Ace.
"Thunder Lord" McGuy!
Why didn't they try to fight and take her back?!
That has misled us... Indeed, the whole world.
I think that you got it when I grabbed you!
DeCalvan Brothers!
I'm made of light. I'm a Logia.
Satan-sama!
Whirl Spider Squad!
They're all big-time captains who are well known in the New World!
I beg you! Please give them punishment!
Made of light?!
Another thing that my darkness drags in is...
There is an island called Batelira in the South Blue.
This can't be for real! He's going to die!
...Devil Fruit powers!
We beg you!
Zoro! Run!
43 ships in total! We can't find Whitebeard or the commanders!
Your mother's name is Portgaz D. Rouge.
That means as long as I touch them, Devil Fruit eaters can't use any of their powers!
Veinte Fleurs!
They're really dependent on other people!
But they're all allies of Whitebeard!
She did something that completely defied natural law...
Ace-chan, can you see us?
Logia, Zoan, Paramecia...
But that young lady is a victim! She doesn't deserve that!
...for the love of her child.
We're here for you, Ace!
All the Devil Fruit eaters in this world who put too much confidence in their powers...
She kept her baby inside her womb for 20 months!
I won't let you move, either. It's no use.
Alright! I owe you for the place to stay and all the panties I saw so I'll do it!
...can't protect themselves from my striking power!
Don't panic! So pathetic!
Yeah!
No way.
Now you will die.
Then I won't let you touch me!
I didn't expect them to come!
And as soon as she gave birth to you,
Vortex!
--Shall we attack?
--Not yet.
Satan! Satan!
she lost all of her strength and passed away right there.
Whitebeard should be somewhere near, too.
St. Elmo's Fire!
Satan! Satan!
And he must be up to something so keep an eye on the sea!
Ace!
A year and 3 months after the father's death,
Satan!
"Luffy-san and everybody!"
This is fun!
the child was born with the blood of the world's most heinous man in his veins.
I'm getting excited! Just come on, Whitebeard!
"Right now, I'm surrounded by a lot of underwear-- and am being called Satan-sama."
"I'm sorry but could you wait a little?"
That was you!
"I owe them and if I don't pay them back, it'll spoil my skeleton-hood!"
Nothing can compete against darkness.
You know it, surely?
"So give me some time."
Even your strength.
"As soon as I finish this, I'll get to wherever you are!"
You're getting involved in this...
But your power is such a valuable one.
...Dark King Rayleigh?!
Ace! You got to join my crew!
No way!
They can't blame a child whose not born.
Old guy!
Don't be plucking these young sprouts!
Garp!
Their era is just about to begin!
If I yield to power, there's no point in being born a man.
Look after my child!
Where is he?
It's been almost an hour since we left Impel down.-- If the wind is right,
I think he'll appear from where we least expect.
Your father is...
I'll never leave anything to be regretted later in my life!
we should have reached to Navy Headquarters already!
Well I guess if Whitebeard is on the move, it can't be helped!
Maybe we got the wrong lineup.
Do you understand, stupid?
...the King of the Pirates -
Aren't we moving too slowly?
This world is worthless if you can't survive.
Gold Roger!
I don't wanna get there after everything has finished!
And the extreme emissary of justice -
What a shame, Ace!
Die in the darkness!
Crocodile!
Admiral Akainu!
The Navy is not the one that will beat Whitebeard! I am!
--I see a shadow in the bay!
--No way!
Flame Commandment!
You still feel that way?
I can beat you first if you want!
The Navy's greatest powers - the three admirals!
Flame Emperor!
I get it now! They got all their ships...
The Seven Warlords of the Sea!
...coated and approached from underwater!
"Fire Fist" Ace is a son of Gold Roger?!
The sun or the darkness - there'll be only one winner!
This formidable lineup stands in the way of Luffy who is heading to Marineford!
I'm gonna make Whitebeard the king!
This is huge news.
It's 3 hours to the execution. We'll take the criminal to the scaffold.
Call the head office! Let's issue an extra!
Luffy-kun!
Does it continue?
I'm on my way! Wait for me!
Here comes Moby Dick!
Still?
Ace!
It's time.
The bloodline of the King of the Pirates?!
Fifty battleships and one hundred thousand marines.
The Moby Dick emerges right in the middle of Marineford.
The secret of Ace's origin has been revealed.
Luffy and the others continue
sailing on the Tarai Current.
Three hours before Ace's exectution at the Navy HQ,
The Seven Warlords of the Sea and the three admirals, Akainu, Aokiji and Kizaru.
His father Roger's feelings, and his mother
Rouge's strong resolve lay behind it all.
all seven Warlords assemble and await Whitebeard's arrival.
On its deck, Whitebeard and his 14 commanders are ready for battle.
It won't be long before they reach Marineford.
Luffy watches the Vivre Card
to make sure Ace is still safe,
At the same time, the three Admirals gather...
The Whitebeard Pirates head straight for Ace.
When the world's greatest powers have gathered,
At Marineford, Whitebeard's fleet silently approaches.
There is an unbroken bond between them an Ace, a family bond!
Tension keeps rising before the inevitable battle!
Fleet Admiral Sengoku reveals the shocking truth!
whiel he reminisces over his past with his brother.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Special Retrospective Before Marineford! The Three Navy Admirals Come Together!"
"A Special Retrospective Before Marineford!
The Vow of the Brotherhood!"
"A Vast Fleet Appears! Here Come the Whitebeard Pirates!"
"Ticking Down to the Time of Battle! The Navy's Strongest Lineup in Position!"
"The Beginning of the War! Ace and Whitebeard's Past!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!