Horo-horo-horo-horo-horo...
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the
Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way
to the New World,
will speed along the
Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy is headed to the Navy Headquarters in order to rescue his brother, Ace!
Meanwhile,  the rest of the Straw Hats are...
"The Friends' Whereabouts! A Huge Tomb and the Panty Debt!"
"Gloom Island
Ruins of the Muggy Kingdom"
Meanwhile, a short time ago,
Zoro who was forced to stay with Perona was...
This is no good! I got to hurry!
Where did he go?! That stupid swordsman!
"A Few Hours Ago"
Dammit!
Where's the room that I was sleeping in?!
Is this building a maze?!
This way?!
What am I doing?
I thought that it'd be fun to use Negative Hollow
to make him depressed when he finds his sword
so I told him where his sword was but that was 2 days ago already...
He can't find it no matter how many hints I give!
Why're you here?! You use your Devil Fruit power again?!
What are you saying?! Don't accuse me!
You're the one who kept losing your way!
If you climb the stairs behind us, all the hallways lead directly to the room!
How can you get lost?!
Shut up! You're not clear enough!
It's not my fault at all!
You're a fantasista, huh?
It's that way!
How can you mishear me so badly?!
I didn't realize you were that pathetic without your sword!
It's so heartbreaking just to look at you now!
How sad!
You put me in this situation!
Good things will happen to you someday!
Fight!
Leave me alone!
You can have it back.
Why're you doing this?
It doesn't mean anything.
Even if you have your sword, you can't attack me because I'm a replica.
Nothing can harm this body.
So a swordsman like you poses no threat to me!
Plus, I don't want any servants who are not cute!
I'm not giving it back for no reason!
If I use him, I can go back to Thriller Bark!
Seems like he's empty-headed so I can easily handle him!
I'll use him as I please,
toy with him and leave him on this island at the end!
That's not so bad!
What?!
Oh no! I let him get away!
Where did he go?! That stupid swordsman!
I wonder how Luffy and the others are doing!
I gotta go back to Sabaody Archipelago!
I hope that they're okay!
Everyone focus on escaping!
As we are now, we can't beat these guys!
I can't just stay here doing nothing!
There he is!
I think I know that castle... or not...
I know!
It looks like the other castle! How confusing!
Do you really think so?! I'm sick of your sense of direction!
I can't believe how nice I am!
I don't have to guide him to the sea.
But it's okay! I'll take advantage of him wisely!
Is this the right way?
You have no right to ask me that!
I checked it!
Just shut up and follow me!
Alright.
Augh! What did I just say?!
Huh? Oh, it's that way.
It's this way, you stupid swordsman!
Huh?!
Why can't you even follow me?!
You have to lead the way properly!
Is it my fault?!
It's exhausting just staying with him.
What's the matter?
You got tired even though you're flying?
Huh?! It's your fault!
Why?
Never mind! I'll get sick just by talking to you.
This tree looks familiar!
Shut up!
What was that?!
Maybe somebody else has been sent here!
I gotta go and check!
Hey, what're you going?
I don't need a toy like you that is just annoying and boring!
Wander on this island forever!
Who is it? I want somebody cute this time!
Hey, what took you so long?
What?!
W-W-Why are you here?!
Why? I thought that the sea was this way.
Y-You're really a fantasista!
I can't believe this!
This guy's really something... probably?
That tree must've been cut down recently!
How disappointing! It was just a tree falling down?
Nobody has been sent so that means...
...I have to settle for him for now?!
But I love the depressing atmosphere after a war!
It's so enchanting!
Maybe some restless evil spirits did that!
I doubt it.
Hey, where are you going? Hey!
Is this a...
...Tomb?
Who made this?!
It has carved out from a big tree. It took great skill!
It's very big!
Again! Somebody is here as I thought!
So fast!
What?! It bounced off!
Hey! Look at that!
You bastards!
"Lazy Bones Island
The Land of Poverty - Hungeria"
This is Lazy Bones Island
the land of poverty "Hungeria."
Brook was mistaken as Satan, the king of devils-- by its residents.
What a clear morning!
Luffy-san...
I wonder if they are all looking at the sun like this...
Yes, I'm sure they are!
Because whatever happens, the sun will always rise!
And if I can stay alive,
I will see them again!
Well, come to think of it, this island is very deserted!
And I didn't notice yesterday but inside that building,
there was an altar and dolls for some kind of rituals,
uncanny tapestries and posters on the wall,
and macabre-looking mural decorations.
And those things on the floor - are they tools for voodoo or something?
When I think about it, it's kind of weird!
Have you awoken?
We were just going to visit your room bringing breakfast.
Is that for me?
Yes, of course!
How generous you people are! You don't even know me!
Oops! I haven't introduced myself yet.
I'm the head of this country Pekkori.
Pekkori-san! Well then, I gratefully accept the food.
Young lady.
Could I look at your panties?
Panties! Hurry and show him your underwear!
Oh no no, um... I don't need to see the guys' underwear!
You don't need to hesitate! Enjoy it as much as you want!
What is that?! Augh!
Thank you for the big meal!
I'm so full that I can barely move!
Actually, I don't have a stomach to be full!
That's our one-week-worth of food!
Be patient for now!
Well, Satan-sama, did you say that you wanted to ask us a favor?
I want to set sail right away! So I need a ship!
N-No! Have we done something that made you upset?
No.
Hey, everybody! Show your underwear for his dessert!
Enough with the underwear! Wow!
You don't like underwear anymore?
No, that's not the point.
I have to get back to my friends at any cost!
Get back?
Yes.
A-At any cost?!
Yes, I feel bad because I've been treated so nicely.
We're over!
If underwear won't do it, there's nothing we can do to keep you here!
It's the end of this country!
It's come to this, we have no choice but to take our lives...
W-W-Wait a minute! Please relax!
What?!
Well, it seems like you have a story there.
That's why you call me Satan and...
...you said something about Longarm Tribe last night.
Why don't you tell me about it?
This country has been overrun by the Longarm Tribe for too long.
Not only money and goods and food...
...but they also take men and women in their prime from us.
And as you see, our country is devastated
and suffering extreme poverty!
Then, those meal were...
I'm ashamed to say this but we made them from what little food we had.
No way!
In order to get out of the situation,
we kept praying to all the gods and goddesses.
Not only that but we have invited famous psychics from around the world...
...to curse our enemies to death!
But when it didn't work, we resorted to black magic
and finally, we got you, Satan-sama - the king of devils, to be summoned here!
Satan-sama! You're our one and only hope!
Please deal the Longarm Tribe a bloody blow!
--We beg you!
M-Me?!
Yes! Will you please curse them to death for us?!
--Satan-sama!
Well, I mean...
It's Longarm Tribe!
What?!
No! Help me!
Do you wanna get hurt?!
Give us back the girl!
Quit messing with us, jerks!
Let my daughter go!
We'll give you hell!
Huh?!
No! Help me!
Um, do you see that they're taking the young lady?
Yes!
Put a curse on them now!
I beg you!
Huh? I mean, we got to help her now!
Satan-sama!
T-They took her!
But why weren't they doing anything...
...though someone was taking their friend or family?!
Why didn't they try to fight and take her back?!
Satan-sama!
I beg you! Please give them punishment!
We beg you!
They're really dependent on other people!
But that young lady is a victim! She doesn't deserve that!
Alright! I owe you for the place to stay and all the panties I saw so I'll do it!
Yeah!
Satan! Satan!
Satan!
"Luffy-san and everybody!"
"Right now, I'm surrounded by a lot of underwear-- and am being called Satan-sama."
"I'm sorry but could you wait a little?"
"I owe them and if I don't pay them back, it'll spoil my skeleton-hood!"
"So give me some time."
"As soon as I finish this, I'll get to wherever you are!"
It's been almost an hour since we left Impel down.-- If the wind is right,
we should have reached to Navy Headquarters already!
Aren't we moving too slowly?
I don't wanna get there after everything has finished!
Crocodile!
The Navy is not the one that will beat Whitebeard! I am!
You still feel that way?
I can beat you first if you want!
Luffy-kun!
I'm on my way! Wait for me!
Ace!
Luffy and the others continue
sailing on the Tarai Current.
It won't be long before they reach Marineford.
Luffy watches the Vivre Card
to make sure Ace is still safe,
whiel he reminisces over his past with his brother.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Special Retrospective Before Marineford!
The Vow of the Brotherhood!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!