Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the
Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way
to the New World,
will speed along the
Grand Line again today!
Couldn't eat another bite!
--Look, my stomach is bulging!
--It's the Navy's food and drinks!
I can't believe that I was thinking "I'll never get out!"
All thanks to...
...Captain Buggy! Thank you!
No problem! No problem!
So, how's it going, Jimbei?
Hm?
Don't hm me, you jerk!
I'm asking you when we will get to Navy HQ so I can conquer the world!
That attitude really gets me!
I can't stop shaking!
The Seven Warlords who sold their souls to the Government
and the 3 navy admirals are no match for us!
That's right!
You should be the next King of the Pirates because you're following in the wake of Roger!
"A Special Retrospective Before Marineford! The Three Navy Admirals Come Together!"
Meanwhile, at Navy Headquarters in Marineford...
May I come in?
Everybody, it's time. We need you to come to the harbor with us.
Without "First Son of the Sea" Jimbei who is with Luffy
and Marshall D. Teech who has burst into Impel Down,
4 of The Seven Warlords are about to leave Marie Jois.
In addition, Boa Hancock is here waiting as well
after her stopover at Impel Down.
4 of these 5 have had dealings with the Straw Hats in the past.
Whitebeard is just a man but you people are beside yourselves with fear.
We still have 3 hours before the execution.
Yes, that's true but we need to be prepared for any contingency.
Bartholomew Kuma!
Ursus Shock!
So, you're still alive, Roronoa...
If you were to take a trip, where would you want to go?
I will protect you, even if it costs me my life!
Damn it!
Luffy... Help m--
Robin!
Luffy!
We will never meet again.
Farewell...
You look so eager to do it.
You're so uncouth.
Dracule Mihawk AKA "Hawk-Eye" Mihawk!
Is it possible... that's...
...Hawk-Eye...!
I came out to sea to meet you.
What's your goal?
To become the strongest!
How foolish...
Tiger...
...Trap!
Kid! State your name.
Roronoa Zoro.
I'll remember it, strong one. I haven't seen any one like you in a while...
As a swordsman's courtesy, I'll sink you using the world's strongest black sword.
Three Swords Style Secret Technique!
Fall!
Three Thousand Worlds!
What are you...?
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame...
Admirable!
Zoro!!
Don't live so hastily, young man.
Don't worry. I didn't kill that man.
It's still too early for you to die. My name is Dracule Mihawk!
Learn about yourself! Learn about the world! And become strong!
No matter how many years it takes,
I will hold this seat of the strongest and wait for you.
Surpass this sword! Try to surpass me! Roronoa Zoro!
I don't want to get behind!
Being able to steal shadows and corpses of strong men in the world as I please,
it'll be a great war for me!
Gecko Moria!
Now, all the shadows in Thriller Bark,
empower me!
Shadows Asgard!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Rocket!
Brick Bat!
Black Box!
He got me!
Break into pieces!
This is...
...a baptism for you!
Doflamingo-dono and Hancock-dono, please hurry.
I know. Don't call my name so casually!
Boa Hancock!
For being charmed by me, your guilty consciences...
...will turn your bodies solid!
Love-Love Beam!
Hanco--!
You piss me off!
Big Sis! Stay strong!
This can't be! No man exists that won't be my slave!
I cannot stand that man's existence!
Medusa Hair...
...Eight-Headed Serpent!
...Salamander!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
...Gatling!
Ouch! Hot!
That man!
You'd rather die than let people see this, right?!
So don't move!
Luffy! Please be safe!
This is the only one who has never met Luffy or the others.
Don Quixote Doflamingo!
Please! Don't do this anymore! Why're you doing this?!
Because I don't need any punks to work under me, kids.
Augh! Damn! My body is hardening!
Don't do this! Have mercy on me!
No!
O-One more chance...
Give me just one more chance.
I... We will follow you!
Such an eager underling! Don't make me cry.
However, I don't need you to follow me.
Doflamingo!
The day is coming! So hurry and prepare!
For a world where only true pirates can survive!
The powerless should flee!
The unstoppable swell of the new era of daring men is coming!
His capability is still unknown.
Also, at the Navy Headquarters,
under the command of Fleet Admiral Sengoku...
You're here! It's time, Aokiji-san!
Oh, it's time for lunch already?
Admiral Aokiji!
Ice Age!
The ocean turns... to ice!
This is what a navy admiral can do.
You got good friends! But you can't change yourself, Nico Robin!
You're wrong! I'm not...
Robin! Look out! Run!
You!
Stop screaming. If you defrost her right, she'll live.
But her body's fragile now so be careful.
If you break her, she'll die. For example...
...if you crush her like this!
No!
T-That was close!
--Yeah!
--You did it, Usopp!
What's going on here?
Usopp! Chopper! Just run to the ship!
Treat her and help her!
G-Got it!
We won't let you...
Wait, guys!
Stand aside. I wanna fight him man-to-man.
Let's sort this out--me and you!
No problem but since there's no ship to take you into custody,
I'll kill you all one by one.
Gum-Gum...
...Storm!
Ice Time!
Not lunch! What are you talking about?!
It's the execution of Portgaz D. Ace...
Yeah, I know. Don't get so uptight.
Please hurry!
Summoning us at lunchtime? So you guys really want to boss us around, huh?
Admiral Kizaru!
Zoro!
Wh-What?! Who are you?!
Get away! Get away from Zoro, you dumbass!
Z-Z-Zoro-san! Zoro-san's been hit by a beam!
Kizaru?!
Be careful! That man is a navy admiral!
Admiral?!
Now you can have a nice, long rest...
Zoro!
Hey! He shoots beams, too! This ain't good! Do something!
At that distance, the beams'll kill him!
Oh no! Zoro's in trouble!
H-Hey, you! Stop that!
Take this!
Damn! What's going on?! Why can't I hit him!
I-I can't even stab him! Hold on! What should we do?!
Take this! Dammit!
Move your foot!
Move it aside!
It's no use; I ate the Glint-Glint Fruit, you see.
I'm made of light. I'm a Logia.
Made of light?!
This can't be for real! He's going to die!
Zoro! Run!
Veinte Fleurs!
I won't let you move, either. It's no use.
Now you will die.
You're getting involved in this...
...Dark King Rayleigh?!
Old guy!
Don't be plucking these young sprouts!
Their era is just about to begin!
Well I guess if Whitebeard is on the move, it can't be helped!
And the extreme emissary of justice -
Admiral Akainu!
The Navy's greatest powers - the three admirals!
The Seven Warlords of the Sea!
This formidable lineup stands in the way of Luffy who is heading to Marineford!
It's 3 hours to the execution. We'll take the criminal to the scaffold.
It's time.
Fifty battleships and one hundred thousand marines.
The Seven Warlords of the Sea and the three admirals, Akainu, Aokiji and Kizaru.
When the world's greatest powers have gathered,
Fleet Admiral Sengoku reveals the shocking truth!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Ticking Down to the Time of Battle! The Navy's Strongest Lineup in Position!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!