Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
these things will never cease to be!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
and set out in search
of something to find
That racing passion makes you shine
ONE PIECE!
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
Compasses only cause delays
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
I'm really, really stuck on you
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
and pretend it isn't there!
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
I don't really need
everything to add up
and set out in search
of something to find
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
Believe In Wonderland!
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wow! What a huge town!
What a huge town!
Don't be stupid! You'll lose your arm!
Its sharpness is the real deal!
The place used to be full of pirates
on their way to the Grand Line.
Raise the anchor!
I'm gonna go get some equipment!
It has everything you could ever need!
Looks like I can get some nice
ingredients in a town this big.
Alright! I'm gonna go get equipment
Nice women, too!
I got something I wanna buy, too.
for our upcoming great adventure!
I'll take it.
Oh? How're you gonna do that, Zoro?
Find Luffy! He's gotta be hiding
somewhere in Loguetown still!
Looks like I can get
some good ingredients here.
--Alright! I'm gonna check
out the execution platform!
--Huh?
Set the sails!
Good women, too!
--Die!
--Yeah!
I got something I wanna buy, too.
Yes, sir!
There's no need.
--Bring the ship forward!
--You idiot!
Oh? How are you gonna do that?
You're flat broke, as I recall!
--Don't shake things, Sanji!
--Full speed ahead to the Grand Line!
He will show himself to me again.
Thanks! I flashily thought
I was a goner there!
Shut up. If you're scared, then go
down and sleep like a good li'l boy.
Alright! I'm gonna check
out the execution platform!
The execution platform!
There's no need to thank me.
Huh?
I wanna see the view the King
of the Pirates saw before he died!
I'm gonna see where the King
of the Pirates was executed!
D-D-Don't be stupid!
Of course I'm not scared!
You're Buggy the Clown, right?
--Glasses... Glasses...
--Hey. Are these them?
I wanna see it now!
--Sanji! Breakfast!
--Yeah, yeah!
How do you know that?! Who are you?
Hey, wait! We still haven't
decided where to meet up at!
I'll get started on it. Hold on.
I'm looking for a certain man.
Man, that guy...
Sorry to bother you!
But... which way is
the execution platform?
What do you say?
Will you team up with me?
Pay me back for those!
Perfect timing! Do you know how
to get to the execution platform?
The King of the Pirates was
born here and died here!
Good morning, Nami-san!
Good morning, Sanji-kun.
"Usopp vs. Daddy the Parent;
Showdown at High Noon"
Follow the smoke.
He might've even walked
down this very street!
"The Wait is Over!
The Return of Captain Buggy!"
Hey. Hey, Zoro. Let's play tag.
Yahoo!
Let's have a toast!
To the Eternal King of the Pirates!
Huh?!
Captain Smoker!
What, what?! Tag?!
Let's play, let's play!
Is this man named Luffy
really still on this island?!
Are you guys stupid?!
You're pathetic, playing at your age!
We need to hurry and blockade the sea!
"The Town of the Beginning and End;
Landfall at Loguetown"
To where are we headed, Buggy?
That won't be necessary.
What?! I smell like I farted?!
To the Eternal King of the Pirates!
How can you be so easygoing?!
I'm gonna get some more
sleep before breakfast.
--Stop!
--Hey! You can't come in here!
No!
That Straw Hat...
Oh?! 'Cause you
don't like losing, huh?!
--How's this?
--Oh! You look wonderful, Miss!
That's the navy captain's room!
It was Monkey D. Luffy!
F-First, we need to find my crew...
What did you say?!
I don't give a damn about that!
--How's this?
--You look so elegant, Miss!
--Elemental, Miss!
--See! You're suddenly mad!
--What?!
I wonder where they are now,
and what they're up to...
--How's this?
--Electrical!
--Heya, Smoker.
--So it's you, Daddy...
The place where the
greatest pirate in history died...
Hold it, you guys!
--How's this?
--Elegy!
But it's the truth, isn't it?! Bleehhh!
Gum-Gum... Bazooka!
Will you be purchasing all of these?
Stop right there!
No, I don't want 'em.
And the place where
the pirate age began...
These are Two-Pistol Pete and
the Police-Killer Riley Brothers.
I want something that's rougher.
Retreat for now, men!
I'm gonna see the view the King
of the Pirates saw before he died!
Come again!
Does that mean you'll
join our crew now?!
All three have bounties, huh?
Everyone! Run away on your own!
But I'm only teaming up
with you, just so you know!
Oh! A top-quality aperitif!
I also dropped one off at the morgue.
Alright! Time to go up!
Wait for us!
Always remember that!
Oh! Two Poinderine
champagne-like beauties!
I just need your signature
and I can get my money today.
--I'm over here! Come get me!
--C'mon, Zoro! Chase me, too!
"Kitetsu III and Yubashiri! Zoro's New
Swords and the Woman Sergeant Major"
The whole town is brimming with
the finest ingredients around!
One million Berries for four people?
These are all small fries...
Is everyone here?!
I'm not playing here!
Are the people who got off
the ship with you all back?!
Damn, I can't decide
what to go after first!
Wanted men headed for the
Grand Line gather in this town.
Nami-san! Your meal's ready!
Yes!
Captain Smoker!
Where are you going?!
Hey, guys! Food's on!
I can earn money
more efficiently this way,
--Yes.
I just found the main dish!
Yeah!
The execution platform.
rather than looking high
and low for just one big name.
Yep!
Hold it! I'm not done with you!
Captain Buggy isn't...
Captain Buggy isn't here!
I wanna see the place where
the King of the Pirates died!
"Love-Love Pirates"
One of the Navy's most gifted snipers,
reduced to bullying weaklings.
Even after he said all that...
Awesome! What is this place?!
Everything here is a collector's dream!
He will be there!
Huh? What, Nami-san?
How you've fallen...
No, it's nothing!
You mean the Monkey D. Luffy?!
I just don't feel like putting
my life in my guns' hands.
Welcome!
Whew, I'm hungry!
We can mobilize
100 men immediately, sir!
Everything here once belonged to pirates
Food! Food! Food!
Because if you die, your
daughter'll wind up on the street?
who returned alive from the Grand Line!
Captain Buggy!
And the entire battalion afterward!
This looks yum!
You guys just don't get it.
Give Carol my regards.
They are especially valuable goods.
Say, what do you suppose
happened to Buggy after that?
Yeah. I'll tell her the
old smoky man said hello.
I'm more than enough on my own.
Then these are all items that went
on adventures in the Grand Line?!
Who knows how long
it's been since then...
Buggy? Oh, that Buggy?
That was Daddy Masterson,
the bounty hunter?
Or even where
Captain Buggy flew off to?
That's absolutely correct!
Who knows? Maybe he's
at the bottom of the ocean.
Yeah. We joined at
the same time, long ago.
We only do business
with warriors of the sea here,
What's going to happen to us?
What's the future of the Buggy Pirates?
Man, that's dangerous...
He was an elite, on the fast track
to being a key player at Navy HQ.
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
so we warmly welcome
gentlemen such as yourself!
Pirates are a stubborn lot,
every last one of 'em.
Hey.
Then why is he doing this now?
What do you say? This was the
favorite gun of the Gold Roger!
Yeah?
This was all because of that girl
thief named Nami or whatever!
Hey, boy.
You're the one who kept
chasing me stubbornly! Oww...
What do you want?
I'm busy right now!
What?! Gold Roger's?!
Roronoa Zoro... I will take
your head by my own hand!
Are you the guy with the
biggest bounty in the East Blue?
A cursed sword, huh?
Yes!
I hunted pirates for years. I can tell.
How about it, sir?
Interesting.
I'm Luffy. Do you need something?
S-Show me more!
Oh! That's a cool sword you have!
Thanks! Come again!
Zoro! Did you finally catch cold
after always sleeping on deck?
Not that it matters,
but your food's gone, Usopp.
I'm Captain Smoker of the Navy.
I'm in charge of Loguetown.
Damn! Don't scare me like that!
What're you doing here, Zoro?
--Here you are, Nami-san!
--Luffy!
--A Special Yogurt Dessert!
--You stole my food again!
I've never gotten sick
before, only injured.
You're under arrest.
--No, what're you doing here?
--Me?
Huh? Arrest? Forget it!
--Oh! Thank you, Sanji-kun!
--Give it back, you idiot!
Come to think of it,
I've never had a headache myself...
I'm lost.
Why're you acting cocky about that?!
I'm just about to go into the Grand
Line and be King of the Pirates!
--Hey, tell me.
--Hey! There he is!
Captain Smoker! Terrible news!
Is someone out there talkin'
about me being a master swordsman?
--How do I get to the execution platform?
--It's him! That bastard!
King of the Pirates?
I refuse to get arrested
in a place like this!
Alright!
Ah, I see. Wait!
A message from Headquarters!
Then you'll have to beat me first.
They've received word that a
Monkey D. Luffy and his pirate crew
I've finally finished my flashy raft!
You don't get into the Grand
Line unless you can beat me.
are headed here, to Loguetown!
Someone's talking about me!
Just you watch!
He just earned a 30 million
Berry bounty in the East Blue!
I, the great and world-renowned
pirate, Buggy the Clown-sama...
That's the rule of this town.
Honestly! Being a hottie is punishment!
That's assuming you're brave
enough to fight me, of course.
Someone's always talking about you...
30 million...
That's worthy of congratulation.
...will get my crew back together
and get my super flashy revenge!
I can't get into the Grand
Line unless I beat you?
He's an incredibly evil villain
Whoa!
who even defeated Don Krieg
and Arlong the fishman!
Then I'll beat you!
No matter what obstacles lie in my path!
Quiet!
--What's that?
--You bastard!
Go ahead and try.
How dare you sell our
buddies to the Navy?!
The score must be settled!
Gum-Gum...
You're gonna pay big-time!
You damn flashy
rubber man! Just you wait!
Damn your shouting.
You made it fall apart.
Die!
He's made out of rubber?!
I absolutely will beat you senseless
and make you cry uncle!
Darn it! My legs are tangled!
I'm sorry, sir!
It's not good to be tense.
I got my own pace I do things at.
Captain Buggy!
Just what the hell are you doing?!
I'm not doing this 'cause
I wanna! It's my legs...!
Isn't that right?
I always felt he was a cold-hearted,
horrible captain when he was well,
Go! Set sail!
Y-Yes, sir!
I'm unstuck!
but now I realize he was a bold
and open-hearted pirate-like pirate!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
So... What, now?
Too slow!
Right! A pirate group!
Stuff like this already?!
When I look back, we were allowed
to ravage to our hearts' content
Word has it they may
show up in town today, yes!
I refuse to lose! Damn you!
Someone as pathetic as you,
worth 30 million Berries?
only because we had
Captain Buggy's backing!
Run on home and have your
mama bake you a cake, kiddo.
What're you so flustered for?
I don't even need to use
my Devil Fruit power.
Have any pirates who've set
foot into this town ever escaped
My fists are more than enough!
Today, let's give the greatest and
flashiest funeral for Captain Buggy!
"Chase Straw Hat!
Little Buggy's Big Adventure"
Here I come!
since I took charge here?
N-No, sir...
That old guy's cool!
Then calm the hell down.
You're gonna screw up my pace.
I think that man might be...
Captain... Rest in peace!
Yes, sir...
...Daddy the Parent.
Please leave the rest
to me, Acrobat Cabaji,
22 years ago, I saw his execution.
Reporting, sir! We have word that
pirates have appeared at the port!
I managed to make it...
to the next island...
the Buggy Pirates' Number Two
and Chief of Staff!
I bought a lot! A real lot!
His proud final moments were
worthy of the King of the Pirates...
Please go there at once!
I promise to rebuild the Buggy Pirates!
It must be Luffy's group!
They've definitely set foot into town!
Now my preparations to be a brave
warrior of the sea are complete!
Hold it!
30 million, huh? I pray he
puts up at least a bit of a fight.
All I'm forgetting now is...
You, King of the Pirates?
Don't make me laugh!
--Cabaji!
--W-What?!
Damn it! Don't scare me like that!
Oh, yeah! I forgot
the most important thing!
You can't even enter the Grand Line!
Sir?
It's only natural for Captain
Buggy's successor to be me,
Just talking to myself. Forget it.
Goggles!
A top-class sniper needs
to have top-class goggles!
There's no point in getting back up.
I'm not some kind of exhibit, dammit!
That's just basic! The most basic of all!
You're not going to look at this?!
Beast Tamer Mohji-sama,
the vice-captain!
Investing every last bit of money
to get the best goggles around
"Justice"
There's no way to
know that unless I try!
is the spirit of a top-class sniper!
Why, you...! Are you mocking me?!
I'm the captain! You can stay
vice-captain for the rest of your life!
Captain! Please give
each unit their orders!
Goggles! Goggles!
You got some real guts, ridiculing me!
No need.
Here goes! Gum-Gum...
But you need to
consider how powerful he is!
...Whip!
I'm gonna eatcha!
You're annoying me.
U-Uh oh!
Don't tell me what to do!
I was just feeling hungry, too!
You've made me mad!
You're done for now!
My apologies, sir!
These ones! These goggles!
It's gotta be these! I like 'em!
Hey, guys!
Never mind that. Where's Tashigi?
We're gonna decide who gets to
be captain by seeing who's stronger!
I really messed that up!
I'm gonna eat you flashily,
so just give yourself up!
Y-Yes. She mentioned she
would be gone this morning,
Lady!
You got a good eye! Them's the
latest North Blue model there!
Fine by me!
but that she'd show up for training.
What's with that boy?
I got 'em from an import ship that
leaves the Navy only once a year!
That dumb girl.
Where the hell'd she go?
Chop-Chop Cannon!
Yay! A triple-scoop ice cream!
There you are,
my beloved mademoiselle!
What's wrong? You got no money?
Mohji! Mohji! Mohji!
Hold on, now!
You'll drop them if you run!
I don't do business with
people who don't got money!
Huh?
What's it gonna be?!
N-No, it's...
Cabaji! Cabaji! Cabaji!
My damn mistake.
Please come again...
Oh! Right! Backpack, backpack...
Quit your flailing!
Just accept your fate!
I'll take these goggles, please!
Huh?
Mohji! Mohji!
Man, was she beautiful...
My! What a cute little girl!
Cabaji! Cabaji!
Yes, yes! You're in luck!
C-Captain Smoker!
Mohji! Mohji!
This is the only pair
of these goggles in town!
Cabaji! Cabaji!
M-My ice cream...
I-I'm very sorry about my daughter!
--Thank you!
--Sure!
Hold it right there!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I was the first to--!
Huh?!
Sorry! I'm sorry!
Acrobat Technique: Monkey Showman!
--Oh! I'll take this, too!
--Thank you, sir!
Butt out... old man!
Sorry 'bout that.
My pants ate your ice cream.
O...
Secret Technique:
Candid Camera Police Trio!
Forgive me!
Here, buy yourself five scoops.
What are they doing?
Old man?
Murder at the Open-Air Steam Bath!
--Let's go.
--Yes, sir!
Stop! Stop right there, you!
T-Thank you!
Listen! Let's set the record
straight! I am not an old man!
Thanks!
Die...
Call me "Mister"! Got it?
Mohji!
Huh?! What for?! You're an old man!
Dammit, you said it again!
Loot everything there is!
Don't leave a single potato behind!
C'mon! C'mon!
That's what you think!
Gimme those goggles back!
I found 'em first!
My plan is flawless!
Huh?!
I knew it. The cards say that
detestable runt is already in this town.
I, Gally the Crescent-sama,
will use these vital food supplies
You got a problem?! Huh?!
on my way to becoming
King of the Pirates!
Keep up yer damn complainin'
and I'll call the marines!
The time for revenge
has flashily come at last!
Hand it all over thankfully!
M-Marines?
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Yep! I'm friends with
a navy captain in this town!
So? Do you successfully take his life?
Hey.
Who's in charge here?
The old smoky man!
Obviously.
What do you want?!
W-Who is this girl?
So you're Monkey D. Luffy?
The one who dies is...
I caught him!
So you don't know who I am, huh?!
I got caught?! Huh?!
Oh. It's you!
I'll test you and see if you're
worthy of setting foot into my town.
I'm Great Captain Usopp! I destroyed
Arlong's fishman pirate group!
Bonk!
How did things turn out this way?!
Looks like I'll just have to fight
you until your body falls apart!
It was truly a battle to the death!
Stop! Stop! No!
Don't give me your crap!
Me, surrounded by 200--
no, 300 fishmen!
Is this the end already?! This sucks!
Yeah. A man-to-man fight.
I'll take you down with these two fists!
All alone, I punched, threw, stomped,
kicked, and tore them all up!
Get 'im!
Captain! W-We just saw--!
Thanks to that, I now have a
30 million Berry bounty on my head!
I see. 30 million...
Captain Smoker?
Yep! That's right!
Yeah. He's one of the toughest
guys from Navy Headquarters.
--Papa!
--Papa?! Why am I your papa?!
Mohji! Mohji!
Why, you...! Am I that bad-tasting?!
This town used to be a hangout
for pirates headed for the Grand Line.
Cabaji! Cabaji!
I sure flew a long way...
Here's a present for you, Papa!
Mohji! Mohji!
What was with that guy?
That's a little bit of a shock!
But ever since he took over, every
single pirate who's come into town
Cabaji! Cabaji!
Happy birthday!
Now what do I do?
Oh, Carol...
has wound up in the slammer.
Hey, look! A hermit crab!
Guess I'll sleep for now!
I wonder when he got on
board. At Nami's village?
What a nice, angelic girl you are!
I love you, Carol-chan!
His strength is extraordinary.
He's a monster.
--Hey, are you okay?
--Do you suppose he's dead?
They even say he has
Devil Fruit powers...
Probably. That, or maybe
at Usopp's village?
Papa! I love you, Papa!
You think?
W-What's with this family?
If so, that's incredible!
Devil Fruit powers?!
That'd mean he's been
traveling with us this whole time!
Where exactly are we going?!
But guess what! That old man there
is trying to swipe your present!
Dammit! Why does this happen to me?!
You broke my glasses.
Incredible, Captain! You captured
Luffy's crew in no time flat!
Now, now! You mustn't say "swipe"!
I told you.
I'll pay you back... somehow.
--Did you just say something?
--Huh? Me? I didn't say anything.
Are your eyes just for decoration?
This guy obviously isn't Luffy.
It's not good manners, you know.
--Yeah! You got 'im!
--Ooh! So close!
You don't look like you
would have any money!
Eh?
Nuh-uh.
Are you the one who's
bullying my adorable Carol?
The world'd be ending if this
shabby fly were worth 30 million.
That's weird. Must've
been my imagination.
Something about you just seems off!
--Hey, Luffy! Quit slackin' off!
--Oh! Sorry! Sorry!
T-True, I don't have any money, but...
T-Then, where is Luffy?
B-B-Bullying...?
He'll show up soon enough.
The fun is just getting started.
Those wrinkles between your eyes!
--That's not all!
--Huh?
That look of having
eaten nothing for days!
Huh?
Do you have a sick mother?!
You have a bounty of
30 million Berries, I hear?
How did I wind up at the port? How?
Did your wife run out on you and
leave you with five babies to nurse?!
Let's see here...
Hey!
Are those the new wanted posters?
There we go...
L-Look, you!
Is he one of these guys?
Yeah, I got 'em from
the outpost just now...
I won't ask for details!
Just come with me!
I don't know. I don't think so...
Where am I now?
600,000... 1,300,000... 700,000...
Perfect timing! Do you know how
to get to the execution platform?
The execution platform?
T-The navy?
Leave!
Damn you... J-Just give up already...
30 million... Straw Hat Luffy?
I got lost on my way...
I've never seen you around before.
A starting bounty at this amount...
Yeah! I just landed on this island!
Who's there?!
Here.
N-No, you give up already...
Hold it, boy.
I am this island's protective god!
The cleaning man just quit his job.
This town sure is huge!
It's way different from Fusha Village!
Y-Y-Yes?!
Leave this island at once
if you value your life!
I'm going to be captain!
No, you see, sir!
If you work for the navy, you'll
never need to worry about money!
Why are you looking for
the execution platform?
I'm obviously not the person
on that poster! I was just lying!
Protective god?!
Shut up!
I wanna see the place where
the King of the Pirates died!
Hey, you! You're one of those, uhh...
You're a very lucky person!
My funny plan to trick people was
a great success! Ha ha! Well, bye!
Screw that! Why should
I work for the navy?!
...weird creatures!
You're just going to run off?!
You're insulting a person's kindness!
That's you, isn't it?
You don't know where? Aww...
I'm gonna kick your ass, you moron!
T-T-That's right!
It sure is! That's me, all right!
Wait. Follow the smoke.
Listen! Just try taking
another step into the forest!
Maybe your poor spirit's more of
an issue than your money problem?!
But I'll tell you this!
Just you try and lay a hand on me!
The instant you do, will you
receive my divine punishment
Oh! That way?! Thanks!
My captain Luffy won't sit by quietly!
and meet your doom?!
Look, you!
He's an evil,
cold-blooded, devilish man!
Sergeant Major! It's time for training!
How should I know, you flashy idiot?!
Why're you asking me?!
Bye! Please work hard, okay?
No one's ever defied him
and lived to tell about it!
Damn, these are expensive!
Too expensive!
Sergeant Major?!
You got a kid, right?
You should really value your life...
What are these things?
Lend you money? Sure!
I bought a lot!
Maybe I'll hit another store!
I see. That sounds bad.
The animals of this forest.
But including interest, you'll hafta
pay me 300% of what you borrow!
Don't mess with them,
unless you want to die!
Yes, given that this Luffy
fellow is worth 30 million Berries,
Oh? These are some
flashily interesting animals...
I can't afford to borrow
any more from that girl...
The navy?
he's clearly no ordinary man.
Papa! You're obviously
way stronger, Papa!
But I can't go into the Grand Line
stuck with just one sword...
Dammit, how'd I get stuck doing this?!
Yes! Our Captain Richie!
I told you not to go any further!
Zoro's... working for the navy?
You're the strongest guy in the world!
--What do I do?
-- "Monster"?! How rude!
Carol. It's all right.
Just pretend you didn't see anything...
Blast it! He suddenly shot at me!
All that matters is that I make
enough money to live happily with you.
Aww, shut up! Our boss is
behind bars all thanks to him!
Damn! I missed!
Damn it!
I'm gettin' nowhere like this!
You're far more important to me
than being the world's greatest!
There you are!
Have you still not learned your lesson?!
Nope! We ain't happy
with things as they are!
Papa...
What is this?!
The guy's wimping out
after I said all that!
Gotcha!
We're gonna bring
your corpse to him to see!
--Come out!
--Oww! Oww! Oww!
Alright! In that case...!
Guess even three brushes is best!
Dammit! You have a Devil Fruit power!
Very well. I will fight you.
Well?! Now do you see
how terrifying I am?!
Take my advice! Just hand
those goggles over to me!
So what if I do?! You're nothing--
--You will, girlie?!
--Don't make us laugh!
Huh?!
You're--
Don't worry! I'll pay for 'em!
So just give 'em here!
Let me try again!
What can a girl possibly do?!
What are you?
--Die!
--Yeah!
Why're you saying that right after
he's just about to let you go--?!
Captain Richie!
You! What are you doing here?!
Are you a boxed and sheltered son?
--Papa?
--Then let's do this.
Yeah. I've been overly pampered
since I was just a little boy...
I knew it! You are Pirate Hunter Zoro!
I assume you have no problem
with us settling this in a fair fight?
Why the hell are you in here cleaning?!
Of course I'm not!
Don't do stupid gags!
--Fight?
--Here!
Intel has it you've teamed up
with Monkey D. Luffy's crew!
Damn you! Don't get cocky!
Fight? Y-You're not
talking about a duel, right?
I don't show mercy to anyone
who messes with them!
You're under arrest!
If you win, the goggles are yours.
--She did it!
--You're strong, lady!
Oh? You wanna fight me?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6... 30 pistols?!
You're amazing!
I commend your bravery,
but don't blame me after you die!
Well... now what?
D-Don't tell me you're...
Oww!
...Daddy the Parent?!
--I can't tell if she's strong or weak!
--Glasses! Glasses! Glasses!
The very same.
What happened here?!
It seems someone attacked them!
There's no trace of whoever did it!
--Glasses...
--Hey. Are these them?
Captain Richie! Captain Richie!
Our great captain!
S-Sorry to bother you!
With Captain Buggy now gone,
the most worthy of us to be captain
"For your glasses."
is Captain Richie!
Thank you!
Captain Richie! Our great captain!
--A showdown!
--There's gonna be a showdown!
--My glasses!
--I-I didn't mean to!
Captain Richie! Captain
Richie! Our great captain!
Daddy the Parent's
gonna duel somebody!
Those were expensive! How could
you do something so horrible?!
Did he say Daddy the Parent?
Captain Richie! Captain Richie!
Our great captain!...
I told you, I didn't mean to--!
Daddy the Parent is the
greatest gunslinger bounty hunter!
Pay me back for them!
Everyone in the East Blue knows that!
I wonder what the idiot who'd
challenge him to a duel looks like!
Man, that freaked me out...
Dammit! She looks
way too much like Kuina!
Not to mention she's
a swordsman, of all things...
Oh. Like that.
Good luck, Long-nose!
The world sure is a big place.
But I doubt I'll ever see her again.
Don't worry if he beats ya!
We already got a place dug for ya!
Gotcha!
H-How did things turn out
this way? Am I an idiot?!
Blast you!
The rules are simple. We both
walk 10 paces and then shoot.
Flying weapons are unfair!
Then what's this thing here?!
--Y-Yeah...
--What are you doing?!
Oh, man.
I'd like some swords.
Don't talk so selfishly!
Say your prayers!
Nami!
I was trying to get to
the execution platform,
Yes, yes! Welcome!
Have a look at anything you'd like!
Fighting Daddy the Parent
in a duel... Are you an idiot?!
but now I'm somewhere else completely.
S-Shut up! Things just turned
out this way! Shut up and watch!
Our shop's been in business
for 200 years, you see!
Oh, well. I'll get
there sooner or later.
You get one shot. Are you ready?
I got 100,000 Berries.
Sell me two swords.
Is it this way?
--Yeah.
--Yeah...
Let's see...
Eh? Two swords for 100,000 Berries?
Gold... Roger?
Damn, he has no money.
Chop-Chop Quick Escape!
50,000 a sword'll only
get you some dull blades.
One!
Oww!
Two!
I'll make do with whatever.
I just don't got any money.
--How dare you?! Blast it! Oww!
--How dare I what?! Huh?!
Three!
Who are you people?!
You'll make do with whatever?
Hmph! What an amateur!
Who gave you permission
to come onto this island?!
Four!
Five!
This is bad... Really bad...
You do realize this island belongs
to us, the Bear Claw Tribe, right?!
That sword on his waist!
Could it be?!
There's no way I can possibly
beat Daddy the Parent...
O-Oh, h-h-hold on. L-L-Lemme
see that sword of y-y-yours!
Six!
Do you work here, old guy?
Captain!
It said "Gold Roger"
on the sign outside...
Am I going to die here?!
This can't be happening!
I've had enough!
What're you all fidgety for?!
Don't move!
Is that this place's name?
Seven!
Oh? So you're these guys' captain, huh?
Too bad! Anyone who messes
with the animals has to pay!
J-Just let me see it!
Scram.
I just started my adventure!
Weirdo.
This ain't a place for a runt like you.
I haven't even gained any courage
or manliness or anything yet!
T-This really is it!
They're this island's treasure!
Amusing! Are you picking a fight?!
Besides, we're closed
for good as of today.
C-Calm down! This is your chance!
Eight!
It went under?
Those weird animals are treasures?
It didn't go under!
I'm shutting it down myself!
An absolute amateur waltzed
right in here with a legendary sword!
Bye, now!
Treasure refers to gold, silver,
and jewels, you flashy idiot!
Now get lost!
You need to act cool!
I was just curious about
the name, that's all.
Wow, that's not a bad sword!
Don't play stupid! You came to
this island to get these animals!
I'm lost. I was wanting
to go the execution platform...
What do you say? I'll buy this
from you for 200,000 Berries.
Can you tell me how to get there?
Then you'll have 300,000 Berries total!
Why would I do that?! I didn't
come here 'cause I wanted to!
What's that on your table?
You could get three good
swords at 100,000 apiece!
Oh! A skull?! It's huge!
Papa! You're amazing, Papa!
You're so cool!
You mean you're not a poacher?
Huh?! What're you talking about?!
Don't be stupid! I might not
look it, but I'm a great pirate!
A-Alright! I-I can make it
250,000! No, 300,000!
--Man, how pathetic.
--What a lame duel.
This is what became of a guy
once known as Killer Giant.
I'm Buggy the Clown-sama!
I'd never do anything as mean as that!
I thought he'd have more guts
than that. What a disappointment.
A villain who sent hundreds
of pirates to the afterlife.
500,000?
Pirate? You're a pirate?!
Look. Raise the price all
you want, this sword isn't--
I only shot his gun away.
Huh?
Alright, then! I'll buy it
from you for 650,000 Berries!
But Gold Roger sent him to
his grave with just one blow.
What's with you?!
Tryin' to cheat like that!
Me, too! I used to be a
pirate a long time ago!
You coward! Weakling!
Can't you even fight honestly?!
W-We surrender...
Fine, you damn professional!
How does 800,000 Berries sound?!
Oh, my bad! My bad!
So you're a pirate, too!
Gold Roger did?!
With truly lightning speed!
I-I'm sorry! Forgive me!
I'm just a lowly, pathetic man!
This guy was famous for the
absurdly huge blade he used,
Hello!
Did you finish polishing my Shigure?
Taking the life of someone like
me wouldn't gain you anything!
but their fight ended
in the blink of an eye!
Hey! Hey!
Right?! Right?!
Thank goodness! You're all right!
And this is the wound he received!
Couldn't you just peacefully let me go?
Someone went on a rampage
at the navy outpost earlier.
What is it?
--W-Wait!
--Nami!
But he was an infamous scoundrel himself!
You don't need to shout so loud;
I can hear you just fine.
Y-Yeah! If it's money you
want, she has tons of it!
You were gone too, so I was worried!
With his dying breath, he muttered,
Whadya think? Good, huh?!
It's my own unrefined sake!
"Roger... My hat's off to you...
--She's a royal-class dimwit...
--Thank goodness! What a relief...
Did you find something good?
Just please don't shoot me!
Please spare my life!
Yeah! That's my...
Yeah, this is the best! How many
days it's been since I last drank...
But the fact that you're
here safe and sound...
May you have honor
as the Eternal Pirate..."
Hold on, now!
Oh? So you're trying
to hide behind a woman?
...means you actually scoffed
at my kindness and ran off!
So awesome! So cool!
...super flashy
Buggy Pirates pirate ship!
You can have as many refills
as you want! Drink up and up!
In any case--!
Eric Down,
the man known as King...
Here's your money back.
No! Forget what I just said!
Silver Silver,
the world's greatest gunman...
But I'm really sorry about earlier!
She's just an innocent bystander
who has nothing to do with this!
I can't accept money from
someone who's heartless.
The giant Gowns Brothers...
What's with this big grave?!
Even if I wind up getting shot,
I can't let her get caught up in this!
Besides, I bought some new glasses!
I just assumed you were a poacher
who came to get these animals!
W-What?! I have a big nose?!
They were all tough men
who were as feared as demons.
--Usopp...
--Please! I beg you!
Who're you calling Big Nose?!
Eh?! Eh?! Are you talking about me?!
"Usopp..."
But for Gold Roger,
they were as weak as infants.
Is this sword the Wado Ichimonji?!
That was some horrible stuff you did!
Is your name Usopp, boy?
But it doesn't matter now!
I said grave! Grave!
It is the Wado Ichimonji!
Yeah.
Red?! Red, you say?!
Plus you let me have
this delicious booze, too!
It couldn't be...
Wado?!
Would ya like to hear more?
Do you know a man named
Yasopp of the Red-Haired Pirates?
You're saying I have a big, red nose?!
Don't say it! Don't say it!
Yeah!
Very few people these days
believe this story, you know...
What? My grave?!
What a beautiful straight temper line!
Yasopp? That's my old man's name.
The only things in this world that
interest me are treasure and alcohol!
I believe it's one of the 21
O-Wazamono swords!
That's okay! Just tell me!
Y-You've met my dad before?!
Took you long enough.
Hold your horses.
I'm likin' you even more!
You're a pirate, all right!
See! Look at this! It's worth
no less than 10 million Berries!
Gold Roger...
I see. So you are his son...
But who did this?! This is morbid!
In those days...
no, even still, I guess...
Papa?
Not to mention this is
an old wanted poster...
You're a real stout-hearted guy!
...he was the one and only man
who didn't fear the Grand Line.
But what are you doing
with such a legendary sword?
Tell me, why are you on this island?
Curse you! You just
had to blurt it all out!
Oh? There's someone
on the ground there...
Oh. I originally came here
in search of treasure, too.
Back then, the Grand Line
was an unknown area,
I'm suing for obstruction of business!
I've never once told a soul
what happened on that day...
Wha?!
O-Obstruction of business?
from which not a single boat ever
returned after being swallowed up.
What?! There's treasure on this island?!
Mohji! Cabaji!
What happened to you guys?!
I'm sorry! Did I say something wrong?
But you're an exception.
Calm down. If there was, I wouldn't
be hanging around here, either.
C-Captain Buggy...
It happened at a hot, dry
port town, much like this one.
You're here for your Shigure,
right?! I'm done polishing it!
It was a sea of evil that people
feared and which few approached!
O-Oh. You have a point.
I-It's so good to see you...
Take it and get the hell out!
Anyways, some stuff happened
and my crew left me behind.
Let's do it, Ensign Masterson!
We each get one shot!
So I've been calling this island
home for the past 20 years now.
I'm so glad you're all right!
Why did you run straight into those?!
Old man. Give me more rum.
The whole bottle'll do.
One! Two! Three!
I thought we'd never see you again!
I-I'm sorry.
I'm so happy, too!
That dumb girl saved you!
20 years?!
You sure are drinking happily, Roger.
You've really had it rough!
It's true, that sword's
so legendary it'd be a waste
But what on earth happened here?
for a guy who doesn't know
its value to walk around with it.
It's not so bad, really.
These guys are here with me.
Of course I am. I'm just about to take
a little stroll into the Grand Line.
All the swords in that barrel
are 50,000 Berries apiece!
Who did this to you?!
This way of life is actually pretty
nice once you get used to it!
Eh? We suddenly got
punched out of the blue, so...
Just take whatever two you want!
I'm excited beyond belief.
What's he so mad about?
I dunno. I'd much rather be living
the pirate life with my crew.
Embarrassingly enough,
we can't remember a thing...
You must really like swords,
carrying three of them around!
Whoa! You're going there?!
Into that sea of evil?!
--He won!
--Yasopp won!
What? Is there something
wrong with that?
Check it out! He beat one
of the Navy's best snipers!
That's almost like this one
bounty hunter out there!
The Bear Claw Tribe did this.
No, not exactly, but...
True, pirate life is nice! It's great!
Bounty hunter, huh?
That was truly a close fight!
He's famous! His name is Roronoa!
Take my advice.
Forget about going there.
You're the man, Yasopp!
Bear Claw Tribe?!
Even I would gladly risk my life to
go on treasure-hunting adventures!
I hear the name a lot.
Yeah.
No one's ever come back!
Yeah. If you're going to
save them, you'd better hurry.
Yes. He's a famous swordsman
all throughout the East Blue,
Yasopp! Finish him!
That's why I'm going.
Yeah! Killin' the loser of
a duel is a sign of kindness!
but he's a notorious person!
Bear Claw tribesmen are famous
for being food connoisseurs.
Right?! It's like, "Hurray for pirates!"
Now, then. Give me more rum.
A whole barrel'll do.
Using swords as bounty-hunting
tools is unforgivable!
What do you say? When I get my
pirate crew back, won't you join us?!
After saying that,
he drank the whole place dry,
Why is evil so strong in this era?
then set sail all too
casually the next morning.
All the famous sword masters
are pirates or bounty hunters...
Eh?!
I greatly welcome guys like you!
Kill me! Now that I've lost a duel,
I have no reason to live...
And almost all of the world's
legendary swords are in their hands.
After all, you have the pirate spirit!
When I heard he had conquered
the Grand Line a bit later,
Yeah. You've got good resolve.
It's a real shame...
Well? Whadya say?!
The captain says that lions taste bad!
I was more happy
than I was surprised--
You're... inviting me?!
I was more excited than
I should have been at my age!
I dunno, maybe everyone has
their own circumstances and stuff?
--We taste bad, too!
--I won't be very tasty at all!
What are you doing?
All jobs need to keep up
with the times somehow.
Your daughter?
--This guy tastes way better than me!
--Lies! Lies! He tastes much better!
And then, 22 years ago today,
Roger died on the execution platform.
I appreciate the thought,
but these guys are my friends.
Give it back...
A navy ensign of all people,
carefully treasuring something like this...
In any case, with my Shigure,
I'm too boney! I got nothing to eat!
I'm going to polish
my skills as a swordsman
She must be really spoiled.
Ever since that day, everyone
proud of their great strength
and someday gather
all the legendary swords
When you live with them for
20 years, they rub off on you,
Don't lecture me, you filthy pirate!
Don't worry! We're the Bear
Claw Tribe! We're iron chefs!
has tossed their hat
into the pirate ring.
that are in the hands of
criminals throughout the world!
That's fine by me!
It marked the beginning
of the Great Pirate Era!
even if they are weird creatures.
The 21 Top O-Wazamonos,
the 21 O-Wazamonos,
You were great, Yasopp!
Some wine and spices
will take your smell away!
I can't leave them now.
But now look! The town's full of
nothing but cowards and scum now!
It was nothin'.
and the 50 Ryo-Wazamonos...
The pain of this wound just goes
to show how inexperienced I am.
I'll risk my life for them!
You took on Daddy Masterson!
You won because you're you!
You gonna take this sword, too?
The Wado Ichimonji, was it?
What do we do with this food?
Men crazy enough to challenge that
sea of evil are all but gone now!
What? What's so funny?!
What are they?
I've never seen such
strange ingredients before.
We never would've stood a chance...
No, I was just
remembering a young pirate
That's why this bar is
closing down for good today.
Do we boil it with them?
No, it's not that I want
legendary swords...
Thanks, Boss!
I just hope it doesn't
give me stomach trouble...
who asked me to be a pirate
again just like you did.
I appreciate your watching
the duel without saying anything!
I'm going to the Grand Line, too!
I'm just saying I don't like
them being in criminals' hands!
Chop-Chop-Chop...
Huh?!
Gold Roger's so cool...
He's how a pirate should be!
...Chop-Chop-Chop-Chop...
Don't be so upset, old guy!
It's a good thing we came after 20 years!
This sword...
That's why I set out to sea.
That's the stuff!
You want some, Ensign?
I'm gonna go to the Grand Line,
get the One Piece,
That sword! I think it's...
30 years later and you
might've been dead!
and be King of the Pirates!
I thought so! Kitetsu III!
Family, huh?
Family's not so bad.
But I'm no good at it.
Straw Hat...
It's the Kitetsu III!
Its predecessor, the Kitetsu II,
is an O-Wazamono sword,
He was such an incredibly nice guy.
Huh?
I got a son of my own.
His name's Usopp.
and the Kitetsu I before that is
listed as a Top O-Wazamono sword!
I'm sure you and him'd be good friends!
Those're some mighty big words!
And in this bar, of all places!
Haven't seen him in years now.
I hit the high seas around
the time he was a toddler.
Mister! Is this sword
really 50,000 Berries?!
I see. So there are
youngsters out there like that...
I only said what I meant.
Why? Do you not love your son?
Y-Yeah...
Not me, though.
I ran into this one horrible kid!
Incredible! It's a respectable
Wazamono, you know!
Kiddo! If there're still
patrons like you out there,
It wasn't about that.
That one! You have to choose that one!
Assemble! Chop-Chop Parts!
maybe I'll hold off on closing this place!
A pirate flag...
Tadah!
It normally goes for one million Berries!
How should I know if there are?!
A Jolly Roger was calling for me.
Is that...?!
You're right!
Of course you wouldn't know!
Looking for these?!
You absolutely have to choose it!
You tell 'im, Yasopp!
My parts!
N-No! I can't sell it!
I haven't been in such
a good mood since then!
Yeah! Selling this for
50,000 Berries is clearly strange!
Way to go, thief!
Chop-Chop-Chop-Chop
Chop-Chop-Chop...
I'll treat you to a drink!
S-Stop!
Go flying, Buggy! Gum-Gum...
I don't drink alcohol.
Now, then...
No, that's not what I mean!
Flashily reassemble!
Right! Then have this!
There's nothing I can do for my son.
Let's have a toast!
To the Eternal King of the Pirates!
...Bazooka!
Just one hopeless
parent like me is too many!
And that's how I wound up
on a wandering journey...
A cursed sword, huh?
Always stay by your daughter's side.
You can't let her feel lonely.
Just thinking about it now
makes me boil with rage!
You knew?!
To the Eternal King of the Pirates!
Though I'm in no position to talk!
No. I can just tell.
I see. Sorry to hear what happened...
Starting with the very first one,
But it just goes to show there are
all kinds of youngsters out there.
all the Kitetsu have been superior
swords, but every last one is cursed!
I lost our duel!
Yasopp! Finish me off!
In any case, let's have fun tonight!
You?!
Many famous master
swordsmen have met tragic deaths
That's certainly a warm hello...
We don't want this
night to go to waste!
Don't give me your lousy sympathy!
...for a regular patron of yours.
Forget it!
after taking up Kitetsu swords.
Yeah, huh?
You navy guys might hang us by
our necks right after you catch us,
Cut the crap! You're tryin'
to shut the place down!
These days, there ain't a single
person who uses a Kitetsu.
I'm back!
--To pirates!
--And to us meeting!
but we pirates are free to let you
live or die however we please!
Because you'll leave this world
even if you use them unknowingly!
--Captain Buggy!
--What?!
It's wrong of you to
hold a grudge against me.
Cheers!
I only come here as a loyal customer.
So long!
Even I wanna get rid of that thing,
but I'm afraid it'll curse me...
It's the pirates' fault that
they're all cowards these days.
Sorry I took so long, men!
I-I'm sorry! I had no idea it
was such a terrifying sword!
Liven things up with
a super flashy Buggy Ball!
I should've minded my own business!
You had a customer? How rare.
Sorry for asking you
to help make a raft, too.
Not at all. It was my pleasure.
I'd like a drink of rum...
I like it! I'll take it!
So that's why a navy elite
turned to bounty-hunting...
There is no alcohol for you here!
A-Are you a fool?! I can't sell it!
So you're really going to stay?
Don't be so iron-hearted.
Today's a special day.
If you die because of it, then
it'd be like I killed you myself!
Yeah. With all my friends here.
Richie!
Papa! You lost to a pirate,
Papa?! He spared your life?!
You're the fool!
Just sell the stupid thing off!
Wouldn't you agree?
Say it isn't true, Papa!
I see...
Honey!
But that's amazing!
Your dad must be really skilled!
Alright! Take care of yourself!
Then let's do this.
You, too!
My luck, and this thing's curse...
Acrobat Technique:
Murder at the Steam Bath!
That's the stuff...
He even beat Daddy!
Let's see which one's stronger.
Plus he hadn't forgotten about you!
Even now, I remember that day clearly...
Let the beast-taming show begin!
Even now,
when he's living an adventure,
he has an image of you
etched in his memory!
How Roger looked at the very end...
Usopp?
You can't be serious!
Yeah. I can understand
how you'd feel...
Stop! Its sharpness is the real deal!
It'll take your whole arm off!
Farewell, friend! Take care!
This is Main Street!
Do you really think you can
hit me, Buggy the Clown-sama?!
No! That's not why...
That's not why I'm crying!
Did Gold Roger walk through here, too?!
Yes...
Would you normally do that?!
Yeah...
It was a humid afternoon,
just like today...
I hafta thank you all for
everything you did to my men!
Would you normally tell
some pathetic boy like me
You, too!
a story about you shamelessly
having your life spared?!
Here I flashily come!
His hands were shackled as
he was led down the main street
Set sail!
You told me that to give me courage!
toward the town square,
where the execution platform stood...
Chop-Chop Kick!
Yet, he walked like
a triumphant general.
Alright!
Most people would be vain
and keep a story like that secret!
You told me even though you
knew it'd make you less cool!
Buggy...
Chop-Chop Punch!
There are many strange
creatures in these waters.
Regardless of how brave my
old man might be! Right?!
Die flashily!
Be ever careful on your way!
Chop-Chop Rice Cracker!
Weaklings or cowards
could never do that!
I'll take it.
Carol! Your dad is
the bravest man alive!
Chop-Chop Festival!
Wait, I forgot to tell him that!
Hey. Could you choose me another one?
You can find strong guys any old place!
Chop-Chop Punch!
But I've never seen a man as
strong and kind as your dad before!
Chop-Chop Carnival!
S-Sure...
H-Hold it!
--H-He's doing this all for us!
--That's our captain!
I... I can't give in, either! I gotta
be brave, or I'll shame your dad!
R-Run, Buggy!
Wealth, fame, power...
Captain Buggy!
Ahh! Look out! Run! Get out of there!
Gold Roger had attained everything
the world has to offer...
The make is black lacquer...
Daddy! Give me a chance!
Fight me in another life-or-death match!
...and the blade's
temper pattern uneven!
Even though he was
walking toward death,
I won't cheat anymore!
I'm so glad you're all right!
he was literally
a king of great pride...
The Ryo-Wazamono "Yubashiri"!
W-What's that?
I've greatly pained you all,
my adorable underlings!
My shop may not be much,
but this is the finest sword I have!
Inherited will...
All right. This will be our real match.
Our pain is nothing at all!
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
I can't buy that. I already
told you, I got no money.
Choose the weapon
you're most skilled with.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
Forget the money. And I don't
need any for the Kitetsu, either.
these things will never cease to be.
Good. Now, then. Let's see...
Who're you calling a weird creature?!
I'm sorry for trying to cheat you earlier.
It's been a while since I've
seen a good swordsman's eyes.
All the hardships you had were
because of that damn Straw Hat!
They say the sword chooses the owner.
I pray for your good fortune!
Try and hit that weathervane.
Weathervane? That?!
Do you have any last words?!
Miss it, and...
Take this off for me.
It's itchy beyond belief.
Y-Yeah! You can shoot
me right through the heart!
Incidentally, who might this
pretty young woman be?
Pretty...
Usopp!
I can't do that!
I definitely feel more
relaxed with three swords.
Don't forget "really cute"!
Who's that?!
Do you think I would run away?
My life is on the line for real this time!
She's super pretty!
Y-Yes. I had been
wondering about that myself...
Oh, what's this?
You sure know how
to make a guy feel lonely.
I can't believe a big skinflint like
you gave the family treasure away!
Well, at least it looks like he's saved!
This nice woman saved
my life! Her name is...
What's wrong with one man
entrusting a dream to another?!
There's...
There's no way he can
shoot that far with that thing...
He had me sweating bullets there!
All right, let's get
this over with quickly.
U-Uhh...
Now take out the damn trash!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Umm, I'm sorry.
What was your name again?
I was so frightened...
that I still can't stand up...
In any case, take care of yourself!
Everyone! The Buggy
Pirates are back in action!
Thanks for the help! I flashily
thought I was a goner there!
What a nice nap!
Alright! Time to go
to the execution platform!
Captain! What is our first goal now?!
There's no need to thank me.
Hey, Pirate King!
J-Just like always...
You're Buggy the Clown, right?
The head of Monkey D. Luffy!
Where did you hide
all the treasure you found?!
Just shoot like you always do...
How do you know that?! Who are you?
Is it in the Grand Line?!
--Found him?!
--No, not yet!
You got it, didn't you?!
That legendary treasure!
I'm looking for a certain man.
Yeah...
Are you sure it was
Straw Hat you saw?!
You know him, right?
--Shut up, you!
--That great treasure!
Concentrate...
Damn rubber man!
Yes! We're sure!
Damn you! Someday, I will settle
the score with you! Just you wait!
Alright! Scour the place again!
The One Piece!
Yes, sir!
This is the guy you're looking for?
Man, where is the execution platform?
Straw Hat, Straw Hat...
Come. I have a meal ready.
I have no idea at all!
Where's the bastard hiding?!
My treasure?
Don't speak without permission!
If you want it, you can have it!
Where is it?
Hey. I think I see an island.
--Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
--Execution!
Eh? Really?!
I see. So that's why you helped me...
You see him?!
You missed!
Where's the execution platform?
What island is that?!
No, Papa! Don't shoot him! Papa!
--That way.
--Thanks!
--I just told you the other day!
--Huh?
That's right.
So, what do you say?
Will you team up with me?
I can't shoot him. Usopp shot
right through its crown!
So that's the island where Loguetown is!
That was...!
It's a pretty big town, right?
H-He really did!
Right through the crown!
Sure, why not?
We both have the same goal.
Yeah, that's what I hear!
Usopp!
Find Luffy! He's gotta be hiding
somewhere in Loguetown still!
Let's be friends.
Then it sounds like there might
be a market with fresh ingredients.
You're an excellent shot.
I'd expect no less of Yasopp's son.
That's great. Then cheers!
Never forget that bravery.
Yes, sir!
I'm hittin' up the weapon stores.
Someday you will
become like your father!
Cheers!
Being stuck with one sword doesn't
suit a Three Sword-Style user.
How many times do I have
to tell you not to shout?
He won't hide.
In that case, I guess I'll
check out some equipment shops!
Go to the Grand Line.
I'm certain Yasopp is there.
As long as I'm around,
he'll show up again.
Daddy...
Sanji... Food...
Captain Smoker!
Did something happen?!
That island is where Gold Roger
was born and then executed, right?
You're pretty good, old man!
You just ate... Gimme a break...
That's how it all began...
Aren't these...
Tashigi! Where the hell'd you go?!
It's okay! So long!
--Papa!
--Carol, you know that's not right.
Wow, you actually remember!
Shut up, you guys... I can't sleep...
Hey!
C-Captain! We have news!
A new wanted poster!
Put it up somewhere noticeable!
It's poor manners to say, "So long!"
It's you guys! Thank goodness!
You're conscious again!
The town where the
King of the Pirates died...
You sleep too much... Help out
with work sometimes... Sheesh...
Yeah! I'm sorry, Papa!
C-Captain Smoker!
Sorry for the rudeness, sir!
Also known as the city of
the beginning and end...
I-It was Roronoa Zoro...
I'm going to grow up to be a nice
lady worthy of being your daughter!
We were attacked by Zoro,
the pirate hunter!
So forgive me!
I'm amazed they can hold
conversations in their sleep.
You're already plenty
nice as you are now!
Zoro?
U-Umm...
Talk about skillful...
That Straw Hat...
Why would he attack you?
--I'm going to be an even nicer lady!
--Even when people say he's a
disgrace behind his back now,
Well, I guess I'll hit the hay, too!
It was Monkey D. Luffy!
he's fought all this time
to protect the one he loves.
Good night.
I'm going to be a
brave man like Daddy, too!
There it is...
He will show up.
I'm gonna become a real warrior
and stand before my dad someday!
So this is where the King
of the Pirates was executed...
I will make it to the
execution platform!
I'm certain of it!
The place where the
greatest pirate in history died...
I'm gonna get another look at
the view the King of the Pirates saw!
Sanji! I've been looking for you, Sanji!
The place where it began...
For ten years!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Oh, yeah! Buggy's
henchmen were neat, too!
They're saying there's
a cooking contest!
So this is the city where Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates, died!
Ahh! This is a town
for meeting pretty women!
Apparently, Usopp's
gonna be in a showdown!
Is he crazy?! There's no way
he can beat him! He'll die!
This place is filled with great
ingredients and beautiful girls!
Huh? Cooking techniques aren't
meant for competing against people!
Yeah, you mean like the
unicycle guy and the lion guy?
Pretty women, indeed...
We can't relax! The marines
here are supposedly tough!
--Think they got any bargain sales?!
--What are you, a housewife?
Who's "him"?
--Cabaji and Mohji, was it?
--He had animals, too?!
They're for delighting Nami-san!
The greatest gunslinger
bounty hunter there is.
Climbing the execution platform
and seeing the scenery comes first!
We just got here!
How about you?
Did you buy your swords?
Are they really pirates?!
Thanks, Sanji-kun!
Cool! Must be thanks
to the wanted poster!
--I want some swords, but...
--Do you have money?
That's the problem. In any case,
I gotta get me two more swords.
What? You're not gonna enter?
Who do you think is their captain now?
Hold on, Usopp! Where are you
going with all that stuff?!
You get that if you win, right?
Cabaji or Mohji, obviously.
I can lend you some at 300% interest!
Wait, that's... an elephant bluefin tuna!
Who knows? Maybe it's that lion!
Is he running away?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Kitetsu III and Yubashiri! Zoro's New
Swords and the Woman Sergeant Major"
"The Town of the Beginning and End;
Landfall at Loguetown"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Wait is Over!
The Return of Captain Buggy!"
"Usopp vs. Daddy the Parent;
Showdown at High Noon"
"Fiery Cooking Battle?
Sanji vs. the Beautiful Chef"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!