ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
The word "thank you" has faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
Am I getting stronger?
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
I don't know the answer yet
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
So let's go
saa yukou
Without stopping
tachidomaru koto naku
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
Because I don't want to lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
The voice inside of me
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
keeps sustaining me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
Wicked rain will get in my way
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
But I won't walk away
nigedasanai kara
So let's go
saa yukou
Without stopping
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
Because I don't want to lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
To the future I believe in...
shinjita sono saki e to...
The time is the
Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way
to the New World,
will speed along the
Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy is rushing to Navy HQ to rescue his brother, Ace,
who is waiting to be executed.
Ace.
The execution is in 3 hours.
All forces of the Navy are expecting an attack by the Whitebeard Pirates at Marineford.
Ace, tell them the name of your father.
My father is Whitebeard.
No!
Your mother's name is Portgaz D. Rouge.
A year and 3 months after the father's death,
the child was born with the blood of the world's most heinous man in his veins.
That was you!
Your father is...
...the King of the Pirates -
Gold Roger!
Does it continue?
Still?
The bloodline of the King of the Pirates?!
"A Vast Fleet Appears! Here Come the Whitebeard Pirates!"
I can't believe that the arch villain had a kid!
The legend of Gold Roger continues!
I'm so relieved that they got him!
If he's a son of the King of the Pirates, he must be atrocious!
If I'd caught him and put him up for auction, I would have made a fortune!
This execution is turning into quite a show!
So the strength of "Fire Fist" is in his blood.
Then, he has the One Piece, too?
"Fire Fist" is as good as dead anyway.
He will be wiped off the face of the earth soon.
"Navy"
He is not the biological brother of Luffy, then?
Roger's...
...Son?
His biological son alive! This must be a miracle!
All people connected to Roger should have been executed at that time!
Since his brother is Luffy-san, I thought that his father was Dragon, too!
I thought so, too! What's the deal here? They're not biological brothers?
Garp.
Can you believe this, Garp?
I'm expecting a baby.
Unfortunately, I won't be around by the time of the child's birth.
Why're you telling that to me a Navy officer, Roger?
The mother of the child--a woman related to you will be executed for sure!
That's why I'm telling you.
The Government will definitely dig up my whereabouts for the last year
and find and kill her.
But they can't blame a child whose not born.
Garp!
We've tried to kill each other dozens of times.
That's why I can trust you as I trust my friends.
You must protect my baby.
Stop being so selfish!
No, I'm sure that you'll do it!
Look after my child!
You sure that it's this island?
People saw Roger acting like he wasn't a pirate here.
As if he were a father.
Roger's era has ended. We have to cut the bloodline.
Find all the babies who are due within 10 months of his going to jail.
All pregnant women, too.
Kill all mothers who are suspicious.
5 were born in this month.
Ones who are due next month are...
Not yet.
Look into the ones with husbands, too. They could be fake.
She'll come back when she is cleared.
No. Not yet.
You can't come out yet.
I'm sorry.
Not yet.
Not yet. Not yet.
There're no more pregnant women.
It's been 10 months since Roger went to jail. I think he has not child.
So Roger's time is really over, huh?
Stop!
You're Portgaz D. Rouge, aren't you?
If it's a girl--Ann.
If it's a boy--Ace.
Those are the names that he picked.
So his name is Gol D. Ace.
Our son.
Ace.
--Rouge!
--Rouge! Stay with us!
You must raise him, Dadan!
No way!
Whose baby is this?
Dadan?!
Yes. You're gonna live with them from today.
No!
You gotta live with them! Be nice to them!
Because Luffy and I unfortunately have the blood of...
...the world's most infamous criminals in our veins anyway.
I took over the name "Portgaz" from my mother to whom I owe so much
but I never wanted to have my good-for-nothing father's blood.
Old man...
My only father is...
Whitebeard!
Garp.
It was 2 years ago.
You took over your mother's name and rose up in the world of the sea...
...as the captain of the Spade Pirates with your exquisite speed and power.
And that's when we noticed...
...that Roger's blood still flowed!
But Whitebeard also noticed that at the same time.
And to make you the next King of the Pirates,
he let the son of his old rival onto his ship.
No!
I got on the ship to make my dad the next King!
No one believes that except you.
In fact, it made it harder for us to catch you.
You were protected by Whitebeard.
If we let you go free, we know you'll use
your abilities to become the next King.
That's why it means a great deal to execute you here today.
Even if it means risking an all-out war with Whitebeard!
Fleet Admiral Sengoku! I have report!
The Gate of Justice is opening without any order.
And we can't make contact with the control room!
What?!
--It'd be nice if it opened with a hit!
--Oh, like "knock knock"...
You think that's all it'd take?!
It's opening!
What is going on?
The Gate of Justice opens on its own!
The Navy guy told us that they weren't gonna open the gate!
The control room must be in Marineford. Who is doing this?
There we go! A little more!
I know it because...
...out of joy, my blade bones are dancing the lambada!
There! There! There we go, there we go, there we go!
Ca-Captain Buggy, don't tell me...
There we go!
Don't tell me that you're opening it!
Are you a messenger of God?!
Is it true, Buggy?!
No, it's not! What kind of role play is this?!
But seriously. Who is opening it?
Well, maybe God really wants me to become the King of the Pirates!
Who cares! In any case...
...let's go!
It's quiet.
But it's almost unnatural.
Alright, let's do it!
There they come!
Everyone, battle stations!
They appeared so suddenly! Where did they get in?
It's the vast fleet of pirate ships!
Where's Whitebeard? Look for him!
Bohemian Knight Doma!
"Thunder Lord" McGuy!
DeCalvan Brothers!
Whirl Spider Squad!
They're all big-time captains who are well known in the New World!
43 ships in total! We can't find Whitebeard or the commanders!
But they're all allies of Whitebeard!
Ace-chan, can you see us?
We're here for you, Ace!
Don't panic! So pathetic!
I didn't expect them to come!
--Shall we attack?
--Not yet.
Whitebeard should be somewhere near, too.
And he must be up to something so keep an eye on the sea!
This is fun!
I'm getting excited! Just come on, Whitebeard!
No way!
Where is he?
I think he'll appear from where we least expect.
Maybe we got the wrong lineup.
--I see a shadow in the bay!
--No way!
I get it now! They got all their ships...
...coated and approached from underwater!
Here comes Moby Dick!
The Moby Dick emerges right in the middle of Marineford.
On its deck, Whitebeard and his 14 commanders are ready for battle.
The Whitebeard Pirates head straight for Ace.
There is an unbroken bond between them an Ace, a family bond!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Beginning of the War! Ace and Whitebeard's Past!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!