ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
Oh
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy is rushing to Navy HQ
to rescue his brother, Ace
to rescue his brother, Ace,
Luffy is rushing to Navy HQ
to rescue his brother, Ace!
who is about to be executed!
who will be executed in public!
who is waiting to be executed.
Meanwhile, at Marineford,
Meanwhile, the Whitebeard
Pirates storming Marineford...
Meanwhile, the world's
greatest pirate – Whitebeard
the great war between the Navy and
the Whitebeard Pirates has begun!
Meanwhile, at the Navy HQ,
with Ace's execution at hand,
has finally appeared...
...begin an all-out war with the Navy!
...at the Navy HQ in Marineford!
No way!
the Whitebeard Pirates suddenly appear!
Oars!
Yasakani Sacred Jewel!
I think he'll appear from
where we least expect.
You better tell me that my beloved son...
He cracked the air?
...is all right.
Maybe we got the wrong lineup.
Pops!
Finally, the war has begun!
Just a little more to get to Ace-kun!
I see a shadow in the bay!
I get it now!
A seaquake! He's distorting the sea!
I knew that you wouldn't let me...
I can hear the ground rumbling!
They got all their ships...
Now it's coming!
...coated and approached from underwater!
...strike your head that easily.
The seaquake that he set up before!
Doppelman!
Coming in the form of a tsunami!
Spiky Shadow Lizard!
I won't...
It's a tsunami!
What is he doing?!
Still some fight left in you?
Stop this if you can!
"Justice for the Winners!
Sengoku's Strategy in Action!"
You are too valuable to let die now, boy.
Here comes Moby Dick!
Ice Age!
If you still wanna run wild,
run as wild as you want
on the sea under my name.
If all three of us left our positions...
...who would cover them?!
What? Do you wanna fight?
Become my son!
Great Eruption!
I just want to figure
out the true distance...
"The Beginning of the War!
Ace and Whitebeard's Past!"
Screw you!
...between us and that man who
seems like right in front of us.
Why...
...do you people call him Pops?
Get away!
Because he calls us "sons."
See? This is how you kill a person!
We are all hated by the world.
No way!
There's more?
He lit up the place too brightly.
"An All-Consuming Inferno!!
Admiral Akainu's Power!"
Captain Oars!
So it makes us happy.
Damn you Warlord!
I know it's just a word.
But it still makes us happy.
Captain!
Th-There are 3 more Whitebeard Pirates ships!
Oars!
"The Force That Could Destroy the World!
The Power of the Tremor-Tremor Fruit!"
They've infiltrated the bay!
Ace-kun...
Oh no!
Why don't you light up birthday
cakes instead, you magma squirt!
Run!
Th-That's the...
...1st division commander--Marco!
Oars!
14 commanders--
Don't you want an illuminated
funeral for yourself, Whitebeard?
they're all here!
Pops!
"A Descendent of the Beast!
Little Oars Jr.--Full Speed Ahead!"
Ace-... kun...
That's a lie! Cut it out!
You told me not to go but I...
I'm the one who told you to go.
I didn't know that there are
such giant men in this world.
Ace-...
He's truly a beast!
He deflected the blow of
the world's greatest swordsman!
...kun...
I'm the one who told him to go.
It's been awhile, Sengoku.
Isn't that right, Marco?
Whitebeard.
Yes, that's what I heard.
You better tell me that my beloved son...
I'm sorry that we put you
through so much, Ace.
If I can have his dead body,
...is all right.
Everybody in this world knows.
that means I can have the
strongest zombie again!
What will happen to someone
who messes with...
H-H-He must be...!
...our crewmate!
I can't believe that
we let them get this close!
We won't let anybody who
hurts you get away with it, Ace!
...3rd division commander--Diamond Jozu!
Count on us! We will save you!
We made it through the gate but...
Get to the scaffold quick!
...what I'm concerned about is
whether your father is here or not.
The Giant unit is on the move!
Prepare yourselves, Navy HQ!
"Your?"
I don't think that Dragon
would let them kill his own son...
Oars!!
Oh, my dad and Ace's are not the same.
We brought this upon ourselves.
It's too late to say such a thing.
Don't be afraid!
My dad is Dragon
but Ace's dad is Gold Roger.
That's so hideous.
He got a great father but he never met him.
On this side, we, The Warlords,
the Navy's greatest powers--3 admirals
They are after Little Oars Jr.!
You better keep your wits about you!
He'd get mad every time I mentioned it.
and a hundred thousand elite soldiers!
Guys! Let's keep advancing!
It's our duty to...
Oh, I shouldn't have said that.
On that side, there are
the Whitebeard Pirates
...Stop him!
and more than 40 allied ships!
I'll create the most powerful
zombie soldier out of his corpse!
Fight them back!
Now, how do you wanna do it, Whitebeard?!
He's unbelievably big -
more than twice as big as a common Giant!
It's so exciting!
Keep shooting!
He's still a human-being
so it should work against him!
Give me a second, Ace.
Do you wanna be on the sideline as always?
Oars...
What fools!
I know that you just came to kill some time.
They want to break through from the front!
Your guard is down, Whitebeard!
So be it.
Artillery unit!
Pops!
Fire at the enemy ships
and approaching pirates!
There are rowdy men everywhere
and I can't stand it.
They brought such an unthinkably
powerful creature with them.
Yes, sir!
He is also a man but he is an exception.
Shoot him! Shoot him up!
I'm praying for you, Luffy!
Forward units, don't allow
them access to this plaza!
Oars, don't!
You're an easy target for them
since you're so huge!
Yes, sir!
Vice Admiral Lonz!
Ace-kun!
Wh-What is that?!
He cracked the air?
H-Hey!
Here I come!
What's wrong?
H-He beat the Giant -
the vice admiral of Navy so easily!
Where's that explosion coming from?!
Oh boy...
No good! The water surface is too high!
The water is receding!
What does it mean?
A seaquake! He's distorting the sea!
The commanders of the Whitebeards
are true to their reputation.
Oh no!
What's going on?!
The other side, too!
Stop him!
They are all pretty much like monsters.
This is the power of Whitebeard!
The ship is flying backwards!
Oars...
To finish this with minimum damage,
Is this for real?!
It was really smooth just two minutes ago!
we just have to cut off
their head nice and quick.
Why all of the sudden...
Climb Oars' body and advance!
Oars opened up a space
for us to get into the bay!
Oh no! My waterworks!
I'm heading out first!
Invade the bay!
INSIDE THE BAY OF MARINEFORD
We've gotta keep moving!
Take care, Ace!
What's going on here?
Yeah. See you, Luffy!
This must be...
Uh-huh!
I-It's bright!
I'll be a lot stronger when
I leave here in 3 years!
Damn! Fall back and tighten
the defensive line!
Wh-What is it?!
Don't let them get to the plaza!
You bet!
Ace!
I-It's Kizaru!
This is great!
Yasakani Sacred Jewel!
Doflamingo! How could you do that to Oars!
We'll show them how it's done!
F-Finally it stopped!
I'll make you pay at any cost!
Hey, that's so bright.
What was that all about?
That bastard! He became a pirate!
What's so funny?
We went back a good distance.
It's a pirate ship! I never seen their flag!
What's so funny?
This feeling that I'm in
the center of history!
I wonder when we can get
to Marineford like this.
This place is the turning point now!
Ow, ow, ow...
What are you talking about?!
This is a pirate whose become
very powerful rapidly recently.
That's our commander!
"D?" Where is he from?
Doflamingo can't do anything but run now!
Wh-What was it?
We can't quite figure that out
Hey, Jimbei!
but even as a rookie,
he has the power of Logia.
Can you hurry up? Please!
I gotta get there before Ace's execution!
Such a dashing young man in the Grand Line.
Wh-Where should we run?!
Don't worry, Luffy-kun. We'll make it!
He refused the offer to join the Warlords.
Stand back, Navy!
Okay.
He warded off the admiral's attack!
Hey, hey!
How long have they been at this?
What's that?
Don't get in my way!
They're still young.
How can you be so sure?
He's engulfed in a blue flame!
They shouldn't rush.
Roll-y roll-y.
Rear Admiral Yukimura,
the slayer of a thousand men!
You think your Fish-Man Karate can help?
R-Rear Admiral Yukimura!
Blue flame?
Are you serious, Captain?!
What are you doing?
Or are you gonna call out
whale sharks to help again?!
I have to see him...
You can't reach...
This is a battlefield!
We have no use for the unprepared!
..."Red-Haired" Shanks.
My power is not enough.
...the king...
Spade Pirates?
Then, who are you depending on?
...so easily!
He said we'll make it! So we'll make it!
The infamous super rookie
came to say hello to me?
"He said we'll make it! So we'll make it!"
So fearsome, these Whitebeard Pirates.
It's not what you're thinking.
Fine! Whatever!
My brother was always talking
about you as his lifesaver
What's with his body?!
That's nonsense.
I'm helpless!
so I came to say thank you.
I'm gonna take a nap.
He took Kizaru-san's attack
directly but didn't fall!
You're Luffy's brother?
I didn't know that he had a brother.
We can't stick around here any longer!
So he has this power as they say?!
Great, I'm glad to meet you!
It's even rarer than Logia.
What happened to your dream to
become the King, Captain Buggy?
Tell me all about yourself!
Let's have a banquet!
Zoan type--Mythical Creature.
I've never had to "look up"
to anyone before this!
Well...
Look! His wounds are disappearing!
If the time is right,
I'm sure that there'll be a miracle.
Me neither!
I can't! I can't! I can't!
So he's still talking about
becoming the King of the pirates?
I must reach Ace-kun!
I-I can't believe it! It didn't hurt him?!
I'm scared and I can't do anything!
But if it's too early,
then I'll just wait for the right timing.
Even those strong fighters
falling one after another!
I guess that's his favorite phrase.
Don't get in my way!
It did.
Y-You're gonna just give up?
I can't take this! A loser like me!
I'm not gonna let you go any further!
I'm disappointed in you!
I feel sorry for him because...
Can't you see it?!
I'm the one who'll become the next King.
Wait, Coby! I'm coming with you!
I mean, can't you see his
magnificent confidence?!
Yeah? You think?
Don't lie.
Get back to the battlefield!
First, I'll let the whole world
know the power I have.
No... It doesn't look like that to me.
Let me go! Please!
Oh? How'll you do that?
This is what they call "perfect composure!"
By beating the strongest man in this world!
Admiral Akainu! Why is he here?
He's got the regal presence
to become the King!
So he's the 1st division commander...
I'm scared of dying
You mean Whitebeard?
No matter what kind of attack he absorbs,
he recovers by flames...
and when I think about my family,
I feel weak at the knees!
Now that you mention it, I see it!
Please! I'm begging you! Please!
How great!
Hey, big guy, I wanna see the
guy who goes by Whitebeard.
Marco the Phoenix!
I can't see it at all...
I cannot introduce a sharp
young man like you to the old man!
We Navy soldiers are...
I have never seen a bird like that.
I know that miracles don't happen that often.
Vice Admiral Lacroix!
...fighting pirates with the "justice" of
the world emblazoned on our own backs!
Captain, that's Jimbei!
But there is nothing I can do but wait.
Oh, the Warlord?
Oars, he'll never change.
Dammit!
Anyone who turns tail and runs
cannot be called a Navy soldier.
Then I'd gain prestige if I beat him.
Brave men don't seek death!
I'm not on the crew of the Whitebeard Pirates
Pops, don't stop me!
but I owe him, so I'll fight you!
I would call him...
I just wanna save him!
...a speck of dirt!
How painful.
I just wanna save Ace-kun
as soon as possible!
Don't lie!
If you truly think about your family,
don't live in disgrace!
I know that.
It's been 5 days since they started fighting.
The tide has changed!
Everyone, help him!
We're going forward!
They're both gonna die!
Did you do something?
Give Oars cover!
N-No! He can't kill a man who's on our side!
I was just steering.
Admiral Sakazuki!
It's speeding up!
How can we defend against someone so huge?!
We are ready to proceed with the strategy.
Kizaru-san got blown away!
C-Could this be...?!
Good! The time has come!
I can't believe it! Kizaru-san!
Ouch! What? What happened?!
Ace!
Captain Buggy!
The miracle that  you were
talking about is about to happen!
You cut Vice Admiral Lacroix!
"The strategy?"
Ace!!
I knew that you wouldn't let me...
What is that?!
I don't think so.
...strike your head that easily.
Which one of you wants to kill me?
I don't know what's happening
but this is it! Go!
Do you see it, guys?!
I'm gonna fight you as you wish.
The time is calling me now!
You can't attack him alone!
We gotta do it together!
Saying "come and become the King!"
Giant unit, you better pay
attention to the sky, too.
Whitebeard Pirates!
You're so great! Like no other!
While Oars has you distracted,
we'll make our move against you!
I'm gonna fight you people single-handedly.
Yes, sir!
Yeah! Captain Buggy!
THE BAY HEAD OF MARINEFORD
Use the space that Oars opened up!
Great! It seems like we can make it!
Get into the bay!
Slave Arrow!
Guys!
H-Hey! Look at that!
Let's destroy the bay
head to open more space!
Flame Fence!
Here come the giants!
Captain!
Fire straight ahead!
Captain Ace, what are you doing?!
Attack their feet! Let's topple them!
Run, guys!
Wh-What a hell is that?!
H-Hey, you guys!
Captain!
All of you! Stand back!
So you're the Pirate Empress!
What's the matter?
Are you backing away after all?
Jozu!
Let my crew get way. Instead...
What power!
Damn! Not even a scratch!
My body's... cracking!
...I'm staying!
Leave it to me!
Perfume Femur!
You snot-nosed brat!
How cheeky you are!
Withdraw for now!
An ice cutter?!
That's "Ice Witch" Whitey Bay!
That was quite easy for us.
Alright, everyone! Let's go!
You bitch! You hit Navy soldiers, too!
Thanks!
I agreed to fight against Whitebeard but...
We must move into the bay, too!
They've quieted down all of the sudden.
Are they waiting for Whitebeard's command?
...I didn't say that I
will become a part of you.
I can hardly breathe!
Allies or foes--men are all the same.
What's the matter, 13th division
commander Water Buffalo Atmos?
So this is the guy who contended
for supremacy with him.
What is he doing?!
Except for him.
The water level is rising again!
Stop this if you can!
M-My body... What did you do, Doflamingo?!
Maybe just--"I have kept my word."
Commander Atmos!
I won't...
What?!
Don't! Stay away from me!
It's a block of ice!
Wh-What's that?!
It's gigantic!
--What's wrong?
--Now!
Still some fight left in you?
Have mercy on my beauty.
Commander!
No!
You are too valuable to let die now, boy.
Y-You!
Commander Atmos... Why?
I can hear the ground rumbling!
If you still wanna run wild,
run as wild as you want
on the sea under my name.
Now it's coming!
I can't control my body!
The seaquake that he set up before!
Don't do this, Doflamingo!
Coming in the form of tsunami!
Commander!
Ace-kun!
Become my son!
Screw you!
The Tremor-Tremor Fruit
made him a quake man!
Come on! Come on now!
Edward Newgate aka Whitebeard!
"Pirates are evil and the Navy is justice?"
Oars!
That has been rewritten
many times  in the past!
Look! What is that?!
It's a giant tsunami!
Values are different to kids
who don't know what peace is
Don't think that our superior forces
will guarantee us victory.
and kids who don't have
firsthand knowledge of war.
We could well fail.
The one who ends up on top will rewrite
what's right and what's wrong.
Because that man has...
This place is the turning point!
...the power to destroy the world!
"Justice will prevail?"
Damn! Those two...
Of course, it will!
It's beginning! The war!
They shouldn't leave their
positions like that.
Because the winners claim justice!
If all three of us left our positions...
Hey, you!
Let's go!
Hey!
...who would cover them?!
I'm the 4th division commander.
The invaders: a fleet of 47 ships
from the New World led by Whitebeard.
My name is Thatch.
If you're gonna join us,
Akainu-san!
They've broken through
the bay head at 2 points!
The defenders: the 2 greatest
forces of the Government--
we should become friends!
The bay will be flooded by allies
of the Whitebeard Pirates!
Shut up!
Navy HQ and The Seven Warlords.
Great Eruption!
So you're grumpy when you wake up?
No matter who wins and who loses,
Oh yeah, you wanna know what
happened after you passed out?
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
I'm gonna save you now!
the times will change!
No problem.
Your crew came to get you back
Oars...
Tsuru-san, let's put it into action.
so we beat the hell out of them.
THE BAY HEAD OF MARINEFORD
It's a suitable time.
But they're not dead.
They're on this ship, too.
Outta our way!
If not, you'll get more than a wound!
Outta our way, old bag!
Don't you have to put
me in cuffs or shackles?
I got washed!
Shackles? We don't need them!
I got hung!
But I feel so good!
Ace-kun!
You're a million years
too early to defeat me.
That gigantic block of ice disappeared...
Connect to all ships and soldiers!
Ring, ring, ring...
...into thin air!
No...
Ring, ring, ring...
Get away!
Volcanic rocks!
He's up to something.
It's a tsunami!
Hey! What are you doing?!
A resourceful admiral--"Buddha" Sengoku.
Too many of them!
Do you know what time it is?
Dammit!
Ursus Shock.
His name is Gol D. Ace.
What power!
He certainly is the legendary monster!
Guys, he fell overboard!
He can't swim.
Somebody, help him.
One of our ships has been hit!
He's been at it every day.
Get away from the ship!
How gutsy he is.
Must be more than 100 times now?
I guess.
This is like watching the end of the world!
Ice Age!
Aokiji!
You young squirt!
Why...
I-It's frozen!
...do you people call him Pops?
He lit up the place too brightly.
Th-That was close!
Because he calls us "sons."
Admiral Kuzan did it!
Partisan!
We are all hated by the world.
So it makes us happy.
Uh-oh.
Oars!
I know it's just a word.
Why don't you light up birthday
cakes instead, you magma squirt!
But it still makes us happy.
That's enough! Stop!
You can't reach me!
Don't you want an illuminated
funeral for yourself, Whitebeard?
Are you gonna keep doing this
after your life has been saved?
You got to make up your mind.
Old man!
You're not capable of killing him.
What are you doing here?
Disagree with the strategy?
It's either get off of this ship
and start over again...
No, they're pirates.
There're 3 more!
There's no room for pity!
...or stay here and...
Keep firing! Don't fall back!
Hey, Oars!
The whole bay is frozen!
Then...
Shut up!
The ships can't move now!
...wear the Whitebeard logo on your back!
I was just wondering...
It's no big deal.
W-We have the greatest force of the
Navy HQ--the admirals--on our side!
I just wanna be here.
Aren't you hot?
Th-That's right!
Because you're closer to the sun?
Are you Doma?
There's no reason to be
afraid of the Whitebeards!
Fire! Destroy the Moby Dick!
Stupid!
I'm hot.
Ace did it again!
I see.
Ace!
What's wrong with you, old man!
It'd be nice if you had some shade.
He made Doma and his crew
surrender  by himself!
"I wanna go out to sea?"
I won't let you at any cost!
You want me to command 2nd division?
Captain Oars!
Don't be bossy, you're not even my father.
It's been a vacant post for a
long time. If you took it...
Don't be afraid!
I don't have to listen to you, old man.
...Nobody would complain.
You better call me grandpa!
Get to the plaza!
Can he still move?
You're one of the originals, right?
Don't you mind it at all?
Old man.
Let's go!
You wanna get another fist of love?
That's great!
We've got a good foothold now!
He's got the toughness of his ancestor!
Show them what we're capable of!
I'm okay, don't worry.
Grandpa!
What's this?
I'm gonna be a lot stronger and...
I've got no such ambition.
...I wanna go out to sea with Ace!
Do it for us! Commander Ace!
I learned how to make it in the Wano Kingdom.
Ouch!
Stupid! I don't wanna hear it from you, too!
The commanders came out, too!
Try it on.
Don't stop firing!
Don't hit Luffy!
Stop the commanders!
Ace-san ruined two others before that one.
Shitty old man.
Shitty?!
Don't let them get ashore!
They burned up!
Hey, Ace! Come here!
Since his body's fire,
he shouldn't braid straw!
Sink the Moby Dick and kill Whitebeard!
Mount a counter-offensive!
Yes!
It's cool under here!
Listen, to be prepared for unexpected battle,
Yeah? That's good.
you got to eat to the fullest when you can!
Pops, you got a minute?
That's important for a Navy soldier!
Th-Th-They are pirates...
Both of you, keep that in mind!
And this is a real battlefield!
He must be the 5th division
commander - Flower Sword Vista!
Navy?! You can't just decide that for us!
Fire at Oars!
Well, that was surprising.
What?!
I didn't know that.
Oh no!
I'll become a pirate!
You'll join the Navy!
--Pirate! Pirate! Pirate! Pirate!
--Navy! Navy! Navy!
I feel weak at the knees
and I can barely move!
Your character is nothing like Roger's.
Yum-yum!
Stay alert, Tashigi!
He was your enemy, right?
Don't you wanna kick me out?
No! He ate everything!
It's impossible...
They're all mighty soldiers -
not just the commanders!
Oars!
It was good!
He shouldn't have gotten off his knees!
He's a ready target!
You said that it's important
but it's such a small matter.
We have nothing on these guys!
Don't forget it!
So quick!
I-I got it, Smoker-san!
I'm gonna become a pirate...
Don't you think so?
No matter who your father is,
we are all children of the sea.
Captain Oars! Why are you staying outside?
If Luffy becomes a Navy soldier,
It's nice to have ice in the water!
They are all monsters.
the food stock of his ship
will be gone within a day.
There's no role to play
for fledglings like us!
Because my blood is burning!
I don't get wet in the rain.
He would be a bigger
handful than the pirates!
Let's get away from here. Okay?
Let's shoot them up and invade the island!
This is very sturdy!
Ace will be our 2nd division commander!
Okay?
I love it!
But...
Are you nuts?
If we try to fight this battle,
It's not that easy, huh?
I have no pity for villains but...
You're a star, don't look dazed. Here!
we won't last even a second
and you know that!
I still... can't get to him!
Don't you wanna become an admiral?!
...family is a different story.
I'll become a Navy...
Here come the vice admirals of the Navy HQ!
...ad...
If I could...
It's so rare to see all of them
together at the same place!
...admiral someday!
Here!
...get one of The Seven Warlords at least!
You wanna fight me, right?
Then, of course you have to
become a big deal like that!
It's like when they have
the Buster Call. But...
What am I supposed to do?!
...when it comes to Pops and us,
it won't work that way!
Hey, the food's not leaving so don't rush.
And you're the star of this banquet so...
Tsuru-san, why don't you stand back?
D-Don't take this the wrong way!
That's why, that's why...
Ace, you fool!
Leave it up to us
Why didn't you lead your life as I said?!
...neither of us can die here!
and have some tea or something
from a comfortable distance.
He falls asleep!
Don't talk smart to me, fledglings!
Our place to die is still far away!
Whitebeard got a powerful newbie again.
What's the matter, beast?
There is no safe place even if
I back up to the end of the sea!
But I promised Luffy-san so...
My foot...
I heard that he's insanely strong!
Captain!
Captain, why are you staying outside, again?
Wh-What is it this time?!
Bring the ship to the ice gorge!
Ace.
The snow's not getting on my head.
You two should become strong Navy soldiers.
Trounce them all and get to the land!
2nd division come to cover us!
It's not cold!
Go!
Okay?
We'd be happy to give our lives for Pops!
Ace!
I really love this!
Thatch, you okay?
Yeah. Thank you!
Become a strong Navy soldier.
We're not scared of the Navy HQ!
Thank you, Ace-...
Let's go, Squard Pirates!
Your bounty will rise again!
Maybe.
Old man...
Here he comes!
Ace, I found something interesting.
It finally started!
Oh, is it a devil fruit?
What fun!
I don't know what fruit it is yet.
If you have your doubts at this final moment,
Oars!
I take no pity on even you, Garp.
If I had doubts,
I would've done something already!
Dracule Mihawk!
Is the Warlord on the move?!
Did you just hear that,
Helmeppo-san? Their strategy...
That's very unusual!
Yeah...
The capricious "Hawk-Eye"
seems like he's willing to fight.
They're gonna forget the schedule
and execute "Fire Fist" Ace.
Come on, Ace, just calm down!
Pops said that this is an exception.
If they do that...
What? Do you wanna fight?
You don't have to go after Teech!
What's that?
H-He must be a monster!
Let me go! I am his commander!
I just want to figure
out the true distance...
If I don't do anything about it,
Thatch's spirit can't rest!
He stepped into the plaza!
What's that?
...between us and that man who
seems like right in front of us.
Something's falling from the sky.
Get him! Get him!
Ace.
Is that a surprise attack
of the Whitebeards?!
It's okay. This is an exception.
Even very skilled soldiers would
tremble and freeze from fear
Break the artillery defense
of the Navy ships!
Just a little more...
I have a bad feeling about this.
just by looking into his eyes.
He is truly a "Hawk-Eye" as he is called.
He killed his crewmate and ran away!
Just a little more to get to Ace-kun!
I've always wanted to see him.
He had been beholden to you for decades
It's every swordsman's dream
to cross swords with him.
and then he threw dirt in your face!
Because he is assumed to be
the strongest in the world.
And above all, he disgraced my father's name
That's the instinct of swordsmen!
and I can't allow that.
Ace-kun!
Damn Doflamingo!
I said that you were doing it too much!
I'll take care of this!
He cut this guy's foot off!
So that's the Black Sword
that everybody's talking about.
It's because of his wink!
Nice! Get them!
I already claimed his body!
Is it my fault, Croco?!
Little Oars Jr.!
To be precise...
Doppelman!
Doesn't matter, we're gonna die!
...it's Black Sword "Night!"
Hey, wait! Come back, Ace!
It's frozen all over down there!
Get him!
It's one of the 12 highest
grade swords in the world.
Spiky Shadow Lizard!
Heehaw!
And its dark blade edge has an irregular
temper line and a double clove pattern.
Oars!
He must be a descendent of
the Continent Puller Oars.
It's a noted sword suitable
for the greatest swordsman.
He's big!
Oh! I'm a rubber man so I'll be fine!
He's way bigger than common Giants!
You just care about yourself?!
Don't let him invade the island!
Do something!
Is it over?
I don't wanna die like this!
It'll give them the advantage!
What caused that quake?
Somebody, stop me!
I shouldn't have listened to you, Straw Hat!
I didn't know that the descendant
of Oars was allied with Whitebeard!
"Hawk-Eye!"
Pops.
Dammit!
I'm gonna... save you now...
Everybody.
I want it!
I want his dead body!
I ignored your advice and took off!
Why didn't you just give up on me?!
I'm the one who caused all of this!
He makes me tingle!
No.
Ace!
Oars!
Ace-kun is a nice person!
I'm the one who told you to go.
I won't let him...
Son.
Ace-kun!
...die!
Oars laid his life on the
line to clear a path.
In the past, the Straw Hats suffered
at the hands of the beast, Oars.
Mihawk and Kizaru launch
their attacks on Whitebeard.
Luffy and his friends suddenly
appear out of the sky
All of the cast has assembled.
Whitebeard's tremendous
power brings a huge tsunami
and drop right in the
middle of the battlefield.
In response, the Whitebeard commanders
The Whitebeard Pirates
rush to the scaffolding,
Now, to save Ace, an ally
of the Whitebeard Pirates,
that threatens to swallow up
Luffy finally spots his brother, Ace,
fight back using their own powers.
all the brave men of Marineford, as
well as the peace and justice there.
but just when it looks like they
can rescue Ace from execution,
the descendant of Oars
breaks through to the bay.
and cries out to him.
As the unpredictable battle rages,
The final battle to save Ace begins now!
How will the Navy deal with
an attacker whose power
Admiral Akainu finally unleashes
his incredible power!
A battle crossing generations begins at last!
Sengoku is already formulating a new plan.
overwhelms even the Giants?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Justice for the Winners!
Sengoku's Strategy in Action!"
"The Force That Could Destroy the World!
The Power of the Tremor-Tremor Fruit!"
"Straw Hat Team Arrives!
Tension Grows at the Battlefield"
"An All-Consuming Inferno!!
Admiral Akainu's Power!"
"A Descendent of the Beast!
Little Oars Jr.--Full Speed Ahead!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!