ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
Oh
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy is rushing to Navy HQ
to rescue his brother, Ace
who is about to be executed!
Meanwhile, at Marineford,
the great war between the Navy and
the Whitebeard Pirates has begun!
Yasakani Sacred Jewel!
I knew that you wouldn't let me...
...strike your head that easily.
What is he doing?!
Stop this if you can!
If all three of us left our positions...
...who would cover them?!
Great Eruption!
Get away!
He lit up the place too brightly.
Why don't you light up birthday
cakes instead, you magma squirt!
Don't you want an illuminated
funeral for yourself, Whitebeard?
"A Descendent of the Beast!
Little Oars Jr.--Full Speed Ahead!"
I didn't know that there are
such giant men in this world.
He's truly a beast!
If I can have his dead body,
that means I can have the
strongest zombie again!
Get to the scaffold quick!
The Giant unit is on the move!
Don't be afraid!
They are after Little Oars Jr.!
It's our duty to...
...Stop him!
He's unbelievably big -
more than twice as big as a common Giant!
Keep shooting!
He's still a human-being
so it should work against him!
They brought such an unthinkably
powerful creature with them.
Shoot him! Shoot him up!
Oars, don't!
You're an easy target for them
since you're so huge!
Ace-kun!
Here I come!
Oh no!
Stop him!
Oars opened up a space
for us to get into the bay!
Invade the bay!
Damn! Fall back and tighten
the defensive line!
Don't let them get to the plaza!
Wh-Where should we run?!
Stand back, Navy!
Don't get in my way!
Rear Admiral Yukimura,
the slayer of a thousand men!
What are you doing?
This is a battlefield!
We have no use for the unprepared!
I'm helpless!
I've never had to "look up"
to anyone before this!
Me neither!
I must reach Ace-kun!
Don't get in my way!
I'm not gonna let you go any further!
Vice Admiral Lacroix!
Oars, he'll never change.
Brave men don't seek death!
Pops, don't stop me!
I just wanna save him!
I just wanna save Ace-kun
as soon as possible!
I know that.
Everyone, help him!
Give Oars cover!
How can we defend against someone so huge?!
You cut Vice Admiral Lacroix!
You can't attack him alone!
We gotta do it together!
While Oars has you distracted,
we'll make our move against you!
Slave Arrow!
H-Hey, you guys!
So you're the Pirate Empress!
My body's... cracking!
Perfume Femur!
You bitch! You hit Navy soldiers, too!
I agreed to fight against Whitebeard but...
...I didn't say that I
will become a part of you.
Allies or foes--men are all the same.
Except for him.
Maybe just--"I have kept my word."
What?!
Have mercy on my beauty.
Y-You!
Ace-kun!
Come on! Come on now!
Oars!
Hey, you!
I'm gonna save you now!
Oars...
Ace-kun!
Ursus Shock.
Oars!
That's enough! Stop!
You can't reach me!
Hey, Oars!
I was just wondering...
Aren't you hot?
Because you're closer to the sun?
I'm hot.
I see.
It'd be nice if you had some shade.
Captain Oars!
Can he still move?
That's great!
He's got the toughness of his ancestor!
What's this?
I learned how to make it in the Wano Kingdom.
Try it on.
Ace-san ruined two others before that one.
They burned up!
Since his body's fire,
he shouldn't braid straw!
It's cool under here!
Yeah? That's good.
Fire at Oars!
Oars!
He shouldn't have gotten off his knees!
He's a ready target!
Captain Oars! Why are you staying outside?
I don't get wet in the rain.
This is very sturdy!
I love it!
I still... can't get to him!
If I could...
...get one of The Seven Warlords at least!
What's the matter, beast?
My foot...
Captain!
Captain, why are you staying outside, again?
The snow's not getting on my head.
It's not cold!
I really love this!
Thank you, Ace-...
What fun!
Oars!
H-He must be a monster!
He stepped into the plaza!
Just a little more...
Just a little more to get to Ace-kun!
Damn Doflamingo!
He cut this guy's foot off!
I already claimed his body!
Doppelman!
Get him!
Spiky Shadow Lizard!
Oars!
I'm gonna... save you now...
Ace-kun!
Oars laid his life on the
line to clear a path.
The Whitebeard Pirates
rush to the scaffolding,
but just when it looks like they
can rescue Ace from execution,
Sengoku is already formulating a new plan.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Justice for the Winners!
Sengoku's Strategy in Action!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!