ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
Luffy finally made it to Marineford
to rescue his brother, Ace!
Luffy is rushing to Navy HQ to rescue his brother,
Luffy has rushed to Marineford,
Ace who will be executed in public!
scene of a battle between the
Whitebeard Pirates and the Navy...
Inside the bay, Luffy and the Whitebeards
are trying to get to the scaffold
There, the Whitebeard Pirates
are trying to get to Ace
Meanwhile, the Whitebeard
Pirates storming Marineford...
...to rescue his brother, Ace!
but the Navy stands in their
way. The battle is heating up!
and the Navy is standing in their
...begin an all-out war with the Navy!
Attention, all ships and soldiers!
When you are all set, we
move the schedule forward...
Gum-Gum...
I'm sorry, "Red-Haired."
...and execute Ace immediately. That's all.
Ace-kun...
...Giant...
Oars!
I will not hold back my power.
...Rifle!
--Luffy-kun...
--Let's move!
That's...
Why did any of them come?!
..."Hawk-Eye!"
I deserve this! They don't have
to risk their lives for me!
Now, I wonder if fate...
Climb Oars' body and advance!
Let's go!
Ace!
...will end the life of the child
of the next generation here.
Don't do this!
H-Hey!
Everyone! Why are you doing
this for a guy like me?!
No! That's not the side!
"Hard Battles, One After Another! Devil
Fruit Eaters vs. Devil Fruit Eaters!"
Or, if it will save him
from this Black Sword!
What's that?
I'm your brother!
Heehaw!
He beat the Giant!
Kuma! Kuma, that's enough!
"The Great Swordsman Mihawk! Luffy Comes
Under the Attack of the Black Sword!"
Awesome, Straw Hat! You beat
the Giant in one sweep!
It's me! Did you forget my face?!
I'm back!
If you don't stop, I'm gonna fight
back although I'm a gentle person!
Straw Hat, I think we caught their attention!
I don't have time to face such a strong guy.
I don't know how you know him
but you may as well give up!
Ace!!
I'm here to save Ace!
"Straw Hat Team Arrives! Tension
Grows at the Battlefield"
It's no use talking to him, Emporio Ivankov,
commander of the Revolutionaries army!
Don't let them advance any farther!
I feel a chill in my heart!
You...! What do you mean?!
What's wrong with him?!
Second Gear!
Don't let the rookie get the best of you!
H-Hey, don't tell me that's...!
Hey, partner! Can't you do something?!
Crocodile!
You're a friend of
Bartholomew Kuma I suppose.
Luffy!
Do you really think that
wax will help in any way?!
That's not all! Who is in that lineup?!
Get them!
All forces are here on both sides!
There are a lot of big names!
Why are Luffy and the others
falling from the sky?
He was once called Tyrant
Kuma and now he is...
Heehaw!
We have to go back a little bit in
time to know what happened to them.
Death Wink!
The world's got to be ready for it!
...dead.
Ace, we're coming to rescue you!
Let's launch a frontal attack
THE BAY HEAD OF MARINEFORD
Your power is not enough to beat me!
Galaxy Wink!
The ship that they were on was
hit by Whitebeard's seaquake.
We're here for you!
and join Pops inside the bay!
We gotta save Ace!
Damn! Get your jutte off of me!
Garp! It's your family again!
It's speeding up!
Drive the Navy out!
You! Leave him alone!
Luffy!
That's it, Straw boy.
She got me although my body is smoke!
The grandson of the hero--Garp and
the son of the revolutionary--Dragon.
Just focus on advancing.
H-Hey! Look at that!
Th-That's...! The pirate
empress saved Straw Hat!
We'll handle the rest!
Hancock! What are you doing?!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
I'll take care of him for good!
Are you gonna resign from The Warlords, too?!
It's a tsunami!
--We'll get this guy!
--Heehaw!
Shut up! I'm deafened by my own anger!
The Navy admirals! They're so strong!
Where's Croco boy?
Oh? I think he chickened out and...
--It's really big!
--We're gonna get caught!
But we can't stop!
How could you hit and pin down my beloved?!
"Hawk-Eye," do you remember us?!
We're gonna rescue Ace!
There he is!
The sea just suddenly drew back and now there's a big tsunami.
We're the guys who challenged you once!
He went ahead of me!
I won't let you survive! I have
never felt this much anger before!
They're a bunch of fools!
This must be...
Long time no see, Whitebeard.
Hey, Jimbei! We gotta do something or...
Bazooka unit, fire at Whitebeard!
You never learn.
I'm gonna cut you up and feed you to beasts!
But now we're powered up as New Kamas!
I don't want to be defeated
by a tsunami here!
Pops!
That's the Haki of Kuja!
I... I gotta save Ace!
I don't remember the face of every worm.
Take in the sails!
Damn! Please don't do this!
"Kuma's Transformation!
Ivan-san's Blow of Anger!"
Luffy-kun, let's ride on the tsunami!
Shouldn't we get away?!
Now that we are here, our
agreement has been fulfilled.
What are saying, you ass?!
Slash him to pieces!
Turn around already!
Why do you want to protect Whitebeard?!
Wh-What's going on here?
Hey, stop it!
As I thought--this old man is Whitebeard.
Why did the pirate empress save Straw Hat?
--We gotta hurry!
--Jump into the sea!
Gum-Gum...
...Twin Pistol!
Then leave him alone! Ace likes this old man!
Help! Help!
How long have you been a pirate?
I'm gonna...
Ace's brother is quite a fighter.
Great! Just gotta keep running and...
...rescue Ace! Don't get in my way!
Are you a bunch of amateurs?
You came here to rescue your brother?
If we turn around now, we'll take the
Yeah.
Luffy! Why did you come?!
Do you know who you're messing with?!
wave on the side of the ship and capsize.
We don't have any option.
Why did any of them come?!
That's right!
I deserve this! They don't have
to risk their lives for me!
A squirt like you will be dead meat!
You are in range.
Hang tight so you don't get
washed off by the big wave!
Damn!
Hurry up!
Shut up! That's not up to you to decide!
No, she didn't save him! She's
gonna turn Straw Hat to stone!
Just hang onto something!
My face is too big.
We, the 2nd division of the Whitebeard
Pirates, will save our commander Ace!
I know what you're up to!
You wanna
become the King of the Pirates, right?!
I always believed that
you'd make it here alive.
Don't do this!
Ow... Ouch! I got cut!
But I'm the one who'll become the King!
Everyone! Why are you
doing this for a guy like me?!
Only Ace-san's brother could avoid
getting a fatal wound like that.
Take this.
I'm your brother!
It's your brother's handcuff key.
What?!
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei!
That's how diabolical the empress is!
How stupid you are! Luffy! Pops!
I won't let you so much
as touch Luffy-kun again!
How saucy you are!
Straw Hat can't move now!
Has he turned into stone?
I won't forgive you if you
cause me trouble, spoiled brat!
Even if it means death!
Become my son!
Hancock!
Why are you doing this?
I'm gonna do as I like!
You just said my name again!
I want to rescue Ace-san!
For one reason, to save our sea!
I'm gonna rescue Ace!
It is too late to stop this war
now but we still have hope.
Luffy's hands... Luffy's hands touched mine!
"Even If It Means Death! Luffy
vs. the Navy; The Battle Starts!"
Namely, Luffy-kun over there.
Hancock!
What's wrong?
Yeah!
You're so...! You're so...!
I understand. But I still don't
know what fate has in store.
I'm ready...
He's the... rookie--Straw Hat!
...to accept anything
that's gonna happen to me.
Therefore, I need you to step back.
Fish-Man Karate!
How does he know Whitebeard?
What happened?
I'll hold a helping hand.
--The wave stopped moving!
--What happened?!
I don't get it!
He should hide after
breaking out of the great prison!
Thank you! I mean it!
Arabesque Brick Fist!
I'll take the blade of punishment.
What the hell?!
N-No... No problem...! Never
mind me, you've got to...
Why bother coming to this living hell?!
The ship has iced in and
we're completely trapped!
You've got to keep going, Luffy!
--Because he is Luffy-san.
--Huh?
I won't make a scene anymore.
This must have done by...
You're right!
That's the way he is!
Thanks!
Look down. You can see what's going on.
Pops! Luffy!
Sharkskin Palm Thrust!
So he is Straw Hat.
--Old man...
--The war has begun already.
No way! He beat the pirate empress?!
Shark Brick Fist!
He must've fought back and thrown
his weight high into her!
Old man must have set that
tsunami as a declaration of war.
--Old man.
--Hmmm?
I heard while on a Navy ship that...
Because I feel sorry for them.
And this freezing is the
work of Admiral Aokiji.
He's such a bonehead!
I wish he'd just get his
ass kicked already! Stupid!
Guys, listen!
I got an idea to get us through this!
How brave he is! Only his son could do it.
Start firing!
We gotta hurry! There's less than 3
hours left before Ace's execution!
See? She looks so tortured!
So they're gonna execute Ace immediately?
He beat The Warlord so easily!
How strong, Straw Hat Luffy!
Uh-huh. And?
Are you sure?
He's really strong as I thought.
What?!
Gum-Gum...
They said they would  after getting
"all set" for something...
You want the ship to slide
down this frozen wave?!
...Balloon!
...but they were using codes
so I couldn't understand.
That's the only way! First, we gotta
get this ship unstuck from the ice!
Like that! Like that!
"Hawk-Eye" is in the sky!
I know that you wanna rescue Ace, too,
so I wanted to share that with you!
Like that!
Are you nuts? It's a Navy
ship! We can't lift it up!
He's suddenly standing out in this battle!
I see. That was important information.
He's right, you idiot!
I wasn't expect him to hold
me so tight like that!
Damn Straw Hat!
Thank you.
We can do it if we work together!
Captain Buggy, we need to
make a strong showing, too!
No problem.
Oh, that makes me think that I can.
How can he talk on equal
terms with Whitebeard?!
I can still feel Luffy's body
in my arms and on my chest!
Let's beat Whitebeard now!
You bastard!
Gum-Gum...
Yeah! We have the next King of the
Pirates - Captain Buggy on our side!
Alright! Let's do it!
Okay! Ace, I'm coming now!
When Captain says that he can
do it, he will do it for sure!
Is this...
Having said that, this war is crazy!
...Jet Bazoo...!
Why is he so confident?
Is this what they call...
Ring, ring, ring...
There're a
bunch of big-time pirates and the Navy soldiers!
Attention, all ships and
soldiers! The target is TOTTZ.
Gum-Gum...
I better keep quiet here...
...marriage?!
...Bazooka!
Hey, you red nose!
Change the line and make
the shift to operation 3.
That was close! If I had reached
out, my arms would've been severed!
Get outta my way!
What did you just call me?! I'm
gonna kick your ass, you bastard!
--It's a Navy operational message.
--Advance the preparation!
So he is Ace's brother.
You could be level-headed.
Snake Princess-sama!
Keep up with the boy! Let's go, 3rd division!
Congratulation, Big Sis!
Huh?
TOT... what was it?
Dunno. Must be some kind of code.
Whitebeard!
We should go, too!
When you are all set,  we
move the schedule forward...
I know you. You're the brat
who used to work under Roger.
Wh-Wh-What?!
...and execute Ace immediately. That's all.
Snake Princess-sama!
Really?!
So beautiful!
It's been a while, huh? So you're alive.
14th division, let's charge ahead!
--Luffy-kun...
--Let's move!
Oh no! I drew his attention!
He's gonna kill me!
Yes, Commander Jill!
This can't wait any longer.
We don't have time to argue!
He's dead! He better run!
Everyone, let's get on with Straw boy's idea!
W-Whitebeard! That notorious Whitebeard is...
Luffy...
Best wishes to you!
They're so encouraged by just one daredevil?
He sliced the mountain of ice
with just the swing of a sword!
...talking to him! How cool!
Let's go!
I knew that you were a living legend!
But our strategy is airtight.
Why're they so thrilled?! Must be
nice if it's not your own problem!
Don't hesitate! Do as I said!
S-So this is what the world's
strongest swordsman can do!
H-Hey!
You're accompanied by so many prisoners...
Damn Sengoku!
No! That's not the side!
Luffy!
I bet he thinks that he doesn't need
Are you here to challenge me?
How strong is he?!
to stick
to the schedule for the execution of a mere pirate.
Straw Hat's dead because he's the target now!
Yes, he is!
And that was how Luffy and
the others started falling!
The key is--after they're "all set" for what?
Oh, sorry. Captain had to say it.
Pops! I heard that they're
moving Ace's execution forward!
Give it to him straight!
The blocks of ice are falling on us!
Dammit! I have no choice now!
I heard. How're Squard and the others doing?
Y-Yeah, at last we meet! Prepare yourself!
They're tied up with the vice admirals at
the bay head. I'm gonna fly there and help...
He's pushing his luck a bit too far!
No, wait.
Oh? I don't mind if you try to beat
me but what are you gonna do next?
I bet it must be a part of his plan that
we'd get some leaked information and advance.
Hancock. You look very beautiful.
Stealthy footsteps oily feet.
Ready, guys?
H-A-P-P-Y!
There are more Navy soldiers
than you can handle.
Sengoku wouldn't let his enemy
know his strategy so easily.
Let's get the "Make Captain Buggy a Star
in Front of Everyone" plan in action!
I'll make you happy for
the rest of your life.
In fact, they're more than I can handle, too.
I know that they're broadcasting
the war to the whole world.
Honey.
He's not that foolish.
What just happened?! Did a
Navy ship fall from the sky?!
Shouldn't we join ranks since we're
both pirates and knock the Navy down?
Keep going!
Yes!
There must be a Video
Transponder Snail somewhere.
It's water, thank god. We fell into water.
Honey...
Find it!
Then, you can beat me after that.
A kick at the speed of light?!
Honey...
Yeah!
I thought I was gonna die
by falling on the ice!
Oh my god! Whitebeard recognizes
you as a powerful man!
Honey...
"Find it?" "Yeah?" I don't think
that things are that simple.
Don't push your luck. I won't
let you invade that easily.
Why isn't it frozen around here?
Honey...
Honey!
Look! The ship landed in the area
where Jozu had cleared the ice!
Like his equal!
No, Whitebeard called him a "brat!"
Luffy! I see it! I can see it!
It's Admiral Kizaru!
You can't fight against the Navy!
You think there's a chance to win?!
Is it a surprise attack from the Navy?
A string that links us together!
You're the guy from Sabaody!
No, they don't look like the Navy.
A string that no one can ever cut!
Team up? Me and you?
Yes, I was gonna ruin you there because
the Celestial Dragons wanted it.
Yeah, if I go all out.
Climb! Climb up!
Yes. The reign of outdated pirates
like Whitebeard will end soon.
It's nothing comparing to
the water torture in hell.
It's a thick red string
of fate like a big snake!
He's losing his grip on reality!
Straw Hat Luffy.
--You sure?!
--I got goose bumps!
And the new era will be our era
where power conquers everything.
S-Straw Hat is dead!
Luffy!
I'm starting to think that
I can do it! I can do it!
I won't let you get away, Straw Hat!
Death...
I can see myself becoming
the King of this world!
...Wink!
Don't you wanna get a piece of it?
Perfume Femur!
It's inconvenient that Devil
Fruit eaters can't swim.
Yeah, we can beat the Navy
if he and I join forces.
Not bad, is it?
No! I wanna go home!
This is too great! I'll faint!
--What, Captain Buggy?!
--I can't believe what you just said!
Alright, Whitebeard, I join
with you! If you insist!
Your title has been stripped away but...
...when you get down to it,
we're both Warlords, aren't we?
Huh? Who does he think he is?!
You mean you wanna destroy Kizaru
quickly so you can rush home?
You outrageous fool, stand back!
Well, he's our Captain Buggy!
Where am I?
You better stop looking at
me as if I'm on par with you.
I won't let you pass through here!
Look! She's really looking down on him!
How many more things can
they take the wrong way?!
Only a legendary pirate could
face Admiral Kizaru without fear!
Oh yeah, I fell from there.
You should be pledging
to work under me instead.
Looking down too much makes her leaning back!
He is unbelievably easy to trick.
Do you know what's
You guys are too positive!
I thought that you became a better person
gonna happen to you
after messing with the Navy?!
Straw boy, are you okay?
The red nose aside, the prisoners
behind him are something.
in hell--Impel Down, the great prison!
That was close! Thanks, Ivan-chan!
Ace!
I can do whatever I want!
My only mission is to save you!
If so, then I wouldn't be here now.
It's a pain to have them as our enemies.
Because I'm beautiful!
Sables!
Kizaru, again!
Get lost, Flamingo shit!
And now, I must...
Huh? No, it's not! That's...
Kuma!
He's the bear-like guy who blew us all away!
This is great. She helped me out again.
Ships in the back,
THE BAY HEAD OF MARINEFORD
I thought that you could be reasoned with.
Rolling Spa!
come forward and deploy the backup!
Where are you? Where are you, Ace?!
Wait for me, Ace!
Our forces are superior!
Ace...
What did you say?! Kuma is dead?!
If you don't fight the Navy, it's easy!
Then, who is this right here?!
Bartholomew Kuma!
I have a report!
How despicable you are!
We can breeze through!
The pirates in the
back are also heading this way!
He's alive! Stop talking nonsense!
I know that you have a
role as a Warlord but...
It's about time.
...we've known each other so long.
How can you just fire a laser at me?!
Forward unit at the bay head,
Get on the ship!
change the formation as Fleet
Admiral Sengoku instructed
B-Breeze through! Breeze...!
He's not on this side!
Hey, how could you...
Captain Buggy!
Ivan-chan! Ah?!
All units, keep fighting
back and back up slowly!
He got caught up in the whirlwind
of someone else's fight!
A hole!
That's the bear guy!
Ivan-chan!
Don't worry about me!
--Did they stop firing?!
--They're backing up, too!
You're not gonna move aside
at any cost, Hancock?
Where are you, Ace?!
Leave this to me and just go ahead!
--There is disarray among the Navy!
--One more push!
Of course not! I won't let
you hurt my beloved husband!
Okay!
Be careful, Ivan-chan! If
you get blown away by him...
Navy ships are coming from either side!
Wait for me, Ace! I'll be there soon!
Let's do this!
Husband?
I'm okay. Now, Kuma, move out of my way!
Yes, my husband!
--It's too late!
--Let's charge into the bay!
After the wedding, we will go on a honeymoon!
Alright! It's our chance to
join Pops inside the bay!
Ivan-chan, do you know him?
Don't get in my way!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring,
ring, ring... Clank!
Yeah, sort of. But he's acting strange.
This is Whitebeard.
Is Squard there?
It's a sweet sweet honeymoon
with Luffy my love!
Pops! Captain Squard... Oh?
Seems like you both have memories of Kuma.
He was in my sight a while ago
but it seems like he's gone.
It's so unlucky of you to run into us!
But the Kuma that you both knew
and this one are not the same!
Ace!
Straw Hat, you're gonna die here!
That bastard.
He was all fired up to
strut his stuff to make Pops proud.
But what if...
N-Not the same? What is he talking about?
Huh? Who are you?
It's about time to eat.
That can't be true!
It can't be helped. Then,
DeCalvan Brothers...
I'm Fullbody!
But the food storage is empty.
I'm absolutely sure that he's
the Paw-Paw Fruit eater--Kuma!
You gotta pay for what happened at
the on-the-sea restaurant--Baratie!
--What is it, Pops?
--Pops, what is it?
There are a lot of things
that we can catch and eat!
Say something, Kuma!
Oh, Sanji beat you there.
Follow my lead and take
command of all pirates.
My honey! I wanna eat your homemade dishes!
You should remember this chakram.
--Okay!
--Okay! And what's your lead?
He's pissing me off! Although
he has always been quiet.
Okay! If you want it... Could
you give me a little time?
You're the hypnotist from Usopp's
village. Why're you here?
Sink the Navy ships around you first.
I told you that it's no use talking to him.
What?! Pops, I think we can
make a frontal attack now!
I honed my skill in the Navy.
If things go like that,
It was just days ago...
Are you giving up?
I'll have to make tons of dishes
With two chakrams, it's twice as effective.
I have a bad feeling about this situation.
that could satisfy Luffy's
appetite all by myself!
When I say "one, two, Django,"
you're gonna get tired.
The Government scientist--Dr. Vegapunk
modified him for the last time
One, two...
I got it, Pops!
Pops, I got it! We'll tell the captains!
and he turned into a complete
human weapon at last!
...Django!
Snake Princess-sama! Let us make it for you!
What?! Pops said that? Alright,
then I'll get the right side!
To be precise, he's the
former Bartholomew Kuma!
Luffy wants to eat my homemade
dishes! Keep your hands away!
We'll take the left.
Modified? Weapon? What
are you talking about?!
What are you two doing?
Honey! Isn't it ready yet?
Okay, got it.
In fact, he volunteered to be a guinea pig
for a study to build a human weapon...
We'll take the right side.
Hina disappointed.
If Pops says so.
--It's coming!
--How admirable!
I know you from Alabasta, don't I?
...run by the Government.
I can head my ship in any direction.
I have no time to play with you people now!
I'm ready for any trouble.
Because I'm... I'm...
Ace...
Squard?! I haven't seen him. Really?!
First, his hands. Second, his legs.
I won't let you get away! Kimono Sleeve Cage!
...his wife!
While his mind worked, they
modified his body piece by piece.
I'll take the left side.
"Wife?"
I will bind anyone who passes through me!
I don't know if she wants to fight or not.
Fleet Admiral Sengoku! Pirates of
the New World changed their moves!
--That's her signature phrase!
--Miss Hina is so captivating!
Stop lying! Kuma hates the Government!
I'll get Straw Hat!
Yeah, they turned to the left and right.
I told you, you outrageous fool, that
I won't let you pass through here!
I'm sick of being in bars! Second Gear!
He wouldn't sacrifice his life for them.
They've started attacking Navy ships!
Perfume Femur!
I know that he wouldn't do that!
Hancock! You...!
Ace!!
Stop yelling.
I don't know what kind of deal
he had with the Government.
Th-That was fast! I couldn't see him!
What are you gonna do now?!
Hina failed!
Only a few days ago,
We failed, too!
We're bound by Miss Hina--body and soul!
Luffy!!
he still had his personality.
Good guess! Whitebeard must have sensed it.
THE BAY HEAD OF MARINEFORD
You're getting farther from your brother!
Ace!!
He didn't fall for that cheap trick.
Maybe it was a bit too lame.
But now, he doesn't even remember
that he was born human so
he is no better than dead.
Don't fight the vice admirals
alone! They'll defeat you!
Damn!
But he can't prevent a
thing just by sensing it!
So this is it after all.
He is a monster who fights
as the Government tells him.
I can see you finally!
Captain Squard! It's getting
frantic inside the bay!
He is Pacifista PX-0!
I know!
I gotta hurry up and get to Ace.
So you better forget about the past!
The wall that Oars broke.
If I sneak in from here,
maybe I can outsmart them.
Breeze through! Breeze! Breeze!
Luffy!
His fighting capability has improved
a bit but I've already seen it all.
Ace! Hang on! I'll...
Damn! There're too many enemies!
It's hard to break through!
H-Hey, don't tell me that's...!
I won't miss it again from this distance!
Crocodile!
Death Wink!
That's not all! Who is in that lineup?!
You are...!
Heehaw!
Don't mind me! Just breezing through!
All forces are here on both sides!
There are a lot of big names!
Ivan-sama, you're alright!
Gum-Gum...
Ivan-chan, I wanna clear the way to Ace!
Oh, you save...
The world's got to be ready for it!
Jimbei!
...Jet Human Shield!
Ace, we're coming to rescue you!
You! What're you doing?! Straw Hat!
Fish-Man Karate!
Death...
We're here for you!
Gum-Gum...
What?! I'm not the one who cut you!
Stop!
Plus you just said "Don't mind
me! I'm here to save you!"
Garp! It's your family again!
5000 Brick Fist!
...Wink!
Luffy!
How deluded is your hearing?
...Bazooka!
Look! It's not only Straw Hat!
Jimbei and Ivankov of the
Revolutionaries army!
--Gum-Gum Human Shield!
--Stop it!
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
Behind them are many infamous pirates, too!
Advance!
Kuma! What's happened to you
over these past several years?!
They must've escaped from Impel Down!
I can't take it! You must be "Hawk-Eye!"
He always causes trouble... Straw Hat.
Ace!
They're all strong!
The Special Muggy Ball! Blow away!
Straw Hat!
Stop Straw Hat and the others!
Now I remember him saying...
--What brought him here?
--And he's not with his crew.
We will never meet again.
Here's a joke!
Straw Hat! I won't let you get through!
How is the Muggy Ball useful
for tunnel construction?
Moria!
Luffy! I'm glad that you're alive!
Farewell...
You've got to fight me, Moria!
And the answer is?
...At that time.
Look, Helmeppo-san!
Say it together, everyone! Because it goes...
Straw Hat! He's high-spirited as usual!
Jimbei!
What's wrong, Kuma?! It's me! Ivankov!
I can handle you on my own, Moria!
What?! Nothing'll surprise me any more...
BOOM!
Oh yeah! I'll cut his shadow off
and implant it in Oars again!
Great, Buggy!
Wh-Where'd he go?!
Straw Hat!
You wanna fight me, Jimbei?
I heard that he was captured
at Impel Down! He's so tough!
--Yeah, red nose!
--That was a good one!
Thank you, Buggy! I'll
never forget about you!
Alright! I have to get rid of you
in order to use zombie soldiers!
He brought some big faces!
Come on, zombie soldiers!
It's far from over!
Go ahead, Luffy-kun! Don't waste any time!
Watch out, you guys! Heads up!
I didn't expect to see him again this soon.
Thanks, Jimbei!
Pad Cannon.
Pffft! It's a pity to think
that I'm letting Straw Hat go!
Vista, Pops said that we
can't let Ace's brother die!
He's the brother that Ace was talking about.
There's a former and an
active Warlord together!
Alright, zombie soldiers!
Go ahead and capture Straw Hat!
Jimbei, you think you can
beat me on the land?! Huh?!
Back him up!
I got it! Count on me!
And that supposed to be the big
troublemaker rookie--Straw Hat!
I never thought that Jimbei
would become our enemy!
Moria! I don't wanna deal with him now!
Smoker-san, look!
Kuma, you bastard!
The Seven Warlords are our crucial
forces! We shouldn't fight each other!
Die!
5th division commander of the
Whitebeards - Flower Sword Vista!
Face...
Straw Hat and Crocodile...
Why are they together?
...Spectrum!
--Huh?
--What's wrong?
Nice to meet you, "Hawk-Eye" Mihawk.
There's something wrong with my shadow.
You've heard of me?
So it is him.
Everybody knows you.
Now, fight for me, shadows
of the damned Navy soldiers!
The grandson of the hero--Garp and
the son of the revolutionary--Dragon.
Take your bullets back!
That was close! Who is that old guy?
I'll take care of him for good!
They're multiplying!
It's not because of his power or skills!
Yes, because this is a battlefield and and
all the corpses provide fresh zombies!
Whatever! Thank you!
I'm watching you!
Of all things, you're working
alongside Straw Hat Luffy...
--Capture Straw Hat!
--He's the main suspect of the escape!
Galaxy Wink!
Keep going!
So that's your response, Jimbei?!
Did you know that I get more powerful
He's got to fight all these officers!
Yes, it is! I resign from The Seven Warlords!
by taking in the shadows of other people?
I wonder how long he can hang on!
It's odd that those people are teaming up.
You have no chance to beat me, Jimbei!
You got bigger.
Luffy!
Prisoners, a commander of
the Revolutionaries army,
But getting stronger by
taking other people's power
some bizarre-looking people and...
doesn't make you any better, Moria!
He seems to rally all those
around him to his side!
Silence! I couldn't care less about
it! All that matters is winning!
...Crocodile.
I don't think that they have a common goal.
Heehaw!
Stay at it! Straw boy!
At least, in this battle.
He made it through fine.
Now, I'm gonna take your shadow!
How could you attack  my sweet candy boys?!
Luffy! Save your brother!
Stay away, Luffy!
Spend the rest of your life
in the dark undersea, Jimbei!
I'm not gonna go easy on you anymore!
Outta my way!
Here!
Kick!
Among all people on the sea,
Let me have your shadow!
he has the most formidable ability!
That's how strong he is!
I know that you know it!
Among all people that I've met...
We're both pirates!
Ace!
You're so quick for a hulking fellow!
My face!
We both sailed on the sea as we liked!
You're the hulking fellow here!
My face!
I have my own adventures!
No one has ever forgotten
my face in my entire life!
S-Straw Hat! I'll get even with you!
I have my own friends!
Fish-Man Karate!
You're great, Captain Buggy!
Oh, uh, hmmm.
Where's Croco boy?
Ace!
Oh? I think he chickened out and...
I want you to...
But...
You pretended that you were beaten by
...keep your hands off of them!
Sharkskin Palm Thrust!
...even if you've lost your memory,
"Hawk-Eye" but shrewdly executed the plan!
There he is!
A wimp like you wants to save me?!
What do you mean?
if you can't remember how scary I am,
Outta my way!
Don't play dumb, Captain Buggy!
You think that I'll allow you to do that?!
He went ahead of me!
I'm gonna beat it into your body!
Shark Brick Fist!
Video Transponder Snail?!
It's so humiliating!
--Crocodile is aiming for Whitebeard!
--Pops!
Be ready for it!
Y-Yeah, that's right!
Go back, Luffy! Why did you come here?!
A hero who can change the world is someone
Long time no see, Whitebeard.
He's recovered, so quick!
who can open his own way to
the future by his own hands!
You never learn.
I'll take it from here!
I beg you, Luffy! I don't
want you to share my fate!
You guys, go ahead and back Straw boy up!
I'll follow you to the end, Captain Buggy!
Roger!
Shh...
You let go of the shadows
that you've taken in!
This is all my fault!
Okay, let's go, Straw Hat!
Yeah!
Thanks, Ivan-chan!
Now, the important part begins here.
You need to train yourself more!
Get to the scaffold!
I'm...
Now, you need to let me through, Moria!
How optimistic can you be?
...your brother!
I have to hurry forward!
Wait, you bastard! The fight is not...
As time ticks down toward the execution,
shocking truths have been
revealed one after another.
They suddenly disappeared in ice!
Did you know?
He knows too well how to fight against me.
We can become brothers
if we exchange this cup of sake!
It doesn't seem like Admiral
Aokiji used Ice Age again...
You can't turn into sand
once you touch water.
From now on, we're brothers!
Where did they...?
From the great, iron-tight prison Impel Down,
This ice is not cold!
Straw Hat!
surprisingly more than 200 people had escaped
What's wrong?
and those same notorious prisoners
have been caught up in the war.
Alright, guys.
Now that we are here, our
agreement has been fulfilled.
Listen carefully.
Move, Tashigi!
Blah-blah-blah... Buggy is great.
--Did he just say "I'm your brother?"
--He's also a son of Roger?
Why do you want to protect Whitebeard?!
Dah-dah-dah... Buggy is genius.
The expanse of the battlefield
is an unearthly site.
When Ace was born, both of his
parents died. That's impossible!
As I thought--this old man is Whitebeard.
Ouch! You are... Smokey!
Right? That's how we want it.
Then leave him alone!
That's nice!
I see you finally, Straw Hat!
It's certainly the showdown at the
summit that will change history!
Ace likes this old man!
I don't give a damn about...
And we want the world to be shaken
by the arrival of the new hero.
Ace's brother is quite a fighter.
Straw boy!
...the rules of pirates!
You hardhead!
Kuma! You're so persistent!
That's a perfect plan!
Don't let him come close to Pops!
Oh, no, no...!
Go, zombie soldiers!
Y-You sure?
Let's go, guys!
People all over the world can do nothing...
Oh yeah, that jutte is tipped with
Sea Prism Stone! That bastard!
...but follow the war that
will change their future
How annoying, Straw Hat!
Second Gear!
S-Seawater?
that seems so changeable now.
Don't fall behind! The plan is called
"Take Captain Buggy to Fame!"
I'm gonna take care of you!
Everybody was surprised
Jimbei!
Now is the time to proceed it!
when a strong guy like you
came back after losing an arm
If I remember correctly, Moria, your
zombie soldiers can't take salt.
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
When we succeed, the whole
world will be stunned!
in the East Blue.
Who is this enemy that you
gave your left arm to?
--Luffy-kun, let me handle them!
--Great!
All of you, do as we planned
and watch what you're doing!
White Launcher!
Fleet Admiral, we are all set.
Those at the bay area, too?
--"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei!
--The former Warlord.
You've got much stronger than before!
Yes, everything.
Straw Hat!
What are you doing?! Don't let this
rookie take control of the war!
Are you sure about that plan?
I put it up for a new generation.
He disappeared!
That's fast! Where is he?
Huh?
Move out of the way!
Hey, squirt, that straw hat you have...
They're getting ready for the execution.
I'm gonna crush him up!
...it looks like the one that
"Red-Haired" was once wearing.
Those bastards!
Crocodile!
What are they gonna do to
Ace? It's not time yet!
There're too many!
Old man, you know Shanks?
He's also a loose cannon!
Shanks left it to me.
I'm too far away from him.
Will it begin already?!
He grew up together with
Ace as his step-brother
It seems like you became
stronger than before, as well!
Look, Pops! This is my brother!
That's impossible! It's
before the announced time!
I won't let you get near Pops!
and he's a biological son
of the revolutionary Dragon!
Don't stand in my...
Cut the connection of the Video
Transponder Snail right away!
...way!
You came here to rescue your brother?
The revolutionary Dragon?!
Yeah.
The worst criminal in history?!
We the Navy and the World Government
What a pain in the ass.
He's still messing around.
Do you know who you're messing with?!
--Sounds very familiar!
--His daddy's got such a big name!
Your power is not enough to beat me!
must win this war in the
name of absolute justice!
Brilliant Punk!
Commodore Smoker pinned Straw Hat!
--He revealed it!
--Luffy-san...!
No matter what it takes.
Amazing!
A squirt like you will be dead meat!
Damn! Get your jutte off of me!
But it's too much to see,
for this naive world.
Luffy...
Now I know why Dragon...
I couldn't care less even
if you were the devil's son!
We don't have to show them the horrific
images that will unfold here soon.
...helped you at Loguetown, Straw Hat!
He's giant but so fast! How can I avoid him?
I didn't know that!
That explains everything!
Pops...
You bastard! Gum-Gum Pistol!
Dragon got in my way at that time but
this time I won't let you get away!
The 3rd division commander--Diamond Jozu!
Hurry up!
D-Damn!
They're really gonna
execute Ace ahead of time!
You! Leave him alone!
Shut up! That's not up to you to decide!
Ace!
She got me although my body is smoke!
The news that will go around
the world afterwards...
I finally understand  what
happened at Loguetown!
Kicking shouldn't hurt him!
How did you get out of the prison, gator guy?
...should be of our victory and only that!
I know what you're up to!
That's why Dragon saved Luffy.
Th-That's...! The pirate
empress saved Straw Hat!
You wanna become the King
of the Pirates, right?!
Did you like the Pool of Blood?
Did you hear that?
Hancock! What are you doing?! Are you
gonna resign from The Warlords, too?!
They mean that Dragon?!
Doflamingo, mind your own business.
But I'm the one who'll become the King!
Head Office! I'm calling from
Sabaody! We've got big news!
Our ships!
Shut up! I'm deafened by my own anger!
Or I'm gonna kill you!
You have a dirty mouth. He-he.
Spread this all over the world!
How could you hit and pin down my beloved?!
Hey, why don't you team up with me?
We can't allow him to live!
Look at the bay head! There's something!
Kill him at any cost!
I won't let you survive! I have
never felt this much anger before!
Stop here!
Don't get in his way!
Who cares? There's no need to hide it anyway.
Keep going, Straw Hat!
That label won't hurt him because
Luffy is already a notorious outlaw.
Thanks!
I'm gonna cut you up and feed you to beasts!
They're not our buddies!
That's the Haki of Kuja!
The Navy soldiers must've
gotten around the ice wall!
You brothers are both fools.
Hancock!
Ace!
They still have soldiers
who can destroy big ships?
Third Gear!
Yes!
You called me Hancock again!
Kuma! Kuma, that's enough!
That's...!
Gum-Gum...
It's me! Did you forget my face?!
Wh-What are they?!
...Giant...
I'm sorry, "Red-Haired."
How saucy you are!
...Rifle!
So that's the Government's
human weapon that I heard of.
If you don't stop, I'm gonna fight
back although I'm a gentle person!
I won't forgive you if you
cause me trouble, spoiled brat!
I will not hold back my power.
I don't know how you know him
but you may as well give up!
I'm gonna do as I like!
Ace!
It's no use talking to him, Emporio Ivankov,
I'm gonna rescue Ace!
The bear guy from the Sabaody!
commander of the Revolutionaries army!
That's...
--H-He's competing...
--...With Whitebeard!
You can say whatever you want!
There're so many of them!
You...! What do you mean?!
What's wrong with him?!
It can't be!
I'm gonna save you even if it means death!
..."Hawk-Eye!"
You're a friend of
Bartholomew Kuma I suppose.
--That brat!
--We all feel the same way!
K-Kuma?
He was once called Tyrant
Kuma and now he is...
--We're Ace's family, too!
--We're gonna save him at any cost!
An hour and a half since the war began,
Now, I wonder if fate...
We can punish all of them by
death, can't we, Sengoku-san?
...will end the life of the child
of the next generation here.
the Navy makes a big move!
...dead.
Marco, we can't let that kid die.
The tide of the war changes
What are you talking...
Absolutely.
Or, if it will save him
from this Black Sword!
Luffy... Pops...
its course quickly and
flows into its final stage!
Alright.
Hang on, Ace!
I'll get there...
Kuma is...
Alright, guys! I'm getting tired of waiting!
I'll get there very soon!
Luffy!
...dead?!
It's showtime!
Ivankov and Bartholomew
Kuma were once comrades,
Dracule Mihawk,
At the Navy HQ, Luffy leads the charge
against the massive forces there.
The Whitebeard Pirates and the Navy
Luffy and the Whitebeard Pirates
continue to run forward.
one of the Seven Warlords of
the Sea, stands before Luffy.
seem to have fallen into
a stalemate as neither
As he watches his friends face off
against foes with awesome powers,
but despite Ivankov's desperate
cries, Kuma's cruel attacks persist.
A single slash by the
world's strongest swordsman
force can manage to get the upper hand.
As the men of the Navy attack Luffy in waves,
Ace comes to a decision.
But then an army of human weapons that
look like Bartholomew Kuma appears,
easily splits a massive wall of ice in two.
Ace shouts at him to stay away.
Then Doflamingo shares the shocking
truth about what happened to Kuma.
Meanwhile, the Navy enacts a new plan.
How will Luffy fight back
How will Luffy respond to his brother's wish?
and the Whitebeard Pirates and Luffy
are under attack from both sides.
against such immense strength?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Hard Battles, One After Another! Devil
Fruit Eaters vs. Devil Fruit Eaters!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Great Swordsman Mihawk!
"Even If It Means Death!
Luffy vs. the Navy; The Battle Starts!"
"Kuma's Transformation!
Ivan-san's Blow of Anger!"
"The Extermination Strategy in Action!
The Power of the Pacifistas!"
Luffy Comes Under the Attack
of the Black Sword!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!