ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has faded into the wind now
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to lose something precious
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
Oh
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to lose something precious
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
Luffy and the others are fighting
hard to get to the scaffold
Luffy and the Whitebeards
are trying to get to the scaffold
Inside the bay, the Whitebeards
Luffy and the Whitebeards are
trying to make it to the scaffold
but the Navy stands in their way.
but they have been walled in!
but the Navy has activated encircling
walls leaving the pirates no way out!
The battle is heating up!
And at the bay head,
the Pacifistas began to attack
Then suddenly, a group of
the Navy's human weapons -
But with Jimbei's help,
Luffy was able to get over the wall
the Pacifistas appeared!
the allies of the Whitebeards
to exterminate them!
and finally make it to the plaza!
Luffy!
Squard!
Look at the bay head! There's something!
Hey, what's wrong?!
It should be fully activated!
I'm on my way!
Stop perpetrating this farce, Whitebeard!
I'm glad that you're alive!
Yeah, barely.
Ace!
I-I'm afraid that the wall
can't lift the giant body of Oars!
Wh-What are they?!
I know about your deal with the Navy!
I see. I was calling for you a while ago.
So that's the human weapon of
the Government that I heard of.
You have their assurance that the
Whitebeards and Ace will remain safe!
How is it at the bay head now?
It seems like his blood is
running down in the system
Wh-What is that?!
Your allies were beaten badly.
and making it less powerful!
K-Kuma?
You have sold the 43 captains
of the allied pirates to the Navy...
I made it here because
I found the way out luckily.
Oars! Y-You're...
Sengoku has no mercy.
"The Extermination Strategy in Action!
The Power of the Pacifistas!"
We can't close it but...
...in exchange for Ace's life!
He's using all the forces he has
in order to defeat us.
...do it, Akainu!
We're enclosed!
What the hell is this?!
Pops, did you notice what the Navy was up to?
You know what you have done, right, Squard?
Do it, Akainu!
I've known Sengoku for a long time.
You thrust a sword into your father's body.
Meteor Volcano!
Squard? Why is he up there?
You're such a stupid son!
There are 43 allied captains here
The Warlord--Bartholomew Kuma!
"Execution Order Issued!
Break Through the Encircling Walls!"
and we are all in your debt beyond words!
How come there're so many Kumas?
He's firing lava fists into the air!
What's going on here?
We risk our lives for the Whitebeard Pirates!
But I love you, son, even if you are a fool.
They can't get away!
Melt the ice that they're standing on!
Why did it black out?!
Let us see the war!
So, Squard, treat him kindly.
Hurry and fix it!
They're the ones who ran wild
here on the Sabaody a while ago!
They're having trouble with
the Video Transponder Snail!
I don't love him any more than any other.
There's nothing we can do!
There're a number of Bartholomew Kumas!
You are all family to me!
Now they've got way more of them!
Is it true that the Navy and
Whitebeard had a secret deal?!
He has never changed at all, Sengoku.
"Akainu's Plot!
Whitebeard Entrapped!"
He shook us up very well.
Do something!
Did Whitebeard sell out his allies?!
How ridiculous to say that I sold my sons!
I'm sorry...
What's gonna happen to the war?!
Head Office! Head Office!
The plan is going well!
I have big news!
What's gonna happen to the world?!
Now let's move on to...
Hello? Hello?!
...the execution of Portgaz D. Ace...
...immediately!
He gave the pirates the way out.
I should never underestimate that guy.
How ridiculous the Navy is!
Jimbei!
If you are a pirate, you pick what
you want to believe on your own!
I need you to do me a favor!
This means it was just a
sideshow up until now?
Is this the real one?
We came back just to see the war!
Ocean Current Shoulder Throw!
I've heard about it from time to time
Those of you who'll follow me,
lay down your life for it!
I can't believe there's
trouble with the snail!
that Dr. Vegapunk was trying
to build a human weapon
So you're buying into that?
You aren't?
and was repeatedly sending
prototypes to various places.
Be ready! He's gonna run wild!
You guys are such fools!
Oh no! You finally made it!
He's the strongest man in the world!
They're not showing it
because there're things...
So they're the human weapon?
You're standing tall, Dragon's son!
...that they don't want us
or the world to see.
Why do they all look like Kuma?
It scares me! His youthfulness!
"The Encircling Walls Activated!
The Whitebeard Pirates backed into a corner!"
Uncle! Didn't everything
go as you guys planned?!
I'm gonna get Ace back!!
I heard that pirates were
going to be easily encircled
inside the bay when we came out!
Captain Bonney...
Shut up! Just leave me alone!
But they're scattered all over!
"Whitebeard sold out his allies?"
Gum-Gum...
That's crap!
...Stamp Gatling!
The broad-axe guy is yelling something.
He wouldn't do that.
That's why he's a living legend!
Let's set sail, Bepo!
Aye-aye, Captain!
I see what the Navy is up to!
Come with us, Jean Bart!
That's right, Head Office! And there's
no chance of recovering the signal!
First, they leaked the information
that they moved Ace's execution
So I don't know what's
going on at Marineford now!
to make us rush.
Then they slowly backed up
"Moving into the Final Phase!
Whitebeard's Trump Card for Recovery!"
Meteor Volcano!
and lured all the pirates
inside the bay, and...
Whitebeard's on the move!
...blocked the bay head with the
human weapons to close the trap.
Checkmate!
That's why Whitebeard said that
we should sink the Navy
ships around us first.
They can't get away!
He saw it coming.
Melt the ice that they're standing on!
We didn't get trapped, thanks to him.
Yeah.
I can't believe that he's
attacking the 3 admirals openly!
He's a damn fool! They're gonna kill him!
Follow Pops' lead!
Clear the way for Pops!
Don't let them come closer!
Even though we couldn't trap them,
Second Gear!
Fire!
we can go at them from
the front and the back!
Attack the allied pirates
first as we planned.
I don't have time to fight those guys!
Get rid of the ones who
wander off of the enclosure!
He fooled us!
Whitebeard!
Did you hear that?
Uncle, is it okay if some Navy ships
get caught in the crossfire?
You're too slow!
Keep it to a minimum.
L-Look! Whitebeard has...
Alright!
Activating the encircling wall!
Whitebeard has...
Do it faster!
Let's begin!
Whitebeard has...
Yes sir!
The ice is melting!
Whitebeard has been stabbed!
Luffy-san!
I told you!
What's wrong?!
I-It seems like...
I don't know what's going on but
you can't beat us that easily!
Th-This water is...
...the ice inside the bay is blocking it!
Old man!
Ouch, it's hot!
Figure out how to fix it!
Wh-Who stabbed him?!
The seawater's boiling because of the lava!
Damn!
Yes sir!
I think he is...!
Yes! But the man who did it is a
captain from among the allies...
Get on the ice!
Hey, look!
...from the New World - Whirl Spider...
What's going on here?
Squard!
Why did you do that?! Answer me, Squard!
Be ready!
I was told that Pops had
sold us, the allied pirates,
Oh... Oh no!
Yes, sir!
S-Shut up! You guys made me do it!
to the Navy in exchange for Ace
They're blocking this side!
What do you mean?!
and that that was all there was to say.
Do it!
Do you know what you've done...?
Can't we break this wall?!
Ace!
Then why does Pops...
Pops! Don't push yourself! Your health is...
Ace-san!
Ace!!
Old buddy!
...save us and keep fighting?!
Go, Pacifistas!
Stop perpetrating this farce, Whitebeard!
It doesn't make any sense!
That's not what I've been told!
I know about your deal with the Navy!
Damn Squard, he's been fooled
by the Navy and stabbed Pops!
You have their assurance that the
Whitebeards and Ace will remain safe!
Whitebeard!
That's so preposterous!
How painful it is!
He blew them away!
Ace!!
What is he talking about?
Pops' blow didn't work!
It's no ordinary wall!
What's going on here?!
If this is the truth...
Everyone, listen very closely!
Alright, let's finish this up!
I...
We've all been trapped!
You never told me...
I've done a horrible thing!
The lava hit the back of the Moby Dick!
...that Ace was a son of
that hateful Gold Roger!
Put out the fire!
Hurry up, everybody!
Do whatever it takes!
They're even willing to sacrifice their own.
I'm sorry, Pops!
Don't let it sink!
We were looking forward to sailing
the world with Ace again on that ship!
I'm sorry, Ace!
When you first found me, I was all alone...
Who did this?!
Whitebeard! Your days are over!
Don't be afraid, guys!
Let's charge the plaza without stopping!
Squard!
You bastard!
Squard is out of control again!
He's dangerous! Stay away!
I thought that it was to
our advantage to have you
Can you pay them back by crying?!
Again?! Please!
since you hold a grudge against Whitebeard.
We can't do anything
about it  when it starts!
Crocodile!
The Moby Dick is...
They played a dirty trick on us!
Isn't there any strong man?!
Damn the Navy!
That guy!
Hey! Bring it on!
Backing down is not even an option.
The ship of our glory!
What is this? I thought this
was my chance to show off.
Bring Gold Roger here!
I'll get to Ace before they get me!
Damn! Our ship!
What? Are you all scared?
He was trying to kill the good old man before.
They sank the ship that
carried the Whitebeards for years!
The winds have changed!
What are you waiting for, guys?
Everyone, get off of the ship!
Counter the human weapons!
I can kill that old, dying buzzard later.
You know why I was all alone.
But before that,
That old man is amazing!
He can fight even after being stabbed!
I don't want to let you taste victory!
Because Roger killed all my precious crew
who had fought alongside me for so long.
Come on.
Anyway, I gotta focus on saving Ace!
Luffy-kun!
I'll fight you!
Jimbei!
I despise Roger and...
Look at that!
I'm sorry...
...you know it!!
Then you should have told me
that Ace was Roger's son
Hey, you, gator guy!
and you want to make him
the next King of the Pirates!
All units, get off of the ice right away!
We're running out of ways
to get to the plaza!
D-Doflamingo!
You turned me down and now,
you wanna team up with Whitebeard?
Don't let the pirates reach the plaza!
Don't mind the Whitebeards!
Back down to the plaza immediately!
What's going on inside the walls?!
Fall back!
The old man wants Ace to be the King?
You know it even if you can't see it!
It makes me jealous.
Hurry up!
Whitebeard is the greatest pirate I know.
They can't advance or back up
and keep being pounded.
They all went up to the plaza
while we weren't paying attention!
I wanna help him to be King of the Pirates...
The encircling walls are none other than
the casket of the Whitebeard Pirates!
Hmmm! I have a bad feeling about this!
I'm not gonna team up with anybody.
But the old man is in
the middle of the action now!
So that means you are still
giving me the cold shoulder.
The casket...
There is no time to think!
The plan is going well!
You were already betraying me at that time!
Yeah! Nothing will stop us!
I didn't expect that I'd get to fight the
world's greatest swordsman in this war.
Looks like it.
Now let's move on to...
...the execution of Portgaz D. Ace...
But I didn't know. I even befriended Ace!
Not ready yet?!
How lucky I am.
I'm sorry!
...immediately!
I must've looked so stupid!
The ice is thicker than we thought!
And then, your dearest son Ace got caught!
You're the number one
swordsman of the Whitebeards.
Let me see the Flower Sword's swordsmanship.
With the Whitebeard Pirates
all inside the bay
and we allied pirates on the outside.
You can have a good look at it.
I don't know what this is
all about but it's helpful!
Rose Rondo!
You have sold the 43 captains
of the allied pirates to the Navy...
Fire!
This is it, Straw Hat!
At a place we can't even see...
...We won't let them kill Ace!
...in exchange for Ace's life!
Die!
Yes! There is still a way!
You alright?!
The allied pirates will be vanquished
It's nothing! Keep moving!
and the Whitebeards and Ace will be safe.
Just one!
That's your deal with Sengoku, isn't it?!
The way that Oars made!
We'll be sitting ducks if we go that way!
Advance!
The Navy is expecting
us to go there for sure!
Don't get in...
Ace is Roger's son?!
The wall isn't activated
yet! This is no good!
...my way!
Yes and our superiors have an agreement
over how they're gonna end this war.
I'm gonna buy us some time!
That's a lie! I can't believe that crap!
Vice Admiral!
What kind of flower should I make bloom next?
There's no time to argue!
He's right! That's the
only way to save Ace...
Whether you like or not,
there's only one truth
Stop, Straw Hat!
I won't let you go any further!
and you all will die in vain.
I'm not gonna let you get to
the plaza, Whitebeard Pirates!
Silence! I won't fall for your line!
--Outta my way!
--Shave!
Moon Walk!
Drive them in, Pacifistas!
Iron Body...
I won't let you! Take this!
I-It's Vice Admiral John Giant!
...Smash!
Can't you see it?
I got you!
Soon you will know that I'm not lying.
Gum-Gum...
Look closely and see
the outcome for yourself!
Iron Body!
...Bullet!
Our converging attack will start soon
Ace!
and only you--the allied
pirates--will be attacked.
You're standing in my way. Move it.
What are they made of?!
Stop Straw Hat!
The Navy won't even touch
the Whitebeard Pirates.
Don't let him go any further!
They're not human!
Are they unbreakable?!
Straw Hat...
We're coming too!
Admiral Sakazuki!
The picture...
We didn't know anything about it
and we followed you here sacrificing
our lives to save Ace and help you
They shouldn't take such an obvious route!
That hurts! Dammit!
Not yet! Let them approach
as close as possible!
and this is what happens!
No matter how much you struggle,
I owed a favor to your grandfather
Fire!
I lost my balance!
we will keep the upper hand, Whitebeard!
In fact, we're the ones who
have been attacked by the Navy!
but I have no choice!
Vice Admiral!
The ground is tilting!
Because you chose to risk your life!
When all videos have been cut,
activate the encircling walls.
Of course they're going to
defend the only way out!
You fool! I won't let you do that to Luffy...
It's more like a trap!
Thereupon, we will execute Ace
and round up all our enemies.
Don't get close to Pops!
Fire!
It's worse than an earthquake!
Yes, sir!
Whitebeard!
Those monsters approach from the back
and the ice is blocking us on both sides
Admiral!
That's...!
Outta my way!
Ace!
and we have no way out now!
Ow, ow, ow...
1st division commander--Marco!
Big buggy, is he telling the truth?!
Ace's in danger! I gotta hurry!
Thanks! You saved me!
Say that he's lying, old buddy!
Don't mention it!
Go back to the beginning!
We've got three invaders in the plaza!
Luffy-kun!
It's a miracle that I could stab you once.
The sea is...
Devil Fruit eaters can fly over the walls!
I can't believe this!
We're finishing them off little by little!
Not just the island but the sea is...
I'm prepared for it! Kill me!
Th... Three?
...also tilting!
A-Am I one of the three
that they're talking about?
Jimbei!
But when did they find out about me?!
The wall of ice is blocking us!
There's no place to go!
Ace!
I escaped Admiral Aokiji's attack by a hair
The admiral has come out!
Is this it?!
Damn!
and survived so many deadly crises!
It's tough but we need to hurry!
And finally I got this far!
We came here knowing that powerful
enemies would stand in our way!
When I come to think of it,
they're attacking just us!
But I'm not safe here either!
Ace...
How outrageous that old bastard is!
Isn't there any place safe?!
Run!
Die, Dragon's son!
Someone's coming!
Old buddy, did you really trade us...
...For Ace's life?!
That was...
Please say something, old buddy!
Ace's brother, are you out of energy already?
Old buddy!
INSIDE THE BAY OF MARINEFORD
Go across the sea towards Oars!
Ace...
The commanders are here!
Get to the plaza whatever it takes!
What a tremendous help!
You can't get blocked by just one guy!
Come with us!
Fleet Admiral-dono!
Okay! That bastard!
The pirates inside the bay are acting strangely!
The Navy is backing down
so now is our chance!
Ace!!
Let's break through at once!
Fire!
That's kinda tough!
Luffy-kun!
Jimbei!
I'm going to pull you up!
It can't be true!
Whitebeard wouldn't sell out to the Navy.
He sold his allies?
No way, Whitebeard wouldn't do that!
Whitebeard and the Navy made a deal?
Thank you! I appreciate it!
Straw boy!
Then the pirates who trusted
and followed Whitebeard...
Luffy-kun!
Don't mention it!
...Are betrayed and will
be killed by the Navy?!
Doesn't that old man care
about his own teammates?
I didn't wanna believe it,
I couldn't believe it!
His crew knew what to do, they evacuated.
10th division commander--Curiel!
I never thought that
old buddy would betray us!
Go across the sea towards Oars!
If you're gonna come for me,
I'll just knock you down!
You fool!
You've been deceived, Squard!
Why couldn't you trust Pops?!
Get to the plaza whatever it takes!
You're dead if you stay inside the bay!
Don't play innocent, Marco!
They are desperate.
Are you alright?
Ace will die and you guys
will be trapped and wiped out!
Ouch... Was that the end of the world?
You're the 1st division commander,
Defend the open space in the wall!
I know that you knew about Ace
and the deal with the Navy!
Yes, sir!
I couldn't care less about who's gonna win
They've gone crazy after losing their ships and the
but it'll nice to see Whitebeard to die!
It's true that Ace is Roger's son.
Luffy!!
I can't believe it!
ice they stood on, stupid pirates!
I won't let Pops and Ace die!
They're fair game for us! Shoot!
They used that to their advantage,
tricking the one man who would
be most angered by that fact.
So this is what the
strongest pirate is capable of!
Their strategy was a notch above us.
Shall we put this match on hold, Vista?
I don't want any delay. Aokiji!
What deadly power!
Seems like it'd be good for both of us.
Shoot everyone who came over Oars!
But in the name of absolute
justice of the Navy,
He's coming towards us?!
This war was a setup?!
I can't let you pass through here!
Everything up to now meant nothing?!
There'll be no win or lose?!
We're ordered to back down, Smoker-san!
I'm gonna save you even if it means my death!
Don't hesitate! Keep going forward!
Turned off!
We've got to go!
What's wrong?
Is it broken?
Head towards Oars!
Yeah.
I know.
Proceed with the execution.
Straw Hat!
Get to the plaza!
Activate the encircling walls!
Wh-What's wrong with them?
How can they keep their
morale in this situation?!
It's coming!
Luffy! Hurry up and save your brother!
Advance!
It will reach the scaffold!
Keep going and destroy it!
That bastard!
How could he let his own
allies stab him that easily?
Have you cut the videos yet?
No, give us another minute!
Shame on you, Whitebeard!
Hey, did you find it?!
Ace-... kun!
N-No! We're still looking for it!
I've no recollection of being
beaten by such a weakling!
PLEASE WAIT A MOMENT
Hey! Is the scaffold alright?!
We're all set!
Gaffer, move aside.
Did it reach it?
Croco boy...
They cut all videos except for one but...
Crocodile.
Why do we have to wait?!
It didn't hit the scaffold!
What made it veer off?!
It's true,
he could've fended off that attack
if he was the same guy he used to be.
Look at that!
Even if it was a surprise attack or
the attacker was one of his fellows,
3 admirals!
You're good to go on camera!
Okay, let's go on the air!
he could've avoid it!
This happened because
the walls are not ready!
5 seconds to go!
4, 3, 2, 1, action!
That's the problem!
Your damn ice is blocking it!
Are you telling me to draw their
sympathy by putting these on?
Why couldn't you just melt it, Sakazuki?
The picture's back!
Er... Um...
Pops!
He allows himself to get out of shape!
Little Oars Jr.! He's still alive?!
Sorry to keep you waiting, everyone.
Somebody's talking!
Ace-kun!
Damn!
We're here at Marineford.
I can't believe that they've
repelled Pops' shock wave!
Everybody, get on board!
There're dead bodies of pirates and the Navy.
Ace-kun!
Don't be scared, guys!
A commentary?
Commander Jozu!
Hold on tight!
Let's charge them while they're off balance!
Ace-kun!
Hey! What's this?! What's going on?!
N-No way! It's a ship!
We have a problem!
Oars...!
Hmmm?! The guy over there must be...!
We cannot miss this chance provided by Pops!
Another coated ship is entering the bay!
I protect Ace-kun!
Oh, he's...! Don't tell me that he's...!
Let's go, Whitebeard Pirates!
You know what you have done, right, Squard?
Oars!!
He's been hiding his origin but...
Dammit! It must've been hidden
at the bottom of sea all this!
...he was one of the legendary crew of
the King of the Pirates--Gold Roger!
Oars!
Oars is alive!
You thrust a sword into your father's body.
Advance!
You're such a stupid son!
Who's that?
Captain!
The great pirate--Captain Buggy the Clown?!
What guy!
Seems like they're all very angry.
Oars...
How scary!
Captain Squard!
Yes, that's who I am indeed!
What's going on with the encircling walls?
I-I'm afraid...
Divert all power from the city!
It's top secret but I am...
Pass it on to the walls!
But I love you, son, even if you are a fool.
I don't remember saying that
that was all of our ships.
...the legendary pirate.
Yes, sir! Right away!
H-Hey! Captain Buggy!
Captain... Squard!
Your nose is bleeding!
Ace!
You all...
It's a paddle boat!
It's coming towards us at full speed!
Cut! Cut!
Wipe it up!
Alright!
What?!
What the hell is this?!
Luffy!
I'm on my way!
Cut the crap...
I'm saying "cut the stupid video right away!"
Are you okay, Luffy-kun?!
Sink it like the Moby Dick!
You sold our lives to...
Ace!
Honestly! You're too reckless!
We can't move on like this!
Who pulled your upright and
loyal heart into the darkness?
Full power!
I-I'm afraid that...
...one of the Video Transponder Snails
Get ready to shoot!
has been stolen by the
prisoners from Impel Down!
Tell me.
He's an insurgent in the Navy.
What did you just say?!
Fire!
No! Not the boat! Shoot at Oars!
Make-up!
We're ready!
Oars!
I'm opposed to this plan.
Wh-What is that?!
Alright, now it's take 2!
Huh? Why Oars?
They'll beat Oars again!
3, 2, 1 and...
People who don't know the truth
It's too late!
Oars!
are calling him a legendary
pirate and honoring him
Get ready, everybody!
Oh! That guy right there!
Th-The walls!
He was one of Roger's legendary crew and...
but that's not true.
Oars!
...the sworn brother of "Red-Haired"
of The Four Emperors!
He's just a scumbag who
offered a secret deal to the Navy
We gotta do something! We gotta hurry!
just to protect his own interests
The great pirate--Captain Buggy the Clown?!
They'll execute Ace!
and betrays and sells out his allies.
Yes, indeed!
Yes, we have to stop them!
Stop them right now!
We're enclosed!
They made up all his legends.
Jimbei!
What the hell is this?!
The one that we have to
kill in this war is Whitebeard!
Whoa! That was close!
I need you to do me a favor!
He pulled the boat out of water!
It's absolutely unthinkable not to!
They found us! Run!
Take this!
They broke the encircling walls!
If you're gonna help me,
I'll save you all--the allied pirates.
You just got cut by the
famous "Hawk-Eye" Mihawk
Did it break?!
Ace-kun!
but you don't seem like you got hurt at all!
How tough!
Stab Whitebeard.
Talking about me?
He's barely alive! Keep shooting!
No, not even a scratch!
Yes, I'm Buggy!
Oh, okay. Let me do it!
This steel wall must be very thick!
We made it to the plaza!
The legendary!
He said he would save us
allied pirates if I slew you.
These steel protection barriers are what
Kizaru-san!
Blow all of them away!
Let's save Ace!
they were calling the encircling walls?!
We have to finish the execution already!
Let us see the war!
Damn! Aren't you gonna fight us, Navy?!
So that's what Akainu told you.
Let's burn down Navy HQ!
What happened to other videos?!
Wait for us, Ace!
I know how much you hate Roger...
Let us see Ace who was about to be executed!
I better take out his
head at a time like this!
Let us see the group of Bartholomew Kumas!
Hey, look at those!
They're all aiming towards us!
...so much so that I can feel your pain.
They got us!
There was only a space the size of a rathole!
Oars!
But, Squard,
Captain Oars!
We gotta run!
But they went for it wisely!
it's ridiculous to lay the blame on
a child for the sins of his father.
We're enclosed! There's no place to...
The walls could become
an obstacle for us this time!
Oars!!
Did Ace do something to you?
It's over!
They keep driving us to the corner!
There is a place!
Pops!
You and Ace have weathered
agony, joy and pain together...
Hey, what's wrong?!
It should be fully activated!
Whitebeard!
I-I'm afraid that the wall
can't lift the giant body of Oars!
Ocean Current Shoulder Throw!
Don't give up!
You still have your head, right, Ace?!
...so many times along with
the others, isn't it right?
We can't go down until we save Ace!
Let's go!
It seems like his blood is
running down in the system
I don't give a damn who Ace's father is.
We did it!
and making it less powerful!
We all met each other
on this wide sea by chance!
Now we can save Ace-kun...
Damn the Giant!
Not only the two of you but
all of you, I take as my sons!
Oars! Y-You're...
Oars!
So, Squard, treat him kindly.
I don't love him any more than any other.
What a guy!
Save Ace-kun at any cost...
You are all family to me!
He is still fighting, you know.
Pops.
Squard!
I'm glad that you're alive!
Yeah, barely.
We have a chance to win!
I see. I was calling for you a while ago.
Lu...!
Anyway...
We can't close it but...
Luffy!!
How is it at the bay head now?
...do it, Akainu!
Your allies were beaten badly.
Oars...
...he has never...
I made it here because
I found the way out luckily.
...changed at all, Sengoku.
Sengoku has no mercy.
He's using all the forces he has
in order to defeat us.
He shook us up very well.
Pops, did you notice what the Navy was up to?
How ridiculous to say that I sold my sons!
I've known Sengoku for a long time.
Meteor Volcano!
Oh no! You finally made it!
I see.
It's better for us if they're
gonna attack us from the rear.
You're standing tall, Dragon's son!
He gave the pirates the way out.
I'm gonna go forward, too!
We gotta invade without stopping!
It scares me! His youthfulness!
I should never underestimate that guy.
I agree.
He's firing lava fists into the air!
Squard? Why is he up there?
The wall of ice has broken down.
Wh-What's going on there?!
This Navy ship is in good condition!
There are 43 allied captains here
The guy who jumped over
the wall was Ace's brother!
We can get away at any time!
Whitebeard has descended to the plaza!
and we are all in your debt beyond words!
That brat!
They vanished into the sky.
If you are a pirate, you pick what
you want to believe on your own!
We risk our lives for the Whitebeard Pirates!
I praise you just for your tenacity.
Stay back, my sons!
But you're not good enough
to reach this stage yet.
Thank you.
What makes you think that you can beat us?
But we are...!
I know.
I knew that it was a lie!
That was the Navy's plan!
You are fighting to save
a member of your family.
What's this noise?
Damn! They fooled us!
The pirate, Whitebeard,
won't give up on his family.
Old buddy would never betray us!
Everybody followed you to this hell
because you're that kind of person.
I'm sorry! I will never lose
trust in you, old buddy!
Me too, old buddy! I'm so sorry!
I'm gonna get Ace back!!
I'll follow you to the end!
Old buddy!
I wish that...
Did you call me a weakling?
Please, Croco brat.
He's so reckless just like his brother!
...we were also...
What are they?!
I'm just a human with one heart.
Oars, stay there!
...members of your family.
Guys! Rescue Ace and...
They can't get away!
I need your power!
People would call me a devil or a monster
Melt the ice that they're standing on!
Pops!
Jozu, the trump card!
...destroy the Navy!!
but I can't continue to
be the strongest forever.
Okay!
Everyone, get ready!
We're gonna charge into the plaza!
If I can save this one young man's life,
I will earn my right to
retire from the world.
Garp.
Gum-Gum...
Those of you who'll follow me,
lay down your life for it!
Yeah.
...Stamp Gatling!
I don't think we can make it
through this unscathed!
Be ready! He's gonna run wild!
He's the strongest man in the world!
I'm on my way, Ace!
Let's go!!
The world's strongest pirate, Whitebeard,
has joined the battle himself.
At last, Whitebeard stands before Ace!
No one expected Squard's betrayal.
Luffy finally leads the
charge into the plaza.
The Whitebeard Pirates
are trapped in the bay.
As they see him approaching Whitebeard,
But he's faced with the two admirals Aokiji and Akainu,
As the Navy's concentrated fire continues,
But the three admirals form
a heavy wall in front of him,
Unleashing his Tremor-Tremor
fruit powers to the max,
suspicion grows in the Navy men as well.
they try to reach the plaza
via the path Oars opened,
he decimates the Navy's
forces one after another.
repelling his advance.
and the conflict becomes a battle royal.
but the order to execute
Ace has finally been given.
The strong bond shared among the
Whitebeard Pirates has been destroyed...
In response, Sengoku finally enacts
the greatest counterattack plan
Meanwhile, in the bay, Whitebeard
prepares to deal his final trump card
Amidst the chaos, Marco finds an opportunity
What will Luffy do now?!
That is the scenario described by the Navy.
to make a dash toward Ace!
to change the course of the battle!
in Navy history!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Execution Order Issued!
Break Through the Encircling Walls!"
"The Encircling Walls Activated!
The Whitebeard Pirates backed into a corner!"
"Luffy at the End of His Tether!
An All-out Battle at the Oris Plaza!"
"Moving into the Final Phase!
Whitebeard's Trump Card for Recovery!"
"Akainu's Plot!
Whitebeard Entrapped!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!