ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
He got over the encircling walls in order to
make it to the scaffold with Jimbei's help
Trying to make it to the scaffold, Luffy
got over the encircling walls with Jimbei's
He and the Whitebeards finally got over the
encircling walls to make it to the scaffold!
cling walls to make it to the scaffold!
He and the Whitebeards finally got over the
and faced the 3 admirals!
encircling walls to make it to the scaffold!
The Whitebeards then used their paddle boat
that had been hidden at the bottom of sea...
The Whitebeards then made
it to the plaza, too!
As an all-out battle between the Navy and
the Whitebeards continues at the Oris Plaza,
In the midst of the Navy's onslaught,
Luffy runs toward Ace with
the Whitebeards' assistance!
An all-out battle between the Navy and
the beards has begun at the Oris Plaza!
...and made it to the plaza, too!
Luffy runs toward Ace!
Second Gear!
Ice Block: Partisan!
If you wanna see the future,
I'll show you now, Whitebeard!
You guys!
Pops?!
From now on, back Straw Hat Luffy up...
You're too slow!
Damn!
Do it!
Pops, move on!
...with all your strength!
Even you can't win out against the
onslaught of time, Whitebeard!
Ace!
I'm counting on you!
Go across the sea towards Oars!
It's no use!
Do you think that I can't
stop you for doing it?!
That's what I was afraid of the most!
If you have an unguarded moment,
you will lose the fight!
They made a path!
Marco!
You can't look away like that!
All you have is courage.
We have a problem! Another coated
ship is entering the bay!
But if you're not strong enough,
Don't do it!!
Should I be the last voice
you hear before you die?
I'm here, Ace!
you can't save him no
matter how hard you try.
Why don't you just get lost?
Sink it like the Moby Dick!
Pops!
Grandpa! Move out of my way!
No! Not the boat! Shoot at Oars!
I'm not going to move!
He is nothing but a bundle of energy
who just bluffs. Young and clumsy.
If I'd be able to do all I could...
Because I'm a vice admiral of the Navy!
I'd be happy to die!
Hey, was that...?!
I've been fighting against pirates
since long before you were born!
Conqueror's... Haki!
But I like fools like him.
Let me fight, Ivan-chan!
Hey, come on! For real?!
Old man!
If I can't fight now
That was surprising!
If you wanna pass through here,
you have to kill me first!
and if I can't rescue Ace, I...
He pulled the boat out of water!
If I let you wreak havoc,
this island won't survive!
Straw Hat Luffy!
That brat...
They broke the encircling walls!
I'd rather take my own life afterwards!!
Pops!
Because of the path you two...
Let me have the strength to fight for now!
"The Scaffold at Last! The
Way to Ace Has Opened!"
Stay back, my sons!
...have chosen to live!!
Then why don't you protect it?
I'm on my way, Ace!
All right!
"Each on Different Paths! Luffy vs. Garp!"
Do whatever you want!
Yeah! Ace is alive!
Hey, stay with me!
Was that Ace's brother?!
--Look at this!
--I almost passed out!
If you wanna go further,
you have to kill me first!
Luffy!
Guys! Rescue Ace and...
Please, grandpa! Just let me go by!
Ace!!
...destroy the Navy!!
Like Pops and "Red-Haired,"
he used the Conqueror's Haki!
"The Power That Will Shorten One's
Life! Energy Hormone, Redux!"
"To Live Up to a Promise!
Luffy and Coby Collide!"
Was he the one who did it?
Luffy!
Seems like he used it unconsciously.
Garp.
Yeah.
I didn't know that  he had
such tremendous power!
Garp the hero...
So slow! What's taking them so long?!
...took part in their protection!
I don't think we can make
it through this unscathed!
C-Coby! S-Stay with me, Coby!
I'm sorry for being late!
He fought against Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates 20 years ago
I brought two executioners as replacements!
--Finally! Hurry and get ready!
--Yes, sir!
and made his name in the world
- he's a legendary Navy soldier!
He was born with it as I thought!
"Luffy at the End of His Tether! An
All-out Battle at the Oris Plaza!"
Damn Straw Hat!
He uses it, too!
Straw boy, once again,
Back down if your heart is weak!
I heard that it was Garp who fought Roger's
competitor--Shiki the Golden Lion...
How could he do this to Coby without mercy?!
you better keep in mind that the next time
you drop, you won't be able to bounce back!
He is not just another rookie!
I'll make him pay!
Conqueror's Haki!
...here in Marineford with Sengoku
and imprisoned him in Impel Down!
But it's not surprising because he's
the son of the revolutionary--Dragon!
I-I have to become...
The Energy Hormone is just fooling your body!
...much much stronger...
Vice Admiral Doberman!
It's curtains for a Devil Fruit
eater if he falls into the sea!
It isn't repairing any of the damage!
Hey, where did you get the power from?!
Y-Y-You are alive! I'm so relieved!
Huh?! What power?!
Never mind!
If nothing is done, I'm
gonna really... really...
Don't get tripped up by his name, you fools!
I...
He's not aware of it!
So it's not ready to be used!
Where's Luffy-san?
He's just an old soldier!
I...
...fall... fall...
But it's no wonder that he attracts people!
That damn Straw Hat is...
...fall...
This is why they say "blood
will tell," Dragon!
Or not!
If you'd lived through that
era, you should know that...
I won't fall again!
...being blocked by Vice Admiral Garp!
What?! Another foolhardy statement!
...you should focus on the
enemy in front of you!
Are they really gonna fight?!
You're not gonna fall?! You got me there!
Don't let him escape this battlefield! If
you do, he'll prove a formidable foe for us!
Look at them!
Hound Blaze!
Luffy-san!
What are you doing, Ivankov?
Make sure he dies!
Be quiet please! I need to hear
what's going on at the plaza!
Wait!
Huh? You are the one who is making noise!
Straw Hat is heading to the scaffold! Dammit!
They're trying to execute Ace again!
You gotta stop destroying the city!
Oh, well, my words can't change Straw
boy's mind under these circumstances!
It's easy to get him from this distance!
I told you to protect it!
Aim at Straw Hat Luffy!
Ouch! I got hurt!
You impertinent fools!
All I can do is keep them from beating him!
I'm sure that the battle is growing
fiercer on the other side of the wall.
Stand back!
Hurry and execute Ace!
--Get a substitute right away!
--Yes, sir!
Straw Hat?!
Maybe, Straw boy is already...
Straw Hat is coming!
Slave Arrow!
Kill Straw Hat!
...boiled!
--We...
--Love...
Or roasted!
--You...
You Navy soldiers are a bunch of cowards!
Make a path!
Or iced!
Yeah, maybe that's what happening to him!
A path to rescue Ace!
Pirate empress! Whose
side are you really on?!
You need such strength to fight a fledgling?!
Oh no! Oh boy!
Of course, Luffy's...
Leave it to me!
I thought you wanted to kill me!
What are you doing?! We need to hurry!
...but what if you hit Vice Admiral
Garp with a stray bullet?!
It's all your fault, Jimbei!
We still got those pains in the ass here!
--What?!
--N-No!
What?! What did I do?!
Vice Admiral Garp! He is none other than...
Yes! It wouldn't have gone like this if you
had just beaten them and rescued Ace boy already!
I won't let you do it, monster!
I'm gonna finish him!
Let's get Whitebeard first!
He's a monster but he's wounded
badly! Bring him down at any cost!
I'll show you...
...my grandfather!
That was impossible!
--Your grandfather?!
--Vice Admiral Garp?!
...the power of the New World!
Destroy Navy HQ!
Bring it on!
If I get married with Luffy, then of
course, he becomes my grandfather!
We're gonna back Pops up!
--Now is the chance!
--Get to the scaffold!
--It's just...
--...In your head!
It's not over! I won't let
you pass through here!
Don't be afraid! Get him!
--If you wanna advance...
--...You gotta beat all of us!
Straw boy, now is the chance!
How is he?
We'll show you the spirit of the Navy!
You gotta find a way, Straw Hat!
Hurry up before the bridge collapses!
Not good at all! First aid won't help him!
Don't let Straw Hat go!
Oars, thank you.
Straw Hat!
He needs proper treatment!
Luffy-kun!
Straw boy can't fight anymore!
But...
Heads up!
Luffy! Straw Hat Luffy!
Death Wink!
Clear the way in front of me!
Alright!
10 points! I'll back you up!
He's gonna do it again!
Thanks, Ivan-chan!
Like I said, if you wanna pass through
here, you have to kill me first!
I have no choice.
What's the matter, "Fire Fist?"
Damn! Navy soldiers have started regrouping!
Ice Ball!
Luffy-san...
Ace...
Ouch!
--Push it through by force?
--I wonder how long he can hang on!
Pops!
You're...
You bastard!
Pops!
Damn! If I could only take these off!
Gol D. Roger?
Pops! Don't push yourself
too far, you're wounded!
Grandpa!
You mean Gold Roger? Did
you ask me if I know him?
Coby!
--Whitebeard got iced!
--We got him!
Why do you want me to fight with these guys?!
You guys!
Don't you realize why there is so much
destruction in the world caused by pirates?
Pops?!
That day...
From now on, back Straw Hat Luffy up...
Pops!
I've decided to be the King of the Pirates,
It's all Roger's fault!
That's your training!
My training?!
...with all your strength!
so if I die fighting for
that, that's fine with me!
His fault?
It just makes me hungry and I
don't wanna get hit anymore!
I heard that right before his execution,
Do you suppose I can do it, too?
If I'm prepared to die for it?
Oh no! The vibrations can't be frozen!
he bullshitted about this
great treasure thing...
Do what?
Don't be such a baby!
Do you think... even I could join the Navy?
...causing the idiot pirates
who believed him to run wild.
You got to become the strongest Navy soldier!
Ice...
Ace's brother?!
Navy?
Yes! Catching bad guys is my dream!
I'm gonna become a pirate,
not a Navy soldier!
He should've never been
born in the first place!
Pops!
Admiral Kuzan!
Take care of Straw Hat right now!
It's been my dream ever since I was little!
--Stabbed with Haki?!
--Did it kill Aokiji?!
He was just a worthless bastard!
Huh?
Even after his death, he causes
the pirates to roam the seas!
You fool!
If I hadn't met Luffy-san, I
couldn't have become what I am now.
Straw boy! Watch out!
Ouch!
Nothing's more painful than grandpa's fist!
He's such a nuisance--living or dead!
That's right! In order to
live as a Navy soldier,
He was the biggest piece of shit
the world's ever! Remember that!
You're...
No! Don't be ridiculous!
...the allied pirate of Whitebeard
- Bohemian Knight Doma!
I have to fight to change myself!
Nice to meet you, Vice Admiral Momonga!
Because this is a battlefield!
Ice Block: Partisan!
Huh? What's wrong? What
are you getting mad for?
I have to commit myself towards killing him!
DeCalvan Brothers!
I mean, who are you, brat?!
Gum-Gum...
--You got to fight...!
--...Against us!
Gum-Gum...
"Thunder Lord" McGuy
I need you to fight me,
Vice Admiral Doberman!
Shave!
I-Is this...?!
What a fool...
We pirates from the New
World will assist you!
I gotta tell you something!
What have you done in the city, Ace?
Ace-chan's right there! Let's go, Straw Hat!
What is it?
I'm not gonna become a pirate!
Pops, move on!
They're making a fuss over some punks
who almost got killed by a kid.
I'll become a Navy...
You finally got it!
I'm counting on you!
The allied pirates of Whitebeard
are surrounding Straw Hat!
I'm not gonna become just a pirate,
...ad...
Oh, I thought they were dead.
...admiral someday!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
What did you say?! If you cause trouble,
I'm the one who'll get chewed out!
Diamond Jozu!
Whoa! Oh, I mean...
--What are they doing?!
--Hurry up, Ace's brother!
You can't be influenced
by "Red-Haired" like that!
I-I-I'm sorry! I got carried away!
Navy forces are focusing on Pops now!
Are you listening, Ace?!
It's embarrassing! I wanna crawl in a hole!
You're dismissed! I got to
beat some character into him!
This is your only chance
to get beyond the admirals!
Honestly! How could he just
leave a kid like this with me?!
After I met you, I became
emboldened a little bit...
We're almost there!
Let's break through all
at once! Come with us!
Grandpa!
You wanna know about Roger?
Coby!
You wanna fight me, right?
I'm not gonna let you become
a pirate at any cost!
The scaffold is right there!
This is a big deal, Straw boy!
Then, of course you have to
become such a heavy hitter!
If only we could gain control of this mess!
The world's greatest pirate
is putting you to the test!
We won't let you! You all die right here!
He was just a great liar and a murderer!
Huh?
Do you think I can become an admiral?
Heehaw!
Whitebeard put all his hopes
on you! That's a big thing!
Next time we see each other,
we'll be much stronger!
It makes me laugh that they
call him "King of the Pirates!"
--He was more like the King of the Bullshitters!
--That's right!
And much greater!
Are you ready to respond
to his expectations?!
I don't know what Whitebeard wants!
Why?
Roger?
But I came here for...
Don't mention the name
that makes me sick, brat!
Although you're worn out and sleeping,
your stomach is active as always.
It's ruining my drink! Go away!
...only one reason, right from the start!
They know that it's just a wild dream that
makes me lightheaded at just the thought of it.
Ace!
The pirates are gaining vigor!
What are you looking at?!
They're gonna break through!
We need more troops!
What do you think you're
doing, you little shit!
Then how can they believe in it?
Vice Admiral-dono!  Let's
get Straw Hat first...!
Wait!
I guess you must hate a grandpa
like me; so intimidating.
They left Whitebeard alone!
Attack Whitebeard now!
...Bullet!
If we can bring Whitebeard
down, we can stop all of them!
Look at you! You got beaten pretty badly!
I thought the war was over once
the walls had been activated!
They think that they can beat me
if they attack me all at one time!
But Luffy,
Damn! Now Whitebeard and Straw
Hat have made it this far!
He's as strong as I thought!
the reason that I'm training you
so harshly to become a Navy soldier is...
It's useless. I have to
become much much stronger...
Hey, Ace? I heard that you're
out of control these days.
...that I don't want you to stray
from the right path at any price.
Next time, I will catch you! I
will be much much stronger and...
Hey, Coby!
That is my wish.
I'll become a Navy...
Old man, you have a grandson, right?
Damn!
...ad...
...admiral someday!
Whitebeard! Is he invincible?!
Does he look happy?
Oh, you're talking about Luffy!
What is it this time?!
I made that promise to him
but I haven't changed at all!
Do it, brat!
You guys are...
He's growing up in fine feather!
Luffy, we'll have a great dinner tonight
You just stopped them from
executing Ace on my behalf!
...the Kuma imposters!
--Old man.
--Huh?
Luffy-san!
because I swiped plenty from the Navy.
Monkey D. Luffy.
I've got to fight too!
Oh no! What a pain in the ass!
You have the middle initial D,
You can eat as much meat as you want!
Do you think...
so show me how the world
will be in years to come!
Grandpa...
...that I deserved to be born?
That's...
"Hawk-Eye!"
Straw Hat Luffy!
I can't do it, grandpa! Move out of my way!
Heads up, Straw boy!
That's something...
I, Momonga won't let you pass through here
in the name of the Navy vice admiral!
If you can't, Ace will die!
Hey you, watch out!
What are you...?!
...you'll see as you live.
No way!
It's the president's order! We consider
the Navy as our enemy for now! Go!
Things don't always go as you want!
I'm not gonna have mercy on you!
Boa Hancock. The Seven Warlords.
Abort attack. Friendly operative.
Vice admiral? The same rank as Grandpa?
Luffy, I consider you...
Carry Straw boy to the ship in a hurry!
You're Daz Bonez, aren't you?
That's right! You guys are on the same side!
Shave!
...my enemy!
Thank you, Hancock!
I have no choice! We gotta
save Ace boy without him...
Moon Walk!
She's the empress, right?
How do you know her?
Straw boy!
Ivan-chan...
Luffy! He called my name again...
You came around!
S-Second...
Thank you, Hancock.
...Gear...
Could you do me a favor one last time?
Seems like you're reaching
your limit! Finger Pistol!
Every time he calls me like that, I'm so...!
Crocodile!
You're sleeping too much, Mr. 1!
Hancock.
We're almost there! We'll be there soon, Ace!
Yes.
Hancock.
Clear the way!
I got out of shape by being in prison.
Yes.
Hancock!
I don't need you here, Straw Hat! Off you go!
Yes!
Luffy!
Hancock.
I'm...
No wonder. He's a rookie after all.
Dammit!
Move aside, Boa Hancock.
--But...
--Hmmm?
Why are you standing in my way, Crocodile?
...he's tenacious.
I'm not in the best mood now.
Ace-san, wait for me! I'll
save you with my life!
I don't want you to call my name!
Garp!
So you better watch yourself, "Hawk-Eye!"
We're almost there!
Luffy!
We're on our way, Ace!
I want to help you, too!
--Ace, we'll save you at any cost!
--Wait for us, Ace!
Shoot Monkey D. Luffy.
Magma brat!
Don't give up!
P-Pops...
Dammit! My mind is so warped!
It's not the right time for this!
I-I'm on my way!
You are off guard!
Pops and brother and friends are...
Boa Hancock. Friendly
operative. Abort attack.
Garp, don't forget that you're one of us!
...going down one by one bleeding, but...!
Take a couple more of these
and get yourself a good rest!
Hey!
Don't say "one last time!"
It'll bring bad luck!
Dammit! My mind is so warped!
It's not the right time for this!
Pops!
What do you think you're doing?!
Things don't always go the way you want!
Pops and brother and friends are...
You're a Warlord, aren't you, Boa Hancock?!
Please! Can you...
Of course,  Marco the Phoenix regenerates!
Why do you keep stopping the Pacifistas?!
...going down one by one bleeding, but...
I'm so happy and I can't stop crying!
I thought you were on the Government side!
Hey! It's your turn now!
I'm so happy that I can't hold back my tears!
You're such a senseless man!
You don't know anything!
At this last moment, I'm starting
to think that I wanna live!
What?!
Let me tell you one thing.
All you have is courage.
Love is always a hurricane!
Sea Prism Stone?!
But, Straw Hat Luffy, if
you're not strong enough,
I beg you! Ivan-chan!
What're you talking about?!
you can't save him no
matter how hard you try.
Commander Marco!
Are you serious about this?!
Vice Admiral Garp!
It looks painful!
Commander Jozu has been beaten, too!
Old man!
Ace...
They even beat our commanders one by one...
You're their parent after all, Garp.
H-He is no competition for an admiral!
They're falling apart!
The Whitebeard Pirates!
No way...
Luffy-san!
He is about to get to the scaffold!
Damn Straw Hat!
You called him a reckless piece of crap!
--Captain Buggy!
--He's awake!
Buggy!
Captain Buggy! How's everything going?
--He's alive!
--I'm so relieved!
He is reckless!
It doesn't look good, guys.
I wonder how he can set "Fire Fist" Ace free.
What happened to me?
You got frozen by Aokiji and...
I appeared sensationally in front
of the whole world a while ago.
Get lost! You fool!
--Kill Whitebeard!
--We won't let you!
But now people are paying attention to Straw
Hat who is running to the scaffold like a fool!
Why don't you just get lost?
Old man!
Captain Buggy!
You Fish-Man monster!
You're not careful.
Oh no! It's too late!
Guys, who should be today's leading star?
Grr! Let me go!
Pops!
Damn! You said that you were
gonna conquer the world!
Now move it!
Captain Buggy!
Everyone, beat Whitebeard!
That's right!
We really believed in you!
I gotta do something flashier
than Straw Hat one more time!
Hey, let me use the Transponder Snail!
Oh no!
Captain Buggy! I'm afraid that
the Snail is still frozen...
Ace's brother!
What?! Defrost it right away!
Ouch!
Pops!
Ace...
It'll melt if you soak it in the seawater
that is heated by Akainu's lava!
JUSTICE
Finally... finally...
I got it!
Captain Buggy wanted to show us
how to save our frozen mates!
It melted!
I made it!
With his frozen body? How great he is!
--Good. Bring it to me!
--Okay!
Luffy!
Here you go!
Let's carry all the other
frozen guys to the water!
You're so...!
Please!
Yeah!
It's shrivelled up!
Hey, before that...
Ace!
Oh, we shouldn't soak it in seawater!
Ow! Save me first, you fools! I mean...
What the hell, I think it still works.
Please help me, I'm drowning...
Whitebeard's command has dulled.
We've taken the trouble to steal it from
the Navy,
Captain Buggy!
we have to take good care of it.
You saved our lives how many times now?!
Pops!
You could've done better than that.
Transponder Snail-san, could
you wake up for a minute?
Damn, you're great! We'll follow
you to the end of the world!
I can't believe that you
let that piece of crap...
Good morning, sir!
Hold on!
...who is so reckless, take the lead!
Take this.
You guys! Thank me as much as you want!
Stay away!
It's your brother's handcuff key.
I have the key!
Looks like I still have my luck!
No, he pulled in his head!
We won't let you lay a finger on Pops!
Luffy, how did you...?!
It's because of your uncanny faces!
How touching!
They think that they can beat me...
By the way, where's Mr. 3?
Please excuse us, we were born this way!
There he is! Straw boy!
The last time we saw Brother 3 was
before the encircling walls came up.
He's there, Jimbei!
Damn! Straw Hat will reach the scaffold any
minute while I'm fooling around like this!
...this easily!
--Who is it?!
--Where is that voice coming from?
That bastard! He made it out of here!
Huh? Is this the wall that
you're talking about?
I don't need any help because I'm...
I knew it! This is exactly
what I thought was happening!
The Navy tried to round up
the Whitebeards with this!
Fire!
I'm...
We're caged birds because of this!
It's up there!
--Why is that face so big?!
--Ivankov of the Revolutionaries army!
I'm Whitebeard!
Not very much longer - make
a path to the scaffold!
How ridiculous!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
Do they really think that they
can stop me with this cheap wall?
--Luffy-kun!
--Are you still alive, Straw boy?!
They're desperate!
--Look! Fleet Admiral Sengoku is using his power!
--I've never seen it before!
Oh, I'm gonna fall, gonna fall...
Or not!
Damn you, Navy! Be ready for it!
You did!
Don't even think that you
can get away with this!
Amazing! To have such conviction
after just being defrosted!
--What are you doing?!
--I'm sorry!
You can't get away from me!
That's how I am!
How boisterous you are.
But what should I do?!
Ivan-chan! Jimbei!
Get out of my way, magma brat!
Let me go!
Sengoku!
O-Old man! I gotta... I gotta...! Let me go!
A giant Buddha!
--He has done a lot already. Treat him.
--Alright!
I can't believe that you even have
such a thing, Straw Hat Luffy!
You bastard!
You don't need to! There's no time for it!
I gotta go! Just let me go!
Damn!
Oh no, the key!
Ace is...! Ace is...!
Pops!
Get ready!
Ace is...! Ace is...!
Aim at them and be ready to
fire at a moment's notice!
Even you can't win out against
the onslaught of time,
Ace is my only brother!!
Whitebeard!
Fish-Man Karate!
No way, the key...!
At any cost... At any
cost, I will... I will...
Arabesque Brick Fist!
That's what I was afraid of the most!
H-He's a monster!
Straw Hat Luffy!
You're a serious criminal who
should be punished by death, too!
Are you telling me to draw their
sympathy by putting these on?
...save him!
I'm gonna execute both of you
brothers with my own bare hands!
Jimbei, what the hell are you doing?!
Pops!
If you have an unguarded moment,
you will lose the fight!
Didn't you hear that I said
"back Ace's brother up?"
--Luffy-kun! Hey!
--It looks very bad!
I don't belong to the Whitebeard Pirates
so I don't have to obey your order!
Please, Surgeon! Save his life!
Marco!
What was that? I passed
out all of a sudden...
Don't hesitate! He's wounded!
Luffy-kun! Luffy-kun!
Stay with me, Luffy-kun!
You can't look away like that!
Stupid!
Straw Hat... Oh!
He is nothing but a bundle of energy
who just bluffs. Young and clumsy.
Jozu!
--Everybody, follow me!
--Yes, sir!
San! Why are you here?!
Should I be the last voice
you hear before you die?
But I like fools like him.
Did he call me wounded?
What is that?!
That's ridiculous! I won't
die from such a small wound!
Hey, San! Protect Ace with a wall!
Gum-Gum...
Those of you who want to die, come forward!
...Giant Balloon!
Pops!
They made a path!
Watch out, it's Whitebeard!
--Hey, Pops is...!
--What?!
I won't die from... such a small...!
The scaffold is close now, Straw boy!
Candle Wall!
Hey! It's too late for you to go out now!
You just run straight!
Look, Coby, there's no question!
It's obviously the Navy's victory!
Alright!
Is he expanding?!
Now is our chance to do it.
I know...
Akainu-san got Whitebeard
If I let you wreak havoc,
this island won't survive!
and Kizaru-san and Aokiji-san got Marco
I'm sorry that you must do this when you're
not fully recovered.
and Jozu, 1st and 3rd division commanders!
...what will happen...
But we need you!
--The scaffold is collapsing!
--What happened?!
It's nothing, Ivan-san.
Then why don't you protect it?
And Straw Hat can't fight anymore
after getting beaten so bad!
...if I die!
Take good care of Luffy-kun!
Don't worry about it.
Ace is still alive!
That was the best they can do
against all the forces of the Navy!
We're falling!
Jimbei, where are you going?!
I'm willing to lay down
my life at this place!
I'll make the key! Uncuff him right away!
Then, you know,
I will be much much stronger and...
Crab-chan!
I can't allow myself to die until...
Alright!
I'll become a Navy...
Captain Buggy! There's brother 3!
...ad...
...admiral someday!
What?! What is he doing in
that ridiculous costume?!
...I see a bright future ahead for my sons!
Whoa! Oh, I mean...
I thought he ran away from here already!
I-I-I'm sorry! I got carried away!
Stay away! Don't get caught up!
It's embarrassing! I wanna crawl in a hole!
After I met you, I became
emboldened a little bit...
Die!
Dammit!
The execution of "Fire Fist" Ace has
to do with the prestige of the Navy HQ!
Coby!
N-No way!
Right, Ace?
You wanna fight me, right?
What a fragile sword!
We have to finish it!
Then, of course you have to
become such a heavy hitter!
That was...
Pops!
After all, it was just a pipe
dream for me to become an admiral!
...the executioners!
Ring, ring, ring... Clank!
Whoa! Wh-What is it?!
Oh, that's good! Admiral Borsalino
stopped Straw Hat in the plaza!
Even Luffy-san's strength gave out
before he accomplished his goal!
Inazuma of the Revolutionaries
army! He did it!
You dotard!
There's a bridge! Alright!
We'll make way for Pops!
Straw Hat?!
It's impossible for me because all I
do is run despite being a Navy soldier!
What is it?!
You gotta save your brother at any cost!
Straw Hat is heading straight
towards the scaffold!
They're swordsmen, too. But...
Do something or he'll reach it!
Mr. 2...!
...poor losers!
Don't let him!
It's just impossible!
W-What are they doing?! Guarding
the back of Whitebeard?!
It's over already! So let's just
sit back and enjoy it from here!
We can't! These pirates aren't letting us by!
Outta my way!
Okay, what should we do now?
Gah! Use guns! Fire at Straw Hat!
Are they willing to die with Whitebeard?!
Alright, Coby?
We're gonna rescue Straw-chan!
Move out of my way!
You guys don't have to understand!
Because I'm his friend! I
don't need any other reasons!
Are you asking me to inject
another shot of Energy Hormone?!
I need to reach Luffy! Don't get in my way!
We'll defend Pops' glory!
That's insane!
Friends?
Bon-chan, the gate's closing.
You gotta stop it now! You've
been fighting since Impel Down!
Oh no!
Boa Hancock is going berserk again!
That's too thoughtful, you fools!
You got poisoned and you were almost killed!
We... have to go.
What?! Th-They are...
You're pushing it too far already!
Pops...
...commanders of the Whitebeards!
Thank you!
Captain Squard,  let's go
and fight with Pops, too!
Like I said before, Energy Hormone is
nothing more than a temporary treatment!
Slave Arrow!
Straw-chan!
--Bon-chan!
--Straw-chan!
Ace's brother! Just run straight, don't stop!
If you just keep using it, you
will die for sure afterwards!
You gotta save your brother at any cost!
The number of dead bodies keeps multiplying!
Break through all at once!
He never ran away.
Captain? Where are you going?
He honored his friendship with Straw Hat!
Don't come with me.
If I'd be able to do all I could...
I'll pay the price in my own way.
Okay guys, hurry up and get ready!
Yes, sir!
I'd be happy to die!
Let me fight, Ivan-chan!
Don't let him pass through!
Gum-Gum...
If you wanna see the future,
I'll show you now, Whitebeard!
I won't let you bother Pops!
...Battle Axe!
I don't think I taste good.
--Pops got beaten!
--Marco! Jozu!
Do it!
If I can't fight now
Ace!
I-It's not over... yet!
Where's the other guy?!
What's taking him so long?!
Luffy-kun, go ahead!
Alright, thanks!
and if I can't rescue Ace, I...
Repel them at once!
Ace!
Since it was such short notice, he's
having trouble getting ready...
Don't let him go!
They are...
It's no use!
Death Wink!
I'd rather take my own life afterwards!!
...the allied pirates who
came from the bay head!
Hey, hurry up!
Do you think that I can't
stop you for doing it?!
Alright, let's go!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Let me have the strength to fight for now!
Yeah, we were expecting you!
No one will pass by here!
Damn! We allowed many of
them to reach the plaza!
Heehaw!
Uncle won't like this!
Just advance, Straw boy!
If I tell you that I'm here out
of respect for my late comrade,
See it for yourself, Whitebeard!
It's a melee so a few
mistakes can't be helped
Straw Hat will make it!
Yeah! Keep going!
but try not to shoot our soldiers
as much as possible, Pacifistas!
Yank Straw Hat down!
are you going to laugh at me?!
Don't do it!
Go, Straw Hat!
No, I won't!
Set Ace free!
Fire! Blow them away!
I can't believe that you use that
kid as a trump card, Whitebeard!
I said I can't! If I let you die now,
I'd be too ashamed to face Dragon!
Save your brother, Straw Hat!
But I won't let him go any further!
Okay!
You hardheaded fool!
I'm on my way, Ace!
Oh no!
Don't do it!
Whitebeard!
Where's the other guy?!
What's taking him so long?!
He's flying!
What are you doing? Shoot him down!
Why don't you stay quiet and watch?
Since it was such short notice, he's
having trouble getting ready...
Straw boy!
No way!
It's not working!
Hey, hurry up!
Ace!
It's alright, just keep shooting!
Alright, let's go!
Don't do it!!
--Brother 3!
--They all got hit!
This is no good!
A-Ace...
"Fire Fist" can't use his power because of
the Sea Prism Stone handcuffs!
--Go!
--Commander Marco!
Luffy!
He's dead!
All right!
And we got Straw Hat, too!
I'm here, Ace!
Do whatever you want!
Hey, what are you doing to Straw Hat?!
There's a tunnel of fire in the smoke!
It's Garp the hero!
Commander Marco!
You've always been like this!
Grandpa! Move out of my way!
Luffy!
I'm not going to move!
S-Straw Hat is...!
I'm on my way!
You've never even listened to me...
Because I'm a vice admiral of the Navy!
Hey, was that...?!
N-No way! I thought he received
a mortal wound by getting kicked
I've been fighting against pirates
since long before you were born!
I never asked you to fight!
Conqueror's... Haki!
...and always done such crazy things!
in the teeth by Kizaru-san!
The hero--Monkey D. Garp!
Hey, come on! For real?!
Old man!
--He finally shows himself!
--The legendary Navy soldier!
--Good!
--Oh my!
H-Hey! Where are you going?!
It's too dangerous!
That was surprising!
If you wanna pass through here,
you have to kill me first!
Ace!
Vice Admiral Garp!
I-I can't believe it!
Straw Hat and brother 3 are alive, too!
Straw Hat Luffy!
--Vice Admiral is on the move!
--He'll be the greatest keeper for us!
Coby...
Because of the path you two...
Old man!
Luffy-san!
That brat...
Garp...
...have chosen to live!!
If you wanna go further,
you have to kill me first!
Luffy!
Ace!!
You brats!
Luffy runs down the path Inazuma created
Using Ivankov's Energy Hormone,
The Whitebeard Pirates slowly begin to
crumble under the Navy's fierce attacks.
Luffy unconsciously used the Conqueror's
Haki and stopped Ace's execution.
Ace is free at last!
Luffy works up the last of
his strength and runs forth.
intent on reaching Ace, but
Garp stands in his way.
Seeing Ace and Luffy taking on the Navy
in such a well-synchronized combination
When Ace sees his friends
injured and falling,
But the Navy, wary of his
display of latent power,
But the Navy forces form a
massive wall in his path.
raises the morale of the Whitebeard Pirates.
The Navy and pirates...
he reflects upon his reason for
existing, and tears come to his eyes.
combine their efforts in an
attempt to eliminate him.
Among them stands one young
man trying to motivate himself
When a grandfather and grandson who walk
different paths meet again in battle,
But Whitebeard, looking to a
future still farther ahead,
Meanwhile, Luffy makes a decision to
put his life on the line to save Ace!
Just then, Iva-san finally
reveals his last trump card!
what feelings are packed into
the blows they exchange?
comes to a decision of his own.
to achieve the heights
he once swore to reach.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Ace Rescued! Whitebeard's Final Order!"
"The Scaffold at Last! The
Way to Ace Has Opened!"
"To Live Up to a Promise!
Luffy and Coby Collide!"
"The Power That Will Shorten One's
Life! Energy Hormone, Redux!"
"Each on Different Paths! Luffy vs. Garp!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!