ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
Trying to make it to the scaffold, Luffy
got over the encircling walls with Jimbei's
The Whitebeards then used their paddle boat
that had been hidden at the bottom of sea...
...and made it to the plaza, too!
Second Gear!
You're too slow!
Go across the sea towards Oars!
We have a problem! Another coated
ship is entering the bay!
Sink it like the Moby Dick!
No! Not the boat! Shoot at Oars!
He pulled the boat out of water!
They broke the encircling walls!
Pops!
Stay back, my sons!
Guys! Rescue Ace and...
...destroy the Navy!!
Garp.
Yeah.
I don't think we can make
it through this unscathed!
"Luffy at the End of His Tether! An
All-out Battle at the Oris Plaza!"
It's curtains for a Devil Fruit
eater if he falls into the sea!
If nothing is done, I'm
gonna really... really...
...fall... fall...
...fall...
Or not!
You're not gonna fall?! You got me there!
What are you doing, Ivankov?
Be quiet please! I need to hear
what's going on at the plaza!
Huh? You are the one who is making noise!
Ouch! I got hurt!
I'm sure that the battle is growing
fiercer on the other side of the wall.
Maybe, Straw boy is already...
...boiled!
Or roasted!
Or iced!
Yeah, maybe that's what happening to him!
Oh no! Oh boy!
What are you doing?! We need to hurry!
It's all your fault, Jimbei!
What?! What did I do?!
Yes! It wouldn't have gone like this if you
had just beaten them and rescued Ace boy already!
That was impossible!
Destroy Navy HQ!
Oars, thank you.
Clear the way in front of me!
Alright!
He's gonna do it again!
I have no choice.
Ice Ball!
--Whitebeard got iced!
--We got him!
Pops!
Oh no! The vibrations can't be frozen!
Ice...
Admiral Kuzan!
--Stabbed with Haki?!
--Did it kill Aokiji?!
No! Don't be ridiculous!
Ice Block: Partisan!
Pops, move on!
I'm counting on you!
Diamond Jozu!
We're almost there!
The scaffold is right there!
If only we could gain control of this mess!
We won't let you! You all die right here!
Ace!
I thought the war was over once
the walls had been activated!
Damn! Now Whitebeard and Straw
Hat have made it this far!
Next time, I will catch you! I
will be much much stronger and...
I'll become a Navy...
...ad...
...admiral someday!
I made that promise to him
but I haven't changed at all!
Luffy-san!
I've got to fight too!
Straw Hat Luffy!
I, Momonga won't let you pass through here
in the name of the Navy vice admiral!
Vice admiral? The same rank as Grandpa?
Shave!
Moon Walk!
S-Second...
...Gear...
Seems like you're reaching
your limit! Finger Pistol!
No wonder. He's a rookie after all.
--But...
--Hmmm?
...he's tenacious.
Garp, don't forget that you're one of us!
All you have is courage.
But, Straw Hat Luffy, if
you're not strong enough,
you can't save him no
matter how hard you try.
Ace...
H-He is no competition for an admiral!
No way...
Luffy-san!
--Kill Whitebeard!
--We won't let you!
Why don't you just get lost?
Ace's brother!
Ace...
Whitebeard's command has dulled.
You could've done better than that.
I can't believe that you
let that piece of crap...
...who is so reckless, take the lead!
We won't let you lay a finger on Pops!
How touching!
There he is! Straw boy!
He's there, Jimbei!
--Who is it?!
--Where is that voice coming from?
I knew it! This is exactly
what I thought was happening!
It's up there!
--Why is that face so big?!
--Ivankov of the Revolutionaries army!
--Luffy-kun!
--Are you still alive, Straw boy?!
Oh, I'm gonna fall, gonna fall...
Or not!
You did!
--What are you doing?!
--I'm sorry!
How boisterous you are.
Ivan-chan! Jimbei!
Let me go!
O-Old man! I gotta... I gotta...! Let me go!
--He has done a lot already. Treat him.
--Alright!
You don't need to! There's no time for it!
I gotta go! Just let me go!
Ace is...! Ace is...!
Ace is my only brother!!
At any cost... At any
cost, I will... I will...
...save him!
--Luffy-kun! Hey!
--It looks very bad!
Please, Surgeon! Save his life!
Luffy-kun! Luffy-kun!
Stay with me, Luffy-kun!
He is nothing but a bundle of energy
who just bluffs. Young and clumsy.
But I like fools like him.
Those of you who want to die, come forward!
Watch out, it's Whitebeard!
If I let you wreak havoc,
this island won't survive!
Then why don't you protect it?
Take good care of Luffy-kun!
Jimbei, where are you going?!
I'm willing to lay down
my life at this place!
Stay away! Don't get caught up!
Die!
Dammit!
N-No way!
What a fragile sword!
We'll make way for Pops!
They're swordsmen, too. But...
...poor losers!
Outta my way!
Move out of my way!
I need to reach Luffy! Don't get in my way!
Oh no!
Boa Hancock is going berserk again!
Slave Arrow!
The number of dead bodies keeps multiplying!
I won't let you bother Pops!
I don't think I taste good.
I-It's not over... yet!
Repel them at once!
They are...
...the allied pirates who
came from the bay head!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Yeah, we were expecting you!
Damn! We allowed many of
them to reach the plaza!
Uncle won't like this!
It's a melee so a few
mistakes can't be helped
but try not to shoot our soldiers
as much as possible, Pacifistas!
I'm on my way, Ace!
He's flying!
What are you doing? Shoot him down!
It's not working!
It's alright, just keep shooting!
This is no good!
--Go!
--Commander Marco!
Commander Marco!
I never asked you to fight!
The hero--Monkey D. Garp!
--He finally shows himself!
--The legendary Navy soldier!
Vice Admiral Garp!
--Vice Admiral is on the move!
--He'll be the greatest keeper for us!
Old man!
Garp...
If you wanna go further,
you have to kill me first!
You brats!
The Whitebeard Pirates slowly begin to
crumble under the Navy's fierce attacks.
When Ace sees his friends
injured and falling,
he reflects upon his reason for
existing, and tears come to his eyes.
Meanwhile, Luffy makes a decision to
put his life on the line to save Ace!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Power That Will Shorten One's
Life! Energy Hormone, Redux!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!