ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
"Ending the Matter! Whitebeard
vs. The Blackbeard Pirates!"
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
He and the Whitebeards have invaded
the plaza to make it to the scaffold!
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
In the midst of the Navy's onslaught,
with the Whitebeards' assistance,
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Luffy finally freed Ace! However...
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
Watch what I do.
Wait!
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
Luffy!
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
Shiryu! You bastard!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
What happened to Magellan?
What's going on at Impel Down?
How did you guys get here?
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who was to be executed!
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
In the midst of the Navy's onslaught,
Luffy finally freed Ace! However,
He and the Whitebeards finally got over the
cling walls to make it to the scaffold!
He and the Whitebeards have invaded to
the plaza to make it to the scaffold!
I think the fact that we're here is the
answer to your questions,
In the midst of the Navy's onslaught,
with the Whitebeards' assistance,
Admiral Akainu landed a
fatal blow against Ace!
don't you think?
In the midst of the Navy's onslaught, Luffy
runs toward Ace with the Whitebeards' tance!
Fleet Admiral Sengoku-san?
Luffy ran on the path that Inazuma
created and finally made it to Ace!
"Looking for the Answer! Fire Fist
Ace Dies on the Battlefield!"
Pops!
Everybody!
If you wanna know more, why don't
you check it yourself later.
And you Luffy.
I'm a remnant from the old times!
Anyway, I've allied with these guys.
Thank you...
Finally... finally...
There is no ship that can
bear me in the new era!
...for loving someone like
me who is good for nothing...
Remember that from now on!
I made it!
...and who has such bad blood in his veins...
Luffy!
Ace...
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
You're so...!
I didn't have a chance to tell you but...
Fire! Blow them away!
Let's get it over with!
...I got a report that the Gates
of Justice have opened again
...up to today.
and an unidentified ship
passed through a while ago!
"The Power That Can Burn Even
Fire! Akainu's Ruthless Pursuit!"
That must've been them!
But the control room is under Navy control
There's a tunnel of fire in the smoke!
and I didn't hear about
any unusual circumstances!
Thank you!
You've always been like this!
--Marineford is in danger!
--Stop Whitebeard!
How did they get here?
Luffy!
ABSOLUTE JUSTICE
I'm sorry.
He's willing to destroy the whole island!
You've never even listened to me...
That's quite simple.
Ace!
Before we, the Blackbeard
Pirates, set off for Impel Down,
Ace!
Pops!
...and always done such crazy things!
I hypnotized the Navy soldiers
in the control room...
I don't wanna leave you!
You gotta come with us!
Ace-san!
"The Navy Headquarters Falls!
Whitebeard's Unspeakable Wrath!"
Pops!
...to open the Gates of Justice
for any Navy ship that approaches.
Ace!!
Ace!
Do you disobey your Captain's order?!
It turns out that it helped the others too.
Why don't you just go, fools?!
Straw Hat and the others?
Pops!
Ace...
If I were regarded as an
enemy by the Government,
Now is our chance! Kill
Whitebeard! He's dying already!
"Ace Rescued! Whitebeard's Final Order!"
the Gates of Justice won't open
for me and I couldn't have
sneaked into Impel Down!
That's why I wanted the
title of The Seven Warlords!
He's been beaten! Dammit!
But I don't need it anymore!
Pops!
Stop Akainu!
Hurry up! Let's do as Pops said!
So you just wanted to free your crew members!
You don't mind leaving Pops behind?!
Can't believe it!
Yes, indeed! That's all I
wanted from the beginning!
Yeah, how dare you!
And that's all that matters!
Stupid! No one wants to leave him alone!
Hurry up! Do something about these handcuffs!
You'll see why!
Then...
Grumbling about it at a time
"F-Fire Fist" Ace is...
I'm trying but... Damn, I can't break them!
like this is the same as trampling
on Pops' determination!
...now free!
Oh yeah! He can do it!
Can't you understand?!
--He?
--Yeah, the guy who uncuffed Ace!
Great! You did it, Straw Hat!
Did you think that I was dead?
He rescued Ace!
Pops!
I'll make the key! Uncuff him right away!
He has been relentless since
Impel Down! That guy is really...
I don't give a damn about any of this!
Hurry and get ready to sail out!
But...!
Yeah, you're right! Bring him here now!
...Something else!
Why are you crying?! I'm not dead, fool!
Ace!
Okay!
Fire!
I'm relieved!
Teach!
You finally accomplished your mission, Luffy!
I promise that I'll never die!
If we can escape here in one piece...
How can I leave a wimpy
brother like you behind?
We're gonna leave soon! Come on now!
Look out! Captain!
We'll be married!
Look, Coby! Damn Straw Hat finally did it!
How's this war going to end?
Commander Marco, let's go!
Luffy-san, you're awesome!
Pops...
Don't lose your cool!  Be ready to fire!
Garp!
Look after my child!
--Shoot them as they land!
--Yes, sir!
--You messed with us!
--Die!
We made you pay for what you've done to
Ace! Have you learned a lesson, Akainu?
His name is Gol D. Ace.
W-Wait! All I want is to get away!
Stay alert, Luffy! Let's split up for now!
I have no intention to fight...
Okay!
Oh no!
That was close! That was close!
We had a narrow escape!
W-What?!
My wax is as strong as steel!
Flame Commandment!
There's no way that a
normal sword can cut it!
Did you know? We can become brothers
if we exchange this cup of sake!
Fire Pillar!
He's also a Devil Fruit eater!
No wonder!
He's strong enough to try to protect
"Fire Fist" even at Fleet Admiral Sengoku's elbow!
From now on,
You have no mercy, huh?! Of course you don't!
No no, don't overestimate me
like that! I'm not a big deal...
we're brothers!
You're the only one that I
refuse to call my son, Teach!
Oh no!
No way! Is he a monster?!
You broke the one and only iron rule
on my ship and you killed your mate!
Damn Whitebeard!
I can't believe he still has that much
power after getting wounded so badly!
I will avenge the 4th
division commander--Thatch
He's so strong! Be careful!
by taking this fool's life
thereby ending the matter!
You got to be kidding me!
Since he isn't concerned about
"Fire Fist" Ace anymore...
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
Can you fight, Luffy?
It's clear his intention is to
sink Marineford into the ocean.
Of course!
Pops!
Ace-san! Luffy-kun!
Marco!
Along with himself!
Looks like you're still alive!
Don't forget! "Fire Fist"
Ace is fire--Logia type!
Ace...!
Pops!
"Fire Fist" Ace!
I never thought that I'd
be saved by you one day!
Vice Admiral Garp! You're alive!
Keep yourself out of this!
He wants to change the era?
Yeah, the time is right.
Ace!
Thanks, Luffy!
Pops!
Don't do it...
Do you hear me?!
Don't do it!
Whitebeard and the others helped me to do it!
Ace!
What happened to Whitebeard?!
His allies who have been
sold out are all dead now?!
Let's get it over with, Teach!
Don't think that you're safe now!
Is the connection still out?!
This is now your execution ground!
How long should we wait?!
I'm looking forward to it!
I can't believe you let your
guard down, Whitebeard!
Damn! We couldn't see the whole picture
I won't let you interrupt!
because Buggy the Clown stood in our way!
Brat!
What is that black stuff
coming out of his body?
The guy over there must be...!
--Now is the chance!
--I'll cut you into pieces!
The great pirate--Captain Buggy the Clown?!
Smoke?!
Jimbei!
He's my brother! Leave him alone!
Yes, that's who I am indeed!
You can't touch him anymore!
What did he want to say?!
Ace!!
You're just delaying the inevitable,
Jimbei! Since you were once a Warlord,
If nothing is done, I can't report
anything to the head office!
Fire Fist!
What's going on at Marineford now?!
I bet you know what I'm capable of!
What?!
Black Hole!
The Transponder Snail hasn't come out yet?!
I'd be happy to risk my
life if I can delay it!
"Fire Fist" Ace is dead!
Damn! Captain Buggy is about to beat
Whitebeard - it's no time for this!
Second Gear!
Shave!
I've been ready to die from the beginning!
Don't say it as if it's so easy!
This is the power of the Devil Fruit
that I stole from Thatch by killing him!
Jimbei!
Gum-Gum...
Marco! He's here!
He's dying but he still has boundless
power - didn't they see it?!
...Jet Stamp!
Gee, thank you for helping
me! I almost got killed...
The most dominant Dark-Dark Fruit!
Enjoy it to the fullest extent!
Why did I even say that I'm gonna beat
that man?! I really screwed this up!
Fire Gun!
Cut the crap and uncuff me now!
I can't do it! It's impossible!
What?! We gotta broadcast Captain
Buggy's big moment all over the world!
Die!
Hey, Pops! Thatch died
and then Ace died, too!
Get it out at any cost!
Straw boy!
V-Vice Admiral Garp!
Let's hurry, Luffy! We gotta
get out of this place!
He's losing it!
--Come out now!
--Or we're gonna burn you out of it!
I looked up to you and longed
to be like you but you got old!
His life is in danger!
No, we gotta soak it into water!
What are you...?
Garp!
Alright!
--Let's do that!
--Come on!
You can't even save your man
from getting killed now!
--Stop it, fools!
--Huh?
They make a perfect pair!
What are you doing?! Are
you losing your mind?!
Make room for them to run!
I tried not to kill Ace at
the Banaro Island for you!
It's not like he volunteered
to be a slave for the Navy.
You better keep holding me
down like that, Sengoku!
It's Akainu!
Don't let them get away at any cost!
I'll get you this time for sure!
But he got beaten up in the
battlefield like this.
That bastard!
Oh no no, it's no use!
Because if you don't, I will kill Sakazuki!
Don't you feel sorry for him?
Firefly!
Just let him go, okay?
Straw Hat!
There's no Devil Fruit power
that works against me!
Fiery Doll!
Then we gotta cancel "Captain
Buggy's beating beard
You fool!
and broadcast it live to the world" plan?!
Execute "Fire Fist" and Straw Hat!
No way! Even you want to
pull out from Marineford?!
Gum-Gum...
Looks like I need to execute a traitor, too!
...Jet Gatling!
Vortex!
I'm not gonna let you kill him!
I'm disappointed in you, Captain Buggy!
Luffy-kun! Luffy-kun! Stay with me!
Oh no!
When it comes down to it,
Move out of my way!
Do you like my darkness, Pops?!
Jimbei, get down!
they're all strong guys who've
been locked up in Impel Down!
It drags in and nullifies even
the powers of Devil Fruits!
I better not make enemies of them!
The war is not over yet!
The Transponder Snail came out voluntarily!
Which means you can't create
earthquakes anymore!
How annoying!
Oh, he's...
...crying!
Take Ace's brother with you, Jimbei!
Oh yeah! He came out because he was
touched by Captain Buggy's kindness!
I can't believe Pops got hit like that!
So you guys are Haki users!
All right!
How could we let that happen?!
Straw Hat's life is how
Ace's life will live on!
I couldn't have more regret about it!
Captain Buggy can even win
the hearts of the Snails!
Can't you see that it's too
late to save "Fire Fist?!"
Commander... Marco!
He's amazing as we thought!
Oops!
That is the man who will conquer
the world - he's our Captain Buggy!
Take a look!
We will protect him at any
cost on Ace's behalf!
Don't you get it yet?!
D-Damn bastard! Why didn't
he just stay inside?!
If we let him die,
How do you like my power?!
Now there's no way that I can back out!
it's a dishonor to the Whitebeard Pirates!
Alright, let's begin!
You got stronger, Luffy!
Captain Buggy, make a declaration
to conquer the world now!
It's no use!
What a poor sport, Pops!
--It's your moment!
--Smoke: good, lighting: good!
Ace...
Luffy-kun, don't lose your sanity!
Stand by!
Oh no, I mean... Dammit!
This leaves me one choice!
I'll become stronger than you someday!
Hey, are you all right? Hey.
I told you that I won't
let the brothers get away!
Alright, shoot my bravery!
Ouch! Damn!
Then, let me protect you for now!
It hurts!
Capture the moment that I kill Whitebeard!
Straw Hat!
"Someday?" There's no tomorrow for you.
Ace, you need to get treated right away!
Arrogance, thoughtlessness...
Those are your weaknesses!
You think that you can escape?
Akainu-san!
--Hey, look!
--The picture's back!
I'm sorry, Luffy...
But I can't see what's going
on because of the smoke!
Admiral Kuzan!
That bastard!
Huh?
Is the Navy losing?! What
happened to Whitebeard and Ace?!
Hey, don't!
Ice Block!
Pops, don't!
In order to save me,
Back up, Luffy.
--Um, well...
--Transponder Snail, go lower!
I'm your son!
you pushed yourself that far but...
How can you kill me...?
...I couldn't make it all the way.
Hi, everyone! I'm Buggy and I'm a legend!
You again?!
I'm sorry.
Pheasant Beak!
Get to the sea now!
Flame Mirror!
Wh-What are you saying?
We who remain have to go back
to the New World safely!
Don't be ridiculous!
Somebody, treat him!
Don't let them get away!
Kill as many as you can!
You did it! Pops!
Please! Please help Ace!
I'm the only one that you
ought to worry about!
Hey somebody! Help Ace! Please!
No, look at that!
--Hurry! This way! Give him first aid now!
--Okay!
Commander Jozu!
Looks like he's badly
injured but he'll make it!
Straw boy...
Ace! Are you alright?!
Captain gave us an order! Come with us!
Damn! I can't believe it! He's tough!
Hurry up and treat him!
Brenheim! You gotta carry Jozu!
Okay, let me see the wound!
A final blow! Give him a final blow, Pops!
Please!
Pops is furious!
--Just one more hit!
--Finish him off!
Straw boy! Why are you standing around?!
Guys, we gotta get out of here!
This is...!
Pops!
Ace, let's go! The old man
has made up his mind...
Huh?
Hey.
What's the matter? Hurry up and help him!
I know! And it won't be in vain!
I'm sorry.
Aokiji-san's ice was instantly vaporized!
Pops! What's wrong?!
Back off, you bastards!
What do you mean by that?
He's our 2nd division commander!
Of course, he's capable of that!
What's going on?! Just do something!
Hey, aren't you a doctor?! Hey!
He isn't moving!
--Cool!
--What brothers!
It's no use.
Stop being impressed, you boneheads!
My organs have been burned.
Fix the Transponder Snail already!
I can't hold out any longer.
I don't think he's frozen by choice!
Y-Yes, sir!
I can tell that my life is ending.
On top of his worsening health,
And now, I wonder how far he can run...
The important part begins here, Straw Hat!
he's taking a lot of damage
from all this fierce fighting!
That's not true!
Oh yeah, Ivan-chan!
Pops' body is already beyond...!
Hey, I beg you!
At any rate, if I can finish off Whitebeard
who's already dying in this confusion...
Inject that stuff into Ace! Please!
Hell Hound!
Like you did to me, why can't you help Ace?!
...then I'll join The Four Emperors!
Hey, I beg you! Please! Help! Help Ace!
Pops!
Wow! He's relaxing during a situation
like this! That's our Captain Buggy!
Please inject that into Ace...
Straw boy!
We don't need words now.
Ace boy... can't make it!
Mr. 2...
Y-You damn monster!
I hardly granted your wish.
Huh? No way.
Just tell me one thing.
You promised me!
And now, I gotta hurry and escape...
You useless old man!
To whom does this traitor owe allegiance?!
You said...
Shut up and die!
...that you'd never die...
Are you happy to have me as your father?
No, he's a prisoner impersonating a guard!
...no matter what!
You must resign!
Oh no!
Ace!!
Fleet Admiral-dono!
Pops!!
I can't believe this blunder!
Even I couldn't stop it!
Pops!!
Still some fight left in you?
You are too valuable to let die now, boy.
Kill him, guys!
Let them go! That way, things
will be more interesting!
If you still wanna run wild, run as wild
as you want on the sea under my name.
Cut the crap!
Even an admiral's power
is useless against them!
Become my son!
How can we fight them?!
Don't lose your head!
Admiral Sakazuki!
Pops!
We won't let them get away from here!
Of course I am!
Pops!
Don't be afraid! Let's beat them!
Ace...
What did you say?
You can't hold out any longer?
W-What now?!
You promised me...
...that you'd never die...
Pops.
...no matter what, Ace!
Heads up, everyone! Their ship is moving!
Don't get close! It's running
on the ground with its paddles!
Hey, who is on board?!
Pops.
Pops!
Wh-What was that?!
Pops!!
--Squard!
--The Whirl Spider Pirates!
Do I even deserve to have been born?
--The scaffold was destroyed!
--So was the Navy HQ!
Did Ace get executed?! What's going on?!
Pops, everyone, run!
What if Gold Roger had a child?
Move the camera to Whitebeard!
Leave the war to us!
I'm Buggy and I'm a legend!
Of course I know what'd happen to him!
He'd get his head cut off for sure!
The great pirate--Captain Buggy the Clown!
Is it true that you're
gonna beat Whitebeard?!
Those fools!
No way! I'm not content if
we kill him that easily!
And with his head in your hand,
Shoot him! Riddle him with bullets!
you're willing to become
one of The Four Emperors?!
How about we prick him with a needle
once for every grudge that
someone holds against Roger?!
I'm Buggy and I'm a legend!
You're just repeating that!
Pops!
No way! Instead, we'll burn him alive first
Say something forward-looking!
Let's do it again!
Pops!
and humiliate him prior to death
in front of the whole world!
Enough with Buggy! Show us
Marineford as it stands!
Oh yeah!
You're not what we're interested in!
Did you say that you're
gonna die soon, Roger?
That's nice!
Everybody will say "that serves him right!"
Yeah, it's only a matter of time.
No, I mean... I just wanna
do something flashy...
Don't be silly, Squard!
Obviously, you have a death wish!
What are you doing?!
I want to hear from him as he dies:
Do you want me to tell you how
to get to Raftel, Whitebeard?
"I'm sorry I was born! I'm
just a piece of trash!"
Run! Run to the ship!
Of course, I have.
I'm not gonna go there anyway
because I've no interest.
What I did to Pops was horrible.
--Ace-san, Luffy-kun, get in front of me!
--Jimbei!
But I don't think that he ever had a child!
They want to get you two!
Do you know what people of the World
Government call me these days?
But what the good old man wants
is as many survivors as possible!
Even if this doesn't make amends for it,
No one wanted me to be born.
Good old man!
I can't let things go like this!
"Gold Roger."
We've stolen a Navy ship! Get on board quick!
What? Is that your real name?
I'm sorry, guys. I shouldn't have let you on.
No, no!
Ace! You caused trouble in the city again!
My name is Gol D. Roger.
--It's okay, Captain! Don't worry!
--We followed you because we wanted to!
Do they really think that they can
get away?! How simple they are!
They're making a fuss about
it! Don't give us a hard time!
I meet people with "D"
in their names sometimes.
Admiral Sakazuki!
We'll choose where to die our own!
You guys, move aside a little bit!
Hey! Are you listening, Ace?!
Captain! We'll follow you to the end!
--Shut up, Dadan!
--What'd you say?!
I have a crew member who
has it. His name is Teach.
I'm sorry...
If I were stronger, I would
have killed all of them!
Everybody, take Ace and run!
What does "D" stand for?
St. Elmo's Fire!
You two, just keep going
until you get to the ship!
I wouldn't even have a will to live...
Ah, do you wanna know that?
As soon as you rescue
"Fire Fist" Ace, you run!
Squard!
...if it weren't for Sabo and a
high-maintenance brother like you.
Alright, I tell you.
The Whitebeards must be a group of cowards!
Navy HQ is collapsing!
It's a story from way back...
What?!
He's trying to stir you up obviously!
Fool!
Oh yeah. If you see Dadan
someday, say hello for me.
If you stop, you're playing into his hands!
Damn Squard! That's not
the smart way to do it!
Well your captain is that guy
so you can't help it, can you?
Whoa, I'm out of bullets!
Hey, give me another gun!
Hey! Hurry up and uncuff me!
You don't need it!
Because after all, Whitebeard is just a...
When I face my own death, I
even miss a woman like her.
Whitebeard is unconscious now!
You guys! Are you all ready?!
He's gonna collapse if you
push him with your finger!
...loser from the old times!
Like I said, don't say that you're gonna die!
You bastard!
It's not you!
Ace!
Advance!
You're still alive?!
There is one thing that makes me wanna stay.
Whitebeard!
A loser?
The man that Roger is waiting for...
That is my desire to see
you fulfill your dream.
...is not you, Teach, at any rate!
Admiral Sakazuki!
Take back what you just said!
But I'm sure that you can do it!
Pops!
Hey, don't, Ace! Don't stop!
Like there are people who
will inherit Roger's will,
--Don't fall!
--Hang on!
Just let him say whatever he wants!
Because you're my brother!
He mocked Pops!
some people inherit Ace's
sometime in the future!
Ace!
Did you say "take it back?"
What happened?!
Not in a million years! I'll tell you why.
That day...
Even if you break their blood bond,
The ship has stopped!
you'll
never be able to extinguish their flame!
Your father Gold Roger
conquered the Grand Line
That's how it came down
unbroken throughout the ages!
Listen, Luffy.
and opened the door to the new era called
We have to live without leaving any regrets.
the Great Pirate Era by sacrificing himself.
And someday in the future,
Uh-huh.
Is it over?
We gotta go out to sea someday...
How's Pops?!
As a Navy admiral, it's
not my place to say so,
carrying hundreds of years
of history on his shoulder,
but he was true to his name:
the King of the Pirates!
...and live as we like.
Pops!
Freer than anyone else.
In contrast, what has Whitebeard done?
W-With just one hand...
someone will fling down the
gauntlet in front of the world!
He stopped the ship!
Pops!
I wonder if he really had
the intention to fight .
Sengoku! You and the World
Government are afraid of...
Like we promised that
day, I have no regret...
I assume that he established
a large family someplace
...the gigantic war that will
embroil the whole world in one day!
and was satisfied being a
big fish in a little barrel.
The plaza has split in two! The
pirates are on the other side!
...in my life.
There are some fools in the world
That's a lie! Don't tell a lie!
who'd say that his name is
keeping peace on various islands
Can't you understand how
ungrateful it is for a child...
We are completely separated from Pops!
I'm not lying.
but if you ask me, he's just keeping
lightweights in fear of him
Pops!
I've no interest in it but...
Something tells me that what
I truly wanted was not fame.
...to die before his parent, Squard?!
...when someone finds the treasure,
the world will turn upside down!
and he thinks that he's a
hero which makes me laugh!
Pops!
When Roger was alive,
Whitebeard had second billing
Did I deserve to be born?
and even after Roger's death,
he couldn't become a King.
And I'm sure somebody will find it!
What I wanted was the
answer for that question.
That means he'll never better Roger
and he'll be a loser forever!
Don't get too confident!
And that day will come!
That little stab wound that you created
doesn't really jeopardize my life!
Become my son!
That's who Whitebeard
is and that's the truth.
You better tell me that my
beloved son is all right.
He still got this much power
after his torso has been charred?
Everybody has his own duration of life!
He's a poor man when you think about it.
The One Piece...
I'm your brother!
He gathered some punks who call him Pops
You can say whatever you want!
...is real!!
and roamed around the sea
with his fake family.
You haven't seen anything yet.
I'm gonna save you even if it means death!
Stop it.
And although he reigned the sea for years,
Guys! Rescue Ace and...
We accomplished our goal here!
he couldn't become a King and gained nothing
There's no need to stay here anymore!
...destroy the Navy!!
and at the end, he was stabbed by a fool,
You bastard!
one of his sons who fell for my line
--Good old man!
--Pops!
I'm gonna get Ace back!!
and he will die to protect that son.
Don't you think that his life is so empty?
What great last words!
Listen carefully, Whitebeard Pirates!
--Pops!
Finally...
From now on,
I made it! Ace!
I'm the only one who you have to deal with!
Pops...
I'm gonna give you an order
from the Captain one last time!
Stop it!
Just tell me one thing.
Don't do it, Ace, come back!
Bring it on!
Forgive me, my sons.
Ace!
What do you mean "last?!"
Wait, Pops, that's too sad!
Are you happy to have me as your father?
Pops gave us a place to live!
I raised such a ridiculous fool.
I don't wanna hear such thing!
Let's go back to the New World together!
You can't understand his greatness!
You guys gave me everything.
Cross Fire!
People don't deserve to live
if they can't live justly!
Pops!
All of you and I will split up from here!
Punks like you guys don't
deserve a place to live!
This is it for me.
Everyone, survive at any cost and
go back to the New World safely!
Stop it!
Everybody, get on the ship!
Whitebeard will die as a loser! It's
fitting for a big fish in a little barrel!
I can't raise my voice to let
everybody hear me anymore.
Pops!
Think about why Pops stayed on that
side and the wish that he left for us!
Whitebeard is a great pirate
who shaped this era!
I've been traveling a very long time.
Could you tell them...
Cry after you get on the ship!
P-Pops! Are you planning to die here?!
Don't make fun of the man who saved me!
--Pops! Ace!
--Hurry up!
...what I'm about to say now?
Don't do it, Ace!
I'm a remnant from the old times!
The name of this era should be "Whitebeard!"
Let's sail out!
Bring all able ships alongside the bay head!
There is no ship that can
bear me in the new era!
Pops!
We won't let you get away!
Everybody!
Hurry up, everyone!
And you Luffy.
It was a great voyage!
Both Whitebeard and you
guys who call him Pops
Thank you...
Salome! I can't stop worrying about Luffy!
That's odd! What kind of pirate
doesn't have interest in treasures?
Go, you guys!!
are the same after all--losers!
...for loving someone like
me who is good for nothing...
What is it that you want?
...and who has such bad blood in his veins...
Forgive me for disobeying you
and staying back to watch, Pops.
Hey, Newgate!
Ace has been burned!
There is something that I've
wanted since I was a kid.
Whitebeard!
Oh, you have something?
Why don't you tell us?
Are you careless because you
ate a Logia type fruit which
is the most powerful of all?
...up to today.
You're just fire but my
magma can even burn fire!
No, Pops!
It's an order! We gotta go!
My power is far stronger than yours.
A family.
Old guy!
Pops!
Thank you!
Ace!
"A family?" What is he talking about?!
Hey, Luffy-kun, you should not fight anymore!
I have deep appreciation.
Goodbye, my sons!
Ace's Vivre Card!
Don't look back!
Gold Roger the King of the Pirates,
Dragon--the revolutionary.
Because the era is changing!
I was amazed to hear that sons
of those two are step brothers.
You two have bad blood in your veins.
Hey, look! What is that?!
I don't care if the others get
away as long as I get you two!
There is something behind the HQ building!
Watch what I do.
Oh, they found me!
Good old man...
Wait!
Not only him! Who are they on the scaffold?
Luffy!
Oh... They noticed us finally.
It's you! How did you all get here?!
Old man.
Huh?
He-He died...
Why are they here?!
Do you think...
You bastard.
...standing!
Whitebeard passed away!
...that I deserved to be born?
They're the most heinous criminals
whose existence has been erased
because of their brutality!
Everything started on that sea...
That's something...
He's the biggest of all living things!
...you'll see as you live.
This is unbelievable!
A Pirate--"Great Battleship" San Juan Wolf!
Hey, why do you look so out of spirits?
"GREAT BATTLESHIP" SAN JUAN WOLF
Oh, not only am I found
but they know who I am!
Join us! There's more than enough treasure!
Although he's dead, his
body doesn't collapse!
Never mind about him.
"Corrupt King" Avalo Pizarro!
"CORRUPT KING" AVALO PIZARRO
Huh? What do you mean? We got
these treasures thanks to him...
I missed being back on the street!
And the way he mowed down enemies
with wounds all over his body...
"Heavy Drinker" Vasco Shot!
Just leave him! He's not
interested in treasures.
...was certainly monstrous!
"HEAVY DRINKER" VASCO SHOT
That's odd! What kind of pirate is he?
Ace...
This is certainly a Vivre Card.
But I haven't told you that this card
Am I allowed to kill them all?
What is it that you want?
The number of sword wounds he
received in this war is indeed 267!
also tells you how much
vital energy the owner has.
"Crescent Moon Hunter" Catarina Devon!
Hey, Newgate!
"CRESCENT MOON HUNTER" CATARINA DEVON
This card belongs to someone
who you care for, right?
Ace...
Can't believe how much you guys want it.
The number of gun wounds: 152!
Yeah, it's my brother's!
And the Jail Manager of Impel Down
And he was shot by a cannon 46 times!
SHIRYU OF THE RAIN
Hold onto it, always.
Shiryu of the Rain!
That paper will lead us to one another.
They're the Blackbeard Pirates!
Yet,
on his proud back...
I've been traveling a very long time.
...or in his whole pirate life,
Long time no see! I'm glad that
I'm present at your death!
there is no scar that he
got while running away!
Pops!
Let's get it over with!
Teach...!
Navy!
It is a reality difficult to accept.
Ace is pierced by Akainu's
fist while protecting Luffy.
Following Whitebeard's last order, the
pirates swallow their sadness and retreat.
The Navy sweeps in to
It all started with this man.
wipe out the pirates as the loss
of Whitebeard slows their retreat,
Ace's death cruelly unfolds
before Luffy's eyes.
Jimbei and the Whitebeard
Pirates try to save him,
Blackbeard, driven by his hidden
ambition, attacks Whitebeard.
But Akainu's cruel words
directed at Whitebeard
and Akainu stands once again in
front of the unconscious Luffy.
But the battle does not pause.
but Ace, realizing he is about to die,
Whitebeard fights back,
intent on avenging Thatch.
stop Ace in his tracks.
Meanwhile, Blackbeard prepares to reveal
As the pursuit intensifies,
finds the voice to convey his feelings
to his friends one last time.
Ace shakes off his friends' protests and
leaps forward--to be met by Akainu's fist!
Whitebeard's rage shakes all of Marineford!
The fated battle begins at last!
what he's really plotting to the whole world!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Looking for the Answer! Fire Fist Ace
Dies on the Battlefield!"
"The Navy Headquarters Falls!
Whitebeard's Unspeakable Wrath!"
"The Power That Can Burn Even
Fire! Akainu's Ruthless Pursuit!"
"Ending the Matter! Whitebeard
vs. The Blackbeard Pirates!"
"The Show Begins! Blackbeard's
Plot is Revealed!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!