ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
He and the Whitebeards finally got over the
cling walls to make it to the scaffold!
In the midst of the Navy's onslaught, Luffy
runs toward Ace with the Whitebeards' tance!
Finally... finally...
I made it!
Luffy!
You're so...!
Fire! Blow them away!
There's a tunnel of fire in the smoke!
You've always been like this!
Luffy!
You've never even listened to me...
...and always done such crazy things!
Ace!!
"Ace Rescued! Whitebeard's Final Order!"
"F-Fire Fist" Ace is...
...now free!
Great! You did it, Straw Hat!
He rescued Ace!
He has been relentless since
Impel Down! That guy is really...
...Something else!
I'm relieved!
You finally accomplished your mission, Luffy!
If we can escape here in one piece...
We'll be married!
Look, Coby! Damn Straw Hat finally did it!
Luffy-san, you're awesome!
Don't lose your cool!  Be ready to fire!
--Shoot them as they land!
--Yes, sir!
Stay alert, Luffy! Let's split up for now!
Okay!
Oh no!
Flame Commandment!
Fire Pillar!
He's so strong! Be careful!
Can you fight, Luffy?
Of course!
Ace-san! Luffy-kun!
Don't forget! "Fire Fist"
Ace is fire--Logia type!
I never thought that I'd
be saved by you one day!
Thanks, Luffy!
Whitebeard and the others helped me to do it!
Don't think that you're safe now!
This is now your execution ground!
--Now is the chance!
--I'll cut you into pieces!
He's my brother! Leave him alone!
Fire Fist!
Second Gear!
Shave!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Stamp!
Fire Gun!
Die!
Let's hurry, Luffy! We gotta
get out of this place!
Alright!
They make a perfect pair!
Make room for them to run!
Don't let them get away at any cost!
Firefly!
Fiery Doll!
Execute "Fire Fist" and Straw Hat!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
You got stronger, Luffy!
I'll become stronger than you someday!
Then, let me protect you for now!
"Someday?" There's no tomorrow for you.
You think that you can escape?
Admiral Kuzan!
That bastard!
Ice Block!
Back up, Luffy.
Pheasant Beak!
Flame Mirror!
Aokiji-san's ice was instantly vaporized!
He's our 2nd division commander!
Of course, he's capable of that!
--Cool!
--What brothers!
Stop being impressed, you boneheads!
Fix the Transponder Snail already!
Y-Yes, sir!
And now, I wonder how far he can run...
The important part begins here, Straw Hat!
At any rate, if I can finish off Whitebeard
who's already dying in this confusion...
...then I'll join The Four Emperors!
Wow! He's relaxing during a situation
like this! That's our Captain Buggy!
Mr. 2...
I hardly granted your wish.
And now, I gotta hurry and escape...
To whom does this traitor owe allegiance?!
No, he's a prisoner impersonating a guard!
Oh no!
Fleet Admiral-dono!
I can't believe this blunder!
Even I couldn't stop it!
Let them go! That way, things
will be more interesting!
Cut the crap!
Even an admiral's power
is useless against them!
How can we fight them?!
Don't lose your head!
Admiral Sakazuki!
We won't let them get away from here!
Don't be afraid! Let's beat them!
W-What now?!
Heads up, everyone! Their ship is moving!
Don't get close! It's running
on the ground with its paddles!
Hey, who is on board?!
--Squard!
--The Whirl Spider Pirates!
Pops, everyone, run!
Leave the war to us!
Those fools!
Don't be silly, Squard!
Obviously, you have a death wish!
Of course, I have.
What I did to Pops was horrible.
Even if this doesn't make amends for it,
I can't let things go like this!
I'm sorry, guys. I shouldn't have let you on.
--It's okay, Captain! Don't worry!
--We followed you because we wanted to!
We'll choose where to die our own!
Captain! We'll follow you to the end!
I'm sorry...
Everybody, take Ace and run!
St. Elmo's Fire!
Squard!
Fool!
Damn Squard! That's not
the smart way to do it!
Hey! Hurry up and uncuff me!
You guys! Are you all ready?!
Advance!
Pops!
What happened?!
The ship has stopped!
Pops!
W-With just one hand...
He stopped the ship!
Can't you understand how
ungrateful it is for a child...
...to die before his parent, Squard?!
Don't get too confident!
That little stab wound that you created
doesn't really jeopardize my life!
Everybody has his own duration of life!
We accomplished our goal here!
There's no need to stay here anymore!
--Good old man!
--Pops!
Listen carefully, Whitebeard Pirates!
I'm gonna give you an order
from the Captain one last time!
What do you mean "last?!"
Wait, Pops, that's too sad!
I don't wanna hear such thing!
Let's go back to the New World together!
Cross Fire!
Pops!
All of you and I will split up from here!
Everyone, survive at any cost and
go back to the New World safely!
P-Pops! Are you planning to die here?!
I'm a remnant from the old times!
There is no ship that can
bear me in the new era!
Go, you guys!!
Whitebeard!
No, Pops!
It's an order! We gotta go!
Old guy!
Pops!
Don't look back!
Because the era is changing!
Everything started on that sea...
This is unbelievable!
Hey, why do you look so out of spirits?
Join us! There's more than enough treasure!
Never mind about him.
Huh? What do you mean? We got
these treasures thanks to him...
Just leave him! He's not
interested in treasures.
That's odd! What kind of pirate is he?
What is it that you want?
Hey, Newgate!
I've been traveling a very long time.
Let's get it over with!
Navy!
Following Whitebeard's last order, the
pirates swallow their sadness and retreat.
But Akainu's cruel words
directed at Whitebeard
stop Ace in his tracks.
Ace shakes off his friends' protests and
leaps forward--to be met by Akainu's fist!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Power That Can Burn Even
Fire! Akainu's Ruthless Pursuit!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!