ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who was to be executed!
In the midst of the Navy's onslaught,
Luffy finally freed Ace! However,
Admiral Akainu landed a
fatal blow against Ace!
Pops!
Everybody!
And you Luffy.
Thank you...
...for loving someone like
me who is good for nothing...
...and who has such bad blood in his veins...
...up to today.
Thank you!
"The Navy Headquarters Falls!
Whitebeard's Unspeakable Wrath!"
Ace...
Did you think that I was dead?
But...!
Why are you crying?! I'm not dead, fool!
I promise that I'll never die!
How can I leave a wimpy
brother like you behind?
Garp!
Look after my child!
His name is Gol D. Ace.
Did you know? We can become brothers
if we exchange this cup of sake!
From now on,
we're brothers!
You got to be kidding me!
Ace...!
Ace!
Ace!!
"Fire Fist" Ace is dead!
Straw boy!
He's losing it!
His life is in danger!
It's Akainu!
I'll get you this time for sure!
Straw Hat!
I'm not gonna let you kill him!
Luffy-kun! Luffy-kun! Stay with me!
Move out of my way!
The war is not over yet!
Take Ace's brother with you, Jimbei!
All right!
Straw Hat's life is how
Ace's life will live on!
Commander... Marco!
We will protect him at any
cost on Ace's behalf!
If we let him die,
it's a dishonor to the Whitebeard Pirates!
Luffy-kun, don't lose your sanity!
I told you that I won't
let the brothers get away!
Straw Hat!
Akainu-san!
Pops is furious!
Guys, we gotta get out of here!
Hell Hound!
Pops!
You must resign!
Pops!!
Pops!
Pops.
Navy HQ is collapsing!
You bastard!
Whitebeard!
Admiral Sakazuki!
--Don't fall!
--Hang on!
Is it over?
How's Pops?!
Pops!
The plaza has split in two! The
pirates are on the other side!
We are completely separated from Pops!
Pops!
He still got this much power
after his torso has been charred?
You haven't seen anything yet.
From now on,
I'm the only one who you have to deal with!
Bring it on!
Everybody, get on the ship!
Pops!
Think about why Pops stayed on that
side and the wish that he left for us!
Cry after you get on the ship!
--Pops! Ace!
--Hurry up!
Bring all able ships alongside the bay head!
We won't let you get away!
Hurry up, everyone!
Salome! I can't stop worrying about Luffy!
Forgive me for disobeying you
and staying back to watch, Pops.
Hey, look! What is that?!
There is something behind the HQ building!
Oh, they found me!
Not only him! Who are they on the scaffold?
Oh... They noticed us finally.
It's you! How did you all get here?!
Why are they here?!
You bastard.
They're the most heinous criminals
whose existence has been erased
because of their brutality!
He's the biggest of all living things!
A Pirate--"Great Battleship" San Juan Wolf!
"GREAT BATTLESHIP" SAN JUAN WOLF
Oh, not only am I found
but they know who I am!
"Corrupt King" Avalo Pizarro!
"CORRUPT KING" AVALO PIZARRO
I missed being back on the street!
"Heavy Drinker" Vasco Shot!
"HEAVY DRINKER" VASCO SHOT
Am I allowed to kill them all?
"Crescent Moon Hunter" Catarina Devon!
"CRESCENT MOON HUNTER" CATARINA DEVON
Can't believe how much you guys want it.
And the Jail Manager of Impel Down
SHIRYU OF THE RAIN
Shiryu of the Rain!
They're the Blackbeard Pirates!
Long time no see! I'm glad that
I'm present at your death!
Pops!
Teach...!
It all started with this man.
Blackbeard, driven by his hidden
ambition, attacks Whitebeard.
Whitebeard fights back,
intent on avenging Thatch.
The fated battle begins at last!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Ending the Matter! Whitebeard
vs. The Blackbeard Pirates!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!