ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
"Ending the Matter! Whitebeard
vs. The Blackbeard Pirates!"
Shiryu! You bastard!
What happened to Magellan?
What's going on at Impel Down?
How did you guys get here?
I think the fact that we're here is the
answer to your questions,
don't you think?
Fleet Admiral Sengoku-san?
If you wanna know more, why don't
you check it yourself later.
Anyway, I've allied with these guys.
Remember that from now on!
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
I didn't have a chance to tell you but...
...I got a report that the Gates
of Justice have opened again
and an unidentified ship
passed through a while ago!
That must've been them!
But the control room is under Navy control
and I didn't hear about
any unusual circumstances!
How did they get here?
I'm sorry.
That's quite simple.
Before we, the Blackbeard
Pirates, set off for Impel Down,
I hypnotized the Navy soldiers
in the control room...
...to open the Gates of Justice
for any Navy ship that approaches.
It turns out that it helped the others too.
Straw Hat and the others?
If I were regarded as an
enemy by the Government,
the Gates of Justice won't open
for me and I couldn't have
sneaked into Impel Down!
That's why I wanted the
title of The Seven Warlords!
But I don't need it anymore!
So you just wanted to free your crew members!
Yes, indeed! That's all I
wanted from the beginning!
And that's all that matters!
You'll see why!
I don't give a damn about any of this!
Teach!
Look out! Captain!
That was close! That was close!
We had a narrow escape!
You have no mercy, huh?! Of course you don't!
You're the only one that I
refuse to call my son, Teach!
You broke the one and only iron rule
on my ship and you killed your mate!
I will avenge the 4th
division commander--Thatch
by taking this fool's life
thereby ending the matter!
Pops!
Marco!
Keep yourself out of this!
Pops!
Do you hear me?!
Let's get it over with, Teach!
I'm looking forward to it!
What is that black stuff
coming out of his body?
Smoke?!
Black Hole!
This is the power of the Devil Fruit
that I stole from Thatch by killing him!
The most dominant Dark-Dark Fruit!
Enjoy it to the fullest extent!
Hey, Pops! Thatch died
and then Ace died, too!
I looked up to you and longed
to be like you but you got old!
You can't even save your man
from getting killed now!
I tried not to kill Ace at
the Banaro Island for you!
That bastard!
Oh no no, it's no use!
There's no Devil Fruit power
that works against me!
Vortex!
Do you like my darkness, Pops?!
It drags in and nullifies even
the powers of Devil Fruits!
Which means you can't create
earthquakes anymore!
I can't believe Pops got hit like that!
Oops!
Don't you get it yet?!
How do you like my power?!
It's no use!
What a poor sport, Pops!
Ouch! Damn!
It hurts!
Arrogance, thoughtlessness...
Those are your weaknesses!
Hey, don't!
Pops, don't!
I'm your son!
How can you kill me...?
You did it! Pops!
No, look at that!
Damn! I can't believe it! He's tough!
A final blow! Give him a final blow, Pops!
--Just one more hit!
--Finish him off!
Pops!
Pops! What's wrong?!
He isn't moving!
I don't think he's frozen by choice!
On top of his worsening health,
he's taking a lot of damage
from all this fierce fighting!
Pops' body is already beyond...!
Y-You damn monster!
You useless old man!
Shut up and die!
Pops!!
Kill him, guys!
Shoot him! Riddle him with bullets!
Pops!
Did you say that you're
gonna die soon, Roger?
Yeah, it's only a matter of time.
Do you want me to tell you how
to get to Raftel, Whitebeard?
I'm not gonna go there anyway
because I've no interest.
Do you know what people of the World
Government call me these days?
"Gold Roger."
What? Is that your real name?
No, no!
My name is Gol D. Roger.
I meet people with "D"
in their names sometimes.
I have a crew member who
has it. His name is Teach.
What does "D" stand for?
Ah, do you wanna know that?
Alright, I tell you.
It's a story from way back...
Whoa, I'm out of bullets!
Hey, give me another gun!
You don't need it!
Whitebeard is unconscious now!
He's gonna collapse if you
push him with your finger!
It's not you!
You're still alive?!
The man that Roger is waiting for...
...is not you, Teach, at any rate!
Like there are people who
will inherit Roger's will,
some people inherit Ace's
sometime in the future!
Even if you break their blood bond,
you'll
never be able to extinguish their flame!
That's how it came down
unbroken throughout the ages!
And someday in the future,
carrying hundreds of years
of history on his shoulder,
someone will fling down the
gauntlet in front of the world!
Sengoku! You and the World
Government are afraid of...
...the gigantic war that will
embroil the whole world in one day!
I've no interest in it but...
...when someone finds the treasure,
the world will turn upside down!
And I'm sure somebody will find it!
And that day will come!
The One Piece...
...is real!!
You bastard!
What great last words!
--Pops!
Pops...
Forgive me, my sons.
I raised such a ridiculous fool.
You guys gave me everything.
This is it for me.
I've been traveling a very long time.
Let's sail out!
It was a great voyage!
That's odd! What kind of pirate
doesn't have interest in treasures?
What is it that you want?
Hey, Newgate!
There is something that I've
wanted since I was a kid.
Oh, you have something?
Why don't you tell us?
A family.
"A family?" What is he talking about?!
I have deep appreciation.
Goodbye, my sons!
Good old man...
He-He died...
...standing!
Whitebeard passed away!
Although he's dead, his
body doesn't collapse!
And the way he mowed down enemies
with wounds all over his body...
...was certainly monstrous!
The number of sword wounds he
received in this war is indeed 267!
The number of gun wounds: 152!
And he was shot by a cannon 46 times!
Yet,
on his proud back...
...or in his whole pirate life,
there is no scar that he
got while running away!
The Navy sweeps in to
wipe out the pirates as the loss
of Whitebeard slows their retreat,
and Akainu stands once again in
front of the unconscious Luffy.
Meanwhile, Blackbeard prepares to reveal
what he's really plotting to the whole world!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Show Begins! Blackbeard's
Plot is Revealed!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!