ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made a raid on the Navy HQ to rescue
his brother, Ace who was to be executed!
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
However, Ace protected Luffy from Akainu's
attack  and lost his life in the process!
However, both Ace and
Whitebeard lost their lives!
Luffy finally freed Ace!
Blackbeard who acquired Whitebeard's
power now is in a standoff with
power now is in a standoff
However, Admiral Akainu landed
a fatal blow against Ace
the Navy at the plaza!
with the Navy at the plaza!
And then, Blackbeard turned up
and brought further turmoil!
Meanwhile, Luffy has collapsed
after Ace's death and...
Meanwhile, Jimbei rushed to the bay
head carrying the unconscious Luffy
Whitebeard, Ace...
and Ace died in Luffy's arms!
Let us handle the burial of those two.
...Jimbei rushes to the bay head
in order to help him escape!
but they got attacked by Admiral Akainu!
This is...!
The man that Roger is waiting for...
Only because it's you, I
allow it, "Red-Haired"!
Let's start with sinking
Marineford into water!
That pose is...!
Good job, you young Navy soldier.
But...!
...is not you, Teach, at any rate!
I will take the blame on myself!
The courageous moments that you
created by risking your life
Thanks.
just now have changed...
Forgive me, my sons.
Treat the injured now!
...the future of the world
tremendously - for better or worse.
Shock Wave!
I raised such a ridiculous fool.
A building can easily be rebuilt!
"The Insatiable Akainu!
Lava Fists Pummel Luffy!"
This war is...
...over!
But the island of Marineford is located
virtually in the center of the world!
You guys gave me everything.
I'm here to...
To protect the people of the world who
are threatened by rampaging villains,
I have deep appreciation.
"Mighty Leaders Face Each Other
Down! Heralding the 'New Era'!"
The HQ building is gonna fall!
Goodbye, my sons!
it is important to them that we are here!
...end this war!
Justice that comes from
humanity will never perish!
"Here Comes Shanks! The War
of the Best is Finally Over!"
Leave your post!
Don't claim to be able to
sink this place so lightly,
"The Show Begins! Blackbeard's
Plot is Revealed!"
We're dead!
you little punk!
Head Office! Head Office!
Well, then:
Is this for real?
There's big news out of Marineford!
defend this place--if you can!
Is it true?!
Somebody please tell me I'm dreaming!
"Red-Haired"! He is the one who
motivated Luffy to become a pirate!
Is Whitebeard really...?! Are you sure?!
Destroy them!
Over the centuries we've kept
watch  over the seas from there!
Can't believe that Whitebeard is...!
Destroy them!!
The news has spread around
the world like wildfire!
What's wrong with it? I can't hear it.
I can't believe the fort of
justice the Navy's citadel...
What's this?!
"The Whitebeards failed to
rescue Roger's son Ace!"
Is it because of a bad connection?
I'll have an advantage once we
get to the sea! I can outrun him!
What happened in the war after all?
...is crumbling before my eyes!
"And the death of Whitebeard,
the legendary pirate captain."
Did the Navy win?
--They did, didn't they?
--It's getting clearer now.
Extra! Get ready to issue an extra!
--The Whitebeards have lost?
--Did the Navy really win?
Here is the breaking news!
There he is!
Oh no! It's frozen!
Blackbeard is the one who caught
Ace and triggered the war
Whitebeard died shortly after
"Fire Fist" Ace! I repeat!
Sables!
Regarding the war occurring at Marineford
and now he has Whitebeard's power!
being waged by the Whitebeards
and we, the Navy HQ,
--At Marineford...
--Whitebeard is...
Look, all you people of the world!
You gotta protect the one you wanna protect!
...Dead!
the process took longer than anticipated
because of the enemy's persistence
Then this is it for the Whitebeard Pirates!
Behold me and my power!
Don't let them have their way!
It's the Red Hair Pirates!
--The war will be over soon!
--We can live in peace finally!
but the Navy soldiers all
fought with a sense of justice
and defeated all the
Whitebeards and their allies
People who witnessed with their own eyes
What's gonna happen to this world?!
What is that?! The ship came out of water!
Prepare for surgery! Both of them
are bleeding uncontrollably!
the historic event which is being reported...
and now we are happy to tell you that
the Navy HQ gained a complete victory...
...stand transfixed, words
frozen on their lips.
That's a submarine!
We need to prepare for transfusions!
Whose ship is that?
Captain, it's dangerous!
Put Straw Hat-ya on my ship!
Sure, you can't often see The Four
Emperors but close the door already!
They did it!
"Straw Hat-ya"? That's really
a strange way to call somebody!
The Navy is invincible!
Praise all our heroes!
So Whitebeard's gone now...
Who the hell are you, brat?!
No way!
I'm gonna help him get out of here.
Let me take care of him for now!
"Red-Haired" had a run-in with Kaido,
another one of The Four Emperors,
I can feel the power
coursing through my body!
W-What?!
just yesterday in the New World!
And he made it here already?!
I'm a doctor!
Dammit!
Sh... Shanks?!
I want to be called to
duty at the HQ someday!
What power! It feels like I could control
everything in the world at my whim!
He was 72 years old.
Why the hell are you here?!
"The Desperate Scream! Courageous
Moments that Will Change the Future"
He stood even against the King
of the Pirates in his day.
Bastard!
The war is over!
He was the captain of the Whitebeard Pirates
Buggy!
Are you kidding me?! Doctors
don't carry swords!
Yes!
The straw hat?!
and was the great pirate Edward Newgate...
I'm glad!
Hey, what's wrong?!
Give it back to Luffy!
The legendary pirate - Whitebeard lost!
...aka Whitebeard.
Do you visit your patients by submarine?!
What are you waiting for?
Doesn't anyone wanna fight?
Why should I?!
He died in the decisive war at
the bay of Marineford between...
I refuse! I was just trying hard to fade out!
What's wrong?! Who is it?!
I'm willing to fight you to your
hearts' content now! What a shame!
Trafalgar Law, a rookie from the North Blue!
I don't wanna draw their attention anymore!
--The war is over, right?
--Yes! You're safe now!
...the Whitebeard Pirates
and the Navy Headquarters
What?!
Oh no! That's too bad!
and their ally The Seven Warlords.
That rookie must be Straw
Hat Luffy's accomplice whom
--This is so great!
--They did it!
I have no choice.
There's a treasure map
that I wanted to give you!
we weren't able to catch when
they had trouble with...
We're safe!
Then, let's start with...
Hurrah for the Navy! Hurray
for the World Government!
...the Celestial Dragons
in Sabaody Archipelago!
Really?!
...sinking Marineford into water!
Yes and it's a great one!
And for victory and justice
and peace! Hurrah!
This is great!
He came to save Luffy by submarine!
Yeah, right! Don't think that
I'm gonna fall for a deal
Things are really gonna change in the world!
You're too slow! Hand him over already!
What did he say?!
But even before that,
that is too good to be true!
I said who the hell are you!?
I don't think that things will
settle down that easily here!
Okay, then I gotta ask somebody else...
With the most heinous criminals and
the jail manager of Impel Down,
Al-Alright, hang on! I'm
gonna go give it to him!
At the scene of the war - Marineford!
There are 7 ships out at sea!
Captain Law! Navy ships are
approaching off the stern!
I wonder what Blackbeard is up to.
Boss!
You haven't seen Luffy for 10 years.
Don't you wanna see him?
What's gonna happen?
Those who would take part in the new era...
Hurry up! Put those two on this ship!
Is this really the end of the war?
...are there to witness this
great turning point in history.
Shock Wave!
Also, the thing that Whitebeard
said before he died...
I said "move out of my way"!
Staring at the dust of the battle
rising above Marineford -
The One Piece...
Yeah, maybe...
It's amazing that such rascal
pirates like you guys are...
evidence of the workings of
justice in the Great Pirate Era -
...is real!!
they sense the restlessness
of the changing of the times.
...risking your lives to protect the son of
A building can easily be rebuilt!
the worst criminal - the revolutionary, Dragon!
It's a matter of time before
the world finds out!
He got you good, boss!
Captain Drake.
Finally... it's over.
Stop undermining the wheels of justice!
I wonder how the pirates will react!
The Navy has to change, also.
But even before that, can we
say this war is really over?
Why are you laughing?!
But the island of Marineford is located
virtually in the center of the world!
Hound Blaze!
That was so uncool! Why
didn't you fight them?!
In no time,
Why did Blackbeard come to Marineford?
Stop Akainu here!
Whitebeard's territory will sink in
a sea of blood in this whirlpool.
No matter how many there are
or how strong they seem,
Fleet Admiral!
you're not men--or pirates - if you
laugh after something like that!
To protect the people of the world who
are threatened by rampaging villains,
I won't let him lay a finger
on Ace's brother again!
Blackbeard is the key.
He has gained new followers
and Whitebeard's power.
Listen all Navy soldiers!
it is important to them that we are here!
Split in two to go after the Whitebeards
and fight the Blackbeards!
I'm sure they're gonna reign for while!
Justice that comes from
humanity will never perish!
Hey, don't cry! You're a man!
That bastard!
Don't claim to be able to
sink this place so lightly,
Marco! Everybody feels the same!
It's all... his fault!
But... Shanks...!
Navy soldiers are coming
out from underground!
But you better hold your tongue for now!
Your arm!
you little punk!
I'll track him down soon enough!
There were tunnels?!
I know, Vista!
Let's go! To the New World!
It's only an arm. It's no big deal.
We have backup! Great!
Let's get them at once!
Hurry up and get on the ship! Don't
you remember our captain's last order?
I'm just glad you're alright...
What the hell is going on?
What are you talking about, Apoo-san?
--Ace!
--Pops!
Such noble beliefs! Huh? Fleet Admiral-san!
That guy will become his enemy.
Is he really gonna save him?
Well, then:
Huh?
I'm talking about Trafalgar Law.
He's known for his brutality.
defend this place--if you can!
Yeah, I wanna see him.
Hey, Coby?! Aren't you feeling well?!
He wouldn't save Straw Hat Luffy
if there wasn't some catch.
Captain! Captain!
You're acting weird!
Jimbei! Bring Ace's brother, hurry!
They're gonna attack us
if we don't submerge soon!
Okay!
Please close the door!
Ace-san! Good old man!
It's odd.
Okay.
I couldn't do anything to help you two!
What's wrong, Captain Hawkins?
Damn!
I've been trying to see the
odds that Luffy's still alive
I want to help Luffy-kun at least!
Hurry up and bring the ship to the
island! We can't leave anyone behind!
--Wait a minute!
--I can't wait anymore!
but it never reaches zero.
--Don't let the pirates get away!
--Kill them all!
Wait for us! We're coming now!
Oh no!
This was left behind! Here, catch it!
To be honest, I was scared
when the war started,
We gotta get out of here alive!
He threw something.
but now the great pirate,
Whitebeard, is dead.
Hurry up, everybody!
So it's really over, isn't it?
--This is...
--Captain, hurry up, hurry up!
Yeah, it is.
The Navy's victory must be unquestionable!
Okay.
We gotta survive and leave
here as Pops told us to!
Only the man who reigns over
the Navy could do that!
What's over?!
"Buddha" Sengoku, very powerful.
Let the pirates know the power
of justice through fear!
The new force who emerged during this
war--that Blackbeard is quite a guy!
But that's not enough to
defend the island against me!
--Justice...
--...Through fear...
Shut your big mouth already!
And be gone from Marineford!
We're almost there!
I wanna see him but...
The New World is ruled by The Four Emperors.
That's right! Now is the chance to
let villains all over the world know!
Whitebeard, "Red-Haired", Kaido, Big Mam.
I'll leave this hat with you.
Our power that will...!
Come bring it back to me someday!
...save the world!
But since one of them is dead,
--B-Blackbeard has...
--...Stopped the shock wave of Fleet Admiral!
We're safe now!
Captain Buggy, where're you going?!
the World is out of balance and no
one can predict the consequences!
Once you've become a great pirate!
The power of justice!
Are you stupid?! I'm getting out of here!
Let me give you a hand, Captain!
That's our promise, Luffy!
This is the beginning of a new era the
likes of which no one has ever seen!
The power of justice!
I can't kill Whitebeard - he's already dead!
Captain Buggy!
K-Kizaru!
I couldn't do it!
Black Hole!
--Captain Buggy, now is your chance!
--Hurry and kill Whitebeard!
I know that you can make it over the crack!
The news of the Navy's victory
in the war at Marineford,
Now is the chance!
W-What was that?!
If I see you now,
Take Straw boy!
Stop telling me what to do! It
wouldn't be smart to just jump him!
the biggest war since the beginning
of the Great Pirate Era,
Garp!
Thank you!
it means I fail to keep the
promise, doesn't it, Luffy?
spread all over the world
in the blink of an eye
I'm waiting for the right time!
I'm a Navy soldier, too.
and people are celebrating
the news everywhere.
--They think that it's easy!
--Vortex!
I have a duty to defend Marineford!
Inazuma!
East Blue.
EAST BLUE
You better stop, Jimbei!
Hurrah!
--Whitebeard is dead!
--Yeah!
You washed-up old farts!
You can't create earthquakes anymore!
You pest!
Oh yeah! Captain Buggy knew
it and waited for this moment!
Let's finish this up!
Take a good look!
--We're safe now!
--I'm so glad!
Alright, let's do this.
--Let us help you!
--Oh no, wait...
I won't let you go any further!
West Blue.
WEST BLUE
This one's been shot through his
stomach and he's barely alive.
--Here you go, Captain Buggy!
--Wait, wait, wait! Wait a minute, guys!
New Kama Kempo: 44 - Aesthetic Technique!
The sea will be in peace now!
Straw Hat-ya is severely injured too but I
Laser Surgery Fist!
Hurrah!
Ouch! Damn!
South Blue.
SOUTH BLUE
think there are more problems deep inside.
We're gonna have a bargain sale today!
Do they need anesthesia?
Captain, we'll soon be in
range of the Navy ships!
So are we!
No, they don't.
--The Navy has won!
--I'm so relieved!
They're both so seriously
hurt that they can't feel any pain.
Do something, Bepo!
North Blue.
NORTH BLUE
What?! You're not Captain, you're a newcomer!
They don't have the energy to complain
no matter how drastic the remedy will be.
Yes! I'm so happy!
I-Is that what a dying
old man is capable of?!
--Let's drink, everybody!
--We have tons of it!
They're coming on this side too!
It's gonna be a fun operation!
Finish them off with a barrage!
N-No! That's what makes
him the legend Whitebeard!
"Red-Haired", you bastard! You
let Dragon's son get away!
Grand Line.
GRAND LINE
What should we do tomorrow?
My nails have melted!
I wanna play tag!
Hide and seek!
I was scared and I couldn't
even approach him!
Alright!
Emporio Ivankov of the Revolutionaries army!
Whitebeard was scary!
God! Thank you!
Ice Age!
The man at the top is
scary, even if he is dead!
You use strange techniques as they say!
Like most of history, some facts are
trimmed off as the news goes around
New Kama Kempo: 44 - Aesthetic Technique!
Fire! Fire!
I don't care if you think that I'm
hopeless! I say goodbye to you fools!
He's after the submarine!
The sea is gonna be frozen!
Fat Suctioning Fist!
and just the two words
"Navy victory" stand out.
I like it hot!
Wh-What is this?!
Captain Buggy!
The people, in their excitement at the
news, failed to notice something...
He's crying... Captain Buggy...
I have no time to play with you guys!
I know why! "Yesterday's
enemy could be today's d!"
His pulse is steadying.
This is...!
Blackbeard is using the
Tremor-Tremor Fruit power again!
He felt pity for his rival Whitebeard
as a human without even noticing!
W-What's going on?!
The one he acquired from Whitebeard!
What's that?
But it's way more powerful than before
when he destroyed the HQ building!
It's an emergency! The water
is starting to turn into ice!
He could've killed that guy!
Look at you people! That's hilarious!
And now he's trying to leave
us  without making excuses!
Whitebeard said that the great
treasure - One Piece is real!
Oh no! Oh no!
If nothing is done, we're
gonna get caught, Captain!
Son of a gun! He showed us something
I'm gonna find it!
more important than killing Whitebeard!
Do something!
I can't believe that he chose
to have pity on the instead of
We'll submerge rapidly!
Not only the ground! The sky and
the sea... Everything is shaking!
Ouch!
There is so much more out
there! Let's set sail!
all the fame he was surely going to get!
I burned my lips, my lips, my lips...
He is one man in a million
as we knew all along!
...or not! Because of
my over-applied make-up!
Navy victory.
You're way too cool, Captain Buggy!
The result is not necessarily peace...
--Wait, Captain Buggy!
--Let us come with you!
NEW WORLD: FOODVALTEN ISLAND
Ouch!
Captain!
I-Ivan-sama!
Did I lose him?
Y-You can't come any further!
Don't come into our town!
You bastards!
W-We made it!
He was so tenacious! Good to
see him drop dead finally!
Don't let them get away! Shoot!
With the loss of a deterrent -
namely, the threat of Whitebeard -
What wonderful power!
It's going as we planned so
far. Now is the time, Captain.
the world of the seas has
become very unsettled...
Yasakani Sacred Jewel!
I won't let you get away!
Isn't this too one-sided?
We already know who won...
Alright, let's begin!
You can't go any further!
Is this really necessary?
Not again!
What is it this time?!
They're up to something again!
Stop the Navy soldiers here! Let as many
of our people get away as possible!
Defeat them decisively!
--Teach, that bastard!
--What is he gonna do to Pops now?!
Let's go deeper--to the bottom of the sea!
Don't ever let them even
think about challenging us!
No way! We won't let
even one of you get away!
It's gonna hit us! I'm sure
that it's gonna hit us!
I'm gonna put on a show!
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
It's a show that will shake the whole world!
Hurry up! At full speed!
What's going on?
We'll let them know...!
Here you are!
You just put on another great show!
...The power of justice that we own!
We've had word from Impel Down!
What is that black cloth?!
Luffy!
But I can't control the power very well yet!
Is Magellan alright?
Blackbeard got inside of it
with the body of Whitebeard!
Destroy them!
He got beaten badly and is barely alive.
Now, please don't trespass for a while!
Destroy them!
Hey, Captain! If you aren't careful, we'll
lose the ground we're standing on, too!
He's been treated intensively
by the medical team.
Destroy them!!
What do you think you're doing?!
He's a dutiful man - he's blaming himself.
Blackbeard, you bastard!
What's this?!
He's someone who deceived us by joining
the Warlords only to betray us!
Whitebeard would be horrified to
know this punk is using his power!
Akainu!
--Damn! They're so persistent!
--It didn't hit them, did it?!
They said that if he could
move now, he'd kill himself.
Stay alert!
Jimbei! Hand Dragon's son over to me!
I can't wait!
Don't let him do such stupid thing!
Ace's brother! Jimbei!
Are we gonna disband if we fail?
How was it, "Buddha"
Sengoku?! Garp the hero?!
Y-Yes, sir!
Luffy...
I'll have an advantage once we
get to the sea! I can outrun him!
Do you think you can stop me?!
If they're still alive after this,
What has been going on at the prison?
Your time ended with Whitebeard's death!
Allow me to tell you the
condition as it stands.
we have no choice but to let
them go and count them lucky!
Hurry up! To the sea!
The situation on level 6 is especially
bad. It's literally a disaster.
Luffy-kun!
Oh no! It's frozen!
Stay with me!
A disaster?
You have to carry on in this
world where Ace-san is no longer lives...
Aokiji!
UNDERWATER PRISON IMPEL DOWN
...tomorrow and the day after!
He's coming!
What will Blackbeard do next?!
Why is that Navy ship taking off on its own?
Fire!
You have to live strong!
--I'm scared!
--He's terrifying!
Looks like you've got nowhere to run!
Hurry up! Go after the submarine!
Urgent! After the earthquake
that hit Marineford,
Jimbei, if I don't escape death...
a tsunami warning has issued for the
south shore of Sabaody Archipelago.
LEVEL 6
But they went underwater
What's up?
and I don't think that they could've
You prisoners're doomed to
be stuck behind bars forever!
It's no good!
escaped the attacks from the admirals!
I'm sorry but could you
look after my brother?
Straw Hat Luffy!
In order to avoid widespread panic, please
remain calm before taking any action.
No, I'm sure that they're alive!
You've got nothing to do except wait to die!
I got you!
Then how about this?! Why don't
you fight each other in the cell?!
Listen to me!
I'm sorry to contradict you, Ace-san,
Run!
but you can't overrate me. I'm
not as good-natured as you think.
Tell the Navy that, being a Warlord,
Please evacuate to the north side -
the elevated area of Grove 40, 50.
I will free those of you who
survive as members of my crew!
I will catch  and kill Straw
Hat Luffy at any cost!
Even if he's your brother,
we're in the pirates' world.
Move! What are you doing?!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
--Really?!
--Get me out of here!
--But I don't know where we should go...
--Shut up and advance!
I'm a nobleman! I'll pay
you to let me go first!
I only help or protect the ones
who I have a high regard for!
Let me be your crew member!
Everybody, please stay cool.
She's reckless but beautiful!
My feelings haven't changed at all, Ace-san!
So he has freed selected members from
the worst criminals in the world?!
I'm not helping him because
he is your brother!
Yes. But only 4 prisoners were taken.
San Juan Wolf, Avalo Pizarro,
Vasco Shot, Catarina Devon.
Jimbei!
I have a high regard for
Luffy-kun! That is why...!
But there are obviously more
prisoners missing from level 6!
It went right through Jimbei
and got to Ace's brother!
The Pacifistas are getting
over the crack in the plaza!
Are they alive?!
Which means...
Hurry up, Jimbei! Give Luffy treatment!
Follow the Pacifistas! Don't
let the pirates get away! Go!
Can't let him hurt anymore!
Pacifista! Kill Straw Hat!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh...
Although he's a Warlord,
Jimbei is our enemy now!
I understand. Then, there are
more escapees from level 6!
What did you just say?!
H-Hey!
We're allowed to kill him!
You guys should go ahead and get on the ship!
You lied about the treasure map?!
You're in my way, Jimbei!
But...
If even one of the prisoners from level
6 sneaks into a country somewhere,
Y-You bastard!
Did you forget Pops' order?!
Perfume Femur!
We gotta get back to the New World
with as many alive as we can!
I just said that on the
spur of the moment, Buggy!
the people will be in grave danger!
It's been awhile, huh?
I got it!
Boa Hancock! Are you gonna
stand in our way again?!
Check to see how many there were.
Alright, stay with me!
Cut the "It's been awhile, huh?" crap!
We won't let you go! None of you can survive!
Get their names, and put a
most wanted list out now!
"Fire Fist" Ace and Whitebeard
are dead already!
Don't forget that I have a reason
to be mad at you, Shanks!
Luffy-kun, I'm sorry! I couldn't save you!
Pops, I'm sorry! I'm gonna disobey
your order for the first time!
I don't like persistent men!
What's wrong?
Well, I...
--What's that?
--Don't forget about it!
I'm gonna die here!
You fool! You have to worry
about yourself right now!
Me, too! I'm gonna follow Pops to heaven!
I'm under orders from the World Government
If you didn't surprise me at that time,
Jimbei! Please take good care of Luffy!
to keep this level 6 matter secret.
Finally, it stopped shaking!
More blunders will harm the
Government's reputation.
I wouldn't have lost the treasure
map and become a Devil Fruit eater!
Jimbei! Get on this ship!
Okay!
What's this?!
I missed a little because you were in my way.
What's the matter with you?!
Damn them!
If it hit his heart, it
would've been easier for him.
--Damn! He froze the sea!
--We can't leave!
I don't know! I feel sad!
Is that what happened?
Thank you for that great reaction.
Sad?!
Hurry up and do something!
Don't you think so, Jimbei?
I always hated that about you!
It's Admiral Aokiji!
Stop Aokiji!
How could you made me work for
free as soon as we met again!
I have no choice! I'll look for another way!
Are you gonna keep protecting
him with a hole in his chest?
The voices disappear one by one in my head!
You said you were here to
stop the war or something
but I can start a war with
you right now if you want!
He's gonna die soon!
--Did you see that?
--Yes, I did.
When I say that I won't let you get away,
He has such sass, even against
"Red-Haired" of The Four Emperors...
Huh? The voices?
why don't you give up your life, you fool!
--We'll show you the justice of the Navy!
--Is this what you call "justice"?!
Stop the Navy soldiers here!
Captain Buggy!
No way! Destroy the pirates!
We will follow you for the rest of our lives!
I understand so just relax.
Jimbei, if I don't escape death...
Say what?!
You bastard!
I'm sorry but could you
look after my brother?
But, wait a minute!
Doflamingo!
That's for my friend who
got killed in the war!
If I stay with them, I can
get off this island safely!
I'm not helping him because
he is your brother!
Moria, you're too weak to go
on with the title as a Warlord.
Damn pirates! Go to hell...
Hand Dragon's son over to me!
I have a high regard for Luffy-kun!
--Akainu! He isn't dead!
--I thought he was beaten by Pops!
I've already made up my mind to save
his life even if it means death!
"Died in the War of the
Best" sounds better...
Let's teach them!
We're the ones that will conquer
the world, not the pirates!
--He traveled underground...
--...By making a path with lava!
...than "done in by the Government".
I got one!
Jimbei!
Whose idea was this?! Sengoku?!
What are you talking about?!
I cannot do that! Because I've
already made up my mind...
Are you losing your mind?!
Get ahold of yourself!
"Red-Haired"...
No, someone much higher up the ladder!
Marco.
H-Help me!
...to save his life even if it means death!
Stop fighting back. Just
back out nice and easy.
Run!
Alright then, I won't ask you again!
I won't let him die!
Coby! H-Hey! Where are you going?!
"Hawk-Eye", where are you going?
Coby! Akainu-san wants to
kill Straw Hat at any cost!
It's hot... Too hot...
Once he sees you as a target,
you can't get away from him!
I agreed to fight Whitebeard
Why is it so hot? I can't take it.
Let as many of our people escape as possible!
but fighting "Red-Haired"
is not in the agreement.
Stay with me! He's alive!
Let's get him treated!
Could you shut up already?!
You're making me feel hot too!
Luffy-san...
Even if I die,
I-I don't wanna die!
I won't let Luffy-kun die!
It's time to quit.
You're hairy. I don't blame you.
Forget about him! The war is not over yet.
--We're gonna protect Ace's brother!
--That's also what Pops wanted!
But...
I don't like it when we submerge.
Now is our chance to show them
the power of our justice!
We have to stay in such a cramped place...
Yeah! Ace's family is our family, too!
...with messy people.
That's nonsense!
There's no time to help the wounded! Go!
You're the messiest!
"Family"? Don't be ridiculous!
I can't take it! I have no choice but...
Y-Yes, sir!
You guys just left "Fire Fist" Ace
Corner the pirates! Destroy
them--to the last man!
and your "father" Whitebeard
to their fate and ran!
--...to make you feel the same!
--Stop it!
--You're so hot!
--That's gross!
Crocodile!
--What did you say?!
--Take this!
Somebody, give me a hand! Somebody!
Sables!
Come on!
I beg you! A little bit is fine!
Let me get some fresh air!
If you continue desiring more and more,
Destroy all the damn pirates!
it will just increase the damage
on both sides purposelessly.
Alright! Now, stop rubbing your sweat on me!
The Navy soldiers are still motivated
even though we achieved the goal!
I-It doesn't work at all!
Somebody, catch them and
put them on the ship!
Outta my way, you cowards!
Surface! Let's surface now!
Okay!
Move aside, Jimbei!
Crocodile!
Those of you who only want to fight more...
Emporio Face Growth Synthesis!
You gotta protect the one you wanna protect!
Guns don't work!
Don't let them have their way!
--Run!
Ivan-san, let me assist you!
--Chase them!
--Damn villains!
Bring it on! We're happy to fight you!
Catch them!
Something is not right! With either side!
Great Scissors!
It's over!
We're not satisfied even though we won!
I'm sorry that I got carried away, everyone.
Keep your hands off of Straw boy!
It's so refreshing! How nice it is outside!
I'll kill Dragon's son for sure!
This is the end of Captain Buggy's legend.
Hell...
Now I'm cool! Right side - okay!
Thank you for your support all this time!
...Wink!
Left side - okay!
Jimbei!
Front...
Snake - okay! Snake?!
--What the hell?!
--How did a snake get here?!
What do you think, Teach?
Since Impel Down, Straw boy
has been under assault...
They're not coming down...
I mean, Blackbeard!
What's going on?!
...physically and mentally and it's
pushing him beyond his capacity!
Oh no!
Captain Buggy!
You're more handsome than ever, "Red-Haired".
A Navy ship!
He helped Straw Hat and Jimbei!
--Tell Captain!
--Someone's there!
Those scars look good on you.
Damn!
If I let something happen to him,
I wouldn't be able to face...
That's exactly what I thought!
Huh?
Listen, guys!
A Warlord - the Pirate Empress, Boa Hancock!
Captain Buggy, you made us
believe that you were gonna run
As long as you're a Navy soldier, you
can't forgive those thugs, the pirates!
...my comrade Dragon for the rest of my life!
but you helped your fellow escapee
Straw Hat when it counted!
Curiel!
I agree!
Admiral Sakazuki!
I have no time to play
with you guys right now!
How beautiful!
Don't worry. I turned all
the Navy soldiers to stone.
You're beautiful and shimmering!
So back off, you two!
They're being weird again!
Bring it on!
So how is Luffy doing?
I'm burning way hotter than you right now!
Is it bad? He'll recover, won't he?
Jimbei and Straw Hat!
How did you know that we
were gonna surface here?
What made you guys fly in the
sky with blood all over you?!
Let's stop this, then!
I was scared thinking that the
Navy was still chasing us.
Hey, are you alright?!
Anyway, why is it so hot here...?
I made Salome follow you underwater.
H-Hey!
I already got what I wanted.
M-Magma!
--I see!
--Don't change the subject, you fuzzy beast!
And we're not ready to fight you guys yet.
--I'm sorry!
--So weak!
Let's go, guys!
Thank you, red-nosed man! You helped us!
How is Luffy doing? Tell me now...
Looks like he's all set now!
Let me see it already, Captain!
I don't know what's going
on and I'm not helping you!
Oh, Captain!
But I allowed Luffy-kun to be injured!
THE HEART PIRATES  CAPTAIN TRAFALGAR LAW
I did everything I could.
He needs to be treated immediately!
You mean, he's okay?
We were able to stabilize him. However...
Shut up! I'm the one who needs help, fool!
Alright, everybody, thank you for waiting!
How could we get him treated here...
...he took greater damage than you think.
It's the greatest show in the world
Did you call me "red-nosed man"?!
presented by Captain Teach
of the Blackbeard Pirates!
There is no guarantee
that he will survive yet.
They keep getting in my way
when I'm about to get him!
Please enjoy it!
Rose Rondo!
No one can stop me! I'm gonna
destroy and devour everything!
It's no wonder!
Who's talking?
Straw boy couldn't even
stand up at Impel Down once!
B-Blackbeard!
B-Blackbeard! He's pretty scary!
I gotta leave here as soon as possible!
--Straw Hat was risking his life!
--We got out of the prison thanks to him!
What was he doing in there?!
Nothing has changed on Whitebeard's body!
Because of him, we can
make our dream come true:
Everybody.
To go to the Kamabakka Kingdom!
And neither has Blackbeard's!
You're fools, one and all!
Let's go!
For now,
To the New Kamas' home from New Kama Land!
Do you wanna die to save that Straw Hat brat?
Why don't you leave Straw Hat Luffy here?
Navy!
you need to do as I say!
Ugh! It's...!
I'll show you what I'm capable of!
We've all seen his limitless tenacity
and power with our own eyes.
--It's Kizaru!
--Get them on the ship!
What are they?
They are prisoners of Impel Down.
Looks like they're Luffy's friends.
Alright, I leave them
to you, Whoever You Are!
We'll turn against each other again!
He's the one who Ace wanted
to save and Pops approved!
Do the best you can!
They have snuck into the ship.
Catch them, Jean Bart!
And we're bound to bring
him into the new era!
I can't believe that he
pushed himself that hard!
Black Hole!
Yeah, that's it!
That's how much he wanted
to save his brother Ace!
I thought that you all were better
than that! Not that it matters!
Submerge!
What's going on?!
How dare you get away from
us at Sabaody, Trafalgar Law?
That's right! We know how much
he pushed himself to do it!
He's severely wounded! Is he alive?!
That's my Dark-Dark Fruit power!
But that brother died in front of his eyes...
Let's run!
And now...
...in order to protect him...
Dammit!
The Whitebeard Pirates!
Give it up!
...this is...!
That's enough!
Akainu!
There is no justice in this world! It's
not surprising that he broke down!
The degree to which you see him as a
risk - that makes you wanna kill him.
That pose is...!
Damn it all! Hang in there, Straw Hat!
The degree to which we have
high expectations of him -
A Navy soldier?
that makes us wanna protect him.
You got to live! You got to, Straw Hat!
They're the same, don't you agree?
You guys got me involved again!
Are you even listening?!
What a tragedy! I wish
I could take his place!
H-Hey, Jimbei?
Coby!
Let's end this now!
Don't tell me that you're unconscious!
Where should I go now?!
Let's not fight anymore!
Poor Luffy!
Hey!
What is he doing?
I'm jealous...
S-Somebody...
It must be nice to have the Pirate
Empress care about you that much...
Whether he lives or dies,
it's as if he's in hell.
That's...
...the power of Tremor-Tremor Fruit!
Yeah, yeah...
H-Help me!
By the way, are you a friend of Straw boy?
Then we can make him suffer
as we please while he lives!
W-Why does he possess the
late Whitebeard's power?!
We're wasting people's lives!
No, I didn't have to save him at all.
We can't resolve this
through dialogue anymore.
Every single soldier has a family
that's waiting for him to come home!
If you're wondering about my motivation,
I can come up with a reason.
No, that's okay. Sometimes your
instinct tells you what to do.
So be it!
You did it, Captain!
We accomplished the purpose already
We're not gonna disband then?
--Hey, wait!
--You can't walk around yet!
but we're still chasing the pirates
who have no will to fight!
Looks like our coverage of
the war will soon be over!
It looks like I made the right
choice by teaming up with them!
--Don't push yourself like that!
--He told you to rest!
We could stop but we're coveting more!
Whitebeard, Ace...
We're giving up on our soldiers
--The wound could open up!
--Where are you going?
who could survive if we
treated them right away!
Pops' tremor power?!
Let us handle the burial of those two.
On top of that, we keep multiplying
the number of victims!
W-We're dead!
What did he do, that bastard Teach!
It's Sengoku vs. Blackbeard over there.
Soldiers who're gonna go down after this...
Jimbei!
The war was broadcast to the world.
The gravity of darkness
brings total annihilation!
Is that Coby?
You're Trafalgar Law from
the North Blue, aren't you?
I won't let you dishonor their
death in public any longer!
They're no more than fools!
And the power of tremor destroys everything!
And it's Akainu vs. the commanders over here!
Uh-huh.
I possess them both! No one
can compete with me now!
Who are you, you fool?!
Hey, is it okay for you
to move around like that?
That's ridiculous!
We raise a shout of victory by exposing
their dead bodies to public view!
I'm the strongest man in the world!
Thank you!
You've wasted my time!
Vice Admiral is right!
You saved my life!
The fighting hasn't stopped!
We have no use for a soldier
who doesn't believe in justice!
Are you trying to bring
disgrace to our victory?!
You must rest. It could kill you.
I don't know how he did it but...
Captain Buggy! Do something!
We're not gonna listen to a pirate!
I can't ease my mind. It's impossible!
he acquired Whitebeard's power!
Oh no, I'm dead! But I
said what I wanted to say!
I agree!
Damn it all, fools!
How is it possible?!
What I have just lost
was too important to me!
Give me a break... Honestly!
Fleet Admiral-dono!
That means we still have to fear
the power of Tremor-Tremor Fruit?!
I have no regret!
That is why I know that Luffy-kun
must be going through far worse!
Only because it's you, I
allow it, "Red-Haired"!
If I'm correct, it's impossible to have
two Devil Fruit powers at the same time!
Coby!
At least, his instinct to protect himself
But...!
I will take the blame on myself!
forced him to lose
consciousness at that time!
It's impossible for average
people, that's for sure.
Even if he survives,
But Teach is a little
different, as you guys know.
Thanks.
I can't stop worrying about
the moment that he wakes up.
Treat the injured now!
His body structure is irregular
compared to common people's.
That's why he was able to do it!
Good job, you young Navy soldier.
Hey, did you guys see that?!
Captain, we reached the
point where it's not frozen.
This war is...
You, fuzzy beast, do you
have a Transponder Snail?
The courageous moments that you
created by risking your life
...over!
Surface.
Tell all the people in the world!
The boring people who love peace,
just now have changed...
Yeah... I mean... yes, ma'am!
...the future of the world
tremendously - for better or worse.
I'm sorry!
Navy soldiers, the World
Government, and pirates!
--I'm jealous. He's like her servant...
--Yeah, yeah...
Hurry up! Bring him inside!
Those of you who are able, help the medics!
This must be a bad dream!
Not a chance!
I'm gonna call the Kuja's ship so we can go
What is that?! The ship came out of water!
Carry for the seriously injured ones first!
The future of this world is determined!
across the Calm Belt even with this submarine.
Don't let anyone else die here!
That's a submarine!
If the Government finds out that Luffy's
alive, they're gonna come after him!
Don't do anything, Kizaru!
Is that another enemy?
Yes, here comes the era that I conquer!
Oops, you're Benn Beckman!
Whose ship is that?
Thus, the biggest war since the
beginning of the Great Pirate Era -
Let us harbor him at the Maiden Island!
What?!
Put Straw Hat-ya on my ship!
Huh? That's...! The ship is...!
I thought that Whitebeard
died and the Navy won!
If they still see me as a
Warlord, Luffy can rest safely!
"Straw Hat-ya"? That's really
a strange way to call somebody!
the War of the Best in Marineford has ended
Let's go!
Why is one of The Four Emperors
from the New World here?!
I can't believe that he now
has two Devil Fruit powers!
and so it will be recorded in history.
Who the hell are you, brat?!
"Red-Haired" Shanks!
Who the hell is Blackbeard?!
Straw Hat-ya will become
my enemy at some stage
but a desirable relationship
is still a relationship.
I thought that the war would be over soon!
There's no point in letting him die here.
Then why is this happening?! Hey, Coby!
THE HEART PIRATES--CAPTAIN TRAFALGAR LAW
I'm gonna help him get out of here.
Although Luffy-san's brother and Whitebeard
died, this war is still not over?!
Let me take care of him for now!
W-What?!
I'm here to...
Luffy...
I'm a doctor!
...end this war!
The "War of the Best" has shattered
the balance of the world.
Blackbeard freely uses the power he
stole from Whitebeard to wreak havoc.
The Navy's relentless pursuit continues.
At Hancock's suggestion,
The "Red-Haired" Pirates have
appeared out of the blue!
Luffy is taken to Maiden Island
so his wounds can heal,
As the meaningless battle rages on endlessly,
Law tries to give Luffy a chance to escape
while the Navy catches their breath,
The end of the war becomes the sign
and there he finally regains consciousness.
Meanwhile, Akainu and the rest of the Navy
one young man stands lost
in grief on the battlefield.
for the pirates to set out
upon the wave of a new era.
but the three admirals attack relentlessly.
But as his memories of the battle return,
chase down the pirates
in the name of justice.
That sadness gives birth to
a great power called courage,
With the menace that was Whitebeard gone,
Then Shanks reveals his real reason
for appearing on the battlefield...
The battle shows no sign of coming to an end,
Luffy is overtaken by deep despair.
setting the very world in motion!
the seas are growing rough again.
but only increases in intensity!
On the next episode of One Piece!
On the net episode of One Piece!
"The Desperate Scream! Courageous
Moments that Will Change the Future"
"Landing at the Maiden Island!
The Harsh Reality Falls upon Luffy!"
"Mighty Leaders Face Each Other
Down! Heralding the 'New Era'!"
"Here Comes Shanks! The War
of the Best is Finally Over!"
"The Insatiable Akainu!
Lava Fists Pummel Luffy!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!