ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made a raid on the Navy HQ to rescue
his brother, Ace who was to be executed!
However, both Ace and
Whitebeard lost their lives!
Whitebeard, Ace...
Let us handle the burial of those two.
Only because it's you, I
allow it, "Red-Haired"!
But...!
I will take the blame on myself!
Thanks.
Treat the injured now!
This war is...
...over!
"Mighty Leaders Face Each Other
Down! Heralding the 'New Era'!"
What's wrong with it? I can't hear it.
Is it because of a bad connection?
What happened in the war after all?
Did the Navy win?
--They did, didn't they?
--It's getting clearer now.
--The Whitebeards have lost?
--Did the Navy really win?
Regarding the war occurring at Marineford
being waged by the Whitebeards
and we, the Navy HQ,
the process took longer than anticipated
because of the enemy's persistence
but the Navy soldiers all
fought with a sense of justice
and defeated all the
Whitebeards and their allies
and now we are happy to tell you that
the Navy HQ gained a complete victory...
They did it!
The Navy is invincible!
Praise all our heroes!
I want to be called to
duty at the HQ someday!
The war is over!
Yes!
I'm glad!
The legendary pirate - Whitebeard lost!
--The war is over, right?
--Yes! You're safe now!
--This is so great!
--They did it!
We're safe!
Hurrah for the Navy! Hurray
for the World Government!
And for victory and justice
and peace! Hurrah!
At the scene of the war - Marineford!
There are 7 ships out at sea!
Those who would take part in the new era...
...are there to witness this
great turning point in history.
Staring at the dust of the battle
rising above Marineford -
evidence of the workings of
justice in the Great Pirate Era -
they sense the restlessness
of the changing of the times.
Captain Drake.
Finally... it's over.
The Navy has to change, also.
In no time,
Whitebeard's territory will sink in
a sea of blood in this whirlpool.
Blackbeard is the key.
He has gained new followers
and Whitebeard's power.
I'm sure they're gonna reign for while!
It's all... his fault!
I'll track him down soon enough!
Let's go! To the New World!
What the hell is going on?
What are you talking about, Apoo-san?
That guy will become his enemy.
Is he really gonna save him?
Huh?
I'm talking about Trafalgar Law.
He's known for his brutality.
He wouldn't save Straw Hat Luffy
if there wasn't some catch.
It's odd.
What's wrong, Captain Hawkins?
I've been trying to see the
odds that Luffy's still alive
but it never reaches zero.
To be honest, I was scared
when the war started,
but now the great pirate,
Whitebeard, is dead.
So it's really over, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
What's over?!
The new force who emerged during this
war--that Blackbeard is quite a guy!
The New World is ruled by The Four Emperors.
Whitebeard, "Red-Haired", Kaido, Big Mam.
But since one of them is dead,
the World is out of balance and no
one can predict the consequences!
This is the beginning of a new era the
likes of which no one has ever seen!
The news of the Navy's victory
in the war at Marineford,
the biggest war since the beginning
of the Great Pirate Era,
spread all over the world
in the blink of an eye
and people are celebrating
the news everywhere.
East Blue.
EAST BLUE
Hurrah!
--Whitebeard is dead!
--Yeah!
--We're safe now!
--I'm so glad!
West Blue.
WEST BLUE
The sea will be in peace now!
Hurrah!
South Blue.
SOUTH BLUE
We're gonna have a bargain sale today!
So are we!
--The Navy has won!
--I'm so relieved!
North Blue.
NORTH BLUE
Yes! I'm so happy!
--Let's drink, everybody!
--We have tons of it!
Grand Line.
GRAND LINE
What should we do tomorrow?
I wanna play tag!
Hide and seek!
Alright!
God! Thank you!
Like most of history, some facts are
trimmed off as the news goes around
and just the two words
"Navy victory" stand out.
The people, in their excitement at the
news, failed to notice something...
W-What's going on?!
Look at you people! That's hilarious!
Whitebeard said that the great
treasure - One Piece is real!
I'm gonna find it!
There is so much more out
there! Let's set sail!
Navy victory.
The result is not necessarily peace...
NEW WORLD: FOODVALTEN ISLAND
Y-You can't come any further!
Don't come into our town!
With the loss of a deterrent -
namely, the threat of Whitebeard -
the world of the seas has
become very unsettled...
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
Here you are!
We've had word from Impel Down!
Is Magellan alright?
He got beaten badly and is barely alive.
He's been treated intensively
by the medical team.
He's a dutiful man - he's blaming himself.
They said that if he could
move now, he'd kill himself.
Don't let him do such stupid thing!
Y-Yes, sir!
What has been going on at the prison?
Allow me to tell you the
condition as it stands.
The situation on level 6 is especially
bad. It's literally a disaster.
A disaster?
UNDERWATER PRISON IMPEL DOWN
LEVEL 6
What's up?
You prisoners're doomed to
be stuck behind bars forever!
You've got nothing to do except wait to die!
Then how about this?! Why don't
you fight each other in the cell?!
I will free those of you who
survive as members of my crew!
--Really?!
--Get me out of here!
Let me be your crew member!
So he has freed selected members from
the worst criminals in the world?!
Yes. But only 4 prisoners were taken.
San Juan Wolf, Avalo Pizarro,
Vasco Shot, Catarina Devon.
But there are obviously more
prisoners missing from level 6!
Which means...
I understand. Then, there are
more escapees from level 6!
If even one of the prisoners from level
6 sneaks into a country somewhere,
the people will be in grave danger!
Check to see how many there were.
Get their names, and put a
most wanted list out now!
What's wrong?
Well, I...
I'm under orders from the World Government
to keep this level 6 matter secret.
More blunders will harm the
Government's reputation.
Damn them!
You bastard!
Doflamingo!
Moria, you're too weak to go
on with the title as a Warlord.
"Died in the War of the
Best" sounds better...
...than "done in by the Government".
Whose idea was this?! Sengoku?!
No, someone much higher up the ladder!
It's hot... Too hot...
Why is it so hot? I can't take it.
Could you shut up already?!
You're making me feel hot too!
You're hairy. I don't blame you.
I don't like it when we submerge.
We have to stay in such a cramped place...
...with messy people.
You're the messiest!
I can't take it! I have no choice but...
--...to make you feel the same!
--Stop it!
--You're so hot!
--That's gross!
Come on!
I beg you! A little bit is fine!
Let me get some fresh air!
Alright! Now, stop rubbing your sweat on me!
Surface! Let's surface now!
It's so refreshing! How nice it is outside!
Now I'm cool! Right side - okay!
Left side - okay!
Front...
Snake - okay! Snake?!
--What the hell?!
--How did a snake get here?!
Oh no!
A Navy ship!
--Tell Captain!
--Someone's there!
A Warlord - the Pirate Empress, Boa Hancock!
Don't worry. I turned all
the Navy soldiers to stone.
So how is Luffy doing?
Is it bad? He'll recover, won't he?
How did you know that we
were gonna surface here?
I was scared thinking that the
Navy was still chasing us.
I made Salome follow you underwater.
--I see!
--Don't change the subject, you fuzzy beast!
--I'm sorry!
--So weak!
How is Luffy doing? Tell me now...
Oh, Captain!
THE HEART PIRATES – CAPTAIN TRAFALGAR LAW
I did everything I could.
You mean, he's okay?
We were able to stabilize him. However...
...he took greater damage than you think.
There is no guarantee
that he will survive yet.
It's no wonder!
Who's talking?
Straw boy couldn't even
stand up at Impel Down once!
--Straw Hat was risking his life!
--We got out of the prison thanks to him!
Because of him, we can
make our dream come true:
To go to the Kamabakka Kingdom!
Let's go!
To the New Kamas' home from New Kama Land!
What are they?
They are prisoners of Impel Down.
Looks like they're Luffy's friends.
They have snuck into the ship.
I can't believe that he
pushed himself that hard!
That's how much he wanted
to save his brother Ace!
That's right! We know how much
he pushed himself to do it!
But that brother died in front of his eyes...
...in order to protect him...
There is no justice in this world! It's
not surprising that he broke down!
Damn it all! Hang in there, Straw Hat!
You got to live! You got to, Straw Hat!
What a tragedy! I wish
I could take his place!
Poor Luffy!
I'm jealous...
It must be nice to have the Pirate
Empress care about you that much...
Yeah, yeah...
By the way, are you a friend of Straw boy?
No, I didn't have to save him at all.
If you're wondering about my motivation,
I can come up with a reason.
No, that's okay. Sometimes your
instinct tells you what to do.
--Hey, wait!
--You can't walk around yet!
--Don't push yourself like that!
--He told you to rest!
--The wound could open up!
--Where are you going?
Jimbei!
You're Trafalgar Law from
the North Blue, aren't you?
Uh-huh.
Hey, is it okay for you
to move around like that?
Thank you!
You saved my life!
You must rest. It could kill you.
I can't ease my mind. It's impossible!
What I have just lost
was too important to me!
That is why I know that Luffy-kun
must be going through far worse!
At least, his instinct to protect himself
forced him to lose
consciousness at that time!
Even if he survives,
I can't stop worrying about
the moment that he wakes up.
You, fuzzy beast, do you
have a Transponder Snail?
Yeah... I mean... yes, ma'am!
I'm sorry!
--I'm jealous. He's like her servant...
--Yeah, yeah...
I'm gonna call the Kuja's ship so we can go
across the Calm Belt even with this submarine.
If the Government finds out that Luffy's
alive, they're gonna come after him!
Let us harbor him at the Maiden Island!
What?!
If they still see me as a
Warlord, Luffy can rest safely!
Luffy...
At Hancock's suggestion,
Luffy is taken to Maiden Island
so his wounds can heal,
and there he finally regains consciousness.
But as his memories of the battle return,
Luffy is overtaken by deep despair.
On the net episode of One Piece!
"Landing at the Maiden Island!
The Harsh Reality Falls upon Luffy!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!