ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
When the Thousand Sunny
drifted into unknown waters,
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
the crew landed on Hungry-la Island,
an island brimming with strange foods,
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
to restock their exhausted food supplies.
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
There they met the Gourmet Hunter
Toriko and the chef Komatsu,
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and they teamed up to capture
the legendary Hungry-la Bird.
Gum-Gum Gatling!
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
Fork!
Knife!
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
Thank you for this excellent meal.
This is exciting!
And so, the time passed
on their lively feast...
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
Now this goes in...
Hey, could I get some more soup?
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Just a moment, please.
Here we go...
What's that?
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
They're spice seeds.
The historic War of the Best
in Marineford has ended.
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made a raid on the Navy HQ to rescue
his brother, Ace who was to be executed!
When I put these in, the spices take
effect and change the soup's flavor.
Luffy made a raid on the Navy HQ to rescue
his brother, Ace who was to be executed!
But his struggle ended in vain
10 years ago, in the East Blue,
as the war came to a close.
and the historic War of the
Best in Marineford has ended.
Luffy met Ace for the
first time when he was 7.
"The Strongest Tag-Team!
Luffy and Toriko's Hard Struggle!"
I won't say it!
Then you die.
However, 10 years ago, in the East Blue...
Ace is really dead, isn't he?!
Whew, I'm stuffed!
Don't!
Yes, he is dead!
Luffy, this is Ace.
That Hungry-la Bird was delicious!
"I Won't Run! Ace's Desperate
Rescue Operation!"
You're gonna live here with them from today.
You're really not going to include this
Hungry-la Bird in your Full Course Meal?
"Landing at the Maiden Island! The
Harsh Reality Falls upon Luffy!"
Take me with you! Let's become friends!
Yeah, that's the thing...
WEST BLUE
Outta my way!
What's wrong?
He says Komatsu and Nami are gone!
Ace!!
--It's him, Porchemy-san!
--He stole the money from us! Damn you!
What left these tracks?
What?
Something smells good.
"Luffy and Ace! The Story
of How the Brothers Met!"
A-Ace!
It's the aroma of fine cocoa.
These tracks were definitely
left by Cocoalas.
It's the end of the forest.
Cocoalas?
You made it easier for us
by coming here voluntarily!
I've never seen one myself,
but they're Capture Level 3.
The War of the Best in Marineford
left a scar in many people's mind.
We were having a hard time
making your friend talk.
"Here Comes Sabo! The Boy
at the Gray Terminal!"
Their meat doesn't taste good enough to eat,
A pirate ship is approaching
Lascamp, West Blue!
but sweet cocoa beans of the highest
quality grow on their backs.
Ace!
But bases in that area have no ships!
10 years ago, in the East Blue,
L-Let me go!
Sabo!
Something that fancy took
Nami-san and the chef?
The nearest bases outside of that area are...
there was a small village called Windmill
Village where people lived peacefully
I can't believe we earned this much!
The 80th division will send back-up!
No, they probably carried
them back to their nest.
Porchemy-san!
Porchemy-san was right!
This is South Blue checking
the location of the site!
That greedy merchant begged for it when we
said that it was treasure from the Grand Line!
Cocoalas are omnivorous.
but not far from it was Mt. Corvo
where people seldom stepped foot.
Ace! Sabo!
They'll take anything and store it as food.
Dammit!
It kind of hurts. Hey!
I thought pirates would be
Only the strong could survive there and
the weak who entered were doomed to die.
And they make their nests
in Multi-fruit Trees.
afraid of us after killing
Whitebeard and gaining victory!
In fact, it was just junk that
we found washed up on the shore!
Do you know what happens
when you mess with adults?!
Multi-fruit?
Instead of laying low, they
are going wild everywhere!
A fruit that combines the
sweet and savory flavors
We were lucky that he was just a
coward who has never gone to sea!
I'll fight you! Sabo, help him!
of wintermelons, watermelons,
apples, mangos, and other fruits.
What I'm saying is, grandpa...
What's gotten into them?
Pirates have made a raid on Lascamp!
Ace!
Well, we've never been to sea, either!
It's also known as the
Fruit Parlor of the Earth!
I'll become the King of the Pirates...
He has a sword! Be careful!
We lost touch with the site! Send back-up!
Cut the crap!
I'd love to eat one!
Let me... Let me go!
I repeat, send back-up to Lascamp!
You're more worried about
food than about your friend?!
On top of eating the Devil
Fruit, you're talking nonsense!
So where can we find these things?
Load supplies! Let's head for the Grand Line!
Luffy! Both you and Ace have to become
MONKEY D. GARP [10 YEARS AGO]
In order to grow the sweetest fruit,
Multi-fruit Trees are said to grow
where the sunlight is most abundant.
the strongest Navy soldiers!
Wow! What is this place?
Ow, ow, ow, dammit!
MONKEY D. LUFFY [10 YEARS AGO]
Oh, he got the knife!
My body is rubber but why is it painful?!
Porchemy-san, that kid...!
Two weeks after the War of the Best,
There is a place like this on the North side
of Mt. Corvo where the Dadan family lives.
Found it!
Let me go, grandpa!
So that's it?
people start to seeing
effects around the world.
It was a mistake to leave
you in the Windmill Village!
There's no doubt. That's Multi-fruit!
Let's go, Ace!
It is a smoky pile of discarded junk.
Of all things, you like
pirates?! What a fool!
Go ahead!
Nami-san! I'm coming!
You fool! Hurry up!
Just you wait, Multi-fruit!
You can't make friends
with "Red-Haired" Shanks!
Y-You can't come any further!
Don't come into our town!
When I come to face someone, I won't run!
Unwanted things ended up here.
I feel so sorry for Komatsu right now...
I wanna become...
What'd you say?! You little shit!
And here live rogues who were
shunned from mainstream society.
Ouch!
...a strong man like Shanks!
You heard the news, didn't you?
Don't do it! He's not like
the thugs in the city!
Hey!
Unsurprisingly, it's a lawless area.
You got that right!
Luffy... What happened to our food?
Alright! Enough playing
around! That's our money.
Then you know that this island is
no longer Whitebeard's territory.
Crime and disease abound
since there are no doctors.
Luffy...
Usopp...
What's this place?
Give it back to us peacefully, brat!
This place is called Gray Terminal.
This symbol is meaningless now!
You've aged a lot.
You must been possessed by
some evil spirit, right?
At this rate, you're gonna
end up all bones, like Brook.
Stop it!! Whoever you are,
do you wanna get killed?!
That's right! Whitebeard is dead!
Give the money back so you won't regret it.
Ace!
It's me.
Nice skull joke...
We have better plans for that money!
G-Garp-san!
What's that?
Wh...
Still...
CURLY DADAN
What did you say?!
Wait here for a minute!
A MOUNTAIN BANDIT: DOGRA
You're so reckless!
Why are you always like this?!
A MOUNTAIN BANDIT: MAGRA
What's this vapor?
Listen, and engrave this in your mind!
I won't run!
You're looking good.
A geyser?
He's not here.
Give me a break! Please,
you gotta have mercy on me!
Stop talking crap!
The man who takes control of
this island from today is me -
Yow!
Look out!
the pirate Brownbeard!
Ace is 10 years old now!
You don't know where they'll burst up from!
Hey! Where did you go?!
If I'm beaten by kids, I may
as well quit being a pirate!
Oh yeah, already? How is he?
That's really hot!
The war ended with the death of
Whitebeard and the victory of the Navy.
But it's sweet! It's chocolate!
--We'll make sure you quit!
It's not funny!
Ace!
We can't handle him anymore!
You have to take him!
I'm gonna kill all of you!
What?! Really?!
But contrary to what the Navy thought,
Ace!
--Putting that aside...
--Don't put it aside!
Quit making your eyes sparkle and just run!
the situation has grown
tense all over the world.
You're annoying, kid!
While we're doing this, Nami-san is...
Look after him, too.
What's that?
Meanwhile, a short time ago,
A big one's coming!
Hey, Luffy, say "hi" to them.
Hancock, Jimbei and others decided
It's afternoon already.
Yo!
to head to the Maiden Island
to harbor the unconscious Luffy
Who is that kid?
Hot!
I heard the whole story,
Porchemy. How pathetic.
Treasure, treasure! Is there
anything valuable here?
He is my grandson.
and joined up with the Kuja's ship.
What?
Did you honestly get beaten by kids?
What?!
Crap! A river!
--Big Sis!
One more?!
What's wrong?
Snake Princess-sama!
People with Devil Fruit powers can't swim!
He's Garp's... I mean, Garp-san's grandson?!
Here's something!
I'm sorry, Captain Bluejam... The money is...
Sorry that I made you worry,
Sandersonia, Marigold, and everyone!
--Give it to me!
--That's mine!
What?!
We can't!
Stop it! I found it!
Alright then, Here's your choice.
Don't look at me! I don't
even want to see your face!
Don't touch it, you fools!
Do you wanna spend all your
life in prison or raise him?
Thank you for your warm greeting!
Let me cash it in for you!
We are all so grateful for
your great work as a Warlord!
--You can't have it!
--Stop!
There are many crimes you
committed that I've overlooked.
Huh? This isn't water.
Now, who will get my money back?
Cream?
Come on!
It's a river of whipped cream!
Well, I don't wanna get arrested but...
Alright then, this is it for my
role in supporting Straw boy.
Don't tell me we'll let
it go without a fight.
Tasty!
Sometimes I think that maybe it's better
to be in prison than take care of Ace...
All right, not much longer now!
Of course not. We'll get it back right away.
--Damn you!
--Give it to me!
Heehaw!
Do you mind if I leave the
rest up to you, Jimbei?
You wouldn't have gotten hurt
if you'd just given it to me!
But you want us to look after your
grandson, too? I bet he's also a monster.
Yes. I can't swim as I want yet.
Crappy shack!
Thank you very much!
The least I can do is stay
here until he gets well.
You wanna fight?!
You asshole!
Not listening!
You have a bad habit, Ace!
Boss! Are you alright?!
I don't know how I can help him, though.
Once we're through this forest,
we'll be at the Multi-Fruit Tree.
When faced with a real
pirate it's best to run!
Thief!
What is it?! Ugh, spit! Gross!
It was a curious turn of fate to meet you.
Why do you have such a death wish?
Who did it?!
This doesn't feel right.
I liked the one I had.
I agree.
What was that?!
Hey, you!
Although we were both locked up in
Outta my way, brat!
Say "sorry"! It's gross!
the greatest prison in the world - Impel Down,
I knew it. A Caste Leo.
Hurry up! Or I'm gonna...
Ace!
We made a stupid mistake.
The Bluejam clan won't forgive us.
if it weren't for Luffy-kun,
Are you back, Ace?
Caste Leo?
He went that way!
we would have never met each
other at all I suppose.
Caste Leo (Mammal Beast) Capture Level 4
PORTGAS D. ACE [10 YEARS AGO]
They'll come after us!
Oh, that was scary!
I thought I was gonna die!
Capture Level 4.
We both tried really hard to keep up
with Straw boy at Marineford, didn't we?
Hey, say "sorry"!
Their manes are exquisite,
fluffy castella cake!
Luffy, this is Ace. He's
3 years older than you.
You're so annoying! Shut up!
Stop crying already!
It's hard to say goodbye to you
Growling in that super deep voice...
Is this supposed to be a joke?
You're gonna live here with them from today.
but I have sweet candies waiting
for me to come back to the kingdom.
I don't like cowards or people who cry a lot!
We're going to where Nami and Komatsu are!
What?! You can't just do that!
I won't let anyone get in our
way, no matter who it is!
Please take good care of Straw boy!
Th-Thank you!
Be nice!
Luffy!
Is it decided?!
You...
Bye, Straw Hat! Thank you for letting us out!
Any problem with that?
You helped me!
What is that?
My dream can come true because of you!
--You...!
--Whoa, he's just being thankful.
We'll take him!
"THE FOREST IN-BETWEEN"
MT COLVO AND GRAY TERMINAL
Sound shock waves!
That's all from me. I'll
stop by when I have time.
His castella sponge cake emits sound.
Say "hi" to him when he wakes up!
It's like a giant speaker.
--Um... What about some child support?
--Put it on my bill.
--See you again if we have a chance!
--Hang in there!
Why didn't you cough it
up in the first place?
Isn't there any way to beat it?
Sabo! Sabo, are you there?!
--This is not a bar...
--Huh?
Well, can you draw his
attacks straight ahead?
You can't die, Straw Hat!
--You're always welcome!
--Boss, we can't take care of one more kid!
They're kind of people who'd kill
women or kids without hesitation!
Okay, let's go!
Oh, Ace!
Right!
--Shut up! Let's just eat first! Fix it!
--Okay!
Sorry I'm late.
To the New Kamas' home and our mecca!
I thought if I said anything...
you wouldn't be my friend.
You sure are.
Okay, now!
I've already done some work in the city.
Toriko!
Say "sorry"!
SABO [10 YEARS OLD] (A BOY WHO
LIVES IN THE GRAY TERMINAL)
To the Kamabakka Kingdom! Heehaw...
His sound attack only works
directly in front of him!
Wait!
It's better than dying, isn't it?
We can get him from the sides!
Why do you wanna become my friend that much?
I'll leave this hat with you.
We have to head for the Maiden Island, too.
Oh yeah? Well, I did, too.
At once!
Because...
Threefold
And the pirate ship that Luffy is on arrived
at the Maiden Island - Amazon Lily,
Whoa! You got a lot! Way more than I did!
Didn't I give you a hard time until now?
Nail Punch!
That's a lot of money! How'd you get that?
the female-only empire
where men are prohibited
How could you follow me this far?
and Kuja, the tribe of
female fighters, lives.
I robbed some thugs near the main gate!
Amazing!
Where did he go?
What was that?!
Damn! You won again!
--Snake Princess-sama!
--Welcome back!
Who are you?
I drive multiple punches into one
spot, like hammering in nails.
Because...
Let me go!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
Give me your money or I'll kill you!
Because I have nobody else to trust!
I don't have any!
It's been 5 years since we started
to put money in our "pirate savings".
It's my Nail Punch.
Then tell your parents
to bring some money here!
I can't go back to Windmill Village
and I don't like the mountain bandits!
I'm so glad that the princess is safe!
--Grandpa is my only...
--That's fine. What's his name?
If I didn't follow you, I'd be all alone!
There are men on the
strange ship in the back!
There were this many of them?
We worked hard for it.
Garp-san.
Being lonely is more
painful than getting hurt!
--Look! There are only women!
--It's true that it's a female-only island!
And they're huge.
Is this kid...?!
Yes, we did.
He's gonna live here with us.
These guys roam in prides.
We're gonna leave the East Blue and go
somewhere these people have never dreamed of.
Where are your parents?
Five Caste Leos and one small Caste Leo...
--They snuck into the ship! Unforgivable!
--W-Wait!
--Why did you accept?!
--This is not a day-care!
Grandpa is all I have.
It's exciting just to think about it!
Our boss has no guts!
--Smells nice!
--I feel lightheaded!
Looks like we're surrounded.
Is it easy for you when I'm around?
Shut up you all!
What?!
Uh-huh.
This must be heaven!
--It's hard without me?
--Uh-huh.
It's time to eat!
Hey, you guys.
Spatula!
You gotta go back in, otherwise you'll die.
--Give it to me, fool!
--It's my meat!
Now put it away. We can't
let anybody to see it.
What if Gold Roger had a child?
I want some meat!
I wonder how much we need
to get a pirate ship.
I hope that there isn't such a child!
Such a beautiful way to make an entrance.
--You already ate!
--I want more!
I don't know. 10 million
or 100 million maybe?
He must be some kind of devil
who'd be better off dead!
Sunny!
I'm not gonna give in to young people!
People, stop! They're not our enemy!
Poison Rifle!
--You got to share!
--It's a dog-eat-dog world.
Long way to go.
"A pirate ship"?!
Snake Princess-sama!
Luffy is in that ship!
You guys! Are you gonna become pirates?!
Endorphin Smoke!
His arm stretches!
He suffered greatly, mentally and
physically, during the battle at Marineford
What now?!
Do you want me to live?
I'm gonna become one, too!
It suddenly got quiet.
Dog?
and he is hanging between life and death now.
Hey, Toriko.
It's your turn to wash dishes!
Luffy's here?!
Of course I do!
Ladies, carry Luffy to the Kuja
Castle as soon as possible!
Coco! Rin!
Can I have some more, pops!
Toriko! I'm so glad you're safe!
I see.
I'm a woman!
--I'm gonna look after Luffy...
--Wait a minute, Snake Princess!
Do you even know where you are now?!
An angel has come down!
But I don't like spoiled kids like you.
--Be quiet!
Wow! They're your friends, Toriko?
No.
Well, yeah...
Then I'll tell you.
But what are you doing here?
This is a den of the Dadan family,
mountain bandits that rule Mt. Corvo!
Ace! I didn't know that you
travel this far everyday!
Granny Nyon!
I'm not spoiled! I'm strong!
We heard that you had set out
to capture a Hungry-la Bird,
It's fine if it's just Luffy.
Mountain bandits? I hate mountain bandits!
But we can't allow those
men on that strange ship
Shut up!
Strong?! You're not strong
at all! You cry like a girl!
so we came to tell you the
secret of Hungry-la Island...
Is this the Luffy that
you were talking about?
to step foot onto the Maiden Island.
Anyway! I can't believe you left
me behind! You're awful, Toriko!
Shut up, you little shit! We're
annoyed by having a kid like you!
It's against our country's policy!
Oh, you told him about me?!
Have you ever gotten hit by
a spiky thing? I'm only 7!
It was so hard to find this island!
I told him how annoying you are.
Then, let's just allow the
doctor to come with him so...
When I become your age - 10, I'll
stop crying and become stronger!
If you don't wanna stay here, that's fine!
I'm so mad!
He also told me that you're empty-headed.
By the way...
Go away and die like a dog somewhere!
No!
We can't allow any men to come onto
the island, even if he is a doctor!
Easy, easy, boss.
I wouldn't cry even if I were
7, stupid! I'm not like you!
Oh yeah?
Where's Komatsu-kun?
I wanna eat more...
You don't realize that
we're dissing you, do you?
Actually, he was taken by Cocoalas.
We have so many good doctors on this island!
I'm gonna become stronger than anyone!
He finally got me here although I
didn't take any walkable routes.
I wanna have that meat, too.
What?!
Yeah! Our friend is with him, too!
I promised Shanks that I'd
become a great pirate!
Well, I don't care either way but...
That creature is unreal! It talked!
Are you a friend of Ace's?
Be my friend, too, buddy!
--You? Become a pirate?
--Yes!
...do you have the same medical
equipment and technology as my ship?
--No way!
--Yes way!
These are all from a bison that Ace brought.
Shut up! You can't call me "buddy"!
They've recovered, huh?
Okay, that's enough!
We don't have time to deal with these guys!
--Then what's your name?
--Sa...
He gave us a cut of the
take so everybody can eat.
If his wound opens up, he's going to die.
Hey, by the way, I have a little problem.
Quick! We've gotta go save Nami!
I'm not telling you!
These guys are gonna be a pain, though.
The mountain bandits' world is rough sailing.
Take Straw Hat-ya if you don't care about it.
This is why I told you to live here with me!
--What? A problem?
--Uh-huh.
You're gonna have to work
pretty hard from tomorrow!
Beautiful...
Luffy's gonna die?!
A heart that cares for its friends...
The daily round trip--training on the
mountain road turned out to be bad!
Bluejam and the others will try to kill the
three of us after this for sure, right?
Cleaning, laundry, polishing
shoes and weapons,
If that happens by any chance...
Oh, I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
That is more beautiful than anything.
What should we do?
burglary, robbery, fraud, and murder!
Toriko, leave this to us,
and go save Komatsu.
It's obvious that we can't save
Luffy-kun without this man.
Well, I think so.
He found our secret. He's gonna
tell somebody if nothing is done.
Remember, you can't tell
Garp what we make you do!
We'll be fine on our own!
This forest that I've been living is close
to where they are - the Cove of Pirates!
If he can't come in, we have no choice.
You guys...
All of you, hurry!
One bowl of rice and one
glass of water for a day!
We must go somewhere else.
Thanks!
What if they attack me when
I fall asleep exhausted?
I'm counting on you!
Impossible! We'd be
attacked by the Sea Kings!
I'll get that Multi-fruit, no matter what!
That's all I can guarantee you.
We gotta kill him.
Even if we get away from them, the
Navy could find us at anytime!
--You're gonna die.
--Yeah, you're gonna die.
Alright, let's do it.
You gotta get everything else by
yourself and grow up on your own.
Multi-fruit?
Right?
What about Komatsu-kun?
What?!
What should we do?!
Okay!
That's why I need your help.
Does it seem like Toriko's goal
is different from everyone else's?
"Okay"?! Why don't you cry or something?
Don't kill me!! Help me!! I don't wanna die!!
Oh, well... We only do
it as an exception but...
Guys, huddle up.
I'm fine because grandpa
threw me into a jungle once
Well, in any case...
...you can stay in the area of the bay.
Shut up, you fool!
and there was water to drink and frogs,
snakes, and mushrooms to eat in the forest!
Sabo, kill him already!
The Sea Kings won't attack you there.
We will take you on!
What?! You do it!
Plus, I'll become a pirate someday so...
I've never killed anybody before!
Then, I'll stay with them
to look after Luffy...
Me, neither! And I don't know how!
...I must be strong like that!
What is it, Toriko?
No!
Oh, I was just wondering why the Caste
Leos didn't attack the Cocoalas,
--Boss!
--Are you alright?!
Don't throw me into water!!
Damn Granny Nyon! You just
keep saying "no" to me!
What're you doing?!
--Okay, let's head to the river!
--Why did he tell us that?
Here we go!
since their Capture Level is lower.
Why are they wounded? They're all bandaged!
Luffy! I hope you'll get better soon!
Huh?
Where is he going?!
He's stupid!
To get to the top of the mountain,
Help me!!
the Cocoalas must have passed
through the Caste Leos' area.
Here we go!
Looking at Snake Princess-sama,
--Shut up!
I can tell that Luffy is
in critical condition.
Where are you going?!
Carrying Komatsu and your friend
would've slowed the Cocoalas down.
Did you just say "pirate"?
I don't wanna die!
He's not listening!
Luffy...
They should've been prime
prey for the Caste Leos.
I hear a voice from the forest!
Hey!
Whoa! Boss! Boss! We have a problem!
Two weeks have passed.
And they were obviously hungry.
A kid's voice!
Law and others are staying in the bay...
Oh no! Somebody's coming!
There must be some reason why
they didn't eat the Cocoalas.
Hmm? It's still early. What's wrong...
See? He's too tough!
Set him free for now!
...to provide Luffy with treatment.
Whoa! What's going on here?!
I've got a bad feeling about this.
We gotta move from
here or they're gonna find our treasure!
That's why I didn't wanna
take care of Garp's grandson!
1, 2...
Easy, easy, boss.
How much longer do we have to
stay in such a small space...
Put me down, you monster koalas!
Hey!
Everybody knows those kids
around here. Ace and Sabo.
Yeah, the only thing to look forward to is...
Huh?
Wait for me!
1, 2...
Huh?
--Guys, sorry to keep you waiting!
--It's a meal time.
This is...
Hey!
Are you sure that it was
Ace who took the money?
CREW MEMBER OF THE BLUEJAM PIRATES PORCHEMY
Ace, Luffy...
Finally!
Multi-fruit!
Huh?
My name is Luffy! I'm not mad
about you spitting on me anymore!
Here it is.
Yes. We're sorry. We shouldn't
let our guard down.
Ace, Luffy... Huh?
--The only consolation is that the food is good!
--I agree!
It's my first time seeing them! I'm so moved!
Ace, Luffy... Huh? Ace, Luffy... Huh?
How outrageous that kid is!
He can't just steal our money!
Huh?!
--Here you go!
--Thank you...
I wonder what they taste like...
Ace... Luffy... Huh?
Please don't push and wait for your turn.
I wonder how they should be cooked
to bring out their flavors...
Why are you laughing?!
If Captain Bluejam finds out about
this, he's gonna kill all of us!
Ace, Luffy, huh? Ace, Luffy,
huh? Ace, Luffy, huh?
Forget about that!
Aphelandra!
He only spilled some booze on me.
It's nothing worth getting mad over.
Think about what's happening
to you right now!
Don't talk to men!
Ace! Luffy! Who is that?!
It's nothing worth getting mad
over. Let's become friends!
Luffy is the exception because
of the princess' orders.
Dammit! I didn't know that those
thugs were working for Bluejam!
Who is who?
Don't forget!
Are you going somewhere?!
Okay!
You mean that you stole the money from them?
Come on, it's no big deal!
Right, Aphelandra-chan?
It's still early - you're too loud!
I shouldn't have taken that money...
He has a real sword. That's
Porchemy who works under Bluejam.
How come there is one more kid?!
I'm not gonna say it again!
That's Nami-san's voice!
He's crazy. Did you know that?
Who the hell are you?!
It's a dead end!
We're sorry!
Are you talking about me?
Sanji!
Nami-san!
He strips off your scalp alive
after you lose a fight with him!
I'm Sabo! Hey, you must be Dadan!
Excuse me.
Sabo? I've heard your name before!
Is Luffy awake?
Koalas... Huh?
Luffy! Sanji-kun!
Oh yeah? That makes it easier! Thank
you for taking care of me from today!
Let's just let them pass for now...
I see.
Toriko-san!
It's up to Straw Hat-ya's spirit.
Nami!
Oh? Where is he?
That's...
"Taking care"? Don't tell me
that you're gonna stay here...
Whether he's willing to live or not.
A Knock-out Koala!
So he's their boss?
--Let me go! What do you want from me?
--How could you get caught?
--Margaret, let's go already!
--I'm coming!
Don't answer me with a fart!
Knock-out Koala (Marsupial Beast) Capture Level 5
Let me go! You bastard!
I'm sorry! Take good care of Luffy!
They say that when Cocoalas reach
adulthood, they become Knock-out Koalas,
You must be kidding! I heard that
you're a worthless brat, too!
Margaret, how many times do I have
to tell you not to talk to them?!
Who is this little shit?
but I've never heard of one getting that big.
Help me! Ace!!
I'm sorry!
Oh yeah? I heard that you're
a worthless old bag, too!
Help me, Ace!!
Now I know why the Caste Leos
didn't attack the Cocoalas.
--That fool! He's calling my name!
--Help me! Ace!!
That's unnecessary information!
They were afraid of the Cocoalas'
boss, the Knock-out Koala!
I don't wanna look after one more brat!
But I heard that you're a good worthless
old bag because you can't refuse a request.
Big Sis...
So now he's shown his true colors.
I heard that you're a truly
manly worthless old bag!
Oh, boy... So if we don't beat these
guys, we can't save Nami-san anyway?
"Truly manly"? I'm a woman!
I'm not a gender bender!
Luffy...
Did you just call for "Ace"?
So what?!
Do you know Ace?
How are they so fast?!
You've always been like this, Luffy!
So the Capture Level of Cocoalas
in battle mode exceeds 3, eh?
I'm his friend!
You've never even listened to me...
Oh, but he just tried to kill me.
Hey, Toriko!
...and always done such crazy things!
Luffy! Toriko!
That fool! He's such a big mouth!
Hey!
You guys can handle things here!
Ace, Luffy, Sabo!
I don't know if you know about this but
Hey! Ace is back!
What?!
I heard that Ace stole some
money from us and ran today.
I'm giving you a place to stay!
You gotta get to work already!
Got it!
Food!
Don't do it...
Luffy, Toriko! Take care of Nami-san!
Don't do it!
Right!
You don't know where is it now, do you?
Ace, did you come back alone?
We'll save Nami!
Thank you, Dadan!
What?!
Um, what about me?!
Where is Luffy? I thought
that you were with him.
--Stop it, Straw Hat!
--You wanna destroy the ship?!
I don't know.
Oh no! They're gonna take
all our treasure away!
That fool, where is he and what is he doing?
I hope that fool doesn't tell them!
I won't let you get in
Luffy and Toriko's way!
Maybe he's dead already.
Ace...
We are dead if Garp finds out about this.
Boss must be pretty worried I bet!
So? What do you say?
--See ya!
Something's making a lot of noise.
Hey, Luffy! You stay here and do
some laundry and clean the house!
There's no helping it.
--Get hold of yourself, boss!
--What did you say?!
Nothing's gonna happen if
we just wait around here.
--What?!
--Huh?!
No way!
Let's take the ship around to
the other side of the island.
I said it's not good that we
lost him on the first day!
I-I don't know...
Luffy-kun!
Oh, Ace, Sabo, wait!
I'm too hungry to move...
Who cares! if he dies, he dies!
A terrible liar!
So this is what they call
"bones broken for nothing"...
Honestly! What annoying brats!
And I'm nothing but bones...
Garp is gonna kill us.
Oh yeah!
Quit your whining! Unfurl the sails!
Ace...
First of all, why should we
look after Garp's grandson?!
Ace...
I forget to tell them.
Hey, Dadan!
Alright, alright! It can't be
helped that you don't know.
We're not nannies! He has to
take care of his own grandson!
While we're gone, the Bluejam
clan might come by so be careful!
Where's Ace?!
Don't worry, I'll help you
bring back the memory!
The Bluejam clan might come by? Why?
--Why don't you say it to him?
--You have a problem?!
Luffy!
Toriko-san!
Luffy! You okay?
What are you doing?! Let me
go! Where are you taking me?!
Yeah!
Damn that thing... It can't
really only be Level 5!
Because we beat some of his crew up! Bye!
Dammit! Stupid! Let me go!
You bastard! Let me go! What
are you doing, bastard?!
What?!
What should we do?!
What if Gold Roger had a child?
You know what we have to do...
Dadan sure is an understanding
worthless old bag!
Not bad!
Of course I know what'd happen to him!
He'd get his head cut off for sure!
She's still a worthless old bag!
Hey, you! Give back Nami!
Plus she's a mountain bandit
and her face is scary!
Yeah! Give me the Multi-fruit!
I want to hear from him as he dies:
What?! You didn't come to save me?!
This is dangerous! Calm down, Straw Hat!
What are we gonna do now?
Let me go!
"I'm sorry I was born! I'm
just a piece of trash!"
First...
I'm not gonna tell you anything!
What is going to happen
if we leave him like that?
Eat something!
Well, it's simple. Like
I said when we got here,
Okay, let's eat!
Luffy!
if his wound opens up, he will die.
You little shit!
I'm already giving up on Ace, too!
Toriko!
Yes, now is the chance!
--Let me go, dammit!
--Stay still, Straw Hat!
I don't care if he dies or not. I'll
just tell Garp it was an accident.
--Shut up! I'm looking for Ace!
--I told you that "Fire Fist" is...
It's true that "the devil's
children have the devil's luck"!
It's incredibly strong!
I said "let me go"!
Okay, now it's my turn!
I told you that my body turned to
rubber after I ate the Gum-Gum Fruit!
He's the devil's son!
Gum-Gum
Shut up!
Where's Ace?!
Luffy, so you ate the Devil Fruit?
If the Government finds out about this,
what do you think they'd do to us?!
--Ace!!
--Damn! He's out of control!
The Devil Fruit, eh?
Uh-huh!
No wonder you can't swim.
Knife!
Easy, easy, boss.
Looks like you had the real one.
--It's Luffy!
--We got to tell Snake Princess-sama!
Here, you can have this, too.
You're drinking too much!
Snake Princess-sama! Snake Princess-sama!
Get me a pair of gloves.
Using Nami and Komatsu to shield
yourself is playing dirty!
Thanks!
ONE WEEK LATER
You're too kind, Sabo.
Y-Yes, sir!
One week later...
Hurry up, hurry up! We're
screwed if they come back!
Luffy woke up!
Well, what's wrong with that?
--Luffy-sama?!
--Really?!
So, what fruit did you eat?
We gotta move our treasure somewhere else!
I'm glad. I wanna see him right away!
Gum-Gum!
Gum-Gum? Gum?!
It's a matter of time
before Luffy tells them!
How annoying!
You can't, Snake Princess!
Everybody wants to see him.
They'll take not only what we stole from them
That's right!
Why don't you shut up?
In exchange for the ability to swim,
your body turned to rubber? So crappy!
You can't discipline your people if
you allow yourself to go and see him.
but all of our "pirate savings" that
we've spent 5 years collecting!
Toriko!
Boss! Boss Dadan!
It's not crappy! I can use
a lot of unbeatable attacks!
Men are prohibited on this island.
Who is it?
We let strange men stay at the bay area
--You!
--Luffy came back!
That's good. Good for you.
Nami! Komatsu!
Listen, you little shit.
That's a Multi-fruit Tree for you.
and that's enough of an exception for us!
You have such a fat mouth even
though you can't catch a fish.
The money that your friend Ace stole
is very important to our pirate crew.
Huh?
It can support that Knock-out Koala's
intense movements without even budging.
I know, but...
Before that, Big Sis, you
need to eat something.
You fool! You're alive! You...!
Your body really is rubber! Interesting!
And you know where it is.
That's right, Big Sis! You've
barely eaten since you got back!
What's more, the recoil gives
its attack power a huge boost!
So I need you to tell us.
Don't play with my body!
Easy, easy, boss.
Where were you?!
Sounds like a pain.
That's right! Luffy must be very hungry, too!
No!
But...
But rubber surely stretches
and shrinks and expands so...
Easy, easy. Where were you
and what were you doing?
Those huge stems must be sending
tons of nutrients to the fruit.
Fix a lot of great dishes
that will give him energy!
I've been chased by wolves
at the bottom of the valley.
...maybe it's useful when you're fighting!
Yes, we'd be happy to!
I'm gonna help you! Ladies, let's do it now!
What were you doing at
the bottom of the valley?
It worked!
Right?! Oh yeah, I came
up with another attack.
Multi-fruit...
Yes, Snake Princess-sama!
I swear I will eat you!
--Anyway, it's nice that you're okay.
--Yeah.
It's called "Gum-Gum Balloon"! I can
deflect cannonballs and everything!
I should just let her do that. She
just wants to fix some food...
You don't wanna make a pirate mad!
He's still talking about that?!
Our captain Bluejam is very brutal!
It's not okay! The pest came back!
Wow! Can you do it for me now?
Then I'm gonna take them to him!
Yeah!
Okay, I'll do it just for
you! Ace can't see it.
So you're going?!
Luffy! You, too?!
Why don't you go to bed tonight?
You gotta work from tomorrow!
We promised that when he gets
well, we would invite Luffy alone.
What are you thinking?!
Don't look!
Here we go! Gum-Gum...
Already?
I give thanks...
Wait for that moment!
It hurts! I'm scared!
...for all this world's bounty.
I can't! I am an empress!
Don't tell me what to do!
Help me!!
Now let's eat!
I said no!
What?! What is it?! What the hell?!
H-Hey!
The most important thing is
the hereditary policy of this country!
Guys, go look for Ace and Sabo! We
don't have time to stand around!
Awesome! You're getting bigger and bigger!
What's up?
Are you gonna go somewhere today, Ace?
Honestly! You're infected
by such a strong virus!
...Balloon! See it?! It's cool, isn't it?!
Take me with you! Let's become friends!
Y-Yes, sir!
I can't believe that the fearful
pirate empress has become love sick!
Well, I don't think it's cool...
Wait for me!
Boss! He's going after Ace again!
However, he must have been like a small ant
It's good for working off my meal!
Hey! You gotta do chores around the house!
You're asking me if I know Ace and Sabo?
What are you doing?!
Gum-Gum...
diving into a tempest at
Impel Down and the Navy HQ.
Sabo, kick it back!
You guys must be hooligans from the city.
No thank you!
Ah, okay.
...Nail Punch!
It must have been an act of God to let
him live and be brought back here.
You don't wanna mess with those two.
You little shit! You're out of control!
Stop it!
Easy, easy, boss.
They're kids but you
can't underestimate them.
Is that the unbeatable attack
that will deflect cannonballs?!
I wonder what God expects from him.
--Bring him back right now!
--Yes, ma'am.
They're like mad dogs
that'd kill even a tiger.
Stop it!
Hey!
Ace and Sabo? I haven't
seen them for a while.
Then, why don't you deflect my kick?!
--Hey, pass me the wrench.
--Okay, here you go.
Stop it!
Anyway, young men, why don't you
leave everything valuable here?
Hey, do you think you can fix the ship?
Yeah, I'll manage.  That aside,
where did Straw Hat go?
--C-Come on, man!
--We'll ask someone else!
Jimbei is gone, too.
They still don't know where we are?
I don't know.
Thank you for this excellent meal.
Well, I heard that if a man enters the
I thought that they'd know by now...
Now, I'll just help myself
to that Multi-fruit...
Maiden Island, he's gonna be turned to stone
--Wait! You can't just eat and run!
Oh no!
but maybe it's worth dying for.
Ace!
Huh?
According to Aphelandra-chan, not
all women were there at the port.
--You bastard!
I didn't realize that it's almost night.
What's going on? It's waving around.
Yes! It's finished!
The female-only island that I dreamed
of! I wish I could take a look inside!
Ace! Let's become friends!
We moved all the treasure!
--Take this!
Wh-What's happening?
You're gonna die, you idiot.
You guys...
I wonder if there are female bears...
Well, what can I say? Let it go.
What's wrong with that kid?
It's Maiden Island!
Hey, this is unreal!
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I can't! I almost got eaten!
The 8th day...
Only humans! There are only humans!
Ace!
Calm down. You can have a lot
of crocodile meat for dinner.
I'm really sorry!
Everyone get down the mountain!
Wait for me!
Ace!
Boss!
Sabo! What's wrong? Have they
shown up to look for the money?
What?!
Work, you little shit!
Then I forgive you guys.
It's no use...
--Bring him back!
--Yes, ma'am.
That easily?
I'm not gonna lose you today!
No, they haven't!
I wanna eat the crocodile already.
I can't wait until dinner.
And I bet they won't!
I can do that!
Ace! I wanna check something quickly.
What do you mean?
That kid, Luffy...
Let's become friends!
He hasn't told them anything!
Can you come with me?
I'm sure that they're torturing him!
10 days have passed...
--Luffy!
--He's gone already...
I thought that he'd just tell them
because he's dumb and cries so much!
The island is about to show its true form.
Look for him!
It doesn't make sense!
--Did you find it?
--Look carefully!
Its true form?
I told you that we came to tell you
the secret of Hungry-la Island, right?
If nothing is done, he'll...
I'm glad that we moved the "pirate savings".
He kept going after Ace and losing him.
Yeah.
Do you wanna check the Gray Terminal, too?
But it went on everyday.
Yeah, okay. Why don't you go home now?
Ace!
GRAY TERMINAL "THE COVE OF PIRATES"
It's so late!
No!
Where am I?
Who is in charge today?
He won't listen to anyone.
It's Porchemy, Captain Bluejam.
Maybe it was all a dream...
You okay?
1 month...
It's sweet.
It's almost sunset.
Yum! This is caramel!
2 months...
Ace!
What?
No matter if it rained and was windy...
There are hooligans from the city
and Bluejam's people everywhere.
It's true!
I'm sure that they've already
cashed it in by now.
What's going on?
The legend of Hungry-la
Island has been recorded
They're serious!
Ace!
Maybe he's running away with the money.
CAPTAIN OF THE BLUEJAM PIRATES BLUEJAM
I bet that Bluejam got really frustrated.
in many texts since ancient times.
Luffy kept going after Ace desperately.
Our predecessors have transcribed
those texts and handed
No way! I don't think that he would risk
getting killed trying something like that!
I'm sorry, Luffy...
them down throughout history to the present.
Luffy is chasing Ace again?!
That's why we relied on the legends
in those texts to find this island
Hey, guys! The kids that you're
looking for are all here!
How does he never learn after
getting hurt so many times?
I don't think so, either!
I couldn't make it all the way.
and capture the phantom
ingredient, the Hungry-la Bird.
There they are!
Damn! He has to stop making me worry!
Stop! You can't run from us!
But it turns out the phantom ingredient
is not the Hungry-la Bird.
So you're worrying.
N-No way! Stop talking nonsense!
Spit it out already!
Huh?
You know, the characters for
"bird" and "island" look similar.
Go away! Go away!
A bee-hive fell on me.
Hungry-la Bird
Hungry-la Island
I can't believe that they bought
over pops at the Terminal.
Apparently, whoever transcribed
it read the name wrong.
P-P-P-Porchemy-san!
It's no use doing it anymore!
Luffy!
Who are you?
We'd better lay low for a
while until things calm down.
Then, the phantom ingredient is...
No!
Ace!
He doesn't have the energy
to even scream now!
Who cares? We'll just fight if they find us.
Not the Hungry-la Bird,
but Hungry-la Island?!
That's true but we don't have
to look for trouble ourselves.
Go away! Go away!
No wonder the Hungry-la Bird
was such an easy opponent!
I bet he won't say anything and to be
honest, I can't stand watching it--it's too cruel!
Ace! Hey!
I agree with Sabo!
You just shut up!
I can't believe he's coming
this far. He's so persistent.
Show some mercy!
This island itself is the
legendary ingredient...
Bluejam... The kids made quite an enemy!
Oh crap!
A natural pudding  la mode!
Look for Ace and Sabo if you
have time to speak for the kid!
Damn! I lost him again! Ace runs so fast!
I'm sure that they're gonna find
this place and come by pretty soon!
We're the ones that are in danger
of death! Can't you see?!
Amazing!
Is it Ace?!
What the heck is this?!
There is no way that we can defeat them...
We're already too late to give
that money to Captain Bluejam!
I wonder if Luffy and the others are okay...
Maybe this is the end of the Dadan family!
I have to say goodbye to the
humble-but-sweet mountain bandit's life?
That's the beast of Mt.
Corvo! No one can beat it!
How could they do that to the little
kid? Should we call sheriff in the city?
It's better to quit the mountain bandit
business than to get exterminated!
Delicious!
It's no use. This area is not
covered by the country's law.
Why is he not running?! It's gonna eat him!
This luxurious sweetness achieved
by condensing a multitude of fruits!
I-I feel weak at the knees!
Plus, he's a member of the Bluejam Pirates.
If I don't escape death...
So this is the Multi-fruit!
"We can't defeat them"?
"Out of business"?
That fool!
It is indeed the Fruit Parlor of the Earth!
And they're paying money to the Nobles.
How pathetic you guys are!
I'm sorry but could you
look after my brother?
They'll be overlooked for any crime and
murder they commit in this country.
Hey, Toriko, you think this whole
mountain is made of pudding?!
Don't you take pride in
being a mountain bandit?!
You're right! It's delicious!
It's easy!
Hey! I was gonna eat that part!
One more dead body will draw
no one's attention here.
The war is over!
If they come by,
What's the problem?! There's plenty!
Ace-san is...
we can just hand Ace and
the other two over to them!
Oh, and apparently the next
mountain is all ice cream!
Don't say it! Don't say anything!
Answer me!
What?! You should've said so sooner!
But, boss, how do we explain it to Garp?!
Wow! This castella is tasty, too!
I won't say it.
I already pinched myself
hard enough to rip my skin!
Isn't that the mane of
one of those Caste Leos?
You little shit! Stop trying to
keep a secret like a grown-up!
Plus, Bluejam is not the kind of guy who
will be satisfied by just handing them over!
What?!
If it were a dream, I should've woken by now!
So after you ate all that, you're not
using any of it in your Full Course Meal?
Th-Then...
Say it!!
It's not a dream, is it?
Well, it's a big world.
Then?
I'm sure there's still lots
more delicious food out there.
I won't say it!
Let's just pretend that
we don't know anything!
I won't say it!
You really are a big eater!
Now, try it! We gotta practice!
I won't say it!
We're stocked up on food now.
We can set sail anytime.
Ace is really dead, isn't he?!
You guys, are Ace and Sabo
here? Just spit it out!
Okay!
I won't say it!!
Well, we're gonna get going.
I-I don't know...
Right. Let's meet again somewhere.
Next time, I'll treat you to
my life's Full Course Meal.
Terrible liars!
Yes, he is dead!
Boss! Boss! Ace and the other two are back!
Sure! I look forward to it, Toriko!
Fine. Enough.
See ya, Luffy!
Bye!
So long!
Hey grandpa, who is Ace?
A cheerful goodbye is a nice thing, but...
Oh, he is...
Who the heck are they?
Now, Luffy had been chasing Ace for 3
months with cuts and bruises all over...
...the guy who will become your brother!
Ace's close friend Sabo
started to live with them
Okay, now that we've got food supplies,
we're leaving these waters!
after being forced to
leave the Gray Terminal.
Luffy! I'll see you at the
top of the pirates' world!
Then you die.
That's all pudding!
Ace, Sabo, Luffy.
No, no! Pudding is a very
variable good that tastes like
Come to the top!
It's the end of the forest.
sea urchin if you put soy sauce on it...
These three soon began spending their time
If you want sea urchin, get it from the sea!
fighting with wild animals in
the mountain and in the jungle
and with hooligans from the
city and pirates at the cove.
Well, Komatsu, ready to get going, too?
In the end, the people at
the center of the kingdom
On our journey to find new ingredients!
came to know their wrongdoing!
Ace!!
Yes, Toriko-san!
Don't!
What is this place?
Next week is a special
collaboration with Toriko!
Discarded junk lies around everywhere,
and smoke fills the air.
Ace and Sabo raid Porchemy's hideout to save the captured Luffy.
His heart deeply wounded after losing Ace,
The names of Luffy, Ace, and Sabo
Those Barbecue Pigs are scary!
gradually gain fame among
the thugs in the town.
This is Gray Terminal, a town of outlaws.
Luffy remembers his life ten years ago.
Whew, I'm stuffed! That was tasty!
Despite the overwhelming strength of the pirates,
Then, one day, the three
of them meet a certain boy.
Apparently there are lots
more of these things!
Ace, who wouldn't accept anyone,
and Luffy, who followed him everywhere.
Ace once took charge of the thugs here,
Sabo finds a moment's opportunity to free Luffy and makes a run for it,
Really?!
That's what Toriko said! I wanna go home!
amassing funds in order to
become a pirate someday.
That meeting would change
their destinies in a big way!
The story of the strange bond that
led them to become brothers begins...
when Ace shares a surprising resolution...
Okay! We're going with Toriko!
Along with one other friend...
What?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
Next week, the special Toriko x
One Piece collaboration episode!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To The Sea Someday!
The Pledge of the Three Brats!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"I Won't Run! Ace's Desperate
Rescue Operation!"
"Luffy and Ace! The Story
of How the Brothers Met!"
"Here Comes Sabo! The Boy
at the Gray Terminal!"
"The Strongest Tag-Team! Luffy
and Toriko's Hard Struggle!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
Don't miss it!