ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After losing his brother Ace during
the War of the Best against the Navy,
Luffy is consumed with sorrow.
Luffy was consumed with unbearable sorrow.
Luffy made it to the Maiden Island
where he was consumed with unbearable sorrow.
Meanwhile, there is an untold story of the
brothers Luffy and Ace from 10 years ago.
where he was consumed with unbearable sorrow.
There is, however, an untold
story of the brothers...
However, 10 years ago,
There is, however, an untold
story of the brothers...
Ace, Sabo and Luffy were competing
...10 years ago in the East
Blue - Luffy and Ace as boys.
to hunt the big tiger to
decide who would be captain.
...10 years ago in the East
Blue - Luffy and Ace as boys.
"To The Sea Someday! The
Pledge of the Three Brats!"
Luffy has been left with Dadan -
the mountain bandit of Mt. Corvo
They met a former pirate
- Naguri who knew Roger,
"Freedom Taken Away! The Nobles'
Plot Closing in on the Brothers!"
and met 2 precocious kids named Ace and Sabo.
Luffy has been left with Dadan -
the mountain bandit of Mt. Corvo
and he agreed to give Luffy
tips on how to become a pirate.
Here I come!
Gum-Gum...
and met 2 precocious kids named Ace and Sabo
...Pistol!
There it is! A storm is coming!
"Leaving the Dadan Family for Good?!
The Kids' Hideout Has Been Built!"
with whom he pledged to be brothers forever.
We're ready for it! Bring it on!
Our brotherhood will always be with us!
"The Battle against the Big Tiger!
Who is Going to be Captain?!"
Now tell me...
Oh, cool! It's getting windier and windier!
What are you doing?!
So from now on,
One point!
Luffy, hold on to the flag!
How are you, Pochi?
we're brothers!
It's uncool for pirates to
have their flag blown away!
Who dug a hole at the front door?!
Alright! Come on, wild wind!
Yeah!!
I'm gonna become a pirate before
you do so just forget it.
Come on, violent storm!
It was Ace and the other
two - to catch boars.
Bring it on, you bastard!
That's not fair! I'm gonna
become a pirate first!
I won't lose a fight!
This is my house! They can't just
dig a hole wherever they want!
Why do you always do that?!
And I will...
Here it comes!
You always attack so openly!
Those brats!
I wanna get stronger!
You're still saying a crap like that?!
--Luffy!
Sabo, who gave you permission
to invade our territory?!
I'm gonna get stronger and I will...
You okay?!
Help me!
Can't you both understand that
you must become Navy soldiers?!
Your territory?! Ha! You
guys are so full of it!
Shut up! What about you?!
What are you doing, Luffy?
Stop talking nonsense and bring it on!
I win, Sabo!
"We will stand on our feet."
Stop laughing and help me!
Alright, get ready!
Ace!
This is nice!
Yeah, it's great!
Pay attention!
Dammit!
Damn! It's always a close
match between Ace and Sabo!
This is our hideout!
Cool! We survived the storm!
Dammit!
But the hideout's been destroyed.
Here they are!
You little shit!
Sabo! You gotta fight me next!
Okay, let's go and collect materials.
That was horrible!
I made a dent!
I want a telescope.
Let's put some poisonous
mushrooms in the bait tomorrow.
"Luffy Becoming an Apprentice?! A Man Who
Fought Against the King of the Pirates!"
Shouldn't you run?! I have no mercy!
You'll never find that kind
of thing there, stupid.
Oh, wait a minute.
I'd rather find a cannon.
Here comes the sheriff! Let's go!
He's big but still a member
of the cat family...
Gum-Gum...
It'd be cool if we could find one!
Seasons come and go and now it's winter.
"Gum" again?
...Shield!
That means catnip might work, huh?
Luffy, Hurry up! It's this way!
That's just stretching your fingers...
It's no good, Ace. I can't find a telescope.
Sabo! He's coming to you!
Don't let him get away!
How interesting is this?
Huh?!
Okay! I won't!
Luffy, we're not here for a telescope.
Look for building materials.
N-N-No, stop it!
It's back!
I wonder how Luffy is doing.
Yes! We drove him to the bay!
It's been a week since he left the hideout.
Maybe this is enough.
Let's get a deer for dinner!
Like I keep saying,
We should have gone to see him by now.
Yeah! I love venison! Let's go hunting!
is there any point in having that power?
It's a telescope! Luffy's gonna be so happy.
You know how he is.
Hey, wait!
Dammit! It's not working! It was so close!
Maybe the training is too hard for him
and he's crying "I wanna go home!"
Luffy! Get ready!
We're home!
Don't come home, annoying brats!
One more time!
Here he is!
Hey, boy!
That's for dinner.
No! Maybe he's dead already!
Let's go!
No! The rule is only 100
matches per person a day.
Cook it now.
I didn't know that one of
the three infamous brats
It's a mealtime!
Wait until tomorrow.
was from a noble family.
Luffy lost 50 times to me and Ace.
Bluejam! How did you know?
Me vs. Ace is 24 - 26.
Alright, guys. But don't leave a mark on him.
You can't get away!
I lost by 2. Dammit!
You guys! When I become 10 years
old, I'll beat you two up!
What?
Do you wanna fight?!
Don't you care about Luffy?
He's your younger brother!
We'll be 13 then. Let's go
get something for dinner.
Shut up! I don't care if
he's crying or he's dead!
Ace! Luffy!
--I feel dizzy...
--You okay, Sabo?
Damn! Stop being stubborn already!
Yeah!
If the three of us fight together,
we can easily beat these fools!
You must...
Okay, let's go for crocodiles!
Don't waste food!
That's right! We even beat
the big tiger of Mt. Corvo!
I love crocodile meat!
Yes! I got him!
Luffy, don't get eaten this time.
You little shits!
He's gonna eat me!
Good job, Luffy!
Let's just finish this up
by killing their captain!
We got two of them today!
You were okay the last time
because you were swallowed whole.
Ow, ow, ow...
Don't come out until you count up to 10,000!
We can have a lot of danpa soup!
W-What happened?
Okay!
I'm sorry!
You wait here, Luffy. You can't
swim so you'd slow us dow...
Yeah!
I did it! I did it! I did it!
Are you okay? Sorry!
Crocodile meat!
I made a kill for the first time! Yeah!
Hey! Stop it!
--What?!
--I said "wait"!!
Hey, look!
--Luffy!
You jerk!
Ace! Sabo! Long time no see!
Luffy, watch your back!
Back?
How've you been?!
Damn!
Uh, well, you know.
The harsh environment of Mt. Corvo
made them stronger day by day.
A big tiger!
Honestly!
GRAY TERMINAL
Why do we have to do a major
housecleaning every night after dinner?!
Alright, brats, don't move!
TIGER
He caught wind of our prey!
I'm gonna kick them out at any cost!
I'm not afraid of that!
What's that? A target?
Luffy, get away from there!
He just wants the danpa!
--Damn! Let me go!
--You bastard!
Hey, Sabo!
On the north side of this mountain,
Go away! Or I'm gonna kick your butt!
I'm gonna show you the result of my training!
Now it's clean!
Let me go, you bastard...
there is the place where all uncertain
things end up called Gray Terminal.
Here I go!
Luffy! Wait, you bastard!
Gum-Gum...
And on the north side of the Terminal,
That's my prize! I'm not gonna let you...
...Pistol!
there is a city with a solid stone
wall that doesn't let anyone enter.
B-Boss...
...h-h-have it!
He's too tough for you! Get away now!
I barely made it in time.
Oh boy...
Dad!
No! Go away, stupid!
The only entrance to the city
is called the Great Gate
We didn't harm a hair on him, mister.
Otherwise, I'm gonna beat you up!
The only time I can relax
is when I'm in my futon.
Oh no!
through which twice daily passes mountains
of junk from all over the country.
Hey!
--Damn! You...!
--Sabo!
That's awesome! You couldn't
reach that far a week ago!
--That fool!
--Luffy!
He wanted to find me so
badly that he hired pirates?
You bastard! Gum-Gum...
The last training for today!
So they are the ones who
tempted Sabo into evil.
Can you beat that?!
--Oh, here they come!
--let's go treasure hunting!
I'll win!
Oh boy...
You'll never learn!
What kind of tips did you give him?
--Here we go!
--Okay!
Give him back!
Residents of Gray Terminal visit the city
sometimes to sell recycled products.
Nothing special.
What do you mean "give him
back"? Sabo is my son.
He was just chopping wood
with an ax for me everyday.
Kids have to live as their parents say
But maybe it helped him
build up his physique.
because the parents brought
them into the world.
How dare you two tempt Sabo to run away!?
You bastard...
Let me have a seat.
Hey wait! What's in that package?
Gum-Gum...
You thug-wannabe brats!
Wait, wait, wait!
Are you after my money?!
We challenged Roger, the King
of the Pirates, to a fight!
It's a crocodile-skin. I'm here to sell it.
Let's run while he's distracted!
What did you say?!
Crocodile?
Okay!
Really?!
But we lost the fight and split up.
Hi, fairy!
I'll get even with you!
Hey, pirate! Be careful about hitting a kid!
G-Go ahead!
I've got that trashy kid's blood all over me!
Beyond the Great Gate, there is a boulevard
where all passersby can be clearly seen
I know that you hate him, too.
Ace!
and then there is Edge Town.
Ack! Hey!
Hate who?
Stop it! Nobody tempted me!
Because he beat you.
Sorry about your first prize.
You mean Roger?
I ran away of my own will!
Edge Town - where all the thugs and
gangsters from the city hang out.
Damn!
Leave him alone. We had no
chance against that tiger.
You stay out of this! Hey.
--Luffy, are you alive?
--What a crappy floor.
I felt frustrated for sure.
But that was my prize!
He can't just steal it!
I'll leave the rest up to you, pirates.
You bastard!
But I lost because I wasn't strong enough.
Hey!
Of course, mister. You've
already paid us for this.
Y-Y-You fool! Don't shake it!
I rather feel grateful to him now.
Hey, pops! Leave your package here!
We will take care of these two so
they won't bother your boy again.
Should we go to sleep?
Yeah.
To someone who beat you?!
That's right.
We gotta kick the brats out!
Hey, why don't you say something?!
--You little...!
--Stop, Luffy!
Wait a minute, Bluejam!
Dad, that's enough! I understand!
If nothing is done, they're gonna
take over the Dadan family!
Shut up, you punk.
What?!
First of all, it's ruining my health!
We give up! You win!
What do you understand?
Easy, easy, boss.
Go ahead and cut my head off! But...
Y-You little...
Don't do it, Sabo!
They got control over us long ago!
When you mug somebody,
I'll do as you say. I'll
live as you want so...
Please spare my crew in exchange for my head!
Shut up! It's just I can't
look after them anymore!
be careful who you pick!
Yes, I'm gonna kick them out!
...please don't hurt these two!
Th-They are the...
Captain!
Forget about the agreement with Garp!
Let's do this!
Have mercy!
I'm begging you.
--Okay!
Hey!
Sabo! Pull us up now!
Garp?
They're very important to
me,  they're my brothers.
I-I got it!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry! I don't
know what made me say it!
Sabo...
Sorry!
Then go home right now.
He was a man of quite high caliber!
We're home finally! Let's just
go to bed on such a bad day
Excuse me. I heard that Luffy is here.
You should stop playing pirate.
It's just a waste of time.
That's why I...
Go to bed on a bad day?
Don't lie! There are dozens
of people who hate him!
Hey! Don't go!
Oh, I'm starving!
In the middle of the walled city,
there is another high stone wall
--It's your fault!
--Ouch!
Be quiet!
Makino!
Sabo, run! You don't have to worry about us!
Luffy!
But if someone steals the prize you
caught by yourself for the first time,
which encloses High Town where
royalty and nobles live.
You look great!
Do they really fight with Roger?
It's been 6 months so we came
here to see how you're doing.
You said you wanna live freely with us!
I can see why someone would get angry.
Hey, mayor!
Sabo, don't go!
In the world of pirates, when you
lose a fight, you lose your life.
Don't tell Garp-san.
--But it's reckless to fight such a big tiger...
--That's something you would do!
Are you gonna put an end to your dream?!
So you're really living with the bandits...
The name of this country is the Goa Kingdom.
But I'm alive.
Sabo!
Humph! Shut up!
You got a problem?
There is no garbage on streets
Let's say that those people fought him.
and it is said
to be the most beautiful country in the East Blue.
Yes, a big one! You're a bandit
- don't give me attitude!
Sabo!
Just think. They can talk about
their grudges because they're alive!
What?! People from the
Windmill Village are all annoying?!
Windmill Village where Luffy was born...
Sabo!!
I have some presents for you!
...is the part of the kingdom even
though it's a forgotten backwater.
I'll get stronger and...
I assume that Garp-san wouldn't
think about these things...
Then what if Roger had a son?!
Here it is! New clothes!
Captain! What should we do with these kids?
Oh, great!
DOWNTOWN
I'm glad that you like them.
It must be hard to be his son.
--Take them to our hideout.
--Yes, sir.
I'll adjust the length
so... I need you guys, too.
I'm glad they paid so much for the skin!
Whether he chooses to live a
normal life or as a pirate,
You bastard! Untie me!
We got more for the "pirate savings"!
It's great to have brothers!
If they come aboard my ship...
Okay?
Fight me again! I'm not gonna lose this time!
I'm hungry!
he will always be haunted
by his father's name.
Oh, hey!
You, too.
Just a little longer. We'll
have great ramen noodles!
Be quiet!
It must be quite hard.
Why did you bring us here?!
If I were his son, I wouldn't
want to become a pirate.
What is ramen? Is it really good?
It must be nice to be a noble,
don't you think so, brats?
Captain, you keep out of this!
I heard that Ace-kun was mischievous
Leave it to us!
but you seem like a good boy.
Whatever's fine! I wanna eat soon!
Because that father's name would
ruin his son's life in the end.
No, I'll fight too because I'm a captain!
They look down on others as if they're
trash and boss everyone around.
N-No, I'm not...
FINE DINING EIICHIRO
It's such an easy life.
--He's so shy!
--You're blushing, Ace!
"Ruin his son's life"?!
Stop talking nonsense!
You don't know anything!
Don't you think it's nice?
--You jerks!
--Oh hey, you can't move!
This is the restaurant!
What are you getting at?!
Why are you laughing?
I'll show you later.
Why don't you fight me, old man?!
Hi, may I help you?
Being a pirate is way better!
That's what Sabo said!
That's not gonna make your stomach full.
W-W-Wait a minute!
I made up my mind!
Ace!
I'm feeling bad for you
guys. Hey, untie them.
What are you doing?! People
like you are not allowed here!
Ace! Sabo! You guys gotta come
aboard my ship! Okay? Say yes!
Like I said, when you lose a
fight, you lose your life...
I hope you like it!
Yes, sir.
That's so sudden!
Why do you think a kid from a noble family
I'm not gonna lose!
The VIP room will do.
We decided to leave it to the future.
Yummy!
Th-That mark is...!
escaped to a place like Gray Terminal?
But it'd be fun to be with each other
We're so honored to have a noble
like you come to our restaurant!
Meals should be good on the ship.
He did it as a mockery of the people
here just like noble adults do.
and you'll need my help, won't you?
We'll prepare a room right away!
I'm gonna get the best cook first
thing when I go out to sea!
You're the one who needs help, aren't you?
I bet he was looking down on you guys, too.
I'm gonna become a pirate before
you do so just forget it.
Yeah.
That thing is pretty handy!
No!
That's not true! Sabo wouldn't do that!
I'm gonna help you!
That's not fair! I'm gonna
become a pirate first!
Yeah, I found it on the street a while ago.
You guys are welcome to come aboard my ship.
He's right! We're brothers!
I win!
Yeah? Alright, I'm sorry.
--No, my ship!
Dammit! Do anything you like with me!
Then, this is not gonna work.
But you're not gonna bother
that brat, are you?
Then, I want you to come with me.
You're still saying a crap like that?!
--Are you sure about it?
--Yeah.
Here are 3 ramen noodle bowls!
Thank you for waiting!
Sabo?
Huh?
If you're planning on doing that,
I'm not gonna work for anyone. Forget it.
Enjoy your meal!
Can't you both understand that
you must become Navy soldiers?!
I'd
have to kill both of you right here.
This is ramen?!
If you think of him as your brother,
it's best to leave him alone.
Come on! It's gonna be fun!
It looks good!
It's this way!
--Dadan!
--Yes, Garp-san...
Oh yeah! How about this?
Well, try it.
For Sabo's good?
I didn't know that there was a cove.
The one who beats the big
tiger can be the captain!
Why should I get hit, too?
Yum-yum!
But Sabo hates the High Town!
You're not educating the brats well!
The big tiger? Are you serious?
Guys! Hurry up and get over here!
You have to let go of him if
you really care about him.
Yeah, it is good!
He's Garp? He's Ace and Luffy's grandfather?
The chances of you becoming
a captain are pretty low.
Guys! Guys! Hustle, hustle!
You'll understand when you get older. And...
Squirt, you mentioned about
going out to sea, too...
I want more!
That's not true! None of us
can compete against him now!
I had an axe to grind with you
about what you did to Porchemy
What do you want, Luffy?
He's not a "Squirt" - he's Sabo!
I need more. 3 more ramen noodles!
We exchanged a cup of sake and
pledged to become pirates!
Don't be shocked!
--Good idea!
but we can forget about it. I rather
liked your show of strength.
Yes, sir! Here they are!
Yeah! Let's do it!
More please!
--Alright!
That's a...
He has such a big mouth...
That's why I wanted to ask you something.
I think you might be interested.
Y-Yes, sir!
Oh, that means now there are 3 fools
...boat?!
More!
Y-Yes, sir! Right away!
I'm short-handed now.
Do you guys wanna work for me?
who want me to give them a real workout!
Isn't it cool?! It's a real pirate ship!
Are you ready?
Next!
A pirate ship?! Is this what
Naguri has been making?!
Yeah!
Well, it's an easy task.
It's not dangerous at all.
You can't get away!
We went through so much to
catch these. What a waste!
Oh boy...
It will take forever to make it on my own.
Don't complain. We caught
these to use them as bait.
There is a map of Gray Terminal.
You must be happy, Luffy.
You have 2 older brothers now.
Could you two give me a hand?
May I come in?
And you just have to carry packages
to the locations marked on the map.
--Huh?
--Give you a hand?
Wait!
Do you wanna do it?
Oh? There he comes!
You said that I can do
anything I like with you!
Alright.
Take this!
What a greedy bastard!
He can't have them today!
Chest!
How much will you pay?
Here, here, here!
M-Manager!
W-W-Wait a minute! I have to help, too?!
This old man is like a monster!
Are you sure?!
You happened to be here, so.
Ace, I don't like it when Sabo is not around.
Sir, we need to talk!
You're not making any sense!
--Damn, they found out!
--Let's go!
He's here!
We're busy hunting the big tiger!
Live with it. I don't like it,
either. I wanna rescue Sabo.
That's it for today! I'm
gonna be harsher tomorrow!
They didn't pay!
I can give you some pointers
to hunt the tiger.
Catch them, somebody!
Is that the tiger?
You can't drop dead yet!
But I don't know what is really best for him.
What?! Well, then maybe...
--The ramen noodles were great!
--I told you!
Let's see how things go. He's fine.
What?! It's a bear!
--Catch them?!
--They're only kids!
Let me ask you a question.
What are you gonna do with the ship?
That's not what we expected!
Go away! Shoo! Shoo!
If he can't take it there,
he can just come back.
I-It's them again! They're such
pests! Why were they let in?!
Let's make some money for the
pirate savings for that occasion.
I'm gonna go out to sea, of course.
Wait, it seems like he's
as strong as the tiger.
If nothing is done, the old
man will kill us tomorrow.
To find my crew that got split up.
We can't beat the tiger if we can't beat him.
Don't let them run away!
Somebody catch those 3 kids!
I can't say it. It's not
Ace and Luffy's fault.
Even if we survive,
To sea?
What? An old man can't go out to sea?
I see! So he's perfect for practice.
he'll keep doing it until
we give up our dream!
Why can't you tell the truth?!
I don't wanna die!
No, I wasn't gonna say that, but...
I can't believe that they
jumped out of the window!
Is it because they warned
you not to say anything?
--I go first!
--That's not fair!
We only have one choice.
This is the 4th floor!
It doesn't matter how old
you are to chase a dream!
It's time to make up our minds, brothers!
That's cheating!
They're not those kinds of people!
We lost 26 bowls of ramen
noodles and a window!
I don't care what anyone says,
I'm gonna go out to sea!
If you have a criminal record, it
damages your family's reputation
I've already decided!
M-Manager! They left a note!
and you can't enter High Town.
Do you have a problem with that?
You were tempted by those two,
Nope!
TREASURE TAB - LUFFY
having no choice but to
get involved in violence,
You're an old man, full of energy.
"Treasure tab"?!
"We will stand on our feet."
Ace?
weren't you, Sabo?
A promise is a promise. I'll
give you a hand. And...
Sabo.
Sabo?
The fate of your friends in the Gray Terminal
That must be Sabo! Wait!
...I will defeat you tomorrow!
is in the hands of those pirates.
You're alive!
What should we do about this?
And I can give them an order.
What was that?
Let's go home!
How smart-alecky of them.
If they're that important to you,
How could you not care?! They're
infamous even downtown!
Hey, Sabo! He's calling you!
Oh no! He's not cooling off!
think about what you have to do.
Who is that?
He confused me with someone else. Let's go!
Anyone will try to kill them on sight
if they aren't sheltered by us!
And so began their training
to be pirates with Naguri.
You're a smart boy.
You know what you should do.
He's gonna kill us!
W-Wait!
My vacation is over!
Through hard labor on the ship,
You promised that you wouldn't hurt them!
You gotta shape them into full-fledged
Navy men by the time I come back!
they gained strength and honed their
skills by fighting with Naguri...
That's why I came back here!
--Are you gonna leave everything to me again?!
--Huh?
A crime is a crime! We did
it of our own free will...
Take care!
...growing both physically and mentally.
Sabo...
Take care!
Seasons come and go but spring
comes late in the Gray Terminal.
Honestly!
It's so sad to have such a stupid son!
How can a bandit raise a Navy soldier?!
W-Who is it?!
Can't you understand my dilemma?
That geezer doesn't know what he's saying!
Oh, it must be so hard.
Easy, easy, boss.
So you are worrying about
those kids after all.
I'll take care of the papers.
--I'm gonna win today!
--I'm not gonna lose!
He better run - that old man!
Who cares?! Come to think
of it, this is good for us.
That's Naguri from Gray Terminal!
I'm gonna win!
Run! He's coming to you!
They left voluntarily! Oh, I'm glad!
What?! I'm not hiding anything!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Oh, you aren't?
We got away successfully!
Yes, you are! Tell us, Sabo!
What're you doing, old man?!
Oh no!
They're not coming - Dadan and the others.
Welcome back, sir.
We can't have secrets among us!
Hey, Luffy! You did it again!
It's true that  "the devil's
children have the devil's luck"!
Okay, Sabo, let's go. It's been
a long while since you left.
--Tell us!
Sorry!
Boy, you guys are only thinking
about getting stronger but...
He's the devil's son!
Oh, don't go in yet - you're filthy.
I said that I'm not hiding...
I can tell that she feels happy now
because her troubles have gone away!
Wash and disinfect your
body in the yard first.
Tell us, you bastard! Or I'll beat you up!
...you think that's enough?
Then take a bath.
I'm glad that you're safe, young master.
What do you mean?
Alright, I'll tell you!
The strongest one among
us will become captain.
Oh no! It's pouring!
Oh, Sabo! You're back. You got bigger.
So what do you think about that?
The son of a noble?!
That's right! The one that kill the tiger!
You know that you don't belong here!
Mom.
Now Stelly, say "hi" to your older brother.
The tiger, huh?
--Who is it?
Well, a captain needs to be
strong - that's for sure.
I am!
Nice to meet you, brother!
My name is Stelly and I'm 8.
Go back to the forest now!
--And?
You two asked me first!
Let's stay here and hide from the rain.
But there is more important thing.
Who is he?
We adopted him. He's a smart
boy from a noble family.
This is exciting!
A more important thing?
The truth is, both of my parents are alive.
Yes, and that is...
But for some reason, his
parents became negligent.
So I'm not an orphan and I didn't
grow up in the Gray Terminal.
I've changed my mind. I don't
wanna get beaten by Garp
And we took him in since
he's full of promise.
I forgot!
The man who called to me today was...
Go and look for the stupid brats already!
Cool!
If you don't work out to be my successor...
Yes, ma'am!
...my father.
What was that? How disappointing!
I was lying to you guys. I'm sorry.
No, I'm telling you too much.
Easy, easy!
It's like that time before!
Go to your room now.
He said "sorry" so we gotta forgive him.
You have to start studying tomorrow.
Let's hold off on forgiveness -
it all depends on your motive.
Why were you living there if
you are from a noble family?
Are you gonna put an end to your dream?!
The reason I ran away was...
What?! You were a pirate
and a captain, Naguri?!
Hey, brother! I heard that
you're pretty stupid.
Listen, Sabo.
Mother and father were always
saying that behind the curtain.
Yes, indeed.
You must acquire intelligence and
knowledge that you'll need as a noble
I knew it! Only a pirate
captain could do that!
But you have the devil's luck
'cuz they're gonna take care of
the burnables tomorrow night.
and become a man that can marry
a woman from the royal family.
"That"?
If you had stayed in the Gray Terminal,
Then, we will live in security and
I'm sure that you will live happily!
You made the big bear turn away
just by staring at him like Shanks!
you would've died tomorrow.
Oh, I didn't know that
you were here, Ace-kun.
You're cool, old man!
Are you sure that if I could marry
a royal woman, I'll live happily?
Well, it would've been better for me
You think so?
if their real son didn't come home...
I can't believe that Naguri
was a pirate because...
What's wrong?
I'm sure!
W-W-What are you doing?! I'll tell father!
Guys!
What does it take to be a captain?
Yes, Sabo!
Ace! Sabo!
What is more important than being strong?
Okay!
What were you talking about?!
He's always collecting junk, hammering
away at them all day long,
Luffy!
I'll do it!
Look at this!
What's going on? Tell me everything!
Tell me!
What is it?
What?!
I designed our hideout. We can't
sleep outdoors forever, right?
Th-There's gonna be a fire in
the Gray Terminal tomorrow.
The cargo ship has sunk?!
making weird stuff,
Alright.
I don't give a damn about the crew!
and getting teased by the people
So we gotta build a hideout right here!
That is...
--A fire?!
--Yeah.
What are you gonna do about the
cargo that I paid for? Huh?
at the Gray Terminal and by Bluejam's crew.
You don't know about
it because you weren't here.
To tell you the truth, I don't know it yet.
A hideout... That's cool!
But they decided it months ago.
He looked pathetic.
Hello?! Hello?!
I wasn't a good captain.
What about materials?
--Clank.
--Damn!
You know nothing, Sabo!
That's how pirates are!
Did you know that the World Government
We've got tons you-know-where.
Such a great loss! By thunder!
has sent a group of observers
to go around the East Blue?
But my crew,
You don't know anything, either!
What do you know about pirates?!
They're gonna arrive in Goa
Kingdom finally 3 days from now!
they called me "Captain"
until the last minute.
Dad!
DAD
I know pirates! Shanks doesn't
do needless killings!
Look at this! I drew it!
And they have a World Noble,
Because of that, I'm still the
captain of the Naguri Pirates.
a Celestial Dragon with them
so people are panicking!
Shanks, again.
Hey, it's cooked.
The members of the royal family
don't want him to see our stigma,
--Ow, ow, ow...!
--Ouch!
Only your crew's approval
can make you a captain!
I'm exhausted from work, Sabo.
Oh, you got more than me!
so they decided to burn
down the Gray Terminal.
You got to pay attention.
If you have time to draw this,
you ought to be studying instead.
Or something like that...
Then this country will be clean!
That's corny.
Have some, Naguri. You helped us.
What are you talking
about? That's impossible!
Oh, thank you.
So, what is a pirate captain
doing in a place like this?
There are a lot of people living there!
Hey, you!
They can't take away their home!
I'm from the royal family!
Which means I'm related to the king!
Let go of me!
Weren't you listening to me?
How could you ask me that?
Yeah! It's done!
Carry me by piggyback to my house!
You don't have to answer
if you don't want to.
They're gonna burn up all
the shame of this country.
No, I'll tell you.
We did it, Naguri!
Cool! It's awesome!
Do you guys know Gold Roger?
You mean, the people, too?
Stop, you rude jerk!
I couldn't have done it
without your help. Thank you!
Hey, are you gonna ignore my royal order?!
Roger?
I know him! He was the King of the Pirates!
I'm really grateful!
Let me go!
H-Hey!
We challenged Roger, the King
of the Pirates, to a fight!
Say, Naguri, are you setting sail soon?
Where are you going?
Really?!
Yes. But before that, I have
to wrap up your training.
But we lost the fight and split up.
You're just the son of some noble family!
You can't just jump down...
I'll teach you a lesson!
Let's go and hunt the big tiger today!
And everything just went downhill after that
Don't!
I-It is not my fault.
Really?!
and I ended up like this.
I'm gonna kill him and
end this stupid training!
It's a lie! He must be lying!
That's basically what happened.
It's not possible to burn
down an area so large!
It's unforgivable to harm a
child of the royal family!
I'm gonna kill him!
But you fought with the King of
the Pirates, right? That's cool!
Don't forget about me!
Sabo! Did you really have a fight
with this royal boy?!
No, no, we were no match for him.
They were from this afternoon...
Yes, I did!
We got beaten badly.
Are we ready for tomorrow?
There can't be any miscalculation.
Because he attacked me with
a knife all of a sudden...
We're ready but the unknown
factor is the pirates.
Oh really? Even you were no
match - that's how much he...
Here he comes!
They have to burn the trash precisely.
I'm sorry! Did you get hurt?!
Yes. And not just Roger, his
crew was also very strong!
Bluejam's clan is setting
boxes of oil and explosives...
There he is!
I'm so sorry!
...all over the Gray Terminal up
until the appointed time tomorrow.
Most importantly, their teamwork
was in perfect coordination!
Let's take him to a doctor
to get checked out!
I go first!
Bluejam has a hand in this?
Then it must be true!
Can we please settle this matter peacefully?!
Awesome! Looks exactly like the design!
It was our honor to fight with them.
But it's so ridiculous!
Great work if I say so myself!
They love those who can maintain their
status and defend their property.
How predictable!
What's wrong, Ace?
This is a hideout so we
gotta set up some traps!
I see! I still have a long
way to go to become a pirate.
Okay, I'll think about it!
Not me!
How's that?!
Are you interested in pirates?
I wonder how's Sabo doing.
--I'm gonna become one!
--Become a pirate?
Shut up and go to sleep.
Yeah!
If I can't marry a woman from
the royal family, I'm worthless!
We have a view of the Gray Terminal,
Yes, a pirate! Oh yeah, old pirate
man, could you give me some tips?!
We agreed to let go of Sabo for now.
the Windmill Village and
the water of the East Blue!
That's why they made me study
and take culture lessons.
It's not so uncommon, is it?
Alright.
You're unguarded!
You gotta fight me now!
And they were arguing everyday
because I wasn't doing well.
This could be better for him.
It's nice to see them from here!
I want to get stronger!
Stop resisting, just give up!
I have to become a captain
to lead Ace and Sabo!
Sabo...
I had no place to be in that family!
A captain?
Luffy!
I'm sorry for both of you but I was
all by myself even if I had parents!
Hey, say yes! You're a pirate master!
Telescope...
--Okay!
--Okay?!
Sabo! Ace!
I heard that you sneak out
and go somewhere sometimes.
Yeah! Then, let's start from tomorrow!
You're right! It's different!
I don't think you do but do you
ever go to the Gray Terminal!
Where did Ace go?!
Yeah, about that...
D-D-Dammit!
We nobles are privileged to live
Gum-Gum Pistol!
What?!
in the High Town with
the king and his family.
The King of the Pirates is his father?!
Those residents there and we nobles
are living in different worlds!
Luffy, there's a tailwind! Set the sails!
Yeah. But you can't tell anybody.
Okay!
Don't mention it to Ace. He's gonna kill you.
I can figure out if there'll be a fire or not
Oh no! Luffy!
Why?
Advance to the treasure!
by the look of people in the town.
Run!
I don't know why but he
doesn't like Roger for sure.
An enemy off the bow and starboard side!
It's Bluejam's ship! Prepare for action!
But that's his father, right?
--Hi, good morning!
--Good morning!
So what?
They've started shooting!
Take evasive action!
It's you again.
--Isn't it a lovely morning.
--Yes, it is.
If you walk around a place like this,
I'm sorry for both of you but I was
all by myself even if I had parents!
Luffy, hard aport!
you might get robbed and killed someday!
Oh great! There is nothing wrong!
Ace! Sabo!
Yeah, I got it!
So heavy! How powerful he is!
Oh yeah. Your parents...
I'll walk around the town.
No! You have to say "steady"
at times like this!
Let me hear the stories again!
Tomorrow morning should be
more lovely, shouldn't it?
Children don't always get
along with their parents.
About countries across the sea
Damn! We're not good enough!
Oh, that's right.
that you guys have seen or visited!
But, what a shame! He's
the King of the Pirates!
Luffy, hard aport!
Yes, it should.
Only your crew's approval
can make you a captain!
Hard aport! Steady!
I can understand that you
wanna ask him about Roger
--You're a strange kid!
--Come and sit down.
But we can't lose!
but just don't, okay?
Everything seems normal as usual.
Uh-huh!
Let's fight hand-to-hand! Lay aboard!
Guys, give me a hand!
Uh-huh! I got it!
And... you too, Naguri.
Nobles have a low opinion
of the Gray Terminal
Oh, it's getting interesting.
Today is windy.
Wait for them to come aboard!
Okay, I got it.
Yes, indeed, your Majesty.
I got it!
but it's better than the stifling High Town
Don't cry, Luffy!
But I can't believe that
that boy is Roger's son...
Accidents could easily happen on a
day like this - especially fires.
Okay!
where your life has been
arranged for years to come!
We're not fast enough but we
can do it with Luffy's power!
There he is. Hey, just act casually.
You're right, your Majesty.
I see.
Sabo, do it!
Ace! Luffy!
Okay! Hey, tiger! Look over here!
Sabo is not in the house?!
Yeah.
--Don't mention...
--I know! Don't worry!
We gotta set out to sea someday!
He's such a spoiled brat!
Kiss my ass!
We won!
He still wants to keep playing
pirate without studying?!
Let's get out of this
country and live freely!
Yeah!
Oh, Ace! I didn't know that you were home!
That'll teach you!
I wanna see the world out there
and write a book about it!
Search the whole town!
--Luffy!
--Okay!
Oh, Ace! I didn't know that
your father was Roger!
He can't have gotten out
of the town so easily!
I'm happy to study if it's about sailing!
This is nice!
Pull it as much as you can!
Yeah, it's great!
I knew he'd say it!
Sabo, this way!
--Excuse me, mister.
--What do you want?
Let's become stronger and
become pirates someday!
I can't! He's gonna eat me!
You idiot, Luffy! I told
you to not to mention it!
This is our hideout!
Do you know that there'll be a
fire in the Gray Terminal tonight?
You can do it, Sabo!
Lure him as far as you can!
Here they are!
--Luffy!
--Yeah!
Of course, I know. What about it?
--Can't you find them yet?!
--I'm sorry!
Who told you that?
I'm gonna become one - you
don't have to tell me to!
We talked to people who saw them at
the Gray Terminal or in the jungle
He knows?
I'm gonna become a pirate and
defeat others and become infamous!
Sabo told me!
Which family are you from?
Are you ready, Luffy?!
Hey Ace, what was Roger like?!
but we couldn't find them!
So it's true!
Yeah!
It's been 2 weeks!
No!
How stupid are you? Don't
just say it casually!
It'll be the only proof of my life!
Gum-Gum...
Hey, kid!
Maybe they were eaten by the
big tiger in the jungle!
What's going on here?
Everybody knows about it?
Let me go! I am acting casually.
...Rocket!
It doesn't matter if all the people
in the world reject me or despise me,
--Boss!
--W-We found them!
--Ouch!
They all know about it and
they're acting normally?!
Really?!
Doesn't anyone care about the
fire in the Gray Terminal?!
Don't you ever mention
that name when I'm around!
They built a hideout in the
huge tree deep in the jungle!
I'll become a great pirate
and show them what I can do!
We can take you there!
I won't run from anybody or lose to anyone!
Why did you hit me?!
Don't be mean - just tell me!
I see!
Oh, there you are, you brats.
--I'm happy for you, boss!
--You were worrying so much!
Because I'm feared or hated or whatever,
Give people a chance to explain first!
Do you want us to carry the boxes?
my name will be known all over!
Shut up!
Yeah, and there will be a
big task for you tonight.
Oh crap! Are they still alive?
I got it! Alright then...!
I'll tell you later.
Tell us about him! You're so mean!
I can't believe that those
brats are so tenacious!
Yeah!!
He's right! You can't have
a secret from your brothers!
So, Ace is gonna be our captain after all?!
W-What?
I'm gonna become...!
Don't just stand around, guys!
Go get something for dinner!
Shut up! I don't care about my brothers!
Dad knows about it, too.
Roger, Roger, Roger! Ace's father
is the King of the Pirates!
I worked so hard for this!
That's why he brought me
back - before the fire.
Yes, ma'am!
Shut up! Don't provoke him!
Give it up, Luffy.
Because he wants me to maintain their status
You fool... I was wondering
what you'd have to say...
and inherit their property even
though he thinks I'm a fool!
Damn!
When you get down to it, it's
your fault for being a bigmouth!
Don't worry. I'm not gonna become captain.
Ouch! What did you say?!
You're funny, Luffy!
What are you doing?!
Why?
Oh, sorry if my dog is bothering you.
I can't wait to see how you
turn out in the future!
Because I didn't beat
the tiger all by myself.
You're out of breath. What's the matter, boy?
We can all become pirates
Ace... Sabo... Wait for me...
Ace!
It's nothing.
We're no longer brothers from today!
Well, I mean,
Yeah? Okay.
but isn't it a problem that
we all wanna become captain?
I'm gonna make you guys
beg me to become captain sometime soon!
When they're sleeping, they
look like ordinary kids.
--That's what I was gonna say!
D-Do you know that there'll be a
fire in the Gray Terminal tonight?
I wasn't expecting that.
Sabo, I thought that you'd wanna
be navigator on my ship.
Are you gonna beg him?
Oh no, don't catch cold.
Hell no!
Yes, I know.
You fools!
You guys can come aboard my ship!
Why doesn't anyone in this town
including you look concerned?
Alright, I'm counting on you.
--No thanks!
Huh?! Come on!
Looks like everything
turned out for the best.
Yes, I'll leave no stone unturned.
Why does no one try to prevent it?
Come aboard! I said "come
aboard", so you gotta do it!
Alright then...
--That will never happen!
--Yeah, never!
You sound like you're a kind boy.
You know what you should do.
Old man!
We'll get to it!
Next time I see you, I'm gonna defeat you!
What did you say?!
Yeah, but if you find him,
don't do anything yet.
But, listen carefully.
But that's okay.
Keep winning until then!
What's that?!
We all have to keep quiet about the plan!
What?
Can't you see? We have to make
his father feel indebted to us.
Man, you're funny, Luffy!
Goodbye!
What if someone outside the
town finds out about it?
Take care!
The longer he worries, the more he'll
appreciate us when we find Sabo.
I'll be waiting for you out there.
We're special! If you're
from a noble family...
Well, let's just leave
it until the time comes.
I see.
Maybe we'll set out independently.
Until the time comes, don't do
anything - just monitor him.
Hey, you!
Ace! Luffy!
Oh, you stole that from Dadan!
"We will have a visit this spring"?
There's something wrong
with this town! Everybody's crazy!
Did you guys know?!
Dogra! Magra! Where is
the country called Goa?!
Even though they know that
people will die soon,
We can become brothers if we
exchange this cup of sake!
they act normally and even smile!
Mt. Corvo, Gray Terminal,
and Windmill Village
I don't wanna stay here!
I gotta tell them quickly!
Brothers? Really?!
Thus, they said goodbye to Naguri
A trap just went off!
When we become pirates, we
might not be on the same ship
are part of Goa Kingdom supposedly.
and Luffy and the other two
returned to life on their own.
That's what I thought.
Someone tried to invade already?!
Today of all days, it's windy!
Easy, easy, boss.
but our brotherhood will always be with us!
Oh? Maybe it was just a glitch.
It's rare to see you reading a
newspaper. Hell must be freezing over.
There he is! Isn't it him?!
Wherever, whatever, we'll
always be bonded together!
Well, we made it in hurry so it could happen.
There's no doubt! That's the runaway boy!
Ouch!
Hey you, stop!
Hey, you know where he is, don't you?
Somebody's gonna visit the Kingdom?!
So from now on,
Ace...
The people in this country
are planning to burn up
Ouch...
It's making the headlines...
Yes. You don't have to worry.
we're brothers!
their national shame tonight!
Damn!
I'll never worry about them again!!
It's about time now.
What's going on here?
Are they that big a deal?
You have to get out of the
Gray Terminal! Ace! Luffy!
A CELESTIAL DRAGON WILL VISIT
Call and tell his father that we found...
These Celestial Dragons?
Run! Ace! Luffy!
Yeah!!
...Sabo.
Sabo makes a difficult
decision in order to save
When the boys are attacked by a huge
bear, a certain old man saves them.
Dreaming of the day when they'll
take to the seas as pirates,
Curious after Luffy is taken in as an
apprentice, Ace and Sabo visit Naguri again.
After learning the secret
behind the fire outbreak,
Ace and Luffy, who are being held hostage.
Luffy and his friends polish
up their bad-boy skills.
Luffy and Ace are pushed into
dire straits by Bluejam.
But Sabo is overwhelmed by the suffocating
The man tells them
Seeing that the boys only care about
getting strong enough to beat a tiger,
Then, when an attack by a certain character
threatens their peaceful lives,
Sabo rushes into Gray Terminal to save them,
that he once fought Gold Roger.
lifestyle in High Town.
Naguri tells them that they can't become
pirate captains just by being strong.
Luffy is thrilled to hear a story
the three boys are forced to say
goodbye to the Dadan family.
Then, as if to deal the final blow,
yet another scheme is revealed...
but the intensely burning flames
What does it really take
to be a pirate captain?!
about the Pirate King that
he's never heard before!
are about to devour Luffy and Ace!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Leaving the Dadan Family for Good?!
The Kids' Hideout Has Been Built!"
"The Battle against the Big Tiger!
Who is Going to be Captain?!"
"Freedom Taken Away! The Nobles'
Plot Closing in on the Brothers!"
"Luffy Becoming an Apprentice?! A Man Who
Fought Against the King of the Pirates!"
"The Fire Has Been Set!
The Gray Terminal in Crisis!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!