ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After losing his brother Ace during
the War of the Best against the Navy,
Luffy was consumed with unbearable sorrow.
However, 10 years ago,
Ace, Sabo and Luffy were competing
to hunt the big tiger to
decide who would be captain.
They met a former pirate
- Naguri who knew Roger,
and he agreed to give Luffy
tips on how to become a pirate.
"The Battle against the Big Tiger!
Who is Going to be Captain?!"
Why do you always do that?!
You always attack so openly!
Shut up! What about you?!
That was horrible!
Let's put some poisonous
mushrooms in the bait tomorrow.
Oh, wait a minute.
He's big but still a member
of the cat family...
That means catnip might work, huh?
Huh?!
I wonder how Luffy is doing.
It's been a week since he left the hideout.
We should have gone to see him by now.
You know how he is.
Maybe the training is too hard for him
and he's crying "I wanna go home!"
No! Maybe he's dead already!
What?
Don't you care about Luffy?
He's your younger brother!
Shut up! I don't care if
he's crying or he's dead!
Damn! Stop being stubborn already!
You must...
Ow, ow, ow...
W-What happened?
I'm sorry!
Are you okay? Sorry!
--Luffy!
Ace! Sabo! Long time no see!
How've you been?!
Uh, well, you know.
GRAY TERMINAL
TIGER
What's that? A target?
Hey, Sabo!
I'm gonna show you the result of my training!
Here I go!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Oh no!
That's awesome! You couldn't
reach that far a week ago!
Can you beat that?!
Oh boy...
What kind of tips did you give him?
Nothing special.
He was just chopping wood
with an ax for me everyday.
But maybe it helped him
build up his physique.
Let me have a seat.
We challenged Roger, the King
of the Pirates, to a fight!
Really?!
But we lost the fight and split up.
I know that you hate him, too.
Hate who?
Because he beat you.
You mean Roger?
I felt frustrated for sure.
But I lost because I wasn't strong enough.
I rather feel grateful to him now.
To someone who beat you?!
That's right.
We give up! You win!
Go ahead and cut my head off! But...
Please spare my crew in exchange for my head!
Captain!
Have mercy!
He was a man of quite high caliber!
That's why I...
Don't lie! There are dozens
of people who hate him!
Do they really fight with Roger?
In the world of pirates, when you
lose a fight, you lose your life.
But I'm alive.
Let's say that those people fought him.
Just think. They can talk about
their grudges because they're alive!
I'll get stronger and...
Then what if Roger had a son?!
It must be hard to be his son.
Whether he chooses to live a
normal life or as a pirate,
he will always be haunted
by his father's name.
It must be quite hard.
If I were his son, I wouldn't
want to become a pirate.
Because that father's name would
ruin his son's life in the end.
"Ruin his son's life"?!
Stop talking nonsense!
You don't know anything!
Why don't you fight me, old man?!
Ace!
Like I said, when you lose a
fight, you lose your life...
I'm not gonna lose!
I win!
Dammit! Do anything you like with me!
Then, I want you to come with me.
Huh?
It's this way!
I didn't know that there was a cove.
Guys! Hurry up and get over here!
Guys! Guys! Hustle, hustle!
What do you want, Luffy?
Don't be shocked!
That's a...
...boat?!
Isn't it cool?! It's a real pirate ship!
A pirate ship?! Is this what
Naguri has been making?!
It will take forever to make it on my own.
Could you two give me a hand?
--Huh?
--Give you a hand?
You said that I can do
anything I like with you!
W-W-Wait a minute! I have to help, too?!
You happened to be here, so.
You're not making any sense!
We're busy hunting the big tiger!
I can give you some pointers
to hunt the tiger.
What?! Well, then maybe...
Let me ask you a question.
What are you gonna do with the ship?
I'm gonna go out to sea, of course.
To find my crew that got split up.
To sea?
What? An old man can't go out to sea?
No, I wasn't gonna say that, but...
It doesn't matter how old
you are to chase a dream!
I don't care what anyone says,
I'm gonna go out to sea!
I've already decided!
Do you have a problem with that?
Nope!
You're an old man, full of energy.
Ace?
A promise is a promise. I'll
give you a hand. And...
...I will defeat you tomorrow!
What was that?
And so began their training
to be pirates with Naguri.
Through hard labor on the ship,
they gained strength and honed their
skills by fighting with Naguri...
...growing both physically and mentally.
Seasons come and go but spring
comes late in the Gray Terminal.
--I'm gonna win today!
--I'm not gonna lose!
I'm gonna win!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Oh no!
Hey, Luffy! You did it again!
Sorry!
Boy, you guys are only thinking
about getting stronger but...
...you think that's enough?
What do you mean?
The strongest one among
us will become captain.
So what do you think about that?
That's right! The one that kill the tiger!
The tiger, huh?
Well, a captain needs to be
strong - that's for sure.
But there is more important thing.
A more important thing?
Yes, and that is...
I forgot!
What was that? How disappointing!
Easy, easy!
Oh, I didn't know that
you were here, Ace-kun.
What's wrong?
What does it take to be a captain?
What is more important than being strong?
Tell me!
Alright.
That is...
To tell you the truth, I don't know it yet.
I wasn't a good captain.
But my crew,
they called me "Captain"
until the last minute.
Because of that, I'm still the
captain of the Naguri Pirates.
Only your crew's approval
can make you a captain!
Or something like that...
That's corny.
Yeah! It's done!
We did it, Naguri!
Cool! It's awesome!
I couldn't have done it
without your help. Thank you!
I'm really grateful!
Say, Naguri, are you setting sail soon?
Yes. But before that, I have
to wrap up your training.
Let's go and hunt the big tiger today!
Really?!
I'm gonna kill him and
end this stupid training!
I'm gonna kill him!
Don't forget about me!
Here he comes!
There he is!
I go first!
How predictable!
How's that?!
You're unguarded!
You gotta fight me now!
Stop resisting, just give up!
Sabo! Ace!
D-D-Dammit!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Oh no! Luffy!
Run!
Ace! Sabo!
So heavy! How powerful he is!
Damn! We're not good enough!
Only your crew's approval
can make you a captain!
But we can't lose!
Guys, give me a hand!
Oh, it's getting interesting.
We're not fast enough but we
can do it with Luffy's power!
Sabo, do it!
Okay! Hey, tiger! Look over here!
Kiss my ass!
--Luffy!
--Okay!
Pull it as much as you can!
Sabo, this way!
I can't! He's gonna eat me!
You can do it, Sabo!
Lure him as far as you can!
Are you ready, Luffy?!
Yeah!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Yeah!!
So, Ace is gonna be our captain after all?!
I worked so hard for this!
Give it up, Luffy.
Damn!
Don't worry. I'm not gonna become captain.
Why?
Because I didn't beat
the tiger all by myself.
Ace!
Well, I mean,
I'm gonna make you guys
beg me to become captain sometime soon!
Are you gonna beg him?
Hell no!
You fools!
Looks like everything
turned out for the best.
Alright then...
Old man!
Next time I see you, I'm gonna defeat you!
Keep winning until then!
Goodbye!
Take care!
I'll be waiting for you out there.
Thus, they said goodbye to Naguri
and Luffy and the other two
returned to life on their own.
Hey, you know where he is, don't you?
Yes. You don't have to worry.
It's about time now.
Call and tell his father that we found...
...Sabo.
Sabo makes a difficult
decision in order to save
Ace and Luffy, who are being held hostage.
But Sabo is overwhelmed by the suffocating
lifestyle in High Town.
Then, as if to deal the final blow,
yet another scheme is revealed...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Freedom Taken Away! The Nobles'
Plot Closing in on the Brothers!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!