ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After losing his brother Ace during
the War of the Best against the Navy,
Luffy was consumed with unbearable sorrow.
There is, however, an untold
story of the brothers...
...10 years ago in the East
Blue - Luffy and Ace as boys.
"Freedom Taken Away! The Nobles'
Plot Closing in on the Brothers!"
There it is! A storm is coming!
We're ready for it! Bring it on!
Oh, cool! It's getting windier and windier!
Luffy, hold on to the flag!
It's uncool for pirates to
have their flag blown away!
Alright! Come on, wild wind!
Come on, violent storm!
Bring it on, you bastard!
Here it comes!
--Luffy!
You okay?!
Help me!
What are you doing, Luffy?
Stop laughing and help me!
Cool! We survived the storm!
But the hideout's been destroyed.
Okay, let's go and collect materials.
I want a telescope.
You'll never find that kind
of thing there, stupid.
I'd rather find a cannon.
It'd be cool if we could find one!
It's no good, Ace. I can't find a telescope.
Luffy, we're not here for a telescope.
Look for building materials.
Maybe this is enough.
It's a telescope! Luffy's gonna be so happy.
Hey, boy!
I didn't know that one of
the three infamous brats
was from a noble family.
Bluejam! How did you know?
Alright, guys. But don't leave a mark on him.
Do you wanna fight?!
Ace! Luffy!
--I feel dizzy...
--You okay, Sabo?
Yeah!
If the three of us fight together,
we can easily beat these fools!
That's right! We even beat
the big tiger of Mt. Corvo!
You little shits!
Let's just finish this up
by killing their captain!
Okay!
Damn!
Alright, brats, don't move!
I'm not afraid of that!
--Damn! Let me go!
--You bastard!
Go away! Or I'm gonna kick your butt!
Let me go, you bastard...
I barely made it in time.
Dad!
We didn't harm a hair on him, mister.
Hey!
--Damn! You...!
--Sabo!
He wanted to find me so
badly that he hired pirates?
So they are the ones who
tempted Sabo into evil.
Give him back!
What do you mean "give him
back"? Sabo is my son.
Kids have to live as their parents say
because the parents brought
them into the world.
How dare you two tempt Sabo to run away!?
You thug-wannabe brats!
Are you after my money?!
What did you say?!
Hey, pirate! Be careful about hitting a kid!
I've got that trashy kid's blood all over me!
Ace!
Ack! Hey!
Stop it! Nobody tempted me!
I ran away of my own will!
You stay out of this! Hey.
I'll leave the rest up to you, pirates.
Of course, mister. You've
already paid us for this.
We will take care of these two so
they won't bother your boy again.
Wait a minute, Bluejam!
Dad, that's enough! I understand!
What do you understand?
Don't do it, Sabo!
I'll do as you say. I'll
live as you want so...
...please don't hurt these two!
I'm begging you.
They're very important to
me,  they're my brothers.
Sabo...
Then go home right now.
You should stop playing pirate.
It's just a waste of time.
Hey! Don't go!
Be quiet!
Sabo, run! You don't have to worry about us!
You said you wanna live freely with us!
Sabo, don't go!
Are you gonna put an end to your dream?!
Sabo!
Sabo!!
Captain! What should we do with these kids?
--Take them to our hideout.
--Yes, sir.
You bastard! Untie me!
Fight me again! I'm not gonna lose this time!
Be quiet!
Why did you bring us here?!
It must be nice to be a noble,
don't you think so, brats?
They look down on others as if they're
trash and boss everyone around.
It's such an easy life.
Don't you think it's nice?
What are you getting at?!
Being a pirate is way better!
That's what Sabo said!
I'm feeling bad for you
guys. Hey, untie them.
Yes, sir.
Why do you think a kid from a noble family
escaped to a place like Gray Terminal?
He did it as a mockery of the people
here just like noble adults do.
I bet he was looking down on you guys, too.
That's not true! Sabo wouldn't do that!
He's right! We're brothers!
Yeah? Alright, I'm sorry.
But you're not gonna bother
that brat, are you?
If you're planning on doing that,
I'd
have to kill both of you right here.
If you think of him as your brother,
it's best to leave him alone.
For Sabo's good?
But Sabo hates the High Town!
You have to let go of him if
you really care about him.
You'll understand when you get older. And...
I had an axe to grind with you
about what you did to Porchemy
but we can forget about it. I rather
liked your show of strength.
That's why I wanted to ask you something.
I think you might be interested.
I'm short-handed now.
Do you guys wanna work for me?
Well, it's an easy task.
It's not dangerous at all.
There is a map of Gray Terminal.
And you just have to carry packages
to the locations marked on the map.
Do you wanna do it?
Alright.
How much will you pay?
Ace, I don't like it when Sabo is not around.
Live with it. I don't like it,
either. I wanna rescue Sabo.
But I don't know what is really best for him.
Let's see how things go. He's fine.
If he can't take it there,
he can just come back.
Let's make some money for the
pirate savings for that occasion.
I can't say it. It's not
Ace and Luffy's fault.
Why can't you tell the truth?!
Is it because they warned
you not to say anything?
They're not those kinds of people!
If you have a criminal record, it
damages your family's reputation
and you can't enter High Town.
You were tempted by those two,
having no choice but to
get involved in violence,
weren't you, Sabo?
Sabo.
The fate of your friends in the Gray Terminal
is in the hands of those pirates.
And I can give them an order.
If they're that important to you,
think about what you have to do.
You're a smart boy.
You know what you should do.
You promised that you wouldn't hurt them!
That's why I came back here!
A crime is a crime! We did
it of our own free will...
Honestly!
It's so sad to have such a stupid son!
Can't you understand my dilemma?
Oh, it must be so hard.
I'll take care of the papers.
Welcome back, sir.
Okay, Sabo, let's go. It's been
a long while since you left.
Oh, don't go in yet - you're filthy.
Wash and disinfect your
body in the yard first.
Then take a bath.
I'm glad that you're safe, young master.
Oh, Sabo! You're back. You got bigger.
Mom.
Now Stelly, say "hi" to your older brother.
Nice to meet you, brother!
My name is Stelly and I'm 8.
Who is he?
We adopted him. He's a smart
boy from a noble family.
But for some reason, his
parents became negligent.
And we took him in since
he's full of promise.
If you don't work out to be my successor...
No, I'm telling you too much.
Go to your room now.
You have to start studying tomorrow.
Are you gonna put an end to your dream?!
Hey, brother! I heard that
you're pretty stupid.
Mother and father were always
saying that behind the curtain.
But you have the devil's luck
'cuz they're gonna take care of
the burnables tomorrow night.
If you had stayed in the Gray Terminal,
you would've died tomorrow.
Well, it would've been better for me
if their real son didn't come home...
W-W-What are you doing?! I'll tell father!
What were you talking about?!
What's going on? Tell me everything!
Th-There's gonna be a fire in
the Gray Terminal tomorrow.
--A fire?!
--Yeah.
You don't know about
it because you weren't here.
But they decided it months ago.
Did you know that the World Government
has sent a group of observers
to go around the East Blue?
They're gonna arrive in Goa
Kingdom finally 3 days from now!
And they have a World Noble,
a Celestial Dragon with them
so people are panicking!
The members of the royal family
don't want him to see our stigma,
so they decided to burn
down the Gray Terminal.
Then this country will be clean!
What are you talking
about? That's impossible!
There are a lot of people living there!
They can't take away their home!
Let go of me!
Weren't you listening to me?
They're gonna burn up all
the shame of this country.
You mean, the people, too?
H-Hey!
Where are you going?
You can't just jump down...
I-It is not my fault.
It's a lie! He must be lying!
It's not possible to burn
down an area so large!
They were from this afternoon...
Are we ready for tomorrow?
There can't be any miscalculation.
We're ready but the unknown
factor is the pirates.
They have to burn the trash precisely.
Bluejam's clan is setting
boxes of oil and explosives...
...all over the Gray Terminal up
until the appointed time tomorrow.
Bluejam has a hand in this?
Then it must be true!
But it's so ridiculous!
I wonder how's Sabo doing.
Shut up and go to sleep.
We agreed to let go of Sabo for now.
Alright.
This could be better for him.
Sabo...
Luffy!
Telescope...
I can figure out if there'll be a fire or not
by the look of people in the town.
--Hi, good morning!
--Good morning!
--Isn't it a lovely morning.
--Yes, it is.
Oh great! There is nothing wrong!
I'll walk around the town.
Tomorrow morning should be
more lovely, shouldn't it?
Yes, it should.
Everything seems normal as usual.
Today is windy.
Yes, indeed, your Majesty.
Accidents could easily happen on a
day like this - especially fires.
You're right, your Majesty.
Sabo is not in the house?!
He's such a spoiled brat!
He still wants to keep playing
pirate without studying?!
Search the whole town!
He can't have gotten out
of the town so easily!
--Excuse me, mister.
--What do you want?
Do you know that there'll be a
fire in the Gray Terminal tonight?
Of course, I know. What about it?
He knows?
Which family are you from?
So it's true!
Hey, kid!
What's going on here?
Everybody knows about it?
They all know about it and
they're acting normally?!
Doesn't anyone care about the
fire in the Gray Terminal?!
Oh, there you are, you brats.
Do you want us to carry the boxes?
Yeah, and there will be a
big task for you tonight.
I'll tell you later.
Dad knows about it, too.
That's why he brought me
back - before the fire.
Because he wants me to maintain their status
and inherit their property even
though he thinks I'm a fool!
Oh, sorry if my dog is bothering you.
You're out of breath. What's the matter, boy?
It's nothing.
Yeah? Okay.
D-Do you know that there'll be a
fire in the Gray Terminal tonight?
Yes, I know.
Why doesn't anyone in this town
including you look concerned?
Why does no one try to prevent it?
You sound like you're a kind boy.
But, listen carefully.
We all have to keep quiet about the plan!
What if someone outside the
town finds out about it?
We're special! If you're
from a noble family...
Hey, you!
Ace! Luffy!
There's something wrong
with this town! Everybody's crazy!
Even though they know that
people will die soon,
they act normally and even smile!
I don't wanna stay here!
I gotta tell them quickly!
Today of all days, it's windy!
There he is! Isn't it him?!
There's no doubt! That's the runaway boy!
Hey you, stop!
The people in this country
are planning to burn up
their national shame tonight!
You have to get out of the
Gray Terminal! Ace! Luffy!
Run! Ace! Luffy!
After learning the secret
behind the fire outbreak,
Luffy and Ace are pushed into
dire straits by Bluejam.
Sabo rushes into Gray Terminal to save them,
but the intensely burning flames
are about to devour Luffy and Ace!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Fire Has Been Set!
The Gray Terminal in Crisis!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!