ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
So let's go
saa yukou
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After losing his brother Ace during
the War of the Best against the Navy,
10 years ago in the East Blue,
there were 3 boys who dreamed
of becoming pirates.
Luffy was consumed with unbearable sorrow.
First, Sabo set sail and then Ace
went out to sea 7 years later.
However, 10 years ago, in the East Blue...
There is, however, an untold
story of the brothers...
What did you do?!
...10 years ago in the East
Blue - Luffy and Ace as boys.
See you, Luffy! I'm going now!
...10 years ago in the East
Blue - Luffy and Ace as boys.
Ace!
Don't do it!!
And 3 years later,
Luffy departed
from his hometown - Windmill Village.
Sabo who became brother to Luffy and Ace...
...has been brought home by
his father, a member of the nobility.
"Take Good Care of Him! A
Letter from the Brother!"
Sabo was first and Ace was second.
"To Live Up to the Promise!
Departures of Their Own!"
"Where can freedom be found?
A Sad Departure of a Boy!"
And I'm third but I'm gonna top them!
I'll do as you say. I'll
live as you want so...
Ace is not dead!
Wait for me, Ace!
Late in the day
I'll catch up with you soon!
Easy, easy, I know. I know how you feel.
...please don't hurt these two!
And now, Luffy is...
on which the Celestial Dragon's
ship arrived at the Goa Kingdom,
But it's too risky to go to Gray Terminal now
I'm begging you. They're very important
to me, they're my brothers.
since you're wounded and
there are troops everywhere!
Dadan!
The King of the Pirates?!
at a small village somewhere
in the East Blue...
--But...!
--It was a big fire! And chances are...
Stop it, you sea cretin!
I'm...
We all have to keep quiet about the plan!
...slim but we all want to believe
that the boss and Ace are alive.
I'm too...
What if someone outside the
town finds out about it?
Let go of Ace!
...weak!!
Dogra went there to look for
them now so trust him and wait.
We're special! If you're
from a noble family...
"I Want to See Them! Luffy's Mournful Cry!"
Everybody's having a hard
time - not just you, Luffy.
Did you see the person with
the gigantic face today?
Yeah, I've never seen someone like that!
What are you guys doing here?
Look, the ship is huge, too!
Let's go along the Grand Line!
Run! Ace! Luffy!
Finally we found you!
--The fishing boat has been hit!
--How's the child?
We're gonna take over the world!
These are pretty serious
wounds, Luffy! Are you okay?
580... 581...
Let's start with that island!
He made the Celestial Dragon mad!
582... 583...
Dogra...
Sabo!
Give me cannonballs!
"The Fire Has Been Set! The
Gray Terminal in Crisis!"
Meteor Fist Shower!
Damn! The ship is catching fire!
I don't see Sabo anywhere!
584...
Here, here, here, here!
Why did they shoot me like that?
Sabo went home. He's not here.
Wait! Stop!
Saint Jalmack! There is a child on the ship!
Of course, I know. What about it?
You're late, Dragon! I got tired of waiting!
When someone flies a black flag, he's
a pirate regardless of who he is.
Ace!
But most importantly...
You're the boss monkey from Mt. Corvo!
They're setting boxes of oil and
explosives all over the Gray Terminal.
You've had enough for today.
Sorry.
I'm the mountain bandit - Dadan!
What happened?!
--Oh, that's very bad!
--Hey, treat him now!
I don't know why but I'm registered
as their foster parent.
Dammit!
--It's Garp-san!
--Garp-san is back with his ship!
A commoner shouldn't cross
the path of my ship!!
Roger!
A-Are you alright?
On business?!
Outta my way!
Honestly! Where have you been?!
I won't stand by and watch someone
try to take my boys' lives...
"EAST BLUE" GOA KINGDOM--WINDMILL VILLAGE
I was watching the ceremony
for the Celestial Dragon.
I-I have to tell them!
...even if I'm not their real parent!
Garp-san, I've read about
the war in the newspaper!
It said it was a great victory for the Navy!
I'll just let you go if you back away.
How could you do that without telling me?
Hey you! Watch out! You have to be careful.
--Hey, how is everybody here doing?
--What happened to Luffy?
If you don't, I'll have
to resort to violence!
Ouch!
You attract too much attention.
What's gonna happen to the world
after Whitebeard's death, Garp-san?
--We got him!
--Hey, relax!
M-My face, you mean?
I've seen pirate ships offshore
frequently over the past few days.
Hey! What was that ship doing?
Ace! Luffy!
This is an important ceremony!
We have to prepare as soon as
possible for what will come!
Huh? Burn down the Gray Terminal?!
Why are you doing that?!
We can't even sleep in peace at night
because we fear their invasion.
We don't
wanna put the Celestial Dragon in a bad mood!
Try it!
Oh yeah? Alright then...
Move the shipwreck already!
Do we have enough food?
Don't worry! I just sank
three of them out at sea!
You fool! Don't scream! We can't
let anyone else know about this!
They gave us some at the
training hall in the village.
Really?! That's great!
This is serious! I gotta tell everybody!
Run!
They were all amateurs who
don't even know how to fight.
Let's leave here! Head back to Baltigo!
He's a bad guy just as I thought!
Yes, boss!
I told you to not to scream.
Hey, hold them down.
But for a while,
Hey, what're you doing?!
Ace, hurry up!
the seas will be uneasy all over the
world because Whitebeard was a deterrent.
I'm not the mastermind.
Ace!
Meanwhile, in the Goa Kingdom
This is a remote village in the East
Blue but you have to be careful.
There was oil and explosives in the boxes
after the observers from the
World Government left...
I...
that you guys carried yesterday and today.
--Hey!
--Yes, sir!
...won't run!
Guys!
And there's gonna be a massive
fire that no one can escape from.
SECURITY BY NAVY VICE ADMIRAL GARP
Hey guys, those two...
"Security by Navy Vice Admiral
Garp"? Oh, I feel safe!
What're you saying, Ace?!
Don't try to fight him!
Here comes some junk!
What is it?
--No...
--Are you out of your mind?
They're back!
We don't have to be afraid of anything!
People are doing exactly the
same thing they did before
Bluejam is a real villain!
Even punk kids like you two are freaking out?
Garp-san, we have another problem.
He's not a guy that a kid like you can beat!
accumulating another mountain of junk.
Mountain bandits came down to the village
But now you know about the plan.
--L-Let me fight, too!
--No, Luffy!
and they're taking over Makino's bar.
We can't let you go.
Mountain bandits?
No! You can't do that!
Here I come, Ace!
You all, why don't you
take Luffy and go ahead!
I want to ask you something before the fire.
Gum-Gum...
B-Boss!
Say, you two, do you have a
treasure hidden away somewhere?
Hey, Garp!
I'll take responsibility
for bringing Ace home!
...Pistol!
Oh, that's her!
I'm so relieved!
How dare you come back
and show your face here?!
Ace... Boss...
Boss!
She's severely wounded!
Hurry up and treat her!
Get in here!
Garp-san!
Go!
B-Boss!
--Y-Yes, ma'am!
--Ace!
You've given me nothing but
trouble! You're such a bad son!
Vice Admiral Garp!
Are you alright?
Boss! Come home safely!
Ace!
What are you doing?! You're no match for me!
I was right to adopt another
child just as I thought.
Luffy!
Stay out of it! I know her.
A woman and a child.
Did you think that I was dead?
No matter how strong you are,
Open up, dad! I gotta go!
it's nothing if you can't hit a target!
--But...!
--Why are you crying?!
If you overestimate your
ability, you'll only get hurt!
There are people that I have
to help! Dad! Dad! Open Up!
Rubber is not useful in
fighting just as I thought!
You bastard...
I'm not dead, fool!
You were there at the battlefield...
Shut up!
Only the strong and the
cowardly survive in wars!
Easy, easy, that's enough.
What?! I'm telling you the truth!
You were there with them!
What did you do to help?!
All you can do is bounce back
attacks  and sink like a rock!
Luffy is just happy.
The brave always die.
What did you do to help?!
Stop making fun of the Gum-Gum
Fruit! I'll make you cry someday!
Why?! Why?! Why?! Why?! Why?!
Is that so?
I...!
I've been creating new attacks
stronger than the pistol!
Can I ask you about the night of the fire?
What a fool!
After we left with Luffy,
Luffy, that was great!
what happened to you and boss?
Your arm stretched farther than yesterday!
We fought against Bluejam...
Why did you stand by and watch Ace die?!
Sabo! You're too easy on Luffy!
Damn!
I'm stronger than yesterday as I thought!
You chose your job over your family?!
I'm a dead man! The fire
is all over the place!
--Don't you think so, Sabo?!
Hey, Garp! You're the hero of the Navy?!
How could this happen all of the sudden?!
Go to hell, you old bastard!
--Easy, easy, boss, stop it!
--Boss!
--It's hot! It's hot!
--There's no way out!
Garp, say something!
Why didn't you help him?! Why
didn't you do something?!
Get on your feet!
We have to give up!
EDGE TOWN
You cold-blooded scum!
Sabo was a good brother...
Shut up!
Stop it, Dadan-san!
H-Hey! Look at that!
What?! You mean it'd be
better if I had died?!
And we barely defeated him.
I didn't say that!
You meant it!
And we tried to follow you guys right away
Something's wrong with the Gray Terminal.
Makino...
Ouch!
Sabo didn't hit me like that!
Isn't it burning?
but the fire was blocking our way.
--What?!
--What?! Be nice to me!
Damn! There's no way out!
We have no choice!
No way!
This is the best game I've ever played!
--Wait!
--What are you doing?!
B-B-Boss! Boss! You gotta see this!
What just happened?
I have no choice since I told them
What are you screaming about?
There's a path!
Ouch.
that I'd take responsibility
for bringing you home...
--The sky in the north, look!
--Is it the town?!
The explosion left a path!
Can't you see that he's taking
it harder than anybody else
I don't know what's going
on but this is great!
No, closer than that! Must be
the Gray Terminal! It's on fire!
Follow my lead. Don't get
separated at any cost!
Hey look, there is a ship!
because he couldn't help them
even though he was there?!
I see a ship!
I HEREBY ESTABLISH AN INDEPENDENT COUNTRY
DOWNTOWN
What's going on? It's like a wildfire!
This path leads up to the shore!
Dadan!
I hereby establish an independent country.
It's never happened before!
We can get away by following it!
Country?!
Let's go before the fire returns!
It's dangerous - evacuate Edge Town!
ME TOO
Th-That's not true.
EDGE TOWN--GREAT GATE
All residents must head to Downtown!
Me too!
ACE'S KINGDOM--
Hey, Dadan! Are you alright, Dadan?!
How awful they are to burn the
area and the residents there!
LUFFY'S KINGDOM
Leave the lifesaving and fire
extinguishing to us military!
That's not true.
ACE'S KINGDOM    LUFFY'S KINGDOM
We finally made it through the fire
That's not true!
but Dadan got severely burned.
By the way,
What do you want this time?
Luffy's having a harder time than anyone!
--We made it to the Great Gate!
--We're safe now!
how did you know the situation in such
an outlying country in the East Blue?
We need to be strong enough
to live on our own!
We managed to get to the riverside
in the In-Between Forest.
You guys belong to Dadan's Kingdom!
Is there something special
about this country?
Wh-What are you doing?!
Let me use your bath sometimes.
We only protect the residents here!
This country is an example of how
the world will be in the future.
Okay, let's start today's lesson
of how to express gratitude.
--No way!
--How can you do this?!
Stay with me! You can't die!
There can be no happiness in a world
Thief!
Yeah, let's get started already!
Wait! Stop!
Oh, you got it, Ace!
where the undesirables are thrown away.
I went to the town to steal some
medicine and get something to eat
No, that's not right.
Someday, I will change the world!
--Let us get in!
--Help us, please!
You have to say "Thank you
in advance" on that occasion.
and tried to save Dadan's life.
If I stay here... I'll never be free!
Oh, that wasn't right?
It sounded cool though.
Ace-kun wants to learn this
Even in a country like
this, there are children.
because he
wants to say "thank you" properly...
Ace! You gotta help me! It's a bear!
You don't have to worry
about me so just go, Ace.
...to the captain of the Red-Haired
Pirates who helped Luffy.
--Everybody, wake up!
--You gotta run!
I thought that you wanted
to live on your own.
Cut the crap! I thought you were
responsible for bringing me home!
To Shanks?!
Yeah, I will be a pirate by
the time I see Red-Haired.
--The fire is spreading all around!
--We can't stay here!
I won't allow you to die!
Dammit!
It's no use, give it up!
You gotta flee your home!
Hey!
As a pirate and as your old
brother, it's my job to thank him.
Some survivors could be around here!
Those of you who are willing to
fight for freedom, come aboard!
Don't let anyone get away! Get them!
Now, let's do it pretending that
he's right in front of you.
Oh! The fire has gotten to the shore already!
Yes, sir!
Luffy!
The entrance to the forest is ablaze, too!
I'm Ace. Who the hell are you?
Okay, okay, we see.
Damn! Where should we go?! We're stuck!
In any case,
I'm glad that you both survived!
Booh! That's not right. It's
not nice to say "the hell."
GOA KINGDOM "ROYAL PALACE"
Sorry that I made you worry.
Burn everything, guys!
Is it "Who the heck are you"?
I can't believe what
happened to Gray Terminal.
HIGH TOWN
Hey, anybody there in Dadan's Kingdom?!
Give me your name.
I wonder if Sabo is worrying about us.
Luffy got hurt! Please help him!
When we complete this task,
Booh.
--Banzai!
Did they find Sabo?
my long-cherished dream will come true!
You have to say "you fool"!
I just called in the military.
They'll find him soon.
Another rude commoner could
appear at any minute.
Magra! Please! Treat Luffy!
Who are you, you bastard?
You're right.
Booh!
Okay, okay, come in now!
We don't give a damn
about the other people living here.
--Watch carefully.
--Yes, sir!
Who is this?
I see. Sabo is giving us
a hard time, isn't he?
Booh!
But even if this place is so crappy,
"Whom" is this?
Yeah...
it's good enough for us to hide in, King.
Booh!
Stop it! Are you serious?
I wonder how's Sabo doing?
I'm aware of that, Bluejam.
Is this town really safe?
But I'm glad that Ace is back
and Dadan is recovering.
You're bugging me by saying
stupid things! Go away!
It looks like the fire will
engulf the town any minute!
But when this is over, you
no longer need to hide.
Well, well, it was no joking matter.
Listen, Ace, I found an anaconda's
nest filled with big eggs!
I will make you and your friends
nobles by my authority.
Ace, at that moment...
He might have died if the
cut was a little bit deeper.
Isn't there any way to enter High Town?
I won't run!
No, there isn't.
Let's go get some now!
Will you really?!
They don't even allow a bug
to enter - nobles only!
What? Big eggs?!
You three fought those beasts
together, didn't you?
Why didn't you run?
The king will give us titles
No, I can't!
I can't help getting fired up sometimes.
--Boss!
I wanna learn how to pay respect!
It's my fault!
and we'll live in the High
Town as privileged nobles!
I'm always afraid that if I run,
I could get hurt if no one's
there and the anaconda finds me!
I'll leave something important behind.
I knew it doesn't prove that you're
strong by fighting on your own!
Ace!
Boss!
At that moment...
But I'll be safe if you come with me! So...
Ace!
Luffy was behind me.
Shut up!
Boss!
I'm not good enough!
We better get moving.
I'm not good enough at all!
I don't know but I think that's why.
He loved his brother so much!
Ace and Dadan didn't return
from the burning Gray Terminal.
Let's get to the Great Gate!
The military is waiting.
Ace...
Captain, we left the brats in the hideout...
Even when he faced a cloud
of enemies beyond his power,
I'm sorry, Luffy!
Forget 'em. They could've joined my crew
if they told me where the treasure was.
I'm sorry!
Roger would never run away.
Was he suicidal? Running
away is a strategy, too.
Makino!
Fools can't live long anyway.
That's right but he'd never do that.
Garp.
Because he'd leave the
people he loved behind.
What happened to Luffy?
It said in the newspaper
that he went missing.
Hey, guys!
But it's closed, Captain!
If he ran, he would put his crew in danger.
Easy, easy, wait, Luffy. You're not
recovered - where're you going?
Makino came all the way bringing us sake!
Mayor.
Don't panic. They just don't
want other people to get away.
Actually, "he wouldn't run
away" isn't quite right.
I gotta go and look for Ace and Dadan!
How to pay respect to other people?
The plan is for me to give them a sign,
then they'll open the gate.
He wouldn't let the enemy have
a chance to go after his crew.
You can't do that!
Uh-huh.
He got away by submarine.
What's gotten into you?
It's me, Bluejam. Open up.
Ouch!
He'd change into a sort of
demon in those situations.
Since I'm Luffy's brother,
See? That's what I told you.
The Navy went after him in full force
and searched for him desperately
it's my job to go see the captain
of the Red-Haired Pirates
He once destroyed a country's entire military
Hey! Don't you hear me?!
because they talked badly about his crew.
who helped Luffy in order to thank him!
but they didn't find any shipwreck.
You're seriously wounded. You
have to rest nice and easy.
He'd become violent when angry.
Is this...
So he's probably alive!
He was short-tempered and selfish.
There are a lot of troops
in the Gray Terminal now
But he was naive and straightforward
like a child at the same time.
Captain, could it be...
Oh, that's great!
to take care of the mess after the fire.
But how does Navy Vice Admiral
Garp-san know the mountain bandit?
Hey, you guys, what are
you doing?! Open the gate!
That's because his early life was like Ace's.
Do you have something to say?!
It's not just burned junk
that they're throing out,
He hated to lose those he loved.
I'm sorry. Alright, I'll teach you how.
The plan was you let us
evacuate from here, right?!
Don't know.
but survivors, too.
This is not what we agreed to! You bastards!
Okay, this would be the first one...
They're gonna kill you if you go there.
Luffy is so stupid.
They didn't pay!
He was that reckless but he survived,
But...!
What happened to your promise, King?!
Stop!
But I'll take his side no matter
what kind of pirate he becomes.
and became the King of the Pirates.
You said that you'd make us nobles...
Oh, we forgot to do it!
Although he got a bad reputation,
his crew trusted him implicitly.
You set us up? King!
It breaks my heart when I think
about how he must feel now.
Oh yeah!
Dammit!
I wanna see Ace!
Even I as a Navy soldier
couldn't help respecting him.
Did you hear?
I know that Sabo is worrying about us, too!
--Thank you for the meal!
Bluejam, a pirate in the Gray
Terminal, started the fire.
Shut up, you brats! You got to pay!
That's why I decided to take care of Ace.
That's what I thought!
No one else would do that.
We're the ones taking care of him!
THE FORMER SITE OF THE GRAY TERMINAL
Luffy!!
Huh? Have something you want to say?
He did it to try to keep the observers
from the World Government away.
I'm gonna win today!
What a great view!
Don't be defeated!!
No, I don't.
How can you be so happy?
How terrible he is!
The people of the world still hate Roger.
It's a pain in the butt
to clean up this mess!
And while Ace hates his father,
It's hot! It's hot!
it really is "like father, like son."
Meanwhile, far away in the
second half of the Grand Line -
Yes!
Alright! Let's see which
one of you will win...
Damn! We didn't wanna be involved in this!
If we find a survivor, we're
to shoot them on sight.
the New World...
Dogra!
We can't get away! I don't wanna die!
There aren't any.
You were looking for Ace and Dadan, right?
I'll leave you behind if
you don't stop complaining!
But there aren't as many dead
bodies as I thought there'd be.
They're back!
It's not hot.
It was a big fire. It could've
burned out the bones.
Oh yeah? That's great.
Whoa, it's hot! No, it's not.
The fire is everywhere outside!
I was nervous yesterday,
W-What?! Sabo is...
I can't breathe.
thinking that the
fire might get to this side of the wall.
Yes, I can!
The air is hot!
Stop lying, you fool!
Don't even joke about it!
They say that Bluejam's
ship was on fire, too.
No, it's not.
--We did it!
It's gonna be alright! I'm here with you!
Stop, Ace!
Bear meat stew tonight!
It's nice to know that
those villains got burned!
I'm not lying or joking
about it! It was so sudden!
Call the police! Sabo did it again!
I could barely believe what I saw!
Hello? Hello?!
I thought I was dreaming!
Red-Haired,
It's morning!
Shut up! Sabo went back to his family's home!
I've no words to express my gratitude.
What are you doing?! You have to evacuate!
How could he be at sea?!
Stop talking nonsense.
That's right! He went home!
Open the gate!
A hoodlum like me can
understand how he feels!
What are you talking about?!
I always respected Whitebeard,
even though he was my enemy.
You brat!
People don't always wanna
go back to their home!
Take him away!
Ace! Luffy!
If he was really happy,
he wouldn't go out to sea!
Even Sengoku respected him.
Run!
Hi! it's a nice day, isn't it?
Whitebeard, Ace...
He wouldn't go out to sea by himself
with a black flag on his ship!
Yes, it is a lovely morning!
Stay away! Stay away from the lock!
Let us handle the burial of those two.
No!
I agree! I will take the blame on myself!
Ace!
Luffy!
Alright, we should go now.
Sabo...
There are still so many of them!
Yes. Thanks.
He wasn't happy!
--Be a good kid and evacuate!
--Don't give us any trouble!
Luffy must be having a hard time.
Enough with this game of tag, okay boy?
I was all by myself even if I had parents!
I can't believe what Ace did.
Why?! Why didn't we go
there to take him back?!
A-Ace... Luffy...
Take back what you just said!
7 YEARS LATER
Where is the guy who killed
Sabo now?! I'm gonna kill him!
Don't make fun of the man who saved me!
K-Kill the Celestial Dragon?!
That's impossible...
The name of this era should be "Whitebeard"!
ACE, 17 YEARS OLD
I'll make him pay!
Wait, Ace!
LUFFY, 14 YEARS OLD
Stop it, you little shit!
Move...
That's what Captain Roger would've done.
Outta my way!
How can you be so confident even
though you're not that strong?!
No matter how many times you
run, you can't get away, Sabo!
What happened to you, boy?
What can you do?! They'll just kill you!
I wanted the captain to run away sometimes
All the police and troops
have a picture of you now!
You'll die and people will
forget you by tomorrow!
You will never get out of High Town...
You're just a nameless kid!
and be able to shed tears.
O-Old man...
or even out of this house!
Sabo was killed by this country! This world!
You two, change your uniforms and
start working here as guards.
The royalty and nobles
are... behind the fire...
Listen, Luffy.
What can you do about it?!
By experiencing both victory and defeat,
But we have our duties...
Take care, Ace!
Your father changed the world by his death!
running away and shedding tears,
There is nothing that a nobleman can't do.
Yeah. See you, Luffy! I'm going now!
When you become a man that important,
Believe me...
a man will become a man.
then you can do whatever you want!
I'll get the approval of your superiors.
Uh-huh! I'll be a lot stronger
when I leave here in 3 years!
This town smells worse than Gray Terminal.
Tie this fool up!
It smells like rotten people!
Sabo, you must barricade
yourself in your room
Y-Yes, ma'am!
and educate yourself in your role as a noble!
Sabo!!
If I stay here... I'll never be free!
Good luck, Ace!
It's okay to cry.
No!
Damn!
As you know, I can make things
happen just by giving the word.
Take care!
Don't catch a cold!
Shut up! Stop crying like a girl, Luffy!
But you have to move on!
You just wait! I'll make my name soon!
I'm...
So I can take care of
you or those two easily.
...ashamed of being born a noble!
Ace, the son of the King of the
Pirates, has grown up secretly
They finally made a kid
say this! Goa Kingdom!
Am I understood?
Dad...
and he quietly departed from
the shore nearby Mt. Corvo.
I know how you feel. I was
born in this country, too.
Ace... Luffy...
But I still don't have enough
power to change the country.
So why don't you mend your ways
and study hard like Stelly.
"CALM BELT" MAIDEN ISLAND
Old man, you really are
listening to me, aren't you?
And...
Yes, and I'll never forget.
...study so that you can make your parents,
He's gone!
Damn!
who brought you into the world, happy!
I'm too weak! I can't save anybody!
Honestly! I wonder what Garp would say.
Have you come to your senses, Ace?
Because that will make you happy, too!
Damn! Damn!
Don't you think so?
--Untie him.
--Yes, ma'am.
Damn! Damn!
Father!
Dammit!!
Run, Luffy!
Hold on.
--Where's Luffy?
--He's been crying all night and he's sleeping now.
Don't worry! I'm here for you!
Boss! You're not gonna believe this!
You're so dependable, Stelly!
Luffy-kun.
Okay, Let me buy you some luxurious clothes
We got a letter from Sabo!
Go away!
TO MY BROTHERS AT MT. CORVO FROM SABO
You must raise him, Dadan!
for the ceremony the day after tomorrow.
He must've sent it before he went out to sea!
No way! Whose baby is this?
Leave me alone!
There, we'll see the
Celestial Dragon in person!
I can't!
Give it to me!
Boss!
I can't just watch you hurt yourself anymore.
I'm not gonna go to the town!
It's for us, isn't it?
Ace is gone!
It's my own body! It's none of your business!
Oh good. But I can see that
Garp will be mad at me.
No... No way!
I can't believe it!
I'm... helpless!
Then you can't blame Ace
for doing what he did.
He was such an useless little shit!
"Ace, Luffy, I hope you guys
weren't hurt in the fire."
His death was not your business!
Oh, Ace left a message for you.
Shut up, you bastard! I'm gonna
beat you if you say another word!
"I'm worrying about you both but
I believe that you're okay."
Okay, that's it for today.
What?! He still has something to
say to me even at the last minute?!
Captain, there's no chance!
"I'm sorry to say it, guys, but when you
get this letter, I'll already be..."
Do it if it makes you happy!
There's no way to put out the fire!
We gotta give up the ship!
We can't flee to the sea!
He said "Thank you for taking care of me!"
I'm injured too but I'm not gonna
get beaten by you in that condition!
Damn the King! How could he do this to us?!
I'll check your homework tomorrow.
"...out on the sea."
Gum-Gum...
"Things led to things and I decided
to set out to sea before you."
Okay, have a nice day!
I'll show that bastard!
...Pistol!
He can't do that! That fool!
Honestly!
Oh? Boss, are you crying?!
It's so annoying that the sky
in the south is bright even in the night.
"My destination will be anywhere but here."
I'm not crying, you fool!
Ace... Luffy...
We are sorry, your Majesty.
Let us close the curtain.
"I'm gonna become stronger
and become a pirate!"
I don't think that you died in the fire.
You guys are okay, aren't you?
"The three of us have to become
the freest pirates ever."
"One day, let's meet up again somewhere."
I have to wait 3 years more.
Say, daddy, why are the people
in the Gray Terminal not humans?
"Somewhere on the wide open sea!
Definitely, someday!"
Gum-Gum...
Jimbei...
...Pistol!
When I was going after Teach,
Why do they have to get burned?
I wish I could see you.
As the phrase goes, "As a
man sows, so shall he reap."
Damn! I missed it by a little.
"By the way, Ace, which of us
do you think is the bigger brother?"
I saw my brother for the first time
in 3 years in Alabasta Kingdom.
Think about it.
You almost got it, Luffy!
But I know I'll put you guys in
danger if I try to see you now.
They could have avoided their
fate just by being born nobles.
"Two big brothers and one little brother."
Why don't you keep the
center of gravity lower?
And I felt relieved instantly as I saw him.
Born nobles?
"It's odd but our brotherhood
is my treasure."
This place is like a birdcage!
Do you know why?
Gum-Gum...
You're right! They should have
chosen to be born nobles!
I don't think I can stand living in
this country filled with stale air.
...Pistol!
They're stupid!
Now, enough about those people,
you have to study for tomorrow.
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow!
"Luffy is still a weak crybaby but..."
You better go to bed.
That hurts, you brat!
Okay!
What is freedom?
Good night.
Where can I find it?
I wanna become stronger!
"...he is our little brother
so take good care of him!"
I wanna become stronger!
Your shift is over.
Can't you see things clearly now?!
Is it the time already?
A FEW MONTHS LATER
You shouldn't be sleeping on the job.
You believed that you
could overcome anything!
Sorry. By the way, how
are things in the town?
And you've never doubted your strength!
The ceremony is just a day away, right?
Luffy!
But all those formidable enemies
took away your confidence!
Look at the newspaper!
It's crazy. People are going
wild getting ready for it.
--There's no way on this side!
--We keep losing ground.
What is it?
Look here!
What bad luck!
And your brother was your guide on the sea!
Wow! Ace made his name!
I don't wanna die here!
It's a once-in-a-lifetime
thing but I got to be here.
I know that you have lost a lot!
He got his own ship and crew!
I wonder if those old men escaped safely.
And the toughest enemies in the world
He's great! Ace is great!
This boy and I will be the only
two in this house tomorrow.
This is no time to be concerned
about other people!
blocked your way time after time!
Damn! I don't even know where I am!
But I'm gonna top him!
How could they call themselves
observers?! They're partying everyday!
Your power is not enough to beat me!
I wanted to see the Celestial Dragon.
Who said that you could get away, you brats?!
It depends on your attitude.
3 YEARS LATER - LUFFY, 17 YEARS OLD
They haven't covered Sabo's story...
Bluejam!
All the citizens will be
at the harbor tomorrow.
You could be level-headed.
Hey, guys!
I heard that his parents didn't take action.
Why are you still here
after setting the fire?!
I'm leaving now. You're not gonna see me off?
It'll be such a pain to stand guard there,
His parents are nobles
You were supposed to have escaped by now!
but they're powerless against the World
Government and Celestial Dragons.
compared with this baby-sitting gig!
Go, Pacifistas!
How annoying.
Shut up, you little shit!
Then, why don't you take my place?
The mayor and Makino won't mind,
We're hopeless, you know.
How's Luffy doing?
but the people in the Windmill
Village will be scared of us.
No way!
He still isn't eating much.
We have an unforeseen dilemma.
But he still eats twice as much as we do!
But...
Humans are strange creatures, aren't they?
Alright, we're leaving now.
I bet Sabo's death really got to him...
Why don't you just go already?!
Take good care of Sabo.
Alright. Then you guys,
When you hit rock bottom,
you can't stop laughing.
You can't get away from me!
Yes, sir.
thank you for everything!
Don't say it - I feel awkward!
Well, well, take care!
Yeah, okay!
They are acting weird.
Oh yeah!
Luffy, let's go!
Dadan, I don't like mountain bandits...
Don't let them!
Shut up, you brat!
You'll never find your way like this!
Because you've lost yourself
in regret and guilt!
...but I like you guys!
Ace! Luffy!
I know that it's painful now, Luffy,
We worked together - we're friends!
We gotta set out to sea someday!
Stop talking nonsense and go
away already, you bastard!
but you have to bottle up those feelings!
The day of the World Noble
from the Grand Line's visit
We have to die together!
Let's get out of this
country and live freely!
Don't just think about the ones you've lost!
We don't wanna die with you!
Not in a million years!
Dammit! Why am I surrounded by such fools?!
to the Goa Kingdom has arrived.
You can't get back what you've lost!
So from now on,
You're so cold.
What is it that you still have?!
A lavish ceremony is prepared
for the arrival of the ship.
Oh, you crying?
Come to think of it, you haven't told
me where you keep your treasure.
we're brothers!
I'm not crying!
Windmill Village at the edge of
Goa Kingdom on the Dawn Island.
I'll save it for you before the fire
gets it. So tell me where it is.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring,
ring, ring... Clank!
Hey, why don't you take my
old fishing boat, Luffy?
Your life is in danger and all
you care about is treasure?
Hello, this is A-team on the coast.
That thing is gonna sink any minute!
If you don't care, then tell me where it is.
The Celestial Dragon's ship
will arrive in a few minutes.
That's a small boat...
This is fine! This is
what I wanna start with!
You've gone mad.
Roger that. It's all quiet here.
If you're not gonna go
get it, it'd be a waste.
How much longer are you gonna lie there?
We'll continue to stand guard.
If nothing is done, it's gonna be
reduced to charcoal like my ship.
Sabo!
Clank!
The treasure that we were hiding
in the forest is all gone.
Watch over me! I'm gonna go out to sea now!
What a waste.
Don't be ridiculous! That treasure is...
The survivors from Bluejam's crew took
it or maybe the military found it.
Alright, I tell you!
Hey, look! There is a ship leaving port!
Sabo was first and Ace was second.
Ace! You and Sabo spent a lot of time...
I don't know where it went.
And I'm third but I'm gonna
top them!
--What?
--Is it a fishing boat?
But I don't care about the treasure anymore.
Sabo would understand!
Wait for me, Ace!
I'll catch up with you soon!
Hey! Come back here! Don't get
in the way of the ceremony!
That was the pirate savings that
I was gonna share with Sabo
What matters the most now is your...
What are you doing screaming and mumbling?
What matters the most now is our lives!
Luffy, don't fool around
here. I'm training now.
Is it some kind of incantation?
but Sabo didn't need it after all.
It's a child! There's a child on the ship!
No, it's not! It's a challenge!
So I'll just let it go, too.
A child? I wonder which family he's from.
--Who's Ace?
--No idea.
Alright, I'm going now!
It's no use having treasure
if you can't even protect it.
Ace...
A child?
Luffy! Tell everybody to take their post!
Honey, could it be...?!
A-Ace... I...
No, that's impossible! The
guard is looking after him!
A storm is coming!
Luffy, you just see if I don't!
We keep our treasure from
last 6 years in this tree.
I wanna become stronger!
I'm gonna catch a big one soon!
He's finally leaving,
mayor. I'm gonna miss him.
More, and more...
I see.
It's a dishonor to the
village to become a pirate!
More and more, more and more...
Luffy, it's almost ready
so just shut up and wait.
Don't cry!
It's alright. This is not the end.
More, more and more, more and more...
What a nice day! It's
perfect for setting sail!
Luffy, no matter how serious your
injury is, you're in good hands!
What nice day for setting sail!
More and more, more and more...
I'll treat you!
What are you doing?! I told you where it is!
I wanna become even stronger!
Oh no! That's mine! Somebody
stole my fish boat!
You're right. This is not the end.
Then I can protect anything or anyone!
I don't have to lose anybody!
Oh, Luffy!
I can teach you about archeology
if you're interested.
Which means you could be lying.
You gotta come with us.
Look! He has a black flag on it!
I beg you!
No way! Then it's gonna
be too late to escape!
Th-That's...!
Does he think that he's a pirate?!
Ace, please don't die!
Hey, Luffy! The Cola engine
is in top shape as always!
No way! A kid can't just become a pirate!
Why don't you guys go on your own?!
--Where is he heading?
--He's disrupting the ceremony.
Cut it out! Worry about yourself first!
Here comes our local sea monster!
You can leave everything
about the Sunny to me!
You don't wanna mess with me now.
The Government's ship will arrive soon!
You're far weaker than me!
Good morning, Luffy-san! It's morning!
Hurry up and do something!
Listen carefully, Luffy!
I'm determined to make a come back,
You don't know who you're messing with.
Y-Yes, sir!
Now here is the first song for today!
Hey!
Look at this technique I've
been training for 10 years!
even if it means stealing from kids
I'll never die!
Kid, come back here now!
so I can take my revenge on nobles.
Gum-Gum...
Uh-huh.
And your brother is one of them.
Sabo told me to take care of you, too.
The scariest fate for me is to
lose myself in this country and...
They think they're so special
Luffy.
I promise that I'll never die!
Luffy!
...Pistol!
turn into someone else!
and look down on others as if we're trash!
Luffy!
How can I leave a wimpy
brother like you behind?
Luffy.
Luffy!
Sabo doesn't think like that!
Luffy.
Uh-huh... Uh-huh!
I'm not gonna go back!
He's the same as them, fool!
Luffy!
I'm not smart so I don't quite
know what really killed Sabo yet.
Luffy-san!
He was with you both just to feel superior!
Luffy!
Is it Sabo on that ship?
That's not true!
But it must be something opposed to freedom.
His parents are loaded.
The Government's ship is here!
That will learn ya, stupid fish!
He doesn't
have to worry about anything!
Sabo died before he knew freedom.
It was just a pastime for him.
We exchanged that same cup
of sake and we're alive!
He was looking down on you guys
I still have...
I still have my friends!
and laughing to himself holding his nose!
Wow! He beat the sea monster
with a single blow!
Zoro! Nami! Usopp! Sanji!
Stop talking bad about Sabo!
So listen, Luffy.
Yeah, Sabo just wants to be free!
Chopper! Robin! Franky! Brook!
He's become quite strong!
We have to live without leaving any regrets.
You little shit!
They are my friends!
Let's start with finding a crew!
Luffy!
Uh-huh.
The ship is huge!
I want at least 10 of them.
I see.
I'll die if I crash into it.
And the black flag!
I'm gonna kill you!
I have to meet them on the ship.
Let's avoid that.
Alright! Let's go!
Guys! Meet on the Sunny in three days!
Let go of me!
Okay!
I'm gonna become...
Good. He's turning away.
Boys from noble family...
I gotta go! It took a while but...
Don't touch Luffy!!
...will become full nobles when they turn 18.
...the King of the Pirates!
...I know that they're waiting for me!
That's why I need to leave here by 17!
It seems like the commoners are welcoming us.
What I saw there, Jimbei, was...
Yes.
We gotta go out to sea someday...
And now,
They're so blessed that
it's rare to even see them!
Older brothers can't help worrying...
Luffy mourns the loss of his brother Ace.
...and live as we like.
Freer than anyone else.
...if their younger brother is weak.
I can't believe that a real
Celestial Dragon is on that ship!
Uh-huh!
I know that he'll be a handful
By the way, what is that?
That means we'll make enemies of many people.
but please look after him.
That looks like a fish boat.
Luffy wasn't just the kid who
used to follow me around anymore.
Even the old man will become our enemy.
You gotta risk everything.
Luffy! You okay?!
Let's go out to sea at 17!
It'd be nice to be captain
of a ship like that someday!
He had...
What did you do?!
Luffy-kun...
And we will become... pirates!
...such reliable friends!
The King of the Pirates?!
Dammit...
Commoner!
You creepy brat!
I'm...
He'll be alright no matter what happens.
Do you wanna make a fool out of me, too?!
I'm...
Shut up, you scumbag!
That's why I felt relieved.
I'm...
You bastard!
How rude is that!
Ace!
I wanna see them now...
The fishing boat has been hit!
Don't do it!!
I wanna see them!!
I'm too...
...weak!!
As Garp returns to Windmill Village,
Dadan greets him in outrage.
Ace and Dadan return to their hideout.
Luffy is missing his friends...
Luffy and Ace are stricken with grief,
Ace and Luffy are cornered by Bluejam!
At the same time, far across the sea,
but they hold on to their
dream of becoming pirates
As everyone is rejoicing
over their safe return,
Trapped among the flames with no escape,
Meanwhile, Luffy is lost in his grief
and helplessness after losing Ace.
the friends he'd been separated from
Ace stands his ground and
prepares to fight alone.
they learn of the tragedy
that struck Sabo at the port.
and set off toward the future again.
are still fighting their own battles to
make it back to the Sabaody Archipelago.
Meanwhile, left behind in High Town,
Their day of departure will come...
Realizing with sympathy
what Sabo had tried to do,
As he watches Luffy writhe in despair,
Sabo finally takes action
to go after his dream!
Meanwhile, news of the "War of the Best"
makes its way to the separated friends!
To achieve the dream that
Sabo was unable to realize!
Luffy and Ace are befallen
by regret and grief.
Jimbei recalls the words of Ace...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Where can freedom be found?
A Sad Departure of a Boy!"
"I Want to See Them! Luffy's Mournful Cry!"
"Straw Hats in Shock!
The Bad News Has Reached Them!"
"Take Good Care of Him! A
Letter from the Brother!"
"To Live Up to the Promise!
Departures of Their Own!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!