ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After losing his brother Ace during
the War of the Best against the Navy,
Luffy was consumed with unbearable sorrow.
There is, however, an untold
story of the brothers...
...10 years ago in the East
Blue - Luffy and Ace as boys.
"Take Good Care of Him! A
Letter from the Brother!"
Ace is not dead!
Easy, easy, I know. I know how you feel.
But it's too risky to go to Gray Terminal now
since you're wounded and
there are troops everywhere!
--But...!
--It was a big fire! And chances are...
...slim but we all want to believe
that the boss and Ace are alive.
Dogra went there to look for
them now so trust him and wait.
Everybody's having a hard
time - not just you, Luffy.
--The fishing boat has been hit!
--How's the child?
He made the Celestial Dragon mad!
Sabo!
Damn! The ship is catching fire!
Why did they shoot me like that?
Saint Jalmack! There is a child on the ship!
When someone flies a black flag, he's
a pirate regardless of who he is.
But most importantly...
Dammit!
A commoner shouldn't cross
the path of my ship!!
Hey! What was that ship doing?
This is an important ceremony!
We don't
wanna put the Celestial Dragon in a bad mood!
Move the shipwreck already!
Guys!
Hey guys, those two...
What is it?
They're back!
I'm so relieved!
Ace... Boss...
She's severely wounded!
Hurry up and treat her!
Are you alright?
Ace!
Luffy!
Did you think that I was dead?
--But...!
--Why are you crying?!
I'm not dead, fool!
Easy, easy, that's enough.
Luffy is just happy.
Can I ask you about the night of the fire?
After we left with Luffy,
what happened to you and boss?
We fought against Bluejam...
And we barely defeated him.
And we tried to follow you guys right away
but the fire was blocking our way.
Damn! There's no way out!
We have no choice!
--Wait!
--What are you doing?!
I have no choice since I told them
that I'd take responsibility
for bringing you home...
Follow my lead. Don't get
separated at any cost!
Dadan!
Hey, Dadan! Are you alright, Dadan?!
We finally made it through the fire
but Dadan got severely burned.
We managed to get to the riverside
in the In-Between Forest.
Stay with me! You can't die!
Thief!
Wait! Stop!
I went to the town to steal some
medicine and get something to eat
and tried to save Dadan's life.
You don't have to worry
about me so just go, Ace.
Cut the crap! I thought you were
responsible for bringing me home!
I won't allow you to die!
Hey!
Some survivors could be around here!
Don't let anyone get away! Get them!
Yes, sir!
Okay, okay, we see.
In any case,
I'm glad that you both survived!
Sorry that I made you worry.
I can't believe what
happened to Gray Terminal.
I wonder if Sabo is worrying about us.
--Banzai!
Another rude commoner could
appear at any minute.
--Watch carefully.
--Yes, sir!
I wonder how's Sabo doing?
But I'm glad that Ace is back
and Dadan is recovering.
Ace, at that moment...
I won't run!
Why didn't you run?
I can't help getting fired up sometimes.
I'm always afraid that if I run,
I'll leave something important behind.
At that moment...
Luffy was behind me.
I don't know but I think that's why.
Even when he faced a cloud
of enemies beyond his power,
Roger would never run away.
Was he suicidal? Running
away is a strategy, too.
That's right but he'd never do that.
Because he'd leave the
people he loved behind.
If he ran, he would put his crew in danger.
Actually, "he wouldn't run
away" isn't quite right.
He wouldn't let the enemy have
a chance to go after his crew.
He'd change into a sort of
demon in those situations.
He once destroyed a country's entire military
because they talked badly about his crew.
He'd become violent when angry.
He was short-tempered and selfish.
But he was naive and straightforward
like a child at the same time.
That's because his early life was like Ace's.
He hated to lose those he loved.
He was that reckless but he survived,
and became the King of the Pirates.
Although he got a bad reputation,
his crew trusted him implicitly.
Even I as a Navy soldier
couldn't help respecting him.
That's why I decided to take care of Ace.
We're the ones taking care of him!
Huh? Have something you want to say?
No, I don't.
The people of the world still hate Roger.
And while Ace hates his father,
it really is "like father, like son."
Alright! Let's see which
one of you will win...
Dogra!
You were looking for Ace and Dadan, right?
They're back!
Oh yeah? That's great.
W-What?! Sabo is...
Stop lying, you fool!
Don't even joke about it!
Stop, Ace!
I'm not lying or joking
about it! It was so sudden!
I could barely believe what I saw!
I thought I was dreaming!
Shut up! Sabo went back to his family's home!
How could he be at sea?!
That's right! He went home!
A hoodlum like me can
understand how he feels!
People don't always wanna
go back to their home!
If he was really happy,
he wouldn't go out to sea!
He wouldn't go out to sea by himself
with a black flag on his ship!
Sabo...
He wasn't happy!
I was all by myself even if I had parents!
Why?! Why didn't we go
there to take him back?!
Where is the guy who killed
Sabo now?! I'm gonna kill him!
K-Kill the Celestial Dragon?!
That's impossible...
I'll make him pay!
Wait, Ace!
Stop it, you little shit!
Move...
Outta my way!
How can you be so confident even
though you're not that strong?!
What can you do?! They'll just kill you!
You'll die and people will
forget you by tomorrow!
You're just a nameless kid!
Sabo was killed by this country! This world!
What can you do about it?!
Your father changed the world by his death!
When you become a man that important,
then you can do whatever you want!
Tie this fool up!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Sabo!!
Damn!
Shut up! Stop crying like a girl, Luffy!
Have you come to your senses, Ace?
--Untie him.
--Yes, ma'am.
Hold on.
--Where's Luffy?
--He's been crying all night and he's sleeping now.
Boss! You're not gonna believe this!
We got a letter from Sabo!
TO MY BROTHERS AT MT. CORVO FROM SABO
He must've sent it before he went out to sea!
Give it to me!
I'm not gonna go to the town!
It's for us, isn't it?
"Ace, Luffy, I hope you guys
weren't hurt in the fire."
"I'm worrying about you both but
I believe that you're okay."
"I'm sorry to say it, guys, but when you
get this letter, I'll already be..."
"...out on the sea."
"Things led to things and I decided
to set out to sea before you."
"My destination will be anywhere but here."
"I'm gonna become stronger
and become a pirate!"
"The three of us have to become
the freest pirates ever."
"One day, let's meet up again somewhere."
"Somewhere on the wide open sea!
Definitely, someday!"
"By the way, Ace, which of us
do you think is the bigger brother?"
"Two big brothers and one little brother."
"It's odd but our brotherhood
is my treasure."
"Luffy is still a weak crybaby but..."
"...he is our little brother
so take good care of him!"
How could they call themselves
observers?! They're partying everyday!
They haven't covered Sabo's story...
I heard that his parents didn't take action.
His parents are nobles
but they're powerless against the World
Government and Celestial Dragons.
How's Luffy doing?
He still isn't eating much.
But he still eats twice as much as we do!
I bet Sabo's death really got to him...
Ace! Luffy!
We gotta set out to sea someday!
Let's get out of this
country and live freely!
So from now on,
we're brothers!
How much longer are you gonna lie there?
The treasure that we were hiding
in the forest is all gone.
The survivors from Bluejam's crew took
it or maybe the military found it.
I don't know where it went.
But I don't care about the treasure anymore.
That was the pirate savings that
I was gonna share with Sabo
but Sabo didn't need it after all.
So I'll just let it go, too.
It's no use having treasure
if you can't even protect it.
A-Ace... I...
I wanna become stronger!
More, and more...
More and more, more and more...
More, more and more, more and more...
I wanna become even stronger!
Then I can protect anything or anyone!
I don't have to lose anybody!
I beg you!
Ace, please don't die!
Cut it out! Worry about yourself first!
You're far weaker than me!
Listen carefully, Luffy!
I'll never die!
Uh-huh.
Sabo told me to take care of you, too.
I promise that I'll never die!
How can I leave a wimpy
brother like you behind?
Uh-huh... Uh-huh!
I'm not smart so I don't quite
know what really killed Sabo yet.
But it must be something opposed to freedom.
Sabo died before he knew freedom.
We exchanged that same cup
of sake and we're alive!
So listen, Luffy.
We have to live without leaving any regrets.
Uh-huh.
Boys from noble family...
...will become full nobles when they turn 18.
That's why I need to leave here by 17!
We gotta go out to sea someday...
...and live as we like.
Freer than anyone else.
Uh-huh!
That means we'll make enemies of many people.
Even the old man will become our enemy.
You gotta risk everything.
Let's go out to sea at 17!
And we will become... pirates!
Luffy and Ace are stricken with grief,
but they hold on to their
dream of becoming pirates
and set off toward the future again.
Their day of departure will come...
To achieve the dream that
Sabo was unable to realize!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To Live Up to the Promise!
Departures of Their Own!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!