ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After the War of the Best against the Navy,
Luffy was suffering after losing his
brother Ace in the war against the Navy.
Luffy, depressed after losing his brother
Ace in the war against the Navy,
Luffy lost his brother Ace in the
War of the Best against the Navy
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy reached the Maiden Island...
Luffy made a raid on the Navy HQ
to rescue his brother,
Ace, who had been jailed,
...only to became depressed by
his own feelings of weakness.
lamented over his weakness but soon
realized the importance of friendship.
The King of the Pirates?!
and has come face to face
with Dark King Rayleigh.
only to see Ace killed right before his eyes.
What is it that you still have?!
Just then, Dark King Rayleigh
appeared before Luffy,
At that moment, Dark King
Rayleigh appeared before Luffy.
What are you gonna do, Luffy-kun?
Taken from the Navy HQ to the Maiden Island,
who was barely back on his feet.
the deeply depressed Luffy is now...
Meanwhile, the rest of the Straw Hats...
I have a suggestion for you.
Here's my second suggestion.
...have all gotten underway
Meanwhile, the rest of the Straw
Hats learned what happened to Luffy
in order to keep their promise
to each other and Luffy.
I'm too weak! I can't save anybody!
"Reunited with Dark King Rayleigh!
Decision Time for Luffy!"
and realized how hard it
must have been for him.
Okay.
"Back to Our Captain!
A Jail Break at the Sky Island and
the Incident on the Winter Island!"
I made up my mind.
Can't you see things clearly now?!
I'm gonna go back.
To Marineford!
"Encounter! The Great Swordsman Mihawk!
Zoro's Self-Willed Deadly Struggle!"
Don't just think about the ones you've lost!
CALM BELT
What?
You can't get back what you've lost!
"A Disaster for Sanji!
The Queen's Return to the Kingdom!"
What is it that you still have?!
Luffy-kun...
THE BAY AT THE CLIFF COAST
OF THE MAIDEN ISLAND
Th-This is a Navy ship #204.
He stopped screaming.
Luffy...
We demand permission to enter.
Now that you mention it, I
wonder where Straw Hat is.
You're right on time.
I didn't expect that...
Okay, may I have your code number?
Rayleigh, what are you saying...
He's gonna die if his wound opens up, right?
The code number is 5963.
Luffy?
I think that's what you and
your friends need the most.
Code number, confirmed.
Open the Gate of Justice.
I got one!
Yes, sir!
But don't you think what Luffy-kun
really needs now is...
Crank.
Alright, well done.
I still have...
This is the Gloom Island in the Grand Line -
GLOOM ISLAND
Luffy-kun, how are you feeling?
...to get his body and mind healed?
I still have my friends!
the ruins of Muggy Kingdom.
What's wrong?
I feel fine now. Not bad at all.
I think I just saw a fish...
I wanna see them now...
There remains an old castle
from the long-dead kingdom...
The former Warlord - "First
Son of the Sea" Jimbei!
But my friends will...
Th-That's big!
I wanna see them!!
which has been occupied
for several years now.
Yeah, I think they will
try to get to Sabaody.
The former first mate of
the King of the Pirates -
The news about you has spread
all over the world already.
I can't believe Moria-sama died in the war!
Dark King Silvers Rayleigh!
"Straw Hats in Shock!
The Bad News Has Reached Them!"
I bet it has reached your friends by now.
And Straw Hat Luffy! What do they want?!
Look! That's a huge Sea King!
Then, I have to see them...
Is it fighting?
I promised them. I gotta go.
This is the Gloom Island in the Grand Line -
GLOOM ISLAND
You're grating on my ears.
Go somewhere else and cry.
the ruins of Muggy Kingdom.
To Sabaody!
How heartless are you to say
that when somebody's devastated?
It's dead! It got killed!
Wh-What are they?
Say something nice and bring
me a cup of hot cocoa!
Meanwhile, in the Birdie Kingdom...
BIRDIE KINGDOM
--But it's huge!
--I couldn't see what did it!
...where the birds and the
humans have stopped fighting.
I'm your guest!
It's scary around here.
Are you really leaving now,
Racoon? We just became friends.
I never invited you.
Then, here's my second suggestion.
B-Baboons?!
You two were living here without
asking when I wasn't here.
Huh?
Huh?!
--A man?
--Hey! Who are you?!
Uh-huh, I read in the newspaper
about my friend's ordeal
And...
...this article is not credible.
What are they talking about?
Huh?! Then you don't think that
Moria-sama died in the war?!
so I wanna get back as soon as possible.
No idea.
Oh boy...
Meanwhile...
They don't look like they
can be reasoned with anyway!
D...
On the small Sky Island - Weatheria,
where scientists study the weather...
I can't believe what happened to...
I don't know if he's dead or alive
but at least in my memory...
D...
...Luffy's brother, who I met in Alabasta!
--Dark King Rayleigh!!
--What?!
I wanna see Luffy soon and
give him medical attention.
...Moria was alive on the battlefield.
Oh, it's you guys. We met
at Sabaody Archipelago.
He must've pushed himself as always.
If he's not dead, why did they say he is?
Racoon!
I'm glad that you and the
birds cleared the air!
I don't know.
He was the first mate of Roger,
the King of the Pirates!
That's because you risked
your life and talked to them.
Well, my ship sank in the storm
and I had no choice but to swim.
H-How did you get up?!
Three-Sword Style...
Well...
Stay in bed - you're useless!
You guys, live in peace with these humans!
Is it really true?
...Bull Demon...
Storm?! The Calm Belt is always
calm - it's never rough!
What do you plan on doing with those swords?!
...Courageous Talons!
That young girl...
All they want are the various
plants that grow on that tree!
There shouldn't be a storm!
...tried to escape from this island?
Are you going to push yourself again?
That means his ship wrecked further
away and he swam all the way here?!
You can't beat those baboons.
They'll kill you this time...
Yes, it's true.
That's right! We don't want your
eggs and we won't hurt you!
I have a good breaststroke.
Shut up!
It's none of your business!
That's not the point.
We're different from those who chased
you away from your home island!
Then, that Sea King was fighting with...
How could you say that to me!?
Can't you see that I carried
you all the way here?!
...you?!
Now that you mention it,
Where are you going, young girl...
Only a legendary pirate could do that!
the medicine that you make out of the
plants on that tree really works!
"Hawk-Eye"!
Oh no! There are more of them!
Oh, I'm sorry.
My wound healed already.
What are you sorry for?!
She suddenly disappeared
from the Weather Field
Of course it did! This medicine
is passed on from father to son.
See?! You can't even walk!
Oh yeah!
and showed up at the Balloon Terminal...
Why are you in such a hurry? You're wounded.
I assume Luffy-kun must
be here on this island.
To be honest, I wanna stay on
this island and study the plants!
They are...
Because you told me what happened to Luffy.
Please! Don't get in my way!
...using weapons like humans!
I'm sure there are ingredients unfamiliar
to me. But I don't have time.
Did you hear
How can I stay still!?
THE CENTER OF THE ISLAND:
THE FEMALE-ONLY EMPIRE AMAZON LILY
that Snake Princess-sama and the others...
Three-Sword Style...
He's still alive probably.
Come see us again!
...have just gone to deliver food to Luffy?
But I assume that he's been
very badly traumatized.
That's right! You're always welcome, Racoon!
I wanna stretch his body again!
Dragon Twister!
Then she hijacked a balloon
carrying a heavy load!
"Fire Fist" Ace...
They said they'll invite him
over when he gets better.
Yeah? I'm happy to hear that!
...died before Straw Hat's eyes.
However...
I can't wait!
I didn't even know that such
a huge war was underway!
When I see my friends, I'll
tell them about this country!
I didn't expect to see him again this soon!
What?!
Men are interesting!
Are you sure that Luffy's
okay?! Where is he now?!
And I'll come to see you all again!
If I could become a man, my body
would be stretchable like his!
What happened?! It's out of control!
Tell me more!
Take this. It's a long journey
and you'll get hungry.
I can't wait!
I told you everything that I know.
My wound from before has been reopened!
Thanks.
Come see us, Racoon!
Yeah, maybe I'll make
clothes for him again...
Damn! What's wrong with this balloon?!
Oh, cotton candy!
Then I'm sorry for bothering you.
...without frills!
Alright, guys, be nice to each other!
Ow, ow, ow...
Hey, wait!
Even if you can make it to the shore
without bumping into those baboons,
We're separated although we're newlyweds!
Goodbye, Racoon!
how are you gonna cross the sea?
Okay, I got a box lunch
and some cotton candy!
I feel like a tragic heroine!
Somebody stop this thing!
"But Hancock... No, my dear wife!"
I'm gonna head for the meeting spot now!
No!!
If you want a small boat,
It's coming this way!
there is one on the west side of this castle.
I don't have a pirate ship!
"Y-Yes!"
"No matter how far away from each
other we are, our love is forever!"
Run fast!
Even if I had one, I don't have a navigator!
Thank you for everything.
Move, move!
So I don't know how to get to Sabaody!
"Luffy!"
Oh, my sweet husband! My heart is aflame!
What the hell?!
Well, I'll just get on any ship...
No, then I'm gonna get lost!
You fool! I'm not gonna
care about you anymore!
Oh, what am I gonna do?!
Like I said before, Snake Princess,
I'll never ever save you!
Hey... Hey, are you breathing?!
R-Racoon...
just because someone hugs
you and uses your name,
Damn! I gotta fulfill my role as
the doctor of the pirates! Luffy!
Shut up... Don't distract me now...
And that's what happened.
it doesn't mean you are married.
Then, what counts as marriage?
How annoying!
I had no clue that she'd
do something like that.
Although you just lost your brother, Luffy,
Huh? What did you say?
How can you say that to someone
who's only worrying about you?
Hmmm... That's a difficult question.
Your father will give me a ride?
Why should I worry about
him in the first place?
I know you'll keep your promise!
Yeah, see you!
I wonder what made her do such a thing.
You can't go to Sabaody now with that wound.
That's why I'll get there,
too, at any cost...!
It's really high and fast!
But I wanna see my friends
as soon as possible.
I'll make it there in a matter of seconds!
CRIME
I have to be there just like I promised.
This is no good.
Huh? You can do better?
Let me out! I'll give you back what I took!
But...
I gotta go somewhere!
Hmm? The submarine is gone.
There you are!
Cool!
Hey, let me out of here already!
I knew you guys weren't
gonna let me go so easily.
It's like a roller-coaster!
Oh, Luffy-kun!
Oh yeah! Haredas-san... Call Haredas-san!
Huh?! The old guy Rayleigh!
Please!
I'm glad to see you this soon!
Why are you here?!
We won't let you out! We don't
know what you'd do next!
I was about to head to Sabaody
using the Vivre Card.
I feel sick... I got carried away...
Bull Demon Courageous Talons?!
How should we punish this young girl?!
Did you see my friends?
Hey, News Coo! Give me the newspaper!
A sentence of flooding or lightning?
No, I don't think they made it there yet.
You common cat burglar!
That was Dragon Twister!
I'll read it as I eat my lunch.
I gave my Vivre Card to Shakky...
They're imitating my
Three-Sword Style skills!
I won't do anything!
The information about the war
should be updated by now.
...in order to go anywhere I want.
Just let me out of here!
No way!
Yum!
Dark King Rayleigh! Is it really
you? I can't believe it!
Hey, hey! Hey, hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
You've got to be kidding me!
Oh, Mr. Haredas!
Hey, you idiots!
You must be the former Warlord...
Why?! What's going on?!
This energy...
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
What made Luffy do this...?!
He's Jimbei, he saved my life.
Hey, hey! Hey, hey!
How can you be so content to
copy somebody else's skills!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
What's wrong?
Hey! Hey, hey, young girl.
Well, I didn't expect to
see a living legend here.
Don't mess with me!
That's too much!
It's...!
Seems like you're really in a rage again.
Here. Isn't this hat important to you?
Damn! He can't mess with me!
It is. Thanks.
You're...!
Ta-dah!
Meanwhile, in the East Blue,
I've done so much for him!
This can help. Let me show you something.
"Hawk-Eye"...
EAST BLUE - ON THE GIANT BRIDGE--
Robin has been freed by the
Revolutionaries army and...
...Mihawk!
I hope he drops dead! That'd serve him right!
It doesn't feel right without it after all!
These are tightly tied Wind Knots!
Why don't you go and look if
you're so worried about Roronoa?
Meanwhile, in South Blue's Birdie Kingdom...
Have you seen a group of pirates here?
Mr. Haredas!!
No way! Why should I worry about that fool?!
BIRDIE KINGDOM
...where the birds and
humans are always fighting.
If you're talking about
Trafalgar Law, he just left.
I said "let me out"! You want
another one?! I'm in hurry!
Well, I don't think that
he'd die that easily.
--You saved me!
--Revolutionaries army, thanks for coming!
He said that you have to rest
in bed for 2 more weeks.
Don't eat me in a hot pot!
Look, he was already seriously injured
by the time Kuma blew him away!
Mr. Haredas! Can you hear us?! Mr. Haredas!
We caught the racoon again!
I'm glad!
Racoon! Racoon!
Robin!
He saved your life, didn't he?
I said I'm not a racoon!
Soran!
It's great. Can everybody
be free from now on?
Yes, this is Haredas...
So he could lose his life if he
fights against those baboons again.
She hit him rather than
talk to him! She's a devil!
Dad, he said he's not a racoon.
Yes.
What a waste! We got that far...
Damn! Damn! Oh, dammit!
Doctor! Call the doctor!
At least, you're not gonna be
forced to build the bridge.
That's ridiculous! A racoon can't talk!
I wanted to get in the female-only empire.
If he dies, I'll be stuck with this guy
I am talking! You need to
listen to your kid sometimes!
who has no interest in cute stuffed animals
They were allowing bears in.
Hey...
Shut up!
What?
Will you accept this?
I'm a reindeer and I can speak
like humans! And I'm a doctor!
I'm sorry.
and who won't bring me a
bagel sandwich and hot cocoa!
She stole Weather balls from the
Weather Field and our research notes?
So weak!
I wonder what the Dark King is up to.
That's ridiculous! A racoon can't talk!
I don't wanna be stuck with
that heartless "Hawk-Eye" guy!
As you see here, Mr. Haredas.
Whatever it is I'm sure that "D." will
cause quite a storm once again...
Dad, he's talking!
Young girl...
I can't stand it!
Can't wait to see him again.
Thank you, Soran.
I used to be a thief and I'm a pirate now.
You got it, finally? Then get me down now.
Oh, Rayleigh?! You must be Rayleigh!
You're leaving, aren't you, Robin?
Let me see your butt.
What's wrong with stealing?
Yes.
Oh, Gloriosa! It's been awhile!
She's the worst kind of human being!
Three Thousand Worlds!
Wow!
--Rayleigh!
--Ray-san!
This is a cream for burns.
We have such a villain in our country!
Robin!
Oh, you two are here too!
We make all kinds of medicine out of plants.
Can I see you again?
Like I said... I wanna
get out of this country!
Luffy!
Hey, Big Sis! How could you ignore
the man who saved your life?
Really? So you have other
kinds, too? Can I see them?
Let me out of here! I'm begging you!
You know the old man Rayleigh?
What are you...
We don't have them now.
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame...
I gotta go now! You got
back what I stole, right?
The plants we make medicine
out of grow on that big tree.
--Yes!
--It's a long story.
Admirable!
Hey, let me out!
Luffy, so you're awake now.
But the mean birds who made
their nest here a year ago
Don't get too close! She's very violent!
I haven't
slept for days worrying about you.
block us from going up to pick them.
You must be hungry. I brought some food.
We're running out of most medicines, so
the number of sick people is increasing.
So go ahead and dig in...
What's the matter with you all of the sudden?
Robin-san.
You can't even look at him.
Are you gonna head for Sabaody?
How could you call it marriage?
She's my friend.
Yes.
You tried to hijack the balloon and
go down to the sea, didn't you?
"The light of revolution."
Hey, are you alive?
Serve him...
This is...
I can't breathe.
Serve him a meal already!
We've called you that and searched
for you for more than 10 years.
Amateurs can't operate a
balloon. You could have died.
He must've gotten to the shore by now,
but I don't see any sign of him...
Her life is in danger.
We have no time to lose!
Jimbei! These are not for you!
Maybe he's lost again!
Let's put this to rest!
You're the only survivor from Ohara,
You were very eager to learn
the science of weather.
It's do or die!
the country that fought against the world.
You can have just a little bit.
This is war! Prepare for anything!
What happened to you?
O-Okay. Luffy-kun, why don't we just eat?
Oni...
When we find you,
Dad!
...giri!
we have to protect you from
the Government at any cost!
Son, take care of your mother!
Luffy-kun, you have to eat. Eating is living!
That's what the boss told us.
It's in that newspaper.
Boss?
Newspaper?
W-Wait a minute! Don't jump the gun!
The leader of the Revolutionaries
army - Dragon.
The "Luffy" in that newspaper
is the captain of our ship.
Stop putting spit on it! Where
did you learn that folk remedy?!
As a doctor, I can't just ignore sick people.
Luffy's father...
I'm gonna see the birds and tell
them to stop making trouble!
What?!
What a curious turn of fate!
Oh, it's this guy.
Really, Racoon?
These bastards, they really
make a fool out of me!
They said he caused quite
a stir in the previous war.
Don't worry. I can talk with animals.
I beg you again.
I'll never make it to the sea at this pace!
Please meet our boss! I'll take you to him.
He's a hot rookie with a Straw Hat.
That's it! That's my Luffy-kun!
And...
...don't make me repeat
myself! I'm not a racoon!
Oh, I never would have thought
that this boy was your captain.
I can't. I have to return somewhere.
Besides that, you don't need to protect me.
After his crew was separated,
"Hawk-Eye"...
Because I have friends.
It's been a while since you left the castle
Luffy must've been fighting
such a hard battle on his own.
and you've only made it this far, Roronoa?
Jimbei! I said "just a little bit"!
You mean the members of
the Straw Hat Pirates.
I got along with the cheeper.
The birds will understand me.
The boat that I gave you seems useless now.
Yes.
Then, let us give you a lift
part of the way at least.
And he took part in the War of the
Best in order to rescue Ace, and...
Shut up!
You can't see the end of this bridge
even if you walk for several days.
Racoon! It's not like I don't trust you
I'll just treat them like planks
and swim while hanging on to them.
Thank you for bringing me
the letter from Shakky.
but I don't think those mean
birds will listen to you.
Let us take you wherever you're going.
Sounds like she hasn't changed.
It's nice that you care about your
friend so much but they're strong.
...he saw Ace killed right before his eyes!
If anything goes wrong,
Yeah, she's just the way she was
when you were living in Sabaody.
We'll be able to unlock the
3rd and 4th prisons soon!
And I didn't even... know about it!
They're called Humandrills - baboons
that develop by imitating humans.
we have no choice!
She's doing fine.
Roger that.
These girls have become very beautiful
and strong over the past 13 years.
Humandrills?
Tell the others to get ready for
the release of the prisoners.
I know that Luffy will be there
They'd be peace-loving, if they
grew up around peaceful humans.
at the place where we promised to meet!
Yes, sir!
Can I ask you something?
Rayleigh, Shakky, Granny Nyon.
But on this island...
Before he is completely broken,
Anything.
What's up?
Why does the Revolutionaries army need me?
You three protected us when we were
running from the Celestial Dragons.
there was a war raging until 7 years ago.
I wanna see him and support him!
Th-That's because...
I'm here to talk to you.
When I came here to live, it still
smelled like blood and smoke
But we have a problem.
The humans in the forest have a big problem!
We should be providing shelter
for Luffy from the Navy.
You'll see several ghost towns before
we get to the end of the bridge.
and dead bodies littered the ground.
That's because the whole country
moved as the construction progressed.
Huh? "We won't let them have the treasure"?
Oh, hey, hey, hey, young girl!
Even though Rayleigh
knows Luffy from before,
These baboons were watching those
violent humans as they grew up
What do you mean?
Let her out now!
if it's easy enough for someone
to guess that Luffy's here,
For your information, the site
you see is from 300 years ago.
We're so violent! We abducted
a young girl and made her cry!
Racoon!
and learned how to use weapons and
became warriors of the forest.
we should be worrying.
W-W-Wait a minute!
Why are they building this bridge?
Huh?! What an old familiar face!
--Give the key to Mr. Haredas!
--The key, the key!
It's an order from the World
Nobles - Celestial Dragons.
You're Rayleigh, aren't you?
Humans can best animals by
using weapons and wisdom.
Here, you can come out now.
I'm sorry, young girl...
Celestial Dragons?
You just noticed?!
How mad are you about him?!
I don't care if there is a reason or not!
Ow, ow... Damn!
But when animals can use weapons,
they become this strong.
It wouldn't bring down the death
toll of those they call slaves!
No, I don't think the Navy
can guess that he's here.
Rumble!
They make great opponents
for an arrogant young man.
Arm Boost!
--Where did she go?
--I don't see Mr. Haredas, either.
First of all, the one who sent him away
Talking about me?
Did you see Straw Hat Luffy -
Dragon-san's son in today's newspaper?
There's no one else.
told me that he sent him in this direction.
It's almost sunset. Come to my castle.
What treasure?
They won't bother you there.
Yes. He went missing after the war,
Why do you hate humans that much?!
Huh? How did she make it that far?!
Kuma...
Don't tell me what to do!
but he showed up again and did such a thing.
I work for the Revolutionaries army.
You guys!
Thanks! Bye!
The talks broke down, Racoon!
We have to show this
article to Nico Robin now.
I've got to make it to the sea!
Since I have a connection with them.
Huh?! What the...!
I see. Do whatever you want.
I wanna let them get away from here.
She's worrying about him.
We have no choice!
She pretended to cry and now
she took Mr. Haredas hostage!
I don't think they got to the end yet.
Oh, I can't believe it.
And she took the stolen goods, too!
I don't care if they're warriors
of the forest or whatever,
And where's Monkey-chan now?
Oh, thank you!
--We can't let her get away!
--Catch her!
I have no time to waste now!
For you, Robin-san.
I don't know.
Weatheria's science of
weather  must be kept secret!
Luffy! I'm glad he's okay!
I'm gonna beat every one of them!
I'm sorry about my abrupt manner earlier.
Chase her!
Damn! Where has he gotten to?
I don't care where! Please
take me down to the sea!
Can I talk to you for a moment?
What is it? Is there something funny?
--That's impossible...
--Make it possible!
I don't have...
That's what I thought! He's still here!
...much time left.
Luffy! I know that you're okay!
Guard Boost!
Yes.
H-Hey!
Straw Hat should be...
I'm sorry!-- You've always supported us!
Racoon!
In the direction that Bartholomew
Kuma blew Luffy-kun away,
It's our chance to return the favor!
there is the Maiden Island.
Catch her! Don't let her get away!
That's not all.
I found out some interesting
information about the War of the Best.
Oh, young girl, you haven't
stop pretending to cry.
It's with regards to the prison break at
Impel Down by Luffy-kun and the others.
Shut up!
When I thought about how Luffy-kun was
able to infiltrate the great prison,
LAZY BONES ISLAND - HUNGERIA
On the Lazy Bones Island -
Hungeria in the Grand Line...
Damn!
Neither the humans nor the birds on this
island will listen to other people!
it dawned on me that Luffy-kun
What is Satan-sama doing?
must have stowed away on a
Navy ship with Hancock, but...
What happened to the ritual to
curse the Longarm Tribe to death?
Meanwhile, on Peachy Island---
It's so quiet.
Dammit!
Believe in him, everyone.
Kamabakka
Kingdom, the island for New Kamas...
Since Hancock hates both
the Government and men,
I'm sure that Satan-sama will deal
Meanwhile, on the Winter
Island Future Land Baldimore
I don't think that she'd
get on a Government ship,
the diabolic Longarm Tribe a bloody blow!
where the genius Vegapunk was born...
GRAND LINE PEACHY ISLAND - KAMABAKKA KINGDOM
especially not to help a man.
Are you the cheeper from the other day?!
Now, this part is all theoretical.
I said "Give me a ship!" I
have a promise to fulfill!
Everybody, thank you for waiting!
You got better!
But how about this?
Is the ritual finally over?
That's our Satan-sama!
I've wasted so much time fooling
around with you people!
Grandpa! Grandpa! Grandpa!
Say that Hancock fell in
love with Monkey-chan,
See, it's finished. As
long as you have this...
Geek! Geek! Geek! Geek! Geek!
Geek! Geek! Geek! Gee...
With that excuse, candy-chan,
Everybody! Listen to me!
you're just trying to
escape from this island!
everything makes sense.
I mean, god!
What is that?
...you'll be okay!
We won't let you do that!
What's wrong, Kitton?
Well... what is this?
Monkey-chan is a good-looking guy.
Yeah, that's absolutely right!
Well, the old man has become
another person again!
--That's...
--Oh, I know!
Of course, I wanna get out of this country
And if I were Hancock,
Huh?
He's like a demon this time!
that's completely devoid of women!
I'd give him refuge on the Maiden
Island to spite the Navy.
Listen, everybody!
Is there a ship?!
What is that ship there?
Satan-sama made us a talisman
Here he comes!
That's a very subjective theory, Shakky.
which enables us to curse
the Longarm Tribe to death!
I bet you put something strange
in his stomach, didn't you?
I-It's Ivan-sama! Ivan-sama is on it!
Huh?
I see!
With this talisman,
Women's intuition is unbelievable.
Like habanero juice or kimchi soda?
even the vicious Longarm
Tribe can't come close to us!
Looks like they came to an understanding.
Huh? Who is it?
--That's my Shakky!
--She couldn't be any more right, as you can see.
No, I didn't!
They'll die as soon they see it!
Hey, what's wrong? Is that person that great?
Yeah? You like it? Good!
Look, that's...
She's the queen of Kamabakka Kingdom...
--I see!
--That's our Satan-sama!
Now everybody, let's put these
talismans up in different places!
The Navy won't take action based
on a ridiculous theory like that.
...Emporio Ivankov-sama!
Hey, grandpa!
What?! That name was in...
I gotta go see my friend as soon as possible!
So this place is safe.
Oh no, look... It's not
something like that...
Listen! The birds had a
compelling reason, too.
Now, let's get down to business.
Give me a ship... A ship to take!
They like glittering things and they've been
Luffy-kun.
Ship?
collecting them from all over the world
You said you're gonna head
for Sabaody, didn't you?
No, I can't do that.
E-E-Excuse me! Everybody!
but some humans tried to steal them
She's the queer queen in
the newspaper?
Because we don't have a ship on this island.
and chased them away from their home island.
How timely!
They're all put up now!
She was with Luffy so I bet she knows a lot.
There is a liner that brings
us supplies once a month
Uh-huh, good job!
That's why they thought
I need to see my friends.
that humans will come after
them on this island again.
--We're safe now!
--Thank you very much, Satan-sama!
and Navy ships that come irregularly.
Is that what you really want?
--Um...
--Minister, we have a problem!
When is the liner due?
These are... the medical plants!
It's been awhile.
It just came a week ago.
Th-The Longarm Tribe is here!
Is that enough?
Can't believe it!
They're like moths to a flame.
Damn! I gotta wait for 3 weeks?!
If you have extra, put
some cream on me again...
Sh-She's my type!
The Longarm Tribe will be all gone by today!
No, wait, wait!
Racoon!
This country is surrounded by thick
ice. It's like a natural fortress.
She's here because she's a queer, too.
As I was saying, um, that's not a talisman.
I almost fell for it!
Sabaody Archipelago.
Who are you?
That's a musical score that I wrote!
In order to get here, you need an
ice-breaker with special equipment.
I-I am...
Remember what happened to
you guys on that island?
Huh?
It doesn't hurt!
What?!
Damn it all!
Her breasts are sticking out!
Her ass looks so tight!
I can build a new ship but
it'll take too much time!
No, I won't be fooled!
Here is a shiny thing for you!
We're dead!
Everyone focus on escaping!
You guys hit it off already!
Ol-Old man, you need to calm down.
Do you want something from me, candy boy?
They're gonna take what little food we have
As we are now, we can't beat these guys!
Oh, News Coo!
Yeah, I have a lot of
questions for you! First...
and men and women, and
do whatever they want...
Thank you for the newspaper!
...what's your favorite type of man?
We have no choice.
No, I mean, about Luffy!
No, you have a choice!
Let's see...
Good smell... Flavor!
Luffy? You mean Straw boy?
Satan-sama!
Bingo!
Everybody, listen to this song.
Meanwhile, on the small
Sky Island Weatheria...
So you were at the Navy
Headquarters with him!
WEATHERIA
I don't have any time for this!
Luffy, you're so lucky!
I have to get off of this island at any cost!
I mean, you guys must've been through a lot.
Tell me everything.
Gee, you need to use the
lower half of your body more!
I couldn't save even one of my friends...!
What is this song?
My lady...
Are you even trying, young girl?
It's filling my body with energy!
No, I'm not! What I wanted to
learn is the science of weather,
With all that he's going through now...
not field work! Do you understand?!
What the hell is this - some kind of spell?
What am I doing here?!
And who are you?
This is a part of the science of weather.
It's hard to tell what those people with just
Dammit! I knew it was coming! Screw you!
Damn!
This is the Weather Field
where we grow Weather balls.
one joint in their arms are thinking!
And how do you know Straw boy?!
Old man.
Seems like you have a good
reason but nothing can be done.
There's always some manual labor in science.
I'm one of his crew.
Ah? Who are you guys?
His crew?!
Damn! He should have told me that.
Do you think you can face those
tremendous powers as you are now?
From today on, we won't
allow you to abuse us!
--So this is a wanted poster of Straw boy.
--Yes, it is.
Oh, News Coo! You brought the newspaper?
Oh yeah!
Huh?
Thank you!
--We decided to fight!
--Yes! You won't take anything more from us!
And this is "Pirate Hunter" Zoro.
If I remember correctly,
Let's see how the weather's
gonna be tomorrow...
Don't know him!
there was an
ice-breaker developed by Vegapunk at his laboratory.
This is "Cat Burglar" Nami.
We're gonna protect our
things with our own hands!
Let me see it!
We're not afraid of anything!
This is "The King of Snipers" Sogeking.
He made it years ago, so I don't
know if it still works...
Uh-huh.
That's it!
BOWIN ISLANDS
On Bowin Islands in the Grand Line,
And this is you.
They look different from usual.
No! It's too dangerous!
I'm not gonna go this time.
No!
But I...
See?! You're not in these posters!
Usopp has been eating an
abundant variety of food
Do you want to be reunited with your
friends just to endure the same fate?
I don't know what's gotten into
them but... let's beat them up!
It's that place again...
Then there's no proof that
you're one of Straw boy's!
and gaining a lot of weight!
"Again"? Don't tell me
that you snuck in there!
Get them!
How do you like my body?
I told you that I am!
I have a suggestion for you.
You better stop eating'n! Usopp'n!
--Yeah, a while ago.
--Uh-huh, a while ago.
Tell me how is Luffy doing
now, you queer king!
What?!
Of course it's up to you to...
Thank you very much, king
of the devils - Satan-sama!
It's not muscle'n.
I can repair it! Because I'm a shipwright!
I know that you were with
him from the newspaper!
...do it or not.
It's visceral fat'n!
Oh no, that's not what I'm concerned...
Then, is this you?
You're gonna get a lifestyle disease'n!
I never even dreamed we'd be able
to put them in a cage one day!
I said that it's not...
Let's go back there now!
I don't care as long as I can get stronger!
It's not but it is...
Listen to me!
I don't know why but when I heard
the score that you wrote...
Meanwhile, on the Bowin
Islands in the Grand Line...
The name is mine.
GRAND LINE - BOWIN ISLANDS
Too cold!
He has no ear'n.
...Courage and strength welled up in my heart
Stop! Usopp'n!
--It's the newspaper'n!
--Ah, hop!
Why are you struggling so much?!
and I took up arms and fight
for the first time in my life.
Don't stop me, Heracles'n!
Grilled Chicken!
Usopp is...
Well, of course.
Don't eat that'n!
That's... me! That is me!
...shaking his body which has grown huge
We have an intruder!
It ended up not working and you're
the one who beat them up finally.
Someone's breaking into
Dr. Vegapunk's laboratory!
That weird guy on that poster
is definitely me so...
from eating an abundant variety
of food in the forest...
But the ones who were abducted
came back safely - thanks to you!
Don't use any firearms inside!
KAMABAKKA KINGDOM
On Peachy Island Kamabakka Kingdom...
...and running.
Remember that you're surrounded by
priceless treasures! Understood?
No no, I only helped a bit.
No, it looks nothing like you!
It's impossible'n!
Hey! Stop!
Then, don't make me say it!
Roger that!
No, it's not! That's why I'll try again!
Neither gods nor devils will help
those who won't fight on their own.
I threw up blood, you fool!
Stop!
I can do it this time!
It's no use.
Damn! I didn't expect Navy soldiers here!
What a beautiful sunset.
Even if it's only 0.1 %, as
long as there is a chance
Since we're in times like these,
I wanted to make sure that...
They tightened the security after I broke in!
that you're a puppet from
the Navy or Government
...you could stand on your
own against evils without me.
Oh, bird-san!
There you are!
Thank you!
I won't tell you any of the
information concerning Straw boy!
How merciful! I think we
can change from now on!
No, I shouldn't.
Get out of my way!
How's my love horoscope today...
I understand. Then let me borrow a ship.
I'm not gonna shoot!
Sure Kill...
Thank you very much, Satan-sama!
I'm gonna go to the meeting spot.
Don't let him get away! Go!
I think I did my duty by them.
Oh no'n! Usopp'n!
I won't give you a ship.
What's wrong?
Treasure? That laboratory?
Then, I'll swim!
Now... I can't believe that news.
What did you just say?!
What the hell is this?!
Yes, Vegapunk works for the Navy
as head of all the sciences
So you're not just saying
that you're his crew!
Luffy-san, I hope you're okay.
It's so heart-wrenching!
Are you okay, Usopp'n?
and we feel proud of him!
Damn...
At Tequila Wolf in the East Blue...
TEQUILA WOLF
I have no choice. You've touched my heart.
Well - I don't have a heart, but...
You can't do that. If you try
to get off of this island,
I mean, you can say that his
brain is a world-class treasure.
Luffy-san, let's sing a song together!
For the sake of your passion, I'll
tell you what happened to Straw boy...
Nico Robin, here...
terrifying living things
will stand in your way
This is where Vegapunk spent his boyhood.
I'm gonna make it there
to save your heart now!
and push you back to the forest'n.
Damn! I can't believe they
have a devil as a bodyguard!
...Or not! Heehaw!
Take a look at that mountain.
It has an odd shape, doesn't it?
If we could bring these unusual people
with just one arm joint back home,
--So you won't tell him?
--You fooled us there!
Ivan-sama!
It does when I come to
think of it... What is it?
Nothing will stop you from
entering the island'n
Shut up, you fools!
we could make a fortune by
putting them on display.
Thank you. How did you know my name?
That's something he made when he was a kid,
Now...
Damn...
but once you've set foot on it, you're dead!
to help the people in this
country from severe cold.
...these Longarm Tribe have
two joints in their arm.
Looks like his defenses are down!
All the soldiers in the Revolutionary
army know about you.
No one ever leaves this island alive'n!
Now is the chance! Dress him
up with the sweets dress!
We can make a fortune by
putting them on display!
And my name is Heracles'n!
He converted animals in the forest
into a work force and almost finished it
Could you trust us and come with us?
I'll never wear it again! Back off!
N-No, wait a minute!
You can't do that! It'd be treating
them the way they treated you!
Oh?! Usopp'n! Where did you go?!
but it's still incomplete.
I'm a true manly man who loves ladies!
It's an earth heating system that
will warm the whole island up.
Huh?
Stay away from me, fools!
I'm sorry, but I have to see my friends!
Everybody, listen!
Boo! Boo!
But as with many of his ideas,
It's very important to me.
What?! Letting them go?! Then
they'll attack us again!
Oh, he's in danger'n!
The sea creature has just
come onto the island!
Hey, so your name is Ivan, right?
I see. That's too bad.
he couldn't make what was in his head real.
Usopp'n is in danger!
No, they won't.
I decided to steal a ship
because I'm a pirate!
I made a devil's contract with them.
"Your friends" means the Straw Hats?
There wasn't enough technology
or money to make it happen.
You gotta fight me one-on-one!
The sweet scent from Bowin Islands
draws the attention of...
We got some information about them.
Listen, you three.
Alright!
But seeing him sad that he
couldn't make everyone happy...
Now, Ivan-sama,
If you break your promise with me
the grand master of Kamabakka
style - New Kama Kempo...
...giant insects and giant birds...
I'll tell you if you like.
and commit a wrongful act
in this country again,
...warmed our hearts.
...vs. "Black Foot" Sanji!
A 3 minute one-game match!
...and even sea creatures and Sea Kings.
Please. I'm very interested!
I'll eat your heart!!
It's a sea hippo!
Even her stand-in was very
strong. She must be formidable!
It's super tearjerking!
On the Winter Island Future Land Baldimore...
BALDIMORE DR. VEGAPUNK'S LABORATORY
--Thank you for letting us go!
--We're gonna go home right away!
I shouldn't get fascinated by it now!
Oh, is it?
I'll go all out from the start!
Cola up!
The scents lure them
deeper into the island...
We are always waiting for him to come home.
Fight!
Oh, I missed this feeling of it
circulating all over the body!
We'll never come to this country again!
Diable Jambe!
...where they find the
forest filled with food.
Premier Hachis!
Listen, you guys. Destroying and
stealing only generates hatred.
If you understand,
I didn't expect to see a mechanical
animal inside of the laboratory.
please don't ever go into
the laboratory with the self-destruct button.
It's easy to enter the island...
If somebody did the same in your
country, I'm sure you'd feel bad.
The mechanical polar bear...
What?
Wh-What a powerful kick!
Did you just throw out the name of
the most unwanted button in the world?
...hit me!
But it's hard to leave...
I-I should be strong but I'm gonna fall...
And the refrigerator that I crashed
into had a load of cola inside!
It doesn't matter if you have
one or two joints in your arms.
And I beat him!
I didn't know that.
Outta my way! Sure Kill - Exploding Star!
...gonna fall...
We're all the same! So let's
be nice to each other!
It ended up great!
Say old man, let's go home!
...fall...
...Or not!
Let's go home and drink hot tea!
Devil-sama!
I'm gonna get out of here!
I can't do that!
Heehaw!
What's that?
Don't get in my way!
Because that's the only place
that has an ice-breaker,
You're not gonna fall?! You got me there!
Here we go!
LAZY BONES ISLAND HUNGERIA
On the Lazy Bones Island Hungeria...
What?!
which I need to get off of this island!
I have to go back!
Why?! What's going on here?!
Seems like you're a staunch boy.
Let's go!
I have to do it!
But I think you need to be disciplined.
To Sabaody!
We don't believe in devils!
What?
I just learned the news
of my captain's ordeals.
New Kama Kempo: 44 - Aesthetic Technique!
You're strong but not so
strong when you get tied up!
Exploding Star!
How terrifying to hear
that voice of resentment!
Exploding Star!
Hair Removal Fist!
--If we bring back this skeleton that moves...
--...We can make a fortune!
Bye! Thank you for everything!
Exploding Star!
Satan-sama must be performing
a forbidden ritual
Exploding Star!
Wait! Don't ever push the
self-destruct button!
Exploding Star!
Wait a minute! I've got somewhere to go!
Death Wink!
to curse the Longarm Tribe to death!
Hell Wink!
Why would I, stupid?!
Satan-sama!
Usopp'n!
Galaxy Wink!
Why did he
put one in in the first place?!
It's a crisis! Satan-sama got kidnapped!
The islands are gonna move again!
I lost my concentration.
What?
Everybody, get ready to summon another devil!
It's getting more ominous!
That's right! We can call
devils with our underwear!
Usopp'n! Hang onto a tree!
Hey, I just saw somebody!
It's this way! Hurry up!
45 degree angle! Oh no, it's 60 degrees!
It's happening again?!
It's gonna eat something!
Luffy-san, just sing when you feel sad!
I got into an awful slump!
I'll tell you how Straw
boy is doing, Spiral boy!
Where's the ice-breaker?!
That's what musicians
are for! So wait for me!
Am I being punished for
seeing too many panties?
Stop!
Why did you change your mind?
Hey, somebody broke into the laboratory!
The name of this flower that
looks like an island is...
I will... I will be there!
This is...!
Because the whole world knows about it now.
Really? That's not good!
Luffy-san, Luffy-san, before that...
Even a blueprint from there is priceless.
I wonder what he is thinking.
Help me!!
You better not do that, Roronoa Zoro.
It's in today's newspaper?
Luffy!
Stop!
You've been injured beyond your limit.
Ivan-san, there is a call
for you from Baltigo.
I think I outran them.
Do you think you can beat me when
you can't even beat the baboons?
Oh yeah?
People call them the Bowin Islands
Go to the transmission facility.
but the scientific name is Stomach
Baron: a meat-eating plant!
To all soldiers!
GRAND LINE LAND OF WHITE SOIL - BALTIGO
What are you gonna do, Luffy-kun?
Because of the recent war,
Why the hell are you here?!
If you break something in the
genius Vegapunk's house while in pursuit...
R-Rayleigh, what did you just say?!
people know so much about you now, Dragon!
Usopp'n!
I've been living in that castle
quite a while. Why are you here?
--...it's a breach of the criminal code!
--Yes, sir!
Didn't it make your men upset?
--Weren't you listening?!
--That's not it!
I got blown away by Kuma, a member
of The Seven Warlords like yourself!
Looks like they're relieved to
know that their enigmatic boss
I can't understand your intent!
was a human after all.
It's all super brilliant! I can't believe
these are all from his younger days.
I see.
You know what's going on in Luffy's mind now.
What's the matter with you, Usopp'n?
It doesn't matter now.
Luffy is not a kid anymore.
That explains why Straw Hat
came to Marineford with other people.
But I can't believe that you were with him.
You changed since reading the
newspaper that News Coo brought!
Depending on your answer,
I won't be able to forgive you!
A lot of these ideas would need a couple
hundred years to implement fully.
You saw Luffy?! How was he?! Was he alright?!
It must be a trick of fortune, huh?
She's right!
They're right. As an engineer, I
don't wanna mess with anything here.
How dare you say a such thing,
He's still alive probably.
I...
But I assume that he's been
very badly traumatized.
knowing what happened to him?
Anyway, it was an unexpected
prison break for me and Inazuma.
...have no time to waste here now!
You're a harsh person.
I said that it's a "suggestion."
I have a lot of things I want to discuss
with you and even more questions.
What happened?
You must decide, Luffy-kun,
what you want to do.
Oh, it's a pirate mark!
Yeah, I bet.
He lost his brother.
We need to quickly summon our
commanders from all over the world.
Luffy lost his brother in the war!
The death of Whitebeard
No way!
I don't ever wanna let my friends...
He must be having a very hard time now!
will change the world situation
and the Government regime.
You can't be serious!
Oh my!
On top of that, I have to tell
you what happened to Kuma.
You must be kidding me...
...go through something like that again!
I can't believe this...
Yes, I want the details.
If I do as you told me to,
I can protect my friends?
What made him obey the Government?
What... did you say?
Can I ask you something? If I
push that button by any chance...
"Fire Fist" Ace...
The Kuma that I knew is gone now.
I think it's worth trying.
...died before Straw Hat's eyes.
Old man?
He tried to kill me!
But you should realize
you'll have a lot to do.
Is it gonna be my fault?
When your friend is having a hard time,
Oh, by the way, Dragon, have
you read the newspaper today?
Of course it is!
Luffy...
you should be there for him!
Straw boy has surprised me once again!
This incident on the Future Land
Okay.
Luffy!!
I made up my mind.
He's as wild as his father.
will be known around the world
as Baldimore's nightmare.
Luffy!!
I can't believe he did such
a thing in Marineford!
I'm gonna go back.
To Marineford!
The Navy HQ was heavily damaged
in the War of the Best.
After learning of Ace's death, Sanji quickly
prepares to return to the Sabaody Archipelago.
After hearing about the War of the Best,
Luffy's friends take
action, concerned for him,
Luffy decides to head for
the Sabaody Archipelago
Zoro races full-tilt toward the sea.
to fulfill his promise to
reunite with his companions.
but Nami is held captive by
the researchers of Weatheria.
Luffy returns to the place where he lost Ace,
Mihawk watches him approach with cool eyes.
But then, Queen Ivan-san returns home.
this time with Rayleigh
and Jimbei at his side.
Just then, the Dark King Rayleigh appears.
Meanwhile, on Winter Island, Franky heads to
a certain place in search of an ice-breaker.
What will come of their reunion?
The Kamabakka Kingdom erupts with joy!
As Luffy expresses his
surprise at their reunion,
The miraculous news would bring great shock
Meanwhile, Luffy sets a huge plan in motion!
What extremely dangerous
button has he found there?!
Rayleigh makes an even more
unexpected proposal...
Sanji finally gets to be a man again,
but a new danger is upon him!
to his friends, as well
as to the whole world!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Encounter! The Great Swordsman Mihawk!
Zoro's Self-Willed Deadly Struggle!"
"Back to Our Captain!
"Reunited with Dark King Rayleigh!
Decision Time for Luffy!"
"Unexpected Relanding! Luffy, to Marineford!"
"A Disaster for Sanji!
The Queen's Return to the Kingdom!"
A Jail Break at the Sky Island and
the Incident on the Winter Island!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!