ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made a raid on the Navy HQ
to rescue his brother,
Ace, who had been jailed,
only to see Ace killed right before his eyes.
Taken from the Navy HQ to the Maiden Island,
the deeply depressed Luffy is now...
I'm too weak! I can't save anybody!
Can't you see things clearly now?!
Don't just think about the ones you've lost!
You can't get back what you've lost!
What is it that you still have?!
I still have...
I still have my friends!
I wanna see them now...
I wanna see them!!
"Straw Hats in Shock!
The Bad News Has Reached Them!"
This is the Gloom Island in the Grand Line -
GLOOM ISLAND
the ruins of Muggy Kingdom.
Wh-What are they?
B-Baboons?!
What are they talking about?
No idea.
They don't look like they
can be reasoned with anyway!
Three-Sword Style...
...Bull Demon...
...Courageous Talons!
Oh no! There are more of them!
They are...
...using weapons like humans!
Three-Sword Style...
Dragon Twister!
What?!
My wound from before has been reopened!
Hey... Hey, are you breathing?!
Shut up... Don't distract me now...
How annoying!
How can you say that to someone
who's only worrying about you?
Why should I worry about
him in the first place?
This is no good.
This energy...
It's...!
You're...!
"Hawk-Eye"...
...Mihawk!
Meanwhile, in South Blue's Birdie Kingdom...
BIRDIE KINGDOM
...where the birds and
humans are always fighting.
Don't eat me in a hot pot!
We caught the racoon again!
Racoon! Racoon!
I said I'm not a racoon!
Dad, he said he's not a racoon.
That's ridiculous! A racoon can't talk!
I am talking! You need to
listen to your kid sometimes!
I'm a reindeer and I can speak
like humans! And I'm a doctor!
That's ridiculous! A racoon can't talk!
Dad, he's talking!
You got it, finally? Then get me down now.
Let me see your butt.
Wow!
This is a cream for burns.
We make all kinds of medicine out of plants.
Really? So you have other
kinds, too? Can I see them?
We don't have them now.
The plants we make medicine
out of grow on that big tree.
But the mean birds who made
their nest here a year ago
block us from going up to pick them.
We're running out of most medicines, so
the number of sick people is increasing.
She's my friend.
This is...
I can't breathe.
Her life is in danger.
We have no time to lose!
Let's put this to rest!
It's do or die!
This is war! Prepare for anything!
Dad!
Son, take care of your mother!
W-Wait a minute! Don't jump the gun!
As a doctor, I can't just ignore sick people.
I'm gonna see the birds and tell
them to stop making trouble!
Really, Racoon?
Don't worry. I can talk with animals.
And...
...don't make me repeat
myself! I'm not a racoon!
I got along with the cheeper.
The birds will understand me.
Racoon! It's not like I don't trust you
but I don't think those mean
birds will listen to you.
If anything goes wrong,
we have no choice!
What's up?
I'm here to talk to you.
The humans in the forest have a big problem!
Huh? "We won't let them have the treasure"?
What do you mean?
Racoon!
W-W-Wait a minute!
Ow, ow... Damn!
Rumble!
Arm Boost!
What treasure?
Why do you hate humans that much?!
You guys!
The talks broke down, Racoon!
We have no choice!
Guard Boost!
Racoon!
Damn!
Neither the humans nor the birds on this
island will listen to other people!
Dammit!
Are you the cheeper from the other day?!
You got better!
Everybody! Listen to me!
I see!
Looks like they came to an understanding.
Listen! The birds had a
compelling reason, too.
They like glittering things and they've been
collecting them from all over the world
but some humans tried to steal them
and chased them away from their home island.
That's why they thought
that humans will come after
them on this island again.
These are... the medical plants!
Is that enough?
If you have extra, put
some cream on me again...
Racoon!
It doesn't hurt!
Here is a shiny thing for you!
You guys hit it off already!
Oh, News Coo!
Thank you for the newspaper!
Let's see...
Meanwhile, on the small
Sky Island Weatheria...
WEATHERIA
Gee, you need to use the
lower half of your body more!
Are you even trying, young girl?
No, I'm not! What I wanted to
learn is the science of weather,
not field work! Do you understand?!
This is a part of the science of weather.
This is the Weather Field
where we grow Weather balls.
There's always some manual labor in science.
Damn! He should have told me that.
Oh, News Coo! You brought the newspaper?
Thank you!
Let's see how the weather's
gonna be tomorrow...
Let me see it!
BOWIN ISLANDS
On Bowin Islands in the Grand Line,
Usopp has been eating an
abundant variety of food
and gaining a lot of weight!
How do you like my body?
You better stop eating'n! Usopp'n!
It's not muscle'n.
It's visceral fat'n!
You're gonna get a lifestyle disease'n!
I don't care as long as I can get stronger!
He has no ear'n.
--It's the newspaper'n!
--Ah, hop!
Grilled Chicken!
Don't eat that'n!
KAMABAKKA KINGDOM
On Peachy Island Kamabakka Kingdom...
Hey! Stop!
What a beautiful sunset.
Oh, bird-san!
Thank you!
How's my love horoscope today...
What's wrong?
What the hell is this?!
At Tequila Wolf in the East Blue...
TEQUILA WOLF
Nico Robin, here...
Thank you. How did you know my name?
All the soldiers in the Revolutionary
army know about you.
Could you trust us and come with us?
I'm sorry, but I have to see my friends!
It's very important to me.
I see. That's too bad.
"Your friends" means the Straw Hats?
We got some information about them.
I'll tell you if you like.
Please. I'm very interested!
On the Winter Island Future Land Baldimore...
BALDIMORE DR. VEGAPUNK'S LABORATORY
Cola up!
Oh, I missed this feeling of it
circulating all over the body!
I didn't expect to see a mechanical
animal inside of the laboratory.
The mechanical polar bear...
...hit me!
And the refrigerator that I crashed
into had a load of cola inside!
And I beat him!
It ended up great!
What's that?
LAZY BONES ISLAND HUNGERIA
On the Lazy Bones Island Hungeria...
How terrifying to hear
that voice of resentment!
Satan-sama must be performing
a forbidden ritual
to curse the Longarm Tribe to death!
I lost my concentration.
It's getting more ominous!
45 degree angle! Oh no, it's 60 degrees!
I got into an awful slump!
Am I being punished for
seeing too many panties?
This is...!
You better not do that, Roronoa Zoro.
You've been injured beyond your limit.
Do you think you can beat me when
you can't even beat the baboons?
Why the hell are you here?!
I've been living in that castle
quite a while. Why are you here?
I got blown away by Kuma, a member
of The Seven Warlords like yourself!
I see.
That explains why Straw Hat
came to Marineford with other people.
You saw Luffy?! How was he?! Was he alright?!
He's still alive probably.
But I assume that he's been
very badly traumatized.
What happened?
He lost his brother.
No way!
You can't be serious!
Oh my!
You must be kidding me...
I can't believe this...
What... did you say?
"Fire Fist" Ace...
...died before Straw Hat's eyes.
Luffy...
Luffy!!
Luffy decides to head for
the Sabaody Archipelago
to fulfill his promise to
reunite with his companions.
Just then, the Dark King Rayleigh appears.
As Luffy expresses his
surprise at their reunion,
Rayleigh makes an even more
unexpected proposal...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Reunited with Dark King Rayleigh!
Decision Time for Luffy!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!