Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm the man who'll be
King of the Pirates!!
Hm...? What's that?
I've been looking all over for you, Sanji!
It's a "guiding light." The entrance to
the Grand Line lies ahead of that light.
Hey! There's a flock of birds to starboard!
Hm?
Ah! My hat!
A storm is coming.
An unimaginably big storm is...!
Alrighty!
For ten years!
Wait!
Gum-Gum...
In order to find the All Blue!
Wait, hat!
...Grab!
In order to be King of the Pirates!
Hold on a sec... Hey!
Out of our way!
In order to become
a master swordsman!
Her name is Carmen.
Good! My hat!
She's the No. 1 cook in the East Blue.
In order to draw a world map!
I'm... dead.
Hm?
I'm a woman of passion!
People call me Fiery Carmen.
Hey, look.
I-In order...
It's a girl!
Wow! So this is the scenery
that the King of Pirates saw...
...to become a brave warrior of the sea!
Ole!
We're going...
And, I'm Carmen-sama's
first apprentice, Leo!
Wow...
Ugh!
I'm her second apprentice, Jose!
Finally... Finally the time
for revenge has come.
...to the Grand Line!
Just wait, you damn Straw Hat!
A wind is coming.
A strong wind is...
"Precursor to a New Adventure!
Apis, a Mysterious Girl"
He finally showed up...
Took him long enough.
"Fiery Cooking Battle?
Sanji vs. The Beautiful Chef"
I'm still alive after all.
Please wait... Captain Smoker!
I got lucky.
Come with me, Tashigi.
Are these all coincidences?
I feel like this ship hasn't
been moving at all for a while...
Yes, sir!
Wow! How beautiful you are!
Ah!
It's as if heaven is trying
to let that man live.
Dammit...!
We've entered the Calm Belt!!
Say what?!
To think that you've looked all over
for me...! What a lucky man I am!
--Charm Belt?
--What the heck is that?
We'd better hurry
or we'll be in trouble!
"Buggy's Revenge! The Man Who
Smiles On The Execution Platform!"
We're gonna make it to
the Grand Line like this!
Calm Belt! It's an area of sea
where nothing moves a muscle!
Hey, it's meal time.
"Nami grew her muscles"?
Hm?
Idiot!
I'm honored to meet you, Carmen-san!
Hey, someone's on
the execution platform!
She's gone?! Hey! Where're you?!
Where're you hiding?!
"The Legend Has Started!
Head For The Grand Line"
Who the heck is that?
Don't you dare...!!
Hey! It's no use!
It's storming outside!
That old man said
that it was 22 years ago
Just come out!
that the King of the Pirates died here...
What was that? An earthquake?
Earthquake? On the sea?
What a passionate woman you are...
Ouch!
You guys, enough chit chat!
B... But, Carmen-san,
have we met befo...?
Ow, ow, ow...
Hey you over there!
Fold the sails and start paddling now!
Hey!
I'm telling you, you can't escape.
Put the ship back on its earlier path!
Jose!! Leo!!
Okay, Nami-san!
If you stay put, we won't
do anything to you.
Come down right away!
What're you panicking about?
Paddling? This is a sailboat.
Explain it to him.
Why?!
No! Let me go!
Yes, Ma'am.
That's a special execution platform
under control of the World Government!
Inherited will...
He's right. Why're we taking
the trouble to go back
Please have a look at this.
--Hey, calm down!
--What're you doing?!
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
Hm? What're these?
to where the Navy is waiting for us?
What?! What?!
Come down right now!
Just do what I say!
We're in big trouble!
These things cannot be stopped.
They're all cooks...
Well, you don't have
to be so strict, officer.
Well, the sea is quiet.
Yes!!
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
Yeah.
They're all famous,
skilled cooks in the East Blue.
All right, fine! Then I'll
explain it for you! Listen up!
these things will never cease to be!
If you don't come down,
I'll just arrest you. I'm coming up now!
Since we rushed and ran away,
we came further south than we planned!
Every single one of them competed
against Carmen-sama and lost.
A pirate, huh? Fine by me.
Hmph! Now's not
the time for small fries.
That's right! I'm the
No. 1 cook in the East Blue.
Then did we enter the Grand Line?
The girl escaped!
All right!
Search the whole ship!
Hm?
What's with this storm?!
If it was that easy, anyone could enter!
I've been looking for you, Luffy.
Long time no see...
Take her into custody
as soon as you find her!
If we don't leave soon,
we'll be stuck here.
She's still a child.
Don't be rough on her!
Nami-san was right when she said
we should hurry back to the ship!
Look. The Grand Line is
running between two sea areas!
Run! Run! Run!
Huh?
Do you get it?
Don't tell me you forgot my face...
Special Move:
My Carnival of Colors!
The area on both sides of
it is called the Calm Belt.
Those cooks who challenge me
are all disappointing cowards.
Ow, ow, ow...
There she is!
Capture her!
The reason is unknown but in these areas,
there's no wind and no current.
--How beautiful...
--She's so pretty!
She is a woman of unrivaled beauty!
Hey! Hold it!
I thought that I no longer had
any rivals in the East Blue.
They're an area of sea with complete calm.
Her skin looks very smooth.
Pardon me!
Sailboats run by catching winds,
so it's an extremely dangerous area,
I don't know anyone like you.
Who the heck are you?
However...!
Attacking me is a waste of time.
indeed, a fatal area, for them!
Luffy, did you get it?
There isn't a man alive
who can touch my smooth skin.
I'll never forget you...
because you're the first man who hit me.
Yeah. At least that we're in trouble.
I see. Good, you got more than I thought.
--It's dangerous!
--Come down!
I came across a feature on
the Sea Restaurant Baratie
So this is what the geezer meant
when he said it was dangerous...
What? I hit you?
from when you still worked there.
For a second there,
I saw a field filled with flowers.
No wonder there hasn't been any wind.
That cook said that the Sous Chef
there is the No. 1 cook in the East Blue.
You're alive, Captain Buggy.
We can't do anything
if the ship doesn't move.
When your passionate
fist hit me that time...
No way I'd die!
We can just wait until
the wind starts blowing.
Buggy, this isn't good!
Like I said, once you're in
this area, wind never blows
Gum-Gum...
They're marines from headquarters.
There'll be no end to them!
He said that you were an excellent cook
and that we were no match for you!
Pistol!
no matter how long you wait!
And, that's not all!
Humph. I could care less if the
marines want to stick their nose into...
We can't have the sail
unfurled like that in this storm!
There's another reason that
people call this area dangerous!
Whose nose did you say is sticking out?!
I didn't say anything like that!
In this area...
Ah! Another one!
Oh, it felt good...
What's going on?
What're we going to do?
Something is coming this way.
Gum-Gum! Go after Gum-Gum!
Since then, I've kept
looking all over for you...
Mohji and Richie should have
burned down his ship by now.
You guys... what's the most
beautiful thing in the East Blue?
searching every nook and cranny
of the East Blue... for ten long years...!
He can't get off of this island.
We'll kick his ass and
leave this island, guys!!
Please protect me, Grandpa Ryu.
It's actually been ten days, though...
Here they are!!
That'd be you!
Yeah!!
Wh-What're you going to do?!
Motor!!
Carmen-sama likes to exaggerate.
Ahhh! It's dangerous! Stop it!
That's right. It's me.
Yes, Captain!
Huh...? What's that?
There's no man in this world that
doesn't bow before my beauty.
Chop-Chop Buggy! Here we go!
Keep your big mouths shut!!
Igniting the bomb engine!
And I like strong men.
I challenge you, Sanji!
Set the slope!
I'll make you mine, Luffy.
They're huge!!
Come to the Cooking Championship
at the market at one this afternoon!
Yes, Big Sis Alvida!
No friction...
Shut up! No way!
Who the heck are you?
I'll defeat you for sure at
that championship! Got that?!
You still haven't figured it out?
Smooth-Smooth Tracks!
The Calm Belt is the
nest of the Sea Kings.
This is the police!
Hey, woman, come quietly!
Idiots! What is this report?!
Moreover, the ones here are super huge!
You're under arrest for
harming the police captain!
They're another reason why
people can't cross the Calm Belt.
Don't let the pirates get away!
That girl may be a clue to the Dragonite
that I've spent years searching for!
And you over there!
Get off the execution platform!!
Oh? Who'd you say you'd arrest?
"Miraculous Creature! Apis's Secret
and the Legendary Island"
Don't you realize how serious this is?!
Y-You!
Wh... What's this smoke?!
Y-Yes, sir!
Are you capable of that?
What're we gonna do now?
Eric!
What the hell...?!
Well, then! We'll see you later!
F-For the time being, no one move.
I've been here all along.
White Out!
I can't lose a clue to the elixir of
immortality after I've finally found it.
Ah, Carmen-san...
What a passionate woman she is!
A-Asst. Captain, this is a problem!
She's beautiful!
They'll probably go back
into the sea eventually.
Then we'll paddle hard using our oars.
So what?! We'll arrest her!
Smoker!
Young man, are you going to
participate in the competition?
Go join my fleet and find her
no matter what it takes.
Are you serious?!
She's so beautiful
that she's dazzling!
I don't have time for you, small fries!
Idiot!
Huh? No, I'm not interested
in things like that, so...
Good for you!
With all due respect,
H-He's too strong!
Sorry.
tracking down someone
wasn't in the contract.
So that's the power
of Plume-Plume Fruit...
Terrorist bombing!!
He took down Buggy's
gang in a split second...
A frog is coming!!
It's heading straight for her!
I'll pay you however much you want.
Fire!
I hired you for a time like this.
Wh-What the...
What?! What?! What?!
The fountain slipped!
Losing a clue now will be a blow
for you as well, will it not?
Oh, no!
What just happened?!
Captain! He caught
us all in one fell swoop!
That was dangerous, you know.
Now, go!
How dare you, Smoker!
Flashily sorry. But your smooth skin
is unharmed, of course. So don't worry...
What's with this annoying steel net?!
Firing a weird pistol like that...
Understood, Your Excellency,
Commodore Nelson Royal.
Damn...! That damn
detestable Straw Hat!
That was a "Cage Shot" developed by
the Navy to deal with Devil Fruit powers.
To think that we can't find him despite
looking all over for him like this...
Y-Your arm is stretching!!
...beautiful lady Alvida.
Dammit!
Luffy! Do you have
the power of a devil fruit?!
But Captain, why in the heck do
we have to wear cloaks like this?
Huh? Alvida?
Bring my Billower Bike here!
We'll go after Straw Hat!
Nami! Aren't we in the Grand Line yet?
Yeah, that's right.
Yes, sir!
Don't you know anything
about being a pirate?!
I don't see Alvida.
We just left Loguetown two days ago.
I'm Alvida! You blockhead!
This is heavy!
There's an annoying Navy captain
named Smoker in this town.
The Going Merry is in danger!
It'll take a few more days.
Wait a little longer.
Luffy!
Really? You don't
look like Alvida at all...
The Navy might be
already heading toward it!
If he finds us, my plan to get revenge
on that Straw Hat will be ruined!
Stretch your arm downwards again!
We have to get out as soon as possible!
Okay!
Hey, Luffy!
Nami! Nami!
Can't I just ditch this thing?
I changed after eating a devil fruit.
The name of the fruit is...
What nice weather!
Anyhow!
What're you doing?!
No, you can't! Run faster!
That storm seems like a dream.
Hurry up and find that Straw Hat!
I knew you'd say that.
I don't know.
Got that?!
Smooth Smooth Fruit!
Man, I'm stuffed!
Apis!
No attack can hurt my skin
because it slides off it.
Watch out!!
We have to eat good
before we leave Loguetown.
Dammit! What's with
this sudden downpour,
Hm...?
One, two...
What the heck is that?
I was starving.
when we have to burn down this ship?!
Hey! I see a flock of birds to starboard!
Unfortunately, my beauty
couldn't be improved that much, though.
To be honest, so was I.
I was hungry, but I didn't have money.
What did she just do?!
--A flock of birds?
--Yeah.
One big change was...
yes, my freckles are gone.
She pulled his nose hair.
Dammit! This is bad, Richie!
We can't get a fire going like this!
I also see something
kind of big on the water...
I'm glad that I ran into you.
Hm? If you mean money,
I don't have any.
I can't see it well.
I wonder what it is.
N-No, that's not really what I meant.
One more time!
--Maybe a fish?
--A small boat...?
Hold on a sec...!
After becoming a new person,
If you do that...
--What?!
--You don't have money?
It could be a big fish, too, but...
Be patient, Richie! I'll feed you later.
I joined forces with him since we
had the same goal-- finding you.
He's gonna sneeze!
Of course I don't!
I often hear that
seabirds flock above fish.
Ahh...
What're you doing?!
Fish?!
Luffy! Let's have them for lunch.
That's true.
Mohji!
That's a huge nose hair!
Alrighty!
But, really... that Straw Hat
is an annoying bastard!
Gum-Gum...
Oh, it's you, sneak thief woman.
All right! We're going back!
Now, the ultimate star
appears super flashily!
Grab!
Go, Richie!
Next time I see him, I'll crush him!
Whoa! Now that's a stretch!
What?!
Then how're we going to pay for this?
Monkey D. Luffy!
His body sure is convenient.
Do it some other way!!
Since the day you blew me off, I've
been obsessed with revenge on you.
I can't let him off the hook!
Amazing! I feel like we're flying!
I wonder if they'd let us off the hook...
Special Attack: Fresh Egg Star!!
I caught it!
There's no way I can!!
Idiot!!
That alone led me to finally find my crew.
We are flying!!
It's pretty big!
It was indeed a great adventure.
I was missing parts of my body.
Nice, Luffy!
H-Hold on a second...
What're you gonna do now?
You...
Oh, lucky!
Laughs. Hell. Friendship. It was
tiny Buggy-kun's great adventure.
Damn! The rain made my hand slip!
Hey, you're going to treat us? Thanks!
Looks like we're back
in the area we came from.
Richie!! You're such a...!!
I don't see any sign of the Navy, either.
Ahhh...
But Buggy-kun was...
Oh... Sorry, Zoro.
Why am I telling you
a story, you bastard?!
Ahhh... I thought I was a goner.
Dumbass!!
What? Well, what was your name?
Thanks again!
Now! Let's get on the ship!
--Good job!
--Yep!
I'm gonna... cut him down... someday...
Yeah!
Boggy? No, Boogie?
No, Behie... isn't right...
Okay! Unfurl the sails!
Hold it! You have to get past me!
Thanks for treating us.
Our destination is...
You're... welcome...
Of course...!
Oh yeah! It's Buffoon!
Hey, look. That's no fish.
I'm Mohji, Vice-Captain of
the Buggy the Clown Pirates!
Thanks for coming!
Warship Island!!
Thanks!
It's a girl!
I won't let you take
one step on this...
Oh? Is she a fishperson?
Where's her web?
We can't see anything.
That voice...?!
Buffoon?! Stop messing around!
Well, we can see the fog.
Oh, yeah! It was that Straw Hat guy.
You idiot. Just how does
she look like a fishperson?
Apis, is it really around here?
Prepare to fire!
You sure haven't lost
your nerve, you moron!
Not sure.
The Navy!
Why was a little girl in
a small boat like that...?
Uhh... Anyone home...?
"Not sure"? You...
I-It's Buggy the Clown!
This is bad!
It should be close by.
Aim!
You flashy idiot!!
Go after him already!!
P-Pirates!!
That's our Nami-san!
It's the Buggy Pirates!!
Fire!
You sure know your stuff.
Yes, sir!
Wh-Which way did he go?
Ah...! Look!
People! Remain flashily where you are!
Huh?
Contact the cannon unit!
We'll capture the pirate ship!
Oh! It's a sailboat! It's huge!
I'll show you good how scary I am.
Yes, sir!
Ouch!
--N-N-N-Nami!!
--Yeah!
So you've come to?
Now listen here...
Seems you're doing
better than I expected.
The word "huge" doesn't
begin to describe it.
Does it hurt anywhere?
Oh! It's Buggy!
Then, a super humongous sailboat?
You just remembered it?!
You must be hungry.
I'm cooking soup right now.
A market, huh?
No!
Lucky!
That's Warship Island.
Wh-What's going on?
Were you in a ship wreck or something?
It's shaped like a warship,
so it's called Warship Island.
Long time no see, rubber man.
Is Roronoa Zoro well, too?
Which direction is the sea?
You could've been in big trouble.
What's your name?
I can't tell where we're going
because of this heavy rain!
I see! Interesting!
When you ask someone questions,
you should give your name first.
Whoa!
There they are!!
Okay, Cabaji. Good job.
Just as you'd expect from Loguetown!
What persistent bastards!
Should we stop and fight?
They have far better quality and more
kinds of seafood than other places!
Good point. My name is Nami.
Ah! That flag is...!
We don't have time for that.
To my several hundred billion
servants around the world! Look!
The one who's cooking soup
in the kitchen is Sanji.
Pirates!
Oh?
Hm?
Hi!
Who's that lady?!
The one with a scary face
wearing a bellyband is Zoro.
Pirates!! Pirates have come!!
We'll now super flashily
start the open execution!
This is premium!
Shut up.
Hm?
Pirates?
You have a good eye, young man!
The one who's unconscious
over there is Usopp. And...
Stay inside!
Monkey D. Luffy! You can
no longer move even an inch.
Those're coastal fish
caught just this morning.
I didn't realize you're Roronoa Zoro,
and a pirate to boot.
I'm Luffy. I'm the captain
of this pirate ship.
Coastal fish?
You gonna take this sword, too?
You feel honored, Straw Hat?!
What?!
It's true that they're firm and fresh,
but I've never seen fish like this before.
You can die in the same place
the King of the Pirates died.
Pirates?!
You... You lied to me!
We're heading to the Grand Line.
Were they really caught in the East Blue?
What?! What'd you do to her?!
Hmm... You're really knowledgeable.
You didn't ask my name. That's all.
What's wrong?
She isn't moving.
As you noticed, these're fish that
you can catch only in the West Blue.
It's not that I lied to you.
What're we gonna do with this kid?
Ahhh, well, what should we do?
Hi! I'm home!
A rogue like you can't be
allowed to own a renowned sword!
The atmospheric pressure
is dropping abnormally.
Apis...!
It's just expected that East Blue
people don't know this fish.
I've never seen such
a bizarre drop before.
Why are you coming out
from the pirate ship?
Let's think about it tomorrow.
West Blue? Why do you
call them costal fish then?
I'll collect your sword,
the legendary Wado Ichimonji!
Why?!
What's going on?
Now that you mention it,
I feel a strange wind...
Why? Why? Why? Why in the heck?!
Young man, I bet you've
never been here before.
Say, you guys...
Try it.
A storm is coming... to this island!
I went through all that trouble and did
scary things to escape from the Navy!
Wh-What?!
Huh? Yeah...
A-A storm?
It may be because Loguetown is
the closest town to the Grand Line,
Is there a BBQ restaurant on this island?!
We'd better hurry back to
the ship or we'll be in trouble.
Of all things, why did I get
picked up by a pirate ship?
--Is it a pretty big one?
--Hey...!
Huh?
but we can sometimes catch fish from the
other seas, in addition to the East Blue.
--Hm?
--Zoro!
Wh-What's this guy?
Have you seen him?
Listen! They're pirates,
but they're good ones.
This isn't funny!
You mean Luffy?
From the other seas...?
Yeah... We got separated.
--Are there really good pirates?
--Yes!
That's right. They probably get
mixed in crossing ocean currents.
I also feel something strange...
In any case, I'll think about
it after I eat something.
Weren't you taken away by
the Navy in the first place?
I see...
...like... something terrible
is about to happen...
That's something that often happens here.
Hm?
That's right. But I escaped.
Oh... sounds like they caught something.
You jerk! How dare you attack a lady!
And these guys, Luffy and
the others, saved me. Right?
Wanna go see it?
--Pirates're here!
Ouch...
--Please don't interfere!
--What?
What's going on?!
--Pirates're here!
--Run!
--It's Buggy the Clown!!
This is the fight between Roronoa
and me! There's no need to step in!
Yeah.
What'd you do, Apis?
Wha...?! This is...!
You again?
What?!
You never learn no matter
how many times I tell you, Luffy.
We don't know why, but the
Navy was looking for you.
You heard her. Go on ahead.
Buggy the Clown!
Can't you get it
through your thick skull?
You should stay away from your home.
Let's go.
They're still around.
Hm? What're you doing?
What am I gonna do?
Hey, Zoro! If you hurt the
lady, I won't forgive you!
What? Then...
We'd like to help, but...
Y-Yes! In addition to Straw Hat Luffy,
Buggy the Clown and Iron Club Alvida,
Yum!
Amazing! That's an
elephant bluefin tuna!
If you ask, I'll make something for you.
Sergeant Major Tashigi!
...they're pirates, right?
So, like I told you,
don't take food without asking.
That's right! It probably got
mixed in from the southern ocean.
Ahh, what should we do?
all notorious pirates in the East Blue,
are taking over the square!
But I'm hungry.
Like she said, we're good pirates.
I caught it with a pole and line!
Apis!
What's wrong? Aren't you eating?
A pole and line?!
Come to my house!
Right under my nose...
You didn't eat this afternoon, either.
Elephant bluefin tuna...
Why're you holding back?
What impudent jerks...
I'm telling ya, it's not
poisoned or anything.
What should we do,
Captain Smoker?
Ah!
--Who's that?
--Don't know.
Look at this!
It's a weird looking fish!
Send Unit #1 to the sea.
If you just sit there like that,
he'll finish everything.
Grandpa Bokuden!
Unit #2 is to secretly surround
the square from the streets.
What're you doing with the illustrated
food reference book? Studying?
If you're not eating, I'll eat it!
I'm glad you're safe.
And have the rest stand by within
shooting range of the square.
--No!
--Huh?
Thank you for saving Apis.
That's the elephant bluefin tuna.
--That's all.
--Yes, sir!
How about this? I'd like to throw
a small welcome party for you.
What? You know this fish?
Yum!!
--Give this order to Unit #1.
--Yes, sir?
Of course! Sanji's the cook I picked!
Of course! That's a miracle
food called a gem of the ocean.
"Crush any pirate ships
as soon as they see them.
I've never eaten anything this good!
Is your place a BBQ restaurant?
Don't let any pirates off of
this island. Not even one pirate."
I've never seen it though.
--You're finally smiling.
--Oh, Nami-san!
It's not a BBQ restaurant,
but Grandpa Bokuden's pork buns
are the best on the island!
Of course not, since it's
a fish from the South Blue.
You're eating again, Luffy?!
I can't let you have this
sword no matter what.
I didn't eat that much for lunch.
You never see it in the East Blue,
All right! Let's go!
You emptied two pots, didn't you?
Sergeant Major Tashigi lost...
but it's a different story
if there's the All Blue.
Well then, we'll go.
I did?
That Sergeant Major Tashigi lost...
--An execution!
--An execution will start!
You got scared when you heard
we're pirates, didn't you?
Now that's impossible.
Buggy the Clown will be
executing Straw Hat Luffy!
Well, then... I'm in a hurry, so...
W-Well...
Well, that's a natural reaction
towards pirates these days.
Yeah, I know.
Luffy's gonna be executed?!
What's the All Blue?
That idiot!
It's a legendary sea. I hear that fish
from all over the world swim there.
Why aren't you finishing me off?!
--You're not gonna sell me off?
--No way!
Let's go!
--Take care of this!
--Ahh... Ahh... Ahhhhh...
Hm?!
You're all evil-looking, so...
Is it because I'm a woman?!
Stop it. He's a kid.
He'll take it seriously.
You've got a right
to talk with that face?
--S-S-S-Sanji!
--Treat it like a lady! Got that?!
There she is!
You're lucky, Zoro. You're a boy.
What're you doing?!
Where is it?
--Oops! Ahhh...
--We have to hurry, too!
Ahh! That's enough!
See? He doesn't get jokes.
Hey! Hey, Nami!
Where're we going?!
It's humiliating that
you won't fight seriously
That was a joke, Sanji.
There's no way such a thing exists.
The harbor, of course!
in a game played in earnest just because
men're physically stronger than women!
We have more, mademoiselle.
Don't worry about it.
Just keep studying.
H-Harbor? Oh yeah, of course!
Eric!
I'm sure you don't understand the
feeling that I wish I was born a boy!
At least, this ship isn't the kind
of pirate ship you're thinking of.
I've been here all along...
Captain Smoker!
Please come here.
I thought that that girl
got lost in the Calm Belt
Things are getting weird.
I don't carry a sword for pleasure!
Don't worry.
and wasn't going to come back alive!
Hm? Wha...! Th-That kid...
I don't like your very being!
Can't be... That girl...?
--Another plate, please!
--As you wish.
All Blue...
What's he doing?
--Me, too!
--Do it yourself!
Okay, then, haul it away.
Monkey D. Luffy. This can't be!
Looks like he's about to be killed!
Listen! Your face! It looks exactly like
my close friend's who died long ago!
You meanie...
She's...
--Okay!
--H-Hold on a second!
--Hm?
--How much is it?! Sell it to me!
On top of that, you started saying
the same thing she used to say!
How pathetic that kid looks!
What?!
...back on Warship Island!
Capture that girl, you bum!
I've got money! Let me buy it! Please!
Don't imitate, you copycat woman!
I want to see the place where
the King of the Pirates died!
What?! Stop talking
like a child! You're rude!
Then they escaped from the Calm Belt...!
I live the way I am! I don't
know what your friend was like,
No, you can't! This isn't for sale!
Hm?
He was somehow
different from the others.
It's been decided just now that
this is going to be a prize. Sorry.
but I'm the one who feels upset!
Isn't she the copycat?!
He caught my attention...
So I thought, but...
A prize...?
Wh-What'd you say?!
That's right.
Does this mean that he's just
another pirate after all?
The annual Cooking Championship
will be starting a little later today.
I see the exit! The harbor is up there!
Wo-oah!
Captain, are we
swooping in right away?
Cooks from all over the East Blue
gather for this competition.
--Huh?
--Wh-What happened?
Idiot. Don't be hasty.
But if we don't hurry...
This'll be given to the winner.
Hey, who is it this time?
I'm the one in command here!
Hey! Just what'd you do?
After all, this is an
elephant bluefin tuna.
Y-Yes, sir!
I was preparing a meal!
It's exactly what a champion deserves.
So we decided to give it as a prize.
You're finally here...
A pirate is about
to kill another pirate.
What?
There,
Everyone! Breakfast is ready!
Straw Hat Luffy...
This is great.
They're saving us the trouble.
the preparations are finished.
Wait a little while.
If you really want it,
you should participate.
Oh, breakfast?!
Didn't I tell you that you can't enter
the Grand Line unless you beat me first?
Cool!
You're a cook, aren't you?
What breakfast explodes?
Listen! Once that
Straw Hat's head falls,
Whoa! Smells good!
Y-Yeah...
I see... This is the real deal.
surround Buggy,
Alvida and their gangs!
The registration is over there.
If you're interested, go register.
Old man, how long do we have to wait?
Oh, yeah. I forgot about it.
--You made this?
--Yep!
Hm? Well...
Don't give them time to think!
It has quite... a unique appearance...
Hurry up or it'll close soon, young man.
You're such an airhead...
maybe about 4-5 hours...
See ya!
Hey, Luffy...
Thanks! I'm digging in!
What?!
In addition to rescuing me,
you're feeding me, too.
Sanji, go on ahead. I'll be right there.
Ah, I'm starving.
A cooking competition, huh?
All right, then!
Pirate Monkey D. Luffy, the criminal,
is to be flashily executed for the crime
I'll do anything to help you from now on!
Bokuden-san,
Well, I don't know about that.
This is the end for you.
why is the Navy after Apis?
Do you have any idea?
Uh... uhm...
Huh...? Wait a second...
Apis! Do you have any idea?
That'll be helpful... Thank you.
of getting me angry
by becoming stuck up!
I challenge you, Sanji!
Not at all!
Is this really edible?
You said there was a reason
but you didn't want to tell.
Go!
Oh that! I lied.
Stop grumbling and just eat it!
Oh, well...
Live it up flashily!
--What?
--Then none at all.
But seriously, is it really safe to eat?
None at all?!
Really? This is good.
Really, there's nothing on this island.
Nothing but an old legend.
This is my first time
seeing an execution.
That's right. It's possible that
just the appearance is bad.
We're executing you.
Huh?
Really?
What?! Stop joking!
Legend?
The residents of this island are said
to be descendants of Lost Island people
You stop joking!
--Take this board off!! You bastard!!
--Okay! We are now going
who prospered but sank into the sea
tens of thousands of years ago.
--Take it off!! You liar!
You jerkwad! You stupid head!
--to start the flashy execution openly!!
Fire!
W-Was it that bad?
On Lost Island, there lived
dragons called Millennial Dragons.
Ahhh!! Stop it!
Ahhh! I don't wanna die!!
The bones of those dragons
are called Dragonite...
Whoa! That's spicy!
Now, the annual Cooking Championship
festivities are about to start!
Fire the cannons!
What is this?!
I put in the wrong seasoning!
...and it's said to be
an elixir of immortality.
We have famous cooks from
around the East Blue gathered here!
Well, that's a common mistake.
I see...
But a legend like that is no reason
for the Navy to get involved.
You'll be fine if you
are careful next time.
What a crowd!
I wonder what's going on...
Yeah. Why is the Navy doing
this in the first place?
This year's prize is
an elephant bluefin tuna!
Hey, she took the trouble
to prepare it for us.
Eat every crumb!
That's the thing I don't get.
It's a treasure of the
ocean and miracle food!
Shut up! Don't waste this
girl's kindness. This girl's...
Who will earn the "East Blue's No. 1"
title and win the elephant bluefin tuna?!
Doesn't this legend hold some
sort of clue or something?
If we stay here any longer,
the Going Merry will be sunk!
I saw a big cumulus
cloud in the eastern sky.
Oh, what's your name, by the way?
A storm is coming.
An unimaginably big storm is...
To begin with, the first king
--Here we go again...
--of Lost Island was Iscardunk.
Apis! My name is Apis!
Now, King PokePortes had three children.
If Buggy, Luffy and the others
go crazy, the Navy will come out.
Apis-chan put her heart into this food!
That will be me!
A-Are you going to set sail?
Luffy and the others aren't here yet!
I'm glad you came instead
of running away, Sanji!
Plus, I won't allow anyone to waste food!
The oldest son was BokeHontas,
the second son was BokeBonboko, and
We don't have any other choice!
It's better than getting sunk here!
We're done for if the ship is washed out
to sea when we have to get out of here.
But the East Blue's
No. 1 title will be mine!
--the third son was BokeBokepon.
I see. That really is a big deal!
I'll cook something
for you later, Nami-san.
--Shhh!
--the third son was BokeBokepon.
Right rudder full!
--Shhh!
--One day, the king said to these three,
This time I'll finally
prove my real abilities!
The Navy may have
already started taking action.
--One day, the king said to these three,
Thanks.
"Listen. Go find the tree that grows stars,
which is said to be in dragon's valley.
I'm sorry. I'm not good at cooking...
but I wanted to be helpful!
So what're we going to do
about Luffy and the others?
The Going Merry is in danger!
Oh, Carmen-san!
I'm excited to see you again!
We'll pick them up somehow.
Don't let them get away! Follow them!
Th-The Going Merry
will be in the Navy's hands?
So BokeHontas,
BokeBonboko and BokeBokepon
Don't worry about it.
We really appreciate the thought.
Here's a kiss for our reunion!
Nami-san!
Don't you dare!!
--journeyed out, one to the sea,
Sanji-kun!
H-Hey, Nami! Hurry up!!
Leave the cooking to me.
Sanji!
--Once Grandpa starts that story,
--journeyed out, one to the sea,
Nami-san, I'm back!
--Once Grandpa starts that story,
--one to the mountain and one to the forest.
There're many other things
that you could help out with.
--it'll take forever.
--one to the mountain and one to the forest.
Wait for me!
You haven't changed...
How passionate...
--I'm not gonna listen to all that.
--one to the mountain and one to the forest.
Where're Luffy and Zoro?
Now, the 317th King IngriMongri III's son
Hurry to the harbor!
Crush every single pirate ship!
Okay!
Can we collect those damn idiots?
Really? This is good.
Hey! Hold on a sec!
Look! Look at that!
You...
I wanna eat barbecue next.
I haven't had it for a while.
--Hey, how long is this gonna go on?
--IngriGrimori was quite a wise ruler.
Yes, sir!
Sanji-kun!
That's Sanji!
Behind you!
--Who knows.
--IngriGrimori was quite a wise ruler.
Yeah!
He had 18 children. His 18 children...
Hey! Hey!
--Sanji!
--Sanji-kun!
Say, why were you
drifting on the sea, Apis?
...He was a king who
Nami-san! You came
to give me your support?!
Riding around on the Richie bike!
Dammit! This is endless!
--carried out major reforms.
--Ahhh, I'm starving...
--This King Ikemenes had so many children.
I'll cover his back! Get closer!
--We won't be able to eat
--This King Ikemenes had so many children.
Not really. I was just passing by.
--until this story is over, will we?
--This King Ikemenes had so many children.
I escaped from a Navy ship...
No! We can't head back to land
because of the strong current.
Who's that man?
Who? Who? Who's that man?!
--We won't be able to eat
--He had many princes. 65 of them!
But why in the heck are you
participating in a competition like this?
From a Navy ship?
--the pork buns until then?
--He had many princes. 65 of them!
Ahhh, dammit!
--Pork buns?
--He had many princes. 65 of them!
...during the stormy
night three days ago...
Oh, Usopp. I didn't
realize you were here.
--Usopp!
--Bastards!
I hear it was like, "If you throw a stone,
In that small boat in such a storm...
Me!
I was the one who
called out to you first!
--Luffy?
--it'll hit one of the princes."
--I gotta take a leak.
You're reckless.
So this is the rubber guy's ship...
Now it's time to start
the championship!
So what'd you do in the first place?
These're the judges!
What?
You had to escape,
He now has a bigger ship,
as if he's become a real pirate.
Also, to be fair, we asked Sam-san,
a member of the general audience
on his way home from a wedding party,
which means you weren't on
their ship as a guest, right?
It's about time for him to get
flashily executed by Captain Buggy.
Pork buns...
Usopp! Sanji-kun!
--to join the judges!
--Where am I?
Are you ready, Sam-san?!
But then the Navy wouldn't
go after every little villain.
Hold on, Grandpa Ryu.
However...! Just in case the rubber guy,
who has no chance of escaping,
--Sam-san?!
--Let's go!!
Oh, no!
The rules are simple. First, each
cook will compete against another.
W-Well... uhm...
He's coming this way!
What am I gonna do?
Whoever receives a higher
total score from the judges wins.
What? Are you a super villain?
happens to escape,
burning this ship is... our job.
No! There's no way I'd do bad things!
And whoever remains
undefeated through all the matches
I never did bad things...
but I can't tell you why...
will be the East Blue's
glorious No. 1 cook!
Please! Don't come here!
What's that about...?
Well then, we'll now
start the first round!
Pork buns smell yummy.
I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
Please save me.
What's the big deal?
She must have her reasons.
The first match is Shoo the Lizard
from the easternmost extremity versus
If she doesn't want to say,
then we shouldn't press her.
Why would I save you, idiot?!
Hmph! This is what happens
when someone goes against us.
Eoccoli, representing Loguetown!
That's true. But can you at
least tell us where you're from?
I'll beat you and
enter the Grand Line.
No way!
I guess this is it for
the man I had my eye on...
Now, ready... Start!
I didn't hit him yet, right?
What? Oh, yes...
I'm the man who'll be
King of the Pirates!
Ahhh, pork buns...
Since you have a big audience,
I'm from Warship Island.
What, Sanji? You're interested
in becoming the East Blue's No. 1?
Enough of your idle talk!
Warship Island?
do you wanna say
something before you die?
Don't be stupid. It's nothing like that.
Do you know it?
And, the 1,111th... no,
No. I'll check it out.
I just want to cook that fish.
Well, that's okay. Whether you
wanna say something or not
Why is it called Warship Island?
the 1,121st King was HokeHontas.
Fish?
It's because the shape of the
island looks exactly like a warship.
Oh yeah, that fish does
look different from others.
doesn't matter since you're gonna die.
What?! What?! What's going on?!
So, NemeNememitas
Though that fish's secrets
can't be obtained so easily...
Oh, that's interesting.
--Hey, where're you going?
--thought about what he could do
I ate the Plume Plume Fruit.
So my body becomes smoke at will.
--I'm worried about Luffy
--thought about what he could do
Ahh! This is the one!
--since he's gone for a long time.
--to protect this kingdom.
I'm the man who'll be
King of the Pirates!!
Oh, it's close to the Grand Line.
--So I'll go check.
--to protect this kingdom.
Huh?
--So I'll go check.
--Then, he made preparation
We're around here right now,
so it's not that far.
--That's not fair.
--Then, he made preparation
--Nami-san's lovely
even when she sneaks out.
--before large countries attacked them.
Phew! Good grief!
--What do you wanna do?
--What?
Do you wanna go
back to Warship Island?
Luffy!
If we keep sailing like this,
we are going to enter the Grand Line.
Ahhh! Not even one bun is left!
Wha...
You were nice enough to save me
and I feel bad burdening you further...
Yeah, this is yummy.
K-King of the Pirates, he said?!
Yummy?! How do you intend to make
up for eating everyone's share?!
What's wrong? Finished already?
In this town, of all places...
but I want to go back to the island!
I'm sorry. I'm selfish, aren't I?
What're you talking about?
That's a crazy thing to say...
Geez... Hm?
What's this?
Well then, I guess I'll do it now...
you damn piece of rubber.
If you hand me to a ship heading
west on your way if possible,
What made this trail?
I'll work things out on my own.
And at last, the final match!
Oh my, that's a real burden!
Gum-Gum Gatling!
--Stop...
--Hm?
There's no way that a pirate ship can
get close to another ship so easily.
Hm? Dead end?
Hey, people're really excited.
--...the execution!
--Hm?
What's the deal?
Yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
Hm?
With his remarkable cooking sense
and skills, Sanji won through to the final!
Zoro! Sanji!
Hey, Luffy, what're you doing?
But since it's not totally out of our way
With her gorgeous dance and cooking skills,
Carmen has kept crushing others!
--A hole.
--What?
--Zoro?!
--Hm?
and we're not really in a hurry...
What? Ahh, that's gross!
Shame on you!
--Oh, what the heck?
--What?!
--Which one will win the
glorious elephant bluefin tuna?!
There's a limit to how much
you can fool around, Luffy.
It doesn't matter either way to me.
What should we do, Captain?
--Hi!!
--Which one will win the
glorious elephant bluefin tuna?!
Hmph!
If you're starting a sideshow,
let me join you.
The anticipated
final match starts now!
Yeah, that sounds fine.
White Blow!
The Grand Line isn't
that far, either, so...
I see. The island looks
like a warship, huh?
What we have to do for now is
drive those damn pirates away?
You bastard! Gum-Gum Pistol!
Rinsing!
--Sounds like they've decided.
--Really?!
P-Pirate hunter Zoro!!
Are you really going to stop
by Warship Island for me?!
--Yeah.
--All right! Thank you, Luffy!
There she goes!
Sanji! Zoro!
You get it? You can't
even enter the Grand Line.
Carmen's cooking looks
showy at first glance,
but what she's actually
doing is quite simple.
All right! All right! I'm so happy!
So you're here, Zoro!
But you are a little too late!
Also her opponents get confused by
those two in front and lose their pace,
Thank you very much! Thank you!
Didn't I tell you that?
Thank you very much, everyone!
--We'll bring down...
--...that execution platform!
but how is Sanji doing?!
Looks like they went across here.
Roronoa Zoro...
To show my appreciation,
I'll prepare lots of dishes every day!
Wanted for a 30 million Berry bounty?
He's not affected!
Luffy!
No, that won't be necessary.
Yep! Gum-Gum...
Far from that, he's exhibiting
amazing knife skills!
Guys... get them!
Why not?
We'll get them!
Suspension Bridge...
You're running out of your devil's luck.
Big Sis Alvida!
Contender Sanji is silently proceeding
with the preparation at his own pace!
Don't be so sure.
Grandpa Ryu!
Out of our way!
Reporting!
You're...
Ship sighted ahead at 13 o'clock!
It's a mid-size caravel.
This is the other side of the mountain.
How far did they go?
I see a flag with a skull
mark on the main mast!
Not even Zoro can stop me now!
Pirates, huh?
It definitely exists!
They don't know their own station,
sailing around in the seas
Ah, that's...
This is the end of your captain!!
Yes, I was fine.
These weird pirates saved me.
under Commodore Nelson's control.
You're still saying things
like that? How silly!
Wh-What? Who's that? Who's that?
I'm sure they're just small fries.
Just leave them alone!
Damn bastard!
That's why we say you're a child!
No, they're not that scary.
The government wants your head.
No. That flag doesn't
belong to small fries.
I'm not a child, you damn bastard!
You must be hungry. I brought
Grandpa Bokuden's pork buns.
If I cut down the execution platform...
That's enough, Sanji! We don't
have time for your stupid stories!
If I remember correctly,
that belongs to Straw Hat Luffy,
The world is waiting for our answer.
a man with a 30 million Berry
bounty on his head.
Listen. The moment Monkey D. Luffy's
head falls, we'll attack all together.
Here you go. No! Slow down!
Oh, the ones people have
been talking about lately?
Forget it and go collect plates!!
Oh, I'm sorry. I still don't know yet.
We still can't find the girl
even with this big fleet.
I know... Theoretically it's
impossible. I know that much...
Although I'm searching very hard,
I still haven't found a clue yet.
All units. Get ready for battle.
It's possible that someone has her.
Yes, sir!!
I wonder who on earth Apis is talking to.
The North Blue, South Blue,
East Blue and West Blue...
Not to mention, pirates of that caliber...
Hey, Apis! Who're you talking to?
They're separate seas
that you can't cross
Isn't it going to be a problem if you
leave them be, Lt. Commander?
Zoro! Sanji!
Don't just jump out and say "hey"!
--Hurry up!
--Usopp!
due to the Red Line Continent
that runs from north to south
--Nami!
--This is heavy!
and the ocean current in the Grand Line
which extends from east to west.
No! Don't come here!
Sorry. I'm... dead.
Capture that ship!
A sea where you can find all
the fish from those four seas...
I wonder what this feeling is...
Whoa!!
Idi...
...should be impossible...
Hey! I see ships
approaching from the rear!
Luffy, what's the matter?
Don't say something so stupid!
But it definitely exists!
He smiled!
Ahh!!
--What?
--Ugh! Oh, man!
That's right. Otherwise how do
you explain those West Blue fish
--They're Navy ships!
--Navy?!
and the elephant bluefin tuna?
And it's not just
one or two ships, either!
The possibility that the damn geezer
was talking about may refer to this.
He's right!
But what's a fleet like that doing here?
--Amazing! Amazing! Amazing!
--Stop it! I said stop it!
If that's the case, I have no choice but
to look for it in the Grand Line after all!
Th-This is...
What? What? What's going on?
Hey, Luffy...
This is the real thing! Is he alive?
It doesn't matter how long
it takes. I'll find it for sure!
Are they after my head?
Wh-What just happened?
Stop it! Leave him alone!
That's a lot even for that!
I can't believe... that it really exists...
It means that they need that
many to capture me, right?
I thought that dragons were just legends!
The legendary sea...
Luffy!
I'm amazing, aren't I?
Luffy!!
All Blue!
This is incredible!
Where did you come from?
How can you be so easygoing?!
Nami!
Hm...? What's wrong?
We'd better hurry up or the
ship will be swept away!
Those ships belong to Branch 8!
Okay!
I escaped from them!
Now it looks like Sanji
is starting to finish up!
Gum-Gum...
What am I gonna do?
Hm...? There! I found her!
I see the girl on their deck!
Carmen is also close to the end!
--Wha?!
--W-Wait!
I see... You want to go home, huh?
Looks like all she has
to do now is dish it out!
I have a bad feeling...
The championship is reaching a climax.
Who will win the elephant bluefin tuna?!
...Rocket!!
What?!
It was just as I said,
wasn't it, Lt. Commander?
Ahhh, I knew it!
Did I hurt your pride?
Okay...
The decision... will be made soon!
But if you make a mistake
and lose that girl...
Grandpa Ryu says that you
can be his friend, Luffy.
...the clue to the elixir
of immortality, the Dragonite,
He did it!
He says he can tell
you're a good person.
Contender Sanji completed it!
Everyone...
I wonder how furious
Commodore Nelson would get.
And here is Contender Carmen!
Looks like she's completed it, too!
Luffy, how could you
read Grandpa Ryu's mind?
Prepare the main cannons!
We'll capture that pirate ship!
--I somehow did.
--Somehow...?
The dishes are all completed now!
Who will win the crown?!
How did you know?
Oh, well, I...
Ugh! They're firing at us!!
Could it be... a devil fruit...?
I'm still alive after all.
You have the power of
a devil fruit, don't you?
Well then, here goes.
That man...
What was that sudden gust?
I got lucky.
The winner of this year's
Cooking Championship is...
Yes. I ate one called
Whisper-Whisper Fruit or something.
Attention pirate ship!
Stop the ship immediately!
Since then, I've become
able to read animals' minds.
He appeared and disappeared
like lighting on the same day
--San...
--Wait!!
Those were warning shots.
The next shots will hit your ship!
--H-Hey, do you believe in god?
--Phew, lucky me.
That's why you knew
a wind was coming that time.
There's no way we'd stop!
that Gold Roger was executed
22 years ago. What on earth...
--Stop talking nonsense.
Let's get out of this town already!
--I was worried what was going happen for a while.
What're we gonna do, Luffy? If you
wanna take 'em on, I'm with you.
Yep. The seabirds told me that.
I'm the man who'll be
King of the Pirates!
--Yeah. Why don't we?
--Ahhh! W-Wait a sec!
Another trouble seems to be brewing.
I met Grandpa Ryu thanks to
the Whisper-Whisper Fruit, too.
Why are you guys always like this?!
--What the heck are you
gonna do against that fleet?!
--Apis, go to the cabin downstairs.
--I can't forgive...
--Hm?
I can't forgive myself!
Now! Corner those pirates!
--We'll make a raid on them.
--O-Okay...
--A raid isn't gonna work!
What?!
Yeah!!
--We'll make it work.
--You can't!
I always wanted to compete against
you some day. So I've trained like crazy!
We're not saying you have to come.
Back us up with the cannon.
--Here they come!
--Tsk!
What? So I'm staying on this ship?
Okay, leave it to me!
If that's your decision, then go!
Who is it?
--And we'll get clear
of them at full speed!
--Hey, Apis. What's the matter?
I wanted to be on a level with you...
--You take care of the rest.
--Hey, Apis. What's the matter?
--He said a wind is coming.
A strong wind is...
Amazing! Amazing!
It's somehow gotten crazy!
Why? Why did you
help that man... Dragon?!
I've never heard such
a sad voice before...
Zoro! Lean the sail towards the south!
But ten years later...
Amazing! Ahh! Amazing!
Usopp and Sanji-kun,
right rudder full! Hurry up!
Hey, Luffy!
...your dream hasn't changed!
Ahhh... Z-Zoro!
--O-Okay.
--Yes, Nami-san!
What reason would there be to
interfere with a man's departure?
I can't forgive myself for being stupid
enough to think that I could defeat you.
This is no time to be excited!
We need to get out of here!
What's going on?
A gust is coming.
We'll ride it and get out of here.
We'd better hurry back to the ship
If we fight them head on,
we'll lose no matter how good we are.
or we'll never be able
to leave the island.
Hold on! I'm coming to help you now!
You win... Your dishes are delicious.
We won't be able to
enter the Grand Line!
We can take them, though...
What?! That's not good!
You're the No. 1 cook
in the East Blue, Sanji.
This girl...
The Straw Hat gang is running away!
Set sail! We'll go after Straw Hat!
--Capture them!
--Go after them!
Their ship shows no signs of stopping.
They're mocking us!
What?
We'll enter the Grand Line.
Was it you who called me?
Oh... To think that Carmen-san
is giving me such a compliment...
Here goes!
Why did he smile?
B-But, Captain! This island
is in your jurisdiction.
He had lost his energy.
I'm so happy!
Ahh! The pirate ship sped up
and changed its route!
Did he know he'd be saved?
He said that he got separated
from his friends and
Don't you dare!!
I don't know what
the higher-ups would say...
that since then he had
been looking for Lost Island,
--What?!
--They're heading south!
No. At that moment, he seriously
thought his life was going to end there.
Tell them I said,
"Don't give me orders."
South?! How foolish!
where the dragons' nest is.
What'd you do that for?!
Do they know what's in that direction?!
I'll come with you!
Didn't Lost Island sink
a long long time ago?
Sergeant Major Tashigi!
He accepted death and smiled
after preparing himself.
I'll withdraw for now, but be
prepared when we meet next time!
What're you doing, Lt. Commander?!
Go after them! Now!
I won't forgive Roronoa.
Grandpa Ryu says that the
island will surface again.
Captain, please go seize the pirates.
I'll capture him without fail!
I definitely won't lose.
Whoa! This is fast!
This is a good wind.
Yeah, if it's a challenge from you,
I'll happily accept it any time.
He says it's about time,
Hey... have you seen any pirates
who smiled on the execution platform?
but he no longer clearly
remembers where it is.
Look at that, Luffy!
The Navy's falling behind!
Whoa!
Ha! You guys're slow turtles!
The winner is... contender Sanji!
He's gotten very old
and lost the energy to fly.
Gee, that flashy gust was lucky for us.
N-No way! Even if it's
a brave-acting big shot,
But he keeps telling me
that he wants to go back.
No good! We can't catch up!
at the moment of death,
he turns pale and dies in despair.
We were able to escape like
this because I always behave well.
I wanna help, but I can't figure out
where such an island exists at all...
A Navy fleet falling behind
such a small ship? Dimwit.
That straw hat man smiled...
Where're we going now?
A small ship has better mobility!
Ah! That was fun!
--The Grand Line.
--The Grand Line?
The legend by itself
doesn't really give me a clue...
...just like Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates,
I don't wanna hear excuses!
I don't know why but today
was a day of face-offs.
Yeah. This is a good opportunity. I have
to settle with that damn rubber man.
Hey, why am I
carrying the heavier part?!
So I asked the Navy who happened
to stop by this island about it.
smiled 22 years ago in this town...
on that execution platform...
Lt. Commander, this ship will soon...
Well... an elephant bluefin tuna, huh?
Let's head straight into
the nostalgic Grand Line...
--Lt. Commander!
--I know!
That was a mistake.
They were looking for Dragonite.
I wonder what it tastes like...
Stop all the ships!
Prepare to turn around!
Looks like I can use
the fins for making stock.
Ugh! It's almost like
the ship's gonna tip over!
Dragonite... you mean
the one for immortality?
Wait, Lt. Commander!
Why are you stopping the ships?
What can I use the ear areas for?
They took you away
because of such a thing?
Ahhh! I can't wait to cook it!
If we keep going,
we'll go into the Calm Belt!
Yes. They told me to tell them
everything I knew and took me away.
Look at that light!
Captain...
--So what? Go after them!
--No!
Hm?
Is that a lighthouse of the island?
Where did that Straw Hat go?
The pendant that I made with a claw
You really don't appreciate the
seriousness of this matter, do you?
It's a "guiding light." The entrance to
the Grand Line lies ahead of that light.
Grandpa Ryu gave me may
have been another reason, though...
What's the matter, Nami?
Yes, sir. He's running towards the sea.
The air has changed...
We can't lose that girl now.
That's why you escaped in that storm...
--Air?
--It'll rain.
The Grand Line is ahead of that light...
What's Unit #1 doing? They should've
blown up their ship by now.
--You are too reckless!
--I know.
What're you going to say
to Commodore Nelson?!
Huh? When the
weather is nice like this?
What do you wanna do?
That's why I keep this a secret to
the villagers and even to Bokuden-san.
B-But there's no reason to
enter during a storm like this...
There's no doubt about it. Let's hurry.
I'm prepared to take the punishment.
Well... They're back for
refitting because they couldn't
Huh? Hey...!
I can't just sit by and let this fleet
I don't want to cause troubles for them.
and my subordinates
be swallowed by the sea!
But I want to take Grandpa Ryu back
to his home no matter what it takes.
light the powder
due to the sudden rain...
No matter what you say,
the chase ends here!
What?!
Ah! My hat!
He always tells me that he'll
get his energy back for sure
A reserve unit is currently getting
ready to attack the ship instead.
How... foolish...
Wait!
once he goes back to the dragons' nest.
Captain Smoker! If we let them sail
out now, they'll enter the Grand Line!
I'll find it for him no matter
how many years it takes.
Okay, then!
Wait, hat!
Shall we hold a launching ceremony
for setting sail on the great ocean?
The Navy isn't following us!
For sure... No matter what it takes,
I'll find it for him.
Did Captain Usopp
scare the pants off them?
--Hey!
--Sure!
The wind is blowing towards the west.
It's a tailwind for their ship.
Luffy?
Let's do it!
Amazing! Amazing! Just as
you'd expect from our navigator!
In order to find the All Blue!
Okay then! I'll take him there!
Well done, Nami-san. To think you
detected such a wind beforehand...
In order to be King of the Pirates!
Luffy! Were you listening?!
Lost Island sank into the sea!
Are these all coincidences?
Phew! Good! My hat!
Well, it was like an instinct, though.
In order to become
a master swordsman!
Oh, Nami-san is lovely
when she's humble, too.
Hm?
It's as if heaven is trying
to let that man live.
But since the legendary
Millennial Dragon actually exists,
In order to draw a world map!
Ahh... I'm here!
Well then, shall we head
straight to Warship Island?
I'm sure Lost Island
also exists somewhere!
--Really?!
--Yeah, really.
--We'd better hurry
or we'll be in trouble!
--We're gonna make it to the Grand Line like this!
I-In order... to become
a brave warrior of the sea!
An island that's not even on a map?
Okay, then! To Warship Island, let's...
Yeah, that's why we're going!
Lucky!
I am White Hunter Smoker.
...go!!
Found him! This way!
On my honor as a
Navy Headquarters Captain,
An island that's not even on a map, huh?
What's wrong, Zoro?
What?! Really?!
I won't let that man
leave this island!!
Oh, what the heck? Let's go!
You've had a serious look
on your face for a while.
He showed up?!
--All right!
--Really?! Really?!
Yes! We were watching
the square like you told us,
Well, I hope it's just my imagination.
--Yeah.
--Thank you!
and the man on the wanted
poster appeared just now...
Now that that's been decided, eat more!
What is?
Okay.
I feel like this ship hasn't
been moving at all for a while.
Oh, Luffy, I forgot to tell you...
Let's go flashily.
So he just walked right up...
Just wait, you brat.
Grandpa Ryu is a little senile.
We're going... to the Grand Line!!
What?
Yeah!
Come to think of it, the sail
isn't catching any wind at all...
That girl had a pendant with
a Millennial Dragon's claw.
Wow! So this is the scenery
that the King of the Pirates saw...
She must know about Lost Island.
Wind, blow!
Ah!
The storm of fate has arrived!
What's wrong, Nami?
And he died here...
That darn girl who knows
the secret of the Dragonite...
Nami-san...?
I'll definitely capture her this time!
Dammit...
We've entered the Calm Belt!!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Hm? What's going on over there?
A flock of birds?
What's the Calm Belt?
Taking the Millennial Dragon
back to his home?
What?! Luffy's gonna be executed?!
We'll head straight to Warship Island!
No way!
Why'd you promise such
a thing without asking us?
There must be fish under that.
By Buggy?! What a shame!
Ahhh!
Catch some, okay?
Hey, let's go to Lost Island!
Leave it to me!
So all we have to do is beat them?
Hey, the Navy is following us!
He always makes us do reckless things!
Hm? It's not fish!
Yep! Help me!
It's a girl!
Everyone, please help us!
Say, don't you think Apis
has an air of secrecy about her?
Okay, then! We'll bring
down the execution platform!
There's trouble! I see a Navy fleet!
Let's go, Nami-san!
I know.
A runaway journey of love
beyond the ocean! Mellorine love.
Zoro, Sanji, Usopp, Nami!
D-Did they come to capture me?
Hey, look at that!
Something incredible's there!
Sorry! I'm dead.
Ahhh! They're firing at us!
Are you stupid?
Th-That's...!
What'd you say?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
On the next episode on One Piece!
"Precursor to a New Adventure!
Apis, a Mysterious Girl"
"Buggy's Revenge! The Man Who
Smiles on the Execution Platform!"
"Miraculous Creature! Apis's Secret
and the Legendary Island."
"Eric Attacks! Great Escape
from Warship Island!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!