ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy, depressed after losing his brother
Ace in the war against the Navy,
Luffy lost his brother Ace in the
War of the Best against the Navy.
Luffy has returned to Marineford
with Rayleigh and Jimbei.
Luffy was depressed after losing his
brother Ace in the war against the Navy.
He sent a message to his crew
realized the importance of friendship
After getting back on his
feet with Jimbei's help,
What is the real reason behind their actions?
in a manner that no one
else would understand.
and sent a message to his crew.
The King of the Pirates?!
Luffy met Dark King Rayleigh.
I'm too weak!!
What are you gonna do, Luffy-kun?
I hope that they'll get it.
I'm gonna go back.
"Living through Hell!
Sanji's Fight for His Manhood!"
But at this time, he realized
the importance of friendship.
They'll get it if they see the article.
To Marineford!
"With Hopes It Will Reach My
Friends! Big News Spreading Fast!"
And the rest of the Straw
Hats learned the news.
They will understand you very well.
And he went back to Marineford
at Dark King Rayleigh's suggestion.
On the small Sky Island - Weatheria...
I have a feeling.
Why?! What's going on?! What
made Luffy do this...?!
Oh yeah! I got it, Luffy!
On the solitary island in the Grand Line...
--There she is!
--We found her finally!
The rest of the Straw Hats got a message
Luffy! I'm glad he's okay!
I got it now! Okay! Okay!
through the news about
Luffy's mysterious behavior
--How could you fool us?
--You didn't just steal our research notes...
I see. That's what it is.
It's in today's newspaper?
and each starting taking
initiatives on their own.
Since they locked you up,
--But you toyed with...
--Our pure hearts!
Luffy!
Roger that, Luffy.
we couldn't even sleep at night
and in order to save you...
Luffy wants to become
the King of the Pirates.
I see, Luffy!
Surrender yourself now!
"Unexpected Relanding! Luffy, to Marineford!"
You thieving girl!
I got it!
...We went east and west and
survived various hardships!
I have to improve myself as a navigator!
I got it, Luffy!
Okay.
Honestly! He's not thinking
about how we feel - how selfish!
--The research notes!
--The Weather ball!
And then,
Hey, Luffy. The Thousand Sunny
still has some life in her.
our captain who should be in prison
became a hero in the newspaper!
At Marineford - Navy Headquarters
in the Grand Line...
And the hostage - Mr. Haredas!
I see!
It's unforgivable even if you return them!
Oh, is that what it's all about?
CONFERENCE ROOM
You're the only captain who can
make it "the ship of dreams."
It's incomprehensible!
I'm sorry. I regret what I've done.
Luffy doesn't do these kind of things.
--Captain Buggy!
--We've been looking for you!
--No, we can't trust her!
--Let's strip her and banish her!
Events in the War of the Best
He's with Rayleigh - it
must be Rayleigh's idea.
revealed he's the stepbrother
of the late Portgas D. Ace
We've trusted and followed
you and we thought,
I know there is a catch.
That's so... naughty...
and the son of the Revolutionary Dragon
Luffy, if I can see you again...
and also, the grandson of
Navy Vice Admiral Garp!
"Look at him, New World! That's our captain!"
Huh? Naughty?!
I'll give you the greatest
support in the world as a cook
Naughty...
I-I didn't know that you guys
had that much trust in me...
No, no, no, no! I didn't mean it
that way! What I wanted to say is...
The pirate - Monkey D. Luffy!
"Pirates Get on the Move!
Astounding New World!"
so you can become the King of the Pirates!
He went missing after the war,
but he was alive as expected
I missed you all!
She changed the subject...
She changed the subject!
Captain Buggy!
and resurfaced here,
at the Navy HQ, again!
Tut!
Since Whitebeard's era ended,
"I Will Get Much, Much Stronger!
Zoro's Pledge to His Captain!"
Did you just tut?
GRAND LINE - NEAR THE SABAODY ARCHIPELAGO
No! How terrible! That's an unjust charge!
ambitious pirates have begun
to stir in audacious ways.
Yeah, that's too much!
You guys...
On the Sword Mountain Island -
GRAND LINE SWORD MOUNTAIN
ISLAND - TEHNA GEHNA KINGDOM
A FEW DAYS AGO...
A few days ago...
Huh, is it my fault?! Didn't
you guys hear that?!
But not Trafalgar Law...
Didn't you give up on Buggy?
Tehna Gehna Kingdom in the Grand Line...
--Huh? We're not gonna go there yet?!
--Let's go to the New World already!
Come one! Come all!
--I don't think so...
--Don't get fooled by her!
It must be a mistake! I
wouldn't do such a thing!
M-Maybe I misheard...
How much longer are
we gonna hang around here?
So many people are here!
What is there to see?!
What are you waiting for, Captain?
She's manipulating them completely.
I heard that they found a weird creature.
How terrible!
So this is how it will be, guys!
I said we're going to wait for our time.
--She's wicked!
--Let's kick her out now!
It was an all-out war
Now, come and see it! A
mysterious creature show!
between the Navy's elite and
the world's greatest pirate.
TRAFALGAR LAW
Don't worry.
I'm the first mate of the
Buggy Pirates - Mohji!
No! I'm sorry! I regret what I've done!
The great One Piece treasure
won't go anywhere.
It's lucky that the island didn't sink.
How could we trust you?!
Brother Mohji!
No chest! No flesh!
But Blackbeard's already started
making moves in the New World
Where did you come from?
Yeah, I understand. Alright,
to show you how sorry I am,
I'm from Alabasta, to do a story
on Crocodile and Straw Hat.
I'm the chief of staff - Cabaji!
No eyeballs!
and there's a rumor he
destroyed a pirate crew!
Brother Cabaji!
It looks almost like a real skeleton!
I'm gonna jump into the water.
Straw Hat could be dead already though.
And he's my buddy - Richie!
And it only has one joint in its arms!
Big time rookies who want to
become one of The Four Emperors
Please forgive me in the afterworld!
I'm sure that the Navy wants to look
for the pirates involved in the war
I wonder if there is a
creature rarer than this!
are rushing to the New World!
Goodbye!
Richie!
There's no time to lose! We'll
be beaten by everybody else!
--We made her cry!
--Don't jump the gun!
Hey, stop lying, you!
but they don't have time for that now.
You're too young to put an end to your life!
Yeah.
By the way, what they said
in the newspaper was true.
Huh? What's wrong with this?
It's better for us if they're
trying to destroy one another.
The One Piece is real!!
Bye!
It's not moving at all!
We're sorry!
We won't get involved in those petty fights.
They're all infamous criminals
with high bounties!
Okay, I forgive you!
It's just a doll, isn't it?
Pirates inspired by Whitebeard's dying words
Stop griping and just follow me.
Now, I'm gonna stay here a little
longer and study about weather!
Of course! They're heinous
prisoners from Impel Down!
are committing crimes all over the world.
We'll get what we want at any cost!
Luffy-san has made up his mind.
Oh, my name is Nami. You
can call me Nami-san.
--Captain!
--We will follow you forever!
Well, then I have to do something, too.
Oh yeah!
All the Navy soldiers who can fight
are dealing with them everywhere.
Hey Alvida, do you wanna see something cool?
I need a house to live in.
Everybody needs a little privacy.
Hey, skeleton, don't mess with us!
Aye-aye, Captain! You can count on me...
I have to do something!
Ta-dah!
And a nice and comfortable bed, a
jet tub, and a big closet as well!
I feel sorry for them.
Oh, now you realize it,
huh? That's right. Move!
This is...!
Sleep talking?!
Speak of the devil, here come the soldiers.
Don't tell me it's Captain
John's treasure mark!
--I'm sorry.
--Don't apologize while you're asleep!
Thank you, grandpas in the sky!
We have to show them something!
Okay, let's do it! Yeah!
That's right!
NEW WORLD--SOME WINTER ISLAND
What can I do to help...
This is amazing! How did you get it?
He just told you! It's enough
if you just move! Just move!
Mr. Haredas, come in! Over!
It's so cold! My body's gonna freeze!
Straw Hat had it!
Good grief...
What's wrong with that ship?
It's not coming into the bay!
What's going on?!
Is anybody here at a place like this?
The wind doesn't blow east or west!
They're acting strange.
It looks like it's blowing right towards me!
X. DRAKE
When he saw me for the first time,
he didn't get scared at all and...
Speaking of Straw Hat, he made trouble again.
--What's that?!
--Something's falling from the sky!
Firing a blank?!
What's going on?!
You were desperate to get
off of this island before.
...asked me if I wanted to join them.
--Have they contacted us?!
--No, sir!
Oh no! Run!
You didn't know? He made
a raid on the Navy HQ!
What made you change your mind?
No way! Why did he come back...?!
Putting that aside, you,
There's a lot going on.
Could you tell me now?
Are you kidding me?
join my crew!
What's the matter?!
It's a miracle he's alive, let
alone doing this sort of thing!
Hm, okay.
Yeah, okay.
It's Straw Hat Luffy!
Weatheria travels on the wind and
wanders around the world in the sky.
Guys, are you okay?!
Huh? Let's see...
What?!
--Did he steal a Navy ship?!
--Why now?
I'm fine over here.
"'First Son of the Sea' Jimbei and
Dark King Silvers Rayleigh..."
For 50 years,
Damn! What's going on on this island?
Sometimes we descend to get
some supplies and information
I was just drifting about on the dark water.
He never learns... Sink the ship!
Captain, let's pull out of this island!
Words can't express how
happy I was to hear that.
Rayleigh?
and then continue on.
Fish-Man Jiu-Jitsu!
I don't think anybody's living here!
What?! Wh-What does Rayleigh-san
have to do with Straw Hat?!
Information?
Ocean Current Shoulder Throw!
Well, to check records.
You don't think so?
This man stole my shadow.
There are still a lot of unknown
weather conditions and phenomena
Anything can happen in this sea.
Wh... wh... wh... wh... wh...
wh... wh... wh... wh... wh...
Don't act like such a stranger!
Look at it.
...what's going on? I can't
grasp this situation at all.
that are difficult to fathom!
What's that semiround pile of snow?
If you need your shadow,
I'll take it back for you!
--What's this?!
--Are you listening?
The icicles are stuck in it!
Wait a minute.
Huh? You gotta be kidding!
Is that the traitor - "First
Son of the Sea" Jimbei?!
If I remember right, his father
is the Revolutionary - Dragon.
Lightning strikes like rain?!
There is someone else!
Yes, literally "like rain."
It's not a pile of snow! It's an iron dome!
And his grandfather is
Garp. And if that's so...
That's how it strikes that island.
That island is in the New World.
Rayleigh-san could be his uncle!
Look! The dome is opening up!
If you're willing to go to that sea,
Don't tell me that that's the legendary...
Hey Buggy!
you have to open your mind to the unexpected.
...first mate of the Roger
Pirates - Dark King Rayleigh!
A Carrier Bat brought a
message from the Government.
Huh?! How do they know that I'm here?!
I'm so happy to be alive!
It's a big world!
D-Don't tell me that the Navy
sent someone to get me here!
I beg you. Teach me, Haredas-san,
everything that you know about...
I bet you are!
And the message is "Be ready for it"?
--Can I join your crew?
--Yes, you can.
...the weather of the New World!
Hey, give it to me!
Why don't they come ashore?
I didn't expect to see a town in the dome.
You're desperate.
What?! So easily...
They went around the island once...
Of course, I am! All of my
friends' lives are in my hands!
This is...!
...He joined!
It's like a funeral at sea!
What?!
--I can't believe this!
--Don't read it before me!
I'm a navigator!
I can't explain how bright
you looked to me...
I have to take
responsibility when we're on the ship!
The famous Kaido-san of The Four
Emperors, loves this island.
Meanwhile, at the place of Thousand Sunny -
I have to navigate the way
wherever my captain wants to go!
Because 50 years of waiting for a
miracle paid off at that moment.
And I'm in charge of security here.
Sabaody Archipelago, Grove
#44 in the Grand Line...
Funeral? Because our main
forces aren't here now?!
And? What do you want from us?
Nothing. I just warned you.
--We want our money back!
--That's right!
You fools, give us that ship!
Damn pirates! Barrage
them from all directions!
Jeez! I thought he could be
profitable. We have no choice.
Luffy wants to become
the King of the Pirates.
You better not piss him off, rookie.
That's Straw Hat Luffy's ship, isn't it?
I have to improve myself as a navigator!
We should just force him to...
You mean, if I kill you or something,
He's the Revolutionary Dragon's son!
--What happened?
--Huh?
Your captain must be happy to have
such a thoughtful crew member.
Kaido won't leave me alone?
We can sell it to the Navy for a good price!
That's right. So why don't you...
I-It's moving...
That makes it easier for me!
--I have no choice.
--You have no choice?
Since we're in the same business,
Oh? An ancient Zoan type? How rare!
Yeah. He's so boastful, but he
doesn't know anything about the sea.
we can share the profit
if you just give it to us!
40 degrees!
How's that, Flying Fish Riders?!
What?!
Oh, it's so hard!
Go ahead and let loose on them!
It's really talking and moving!
Yeah!
--So creepy!
--What is that thing?!
Catch Straw Hat!
Scratch! Boom!
NEW WORLD--SOME SPRING ISLAND
If I try to go further than 45
degrees, I slip, just as I thought!
I'll fight you guys!
What? I'm handsome?
He always does ridiculous
things. If I left him alone...
I didn't say that! Give us the ship, fool!
Check it out!
I want you guys to play with me as well!
But when I overcome that...
SCRATCHMEN APOO
Gum-Gum...
I won't give it to you!
Luffy...
...Whip!
Maybe I can help Luffy-san more.
That was a pain in the butt!
Help me...
--That's our Captain Apoo!
--So dependable!
No, maybe I have to look for another way...
What is he up to?! He's heading west!
Y-You bastard!
Of course I will!
Does he want to bring the HQ down?!
--He holds a guitar!
--What is he gonna do?!
--There are still that many?!
--You gotta be kidding!
What is it this time?!
Listen, you all. I, good-looking Duval...
If I left him alone, he'd
probably end up dead.
You don't have to do anything!
It's enough that you're a freak!
Oh no...
Guys, don't worry! Captain Apoo will save us!
...won't let you fools become popular...
What is he gonna do with the Ox Bell?
Alright, a freak! Call me whatever you like!
He's not-so-bright and high-maintenance!
I mean, take our ally's ship!
I won't make that popular...
--Listen, guys!
--Yeah!
"Loneliness" is no longer
a part of my vocabulary!
I mean, mistake!
Must be hard to have a captain like that.
--Let's run!
--What?!
You screwed up your whole speech!
Uh-huh. That's why I wanna help him.
As long as I live, I won't let you
touch the Young Master's ship.
I can't beat that big group of violent boars!
But, everybody, isn't it boring to just look?
Like he helped me.
I'd rather touch a girl...
Oh, I made mistake!
--What's this rhythm?
--It makes my heart skip a beat!
Hey, tell me about the Weather ball.
Captain, there's only a dead end ahead of us!
It's not that simple. That's one of
the great inventions of Weatheria!
I mean, you can't touch it! Right, guys?
Save yourselves however you can!
--Oh no! We're dead!
--Don't give up!
If you misuse it, it could
turn the world upside down!
Yes, Rose-Some!
Check out my latest single -
Let's go!
But we're gonna fall into the water!
It could be used as a weapon?
Bone to be Wild!
Duval-chin, you're so cool!
Who cares! Jump!
Hey, hey, that's too dangerous.
What?!
Don't smile like that!
Because I'm so handsome,
girls won't leave me alone!
Huh?
Captain, we're running in the air!
Meanwhile, near the giant
bridge in the East Blue...
I-I love you, too!
EAST BLUE - GIANT BRIDGE
The boars are coming
after us in the air, too!
I can see that! What's
wrong with this island?!
Mermaid Cafe should be the
first! It's very sophisticated!
What made you change your mind?
No, the most popular place
on the Fish-Man Island
Now you agree to go to Baltigo with us.
Nami!
is the Fish-Man Karate training hall, Camie!
It's hot!
Well, we're really glad anyway.
Youre my friend!
Dragon-san has always longed to meet you.
I promised Bones that I'd introduce
him to the Mermaid Princess!
SAN JUAN WOLF
My legs can't take it anymore.
My body's exhausted.
Duval-sama! She's not aware of you!
I didn't know there are people like you.
Ouch, some fish bit me.
I wish that you guys had
come to see me earlier.
Oh yeah! Don't mind me!
NEW WORLD - SOME BURNING ISLAND
I-I'm sorry!
Stop complaining, Wolf!
Shakky-chin, we can get together
again using the Vivre Card, right?
We didn't know that you
were allied with Crocodile.
The raft was almost broken because of you.
Now we learned that Luffy-chin's
alive from today's newspaper!
That's why we're doing this.
Just kidding. I'm just teasing you.
It was so reckless to try crossing the
New World by raft in the first place.
No offense but I'm glad that
things turned out this way.
I think so. It will take a little time but...
...Ray-san met Monkey-chan
using it without any problem.
Let's go! Let's head for Baltigo!
MARSHALL D. TEACH
We should've taken a Navy ship at Marineford.
Flowers?
Meanwhile, on the Mechanical
Island Future Land Baldimore...
We have to protect this ship until then.
But you can't help becoming
attached to things.
JESUS BURGESS
We're here to do that, sis!
You guys don't prepare for anything.
SHIRYU
The unexpected bombing at
Dr. Vegapunk's laboratory!
Whether it's the Navy or somebody else,
This is gonna be a great picture!
Let me handle it!
AVALO PIZARRO
we won't let anyone take the ship!
You want me to be captain, Teach?
We haven't found who did it!
LAFITTE
Hey, hurry up!
I'm counting on you!
Shut up or I'll kill you.
We're Blackbeard Pirates.
Duval-sama, we have a
crisis! Here comes Kuma!
Heaven knows what'll happen to us... Oh...
DOC Q
It's not too much to say that it
was a greatest loss of our time!
Kuma?! There aren't any
bears on this island...
Do you have any information?
Go and meet your friends
VASCO SHOT
who must be waiting for you
somewhere out there, Robin!
I heard there was an intruder
that looks like a gorilla.
That's...!
I need more drinks!
Can we go to an island with a town?
How mysterious!
CATARINA DEVON
Chase him! Don't let him get away!
--A bounty of 79 million berries?!
--For an 8 year old girl?!
In order to reach the harbor of this
island, you need a large ice-breaker.
Yeah, I'd prefer some
gorgeous outfit to a ship!
Now he's leaving...
It's the Warlord - Bartholomew Kuma!
What was that all about?
She's a survivor of the demons of Ohara,
I'm sick of this jail clothing.
Dark King Rayleigh and
the Warlord - Jimbei...
You have to live with it.
But no one has seen one.
who attempted to destroy the world.
I can't live with it forever.
Are they taking his side?!
That Ohara?!
They say that the intruder was Cyborg
Franky of the Straw Hat Pirates
Rayleigh was a crew member
of the King of the Pirates.
I don't know how she did it,
Me, neither! How much longer should we wait?!
but they said she sank 6 Navy ships.
Does that mean Straw Hat
is Roger's successor?!
but he's just been seen on Sabaody
Archipelago within the past month and...
Is the Navy coming?
N-No way! He's Dragon's
son! That can't be true...
That's why the price is so high...
VAN AUGER
I'll go and look. They can't be this slow.
...we don't know how he
could've gotten to Baldimore.
She shouldn't be alive!
She's the child of a demon!
Don't panic! He came to see Ray-san before.
In any case, this is...
No, they can't!
Captain Gorilla! The search team
is leaving for the mountains!
These guys are getting tired of waiting.
...big news!
Alright, wait there!
Okay! I'm coming with them!
You're on our side, aren't you?
Why did you come to help?!
Th-This is...!
Right, Jewelry Bonney?
The hidden entrance has been
uncovered by the explosion.
JEWELRY BONNEY
When did I ask you to do that?!
Captain Bonney...
What a surprise. We didn't
know about this place.
Meanwhile, at Sandy Island - Alabasta
Kingdom in the Grand Line...
I can't believe it.
I can't believe they put a price of
over 100 million on a girl like you!
I want to die already!
There was another laboratory!
This article has spread all
over the world already!
The capital - Alubarna...
The working cyborg animals
must have been created here.
The New World is the sea
for the chosen strong ones.
I understand Robin's enemy very well.
It even covers the fact that
we let Straw Hat get away!
Although you came all the
way from the South Blue,
What happened to the pirates?
Shoot that flag.
Hey, don't break anything!
How humiliating!
you can't go any further.
We chased them away. The
city is virtually undamaged.
You can't talk to me like that!
If you look at it simply, what
Straw Hat did was pay a tribute...
In the laboratory that was blown away,
I see. Good job.
...to his brother and Whitebeard and
all other people who died in the war.
there
were some far-out inventions useful in daily life.
We're tightening our
security across the country
You're too weak to join my crew but...
No way!
No doubt about the moment of silence
and going around the island
but pirates have become more active around
the world since Whitebeard's death.
But what I wanted to know about
are the weapon inventions,
Are you guys insane?!
How about this? You can come
with me if you become my girl.
You think you can live when the
whole world is your enemy?!
but the bell should only have
been rung twice not 16 times!
like the ones here.
We have to be careful for the time being.
I'm looking forward to it!!
To go further. Huh?
I wish all pirates were like
Luffy-kun and his crew but...
So the 16 bells could be a challenge to us!
This is great! Everything from
battleships to human cells...
Screw you!
You bearded pig!
Robin!
...they're not.
How did he come up with
all these kinds of things?
He got turned down.
Honestly! How controversial he is.
I need to hear you saying it!
Speaking of which, King, have
you read today's newspaper?
No good! You're indecent! Women
need to have some decency!
Straw Hat Luffy...
Yes, of course.
Okay! I made up my mind!
But it's not so surprising
considering he's Garp's grandson.
Say that you wanna live!!
I already have an indecent crew!
Vivi-sama was happy about
Luffy-kun and the others.
I'm gonna live here!
I wonder how he knows Rayleigh.
Huh? Live here?!
Thank you for saying that!
Yeah!
I bet she is.
I don't think Rayleigh wants
to come back to center stage.
I'll come down the mountain sometimes
But...
A FEW HOURS AGO
Let's just give her over to the Navy
to get more cola from your place.
Jimbei finally turned against us.
If you allow me to say what I
want, even a little bit, I...
and get a ship in exchange as we planned!
Okay?
He being a Warlord was a
symbol of intertribal peace.
Karoo!
Don't worry!
Captain. The Navy is coming.
Look at this, Karoo!
As long as you don't tell anybody,
Luffy-san is alive as I thought!
What a shame!
I won't cause you trouble
because I'll live here.
They brought a ship for us?
The Three Great Powers are off-balance now.
They brought one but they
won't give it to us.
...wanna live!!
I'm glad! I'm so glad!
Don't panic every time you see my face!
How should we fill the 3 vacancies
among The Seven Warlords?
Take me out to sea with you!!
Huh? How can you tell?
--Don't look at us!
--That scary face is getting scarier!
Huh? What is this?
How's this? A tiger rug!
We need to see what will
unfold in the New World.
Because Akainu is on it.
In just a moment, she became very serious.
Damn! That's not what I want now.
And as soon as she made that face,
There'll be some changes in power
relationships among pirates.
--That's not bad...
--F-F-F-Franky!
Let's go, guys!
she took the newspaper to her room.
We have to pick the most powerful ones.
Robin-san, come inside. It's cold out here.
--It's cold especially my legs.
--Why don't you wear your pants?
We messed this one up!
Blackbeard made his move
already in the New World
I'll stay here. I'm a pirate and
you people are Revolutionaries.
--Okay, now it's warm!
--Why don't you just wear your pants?
What's on Luffy-san's arm?
Numbers? Marks?
and took out one of the rookies
with a bounty of over 100 million.
--Did you catch Blackbeard?
--He's gone!
I can't trust you so easily.
But you said you wanted to get off
of this island. What happened?
When I heard that you escaped
from the Government,
Or is it some new fashion?
I can't just go into a
cabin that has no exits.
He knows all there is to know
about Whitebeard's territory.
I don't think so. Luffy-san wouldn't do that.
it made my blood freeze.
Well, not much but...
Please! We don't bear any
hostility toward you!
But it's all over now.
He has a lead over the pirates who want
to become one of The Four Emperors.
Let me stay here. This is how I
got through when I was on my own.
My dream...
You bastards! I won't forgive you!
No one has ever eaten 2 Devil
Fruits in history except for him.
I want you to sail on the ship...
Meanwhile, at some city in some
country in the Grand Line...
I'm sorry. I understand.
Hey, bring as many blankets as you can!
...that I built!
THE HOLYLAND OF MARIE JOIS
And something hot to drink and eat, too!
The people who might be able to
stop him are The Four Emperors...
Luffy...
Disappeared?
Yeah, to be honest.
You let me hold a dream.
But it's all prepared inside...
H-Hey, why is he here on this island?
--Hurry up! And a wind guard and a sofa, too!
--Yes, sir!
...or Marco the Phoenix and the
remnants of the Whitebeards.
Whose idea was this?! Sengoku?!
Shh! He can hear you!
Franky!
It's only been 3 weeks since the war.
Luffy, do you think I can get stronger
No, someone much higher up the ladder!
Thank you for the ship!
It's always the "D."s who make
trouble including "Portgas."
They just barely escaped death...
by swimming with the flow of the times...
It's a great ship! I'll take good care of it!
...under your father?
Those names are exposed to the public
a little bit too much these days.
It's not a metaphor. Literally,
it was like "poof."
If you want these shorts back,
...and what are they doing now?
you'll have to join us!
I never thought that I'd
want to get stronger...
I was surprised. Is that the
power of the Shadow-Shadow Fruit?
They've got to be up to something.
If not, they're just crazy.
You brought me out into this big world!
...for somebody else.
It's no joke!
Don't worry. He was dying.
You think so, Daz?
Straw Hat is wounded and wounds
won't heal that easily,
We'll cross many seas and have
tons of battles and challenges.
Nothing can save his life.
That's right. Unless he arises as a zombie.
don't you think so?
You smart ass! Are you being sarcastic to me?
And when we get to the end of the sea,
I tried to talk him out of it
but Garp virtually resigned.
Well, he looks like one!
RED LINE THE HOLYLAND OF MARIE JOIS
You've done such sloppy work!
I will call it "the ship of dreams."
Meanwhile, on Bowin Islands
in the Grand Line...
I'm healed.
Hey, don't get cocky!
But he has to keep his
title and stay in the Navy.
GRAND LINE - BOWIN ISLANDS
In fact, I'm gonna head back
to the sweet old New World.
When did you become my boss?
Hey, Luffy.
Educating young Navy soldiers.
The Thousand Sunny still
has some life in her.
What is it this time'n, Usopp'n?
No matter how powerful you are
in the Government, I'm a pirate!
First, I'll lose weight!
Then, improve my strength!
You coming?
If you want to resign from your
position as fleet admiral,
You're the only captain who can make it...
It doesn't matter to me!
Oh, you better do that!
could you at least do that?
Of course.
..."the ship of dreams."
And get stronger!
When I lose interest in doing
business with you guys,
Sengoku.
Yeah, that's the only way
to get off of the island'n!
Yes, sir.
I'll acquire skills that'll enable us to have
I accept that offer. It's not a
bad way to spend my retired life.
I'll quit as a Warlord anytime!
And get much stronger!
Don't ever forget that.
Yeah, that's good, too'n!
an even more harrowing adventure than before.
And get much, much stronger!
So Luffy...!
Oh? Th-That much'n?!
The two of you who have led the
Navy at the front since Roger's era
Much, much, much, much, much, much stronger!
Hey, the tiger is burning.
are stepping down.
Wow, you've become so serious'n!
That's going to make quite a splash.
You suddenly got with it...
Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
Including the escaped prisoners
from level 6 at Impel Down,
What was it in that newspaper'n?
The news about Luffy's recent exploits...
What is that?!
A monster?! Watch out!
there are a lot of infamous
pirates still on the loose.
SOUTH BLUE - BIRDIE KINGDOM
...has reached each crewmember's hometown...
Meanwhile, at the Birdie Kingdom...
Each of the Straw Hats has begun
moving in different places as well...
And Newgate was at the top of the list.
I received a message from our captain.
A message?
The Pirate Era is changing now
What're you talkin' about? Get on already.
Racoon is gone now.
So Luffy, we have to get over
the rough sea of the New World!
and old soldiers shouldn't
cling to power in the Navy.
Eh?!
We're friends now, aren't we?
Look at this, Ace!
Justice is based on values. And
those change every generation.
The birds feel the same way we do.
You saved your brother's
life - Luffy is alive!
We're looking forward to
see you again, Racoon!
This incident will be known
around the Grand Line
That's not what I want to hear.
By the way, Kong-san,
as the Legend of Baldimore's
Sacred Burning Beast.
I want to recommend Aokiji
for next fleet admiral.
Rest in peace!
Luffy!
Now, let's get back to work.
U-Usopp...? You... You came here, too?
Meanwhile, in the Grand Line...
NAVY HEADQUARTERS--MEDICAL CARE FACILITY
They call the power Haki.
Beat him! And we'll all
go back together, Luffy!
Ah? What is it?
Sorry girls, for the long trip.
It's safe to say that's what you got.
That's...!
Of course!!
Don't worry, we're used to travel.
--The bird came back!
--Huh? It's too soon!
I guess it was awakened
by the trauma of the war.
At the Kamabakka Kingdom, Grand Line...
What are you doing?
We have to make sure that you're resting.
Hey, what was it you saw in the newspaper?
I thought...
Normally, you can only obtain
it through long-term training.
--Oh? I don't see Racoon.
--What happened to Racoon?
...that Luffy could become the King
of the Pirates without my help.
It's Snake Princess-sama's order.
I see!
Snake Princess-sama collapsed from too
much heart-fluttering a while ago.
--Maybe he fell into the water!
--That's not good! Let's go look for...
You got so calm all of the sudden.
Haki...? That's what it is?
I received Luffy's message because it's
exclusively for his friends,
The vice admirals are all using it.
That's why we have to keep an eye on you.
We made it here finally!
Really?!
from the newspaper.
We'll see this wall again when
we go half way around the world!
Wh-Who is it?
I hope that they'll get it.
If you don't believe that I'm his
friend, I'm not gonna tell you, fool!
As a matter of fact, in order
to defend peace in the world,
And by that time, I'll be
the King of the Pirates!
This guy's annoying!
They'll get it if they see the article.
I fight evil because I'm the
hero of justice - Chopper Mask!
But I was wrong.
The key is your actions and how
uncharacteristic they are of you.
Hey, who made this meal?
There are a lot of
enemies who are beyond his power.
Hey, stop!
Oh, you have quite a discriminating palate!
I feel other people's presence too
strongly...
There is one guy who looks a bit dull.
Luffy could lose.
It's uncomfortable...
It tastes good and oddly, I feel
like I'm overflowing with energy!
But I'm sure he'll manage
to understand it, too.
He's pushing himself and crying out for help!
Ra-Racoon!
You two are apprentices to Garp, aren't you?
They will understand you
very well. I have a feeling.
I know I said "come see us again"
but isn't it a little bit too soon?
Ask him about it.
That's why...
Hey, doctor! Do you think
I will get the power, too?
...he needs my support!
That's right! It's a dish of aggression!
No, you're wrong! I'm not him!
Up in the air above the Grand Line...
How do I know?
Maybe we look alike but I'm
his friend--Chopper Mask!
There are a lot of chefs who
can make that on this island!
Dammit! It's like you're ahead of me now!
--Yes!
Heracles'n, I wanna get stronger!
It's too obvious, Racoon.
Yes!
Oh yeah! I got it, Luffy!
You're wearing a disguise because
you feel embarrassed to come back?
I wanna get much, much, much stronger and...
Look at the beautiful tough
bodies of these candies!
I don't know what's going on...
I got it now! Okay! Okay!
No! I said I'm...
But what is this feeling?
It's like I'm a different person from before!
And their gentle hearts.
Hey, Master Heracles'n...
On the giant bridge in the East Blue...
The candies grew like this by
eating the dish of aggression!
What? M-Master'n?
Maybe... If I try hard, I can get stronger!
Are you okay, Racoon?
I've been curious about your weapons.
Don't make me repeat myself!
I'm his friend and I'm...
What you eat is important for your condition,
You guys, don't be such jerks.
You're strong enough to live
on such a dangerous island.
physique, and personality!
Much stronger than I am
now... As strong as him!
I see. That's what it is.
It builds the whole human body!
You gotta play along on these occasions.
I wanna learn a lot from you!
Huh? What's the matter, Robin-san?
Strong? Am I a strong master'n?
If all the people in the
world drink milk everyday...
--We got confused!
--Yeah, that's right!
Yes, you are a strong master!
I'm sorry! I couldn't hold the fort!
Roger that, Luffy.
--So you're Chopper Mask! Cool!
--Yeah, you don't look anything like Chopper!
And... my name is...
there'll be less crime - don't you agree?
...Heracles'n!
What a cool name!
Kamabakka Kingdom...
Sorry, sorry, we were...
So, it's good to be aggressive!
Don't mind it!
A-Alright, why don't you sit down, Usopp'n?
That's enough! It's too pitiful!
Food builds body? I never
thought about it that way.
Oh, Racoon!
Yes, master!
He was alive, huh? Amazingly!
Listen, my pupil Usopp'n!
I see, Luffy!
There are many plants in this forest
I can help them building their
bodies with daily meals.
Did you hear about it? Straw
Hat caused trouble again.
What's going on?
called Pop Green, which
grow hostile instantly.
That tickles! You fool!
Yes.
The War of the Best ended not so
long ago and the 16 bells now?
Bowin Islands...
But besides that,
And these are the seeds'n.
what'll I do if Nami-san and Robin-chan
get sexier than they are now?!
I...
Pop Green?
Is this some kind of message?
The thing is, I suddenly have something that
I need to do.
...have to...
Each of them has an effective usage'n.
--What should we do with this guy?
--What should I do?!
...get off of this island!
I don't know.
Can I stay a little longer?
That aside, what about my transfer?
Whatever the reason, you're always welcome!
Usage'n, huh?
I'm burning with passion!
Wait for me, Luffy!
Teach me how to cook the dish of aggression!
Bowin! Bowin!
Well, I'll talk to Sengoku-san
about it but are you serious?
There are many plants
Bowin Islands!
The answer is "No!!"
that I've never seen in any
book growing on that big tree.
Run, Usopp'n! This forest
will make you stronger!
No one would say such a thing as a joke.
Ouch...
Let me study them.
That was very wishful thinking!
To make you the King of the Pirates,
I know. G5 is not a place
that you go voluntarily.
Then we have a suitable place for that.
This "99 - Vital Recipe" is...
I'll
become the real King of the Snipers!
I need to improve my strength, too.
No matter what you have to say to me,
...a part of the New Kama Kempo
techniques - Training for Married Life!
That place has a bunch of problems.
I have a lot to do.
Oh, Racoon! You're back already?
I gotta go see Luffy!
Navy - Grand Line 5th branch.
I can't just teach it to a nobody like you!
That's great!
Meanwhile, on the Gloom
Island in the Grand Line...
How's that? Have I finally
reached the edge of this island?
You guys, I'm gonna stay
on this island for a while!
GRAND LINE GLOOM ISLAND -
THE RUINS OF MUGGY KINGDOM
That means you wanna go to the New World.
If you wanna learn it, you gotta
have a girlish heart and...
the ruins of Muggy Kingdom.
It's better to be closer to your target.
You only traveled 20 meters'n.
Okay, this is it.
Please!
...learn the New Kama Kempo!
No!
What's this place?
No way!
This is...
Damn! What's wrong with my body?!
The news about Straw Hat Luffy
is spreading all over the world.
I wasn't born to become friends with ladies.
Oh, I'm hungry!
Train me as a swordsman!
NEW WORLD
Even in the New World...
Don't, Usopp'n!
I was born to...
I'm disappointed in you, Roronoa!
You're falling into
the island's trap by eating madly'n!
"Straw Hat Luffy was alive!"
EUSTASS "CAPTAIN" KID
...love ladies!
...the library of our
village. You can study here.
Gah!
Shut up! Leave me alone!
Are you asking your enemy for instruction?
"Rang the 16 bells for a
new era in Marineford."
Heehaw!
So many books!
Shame on you.
What's the Ox Bell?
There are more! To the very end!
Get out of here. I have
no time for a boring man.
You're quite a reasonable man. I like you!
The Ox Bell is...
I think I was overestimating you.
I got it!
Okay, I'll give you a chance!
Cool!
...the holy bell from the Ox Lloyd's,
What is it this time, Usopp'n?
A chance?
All these books are about the plants
and the medicines that I wanna study!
KID PIRATES--KILLER
a Navy ship that was quite
influential a long time ago.
I got it, Luffy!
I'll hand out the recipes to 99 grand masters
What are you doing? That's just embarrassing.
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
And there're so many!
At the year's end, they ring it 8
times to appreciate the passing year
The Sky Island - Weatheria...
There are so many plants on this island
that you can make medicine out of.
of the New Kama Kempo on this island.
I wanna get stronger!
You were beaten by the baboons
and 8 times at the beginning of the
year as a prayer for the new year.
If you're a real pirate, get
all the recipes from them!
And we knew how to make them
but the birds were in our way
and you couldn't get to
sea, so you came back here.
So they ring it 16 times in total
- that's the Navy's custom.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, young girl.
I have nothing to teach someone like that.
so we couldn't get the plants and
make medicine - we were stuck.
However, every new kamas on this island
That's the meaning of the 16 bells.
Shh! That's too much!
I was judging the people on
this island by their looks
will try to put this sweet
dress on you day and night!
But they closed the Balloon Terminal
I beat the baboons.
But it's not the season yet.
but when I think about it, their
weapons are very high-tech.
so we have nowhere to run since
this Sky Island is so small.
He beat them?
So maybe he did it to announce the
end and the beginning of the era.
I wonder if you can maintain your manhood.
You're the only one left to beat here!
They look like they're dumb but...
But I have to run! Think of something!
He wants to say,
But I'm not so stupid as to think
that I'm good enough to beat you!
...their cultural level is pretty high!
--Sanji-kun!
--We won't let you sleep!
It's not that easy... Can we
go back to my place for now?
"Whitebeard's era is over.
I'll shape the new era"?
I have a lot to learn!
The sweet dress!
What?
I don't understand.
Racoon!
If it's not for those purposes, he
wouldn't go back to the place...
I'll bring back the exciting
feelings of wearing skirts!
You thought you were saying that to
yourself, but you actually said it.
You still see me as an enemy.
...where he has to relive the
pain of losing his brother.
Sanji! It's nice to be girly!
Then why are you bowing to me
and asking for my guidance?
And that was very rude...
I wonder how much I can do in this country...
What's the purpose?
What an annoying bastard!
You...
Hey, hey, can't we go in?
...vs. the home of the New Kama Kempo!
I wanna beat you!
In fact, after the war,
Hey, what's that thing?!
he took the lead among the rookies
with a bounty of over 100 million.
I see.
It must be the Snowman!
If you can win this fight, I'll give
you a ship, too! You can have it all!
Honestly! He's not thinking
about how we feel - how selfish!
It's dangerous! Tell the
kids to get in the house.
But I won't let him do whatever he wants.
So what do you say?!
Gun! Bring me the gun!
You're asking me to train a
swordsman who wants to kill me?
Young girl! They're coming!
Kill it! Go away, monster!
Future Land Baldimore...
Hey you, cook!
The New World...
You're weird. And what
you're asking is nonsense.
Don't let it come any closer! Kill it now!
Join my group!
I thought I could have a lot of fun
here but what's with these cowards?
Even so, what you're doing
is still embarrassing.
Huh?
Be the cook on my pirate ship!
--It's the Snowman!
--Kill it!
Seems like you found something
more important than your ambition.
Come on! I didn't cause any harm to you!
--Don't let it get away!
--Kill it!
I won't die.
Grandpa, what do you think
happened to the old man?
We were about to get out of this sea!
Let us go back to paradise alive!
Hey, ghost girl, treat him.
Listen, Kitton, forget about everything.
Hey, don't tell me what to do!
Paradise? You mean, a loving home?
About that man and about the incident.
The training will begin
when you're recovered.
I'm not gonna die here.
You just got here so you have no
idea how horrible this sea is!
That was a big explosion.
There's no way that he's alive.
Dammit! Everybody keeps
demanding so much of me!
You see idiots like that
every once in a while...
I told him not to push the
self-destruct button repeated...
ones who will fight to the death once
they've set their eyes on a target...
Come on, move it now!
Skull?
This is a symbol of the belief
that nothing is impossible.
...ly...!
What?!
What a clumsy fool.
Straw Hat?
When a man like you swallows his pride,
By raising this, I'll fight
just like pirates do!
1, 2, 3!
Yes, he caused trouble again.
I can't hear your answer -
does that mean you give up?
Oh, boy!
it's always for someone else.
CAPONE "GANG" BEGE
No need to be panic.
It's cool to be a pirate!
The one who has the final checkmate...
Old man!
There're tons of incredible guys at sea!
Yeah, if you lose...
"3D" is crossed out and "2Y" is written?
...will become the winner.
When I win...
Chopper, go out to sea some day.
What happened?!
Oh yeah! There is a tattoo on his right arm!
When I beat all of them, I bet I'll
be much stronger than I am now.
Father! The ship is not touching
the water - it's in the air!
If you do, you'll understand very
well how small your problems are.
We made a promise to meet again
at a certain place 3 days later.
This island you were born on is
like this compared to the world.
What?!
What did you say? What do you
mean? Control the ship, dammit!
Even if hundreds of weapons are built in,
But we couldn't make it.
Really?
So "3D" means "3 days"!
No, it's smaller! Like this! It's true!
he can be defeated by someone with
a spear of blind determination.
Father! Something's coming
down from the sky...
I see!
But "3D" is crossed out and "2Y"...?
Hey, Luffy, don't lose.
No, we are going up!
Your future lies beyond that sea!
--2 years!
Tehna Gehna Kingdom...
The meeting will be 2 years
later instead of 3 days later.
But I'm hoping to go some
day... to the Grand Line.
Hey! Let's be pirates together!
And everything else was done
just to get all the publicity.
NEW WORLD FOODVALTEN ISLAND
I'm so sorry.
Then let's go now.
It's true... that I wanna be a pirate but...
This is a message exclusively
to us. Luffy made a decision.
It's not the right time yet.
BASIL HAWKINS
Could you say it again? I couldn't catch it.
There is no time to relax for
me in a place like this...
I'm not even a human! I'm a monster!
--Say... do you know the All Blue?
--No...
--Hey!
--Yes.
I'm Brownbeard!
Even if we rush now, we're not good
enough to get far in the New World.
Finished eating? I'll take the plates.
A pirate with a bounty of over 80 million!
I can't become your friend! So...!
Oh, you don't?! It's a miracle sea!
Go ahead. And I thought I
asked for the newspaper...
We have to stop once and get stronger.
Brownbeard-sama!
So I just came to say thank you...
Make sure you remember my
name! This is my territory!
And meet again no matter what!
We both have foolish dreams.
Maybe there is a follow-up
story about my friend.
What you did to my men is horrible!
Hm?
I do appreciate you guys.
Honestly! You don't even have eyes.
How can you read a newspaper?
In order to achieve my goal, the All Blue...
I'll make you pay for it in blood!
Thank you for asking me to join you.
I see. I thought I misheard it
because it's such a stupid name.
Hey, I told you to rest!
Sanji?
I'll stay here, but...
I-It irks me to hear someone mention that.
Yeah. I'll come along... on your journey
to become "King of the Pirates"!
one day... if you feel
like it, stop by agai...
You're up soon! Give it everything you got.
I'll tell you two things.
First, I don't like jokes.
What?
Shut up! Let's go!
Here you go.
I'll be the cook for your ship.
Jokes?
Luffy-san!
And here is another thing,
Thank you for waiting!
Luffy, if I can see you again...
I can see the shadow of death on your face.
Behold! The Supernatural Moving Skeleton!
What are you...?!
...I'll...
That doesn't work!
I'll give you the greatest
support in the world as a cook
W-Who the hell are you?!
so you can become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy took me out to sea.
Oh, is that what it's all about?
I'm Monkey D. Luffy!
Are you sure that the Log Pose
is pointing at that island?!
I was desperate to just follow him.
After...
The man who's gonna be King of the Pirates!
I understand, Luffy-san!
Have I done anything to help Luffy?
Lightning is striking the island like rain!
...I live through...
Until the day I defeat him and
become a master swordsman...
UROUGE
...this hell!
The ruins of Muggy Kingdom...
We can't go there!
I'll never... be defeated!
Got any problems with that...
Hey, wake up! How long are
you gonna stay asleep?
I don't wanna go through that again.
I accept...
Seriously! How many times
do you wanna get beaten?
How can we get to the shore?!
...the challenge!
...King of the Pirates?!
But, at that time...
I'm taking care of you - see it from my side!
Great! We won't go easy on you!
Bold men who set foot in
the New World even once...
Nope!
Mind your own business!
There isn't enough time
for everything anyway.
I'm looking forward to it!
Oh yeah? I brought you today's
newspaper that I got from News Coo!
High Priest, somebody is approaching!
Alright, let's do it!
So let's do it.
Who is it?
Sanji-kun!
...all call the first half of
the Grand Line the same thing -
There is an update on your captain!
Don't give me the cold shoulder!
You said you beat the baboons.
--Shut up!
--Otherwise...
Say, young man...
What did you say?!
They acquired their swordsmanship
by copying humans.
Luffy must have felt more
pain than the rest of us!
Who is this grandma?
There are ranks among them
and there is a master.
"That sea was like a paradise."
H-Hey, you! What did you just say?!
I can't lose here!
He is the leader that rules all
the baboons on this island.
R-R-Relax! You better relax!
Because he let me join his crew,
No!
Do you want an umbrella?
I no longer care what people say to me!
Doesn't work!
Hey, are you done yet? My hands hurt.
If we stay here, we'll be dead soon!
That sword is...
He mastered it by copying what I do.
Give me a minute! There should be a catch...
I got you!
We just wanna go back to paradise! Please!
He's different from the
baboons that you fought.
Luffy doesn't do these kinds of things.
If it helps him,
You're such a wet blanket.
Sounds like fun!
I'm not gonna lose either, Luffy!
He's with Rayleigh - it
must be Rayleigh's idea.
I'm gonna get much, much stronger!
I can become a real monster!
If you're not prepared to die...
I'll fight you now!
I know there is a catch.
I don't care - just hurry up!
Chopper!
Get the recipe from me - Caroline!
...then stay out of...
Chopper!
...this sea!
This is great!
I'm gonna get revenge for the other day!
I'll take you down soon!
You better be ready for it!
Luffy!
Here I come!
I promise you that I'm gonna get stronger!
I will win!
Straw Hat!
See you at Sabaody Archipelago in 2 years!
Luffy's messages have
reached his friends safely.
The Straw Hats have decided to become
stronger and reunite in 2 years.
Reports on the new incident
involving Luffy at Marineford
Luffy's friends have received his messages.
Just as Luffy's friends are
receiving his messages,
Nami, in Weatheria,
the pirates, who have made
their way to the New World,
spread throughout the world
in the blink of an eye.
and Franky, in Baldimore, take
action in their own ways.
Taking Luffy's feelings to their own hearts,
Luffy arrives on the
uninhabited island Ruskaina,
begin to fight over who will take
Whitebeard's place as one of the Four Emperors.
The people are bewildered
by his mysterious actions,
his friends make a decision
toward pursuing a new goal.
And Sanji, in Kamabakka Kingdom,
where he begins training in a new power
as are his friends.
in order to face new enemies and adventures
They meet at the captain's side once more,
throws his all into an epic battle to learn a
secret handed down in the kingdom for generations!
As the battle intensifies, a Navy admiral
arrives to put down the pirates!
But Luffy has a reason for his behavior.
their sights set on the day they'll
set out on a new adventure!
awaiting him in the New World!
What exactly is Luffy thinking?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Living through Hell! Sanji's
Fight for His Manhood!"
"Luffy's Training Begins! To the
Place We Promised in 2 Years!"
"Pirates Get on the Move!
Astounding New World!"
"I Will Get Much, Much Stronger!
Zoro's Pledge to His Captain!"
"With Hopes It Will Reach My
Friends! Big News Spreading Fast!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!