Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
Am I getting stronger?
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
I don't know the answer yet
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
So let's go
saa yukou
Without stopping
tachidomaru koto naku
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
The voice inside of me
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
keeps sustaining me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
Wicked rain will get in my way
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
But I won't walk away
nigedasanai kara
So let's go
saa yukou
Without stopping
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
To the future I believe in...
shinjita sono saki e to...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy lost his brother Ace in the
War of the Best against the Navy.
He sent a message to his crew
in a manner that no one
else would understand.
I hope that they'll get it.
They'll get it if they see the article.
They will understand you very well.
I have a feeling.
Oh yeah! I got it, Luffy!
I got it now! Okay! Okay!
I see. That's what it is.
Roger that, Luffy.
I see, Luffy!
I got it!
I got it, Luffy!
Honestly! He's not thinking
about how we feel - how selfish!
I see!
Oh, is that what it's all about?
Luffy doesn't do these kind of things.
He's with Rayleigh - it
must be Rayleigh's idea.
I know there is a catch.
"Pirates Get on the Move!
Astounding New World!"
Since Whitebeard's era ended,
GRAND LINE - NEAR THE SABAODY ARCHIPELAGO
ambitious pirates have begun
to stir in audacious ways.
But not Trafalgar Law...
--Huh? We're not gonna go there yet?!
--Let's go to the New World already!
How much longer are
we gonna hang around here?
What are you waiting for, Captain?
I said we're going to wait for our time.
TRAFALGAR LAW
Don't worry.
The great One Piece treasure
won't go anywhere.
But Blackbeard's already started
making moves in the New World
and there's a rumor he
destroyed a pirate crew!
Big time rookies who want to
become one of The Four Emperors
are rushing to the New World!
There's no time to lose! We'll
be beaten by everybody else!
It's better for us if they're
trying to destroy one another.
We won't get involved in those petty fights.
Stop griping and just follow me.
We'll get what we want at any cost!
--Captain!
--We will follow you forever!
Aye-aye, Captain! You can count on me...
Sleep talking?!
--I'm sorry.
--Don't apologize while you're asleep!
NEW WORLD--SOME WINTER ISLAND
It's so cold! My body's gonna freeze!
Is anybody here at a place like this?
X. DRAKE
--What's that?!
--Something's falling from the sky!
Oh no! Run!
Guys, are you okay?!
I'm fine over here.
Damn! What's going on on this island?
Captain, let's pull out of this island!
I don't think anybody's living here!
You don't think so?
Anything can happen in this sea.
Look at it.
What's that semiround pile of snow?
The icicles are stuck in it!
It's not a pile of snow! It's an iron dome!
Look! The dome is opening up!
I didn't expect to see a town in the dome.
The famous Kaido-san of The Four
Emperors, loves this island.
And I'm in charge of security here.
And? What do you want from us?
Nothing. I just warned you.
You better not piss him off, rookie.
You mean, if I kill you or something,
Kaido won't leave me alone?
That's right. So why don't you...
That makes it easier for me!
Oh? An ancient Zoan type? How rare!
Scratch! Boom!
NEW WORLD--SOME SPRING ISLAND
Check it out!
SCRATCHMEN APOO
That was a pain in the butt!
--That's our Captain Apoo!
--So dependable!
--There are still that many?!
--You gotta be kidding!
Oh no...
Guys, don't worry! Captain Apoo will save us!
--Listen, guys!
--Yeah!
--Let's run!
--What?!
I can't beat that big group of violent boars!
Captain, there's only a dead end ahead of us!
Save yourselves however you can!
--Oh no! We're dead!
--Don't give up!
But we're gonna fall into the water!
Who cares! Jump!
What?!
Huh?
Captain, we're running in the air!
The boars are coming
after us in the air, too!
I can see that! What's
wrong with this island?!
It's hot!
SAN JUAN WOLF
My legs can't take it anymore.
My body's exhausted.
Ouch, some fish bit me.
NEW WORLD - SOME BURNING ISLAND
Stop complaining, Wolf!
The raft was almost broken because of you.
That's why we're doing this.
It was so reckless to try crossing the
New World by raft in the first place.
MARSHALL D. TEACH
We should've taken a Navy ship at Marineford.
But you can't help becoming
attached to things.
JESUS BURGESS
You guys don't prepare for anything.
SHIRYU
Let me handle it!
AVALO PIZARRO
You want me to be captain, Teach?
LAFITTE
Shut up or I'll kill you.
We're Blackbeard Pirates.
Heaven knows what'll happen to us... Oh...
DOC Q
VASCO SHOT
I need more drinks!
Can we go to an island with a town?
CATARINA DEVON
Yeah, I'd prefer some
gorgeous outfit to a ship!
I'm sick of this jail clothing.
You have to live with it.
I can't live with it forever.
Me, neither! How much longer should we wait?!
Is the Navy coming?
VAN AUGER
I'll go and look. They can't be this slow.
No, they can't!
These guys are getting tired of waiting.
Right, Jewelry Bonney?
JEWELRY BONNEY
Captain Bonney...
I can't believe they put a price of
over 100 million on a girl like you!
The New World is the sea
for the chosen strong ones.
Although you came all the
way from the South Blue,
you can't go any further.
You're too weak to join my crew but...
How about this? You can come
with me if you become my girl.
To go further. Huh?
Screw you!
You bearded pig!
He got turned down.
No good! You're indecent! Women
need to have some decency!
I already have an indecent crew!
Thank you for saying that!
Let's just give her over to the Navy
and get a ship in exchange as we planned!
Captain. The Navy is coming.
They brought a ship for us?
They brought one but they
won't give it to us.
Huh? How can you tell?
Because Akainu is on it.
Damn! That's not what I want now.
Let's go, guys!
We messed this one up!
--Did you catch Blackbeard?
--He's gone!
When I heard that you escaped
from the Government,
it made my blood freeze.
But it's all over now.
You bastards! I won't forgive you!
THE HOLYLAND OF MARIE JOIS
Disappeared?
Yeah, to be honest.
Whose idea was this?! Sengoku?!
No, someone much higher up the ladder!
It's not a metaphor. Literally,
it was like "poof."
I was surprised. Is that the
power of the Shadow-Shadow Fruit?
It's no joke!
Don't worry. He was dying.
Nothing can save his life.
That's right. Unless he arises as a zombie.
Well, he looks like one!
You've done such sloppy work!
Hey, don't get cocky!
When did you become my boss?
No matter how powerful you are
in the Government, I'm a pirate!
It doesn't matter to me!
When I lose interest in doing
business with you guys,
I'll quit as a Warlord anytime!
Don't ever forget that.
SOUTH BLUE - BIRDIE KINGDOM
Meanwhile, at the Birdie Kingdom...
Each of the Straw Hats has begun
moving in different places as well...
Racoon is gone now.
The birds feel the same way we do.
We're looking forward to
see you again, Racoon!
Now, let's get back to work.
Ah? What is it?
That's...!
--The bird came back!
--Huh? It's too soon!
--Oh? I don't see Racoon.
--What happened to Racoon?
--Maybe he fell into the water!
--That's not good! Let's go look for...
Wh-Who is it?
As a matter of fact, in order
to defend peace in the world,
I fight evil because I'm the
hero of justice - Chopper Mask!
Ra-Racoon!
I know I said "come see us again"
but isn't it a little bit too soon?
No, you're wrong! I'm not him!
Maybe we look alike but I'm
his friend--Chopper Mask!
It's too obvious, Racoon.
You're wearing a disguise because
you feel embarrassed to come back?
No! I said I'm...
Are you okay, Racoon?
Don't make me repeat myself!
I'm his friend and I'm...
You guys, don't be such jerks.
You gotta play along on these occasions.
--We got confused!
--Yeah, that's right!
--So you're Chopper Mask! Cool!
--Yeah, you don't look anything like Chopper!
Sorry, sorry, we were...
That's enough! It's too pitiful!
Oh, Racoon!
That tickles! You fool!
The thing is, I suddenly have something that
I need to do.
Can I stay a little longer?
Whatever the reason, you're always welcome!
There are many plants
that I've never seen in any
book growing on that big tree.
Let me study them.
Then we have a suitable place for that.
I need to improve my strength, too.
I have a lot to do.
Oh, Racoon! You're back already?
That's great!
You guys, I'm gonna stay
on this island for a while!
Okay, this is it.
What's this place?
This is...
...the library of our
village. You can study here.
So many books!
There are more! To the very end!
Cool!
All these books are about the plants
and the medicines that I wanna study!
And there're so many!
There are so many plants on this island
that you can make medicine out of.
And we knew how to make them
but the birds were in our way
so we couldn't get the plants and
make medicine - we were stuck.
I was judging the people on
this island by their looks
but when I think about it, their
weapons are very high-tech.
They look like they're dumb but...
...their cultural level is pretty high!
I have a lot to learn!
Racoon!
You thought you were saying that to
yourself, but you actually said it.
And that was very rude...
I wonder how much I can do in this country...
Hey, what's that thing?!
It must be the Snowman!
It's dangerous! Tell the
kids to get in the house.
Gun! Bring me the gun!
Kill it! Go away, monster!
Don't let it come any closer! Kill it now!
--It's the Snowman!
--Kill it!
--Don't let it get away!
Skull?
This is a symbol of the belief
that nothing is impossible.
By raising this, I'll fight
just like pirates do!
It's cool to be a pirate!
There're tons of incredible guys at sea!
Chopper, go out to sea some day.
If you do, you'll understand very
well how small your problems are.
This island you were born on is
like this compared to the world.
Really?
No, it's smaller! Like this! It's true!
Your future lies beyond that sea!
Hey! Let's be pirates together!
It's true... that I wanna be a pirate but...
I'm not even a human! I'm a monster!
I can't become your friend! So...!
So I just came to say thank you...
I do appreciate you guys.
Thank you for asking me to join you.
I'll stay here, but...
one day... if you feel
like it, stop by agai...
Shut up! Let's go!
Luffy took me out to sea.
I was desperate to just follow him.
Have I done anything to help Luffy?
I don't wanna go through that again.
But, at that time...
Luffy must have felt more
pain than the rest of us!
Because he let me join his crew,
I no longer care what people say to me!
If it helps him,
I can become a real monster!
Chopper!
Luffy!
I promise you that I'm gonna get stronger!
Luffy's friends have received his messages.
Nami, in Weatheria,
and Franky, in Baldimore, take
action in their own ways.
And Sanji, in Kamabakka Kingdom,
throws his all into an epic battle to learn a
secret handed down in the kingdom for generations!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Living through Hell! Sanji's
Fight for His Manhood!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!