Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
2 years have passed since the war between...
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
...the Navy Headquarters, The Seven Warlords, and the Whitebeard Pirates.
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
On the desert island north west of the Maiden Island - Ruskaina...
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Luffy!
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
Yeah! I'm coming!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
I can't believe it. It's been 2 years already.
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
saa yukou
So let's go
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
Hey!
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Look carefully. She's my friend.
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
Luffy, the ship is ready to sail out at any moment!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
Okay, thanks!
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
That's amazing.
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
He's the boss of the island now.
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
But because I became friends with them, I couldn't eat them.
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
saa yukou
So let's go
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
They look yummy.
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
It's okay, Luffy.
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
We put everything that you like on the ship.
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
And I think I'll be a good wife since I'm thoughtful like that.
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
I'm not gonna get married. Thank you for the food!
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
I can't help loving you even if you're so bitter!
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
Rayleigh left 6 months ago.
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
He must be waiting to see you at Sabaody.
He was done teaching me the basics in first 18 months.
I have to say goodbye to you guys and the island.
WE GO!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Alright...
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training
Let's go!
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training
and returned to Sabaody Archipelago
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
and returned on Sabaody Archipelago
to go on to the next stage - the New World.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates, once attained everything this world has to offer.
to go on to the next stage the New World.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Did you know about this?
What is Soul King?
The words he uttered just before his death drove people around the world to the seas.
Oh, about Brook.
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
Oh!
"The Navy Has Set Out! The
Straw Hats in Danger!"
What? Nobody has arrived yet?
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
He might not...
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
...come back to do pirating again.
Find it! I left everything this world has to offer there!
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
Check the poster once again!
This is exciting!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Look!
It says "At least 70 million berries bounty."
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
We're not gonna deal with
captains with less bounty.
The crew, on its way to the New World,
Oh, you guys!
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Go home.
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
I'll only say it once!
Realizing the importance of friendship,
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
You're no match for me so I'm
not gonna drink with you!
Luffy went back to Marineford at
Dark King Rayleigh's suggestion.
This is Grove #46.
Sure Kill: Green Star...
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Rookies who have joined the
Straw Hats keep showing up here.
And the rest of the Straw Hats got a message
through the news
..."Devil"!
about Luffy's mysterious behavior.
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
I see some captains.
So, young lady, do you wanna drink with me?
Luffy doesn't do these kinds of things.
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Sunny!
I know there is a catch.
Oh yeah! I got it, Luffy!
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
I got it now! Okay! Okay!
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Sorry to keep you waiting for 2 years.
Come on, baby!
I see. That's what it is.
Yeah!
"Big Guns Assembled! The Danger
of the Fake Straw Hats!"
Because I'm a skeleton, it's...
I see, Luffy!
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
I'm glad that you're fine!
Bone!
I got it, Luffy!
I'm a real man--Sanji!
Just come back from hell!
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
Honestly! He's not thinking
about how we feel - how selfish!
Brook's concert?
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
What an attractive woman before me!
The Straw Hats' recruitment?
You're our super archaeologist -
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I see!
What is going on?
Oh, is that what it's all about?
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Sorry to keep you waiting, Sunny!
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
I understand!
We'll be sailing out soon!
Robin, aren't you?!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Thank you!
See you at Sabaody Archipelago in 2 years!
Thank you, baby!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
Oh, did it hit you? Sorry!
Oh, here we go!
"Luffy's Training Begins! To the
Place We Promised in 2 Years!"
45 degrees!
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
Bye!
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
A FEW DAYS AGO - IN THE CALM BELT
Wait a minute!
Thank you!
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Huh?
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Here he comes.
That was great!
"An Explosive Situation!
Luffy vs. Fake Luffy!"
the future that I’m aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
--Here you go, sir!
--Oh yeah!
You haven't changed, Franky!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Jimbei! Thank you for everything!
I've changed, silly!
No, I should be thankful to you!
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
Look at my body - it's full
of romantic masculinity!
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
Look upon this fantastic transformation
such as no one has ever seen before!
This feels great!
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
Although I begged you to set
me free from Impel Down,
I'm beyond human understanding now!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
It sinks into my bones...
I'm ashamed of myself for being still alive.
Yeah, it's probably hard to
see you as a mere human now.
This is not good...
I'm sorry!
WE GO!
Hey, hey, you mean I'm a pervert?
That's Sabaody Archipelago in the distance.
I told you to not say such a thing.
Ring, ring, ring...
You're good at praising people!
Luffy, we have to say goodbye here.
If it weren't for you, Jimbei,
I probably couldn't have
made it to the Navy HQ.
Ring, ring, ring...
SHAKKY'S RIP-OFF BAR
We can't let them discover our relationship.
SABAODY ARCHIPELAGO GROVE #46
So show your face.
This is Grove #46.
Uh-huh.
Put this on...
A MEETING SPOT FOR THE STRAW HATS
It's been 2 years.
There are more than 100 pirates here now.
This is the coating?
It went by fast when I look back now.
...like this!
I don't need that! That's too much!
It's like jelly.
Yeah.
That's right! Rayleigh is really skilled!
Yeah?
If they all work for Straw
Hat Luffy, it's gonna be...
I can't wait to see how much they've grown.
But in case something happens...
Now we can go into the depths of the sea!
You're right.
Uh-huh.
What a technique!
You have to be careful.
There may still be something I
can do for you again in the future.
Don't be hasty.
Make sure you hide your face.
We don't even know if they can all get together safely.
I just saw Rayleigh and the others.
Hey, what's wrong?! Answer!
So you went to the bar.
The world thinks that you're dead but...
In any case, see you at the
Fish-Man Island in 2 years!
Because they're infamous throughout the world now.
What number were you?
This is bad news!  Tell the backup to hurry!
8th.
...people know what you
look like from 2 years ago.
I'm looking forward to the day when
you and your friends visit us!
Everybody's here except for Luffy.
Hey, hey, hey!
I see. We'll begin a new journey soon.
If you cause trouble, you
won't be able to set sail.
Yeah!
I was wondering who you were,
but you're a Navy soldier!
I've got the ship in top condition.
I got it.
Take care!
And in the backpack, I put 50 extra
changes of clothes, 1000 lunches,
Oh gee!
A new weapon is ready, too!
Oh!
What is going on here?
handkerchiefs and tissues,
Luffy, I'm glad that you
got back on your feet.
Ah, you're the first to arrive.
5 years' worth of towels, 3 years'
worth of water and snacks,
I can't wait.
Your hands, your smile, and all
of your casual gestures make...
By the way, where are the others?
silverware, toothbrushes, soap,
What? Nobody has arrived yet?
I saw Usopp and Sanji here
then Usopp went to get fuel
Oh! Oh! Don't tell me...
hand creams and 3 years' worth
of bug bite ointment and...
...my heart flutter and twinge!
They never change.
Make it lighter!
If nothing is done, I could
die from this fluttering!
and Sanji went food shopping.
...that you just informed the Navy-san?
I see. Actually, on my way here,
I hope you can meet your friends safely.
"The Beginning of The New Chapter! The Straw Hats Reunited!"
Yeah. Thank you for everything!
I found this.
I feel dizzy...
What?
Are you okay, Hancock?
Did you know about this? What is Soul King?
He's a Navy soldier!
Good luck!
N-No, I haven't called them yet!
I've heard Sabaody has
become unsafe these days.
Oh, about Brook.
OVER 10 DAYS LATER AT A BAR
I was just about to...
Don't worry!
Yeah, I knew about it.
I saw his TD everywhere.
Oh no, I don't want you to!
Yes. That's why the Navy is paying a
lot of attention to what goes on there.
We'd like to go to the training spot.
Can you take us there now?
Otherwise, there's gonna be blood all over!
He's quite a shining star now.
Take extra care!
I-I see!
Yeah!
Hey, set sail for Ruskaina!
Did you know that the Navy HQ has been relocated?
You and your friends' blood!
If you need us, we Kuja Pirates
will always come to help you!
From the dark, silent, foggy sea,
Yes, Snake Princess-sama!
What? Was it?
Isn't it right, Coribou?
he made it to the footlights,
where people cheer for him.
Yeah, they switched its place with the G1 branch
Huh?! I'm sorry, brother, I'm so sorry!
Don't forget it.
A DESERT ISLAND NORTH WEST OF
THE MAIDEN ISLAND - RUSKAINA
symmetrically over the Red Line.
I'm here, you fool!
And could you do me a favor?
That's how determined the new Fleet Admiral after Sengoku is.
This island is perfect.
What? I'm not gonna marry you.
I'm sorry!
He might not...
It has 48 seasons a year, so it
changes weekly. It's a harsh island.
No, I just want you to leave
without saying goodbye.
No that way, you dumb fool!
After all, he set up the HQ in the sea where The Four Emperors operate.
...come back to do pirating again.
Caribou, the Navy soldier killer!
Oh, I see.
GROVE #33 SABAODY DOME
Oh, I've never said it to anyone.
But thanks to the switch, the HQ has less sway here
Luffy!
...King is mysterious
I wanna see you again.
so there are more lawless areas on this island.
I'll bring food for you everyday
from the Maiden Island!
Hmm, no wonder this town seems rougher than 2 years ago.
He's nothing but bones!
Alright, I'm off!
What?! Really, Hancock?!
--See you!
--Take care, Luffy!
Afro on the skull! Girls love the contrast
Hey, did you see this?!
Could you bring that
specialty-gorgon-something?
See ya!
Yeah, I was shocked, too.
He said he wants to see me again!
I can't believe the Straw Hats have surfaced again!
That was so good!
Is it what they call...
O-Of course!
Wow, Snake Princess-sama!
Yeah, no one has heard from them for
If you wanna make out with her
...a proposal?!
No, it's not!
2 years so we thought they were dead.
I can bring anything you want in any amount!
Got milk! Got milk!
Enough jokes.
URGENT CREW NEEDED
I can't believe they're recruiting!
I've been told by Hancock
not to cause trouble.
You need calcium more than protein
And that was the 10th time
that you said my name!
--He did it!
--He's true to his reputation.
Pirates who survived through the first half of the
Hey, did you hit me on purpose?
Grand Line keep coming to this island.
Oh, gods, have mercy!
I-It means we're engaged now!
So he wants to expand his group here to run wild in the New World!
H-He's in danger!
No, it doesn't! And why are you backpedaling?
Captain!
This silly Navy soldier tried to reach
his weapon and attempted to kill me!
Captain Luffy!
GROVE #13 SHAKKY'S RIP-OFF BAR
It's so exciting! Maybe I wanna join!
Wh-What?!
You said that you were married a while ago!
Damn!
The stupid swordsman got here first?!
Luffy!
No way!
Please have mercy on him!
Hancock! I don't want you
to spoil him like that!
There are people with bounties over 100 million on the island now.
I can't believe it!
I missed you guys!
I'm sorry, gods, I'm so sorry!
Our new voyage will be rough.
They're not gonna take you for sure!
Hey!
While Luffy-kun is training,
women are not allowed to be here!
Luffy!
And Franky-chan came
second, about 10 days ago
What?!
Bury him, Coribou!
Franky!
What?!
and went out to see the ship.
Bury this sinful Navy soldier alive!
Nami!
What gives you the right to decide
those kinds of things, Rayleigh?!
Sunny is alright?
Of course--there isn't even a
scratch and the coating is done.
Okay! I dig, I dig...
I'll turn you to stone
depending on your answer!
Sogeking?!
W-Wait a minute! Don't do it!
Cool!
That's good.
We can find things to eat in
mountains, forests, rivers and sea!
He did a good job.
You guys have changed in these 2 years!
I didn't call for the Navy!
There's no regret for honorable wounds!
I bet you got stronger!
That's enough, Caribou!
Hey, old man! Give me a drink!
Not his nose! Stop, Snake Princess!
Yes! A year to heal!
Hmmm...
And something to eat, too! As much as you have!
If you can't live like that,
you should not be a pirate!
It's the Straw Hats.
I didn't know you had such
a strong sense of duty.
Just dispose of that small-time
Navy soldier somewhere.
Y-Yes, right away!
What are they doing on the street?
Hey, could they be...
What just happened was...
It's all for Luffy-kun's benefit!
Thank you, Duval.
Don't look them in the
eye. You can't fight them.
What, you think I'm handsome?
I have no doubt! They're...
Here comes Captain Straw Hat Luffy!
Did you just say "it's
all for Luffy's benefit"?
I returned your favor, young master!
The Straw Hats...
Even on rainy days and windy days,
Dammit!
You guys, look around you!
Yes.
It's all for Luffy...
dangerous pirates tried to steal that ship.
What happened to you?
You probably don't know each other
GROVE #33 SABAODY PARK
I don't know!
But I fought day after day
even with cuts and bruises!
but you are all gonna
work for me from now on!
Then I'll be patient!
I felt chills all over my body!
A CONCERT HALL SABAO DOME
It was very painful!
As a crewmember of the Straw Hats!
But, Rayleigh, this island
is truly dangerous!
Duval-sama!
What kind of trick did he use?
If anything goes wrong...
Even so, how did you get hurt so badly?
Oh yeah! We have another problem.
That's why it's good for his training!
That means when I become
the King of the Pirates,
Well, fall for me... I mean,
listen to me, young master.
Just pray for him if you feel concern.
The thing is Cocoa got...
you're gonna be a shipmate of the King!
No, I mean... Nico Robin got...
--That's because the Navy finally...
--And Nami-chan came third...
Shall we go, Luffy-kun?
Hey, don't say that!
Yeah!
To make that happen, from now on,
Nami-san!!
Can't you do anything...?
What did you say, Zoro?!
--Luffy!
--Good luck!
Tickets are sold out! Of course they are!
you guys should wait on me hand and foot
Nico Robin has been abducted?!
Where's she?!
and fight for me at the
risk of your own life!
I'm sorry. It happened in front of our eyes.
She went out shopping to kill time.
Yeah!
It's the world tour of the superstar Soul King Brook!
No interest in my story anymore?!
Luffy, please be safe!
Yeah, that's right! This is serious, Luffy!
It's like a dream to work under
Nami-san's shopping! Nami-san's shopping!
the unheard-of pirate
who caused trouble at...
And today is the last show!
She could be kidnapped like Camie!
...all of the 3 strongholds of the World
Government: Enies Lobby, Impel Down, Navy HQ!
The place is already packed!
Usopp-chan came fourth 3
days ago and went to town.
Chopper-chan came fifth yesterday.
You ought to remember this tree.
Who did it?
Brook-chan has a concert
today on this island...
I have no idea.
Manager!
Even savage beasts stay away from it.
He'll be one of the strongest candidates
for the King of the Pirates!
Captain.
I'll put on a great show today!
A concert?
It's the only safe area on this island.
I think people who have a
problem with the real Robin
What's that?
This is what they call
"getting on the bandwagon"!
And then you came.
Yes, that'd be nice!
Hmm, it's kind of funny looking!
have taken Cocoa by mistake.
So 7 members including you have
already arrived on this archipelago.
Your TD is doing very well and they were sold over million copies now!
That's possible.
Most of them are here already.
She really looks like the real
Robin but that worked against us.
You certainly are the king of soul music!
We haven't seen Nico Robin and Luffy yet.
Is that it?
Can't wait to see everybody!
Listen to the crowd!
Hey, stop talking in whispers!
It's extremely difficult
just to get to this island.
Soul King! Soul King! Soul King! Soul King!
Now, we are the only humans on this island.
So you guys are all quite something.
Oh well, let's leave it at that.
Shut up!
Manager...
I'm glad that you can meet them soon.
That's her fate.
Before the concert,
Look at this vast wilderness!
--What?!
--What?! Okay, Captain.
Yeah. But I can't believe
that you trained Luffy.
We asked you to assemble here because...
I heard there was a country
here a long time ago.
Hey, Luffy! Robin has been abducted!
I have something important to tell you.
But humans have lost the
struggle for survival.
...I've had my honor insulted - your
big boss who is important to you all!
He must be incredibly strong now.
What is it?
I've been thinking, what is this creature?
Nature here is relentless
and the land is rough!
I haven't seen him for 6 months.
Can't wait to see his progress.
Is that a joke?!
Progress...
Don't say that even if it's joke!
The perpetrators have to be somewhere
here on this archipelago!
I wonder what kind of progress Nami-san made!
How can he speak? Is he a stuffed animal?
I want you to find them and drag them to me!
Take it back, Luffy!
Hey, are you alright?
Shut up!
Y-Young master?
Come on, baby!
Consider it done, boss!
But I endured 2 years of arduous training.
Yeah!
More importantly, assemble the 100
members that we recruited here
I won't forgive those fools!
Because I'm a skeleton, it's...
So I have to shake off any sign
of seduction and show my results!
Bone!
Well, people change a lot in 2 years.
on this island at Grove #46!
--Bone to be wild!
I smell a great adventure!
You guys don't talk much now, do you?
He's just saying that!
That man who has a long nose.
--Bone to be wild!
That woman with long orange hair.
This mustache guy knows the
real Straw Hats as I thought.
GROVE #47
That brat with a cape and a huge backpack...
Bone!
There are a lot of savage
beasts! They're uncountable!
Run!
Bone!
Find those three
Who is he?
Bone!
I don't know but he'll notice so don't talk.
Some thugs are fighting again!
--Bone!
and make them regret that they
messed with Straw Hat Luffy!
--Bone!
Bone! Bone! Bone!
I thought that the pirates would
settle down after Whitebeard died...
Bone!
All we gotta do is take him to Captain.
There are about 500 living things here
beyond your capabilities now.
--Roger!
Okay.
It's the opposite!
We must try not to kill them
before we bring them here.
And I don't think you two
were ever so friendly.
They're coming from everywhere
You have to get stronger, or
you can't even sleep at night.
This is a good opportunity to
show them how formidable we are!
and the whole island has become lawless!
It's nonsense to become macho just to attract women
How are you able to know
about them and their number?
But maybe 2 years has changed all that.
I didn't know that. It's dangerous.
Okay, let's go!
Wait a minute, you guys!
Your looks have changed also.
This is something that concerns you.
You must obtain this power.
Are you guys wearing disguises too?
The last 2 years changed your personalities?
Soul King is mysterious
Did you get it?
Luffy!
Blackbeard, Kid, and Drake are doing
I... I... feel sad...
The power called Haki!
whatever they want in the New World
Hey, wait!
He's nothing but bones!
and can't help crying!
Haki?
and we're the ones who'll
follow... I mean, beat them!
Encore! Encore!
Again, what is this creature?
What about Robin?
--Hey, look!
--Th-They are...
Why don't you guys say something?!
I can't believe it... How selfish can he be!
Encore! Encore! Encore!
Huh? How can he talk?
Oh no! Something is here, old man Rayleigh!
What they say was true as I thought.
Toys today are pretty well-made!
Hey, give me a Transponder Snail!
Hey, it's right behind you!
They were thought to be dead fighting
against the Navy 2 years ago
I see. The Navy, huh?
Dammit! I'm disappointed in you guys!
Listen, Luffy-kun.
I'm not gonna let you do whatever you want, Brook!
Haki is a
latent power that everybody has!
I got it.
Don't push!
I'm gonna go help her alone!
but they showed up again on this island.
Let's make today a great anniversary!
Soul King, come on now!
It's an elephant! 5 times bigger
than usual! What an elephant!
Yeah, and they're the most powerful
pirate group on the island...
I need a little more time.
Yes... My fans are calling for an encore...
The Straw Hats...
Wait for me, Robin!
Presence, fighting spirit, intimidation...
Huh? Is it Nami?! Usopp?!
It's no different from the
senses that normal humans have.
What? The Straw Hats...?
What happened?
"Pirate Hunter" Zoro. A
120 million berry bounty.
They had a fight among themselves?
...and they won't stop so I'll go back.
That's...
However, most of them
don't realize their power
I've missed Sabaody.
There's no doubt!
I'm finally back.
Straw Hat Luffy and other
or don't know how to bring
them out, until the very end.
"Black Foot" Sanji. A
77 million berry bounty.
members may look radically
different from 2 years ago
but no one else has a weird pet like that!
Having no doubt!
She obtained a bounty at
the age of 8. Nico Robin.
Women! Real ones!
They're...
That makes you strong!
An 80 million berry bounty.
...the Straw Hats! They're alive!
Ah, there's no doubt!
And a cotton-candy lover--Tony Tony Chopper.
Watch out!
There are actual ladies in front of me!
Thank you for waiting, everybody!
This is Grove #47. We identified
the pirate group - the Straw Hats!
A 50 berry bounty!
Second Gear!
It's too low!
Jet Pistol!
"THE STRAW HATS" ZORO SANJI ROBIN CHOPPER
These are the real ladies that I've longed for
every single day, on this island!
Who is there? Is Luffy there, too?
It seems like the pirates
that Straw Hat recruited...
Viva Sabaody!
Move out of my way!
I need lady!
URGENT CREW NEEDED
Damn... What an elephant!
...on this island are
assembling at the Grove #46!
They're a good match for us!
He's not just strong, but fast!
Sanji-kun!
Let's do it!
There is something that
I have to tell you guys.
Wait!
Understood! Roger that!
We'll leave you here.
Why're you stopping us, Captain?
I don't want to part but see you again somewhere!
Go now and help the locals evacuate!
If we cause trouble with them,
Straw Hat Luffy won't keep quiet.
Watch very carefully!
Roger that!
There are two prominent types of Haki!
Pirates are gathering at Grove #46!
I don't wanna see you again!
It's not wise to have an
unnecessary conflict before
Thank you for the ride! Say "hi" to Ivan! Bye!
The target is the Straw Hats!
Watch out!
we go to the New World!
Don't worry.
We'll make a raid on the lawless area!
I'm a real man - Sanji!
Today, I, Soul King, will...
He's trying to hit me with
his nose from the right.
Just come back from hell!
Get ready for action!
Close in on them from Grove #40, 42, 44!
You know what they say?
This is it! The show is over!
Boys can't help swearing at a girl they love.
The Navy? Why are they here?
Backup from G1 will come soon!
I know. It happened to me.
It's the power to feel other's
presence more strongly,
Hey, Zoro! Sanji!
The acting captain of the Rumbar
Pirates - "Humming Swordsman" Brook.
I don't wanna let him go!
called Observation Haki!
Robin! Wait for me!
Wait for me, Nami-san, Robin-chan!
A 33 million berry bounty.
S-Sentomaru-san!
What is that talking racoon?
We suspect that you're this pirate!
Awesome...
Huh? What are you talking about?
I'm gonna go first!
If you enhance this power, you can
tell where your invisible enemy is,
Racoons can't talk...
In addition to that,
I'll take PX-5 and PX-7 with me!
we have information that you're
working for Straw Hats Luffy now!
But...
Ah? Did I hear it wrong?
and how many there are, and
what their next move will be.
I heard that you got here first, Zoro!
Oh, you're deploying Pacifistas?!
Soul King Brook!
Can't believe you didn't get lost.
A 55 million berries bounty?
Of course!
No, Pirate Brook!
A left leg kick!
Sanji and Robin, you guys finally made it!
You're under arrest!
A PIRATE "STRAW HATS" CAPTAIN - MONKEY D. LUFFY
Mantra.
You are all underestimating the Straw Hats!
Check the poster once again!
You see it?
It says "At least 70 million berries bounty."
Yeah, I've never seen something like that.
It's been 2 years since the war now.
No, Brook-sama is not...!
They call it Mantra on
the Sky Island--Skypiea!
We're not gonna deal with captains with less bounty.
He might cause us trouble. Ignore him.
Soul King is a criminal?
They must have gotten stronger!
He's a pirate?
How did you guys even get here safely?
They're different from any of the other
rookies who have come to this island!
But I heard Straw Hat Luffy was dead!
Oh, wait!
Oh, damn!
Hey, wait a minute!
Next, the Armament Haki.
It's all over, Brook.
Dammit!
Our target, Nico Robin,
is a Devil Fruit eater.
This power is the same as
wearing invisible armor.
Go away, pest.
What was behind
I thought that you guys might be behind this,
It'll be painful if she fights back.
Don't you know that I'm Dragon - the Revolutionary's - son?!
the Kuma-kou's doing from 2
years ago is still a mystery...
Let's catch her off guard!
Manager.
NAVIGATOR - NAMI
It was shocking to me when
you told me honestly
Old man!
SHIPWRIGHT - FRANKY
We don't need some half-ass!
I better hurry up. I wonder
if they're all here.
about your retirement backstage.
But when I examined his eccentric behavior
carefully after he lost his personality,
Because we're the chosen pirates!
You've became very popular so we
were about to make a lot of money.
SNIPER - SOGEKING
We're in another league.
I want Nami-san and Robin-chan
to try my improved food soon!
I was able to deduce that the
Straw Hats would reunite one day!
Don't think that just anyone can join us.
You betrayed us!
And our company will be out of business.
I-I've seen it before.
Before that, I better go see if
the kitchen in the Sunny is okay.
Go home.
Ashigara Dokkoi Shove!
Let's go!
And then, go food shopping!
Let's die together, Soul King.
He's so merciless. Straw Hat Luffy!
Is that Sanji?
If the armor is hard enough, it can
be used as the offensive power.
Can't be helped - he has achieved a lot.
Why don't you say something?
Hey, Franky. How many people we got so far?
Ouch! I'm a rubber man
so I shouldn't feel pain!
Did you hit me knowing who I was?
This is an efficient part of this power.
About 100 people.
Did you see it? You made me look like a fool.
3 whole pirate groups joined us.
Other than exploiting their weak
point, this Armament Haki is...
You humiliated me in public.
10 of them are with a bounty.
That's good. 2 of the 10 are high-profile rookies.
It shouldn't happen to me.
...the only effective countermove
against Devil Fruit eaters.
I'm an elite pirate with
a 400 million bounty!
GROVE #17 THE ISLAND
WHERE THE SUNNY IS DOCKED
Cool!
Kneel down on the ground in fear now
"Wet-Haired" Caribou and "Blood Splatter" Coribou
Isn't it?! His body is amazing!
Oh, it's reacting! So I think it's this way.
and beg for your life!
Logia-type Devil Fruit eaters
who are known for killing Navy soldiers.
seem almost invincible
because of their fluid body
They're captain brothers with 210 million and 190 million bounties.
but you can hit them solidly.
Oh, that's why you could touch Kizaru!
It's great to have them!
You're like a robot!
Let's get more followers! Old man, we need more drinks!
Can you shoot beams or missiles?!
And that means I could land a blow
against Smokey of the Navy or Aokiji!
What can you transform into?!
You got hurt because you messed with me.
Y-Yes!
Yes! With the dreams and enthusiasm
of men riding on his back,
Hurry up!
Damn!
Run!
Oh? And you woman, who's been there for quite a while.
he goes into action now!
You can transfer this power to your weapon.
His name is...
Have you ever seen the Kuja's arrow?
There are too many pirates...
...Armored Me!
Stop drinking alone quietly and come join us!
Yeah...
Robot! Robot!
She's cute.
Hmmm, maybe I should put it on.
It was almost like a steel arrow!
Calm down, Chopper!  Too much
excitement could kill you!
Just...
Observation Haki, Armament Haki...
Just apologize!
Doesn't he wanna live?
Those are two types of Haki.
Hey sister, can't you hear me?!
I said, give me a better discount.
But, Franky,
However, there are a few rare people
who can use another kind of Haki.
you can't do detail work with
those huge hands, can you?
I think you realize now how
audacious your actions were!
N-No way, ma'am!
Hey, he's talking to you.
You're asking me to sell these
many clothes for half price?
What did you say?
That's okay. I'm waiting for someone.
That's a bit...
Whoa! A hand!
That's why you're so scared
that you can't even talk!
Hey, Nami.
A hand came out from a hand!
Watch.
What?
You can buy clothes at the Fish-Man Island!
She turned him down.
A few moments ago, a man who
has a long nose and a woman
Robin!
Hey, hey, you better say yes!
We need to buy fuel...
No!
Nami!
He's Straw Hat Luffy!
You look great!
with long hair messed with us
Remember?
He's the crazy pirate who burst into the War of the Best 2 years ago!
Here! I'll buy these too
so discount them by 90%!
so our captain is in a bad mood.
What's wrong with his body?
You better apologize now.
You know him, right?!
No!!
Kneel on the ground!
I don't know. I don't understand.
Waiting for someone?
Otherwise, you're gonna throw away
your life with just one mistake.
Hey, hey, you got better at
bargaining after 2 years.
He must be a wimp who'll apologize in tears
Oh, this is the coating?
once he hears Captain Luffy's name anyway!
Press my nose.
Our captain pulls his trigger very easily.
So come here now!
Nose?
Press it for a long time.
More than 3 seconds...
I'll only say it once!
Kneel on the ground already!
He's Straw Hat Luffy!
Hey, Moss Head!
Please press the nose
for more than 3 seconds.
You're no match for me so I'm not gonna drink with you!
You gotta stay with me!
He tried to sound like a robot!
He wants to get killed? Apologize!
I don't want you getting lost.
Exciting! Exciting!
Huh? Who do you think you're
talking to, Mustache Eyebrow?
I'm really sorry!
1, 2, 3...
What?
I better go now.
Do you understand, Straw Hat... who?
What did you just say?
Whoa! Hair!
What's wrong with him?!
Hair...!
Oh! Something smells good...
Can you set your hair?
Yes, I can!
Oh, it looks good!
Okay!
--Wow!
Hi!
Very well!
Oh, Nami! Hey!
Try some!
Oh, how dazzling! There's
a woman within my reach!
Okay, okay...
What was he doing for 2 years?
That was the power to intimidate your enemy!
Can I see your weapon? Can I?!
Conqueror's Haki!
Oh? That bastard! Where did he go?!
The people who are the biggest names...
No way! That's the main event -
you gotta wait for Luffy-mecha.
I need a fishing pole to fish.
Did you say "who"?!
...often have this power.
Oh, a fishing store.
I'm Straw Hat Luffy!
He moved like a robot!
However, unlike the other two,
He said "mecha" at the end!
Hey, you better apologize! You're in danger!
He's not here... That bastard!
you can control the Conqueror's Haki
but you can't train yourself to use it.
Guys.
Huh?
Rayleigh-san! Shakky!
That's because it's the
owner's spirit itself.
Robin!
I'm sorry to interrupt your reunion but...
You can enhance it only
by developing yourself!
You've got a lot of nerve!
Where did they take her?!
...there are things going
on on this archipelago.
Oh, that's what you did at the auction house!
What?!
Damn! Damn! Damn!
Let me handle it.
Pirate Brook!
Drop your instrument and
put your hands in the air!
Hey, did he do something?
You know what it is.
Damn!
Hey you! You're a funny woman.
You have awakened the ability
of Conqueror's Haki already.
What happened to everybody?!
Hancock was right. I should put it on.
Band.
Then I'll make it easier for you.
Luffy, Zoro, Nami, Sanji, Franky...
Don't do it!!
Backup singers and dancers!
Are you gonna drink with Captain Luffy?
I want you to support me for one more song!
Or do you wanna die?
They used to be so compassionate!
Hey, Zoro! Sanji! Robin!
For your information, I have a bounty, too.
Robin is abducted and he
says "leave it at that"?
I'm a cat burglar - Nami!
Don't worry!
We finally see each other
but you're acting weird!
My music's got power!
Don't mess with me!
How awful is that?!
Zoro and Sanji, you guys did
pretty well in these 2 years.
Sure Kill: Green Star...
What have I been working
for for the last 2 years?
Are you insane?
It's all over for you, Brook.
But why aren't you guys talking to me?
But don't use it until you become
capable of controlling it fully.
..."Devil"!
Manager, thank you for everything
during the past 2 years.
For whom?!
Hey, he's still following us.
Because you would intimidate
innocent people around, too.
Oh, you're being shy, you bastards!
Huh?
Wh-What is this?!
And thank you for bringing
me here to this archipelago.
Hey, Chopper!
And that racoon knows about us
the Straw Hats a bit too well.
What is this?!
Hey!
We have a sad memory of losing
a fight on this archipelago
Hm? What's wrong?
Help me, Captain!
I've been thinking about that,
too, but maybe... Look at this.
Here, here!
You fool! Stay away from me!
but this is where we start again!
I knew it was Chopper!
What is that plant?
Amazing!
I'm a musician.
Don't tell me he's...!
A crewmember of the King of the Pirates
So, young lady, do you wanna drink with me?
My role in the Straw Hats is
to make the journey more fun!
can beat these beasts
without even touching them!
Usopp!
Oh man, you got so big!
The real cotton-candy lover--Chopper,
a 50 berry bounty!
People think Straw Hat Luffy is dead?
You must be comfortable to ride!
So he's their pet!
Do you respect me a bit now?
You guys changed a little. But I don't care.
That's nonsense!
Doing okay?
Usopp, long time no see!
Uh-huh!
He's right! You're much softer than before!
Tell this to the whole world!
I can't believe it! You became stronger!
But I've seen those Haki
powers at various places!
He was abandoned on this island before
The pirate - Straw Hat Luffy is alive!
they died and he's been living in the wild.
You have blossomed yourself!
It's been a long time, Chopper!
He thinks his masters are back
and that's why he's following us.
Shanks, grandpa, Eneru, Aisa,
What?! She had been waiting for that geek?!
Oh?
Hancock and the Kuja warriors!
Then let's get rid of that
fox and take him instead.
Nami?
Yes.
He will become the King
of the Pirates someday!
Did you do that?
If the pet looks the same as the
poster, we'd look more authentic.
Yes, I bet you have.
Yes, I did! That's my new weapon - Pop green!
Oh yeah!
But learning
how to use Haki is not easy.
Head Office, can you hear
me? I have some big news!
I'm glad to see you guys but
this is no time for that!
We're gonna keep him? What does he eat?
It's not like I was watching the sea and doing nothing for 2 years.
Looks like cotton candy.
His departure shouldn't
be a quiet one! Oh baby!
Robin is in trouble!
Uh-huh!
We don't have any.
I'm sorry
We don't need you anymore! Go away!
but I no longer belong to the weak trio with you and Chopper.
Soul King!
Huh? You mean they're imposters?
I became a warrior who isn't fazed by anything!
Usually, we'd need more time
but you're well qualified.
Love me to the bones!
Come here, Chopper.
That's why there are 2 Namis?
Yeah!
Hey, dude! Is this what you've done?
Oh please!
I'm gonna teach you the basis of
Observation Haki, Armament Haki,
It's a cucumber.
I'll dedicate this to my dear friends.
What?! Sogeking?! Why?!
Robin's escaped the Government for 20 years!
Scary! Robin, you're scary!
Now is the chance!
Listen to my last soul!
Usopp, forget about them!
and even Conqueror's Haki in 2 years.
It unthinkable to me that
she could be put into a bag
Let's go somewhere else.
Yeah!
I need a favor to ask of you, too.
Uh-huh.
Oh, Robin!
and taken so easily!
Luffy-san, let's go to the New World!
Wait, you guys!
What? Hey, Nico Robin!
Most people would lean towards one
type as their preference dictates.
I got it!
Huh, Luffy?!
I thought there was something wrong...
Let's go!
Who are they?
You fool! I said the show is over!
Hey, ma'am, you haven't paid yet!
What a crisis! Robin has been abducted!
She didn't even smell familiar!
Keep the change!
Shut up, Navy!
They're kidnappers!
They find which one they prefer
and strengthen that one.
Damn, this is setting a bad example for others!
Now, I'm starting to get mad!
Hey, shouldn't we tell Captain Luffy?
Let us hear one more song!
Bring them back!
What's wrong with them? Posing like us?!
Let him sing it!
But if you can enhance each of them,
What?! Did you guys see Luffy already?!
She's right! We don't care who he really is!
Dammit!
you can expand what you're capable of.
I won't allow them to imitate us!
You're right!
Huh?! What are these black bubbles?!
Uh-huh, I got it.
They must have new members by now, too!
See? Music is always on my side!
As if we're...
Yeah, we better rescue Robin already, huh?
Now,
Take me there with you!
...stars, those bastards!
as a trainer, I'm not easy, Luffy!
1, 2, 3, 4...
This is Sabaody! We caught Nico Robin!
Don't let it go to your head!
What the hell is this? A cloud?!
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it!
"New World"!
Well, it can't be helped if we have
imitators since our captain became famous.
With a fox kind of thing
that won't let go of her.
I have to think about how
to sign my autograph.
Franky was all fired up.
Oh yeah!
I have one already!
I don't have to worry about the Sunny now.
Kid!
We're famous in a bad way! Don't you get it?
What I have to do is...
--Now then, let's...
--Oh, give me a minute!
Wh-What happened?!
Viva Sabaody!
This is the story of a hero
...So I studied about the new technology...
Oh no, I gotta focus on cooking!
The story of a man who will become king
Really? You were in the sky?
I have to get the best ingredients first.
Hey, Chopper!
If I'm correct, he said that
this is the only safe place.
In war there are no "do-overs"
It's a beautiful...!
Chopper!
I need lady!
Honestly! We got the real Straw Hats'
pet by luck and now we lost him...
But he stands firm with
sandals on his bare feet
And cook something really good that'll
surprise Nami-san and Robin-chan!
The pirate Straw Hat Luffy
will be on hiatus for a while.
Oh yeah!
Ouch! My side!
But,
What did you say?!
I can't find anything special.
Come on baby!
That strange creature is a
survivor of the real Straw Hats?!
What should I do...?
Why didn't you say so?
Bring him here again!
Well, you might want to check the
shop on the beach at Grove #42...
Dreamers always struggle
--What?!
That's impossible! We don't
know where to look for him!
Because sometimes their
dreams are out of reach
We lost him completely!
Sabaody Archipelago is big!
Oh, thank you! I appreciate it!
Find those two and kill them!
In order to live through the days in
which you have to battle your own demons
Ouch! My side! It hurts!
Ace! Luffy!
Hey, fisherman, sell me some
fish at your best price!
I have a report! At the Sabaody Archipelago...
We can't run anymore! Let'
walk! Let's just walk!
We gotta set out to sea someday!
It's a big dream that seems quite a handful
Huh? Nobody's here?
What? The Straw Hats?!
Let's get out of this
country and live freely!
Hancock was right. I need this mustache.
Yes, sir! Word is that they're recruiting new crewmembers there.
Let's become stronger and
become pirates someday!
Hey, are you the owner?
I shouldn't cause trouble.
But when he mentioned it,
I could see it coming true
What's the matter?
Let the headquarters know about it.
He's gone!
I'm gonna become a pirate and
defeat others and become infamous!
If he's really alive, that's not good.
The green-haired man!
Look!
Is that the brat with a cape and
Call soldiers up right away!
Green-haired? What happened?
a huge backpack that
Captain was talking about?
Today is the day We got tired of waiting
And intensify the search on the Sabaody Archipelago!
It'll be the only proof of my life!
Is it some brat?
I did something horrible!
It happened just now...
Looks like a happy old man.
We don't need nights because
we're short-tempered
I got it! Alright then...!
Oh, you guys!
Old man, I wanna fish.
Today is the day It's a great day
Huh?
I'm gonna become...!
Hey, friend, we need you to come with us.
Kick the clock that was stopped
Young man, you don't look
like a fishing type of guy.
If you just come quietly,
we won't have any trouble.
I promised to meet friends on this island
Our captain is very angry.
Give up on living a long life.
For the New world For the New world
but I got here first and I
don't see any of them yet.
What? Are you too scared to even talk?
So I have nothing to do.
Did I shake them off?
So you're Sanji, aren't you?
Oh yeah!
For the New world The world is gonna change
Can you take me out to
sea on your fishing boat?
And you must be Zoro! Long time no see!
Sure, I'll take you out on that
boat right there so go ahead
Brook's concert?
This one, too!
and wait for me.
The Straw Hats' recruitment?
H-Hey, it's been a while! Hasn't it?
That's what I told him.
What is going on?
Yeah! Let's go now!
Green hair, 3 swords, and a belly warmer?
Everybody...
Oh, everybody's here already?
What is Soul King?
Luffy!
One more time!
Yeah, and he has a deep scar on his eye.
Sorry to keep you all waiting!
Luffy!
There's no mistake...
You know him?
Luffy!
A scar on his eye?
There isn't even a scratch on it.
Luffy-san!
Was it this guy?
Do you think he's mistaking us?
Oh yeah, this is the guy! Is he your friend?
Luffy!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Sunny!
Who cares!
We'll be sailing out soon!
Well, I only know him a little.
We just have to take him to Captain!
I told him to get on the fishing boat.
Grand-Bun is good, indeed!
Hey, hurry up! Let's begin!
What?!
That's for sure.
I wonder how everybody's doing.
But when I came back here...
Alright!
I wanna go to sea. I wanna fish.
I hope I can see them soon!
No, you can't, shithead!
No, young man, that's not it!
You fools!
Why can't I?!
That's a pirate ship!
--Mister, make it bigger!
--Thank you!
And why should I listen to you?!
I let him get away because of you guys!
You guys! We're gonna set
sail for the New World
He was a money spinner!
Do you think I'm walking
with you because I want to?!
Let's do it, old man!
that we've been dreaming of!
The Navy?
Yes, they think that the fake Straw Hats
No, you must say "Thank you, Rayleigh-san."
You'll cause me more trouble if you
wander about this island again!
W-Wake up, young man!
are the real ones and
have started mobilizing.
You're on the wrong ship!
Hey, you alright?! Hey!
No, Professor Rayleigh... Or Master...?
You Stray Moss!
So I think he's heading for
the Fish-Man Island like that.
Everybody's coming soon so
just walk to the ship with me!
I wiretapped them so there is no mistake.
He's horrible!
Thank you, Rayleigh!
He shot her out of the blue!
Terrible!
Okay, whatever!
I told Brook-chan what's going
on through the Transponder Snail
Hey, stay with me!
Dammit!
at the venue.
Why did you do that?!
Did we do something to you?!
That idiot!
He's on his way here.
How could No. 7 talk bossily to No. 1?
Oh, so he's gonna abandon stardom?
I said "sorry"!
I mistook her for someone else!
We're going to gather up all our dreams
Why are you ranking us in
the order of our arrival?!
He has backbone as I thought.
I'm sorry. I was looking for a couple like you guys.
I thought it was unlike him to show up first.
You got here first by chance!
Don't get carried away!
Nami-chan, you're a navigator, aren't you?
I knew he'd do something like this!
and set out in search of something to find
I'll teach you how to operate
the coated ship so remember it.
A long-haired woman and a long-nosed man.
Okay, I'm sorry... No. 7.
It's a pirate ship! Maybe they'll kill him!
You mistook her and shot her on the spot?!
Okay.
ONE PIECE
No, no, it's okay. It's
not your fault at all.
I'll try my best!
Alright, I'll fight you!
How horrible he is! Straw Hat Luffy!
Oh, what is this?
I trained my legs in hell for 2 years!
It got tense all of the sudden.
He won't die. We're lucky
to know where he's heading.
Huh? Don't tell me that you have something against me!
But, Rayleigh, Luffy is not here!
Compasses only cause delays
Bring it on! I'll cut you in half!
That aside, can I have some fish?
Don't worry!
Well, but...
Captain!
Looks like you do.
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
Hey, what's that?!
Huh?
Call me big boss, fool!
Look at the water! Something is surfacing!
We couldn't find the real pet but
isn't he the guy you're looking for?
Don't hate me, hate those two!
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
Hey, stay with me! You alright?!
What is it?
That's huge!
Find them, guys! Those two!
GROVE #46 A MEETING SPOT FOR THE STRAW HATS
Oh!
Luffy is here already!
We can't just let them get away!
When it comes to personal storms,
Kill them as a warning to others!
I can't wait!
This is Grove #46.
simply ride aboard someone else's biorhythm
I gave Sanji a Baby Transponder
Snail when he came here.
It's a galleon ship!
Rookies who have joined the
Straw Hats keep showing up here.
It wasn't coated well and was
crushed by water pressure?
He's with Zoro.
and pretend they aren't there!
Oh, that's good because
you guys have to hurry
Or attacked by Sea Kings?
I see 4 captains.
But it looks like it's been
cut by some kind of knife.
- the Navy will be here soon.
We're going to gather up all our dreams
"GASHED" ALBION BOUNTY: 92 MILLION BERRY
A 92 million berry bounty.
Don't be a fool!
So it's only Monkey-chan that we can't reach.
Who could cut a ship this big?
"Gashed" Albion.
and set out in search of something to find
LIP "SERVICE" DOUGHTY
BOUNTY: 88 MILLION BERRY
You bastard!
But take this Vivre Card.
A 88 million berry bounty.
How dare you ruin our dream
to go to the New World?!
Lip "Service" Doughty.
Oh, did it hit you? Sorry!
It will lead him to you.
A coin in my pocket, and
do you wanna be my friend?
And there are some super rookies...
Bye!
Grove #42 will be perfect - it's on the sea.
It's a quirk of fate!
What's wrong with him?
"WET-HAIRED" CARIBOU
BOUNTY: 210 MILLION BERRY
You should blame your own fate that
The captain of the Caribou Pirates.
Take the ship there and rendezvous!
He doesn't know Straw Hat Luffy?
We are, We are on the cruise!
brought a plague onto your ship.
A 210 million berry bounty.
H-He's gonna get killed!
It's a little busy but you
all got through these 2 years
"Wet-Haired" Caribou!
No, you're the one...
"BLOOD SPLATTER" CORIBOU
BOUNTY: 190 MILLION BERRY
We are!
Look!
And his brother is also the captain.
Somebody's on the ship!
Wait a minute!
and it's time for the new journey!
Oh, he's back! I couldn't
care less about him.
A 190 million berry bounty.
"Blood Splatter" Coribou!
Zoro! Usopp! Sanji! Nami!
Chopper! Robin! Franky! Brook!
And Ace! Sabo!
To take a pledge again...
I got on...
I'll get stronger!
Huh?
...the wrong ship.
We are!
The Straw hats slowly gather on the Sunny,
Only Luffy is still missing.
The Straw Hats are gathering
The fake Luffy who appeared in front of Luffy
Two years after the War of the Best,
Everyone is waiting for the captain's return.
on the Sunny, preparing for departure.
the time comes for the Straw Hats to reunite
attempted to boost his crew's power
but, attracted by the actions
of the Fake Straw Hats,
But the Marines caught wind of this,
But Luffy got caught up in battle between
with the new powers they've
gained through their training!
by calling them Straw Hats.
the Marines raid Brook's live performance.
and set out for the Sabaody Archipelago.
the Marines' Pacifistas and
the Fake Straw Hats.
Their sights set on the last sea
Amongst the confusion, Brook starts
Facing the pistol-wielding fake,
The opponent who cornered
Luffy & Co. two years ago
in the Grand Line, the New World,
Luffy and friends set out once more!
Luffy's newly acquired powers activate.
to sing his last song as the Soul King.
The results of his two years of
training become apparent.
is targetting them again.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Beginning of The New Chapter!
The Straw Hats Reunited!"
"An Explosive Situation!
Luffy vs. Fake Luffy!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Big Guns Assembled! The Danger
of the Fake Straw Hats!"
"The Navy Has Set Out! The
Straw Hats in Danger!"
"The Battle is on! Show Them
What You Got From Training!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!