Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training
and returned on Sabaody Archipelago
to go on to the next stage the New World.
Oh!
What? Nobody has arrived yet?
Check the poster once again!
It says "At least 70 million berries bounty."
We're not gonna deal with
captains with less bounty.
Go home.
I'll only say it once!
You're no match for me so I'm
not gonna drink with you!
Sure Kill: Green Star...
..."Devil"!
So, young lady, do you wanna drink with me?
Come on, baby!
Yeah!
Because I'm a skeleton, it's...
Bone!
I'm a real man--Sanji!
Just come back from hell!
Brook's concert?
The Straw Hats' recruitment?
What is going on?
Sorry to keep you waiting, Sunny!
We'll be sailing out soon!
Oh, did it hit you? Sorry!
Bye!
Wait a minute!
Huh?
"An Explosive Situation!
Luffy vs. Fake Luffy!"
This is not good...
That's Sabaody Archipelago in the distance.
Luffy, we have to say goodbye here.
We can't let them discover our relationship.
Uh-huh.
Put this on...
...like this!
I don't need that! That's too much!
Yeah?
But in case something happens...
Uh-huh.
You have to be careful.
Make sure you hide your face.
The world thinks that you're dead but...
...people know what you
look like from 2 years ago.
If you cause trouble, you
won't be able to set sail.
I got it.
And in the backpack, I put 50 extra
changes of clothes, 1000 lunches,
handkerchiefs and tissues,
5 years' worth of towels, 3 years'
worth of water and snacks,
silverware, toothbrushes, soap,
hand creams and 3 years' worth
of bug bite ointment and...
Make it lighter!
I hope you can meet your friends safely.
Yeah. Thank you for everything!
Good luck!
I've heard Sabaody has
become unsafe these days.
Yes. That's why the Navy is paying a
lot of attention to what goes on there.
Take extra care!
Yeah!
If you need us, we Kuja Pirates
will always come to help you!
Don't forget it.
And could you do me a favor?
What? I'm not gonna marry you.
No, I just want you to leave
without saying goodbye.
Oh, I've never said it to anyone.
I wanna see you again.
Alright, I'm off!
--See you!
--Take care, Luffy!
See ya!
He said he wants to see me again!
Is it what they call...
...a proposal?!
No, it's not!
I've been told by Hancock
not to cause trouble.
Hey, did you hit me on purpose?
H-He's in danger!
GROVE #13 SHAKKY'S RIP-OFF BAR
Wh-What?!
The stupid swordsman got here first?!
I can't believe it!
Our new voyage will be rough.
And Franky-chan came
second, about 10 days ago
and went out to see the ship.
Sunny is alright?
Of course--there isn't even a
scratch and the coating is done.
That's good.
He did a good job.
There's no regret for honorable wounds!
Yes! A year to heal!
I didn't know you had such
a strong sense of duty.
Thank you, Duval.
What, you think I'm handsome?
I returned your favor, young master!
Even on rainy days and windy days,
dangerous pirates tried to steal that ship.
But I fought day after day
even with cuts and bruises!
It was very painful!
Duval-sama!
Even so, how did you get hurt so badly?
Well, fall for me... I mean,
listen to me, young master.
--That's because the Navy finally...
--And Nami-chan came third...
Nami-san!!
Where's she?!
She went out shopping to kill time.
No interest in my story anymore?!
Nami-san's shopping! Nami-san's shopping!
Usopp-chan came fourth 3
days ago and went to town.
Chopper-chan came fifth yesterday.
Brook-chan has a concert
today on this island...
A concert?
What's that?
And then you came.
So 7 members including you have
already arrived on this archipelago.
We haven't seen Nico Robin and Luffy yet.
It's extremely difficult
just to get to this island.
So you guys are all quite something.
I'm glad that you can meet them soon.
Yeah. But I can't believe
that you trained Luffy.
He must be incredibly strong now.
I haven't seen him for 6 months.
Can't wait to see his progress.
Progress...
I wonder what kind of progress Nami-san made!
Hey, are you alright?
Y-Young master?
But I endured 2 years of arduous training.
So I have to shake off any sign
of seduction and show my results!
He's just saying that!
GROVE #47
Run!
Some thugs are fighting again!
I thought that the pirates would
settle down after Whitebeard died...
It's the opposite!
They're coming from everywhere
and the whole island has become lawless!
I didn't know that. It's dangerous.
Did you get it?
Blackbeard, Kid, and Drake are doing
whatever they want in the New World
and we're the ones who'll
follow... I mean, beat them!
--Hey, look!
--Th-They are...
What they say was true as I thought.
They were thought to be dead fighting
against the Navy 2 years ago
but they showed up again on this island.
Yeah, and they're the most powerful
pirate group on the island...
The Straw Hats...
Huh? Is it Nami?! Usopp?!
What? The Straw Hats...?
"Pirate Hunter" Zoro. A
120 million berry bounty.
"Black Foot" Sanji. A
77 million berry bounty.
She obtained a bounty at
the age of 8. Nico Robin.
An 80 million berry bounty.
And a cotton-candy lover--Tony Tony Chopper.
A 50 berry bounty!
It's too low!
"THE STRAW HATS" ZORO SANJI ROBIN CHOPPER
Who is there? Is Luffy there, too?
Move out of my way!
They're a good match for us!
Let's do it!
Wait!
Why're you stopping us, Captain?
If we cause trouble with them,
Straw Hat Luffy won't keep quiet.
It's not wise to have an
unnecessary conflict before
we go to the New World!
Hey, Zoro! Sanji!
Robin! Wait for me!
What is that talking racoon?
Huh? What are you talking about?
Racoons can't talk...
But...
I heard that you got here first, Zoro!
Can't believe you didn't get lost.
Sanji and Robin, you guys finally made it!
You see it?
Yeah, I've never seen something like that.
He might cause us trouble. Ignore him.
Oh, wait!
Hey, wait a minute!
Our target, Nico Robin,
is a Devil Fruit eater.
It'll be painful if she fights back.
Let's catch her off guard!
I better hurry up. I wonder
if they're all here.
I want Nami-san and Robin-chan
to try my improved food soon!
Before that, I better go see if
the kitchen in the Sunny is okay.
And then, go food shopping!
Is that Sanji?
Why don't you say something?
Did you hit me knowing who I was?
Did you see it? You made me look like a fool.
You humiliated me in public.
It shouldn't happen to me.
I'm an elite pirate with
a 400 million bounty!
Kneel down on the ground in fear now
and beg for your life!
Just...
Just apologize!
Doesn't he wanna live?
I think you realize now how
audacious your actions were!
That's why you're so scared
that you can't even talk!
A few moments ago, a man who
has a long nose and a woman
with long hair messed with us
so our captain is in a bad mood.
You better apologize now.
Kneel on the ground!
Otherwise, you're gonna throw away
your life with just one mistake.
Our captain pulls his trigger very easily.
Kneel on the ground already!
He's Straw Hat Luffy!
He wants to get killed? Apologize!
I'm really sorry!
I better go now.
What's wrong with him?!
Okay!
Very well!
What?!
Hey, did he do something?
Hancock was right. I should put it on.
Hey, Zoro! Sanji! Robin!
We finally see each other
but you're acting weird!
Zoro and Sanji, you guys did
pretty well in these 2 years.
But why aren't you guys talking to me?
Hey, he's still following us.
Oh, you're being shy, you bastards!
And that racoon knows about us
the Straw Hats a bit too well.
I've been thinking about that,
too, but maybe... Look at this.
Don't tell me he's...!
The real cotton-candy lover--Chopper,
a 50 berry bounty!
So he's their pet!
You guys changed a little. But I don't care.
He was abandoned on this island before
they died and he's been living in the wild.
He thinks his masters are back
and that's why he's following us.
Then let's get rid of that
fox and take him instead.
If the pet looks the same as the
poster, we'd look more authentic.
We're gonna keep him? What does he eat?
Looks like cotton candy.
We don't have any.
We don't need you anymore! Go away!
Come here, Chopper.
It's a cucumber.
Scary! Robin, you're scary!
Now is the chance!
Oh, Robin!
What? Hey, Nico Robin!
Who are they?
What a crisis! Robin has been abducted!
They're kidnappers!
Hey, shouldn't we tell Captain Luffy?
What?! Did you guys see Luffy already?!
You're right!
They must have new members by now, too!
Yeah, we better rescue Robin already, huh?
Take me there with you!
This is Sabaody! We caught Nico Robin!
With a fox kind of thing
that won't let go of her.
Franky was all fired up.
I don't have to worry about the Sunny now.
What I have to do is...
Viva Sabaody!
Oh no, I gotta focus on cooking!
I have to get the best ingredients first.
It's a beautiful...!
I need lady!
And cook something really good that'll
surprise Nami-san and Robin-chan!
But,
I can't find anything special.
What should I do...?
Well, you might want to check the
shop on the beach at Grove #42...
Oh, thank you! I appreciate it!
Hey, fisherman, sell me some
fish at your best price!
Huh? Nobody's here?
Hey, are you the owner?
What's the matter?
He's gone!
The green-haired man!
Green-haired? What happened?
I did something horrible!
It happened just now...
Old man, I wanna fish.
Huh?
Young man, you don't look
like a fishing type of guy.
I promised to meet friends on this island
but I got here first and I
don't see any of them yet.
So I have nothing to do.
Can you take me out to
sea on your fishing boat?
Sure, I'll take you out on that
boat right there so go ahead
and wait for me.
That's what I told him.
Green hair, 3 swords, and a belly warmer?
Yeah, and he has a deep scar on his eye.
You know him?
A scar on his eye?
Was it this guy?
Oh yeah, this is the guy! Is he your friend?
Well, I only know him a little.
I told him to get on the fishing boat.
That's for sure.
But when I came back here...
No, young man, that's not it!
That's a pirate ship!
You guys! We're gonna set
sail for the New World
that we've been dreaming of!
W-Wake up, young man!
You're on the wrong ship!
So I think he's heading for
the Fish-Man Island like that.
That idiot!
I thought it was unlike him to show up first.
I knew he'd do something like this!
It's a pirate ship! Maybe they'll kill him!
No, no, it's okay. It's
not your fault at all.
He won't die. We're lucky
to know where he's heading.
That aside, can I have some fish?
Well, but...
Hey, what's that?!
Look at the water! Something is surfacing!
What is it?
That's huge!
It's a galleon ship!
It wasn't coated well and was
crushed by water pressure?
Or attacked by Sea Kings?
But it looks like it's been
cut by some kind of knife.
Don't be a fool!
Who could cut a ship this big?
You bastard!
How dare you ruin our dream
to go to the New World?!
It's a quirk of fate!
You should blame your own fate that
brought a plague onto your ship.
No, you're the one...
Look!
Somebody's on the ship!
Oh, he's back! I couldn't
care less about him.
I got on...
...the wrong ship.
The Straw Hats are gathering
on the Sunny, preparing for departure.
But the Marines caught wind of this,
and set out for the Sabaody Archipelago.
The opponent who cornered
Luffy & Co. two years ago
is targetting them again.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Navy Has Set Out! The
Straw Hats in Danger!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!