Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training
and returned to Sabaody Archipelago
to go on to the next stage - the New World.
"The Navy Has Set Out! The
Straw Hats in Danger!"
Sunny!
Sorry to keep you waiting for 2 years.
I'm glad that you're fine!
What an attractive woman before me!
You're our super archaeologist -
Robin, aren't you?!
You haven't changed, Franky!
I've changed, silly!
Look at my body - it's full
of romantic masculinity!
Look upon this fantastic transformation
such as no one has ever seen before!
I'm beyond human understanding now!
Yeah, it's probably hard to
see you as a mere human now.
Hey, hey, you mean I'm a pervert?
You're good at praising people!
This is the coating?
It's like jelly.
That's right! Rayleigh is really skilled!
Now we can go into the depths of the sea!
What a technique!
I just saw Rayleigh and the others.
So you went to the bar.
What number were you?
8th.
Everybody's here except for Luffy.
I see. We'll begin a new journey soon.
I've got the ship in top condition.
A new weapon is ready, too!
I can't wait.
By the way, where are the others?
I saw Usopp and Sanji here
then Usopp went to get fuel
and Sanji went food shopping.
I see. Actually, on my way here,
I found this.
Did you know about this? What is Soul King?
Oh, about Brook.
Yeah, I knew about it.
I saw his TD everywhere.
He's quite a shining star now.
From the dark, silent, foggy sea,
he made it to the footlights,
where people cheer for him.
He might not...
...come back to do pirating again.
GROVE #33 SABAODY DOME
...King is mysterious
He's nothing but bones!
Afro on the skull! Girls love the contrast
If you wanna make out with her
Got milk! Got milk!
You need calcium more than protein
Captain!
Captain Luffy!
Damn!
Luffy!
I missed you guys!
Hey!
Luffy!
Franky!
Nami!
Sogeking?!
Cool!
You guys have changed in these 2 years!
I bet you got stronger!
Hmmm...
It's the Straw Hats.
What are they doing on the street?
What just happened was...
Don't look them in the
eye. You can't fight them.
Dammit!
What happened to you?
I don't know!
I felt chills all over my body!
What kind of trick did he use?
Oh yeah! We have another problem.
The thing is Cocoa got...
No, I mean... Nico Robin got...
What did you say, Zoro?!
Nico Robin has been abducted?!
I'm sorry. It happened in front of our eyes.
Yeah, that's right! This is serious, Luffy!
She could be kidnapped like Camie!
Who did it?
I have no idea.
Captain.
I think people who have a
problem with the real Robin
have taken Cocoa by mistake.
That's possible.
She really looks like the real
Robin but that worked against us.
Hey, stop talking in whispers!
Oh well, let's leave it at that.
That's her fate.
--What?!
--What?! Okay, Captain.
Hey, Luffy! Robin has been abducted!
I've been thinking, what is this creature?
Is that a joke?!
Don't say that even if it's joke!
How can he speak? Is he a stuffed animal?
Take it back, Luffy!
Shut up!
More importantly, assemble the 100
members that we recruited here
on this island at Grove #46!
That man who has a long nose.
That woman with long orange hair.
That brat with a cape and a huge backpack...
Find those three
and make them regret that they
messed with Straw Hat Luffy!
--Roger!
We must try not to kill them
before we bring them here.
This is a good opportunity to
show them how formidable we are!
Okay, let's go!
Wait a minute, you guys!
The last 2 years changed your personalities?
Luffy!
I... I... feel sad...
and can't help crying!
Again, what is this creature?
What about Robin?
Why don't you guys say something?!
Huh? How can he talk?
Toys today are pretty well-made!
Dammit! I'm disappointed in you guys!
I'm gonna go help her alone!
Wait for me, Robin!
What happened?
They had a fight among themselves?
That's...
There's no doubt!
Straw Hat Luffy and other
members may look radically
different from 2 years ago
but no one else has a weird pet like that!
They're...
...the Straw Hats! They're alive!
This is Grove #47. We identified
the pirate group - the Straw Hats!
It seems like the pirates
that Straw Hat recruited...
URGENT CREW NEEDED
...on this island are
assembling at the Grove #46!
Understood! Roger that!
Go now and help the locals evacuate!
Roger that!
Pirates are gathering at Grove #46!
The target is the Straw Hats!
We'll make a raid on the lawless area!
Get ready for action!
Close in on them from Grove #40, 42, 44!
Backup from G1 will come soon!
S-Sentomaru-san!
I'm gonna go first!
I'll take PX-5 and PX-7 with me!
Oh, you're deploying Pacifistas?!
Of course!
You are all underestimating the Straw Hats!
It's been 2 years since the war now.
They must have gotten stronger!
They're different from any of the other
rookies who have come to this island!
What was behind
the Kuma-kou's doing from 2
years ago is still a mystery...
But when I examined his eccentric behavior
carefully after he lost his personality,
I was able to deduce that the
Straw Hats would reunite one day!
Let's go!
Oh, it's reacting! So I think it's this way.
You got hurt because you messed with me.
Damn!
Run!
There are too many pirates...
Hmmm, maybe I should put it on.
I said, give me a better discount.
N-No way, ma'am!
You're asking me to sell these
many clothes for half price?
That's a bit...
Hey, Nami.
You can buy clothes at the Fish-Man Island!
We need to buy fuel...
No!
Here! I'll buy these too
so discount them by 90%!
No!!
Hey, hey, you got better at
bargaining after 2 years.
Hey, Moss Head!
You gotta stay with me!
I don't want you getting lost.
Huh? Who do you think you're
talking to, Mustache Eyebrow?
What did you just say?
Oh! Something smells good...
Oh, it looks good!
Hi!
Try some!
Oh, how dazzling! There's
a woman within my reach!
Oh? That bastard! Where did he go?!
I need a fishing pole to fish.
Oh, a fishing store.
He's not here... That bastard!
Robin!
Where did they take her?!
Damn! Damn! Damn!
Damn!
What happened to everybody?!
Luffy, Zoro, Nami, Sanji, Franky...
They used to be so compassionate!
Robin is abducted and he
says "leave it at that"?
How awful is that?!
What have I been working
for for the last 2 years?
For whom?!
Hey, Chopper!
Hey!
Here, here!
I knew it was Chopper!
Usopp!
Oh man, you got so big!
You must be comfortable to ride!
Doing okay?
Uh-huh!
He's right! You're much softer than before!
It's been a long time, Chopper!
Oh?
Nami?
Yes.
Oh yeah!
I'm glad to see you guys but
this is no time for that!
Robin is in trouble!
Huh? You mean they're imposters?
That's why there are 2 Namis?
Oh please!
Robin's escaped the Government for 20 years!
It unthinkable to me that
she could be put into a bag
and taken so easily!
I got it!
I thought there was something wrong...
She didn't even smell familiar!
Now, I'm starting to get mad!
What's wrong with them? Posing like us?!
I won't allow them to imitate us!
As if we're...
...stars, those bastards!
Don't let it go to your head!
Well, it can't be helped if we have
imitators since our captain became famous.
I have to think about how
to sign my autograph.
I have one already!
We're famous in a bad way! Don't you get it?
Hey, Chopper!
Chopper!
Honestly! We got the real Straw Hats'
pet by luck and now we lost him...
Ouch! My side!
What did you say?!
That strange creature is a
survivor of the real Straw Hats?!
Why didn't you say so?
Bring him here again!
--What?!
That's impossible! We don't
know where to look for him!
We lost him completely!
Sabaody Archipelago is big!
Ouch! My side! It hurts!
We can't run anymore! Let'
walk! Let's just walk!
Hancock was right. I need this mustache.
I shouldn't cause trouble.
Look!
Is that the brat with a cape and
a huge backpack that
Captain was talking about?
Is it some brat?
Looks like a happy old man.
Oh, you guys!
Hey, friend, we need you to come with us.
If you just come quietly,
we won't have any trouble.
Our captain is very angry.
Give up on living a long life.
What? Are you too scared to even talk?
So you're Sanji, aren't you?
And you must be Zoro! Long time no see!
H-Hey, it's been a while! Hasn't it?
Yeah! Let's go now!
Oh, everybody's here already?
Sorry to keep you all waiting!
Do you think he's mistaking us?
Who cares!
We just have to take him to Captain!
I wanna go to sea. I wanna fish.
No, you can't, shithead!
Why can't I?!
And why should I listen to you?!
Do you think I'm walking
with you because I want to?!
You'll cause me more trouble if you
wander about this island again!
You Stray Moss!
Everybody's coming soon so
just walk to the ship with me!
Dammit!
How could No. 7 talk bossily to No. 1?
Why are you ranking us in
the order of our arrival?!
You got here first by chance!
Don't get carried away!
Okay, I'm sorry... No. 7.
Alright, I'll fight you!
I trained my legs in hell for 2 years!
Bring it on! I'll cut you in half!
GROVE #46 A MEETING SPOT FOR THE STRAW HATS
This is Grove #46.
Rookies who have joined the
Straw Hats keep showing up here.
I see 4 captains.
"GASHED" ALBION BOUNTY: 92 MILLION BERRY
A 92 million berry bounty.
"Gashed" Albion.
LIP "SERVICE" DOUGHTY
BOUNTY: 88 MILLION BERRY
A 88 million berry bounty.
Lip "Service" Doughty.
And there are some super rookies...
"WET-HAIRED" CARIBOU
BOUNTY: 210 MILLION BERRY
The captain of the Caribou Pirates.
A 210 million berry bounty.
"Wet-Haired" Caribou!
"BLOOD SPLATTER" CORIBOU
BOUNTY: 190 MILLION BERRY
And his brother is also the captain.
A 190 million berry bounty.
"Blood Splatter" Coribou!
The Straw hats slowly gather on the Sunny,
but, attracted by the actions
of the Fake Straw Hats,
the Marines raid Brook's live performance.
Amongst the confusion, Brook starts
to sing his last song as the Soul King.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Big Guns Assembled! The Danger
of the Fake Straw Hats!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!