Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
and returned to Sabaody Archipelago to
go on to the next stage - the New World.
Why are they calling you Straw Hat?
However, no one has ever fully explored it
Hey, you! Don't you know who I am?
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Get out of my way or I'll kill
you and pull out your bowels!
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Oh, what is this?
Straw Hat is not scum like you!
It got tense all of the sudden.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
But, Rayleigh, Luffy is not here!
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
What?!
Don't worry!
I see. They all got fooled
and became his crew.
Captain!
and his friends venture into that sea.
Huh?
Isn't he the guy you're looking for?
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
And I don't know why but the
real Straw Hat is here too.
Oh!
Luffy is here already!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
I gave Sanji a Baby Transponder
Snail when he came here.
That was close!
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training
H-Here's his poster...
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training
He's with Zoro.
and returned to Sabaody Archipelago
to go on to the next stage the New World.
to go on to the next stage - the New World.
Alright, I'll fight you!
and boarded the newly coated Sunny
setting sail for the Fish-Man Island...
I trained my legs in hell for 2 years!
Looks exactly the same!
Bring it on! I'll cut you in half!
Second Gear!
...located 10,000 meters below the sea level...
Rise to the top!
Let's go to the Fish-Man Island!
...in order to go on to the
next stage - the New World.
Oh, that's good because
you guys have to hurry
You guys!
Okay, that's good!
Gum-Gum...
I've got a lot of things that I want
to share with you but in any case,
- the Navy will be here soon.
That's the extra-vehicular Flutter Kick Coating!
There's something at 6
o'clock! Is it a creature? No...
So it's only Monkey-chan that we can't reach.
An extra-vehicular diving suit!
thank you for going along with
my selfish decision for 2 years!
...Jet Pistol!
Wait! You have to attach the safety rope!
Are you guys all ready?!
But take this Vivre Card.
Straw Hat... He is using Haki!
--Yes, brother!
--Yes, yes!
It will lead him to you.
Set sail!!
Luffy! I knew it was you!
Grove #42 will be perfect - it's on the sea.
The target is right there!
Rocket Launcher!
Why are you always in trouble?!
Hey, guys! There is a ship kind
of thing coming from behind!
Take the ship there and rendezvous!
"A Surprising Fact!
The Man Who Guarded the Sunny!"
It's really been a long time!
I wonder how everybody is!
Another arm!
Charge!
It's a little busy but you
all got through these 2 years
Guard Boost!
I'm so happy!
Are you guys okay?
and it's time for the new journey!
It's a pirate ship!
I came here to check but you seem alright.
Brother, it's hard to dig!
Mil Fleurs!
SABAODY ARCHIPELAGO
That's because this island is
made mostly out of tree roots.
Gigantesco Mano!
"Deadly Combat under the Sea!
The Demon of the Ocean Strikes!"
Uh-huh!
Rayleigh!
Please forgive us, don't bury us!
I'll do it!
"The Battle is on! Show Them
What You Got From Training!"
I'll do anything, just don't kill me!
They did great.
The captain, Black, forced us to do it!
Run!
Alright, it's my turn!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Hard to port!
"Lost in the Deep Sea!
The Straw Hats Get Separated!"
As for the rest, read
this before you set out.
Once we joined them, we thought...
You can learn how to operate
a coated ship in detail.
...we could kill the Straw Hats...
"Everyone Together! Luffy,
Setting Out for the New World!"
Go, Sea Cow!
Okay, thank you!
I wonder how Luffy has
changed in these 2 years.
Third Gear!
...with high bounties...
--They're coming after us!
--That sounds so familiar...
I can't wait to see him!
...easily from within, as we like!
They're so persistent!
Me too!
Okay, let's go to Grove #42!
What do they want from us?
Oops, I have to call Zoro and Sanji.
Drip!
It seems like things are
getting hectic over there...
But Luffy...
Hey, stop! He's gonna die!
Are you a Devil Fruit eater?
Stop!
I hope he doesn't get
caught up in some trouble.
The bubble is gonna pop!
--You're doing great, Sea Cow!
--Yes!
Don't do it!
Oh, that's right, it's Luffy.
Armament; Hardening!
--Are they gonna come aboard?
--Sea Cow?
Yes! I got him...
We never set out peacefully because of him.
Leave it to me!
Wait a minute! That's...
What is that?!
I'm gonna go pick him up! I have an idea.
It wasn't like that before!
Huh? What's going on here? Logia?!
The bubbles are joined!
Brother, now is the chance!
Hey, you fools! We're gonna
arrest all of you in our way!
I feel weak because of the sea!
But, look what happened!
--Alright, should we do it?!
--Yes!
I thought he just looked different
because I hadn't seen him for 2 years.
What are you doing, Navy?!
Don't bother Soul King!
Hey, Momoo! You're Momoo of the
Arlong Pirates, aren't you?
Damn that octopus! Is it trying to stop him?
Hey, what's going on there?
The pirate - Straw Hat...
No wonder! He was just a fake.
It's out of control!
Blue Walk!
Do you remember me?
The Navy who came here to
arrest Soul King has been
I'm Nami! I was there at the Arlong Park!
Whoa, Sanji-san got out of the bubble!
blocked by his fans
What are you guys doing?!
Do you think the gods
will forgive them, Coribou?
Get Straw Hat already!
and he got away somehow!
That's really fast!
He's like a Fish-Man! That's so cool!
I dig! I dig!
--Oops!
--Hurry up, Luffy!
Hm? Hey, Luffy, doesn't he look familiar?
That's right! Let's bury them!
Damn! That traitor!
Rayleigh, thank you for everything!
Yeah?
Oh gods! Let us bury these fools!
Yes, I have some big news!
Well then, Rayleigh...
I've been running and running
Die, you damn thing!
The musician, Brook, is a
friend of Straw Hat Luffy
Thanks again for everything!
in order to get away from those hideous people for 2 years.
Gum-Gum Pistol!
and he is a pirate himself!
I'm going now!
Don't! Please don't kill us!
Compared to them,
--Let's board their ship!
--Yes!
the monster is nothing.
But I saw the real Straw
Hat Luffy for myself!
It actually looks rather cute to me.
Yes...
Diable Jambe!
Thank you! The timing was perfect!
Whoa! He's coming through the bubble!
No, somebody's coming!
I told you that I had no choice!
Sister Shakky asked me to do this!
THE PLACE WHERE "THE FAKE
STRAW HATS" ASSEMBLED
We gotta fight!
Your friends will be waiting at Grove #42!
Bien Cuit...
...Grill Shoot!
It's been a while! My heart
is filled with anticipation!
Dark King Rayleigh stood in our way!
--Guys! Are you ready?!
--Yes!
Oh, I don't have a heart to be filled.
He could even fight Uncle Kizaru equally
- what would you expect us to do?
While they're dumbfounded,
The Caribou brothers and their crew
and some of the fake Straw Hats...
...got away successfully.
kill them all!
I need to breathe!
We caught all the others
but 2 Pacifistas were severely
damaged by the real Straw Hats.
Let's go!
What's wrong with them?!
Yes!
They're both extremely strong!
Guys, follow my lead!
You've improved a bit, you
third-class swordsman.
One of them was the prototype that
cornered the Straw Hats 2 years ago.
You've learned some idiotic
kicking skills, yourself!
Of course, his strength hasn't changed.
So they must have gotten stronger!
What?!
I hope your cooking skills have
worsened, you shitty cook!
Three-Sword Style technique;
Crossing the Six Paths!
--What's the matter, Sea Cow?
--Why, Sea Cow?
--what did you say?!
They've improved themselves
in last 2 years, big time!
--Ring, ring, ring...
--Huh?
--Oh no, we left Captain Caribou on that ship!
--Brother!
Ow! That's right!
Make sure to tell the
Navy HQ in the New World.
The Navy has set out and Luffy
should be here somewhere!
Alright, by way of greeting,
We're gonna take Sunny to Grove
#42 so come meet us there!
The Straw Hats are completely revived!
The demon that rules the
realm of water... So weak!
fire the gatling gun!
They went that way!
--Go after them!
--Don't let them get away!
Roger.
Clank.
--What did he want?
--Weren't you listening?
Kill all the Straw Hats and...
I feel grateful when I think about it.
Rise to the top!
Well...
I got to fight every single day for the past 2 years.
Navy. Come. We. Ship. Run.
The Straw Hats are heading for Grove #42!
To top him...
They're gone before you know it.
Get that?
Catch them at any cost!
I'm still gonna get stronger!
No, I don't! Why are you talking like that?!
Say it in a proper sentence!
Huh?
That was great...
Monkey-chan and everybody,
they all got stronger.
I-I couldn't see his movement!
I thought a musclehead like you
couldn't understand sentences.
What was that?
He shouldn't have done it!
Okay. You. Later. Slashed.
Did you say something, No. 7?
--Were you watching?
--Yes, I'm a fan of theirs.
Dark King Rayleigh!
--I'll kill you!
--Bring it on!
It's a new beginning for my pupil!
Yeah, yeah.
Don't be too hard on him.
By the way, do you hear that uproar?
Hey hey, Zoro! Sanji! You can't cut his arms!
You're thinking about
something, aren't you, Ray-san?
Wh-What is this line?
No! Don't throw me out into the water!
You're right. There. Noisy.
Hmm? Well... Yeah...
Gum-Gum...
I recommend you not to cross it.
...Elephant Gun!
That's something...
...you shouldn't do!
Oh, Bon Bags! A lot of them!
You have to value people's life!
Hey, that's a nice ship!
What's in them?
The gods... the gods are watching
over you! Don't you think so?!
I stole it. My house burned
down so I'm living here.
They're all filled with food.
He blew it away!
I know everybody's stomach got
bigger these past 2 years.
Huh? What's going on here?
He's gotten so much stronger!
Yeah? And what's your name?
You're being inconsistent!
Even while he's in the sea...
I'll let you fill up later!
Rayleigh.
Shut up, you guys!
Weren't you gonna fire a
gatling gun and kill us all!
Really?! Can't wait to eat your food!
I'm Roger! I think we were
destined to meet, Rayleigh!
No, that was just... That
was just a play on words.
We already found one of the
perpetrators who have insulted me!
There they are! They're this way!
Hey! Something is in there!
Destined?
Do you wanna turn the
world upside down with me?
Oh? They went round!
That wasn't playing.
Who are you? You must be
the captain of the ship.
A shark?
We have no choice!
Huh? The world?
It's this guy!
Everybody, charge!
I'll teach him a lesson first!
Oh, Roronoa Zoro!
Yeah!
Who are you and where you from? Go away!
About how formidable I am!
--A shark?
--Isn't that shark wearing something?
No way! I'm not a captain! I'm just...
Your ship is small but it looks like it
can endure storms if you handle it right.
I wanna become a flea...
That's fairly big.
And what I'm about to do to him
What's wrong? What're you...?
I was forced to be a slave for them!
is a warning to you all, my men!
I wanna become a mite...
It's perfect for us to set sail in!
What?!
Oh, I'm sick of being on that ship!
If you mess with me, this
is how you're gonna end up!
What happened?!
What is it?
Us? Set sail? Don't decide for me.
Thanking us for helping him?
He's making ridiculous excuses.
Do you understand?!
What a polite shark.
Why should I join you?
Oh yeah! This is great!
I... I...
Can I stay on this ship for a little while?
Like I said, to turn the world upside
down! Alright, let's set sail, Rayleigh!
A guy with a 400 million
berry bounty sure is scary!
I wanna become a louse...
Please?
Well, he is kind of pathetic...
What's the matter with this guy?
Zoro, Sanji, do you know him?
It must be...
What?
No way! He just made it up!
We're being drawn into the sea current!
Huh?
Well you see, a little while ago...
Maybe nothing in this
world happens by accident.
I knew it was you guys causing all of this!
What?! He just made it up?!
Luffy, let's go back to Sunny!
That's it, you pirates!
Hey, where did you find the Sea
Cow who was drawing your ship?
Yeah!
As everything happens for a reason,
Straw Hat Luffy and his
following! Just surrender!
I can't believe it!
Oh...
our destiny slowly takes form.
You haven't gotten anywhere yet!
The Navy...?
Here is... mmm... Cutie-san!
We're blocking off every exit of Grove #46!
At any rate, Luffy looks great in that hat,
Oh! I know you from Thriller Bark!
You're the cat burglar.
You can't get away now!
better than ever.
Who was she?
They've been swept away
by the downward current!
Stop looking at our navigator like that!
Huh? How did the Navy find out about me?
What are you still doing here?
Maybe I want to live a little longer.
Oh no! Follow them! We have to stay together!
You can't talk to me like
that! I brought you back here!
What are you talking about?
Okay!
Nami-san! You're safe...
Captain! We're under siege!
UNDER THE SEA NEAR SABAODY ARCHIPELAGO
The surface is far up there already.
If it weren't for me, you would be...
You fool! Don't panic!
...now!
--I don't wanna die here!
--You've got to be kidding me!
What a view!
Submarines can't have windows this wide!
This is why we recruited the new members!
That's getting to be a pain!
You must learn your place...
We have guys with bounties over 100 million!
I just caught that sea monster somewhere...
--You're still here?
--You're too calm!
Sniff, sniff...
We're sinking and sinking!
But there are a lot of them...
A real woman! A real woman!
Stupid! Watch this!
My eyes are spinning! But I don't have eyes!
I can't stop worrying about flooding!
Of course I am! What kind
of sickness do you have?
Experienced people have
those animals pull their ship.
Hey, Caribou!
Feels like we're leaving the
inhabited world. It makes me nervous!
Use the Navy soldier as a
shield and make a way out!
Anyway, set sail already!
I saw some Navy ships around here!
What?!
Navy soldier?
C-C-Can we go back on the
surface again for sure?
Keep the yard level! Hard to Port!
What?!
Is that so?
They caught our scout!
Soon, there'll be no way out!
We're gonna crash into the continental shelf!
--Stop! Stop, Sea Cow!
--What happened?
Damn, that's not good!
That's no good. But it's strange.
I-It's not like I'm scared but...
I got it!
Huh?
Don't lose your concentration,
or the ship will wreck!
What did you say, Big Boss?!
Brother! I'll save you!
I can't move from here.
It's beautiful down here!
What?!
What are you talking about?!
I said "use the Navy soldier
as a shield," you fool!
Real ladies are great!
Don't get thrown off!
I see. Use this Navy soldier as a shield...
I wanna find a sea monster.
Stay in the center of the current!
I am scum...
Hey, Luffy! What are you up to?
Alright!
Look at that!
What's that?
Oh, it's just a turtle... It's too small.
There you are!
Trees... No, roots!
Come on!
Let's start his rehabilitation
with some less stimulating pics.
THE SHORE AT GROVE #42 THE
RENDEZVOUS POINT OF THE STRAW HATS
Oh yeah! Come to think of it,
Sabaody Archipelago consists of giant mangroves!
It's really fast!
Hey, Nami.
--Oh!
--That must be...!
The direction we're heading is slightly off
What are you doing, Caribou?!
This is fun!
Usopp-san! Nami-san! Robin-san!
from where Log Pose is pointing.
We got to use him to get away from here!
I'm overwhelmed by the beauty of nature!
I'm so surprised - my eyes could pop out!
Yeah, that's fine.
The right course should be south
west of where it's pointing.
FFFranky-san!
I can't do that, Big Boss!
I don't have eyes though!
It's faster to go straight.
Why should we do that?
What?
I've seen this already.
Because this soldier lied to me saying
he hadn't called the Navy yet!
Yeah, because you got on the wrong ship!
Shut up! Everybody's having a great time!
If you go straight, you'd be
taken away by the sea current
Brook!
Hey! I can't believe you abandoned stardom!
Attaboy!
I can't believe these roots are
running down to the sea bottom!
and get stuck by an undersea
mountain or volcano.
No, stupid!
Usopp!
It's been a long time, everybody!
Oh, ow, ow, ow!
What?! Volcano! It's
scary to be in the water!
They're enormous and magnificent!
You two have become even more beautiful!
But I thought the sea currents
in the Grand Line were volatile.
I'm alive!
That crazy ass! He ignored my order!
Alright, Nami-san!
Is there any stable current?
I can't hold it any longer!
It's been 2 years so...
Hey, Chopper...
There's something behind that tree!
Yes, just one.
Uh-oh, he did it...
What? Why are you all so glum?
This is good. Stay calm.
Oh, are you gonna sing for us?
What?
There is an unspoken rule that you
can just tell a lie to bad guys
Everyone! It's gonna get
colder from here on out
Oh I know! You guys can't
do anything without me...
Wow, it's huge!
so wear a coat or something.
How exciting! An underwater
adventure! It's like a dream come true!
but we should put a stop to that!
...Could I look at your panties...
Yes, it's getting chilly
- I can feel it on my skin.
It's so cold here!
What do you think?!
We can't find Luffy and the
other two. We got separated.
Looks like you guys have
no intention to surrender!
I never let you see them even 2 years ago!
Oh, but I don't...
Oh, fish!
You're a skeleton--you don't have skin.
I think I can catch them!
What?!
Let's get the pirates!
I-I'm so excited to see you again... See?
I hope they haven't been
shredded to pieces by the monster.
The fish here look delicious too.
It's shaking my soul...
Chopper-san, you can't do that...
Fools! Our boss is a man with a 400
million bounty - Straw Hat Luffy!
Your imagination is terrifying...
--Although I don't have a soul to be shaken...
--Hey, the big star is having a spasm.
Stop it, you fools!
You can't steal my line...
What if the bubble pops!
Don't ever do that again or I kill you!
Let's fight!
Are we going somewhere
cold? Not the deep sea?
Honestly! None of you guys have grown up.
Nami-san, give us some dos and
don'ts on the coated ship
Don't you know that the
water in the deep sea is cold?
This is no good, Captain, let's run!
You fools! You have to listen to me!
By the way, I don't see everybody here yet.
before they do something stupid.
Like in a bath tub, hot water
goes up and cold water goes down.
Huh? What are they calling me "boss"?
Okay, Sanji-kun! Rayleigh-san gave me a note.
Oh yeah? I'm not a big fan of
baths so I wouldn't know.
--Oh yeah, Chopper went to pick them up.
--Hey!
Again, what are you talking about?
I see.
Alright, everyone, listen...
If the sea is the same as a bath tub,
She's moving! A real, beautiful woman!
it's gonna get colder as you go deeper.
Sanji!
It's too dark - I wanna look for
them but I can't see anything!
The temperature isn't the only difference.
--It's gonna pop! It's gonna pop!
--How can you fly that far with nosebleed!
I'm not good with darkness.
I feel something, don't you?
Here they come finally!
You're still depressed?!
Wow, hey!
In the deep layer of the sea,
What?!
Don't be scared! Go!
there are giant currents
called deep currents
Sanji flew out into the water!
We probably submerged around 7,000 meters.
Everybody!
It's amazing.
You're...
that you don't get to see very often.
The bubble doesn't break even under
tremendous pressure in this deep water
Even the Shark Submerge can't
take the pressure this deep.
The 88 million berry bounty
- Lip "Service" Doughty!
I brought them!
Those currents flow totally
independently from surface currents.
Are we near the Fish-Man Island?
Maybe they got there already...
I liked the way you fight.
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
but things can pass through it like that.
There are currents under currents?!
You know many things!
Don't be scared! Get ready to shoot!
Camie-chan said it's located
at 10,000 meters below sea level.
Hey!
Sanji! Come back!
Luffy-san! I missed you so much!
Because I'm really old!
We have to submerge 3,000 meters more?!
He's got a 92 million berry bounty...
All currents are connected.
All they have is a small bubble.
You guys sure do look stronger!
I feel weak in the water...
"Gashed" Albion!
One current flows eastward and
the other one flows westward.
Hang in there!
Even if they're alive,
there isn't enough air so it's dangerous!
They could also flow upward or
downward. It's like a giant dragon.
We all got together again!
Don't back down! Fight for justice!
That's why I told them to
attach the safety rope!
Yeah!
We won't accomplish anything
standing around like this.
Finally...
Deep currents flow really slowly.
It stinks! Hypocrites' blood!
Let's look for them. I now have a search light.
Guys!
What?!
Once they flow to the deep
sea, it takes 2000 years...
What happened to you, Sanji?!
You've become even more susceptible to women!
A 210 million bounty - "Wet-Haired" Caribou!
Is it your eyes?!
Franky...
Just surrender!
...until they flow upward to the surface.
This isn't like you!
What?! You're a Devil Fruit eater?!
What?!
...Nipple Lights!
I feel sorry for him... What happened to this
ladies' man - Sanji-san in the past 2 years?
2000 years?!
Yes, that's why there
are a number of myths...
Why there?!
Sanji!
You should not do that!
It's not healthy to push yourself too hard!
At this rate, he's gonna
bleed to death once he meets
Oh?
about the dark and
undiscovered deep currents.
Th-That's huge!
Terrifying!
My sword...!
Well then, thank you!
the Mermaids
that he's longing to see.
Monsters! Curses! Spirits of the dead!
Say "hi" to everybody in
Birdie Kingdom for me!
I can't help worrying.
No way...
We can beat them, Captain!
Those pirates are strong!
We'll have to call for blood
donations at the Fish-Man Island.
What?! There are ghosts in the deep sea?!
Usopp! Is Sanji alright?!
That's...
Yeah, you're right.
O-O-One beautiful woman...
I wonder if Fish-Men and Mermaids
have the same blood as humans.
--Huh? Really? I'm scared!
--It's exciting!
Let's get away!
Hey, guys!
--Hey, stay with me!
--Two beautiful woman...
Ghosts... I don't know about that.
The one who kills the most Navy Soldiers
will become my right-hand man!
The bubble that coats the
Sunny has the same quality...
Hey, this is no good,
Chopper! Stop the bleeding!
But we're gonna get on a downward flow.
...as the bubbles at Sabaody
Archipelago as we just saw.
Just look all around.
F-F-Franky, you're...!
So go for it!
They must be looking for us too.
That's how we get to the deep sea.
Yeah!
What's the matter?
Stop analyzing the bubble
in such a calm manner!
Your right-hand man?
What about us?
Is there something that concerns you-mecha?
Yes, Robin's right.
Basically, they're the same.
You guys better do something too
because, with this much power,
Deep layer...
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
Surface...
--Mecha?! I wanna play!
--Wait, Luffy!
Downward flow...
It stretches to a certain point and beyond
that, it allows things to get through.
I'm gonna launch out into the world!
Where did you go?
I don't know what's so
great and besides that,
Submerge...
Twang-twang!
it looks like the Navy
ships are already here!
Come back!
Which means if we fire a gun or a
cannon at a creature that attacks us,
So there are wonderful currents...
Luffy-san! Zoro-san! Sanji-san!
Whoa! What is it now?!
You guys didn't understand a bit, did you?!
Oh no! When did they get here?!
the bubble won't break.
Pacifistas!
Huh? Then, on what occasion
will it break instead?
Dammit!
What?!
You wanna sing, Nami-san?
There are 3 Navy ships!
In this vast, submerged expanse,
the Sunny Eyes don't help that much.
Shut up!
As you can imagine, when there are too many
holes at once, it'll break. For example,
Hey, should we fight back?!
They're gonna get us!
We're stuck...
Why are the Navy's human weapons here?!
The darkness is stirring up our anxiety.
Shoot! Shoot and sink them!
if we are bitten by a Sea
Kings' fangs, it'll be trouble.
They're the bear-like men!
What is that sound?
In fact, we're not getting
anywhere. What should we do?
But Hancock told me not to cause trouble...
This is it!
Oh no! It's gonna hit us!
Nami, I see it!
Again, what the hell are you talking about?!
It's coming from behind!
Yeah?
We can't stop the ship so try
not to overlook anything.
The wonderful current?!
Slave...
They're fighting... We're safe!
...Arrow!
Or if the ship itself breaks up by
crashing into a rock or a trench,
Where is it?
That's cool!
There should be some trace of them.
A pirate--Straw Hat Luffy. Verified.
--Oh!
--What is that?
the broken mast or planking will break
the bubble and that also spells danger.
Let's find them.
So that's the downward current!
Yeah.
Wh-What just happened?
Are those real Pacifistas?
They're aiming at me?!
I-It's...
The downward flow--plume!
So we have to be careful with
creatures and obstacles in the sea.
Oh, it's a jellyfish! There's a
massive jellyfish above us!
Pacifistas, huh? It's exciting!
How... cool!
...The Kuja Pirates!
As long as we don't do anything
foolish from inside, it'll be fine.
That's huge! You're right!
It's like a massive...
Who...
I see! It's tougher than I thought!
They're twinkling! Like stars in the night!
...put a Navy ship...
88 million berry bounty. Lip
"Service" Doughty. Subdued.
...waterfall in the sea!
But 70% of ships that head
for the Fish-Man Island...
That's beautiful!
...in my way?
Oh, a tentacle!
Captain Doughty!
...end up sinking. So be cautious.
D-Do you wanna be my friend?
What's gonna happen?!
Don't touch it, Chopper!
Follow the Pacifistas! Catch the pirates!
With my Gatling, I can catch
a whole school of fish!
It's probably venomous!
Yeah!
A single blow?!
He had an 88 million bounty
and he was no match...
Then let's see which of
us can catch more fish!
Interesting!
This is bad news... Oh,
Captain, where are you going?
Oh no! A little...
The sea is "falling" far below!
At an extraordinary speed!
...Coup de Burst!
Weren't you guys listening to what Nami said?!
--Wait for me!
--Hey, hey!
Fools! I don't wanna fight
him - he beat Doughty!
"Too many holes" is no good!
Wh-What?!
We better run!
Don't ever try it again or I'll kill you!
Nature's great!
The jellyfish got eaten!
That's Kuja's logo!
What a spectacular stream!
I wonder how deep it is.
Damn! Hachi said he'd show us
the way to the Fish-Man Island
Oh, we lost some air.
Kuja?
They're strong amazonian pirates led
by a pirate empress - a Warlord.
Straw Hat Boss, do something!
Better than getting eaten!
so I thought it was gonna be a safe trip!
It's far greater than I had heard.
Coup de Burst is a weapon that
shoots a fair amount of air.
A Warlord?!
If nothing is done, those human
weapons will kill us all!
Oh yeah!
Her name is Boa Hancock.
They gave me a lot of lunches!
I can't see the bottom! It's completely dark!
They say anyone who sees her
will be attracted by her beauty
But since we're in the water,
we only have a limited amount of air.
Big Boss!
Since Sanji is sick,
let's eat these, everybody!
Huh?
and turned to stone in the end.
We're dead!
Big Boss is gone!
With that speed,
we're gonna be slammed
So when we shoot the air
out, the bubble shrinks!
I'm so starved!
Big Boss?
Oh, too bright! She is dazzling!
into the bottom and die!
My bones are starved!
That's how they call Straw Hat?
I see. But it makes me nervous
to see the bubble shrinking.
There is no end to her beauty!
Is it really okay to go with the flow?
Nami, the ship is gonna
be stable for a while?
Wait! My side hurts!
Wow! She must be a goddess!
Don't worry about the ship.
Fool! Run! They're gonna kill you!
Don't we have to do anything?
Goddess?!
Sunny is the strongest ship built
from the treasure tree Adam.
Nope. We just have to ride
this big sea current for now.
Where is she?! Goddess? Goddess?
Stupid! You're in my way!
That fish that got bitten
turned upside down!
Huh? Who are you?
Goddess... Oh, goddess... Goddess... Godd...
Alright!
So, yeah, we can continue
on like this for a while.
So they contain a neurotoxin as I thought.
Advance!
The deep sea's scary! It's dark too...
--G...
--He turned to stone!
We don't have much to do until later.
That's...
No way!
Oh, that's Hancock and the others!
I didn't know that it lives here...!
Big Boss!
There are a lot of fish with
white eyes... It's creepy here!
Then we have a little time, huh?
Move your ship, Boa Hancock!
There's something that I
have to tell you all about.
Are you trying to interfere
with us fulfilling our duty?
That's interesting!
--Look at that, Coribou!
--Yes, brother!
No, I'm not!
I just don't feel like making way for you.
--Not that way, fool!
--I'm sorry!
Big Boss Luffy, beat them up!
Sh-She's acting like a child!
It's a demon that rules the realm of water!
Is that a problem?
Show them Straw Hats' power!
And the enemy of the human race!
Go, Luffy... Now is the chance!
Why are they calling you Straw Hat?
She just winked at us...
Hey, you! Don't you know who I am?
She helped us. Let's set sail now!
Since the deep sea is always dark,
there are many creatures with rudimentary eyes.
You know that Warlord?
Get out of my way or I'll kill
you and pull out your bowels!
Yeah, I was sent to the Maiden Island
and I became friends with them.
There's something that I
have to tell you all about.
This may surprise you! I'm the
Revolutionary Dragon's son!
So they can't see well.
That's the legendary
female-only island, right?
Fools! See this? Come here!
And the grandson of the hero--Garp!
I didn't know they were real...
But there are some with developed eyes too.
Friend with the pirate empress?!
I wreaked havoc during the War of the Best!
Hey, were you really training hard?!
I'm a big-time pirate with a
400 million bounty--Straw...
Straw Hats! You should turn back now!
What's that? How can I see things without eyes?
Yeah, I'm so ready!
It's dangerous!
Damn... It's not fair...! It's not fair...!
Could it be about...
I had forgotten about you.
Do you people wanna know why?
--There is a monster!
--What?!
Straw Hat is not scum like you!
What's the matter, Sanji?
What are you talking about? Cut that crap!
Whoa, so they're Luffy's friends!
...The robot's secrets?!
You have more secrets?!
There are a bunch of creatures
that I've never seen before.
The answer is... Tum, tum, tum, tum, tum...
What can you transform into?!
Or you have a secret weapon?!
--1, 2, 3, 4...
--Looks like they're having fun!
...a secret!
Tell us, robot brother!
Okay, let's get ready to set sail now!
Are you talking to yourself?
Super Armored Me!
--Yeah!
--Yes, Nami-san!
No problem. I'm used to being lonely.
What's the matter, Usopp?
Hey! Stop fooling around and look for them!
I was just thinking... did you
guys beat all those Navy soldiers?
Why are they calling you Straw Hat?
No, I'm afraid...
Those myths are just made up by someone.
No, we heard them shouting
while we were flying.
Hey, you! Don't you know who I am?
I'm afraid it's not about that-robo.
Why did I get hit?
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji! Where are you?!
Wow, cool! He speaks Robotese!
Get out of my way or I'll kill
you and pull out your bowels!
Then, why aren't they coming
after us from inland?
This is what I wanna tell you about.
This may surprise you!
I'm the Revolutionary Dragon's son!
Oh?
It... It's right there...
Go ahead and eat while you're listening.
This rope must be...
And the grandson of the hero--Garp!
Cut it out, guys!
Everyone.
B-Behind you...
I wreaked havoc during the War of the Best!
This is Backup Unit Platoon 3!
Hachi told us that he would show
us the way to the Fish-Man Island
Have you seen that pirate guy?
What are you saying...
Can you hear me?
I'm a big-time pirate with a
400 million bounty--Straw...
Oh yeah, he's still here!
I totally forgot about him.
--What's wrong? What happened?
--We can't get to Grove #42!
but he got severely injured at Sabaody and
Be... Behind me?
he's under medical care at Fish-Man Island.
Where did he go?
--Why is that?
--B-Because...
I haven't seen him since we got this deep.
Uh-huh.
Straw Hat is not scum like you!
He got injured for the same reason as Duval.
...there are huge bugs standing in our way...
Maybe he got thrown off
during the downward pull.
He had been protecting the Thousand Sunny.
What? Bugs?!
Behind me...
That could be it!
Huh?
His hands and legs were tied up so
he couldn't hold on to anything.
Around a year ago, the Navy
found out about the Sunny
What are they?!
What?!
Well but...
Straw Hat Boss!
and those two both faced fierce battles
and were taken out of commission.
It's the Kraken!
...he untied himself. See?
Shoot!
Huh? Then how did the ship
remain undamaged after that?
I see.
How huge!  The monster octopus!
They all got fooled and became his crew.
Th-Then, he's somewhere
on the ship? Where is he?
Looks like he broke a lot of ships!
There was someone else who fought for it.
PX-5, who is he for real?
I won't let them mess with
Usopp'n's new adventure'n!
Ships that had left for the
New World have been attacked!
He's got to be hiding somewhere...
There was someone else?
What?!
He's the one who separated us 2 years ago.
Please! I don't wanna die! Go back!
"Triple-Tongued" Demalo Black.
Oh no...
When men part ways, we don't shed tears'n.
I'll sneak into the girls' room--
if that's what you want, honey.
If you just wait for a few days, it would...
A 26 million berry bounty.
Good luck, Usopp'n!
The big Warlord - Bartholomew Kuma!
--What?!
--26 million? That means he is...
Shut up!
I have a good idea!
Damn! We have enough problems already
As long as they're not coming, that's good.
I couldn't believe my eyes when
I got to the Sunny a few days ago...
...An imposter?!
but now we have to look out for him too.
If they're in trouble, we're lucky.
Let's tame him!
They found out! Let's run!
Let's just leave now!
Who cares! He's not that strong anyway.
Huh?
What did you say, Luffy?!
Nami, lead the way!
What's up with that shit?!
So he posed as Straw Hat
Luffy and tricked us!
Let's tame the octopus
and make him pull our ship!
You can count on me!
I've been expecting you.
Alright!
No way!
Because the real one is dead!
What are you doing here?!
Take a good look!
This is Platoon 4.
Damn! I almost got ripped
off by a jerk with a
It's great.
No, you don't have to take
a good look since it's huge!
I'm sorry. All of the sudden,
it started raining and the
Mission accomplished.
Those formidable 3 who were fighting
against the Kraken went missing.
measly 26 million berry bounty!
Oh, it's big!
gunpowder got wet!
What?
Rain? Where?
We're dead!
So He was posing as me?
It must've been around for
several hundred years!
Sabaody Archipelago should
be clear and sunny today!
That Sanji and Zoro, too?
The Kraken appears in many
myths in the world -
There's no way they could have
survived after getting lost
They looked just like the real ones!
it's like a visionary creature!
I better leave here before it's too late.
with just those bubbles to protect them.
No thunder. We don't want
normal people to get hurt.
It has no bones and I'm a
skeleton without any flesh...
The one who fooled you is an idiot
but you guys are just unlucky.
There isn't even a scratch on the Sunny.
The bubbles are a pain in the neck here.
It's the polar opposite of me.
You all have to come with us.
And Rayleigh told me later...
But I can't believe we
caught such perfect wind.
I don't care!
It's a shame that I couldn't kill Straw Hat
I work for the Revolutionaries army.
And I don't know why but the
real Straw Hat is here too.
You're quite good.
It brought us here just as we wanted.
You can't see this kind of thing often, so...
Since I have a connection with them,
I wanna let them get away from here.
but I can prove that he's dead by killing
That's because Nami-chan is a good girl.
What?
Sketching? How relaxed?!
When we entered this area, PX-5 detected him.
I think you guys half expected that.
I'll help you but do you
have any plan, Luffy?
these crewmembers and taking their heads.
Shoot at him, PX-5!
The problem is that we're in the sea.
He saved our lives!
Good luck! We will miss you on Weatheria!
No. No. No.
But don't rush, Caribou!
And after we vanished from the island,
The problem is the size of it.
You can't rush!
Kuma-san visited Rayleigh and told him...
It would be dangerous
even if we were on land.
If I kill them here, there's no one else to sail the ship.
What's wrong with them?
I don't have much time left.
That was close!
They navigate the ship pretty well.
This is the kind of situation
when everybody agrees to
What are you doing?!
As soon as you get to the Fish-Man Island,
This bag is holding all my precious lunches!
I don't know what made him obey the Navy
run away at full speed!
you all will be dead!
Shift the helm to the south!
but he agreed to be a guinea pig and let
Oh, it's inflating!
Hey, Nami, go straight towards the octopus!
his body be modified into a cyborg
Don't be a fool!
piece by piece and he somehow
What? This jelly inflates?
H-Here's his poster...
--The octopus will...
--Whoa, whoa, Nami-san. I'm here for...
lost his personality before the War of the Best.
...here for...
Oh, we got a bubble roof!
But I don't think he could guess what
Looks exactly the same!
each of us would do after we get separated!
Listen, guys.
...for you!
You held it! Good job!
A coated ship has the ability
to reduce any kind of pressure.
Even so he waited for us at the
ship without his personality?
So that guy is the real Straw Hat!
Thanks to the rehabilitation
and to Nami for wearing a coat.
So once the floating bag at the ship's
bottom which keeps it on the surface
Here he is!
He made Dr. Vegapunk, who modified him,
Brace up!
It's dangerous to be on this ship!
I've got to protect myself!
We came here to catch the real one anyway!
has been removed,
agree to program a mission into his mind.
--Oh no! Shoot! Dammit!
--Now he can't get away.
Something's coming from behind!
it'll be less buoyant and start to sink.
Straw Hat!
Oh, it's you! Are you gonna
get in my way again?!
How did he get in there?
That's how it works.
"Defend the pirate ship until the day that one of the
Brother!
I see.
We weren't paying attention. If he
wasn't so stupid, we could be in danger now.
I've been told not to cause
trouble in order to set sail!
Too complicated, huh?
They came back!
Anyway, spread the sail now!
Straw Hats comes back to the ship."
Coribou! Guys!
Don't worry! You don't need to set sail!
His body wasn't taking form.
It has melted like mud.
Sail?
That's why, for the past 2
years, without his own memory,
A coated sailing ship
--We're gonna save my brother!
--Yes!
is driven by the sea current
instead of the wind.
Unlike 2 years ago, I'm officially
a member of the Navy now!
--Like mud?
--Yeah, I'm sure it's a Devil Fruit power.
he had been carrying out his own
You came back to save me, huh?!
I thought it just submerged and travelled.
orders, as a human weapon, waiting for us.
So I'm gonna catch you here!
He must've eaten a Logia-type fruit.
Alright, we better hurry
before the Navy comes again!
PX-5!
He was only pretending to be caught.
That's insane.
This is Central Unit Platoon 5 at Grove #42!
Why did he do such a thing for us?
Don't do it!
Hey, get me out of here, mister!
Mister in swimshorts!
Terms like "connection,"
"Revolutionaries army,"
This is an emergency situation!
All the troops in Platoon 2 that
came before have become negative...
That's slow...
remind me about Luffy's father - the
leader of the Revolutionaries army.
--The coating popped!
--That ship is even bigger than Sunny!
I'll become your servant!
What are you saying? Negative?!
I wanna become like moss...
What?!
I don't know my father that well.
I'm no good. I wanna become a water flea...
Oh... Guys!
But that bear-like guy was a good guy, huh?
What's the matter, Chopper?
According to them, Straw Hat Luffy got on a
Second Gear!
I don't know. I feel hot all of the sudden.
giant bird and flew away!
Kuma...
Bird? What are you guys doing now?!
There is no mistake that he's the one
who gave us the past 2 worthwhile years.
I can't stand the heat.
We're fighting against unknown enemies!
It's hot! What happened?
Gum-Gum...
--They look like a school of jellyfish.
--Shut up, Roronoa! Cut it out!
Damn, that bastard!
Wh-What's this? Smoke?
It's blocking our view forward!
He gave me trouble to the last minute!
We can't even ask him why he
did it but just remember that.
I've got to find a new boy-toy...
It's coming!
Smoke from the sea floor? Why?
--It's too big!
--How can we fight against it?!
Bartholomew Kuma turned out
to be one of our greatest allies.
...Jet Pistol!
It's...
It could be...
Third Gear...
No!
Navy reinforcements! We
were about to leave...
You'll break the bubble!
But even if we meet him again,
Kuma is now a heartless human weapon.
Everybody!
Straw Hat...
Hydrothermal deposits!
Chicken Voyage!
He is using Haki!
--A volcanic area in the sea!
--What?!
Straw Hat's ship is in range now!
That's all I have to say.
Can we... get away somehow?!
Look, you can see that there
were volcanic eruptions here!
Wait a minute! A giant
bird is coming towards us!
I appreciate what he did but
there are still some mysteries.
He beat the Pacifista with a single blow!
Don't do anything! I'll beat it!
Let's get away from here!
If it erupts, we're gonna die!
I hope we can find out his motive one day.
No! You're gonna break the bubble!
Ally?
--Oh, you woke up, Sanji.
--Eat lunch! It's from the Maiden Island!
Listen! If you wanna fight against
it that much, here is an idea!
It's hot... It's hot...
See ya!
Maiden Island? Is that
Kuma guy really an ally?
He...
What is it? Tell me.
Something's after us!
I think I'll see you somewhere again!
Carnivorous Tubeworms!
They're coming from behind too!
Wait, Straw Hat!
Don't you realize where
I was for the past 2 years?
I got it!
We have no choice.
Don't let Straw Hat get away!
Okay, that's good!
A little Coup de Burst!
Yeah!
What kind of training were you doing
at the dream island full of women, Luffy?
That's the extra-vehicular
Flutter Kick Coating!
How do you like it, Nami-san?
Did you see me getting stronger?
Hey, Luffy!
An extra-vehicular diving suit!
Faceless Crabs!
Whoa, whoa, Sanji-san, I don't
know what you've been through
Oh?
Luffy! I knew it was you!
As long as you're in it, you can
fight as you want even in water!
A little Coup de Burst!
Sanji!
Why are you always in trouble?!
but let's enjoy the voyage now!
Do you wanna sing with me?
I don't even know what they are!
Oh!
Answer, Platoon 5! What's going on?!
If I let these fools do whatever
they want, I'll be in danger too!
A little Coup de Burst!
It's no mistake this time!
It's been a while, guys!
Stop trying to cheer me up! I feel pathetic!
W-We are...
The deep sea's scary!
Brother, there he is. Straw Hat.
You shouldn't have done that, stranger!
We're facing an unexpected obstacle...
Roronoa! "Black Foot"!
I knew they were alive!
Luffy and the others can't survive here.
We wanted to run away!
I can see that, you fool!
Don't do it!
Now, they're gonna fight!
PX-7!
I'm starting to get sad.
I finally got to see him after 2 years...
I told you guys to run from the beginning
I'm gonna join them this time for sure!
How could you turn us down?!
but that Captain-san won't listen!
Cut it out! They're not gonna die so easily!
How deeply are we submerged now?
Maybe they're all shy.
I used Coup de Burst little by
little but we lost so much air.
Would you rather they fought on this ship?
It's getting darker and darker.
You don't have to be ashamed!
Outta my way!
Okay, good luck! Go far away!
We went through the euphotic zone and
Let's have a cup of tea together!
we're at the bottom of the twilight zone.
This rope is annoying.
Stay away from this ship!
What is that?! It's so bright!
I-I-I'm gonna go out of my mind!
I cut him!
It must be more than 1000 meters below.
No, I broke his neck!
Alright.
Is that the Fish-Man Island?
It's really quiet.
--Okay, let's go!
--Yeah!
It feels different from submersibles.
Do you think Luffy and the others are there?
The Straw Hats! The real ones!
Oh! You've got such a cute face!
We haven't submerged
another 3,000 meters yet.
Huh?
It feels like flying in the sky.
They're nothing like the imposters!
Wait! You have to attach the safety rope!
No, don't do it!
"WHO-ARE-YOU?"
The sky, huh?
I have to start using what
I studied on Weatheria for 2 years.
You'll be separated!
Hey! What are you sending
the flashing signals with?!
What's wrong? Answer, Platoon 5!
Nami-san's worrying about me!
Whale! There is a whale!
Hey, Luffy, you're the 9th.
--Do you see anything?
--No, it's still too bright.
Sanji-kun, now is the chance!
--Laboon! Laboon!
--No, that's old man Whitebeard!
You guys! Draw his attention for me!
Shut up! Cut it out!
Luffy, hurry up!  Everybody's
waiting at the ship!
I'm gonna beat him with one strong blow!
Hey, hey, what's wrong, Sanji?!
Okay!
Oh no!
I could beat him right away!
I-I-I don't know... Suddenly,
Don't let them get away!
Catch them at any cost!
You can't cut him!
It's an angler! He tricked us!
it felt like someone was
squeezing my heart...
Hey, hey, there is no time
to relax and watch whales.
I want the octopus as a pet!
We were fooled by the deep-sea hunter!
It's really been a long time!
I wonder how everybody is!
The floating bag is removed!
70% will sink! 70%! I can't just sit around!
Okay! What about sail?
Are they okay?
Stay as far away as you
can! Even a millimeter...
I'm so happy!
We're ready!
That was close!
I can't believe we have less than a 50%
Is it time to go, Nami?
We're totally trapped! Can we get away...?
But it's attacking us!
Yes, at your command, Captain.
chance to get to the Fish-Man Island.
Move aside, guys!
I don't see any creatures or Sea Kings
Hey, what's wrong?
Franky...
or obstacles that look dangerous yet.
Oh!
What is it this time?!
...Rocket Launcher!
There's something at 6
o'clock! Is it a creature? No...
Rayleigh!
I-Is it a human?
Alright...
What the hell is it?!
What?!
Are you guys all ready?!
A monster in the sea that looks like a man...
No way!
--Got it!
--How powerful!
--Yes, brother!
--Yes, yes!
You guys!
D-Dark King Rayleigh?!
No, another arm!
It's a Sea Bonze!
The target is right there!
I've got a lot of things that I want
to share with you but in any case,
Why does he keep attacking us?!
It's easier to just destroy their
ship and let it be swallowed by the sea
I came here to check but you seem alright.
It's gonna hit us!
thank you for going along with
my selfish decision for 2 years!
Guard Boost!
He's gonna capsize the ship!
Your power sure has improved.
They got a hard hit!
but that's no good because they
won't know who did it to them.
That wasn't the first time.
Uh-huh!
Now go to your friends!
He's right! You've always been selfish!
That?!
Are you guys okay?
Hey, Ankoro! You can't do that!
We gotta cut their heads
off and bring them back
H-He did it!
Uh-huh! Rayleigh, thank you for
everything these past 2 years!
--Well done!
--Yeah, Chopper!
to show the world what Caribou is capable of!
Don't eat ships! How many
times do I have to tell you?
Rear Admiral-dono, the
pirate ship is submerging!
Yes!
You're out of character. Just go!
We're gonna hit the mountain!
They're not ready to fight!
It's a complete surprise attack!
What?! Damn!
Captain Vander Decken-sama won't like this!
You fools!
Mil Fleurs!
Do you have any idea...
how heinous they are? Hey!
D-Did he help us?
Don't make a mistake, guys!
Gigantesco Mano!
--Yes!
--Yes! Yes!
Let's go! We have to get away
anyway! He is a monster too!
Rear Admiral!
Take care, Luffy...
Hey, guys! There is a ship kind
of thing coming from behind!
Rayleigh!
What big hands!
--What?
--A ship?
I'll do it!
Spread the sail!
It's coming towards us!
--Yes!
--Nice, Robin! You saved us!
Charge!
--Yes!
--Yeah!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Good. Although I'm in water,
I was okay because it
was just a brief moment.
What the hell is that?!
They did great.
Set sail!!
--It's a pirate ship!
--They're pushing against us!
Alright, it's my turn!
Yeah!
Go away! The bubble is gonna pop!
Here is the new technique!
Third Gear!
Let's go to the Fish-Man Island!
No! They're gonna come through the bubble!
Who are they?
The infamous ghost ship, the Flying Dutchman,
emerges from the dark.
Along with the attacking Caribou Pirates,
the Sunny sinks to greater depths.
Facing the Demon of the ocean floor, Kraken,
Having departed for the New World,
After two long years
Luffy, Zoro and Sanji use the techniques
the Straw Hats finally assemble on the Sunny.
But suddenly, a submarine volcano erupts,
creating yet more danger.
the Straw Hats are amazed
by the unknown underwater scenery.
They reach the giant
acquired during their two-year training.
But there is no time to rejoice.
submarine waterfall Plume.
But then, the Straw Hats are
scattered in the Deep Sea
Franky tells them about the
man who protected them.
As they are about to depart for
But there, the bane of the high seas,
Evading falling rocks,
they make it to the ocean floor,
the sea floor paradise, Fish-Man Island,
by the massive current caused by the battle.
But there's something dark
lurking behind the Sunny.
where a scenery not expected
in the Deep Sea awaits them.
the Kraken, is living.
the pursuing Marines arrive on the scene.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Lost in the Deep Sea!
The Straw Hats Get Separated!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Deadly Combat under the Sea!
The Demon of the Ocean Strikes!"
Undersea Volcanic Eruption!
Drifting to the Fish-Man Island!
"Everyone Together! Luffy,
Setting Out for the New World!"
"A Surprising Fact!
The Man Who Guarded the Sunny!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!