Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he
ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
However, no one has ever fully explored it
and his friends venture into that sea.
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
And on their way to the
next stage - the New World,
they reached to the Fish-Man Island located
10,000 meters below sea level.
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
However...
The pirate boy with a straw hat!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Throw him out of this country!
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training
Luffy and the rest of the Straw Hats
returned to Sabaody Archipelago.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training
and returned to Sabaody Archipelago.
and set sail for the Fish-Man Island...
And on their way to the
next stage - the New World,
And in order to go on to the
...located 10,000 meters below sea level
to go on to the next stage - the New World.
A human with a straw hat on...
they reached the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level...
And in order to go on to the
next stage--the New World,
they set sail for the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level!
At Straw Hat Luffy's hands... at his
hands... the Fish-Man Island will be...
Gum-Gum...
they set sail for the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
You guys!
...only to be attacked
by the New Fish-Man Pirates
out of  the blue and
...Elephant Gun!
...destroyed!!
become separated again.
Set sail!!
Hey guys, come here!
"The King of the Fish-Man Island!
Neptune, the God of the Sea!"
Luffy and the others were rescued by
Mermaids and were brought to Camie's house.
The Fish-Man Island!
Hey, Ankoro! You can't do that!
I give you an option.
It's huge!
Do you wanna enlist under our
banner - the New Fish-Man Pirates?
It's in a big bubble! There are
clouds? Maybe there is air inside.
Don't eat ships!
Sanji-chan!
D-Did he help us?
Or do you refuse?
We don't have time! Anyone?!
If you refuse, we'll sink you.
That's the Fish-Man Island
so we're 10,000 meters deep now!
Let's go! We have to get away
anyway! He is a monster too!
Somebody please! I beg you!
No way! Stupid!
Give blood to Sanji!
Guys! Hurry up-chin!
Here we go! Coup de Burst!
"The Fish-Man Island Will Be Annihilated?!
Sharley's Prophecy!"
Quiet! Stay quiet!
What the hell is that?!
Yeah! We made it!
We're in trouble if they notice.
The bubble here is a double structure!
"Undersea Volcanic Eruption!
Drifting to the Fish-Man Island!"
We're gonna run into one
more bubble! Hold on tight!
Now is the chance! Get on the ship-chin!
Please! Spare him some blood!
My friend is dying!
Hey, what are they?!
Everybody, grab an oar and be ready!
Water?!
Someone with blood type S RH negative?!
Who are they?
We don't have time! Donate your blood!
The group of sea monsters!
THE FISH-MAN DISTRICT "NOAH"
The current is strong!
We beg you!
We're dead! After we got all the way here!
--Dead men tell no tales, they have no desire.
--Is that...
Help... me...
They're so cool! The sea monsters!
Can't breathe...
--...me?
--In the dark land where even crows can't fly.
Hurry up! They'll come
after us at any minute!
We have 4 Devil Fruit eaters but...
I'm sorry, Sanji-chin.
I'll never return to the Fish-Man Island!
Hurry up and cross the Red Line!
It's very hard for humans to get a
blood transfusion on this island.
Somebody's riding it!
Dead men don't need jewels on their finger.
Damn! The Mermaid Cafe of my dreams!
"Landing at the Fish-Man Island!
Beautiful Mermaids!"
But Luffy-chin and the others will...!
Reach...
I wanted to take one look
at the beautiful Mermaids!
You can't even see
somebody's sorrow in the dark.
...out!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
Let it go, you idiots! Shut your
mouths and just keep rowing!
Damn! I've been looking so hard but I
can't find anybody who'll give blood!
Look for it! Look for it!
Sunken treasures are mine!
Why are you obeying such fools as humans,
Damn! What a disaster!
Damn! I can't swim against the current!
I'm not gonna give up!
There must be somebody!
Kraken!
As soon as we got away
from the sleeping Kraken,
Sanji...
I am the richest person in the
world - Captain Vander Decken!
we were surrounded by...
A PIRATE FROM THE SOUTH BLUE "CRAB-HAND" GYRO
Human!
...so many sea monsters at
10,000 meters below sea level
Luffy! I found a human here!
and couldn't even fight back!
Where am I?
Oh, Luffy-chin!
Don't tell me it's...!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Should I enlist under the
Fish-Men's banner or die?
What are you doing, Surume?!
We were almost there!
This is a coral apartment in the sea.
Even in the sea?!
That barrel drifted here along
with Camie's friends. What's in it?
The dorm is at the very
bottom so the rent is cheap.
I had no choice but to enlist
under their banner for a while!
Saying that won't help!
Hang on! Don't get thrown off!
Liquor? Treasure?
How absurd!
I don't know. It's very tightly-sealed.
We're here, on the surface!
My eyes are spinning!
A ghost ship?!
Why do we humans have to enlist
under the Fish-Men's banner?!
So are mine! But I don't have eyes!
You shouldn't be so scared!
Hey, Camie!
What do you think? Should
we open it secretly?
I turned! For no reason!
Oh, we're moving away from the Mermaid Cafe!
Everybody!
Is it okay to do that?
I found it!
I think so.
Stop crying and let's go, guys!
We are lucky to even be alive!
Oh no!
Oh? You're well-prepared, Ishilly!
This is my All Blue!
It's a ghost ship!
Huh? They escaped?
I see.
Yes, Boss. As soon as my back was turned.
Straw Hat Luffy finally got this far.
What should we do, Boss?
We thought that you were
a ghost at that moment!
Sanji! Are you awake?
Did they escape again-dosun?
They never learn, don't they-dosun?
Sanji-chin!
Th-That is the real one! Look at that sail!
Bring him...
Where am I?
Humans always escape.
The infamous Flying Dutchman!
...here!
Should I bite off their flesh?
"Excitement Blow-out!
Sanji's Life Under Threat!"
What a relief!
We're in a town at the harbor.
It shouldn't exist in the real world!
Sanji-chin, you lost almost
all the blood from your body.
It happened several hundred years ago.
We're right in middle of the sea monsters!
What a pain in the butt-ch!
I'm so glad that we found the blood donor!
One stormy day, the captain of the
pirate ship suddenly lost his mind
You guys are the Straw Hats, aren't you?
No problem!
Wh-Who are you? How do you know about us?
Oh, blood...
We can make them an example as always.
THE CAPTAIN OF THE NEW
FISH-MAN PIRATES HORDY JONES
and killed all his crew by throwing
them into troubled waters one by one!
Even if the Straw Hats survived, they're humans,
What's wrong with me?
Yes, I know you all very well.
Then I'll go get them-ch!
Don't get up so fast! You need to rest more.
And he even cursed the gods!
they can't live in the water.
You are the ones who foiled the
plans of the Arlong Pirates.
No, you won't, Ikaros.
Then they must be somewhere above the water?
But why won't the Fish-Men donate blood?
The name of the captain was Vander Decken
Much, yes sir!
Let's just find them!
I'll go!
and the ship was the Flying Dutchman!
We looked everywhere in the
town but we couldn't find a human.
Huh?
That act was easy enough to understand.
Get the bubble ready!
The gods got mad at him
But then you stood up for Hachi-san,
I almost gave up!
and set him adrift forever
under constant tortured!
the former officer of the Arlong Pirates 2 years ago
Guys, thank you for doing that.
and knocked one of the hateful
Celestial Dragons out!
But I don't remember anything.
And the ship right in front of us is
Captain Vander Decken's haunted ship!
Where was I and what was I doing?
I can barely remember...
Just like Fisher Tiger, the hero of
the Fish-Man Island who we respect.
You can't take that much at once!
That's the power drug!
Now, what should I do?
No, don't think back!
It's hard to believe that
this place is in the deep sea.
Calm down!
We don't want you to have a nosebleed again!
Fisher... Tiger...
We thought that Brook's ship
was a ghost ship but it wasn't.
THE NEW FISH-MAN PIRATES - FIGHTER HAMMOND
Oh yeah, Sanji! Let me introduce you
It's hard to decide what I should do with you.
to the blood donor that
we finally found at a bar!
What we found on that ship was nothing
special - just this funny skeleton!
So, tell me. Are you guys our enemies or not?
THE NEW FISH-MAN PIRATES – ASSASSIN HYOUZOU
You have to say "thank you"!
Franky-san is harsh!
THE NEW FISH-MAN PIRATES - FIGHTER KASAGON
I give you an option.
And 30 degrees is hard!
Huh? Don't tell me that I got
blood from such a delicate lady!
You're right!
Do you wanna enlist under our banner -
Ghost ships aren't something
that you see often.
the New Fish-Man Pirates?
Or do you refuse?
We just saw the Kraken which was
believed to be an imaginary monster
Super!
If you refuse, we'll sink you.
It's okay! We're both humans.
What did you say?
so it's not that surprising
to see a ghost ship.
We have to help each other
when we're in trouble.
Franky, fuel up!
Hey, Nami! I'm glad that you're okay!
What are you gonna do?
I just thought I was gonna die because of you!
You know that Luffy and the
others won't give in to them.
It's okay, silly!
But we're 10,000 meters deep now.
Robin!
If you want...
Then maybe that's...
...We can give you more, silly!
Robin.
We can't even fight and
there's no chance to win.
A real ghost ship!
Robin!
I'm scared!
Nami?
So we run!
Are you alright?
Robin, you can't entertain
yourself by making them upset.
Do the Coup de Burst using all the air we
Where are we? The Fish-Man Island?
have and charge into the Fish-Man Island!
Yeah, probably. Franky is scouting it out now.
Now here we are!
Captain Vander Decken!
Wadatsumi and Ankoro got a pirate ship!
This is my house!
I'm glad that he's back to his old self!
Are you serious?
Oh, you're up, Robin!
Otherwise, we are all gonna
die after coming this far.
Stupid humans! But they
have quite a good ship.
Hey, say "thank you" to them!
--Thanks to you.
--Did you see Luffy and the others?
It seems like that's the
only way that we can survive.
It's huge!
Luffy, let me see your right arm.
No, I can't find them.
They have a whole bunch
of treasure! I suspect!
Okay, I'll fill it up. Franky, steer the ship!
We just got together again...
Welcome home, Master-sama!
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
But there's no need to worry!
They wouldn't die so easily.
Alright, super count on me!
Positive reaction for poison!
Hey, that's Monsieur Pappagu!
Please come back!
That's a poisonous wound as I thought!
--You mean that really famous guy?!
--Wow! Is it really him?
He's right.
Come to think of it, when I
fought against the Fish-Men...
We have to find the Sunny too
Looks like they're getting busy.
Aren't they up to something?
Shut up! We have to get
through this by ourselves!
Oh, you're popular, huh?
but first, should we check
with some inhabitants?
I felt something sting me.
So Luffy and the others can come back to us!
I found a town nearby.
But you're okay?
Humans are not so clever anyway.
It's no use doing anything.
Uh-huh.
The water temperature has been
increasing for quite a while.
Okay, let me see it.
Yeah! Are you guys surprised?!
This must be deadly poison.
Are you really okay?
So, do you wanna work under us, Straw Hat Luffy?
Sanji-chan!
When I'm in the water, I'm just a...
Uh-huh.
I'm on my way!
I can't believe it!
An antibody must have developed
in your body to counter such poison.
...fashionable starfish but...
...on the Fish-Man Island, I'm the president
I'll...
No way! Stupid!
Could this be...
...live...
Have you ever been poisoned before?
and a very popular designer
of the Criminal Brand Co.
Ankoro! Wadatsumi!
...here!
We can't seize their treasure
if you eat the ship
Poison, huh?
The brand is known all over the world now
Sanji-chan, you're so funny!
You refused... the offer to join
the New Fish-Man Pirates!
so knock it down!
and we have stores in many countries!
Even the famous Doskoi Panda is...
He seems to have recovered after all.
By his willpower alone?
I almost died from
poisoning in the Impel Down.
I got it!
--Oh no, the Sea Bonze is...
--He's our enemy after all!
Then you guys are the Fish-Men's
enemy! Just sinful human beings!
Oh, look at that! What is it?
I wanna swim like you guys.
Luffy-chin, you can swim with a bubble on.
--Franky, use Coup de Burst!
--I can't! The fuel has run out!
Almost died? It's not funny!
Are you listening, Straw?!
--The 1st floor is a Criminal store.
--Oh!
Really?
Bleah!
Yeah, any craftsman in the city
can make one for you right away.
I think it was that guy!
Why should we work under you?!
Camie... Camie...
I have to fill up with
cola in the energy room!
The swordsman with octopus tentacles.
I'm glad because if he has a nosebleed now,
--Let's go there!
--Uh-huh!
Luffy, don't rub them the wrong way!
He blocked my punch!
Hey!
we don't have blood for a transfusion.
Listen to my story...
It's a shame. Then we can't
let you pass through here.
We don't have time!
And Sanji's blood type is very rare.
I bet he's very strong!
--No!
--He's gonna get us!
Huh? That's not good, is it?
Whoa, Miss, that's impossible!
This is where we sink you!
Hey, Camie.
What is it?
Sea Lion!
A shop assistant sounds troubled.
A complaint?
There is somebody that I really
wanna see on the Fish-Man Island.
As I said, the clothes
here are too expensive!
That's coming from the cove.
It's done! Franky, do it!
Who is it? The Mermaid Princess?
Those Mermaids are really noisy.
They're cute but...
Nope.
That must be...
Roger!
Now what should I do?
So let's make it 10,000 berries.
It's Jimbei!
Kraken!
That's too cruel, Miss!
It's less than half price!
These guys are all messed-up.
Sink it!
Boss Jimbei?
Wanna fight?!
And I accidentally poisoned Straw Hat.
Hey Luffy, you mean Jimbei the Warlord?!
It's her as I thought.
The Monster of the Arctic--Kraken?
No, he resigned during the war so he's the former Warlord.
Hey, Nami!
I'll be in trouble if he dies.
Go, Franky!
--Luffy!
--Nami-chin!
Yeah, he's my friend!
The Sunny is a lion too!
Ishilly and the others were screaming!
You bastard!
What's up with you?
You know the pirate empress, too.
Camie!
Ishilly!
Let's fight someday, Sea Lion!
It's been a while! How are you?!
Ishilly!
Fine!
Here we go! Coup de Burst!
Hey, what's going on?
I heard them around here!
When Ace died 2 years ago, I didn't lose heart...
Where did they go?
Oh, Monsieur Pappagu,
you came at the right time!
I heard them talking about opening a barrel.
...thanks to him!
We have a troublesome customer.
You brat!
Alright, that's enough. Stop!
Hey, so you own this store, huh?
The ship is...!
Everyone, come here.
There's somebody I'd like you to meet.
Why is everything so expensive?
Are you ripping me off?
Can't you see things clearly now?!
Monsieur!
Well, that's what they call brand
Good job!
You can't get back what you've lost!
equity because I'm a popular designer...
The owner of the Mermaid
Cafe who let Sanji stay...
We're losing air...
What is it that you still have?!
--Give me a discount!
--No, you...
What is this?
We're gonna get crushed...
Hey!
...Madam Sharley.
We're friends, aren't we?
Oh yeah? Thanks!
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
I owe you guys big time from 2 years ago!
I can't breathe! But I don't have lungs.
Is the blond boy okay now?
I'm glad that you're all alive!
THE OWNER OF THE MERMAID CAFE MADAM SHARLEY
Uh-huh. But since you're
such a beautiful lady,
What were you doing?!
Endure it! Until we reach the Fish-Man Island!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
It's all free! Take as much as you want!
it's best you stay away from the room.
I still have my friends!
And let's not tell Sanji-chin
that this place is in the
Free?! Really?!
We've been looking for you guys!
What's wrong with that ship?!
I wanna see Jimbei!
--Guys! Let's not show mercy!
--Yeah!
See you at the Fish-Man Island in 2 years!
They're so high-maintenance. They got lost!
back of the Mermaid Cafe.
We're heading in!
I'm looking forward to the day
when you and your friends visit us!
Why's that?
Wait for me, my dear Mermaids!
Thank you!
His doctor, Chopper-chin said that if
he finds out, there'll be trouble again.
Monsieur! They took everything!
Sanji, no! He's relapsing!
We made a promise to meet
again on this island.
You're so merciless!
What a strange prognosis.
I'm happy for you, guys!
Oh yeah, I read in the newspaper
that you were with Jimbei.
He needs rehab with less stimulating pics!
Hey, Big Mermaid!
The coating came off!
It got stuck on the giant bubble!
It's Madam Sharley, Luffy-chin!
Hey! Wake up, Wadatsumi!
Oh? What is it?
Yoo-hoo!
--What's this?
--It's beautiful!
Something's going on outside the store.
Avenge yourself! Get back at it!
Monsieur! Th-This is serious!
Oh, look ahead!
Don't touch it, Straw Hat boys.
Where's Jimbei?
What is that?!
What is it?
Um, Boss is not on the island now.
Well, Sanji's bubble and mine
popped so we got into Zoro's.
That's the crystal ball she
uses to look into the future.
The bubble here is a double structure!
I-I-It's him!
Madam's pre-vision is
famous in the Coral Hill.
Huh?
Him?
Normal ships will fall in this
layer because there is only air!
He resigned from the Warlords
during the war 2 years ago.
I thought I was gonna die!
It's him!
We're gonna run into one
more bubble! Hold on tight!
Don't make us worry!
I'm not practicing anymore.
It's him!
So the former members of the Fish-Man
Pirates could no longer stay here
Alright, here's a song to
celebrate your return.
Look! There in the air...
and they left with Boss Jimbei.
Lots of space!  There's no place like home!
He came from the palace!
It's better not knowing the future.
Luffy! I was scared!
What?! So I can't see him here?
Jamon! Jamon!
Water?!
It's a long story. But the war had a
lot of effects on this island too...
Well, how about this? Do you Mermaids poop?
You all have an amazing ability to survive.
Jamon! Jamon! Jamon!
I can't believe it!
You really tamed the monster octopus?
What does that have to
do with her pre-vision?
What is it? A whale?
--Camie!
Don't you have any class?
A-Apologize to her, Luffy-chin!
Camie!
And are you gonna use the Kraken?
--A ship is coming!
--It might be!
Sorry.
Yeah, I'm gonna use him like
experienced people do!
The current is strong!
Camie, you can take a day off today.
--The royal family's ship!
--Maybe no one's on it!
I'm sure somebody is!
Right, Surume?
Show them around the island.
That's a squid snack!
Who's on it, Medaka-chin sisters?
Surume!
Huh? Really?
Help... me...
We don't know yet.
--You don't often see the royal family's ship.
--They seldom come here.
You always work hard.
The Kraken is an octopus but
he named it Surume, oh yeah!
Can't breathe...
Why did he come down to the lower world?
And...
Maybe they're coming to catch Luffy-chin
and the others for illegal entry!
We have 4 Devil Fruit eaters but...
...these days we don't
have human pirate guests
This is the first time
I've seen him in person!
Alright, draw the Sunny, Surume!
What's this about?
He doesn't even have guards.
So what?
and my business is drying up.
What?
You guys need to hide!
Well, instead of making him draw the ship,
The girls from the cove will come soon
This can't be happening!
He's never travelled like this!
we have to make sure that
he's not gonna smash it up.
Sanji-chan, this way!
so we have enough hands (hitode).
Okay!
Enough starfish (hitode)...
Something wrong with the kingdom?
Reach...
Captain, the pirate ship is...
Oh no! I should have delivered
those clams to Pappagu by now!
He doesn't bother coming down
here unless there is a problem!
...out!
Don't let it get away! Go after it!
RYUGU PALACE
Yeah!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
That was so out-of-context!
Is it the royal family's gondola?
He must be hungry...
You think so?
--It is!
--Maybe!
--I bet so!
--So what?
What is it?
Damn! I can't swim against the current!
But it can't be somebody
from the royal family!
What? Monsieur Pappagu is having
fun at the cafe with his old friend.
Who is that old man?
They don't bother coming all the
way to this corner of the island.
Idiot, don't you know who
he is? That man is...
At the cafe?
Old friend?
...the king of the Ryugu Kingdom
on the Fish-Man Island -
This is no good, Captain Vander Decken!
Neptune-sama!
I couldn't mention this in front of her,
THE KING OF THE RYUGU KINGDOM
NEPTUNE THE GOD OF THE SEA
That's a crazy way to get in there.
Maybe they tried to self-destruct.
The Neptune 3 brothers-sama are here!
Oh no, the undersea volcano's gonna erupt!
Neptune!
but when Madam was a little child,
Whale!
Do you wanna go after them, Hammond?
HOE (A PET WHALE)
What?!
she said that many pirates
would come to the island.
That's a big Merman there...
We are too close to it!
I don't know if they're still alive though.
Hello, girls of the cove.
That was the year before
the Great Pirate Era began.
RYUGU KINGDOM THE NEPTUNE 3 BROTHERS
I prefer Mermaids...
I want to ask something.
Everyone! Let's go back for now!
Yeah, we'll go in.
Cut it out, guys!
What?!
He's a very hairy old man!
I don't want Neptune's army to find them first.
--Princes!
--What brought you here?
Among a host of other things,
Roger! Captain Vander Decken!
Princes?
That's rude! Get down on your knees now!
But first, let's go back to
Noah and let Boss know that...
she recently predicted the war at Marineford
Ankoro! Wadatsumi! Draw the ship!
No, Sanji-chan!
and Whitebeard's death.
The whale's cute!
...Straw Hat who shattered
Arlong-san's ambition is here.
What?!
--He came to see those humans?
--He personally came for that?
Oh, okay!
She can't stand knowing
what bad things will happen.
I am the richest person in the
world - Captain Vander Decken!
Hide here and stay still.
Must be scary!
Hey, Megalo! Are you sure that
it was these people-jamon?
What is this? Marshmallow?
Where's Chopper?
THE FISH-MAN ISLAND - THE SEA FLOOR
Oh, he's taking care of Sanji.
Oh no!
Luffy, tell Kraken to get away from here now!
--Luffy-chin! Usopp-chin!
--Yeah!
Oh? We saw that shark in the water!
Ah, no, it's not.
Yeah!
The milky sweet smell.
--Hey, Surume!
--Wait, don't need to!
Yeah, the one with clothes!
Don't know why but it makes me feel comfortable.
This is the main street of Coral Hill.
Is it a fruit from the
Fish-Man Island? Sniff, sniff.
Hey.
Look! That's the entrance
of the Mermaid Cafe.
He's running like hell already!
He had been captured by Surume!
Hey, what is...
That's a terrible look for
such a mythical monster!
Hey, look.
--I'll look.
--I won't!
You Straw Hat people.
Nice! Maybe we can hit it off!
--Maybe I'll look.
--I looked, so what?
Oh, I'm getting hungry!
It's a cafe!
He runs awful.
We have food too! Cakes and sea fruit.
Hey, he's moving!
Don't say that. That's how
horrifying the eruption is!
I received a report of an illegal entry.
--He moved!
--He didn't!
FIRST SON - FUKABOSHI (SHARK MERMAN)
What about meat?
Wh-What do you want?
--Maybe he moved.
--He moved, so what?
We Merfolk don't eat meat and fish
Didn't they come here?
That's right!
And what is he doing?
If you've seen them, tell me-fa-so-la-ti-do!
SECOND SON - RYUBOSHI (OARFISH MERMAN)
so what we have is; Wakame Brûlée,
Mozuku Tart, Kelp Soufflé...
I'm going to...
Wow! Yes!
If you haven't seen them, that's fine-mi-re-do!
--Come on!
--It's rehab!
Are they edible?
Moonfish! Shake, shake!
Yeah, he woke up!
--Oh, we have meat too!
--What?
THIRD SON - MANBOSHI (MOONFISH MERMAN)
I wanna stay here and play!
Luffy!
Shellfish meat! Scallop
Sandwich, Freshwater Clam Pizza...
We haven't seen anybody.
But I wanna see the eruption!
Are they that important?
That's not meat!
Don't ruin meat's reputation!
--Evacuate to the front of the ship!
--Yeah!
Where am I?
Oh, Luffy-chin!
Whoa... Anyway, let's
go in! The Mermaid Cafe!
That you princes have
to come all the way here?
It doesn't change anything!
It's only a few meters.
...invite you to the Ryugu Palace-jamon!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Yeah, Pappagu will be there.
Well, I'm not sure if they're
who I think they are yet.
How are you?
Hey, don't ruin meat's reputation!
Thank you very much!
He's not sure-mi-re-do!
I can't hold it any longer!
Resting my bones! Resting my bones!
What?!
Everybody, let's dance together!
Ryu-Ryu-Ryu-Ryu-Ryu-Ryugu Palace!
I'm happy for you, Bone!
Ryugu Palace?
What's going on?
Lava's flowing along to the sea floor!
The temperature is soaring!
Hey, look! They're the
princes of Neptune's army!
Feels like I'm in boiling water!
Why're they here?
What a pain in the ass. What should we do?
I'm gonna be cooked!
Camie! It's been a while!
Let's see how things go.
--Brook!
--Brook-chin!
You've gotten prettier, Camie-chan!
Oh, Luffy-san and Usopp-san!
And it's been a while, Camie-san!
THE RYUGU KINGDOM CORAL HILL
Hmmm. Okay. Thank you very much.
Yeah, long time no see!
I'm glad to see you again!
MADAM SHARLEY'S HOUSE
We'll check somewhere else.
The ghost ship and the Sea Bonze!
Could I look at your panties...
Sorry to bother you when you're having fun.
Good! Your pulse is getting back
to normal. You should be fine now.
Camie is here - that means...
She's a Mermaid!
Straw! Nose!
Let's dance another time!
We landed on the Fishman Island?!
Run, Surume!
I missed you guys!
I didn't know that you were here!
You have to thank those
two for donating blood.
Sorry for the bother-so-fa-mi-re-do!
You can do it!
Yeah, we did!
I've been told that we were
Anytime!
Go faster, Surume, or you're
gonna become boiled octopus!
Long time no see!
drowning but some Mermaids rescued us!
Maybe the border guards
were just seeing things.
Those two...
So you were with Pappagu!
That's right.
It's okay, silly!
They're leaving.
Yes, I didn't expect to be
rescued by Pappagu-san!
As a matter of fact, we just woke up a couple minutes ago too.
If you want, we can give you more, silly!
Boiled octopus? That's
great! I wanna eat some!
This is Camie-chan's house.
I was so lucky!
Here's your hat.
Oh, this is Camie's house.
Yeah, that was just as surprising to me!
Sniff, sniff!
I thank them but I wanna forget about them.
Because of the difference in temperature,
I'm sorry!
Sniff, sniff!
the sea current's starting to swirl!
I'm so glad!
I was gonna pick you guys up
While I was polishing off an
idea for a new design at the cove,
Sniff, sniff!
Nami-san,
It'd be crazy if you died
but I thought it was a month later.
which way is the Fish-Man Island...
I saw some bones drifting
towards me rolling along.
Sniff!
from loss of  blood before
you saw Nami and Robin again!
Don't worry!
--Sanji!
--What is that?!
Even at a time like this?
Where are the others?
Well... it looks like we got separated.
Sanji, you have to focus on your rehab!
Those are bones!
Nami-san...
Keep going straight!
Robin-chan...
Soul King, come to see us again!
I wonder if they're okay.
Oh no! Sanji is in danger!
We're getting close!
Sanji-chan!
Is that so?
I had a wonderful time!
Yeah, I was following them up to some point
That was too much blood! He's in danger!
Hey, come here! Splash! Splatta!
He couldn't hold it! All that
pent-up excitement exploded!
What is it? Do you need our blood again?
but they were taken somewhere else.
Jump into that trench!
I'll be back, beautiful Mermaids!
Well, I'm sure they'll be fine!
Sanji!
What?!
If it's so, just tell us! You can have...
I'm going boneless!
That's...
I think so. The bone can't do much in the sea
No mistaking him.
...As much as you want!
Oh, I can't exist without bones!
What?!
The pirate - Straw Hat Luffy!
but they got the robot and the
green one so they'll be fine!
In there?!
You have to stay calm, silly!
Oh, I don't care if I die now!
Yeah, they'll be fine
Oh no, I'm already dead!
We'll stay here and...
No!
I wanna see the others too.
--Ammo Knights!
--Yes, sir!
...Take care of you!
How cool!
Oh, here! I know you're all freezing.
He got so hyper in the cafe...
No thank you!
Yeah, I wonder what's going on inside.
--Don't be shy!
--Stay calm - it's bad for your health!
I made soup so have some and get warm.
Wait, wait, wait!
Ta-dah! Cold seaweed soup!
You two are the worst for my health!
You aren't leaving today, are you?
You'll love it!
I know you are interested in the cafe
--So shy!
--Stay away!
Be patient, Sanji!
but you can come back with everybody later.
Go away, fools!
Cold soup?
I was gonna take Bone to my house now.
Uh-huh!
Ryu-Ryu-Ryu...
It's a sheer cliff! You've got to be kidding!
You can't get warm with
cold soup! What should I do?!
Ryu-Ryu-Ryu...
Come with me! Do you like sea monster meat?
Ryugu Palace?!
It's darker than dark!
Do you have meat?!
What?!
That's right-jamon!
I made a mistake!
Are you sure that the
Fish-Man Island is in there?!
Damn!
What?!
I'm wild, I don't wanna eat
seaweed or shellfish!
They look all the same!
I can't believe they're invited
to the palace...
Don't worry, Camie-chan!
Doesn't feel like I've advanced even a little!
What I mainly eat is violent sea monsters!
Who are those humans?
It warms me up anyway!
King Neptune came to pick them up himself...
It's hot in the back!
Oh, Pappagu, I almost forget!
Here are your clams for today.
How is that possible?
They know Monsieur Pappagu!
Maybe they're famous...
It's totally dark in the front! Scary!
Hey, Sanji! I want some too!
Yeah! Camie's best clams!
I'm sure there'll be another monster!
--Look, there's Soul King!
--Yeah!
So you eat shellfish!
Your clothes are dry!
I don't think we can make it home alive!
Are you the Pirate Hunter
Zoro from the Straw Hats?
Damn!
--They are dry.
--They aren't dry!
Luffy! The darkness is a bottomless
pot that connects to hell!
What's the Ryugu Palace?
--Maybe they are dry.
--They are dry, so what?
Idiot, don't you know what it is?!
Yeah, so what?
Lovely Mermaid...
Iron pot! Tea caddy! Tea-tea caddy!
I'll tell you.
Yes?
Jump in, Surume!
It's pretty much a holy
place for us citizens.
You dried our clothes! Thanks!
There they are! Straw Hat and the others.
Thank you!
Fantastic Mermaid...
By the way, who are you guys?
A celestial world where
ordinary people are not allowed!
What should we do? They'll catch them first.
Oh, they're my friends.
The Medaka Mermaid Quintuplets.
But we don't wanna cause any
trouble with Neptune's army.
Are you alright?
--I'm Ichika!
--I'm Nika!
--Beautiful! Elegant! Wonderful! Sniff, sniff!
--I wonder how they're doing...
The Ryugu Palace is...
--I'm Sanka!
--I'm Yonka!
...the place where King Neptune,
the Neptune 3 prince brothers,
I'm Yonka Two!
Wait a minute!
Why can't it be Goka?
We're sorry about the illegal entry!
But you can't arrest us now!
Unlike Merfolk, Fish-Men eat meat and fish.
and the Mermaid Princess live - it's...
They swim fast and they're pretty savvy.
Oh, really?
Can somebody donate blood now?!
It's not like we don't have them here.
It's erupting again!
...The royal palace of the Ryugu Kingdom!
We're at the sea floor of the Mermaid Cove.
Oh, glad to hear that!
If nothing is done,
our friend is gonna die within an hour!
Oh...
And this is the girls' dorm for the Mermaid Cafe
Oh, just what I was looking for! Hey, taxi!
Camie, again!
so I have a lot of friends here!
Here I go!
His blood type is S RH negative.
Hmmm... So, old man...
What?
What is that?! Right above us!
G... G... G...
Don't call him that!
It's rare but does anybody here share the same blood type?
What?!
--Rocks?!
--Mud?!
Is there a lot of good
food at the Ryugu Palace?
Or are Fish-Men and Mermaids'
blood totally different?
It's an avalanche of rocks and earth!
Girls' dorm?!
Vander Decken! He's a ghost -
Why are they looking for him?!
Straw!
The eruption caused it!
Of course. We are prepared
to have a banquet-jamon.
Oh no!
Chopper-chin.
Camie-chan!
I think even the Sunny would break apart
We don't have time! Anyone?!
What... what... What is Mermaid Cafe?
Oh, this guy was on the
ghost ship that we saw?
Oh yeah? I can't wait!
if one of those giant rocks hits it!
This is... This is the dumbest way to die!
It's a cafe where I'm working as a waitress.
--What?! Did you guys see him?
--Yes.
Get away, Surume!
Somebody please! I beg you!
I'd like to see the Ryugu Palace!
There are a lot of beautiful Mermaids!
The whole nation has been
looking for him for years!
Give blood to Sanji!
B-Beautiful Mermaids?!
My heart is filled with expectations.
I'm gonna go out and cut them!
He's a pirate--an undersea bandit!
Luffy-chin, Chopper-chin!
But I don't have a heart to be filled!
Luffy! Hold on tightly to my leg!
Do you want a cup of coffee? Or...
I'll tell you about it later. Get on first!
Mermaids and Fish-Men blood
Okay, I got it!
are the same as humans so we can donate blood!
I wanna go too!
Zoro, no!
Ryugu Palace! I sense treasure!
--Sanji is...
--...In danger!
But...
--Hey, let me go!
--Why are you stopping him, Robin?
I knew that'd be what you're interested in!
We're 8,000 meters deep now!
--Dammit!
--He endured!
Okay, let's go!
Those humans are talking nonsense!
If you go out, you'll be crushed
by the water pressure!
Vander Decken was sending love letters...
I...
Hmmm. Alright, Megalo,
I swore that I'd never have
a nosebleed and pass out...
give the Straw Hat
people a ride to the Ryugu Palace-jamon.
Then what should we do?!
...to the Mermaid Princess of the
Ryugu Kingdom at least once a week.
Those guys with sea monsters!
If we can buy some time to
get away from the cliff!
Prince Fukaboshi, that's Hammond
from the Fish-Man District.
...on the Fish-Man Island!
Leave it to me!
Before long, the letters became
packages, then threats to marry him...
Sure Kill; Green Star...
So I should be rewarded by now, shouldn't I...?
There is nobody on this island who would
..."Sargasso"!
Can I get on?
Oh, it's fluffy! Feels good!
give blood to such lowly creatures as humans.
Wow! Cool!
Yeah, it's like heaven!
How desperate...
Are we gonna meet the Mermaid Princess?
Oh yeah, let's go up!
I want you to meet my friends.
Listen to a starfish!
If somebody does,
I can't wait!
--Okay!
--Oh, sorry.
he risks the Punishment of the Dark Night from human haters.
The sea plant popped out!
His eccentric behavior made
the Mermaid Princess afraid
What are you doing? Come with us!
Oh, it's a turtle!
Punishment?
Huh? Well, we don't deserve to
go to the Ryugu Palace... Right?
--It stopped...
--...The avalanche.
He can just keep losing
blood helplessly and die!
and it became a national concern...
It says "Sea Turtle Elevator."
That's so cool, Usopp!
Cool!
Yeah, the Mermaid Princess'
father - King Neptune got mad
Stop grumbling and come!
Let's have a banquet!
Turtle-chin, take us up.
It only holds for a while.
There is this old law in our kingdom.
Now is the chance to get away, Surume!
--You can't say goodbye here!
--Is it okay, grandpa?
and those 3 princes that we just met
Donating blood to humans is prohibited.
have been looking for him with the army
You can't say "grandpa"...
This is a coral apartment in the sea.
but they can't find him.
Your friends can come-jamon.
The dorm is at the very
bottom so the rent is cheap.
What?!
Make no mistake!
You humans set the rule first!
Camie, Camie... I was just
telling them about it...
Hear that? Grandpa,
you're an understanding person!
The top floor gets natural light
so it's the most expensive.
King Neptune, the God of the Sea,
who runs this country...
Like I said, that person is...
You guys... really... please!
Just in time!
You people have a long history
of fearing us as monsters
Are you poor? By the way,
where are Hachi and Pappagu?
...has 4 children including
the Mermaid Princess.
and refused to get your blood mixed-up!
Alright, let's go!
Ha-chin got severely
injured about a year ago.
Usopp, that was great!
The Mermaid Princess is the youngest
and the 3 princes are older than her.
To the Ryugu Palace!
He tried to protect the Sunny at Sabaody.
That's why Fisher Tiger,
the hero of the Fish-Man Island, died.
Yes, it was great judgment!
I heard that he's pretty much recovered now
We made it through!
Hey, Camie...
Fisher... Tiger?
But what I can't understand is
It's not like I was fooling
around for the past 2 years.
but Ha-chin is originally from the Fish-Man District so
He risked his own life to
free slaves of all races
Hurry up, hurry up!
Vander Deck must be a ghostly
pirate from hundreds of years ago...
he's resting there.
Go faster-chin! They'll come any minute!
Let me tell you about it!
It's a very touching story!
but after a bloody war,
Fish-Man District?
It's hard to catch a current in the deep sea!
he lost his life although he could've
survived if he had a transfusion!
Yeah, it's kind of a rough area
The days of the relentless
diet with Master Heracles'n...
but I can take you there since
I feel safe with you guys.
Well, those legends are often exaggerated.
This is why we should've
put paddle wheels on!
Maybe next time.
Those heartless humans
refused to give blood so he died!
Let's go later! I have to
thank him face to face.
Why next time?!
You know, the New World is...
Nami-san is harsh!
He truly existed and in fact,
Okay, I got it! And Pappagu is...
Surume, you did great too!
I heard that the legendary
captain--Vander Decken...
Captain! Look!
Straw Hat, here is what I want you to do.
There's something in front of us!
--We're safe now!
--Thank you, Surume!
...reached the Fish-Man Island and died here.
He's a very famous designer
Just give up on your crewmember's life
Surume! Surume! Hey!
so he has a big mansion in Fishverly
Hills, the high-class district.
That's...
and come to the Fish-Man District with us!
Surume! Hey! Surume! Come on!
The ship that you saw was the
Flying Dutchman, wasn't it?
Hordy Jones!
The captain of the New Fish-Man Pirates
I'm gonna deliver clams
there today so come with me!
N-No way! He found us!
Su...
- Hordy Jones is expecting you guys.
It's his descendent who is on the ship!
He's your pet, right?
Why don't you live with him?
What? He has...
Shut up!
Vander Decken IX!
Hey, I don't know about the law but please!
That area is way beyond my means.
What the...? He has handcuffs on.
Isn't there anyone with S RH negative?!
What?! His descendent?!
We have better clams here, anyway.
No way! He's gonna fight us, isn't he?
Oh, is that so?
I'll do anything to repay you!
We're almost there!
That means he's not a ghost.
Just as long as you save his life now!
I thought that it was a real ghost and felt
What's that straw-like thing?
more dead than alive since I'm a skeleton.
He vanished!
I said "It's no use"!
Oh, that's...
10,000 METERS BELOW SEA LEVEL "THE DEEP"
(THE BOTTOM OF THE OCEANIC TRENCH)
Where did that bastard go?!
...the Water Road that a bubble craftsman made.
That's good. That's just good.
Camie!
Camie... Camie... Camie...
If you don't comply...
We and the fish get in and...
Second Gear!
Here, watch.
When I look closer,
Merfolk and Fish-Men are all different.
...I'll take you by force!
There are old Mermaids! Like Grandma Kokoro!
Oh, that's fast!
Trawl Net!
It's great!
I told you that we weren't gonna join you!
I... I'm alive!
Camie-chan, where are you going?!
Look, there's a baby!
What?! What happened?!
The father is a Fish-Man and the
children are Merfolk and Fish-Men.
...Jet...
Pistol!
Light? This deep in the sea?
We're here, on the surface!
When a Mermaid and a Fish-Man get married,
We've taken damage!
Luffy-chin!
He's too fast!
It's too bright! My eyes are dazzled!
their kids would be either Merfolk
or Fish-Man, either boy or girl.
See? I can even swim in the sky!
But I don't have eyes to be dazzled.
So there are 4 possibilities.
Luffy, a monster behind you!
Oh, looks fun!
Hey guys, come here!
Hmmm, that's why they're all different.
Wait a minute!
Look at that!
Besides that, there's a sky
and clouds in the deep sea!
Interesting!
Alright, let's get on the highway!
I can't see it--it's too bright.
You're right! I wonder how it's possible!
Hey Nami, is that it?
Hammond and the others got...
Yeah, there's no doubt.
The needle is pointing at the island!
Hey, Camie!
The monster gave up without fighting!
He's here on the ship!
It's fast!
Huh? It's a girl's voice!
Take him out! He's the only enemy!
That is...
What's that?
Where is she?
Cool!
That's a candy factory.
Everybody!
What was it? Luffy-chan's unbelievable!
The Fish-Man Island!
No, why is there a pirate flag?!
That's...
Impressive.
That? You can see the same flag at the
Luffy-chin and everybody!
Are your friends fine now?
The pirates who were drowning.
entrance of the island and at the harbor.
That flag is protecting
the Fish-Man Island.
No way! It didn't work!
It's huge!
Bring Sanji-chin, too! Let's go to the town!
You guys didn't come in by the entrance.
The mark belongs to a pirate called
Charlotte Linlin of the New World.
It's in a big bubble! There are
clouds? Maybe there is air inside.
I fought a Fish-Man before!
I've been through hell to get here!
It's the Ryugu!
Also known as Big Mam,
one of The Four Emperors!
Hello! You guys don't look that scary.
There are many humans at the
harbor of the town! Hurry up!
You're only a fish - Don't
mess with humans, you fool!
That's the Fish-Man Island
so we're 10,000 meters deep now!
You guys entered illegally?
So wild! I love pirates!
Th-The Four Emperors?
Okay!
Before the war, Whitebeard was
protecting the island from pirates
How is there such a big
tree this deep in the water?
Captain!
Dammit!
but now it's Big Mam.
Hmmm.
But she demands a lot of sweet
candies every month in exchange.
Alright, we're ready! Camie, let's go!
It's like a living fairy tale!
Uh-huh! Please, Ryugu-chin,
take us to the town!
A land of coral! The Mermaid Cove!
That's what the factory is for.
Yeah! We made it!
Mosu!
Candies?
Hey you, wait! The Ryugu is Princes'...
This country can't exist without the
protection of those powerful people.
Boy, what we got is a hell of a thing-ch!
It's a popular site in the Grand Line!
I'm sorry! I'll bring it back to
you as soon as we save Sanji-chin!
That's how dangerous this place is,
where pirates come and go frequently.
The power drug - Energy Steroid!
They made it there!
They're leaving!
We don't have a ride home-fa-mi-re-do!
Fish-Men were born to be 10
times stronger than humans.
But she's protecting the country
after old man Whitebeard.
The Mermaids dance around
here. The beautiful Mermaids!
Isn't Big Mam a good person?
Hmm.
Sanji is crying!
But once we take one Energy Steroid,
our physical strength will double.
I'm finally here!
It's hard to say.
He's crying harder than
when he left the Baratie.
I'm sorry. If my blood type
matched, I wouldn't refuse.
Whitebeard never demanded anything.
The paradise that I've been
dreaming of since I was a kid!
So Big Mam views it as business, maybe.
20 times stronger than humans.
I found it!
You don't have to apologize.
If we take 2, it'll double that!
Mermaido! Mermaido!
Big Mam...
It all started because of his lecherous feelings.
This is my All Blue!
This dream power will shorten our lives!
One of The Four Emperors like Shanks.
Look. He's still smiling a little.
Wonder if I'll meet her someday.
Mermai...
But we're not afraid of dying
- we just adhere to the plan!
Sanji! You're not ready!
You shouldn't even think about it!
Look forward!
Is it really what you want, Sanji?
...And at the same time, it's nice and bouncy...
We're in Fishverly Hills,
the town of the celebs!
Sanji!
Let me introduce them to you!
Sanji, that's enough!
Don't think about anything!
He's the captain - Luffy-chin.
--Wh-What is he doing?!
--What is he gonna do with the mast?!
That tall building right in
front of us is Pappagu's house.
You're in a delicate state!
Yeah, good to see you!
The crying one is Sanji-chin.
That?! That's too much for a starfish!
Is that why he has those handcuffs!
The one with the nose - Usopp-chin.
You and Hachi were discriminated
against at Sabaody 2 years ago
I'm sorry, Sanji! The rehab didn't work yet!
Nice to meet you!
He wants to show us that he can sink
us without even using his hands!
The racoon is Chopper-chin.
so I guess it really runs deep.
You shouldn't look at real Mermaids.
I'm a reindeer!
I can't believe Sanji's dirty
mind caused such a big issue!
Humans killed Fisher Tiger
and shattered Arlong's dream!
We have to do something!
What's wrong? Why are you crying?
Doctor! It was his dream to see the
Mermaids on the Fish-Man Island!
Yeah, and even if we get to the town,
She's a madam from the Mermaid Cafe.
Come with me! Let's dance in the water!
The dark and tragic history
of the Fish-Men will end now...
I don't know if we can find a donor right away.
But he's gonna die if he sees them!
What's the matter, Madam Sharley?
Why are you so upset?
What?
We haven't had that many
human visitors for a month.
No!
...with the help of us,
the New Fish-Man Pirates!
We have to do something before it's too late!
I don't care...
Oh yeah, I get it now. This is too good to be true.
Sanji!
You guys are our first visitors in a while.
Hey, Madam! What's wrong?
Rather than live longer without a dream,
Why? I thought this was the famous scoop.
I'm probably gonna die today!
Look for him!
I wanna die staring at the
Mermaids in a disgusting way!
Yes, it is a famous spot.
The pirate boy with a straw hat!
How negative!
We don't know why.
Seriously, what happened to you in the past 2 years?
You're scum!
They say maybe somebody
is standing in the voyagers' way.
I'm gonna look at the Mermaids!
And throw him out of this country!
This is the paradise that
you've been dreaming of!
Take them to the New World
and set them adrift.
Somebody powerful is up to something
- that's the talk of the Kingdom.
Is it a pre-vision again?
--He's burning!
--The flame of his eroticism!
You're so funny, Sanji!
I wasn't planning on using it.
No, he's not trying to be funny!
But I felt something about him
I can't wait! I wonder what
kind of meat is in their dishes!
Oh no! You didn't kill all of them, did you?
That was no good, ladies.
so I couldn't help looking into the future!
Why were you hiding the pirates?
Luffy, wipe your drool.
Can you give an order to Surume?
No, I need them alive.
What's wrong?! What did you see?!
I'm sorry, Prince Fukaboshi.
Let's look for the entrance.
You humans, survive with cuts and
bruises to show the people on earth...
Madam!
They were Camie's friends.
Hey, what are they?!
Sharley! Say it!
THE FISH-MAN DISTRICT "NOAH"
And they were good people and we
didn't want them to be arrested.
--Madam!
...what happened to you in the sea.
I hope it won't happen!
I hope it'll be proven wrong!
And who you met.
Who are they?
I hope Sanji-chan will be fine.
You ladies mistook us.
He's a well-known pirate,
Tell them how horrendous it was.
he didn't need to go through immigration.
We'll capture the center of
the world, the Fish-Man Island,
The group of sea monsters!
from the gutless God of the Sea - Neptune
Because we know his identity.
I see.
We're dead! After we got all the way here!
We were looking for them for
another reason-re-mi-fa!
Straw Hat Luffy finally got this far.
and drag you humans down
to the dark sea bottom!
A human with a straw hat on...
Oh, is it so?
Yes.
You'll all learn that the
Fish-Men are the supreme race!
They're so cool! The sea monsters!
What should we do, Boss?
At Straw Hat Luffy's
hands...  at his hands...
And we were unable to deliver
the message from Jimbei, as well.
Bring him...
the Fish-Man Island will be...
...here!
Somebody's riding it!
...destroyed!!
Fish-Man Island shines with beauty.
Sanji's overexcitement has put him in danger.
At the king of Fish-Man Island, Neptune's invitation,
Luffy and his crew make their to a banquet at the Ryugu Palace.
At Mermaid Cove Sanji reverts to his
old self and fools around with the mermaids.
Mysterious Fish-Men block their
entry to the Fish-Man Island.
But history has created a darkness
Luffy and his crew follow Camie to the Mermaid Cafe
in search of a blood donor to save his life.
They mention Arlong,
whom the Straw Hats had defeated,
However, Luffy's hunger gets the better of him and as soon as he smells food,
Hating humans, they desire retribution.
But then the three Princes
of Fish-Man Island arrive.
and call themselves the New Fish-Men Pirates.
There, they meet a gifted psychic, Madam Sharley,
Their plans are mobilizing beneath the surface.
he separates from the group.
Not knowing what to expect, they hide,
To evade the menacing sea beasts,
Meanwhile, Luffy and his crew run amok at Pappagu's shop,
and she predicts a terrible future for Luffy's crew!
Luffy then and discovers a gigantic tower locked with a door stuck with swords and axes!
and the king of Fish-Man Island, Neptune himself descends from his palace.
Luffy and Co. decide to force
their way onto Fish-Man Island.
though then an unimaginable accident occurs.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Landing at the Fish-Man Island!
Beautiful Mermaids!"
"The King of the Fish-Man Island!
Neptune, the God of the Sea!"
"The Ryugu Palace! Taken by
the Shark that They Saved!"
"The Fish-Man Island Will Be Annihilated?!
Sharley's Prophecy!"
"Excitement Blow-out!
Sanji's Life Under Threat!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!