Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he
ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew returned
to Sabaody Archipelago.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training.
And on their way to the
next stage - the New World,
And on their way to the New World,
they reached the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
and his friends venture into that sea.
they reached the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
I'm going to invite you to
the Ryugu Palace-jamon!
But they have yet to gather and are
stirring things up as a fragmented crew!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Go, Shark!
"Hordy's Onslaught! The Retaliatory
Plan Set Into Motion!"
"The Ryugu Palace! Taken by
the Shark that They Saved!"
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training.
Luffy and his crew returned
to Sabaody Archipelago.
And on their way to the
next stage - the New World,
To the Sea Forest!
And on their way to the
next stage - the New World,
they reached the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
located 10,000 meters below sea level,
"The Ryugu Palace in Shock!
The Kidnapping of Shirahoshi!"
However, there they found the New Fish-Man
Pirates disturbing the peace and order.
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom
Look at that, Luffy-sama!
SOUTHEAST OF THE FISH-MAN ISLAND
IN THE DEEP SEA
That cloud looks like an animal called a
"racoon" that I've seen before in a book!
along with Vander Decken who is after
A FEW HOURS AGO
the Mermaid Princess are
engaging in secret maneuvers.
A few hours before...
Thank you for coming all the way to see me!
...Luffy and the others met King Neptune...
Nice to meet you, Hordy Jones!
Ah, that looks like Chopper!
Well, Tom-san told me that one of his family
members at home is also a shipwright, so...
THE RYUGU KINGDOM MERMAID COVE
At the Mermaid Cove in the Ryugu Kingdom...
What's wrong with you?
The Straw Hats find themselves caught
up in the turmoil little by little...
Chopper?
Somebody sealed this very tightly!
Uh-huh! Chopper is my friend!
Who are you, sir?!
But it must've been difficult
to come to the Fish-Man Island.
Friend?
Difficult?
--I wonder what's inside.
--Let me guess...
Isn't there anywhere you wanna go?
Something is flying...
I was trained by Tom-san since I was a kid
and I came here with a ship that I made.
What?! It was a big
person... I mean, Mermaid!
Huh?
If the barrel is so important to them,
I can't see clearly, it's too far.
Of course, there are a lot
of places that I want to go...
Since you were my brother's pupil,
I bet it's quite a ship.
like a treasure chest, it must be
high-quality liquor or something.
Luffy-sama, what's wrong?
That's what I thought.
Then let's get out of here!
THE RYUGU KINGDOM
THE PORT TOWN--CORAL HILL
Somebody! Father-sama! Brother-sama!
It's really tight!
Yeah, it's called the Thousand
Sunny and it's my masterpiece!
Mom, what is that?!
Wait! That's enough!
If something's thrown at
you again, I'll deflect it!
Whoa, whoa! I didn't do
anything to you, did I?!
I would love to see it.
You loosened it up pretty
well and that's enough for me!
Well, after we entered the Fish-Man Island,
it was taken away by the tide.
He's formidable!
Oh, damn! What's with you?!
That's part of reason that I came to see you.
Take this!
Hey, look at that!
What? There's someone inside?
I was wondering if you could give
me a clue as to Sunny's whereabouts.
What is it?
"A Coward and a Crybaby!
The Princess in the Hard Shell Tower!"
No way!
Zoro!
I thought you'd been captured!
You'll find it.
Ryugu Palace! Ryugu Palace! Come in!
THE MAIN ENTRANCE
BORDER CONTROL HEADQUARTERS
I heard the sound of this
festival so I let myself out!
I hope so...
Ryugu Palace! This is Border Control!
When a ship sinks in these parts,
it usually gets carried by the tide
"It's an Emergency!
The Ryugu Place Is Occupied!"
Hello? Hello?
and ends up at a certain place.
Hey!
I think the Sunny will be there too.
Count on me, completely!
--That's weird.
--Clank.
Keep lighting up!
Why can't we reach them?
Is the Transponder Snail sick?
How many times do I have to tell you?
A CREW MEMBER OF THE FLYING PIRATES
WADATSUMI, THE GREAT MONK
Completely, huh?
We'll get there soon.
The place known as the Sea Forest!
Thank you!
It's not time for playing!
What the...
Why are they coming in flocks
to the Fish-Man Island?
I appreciate your help, Mermaids!
A snack!
The Sea Forest?
How did he get out of jail?!
I have no idea.
Wadatsumi!
I know those dangerous people
from the Fish-Man District
Hey hey, Luffy-san!
Don't try to get away!
Hey wait, Megalo! Where are you going?!
don't just come here for the shopping.
Get to the water now!
Didn't you get a reply yet?
A reply from Princess Shirahoshi?
What a fighter!
He warded off the God of the Sea -
King Neptune's attack easily!
Father-sama, Brother-sama,
everybody at the palace, please forgive me!
No, not yet, Captain Decken.
It's too late!
If you resist, we'll have
casualties on both sides.
I am going out without permission!
How long have I been waiting for it?
Surrender with good grace-jamon, Zori!
I'm sinking!
For 10 years or so. And it hasn't come yet.
It's Zoro!
You guys! Rupture the
bubbles around them at once!
It's a swamp! On rocky ground?!
I'll be home by dinner!
It's a muddy swamp that you can't escape!
Minister of the Right!
It's better for us to
fight them in the water.
It's all because of that hateful Neptune!
Let's go for a "walk"!
Listen, guys!
It's a bottomless swamp!
Today will be remembered as the day
Hurry up!
I'm a Devil Fruit eater!
What is going on, Megalo?!
He wants to plunge Princess
Shirahoshi into a political marriage!
that everyone on the Fish-Man
Island united under one flag!
I ate the Swamp-Swamp Fruit
and became a swamp man!
I can't believe he left the doors open!
All Fish-Men, including the Merfolk,
have to be like-minded!
I suspect!
The more you struggle...
What if something happens to...
Ah, we've been driven to the wall.
In fact, the Princess has been locked
up in the steel tower for 10 years!
Skeleton, hurry up!
See if the Princess is okay!
No!
You're right. This is no good. Hey, Nami!
...The more you sink!
We must dominate the humans
Hey! You're riding my bones too hard!
Help!
Oh? Nami?
Stop calling for help!
I'm not gonna kill you!
Oh, how painful this is!
since they're such lowly creatures
who can't even breathe in the water!
Wh-What the...
Because we love each other!
Somebody...
I said "Stop," didn't I? You fool!
She's not here!
Princess Shirahoshi is not here!
I suspect!
THE CAPTAIN OF THE FLYING PIRATES
VANDER DECKEN IX
What?! The Mermaid Princess is not here?!
Let's correct the mistakes of history now!
Ishilly!
Princess Shirahoshi! I love you!
I just want you to sleep for a while!
What?! All the water is gone?!
This is bad! This is a matter of
great consequence to the kingdom!
When did this happen?! Who did this?!
She must have been kidnapped!
I love you! I love you!
Sorry!
Today will be the anniversary
of our engagement, Shirahoshi!
I love you!
I just found a Bubbly Coral, this big.
Kidnapped?!
Princess-sama!
No matter how much I roam this vast seafloor,
Wow, that's big!
No need to hurry. Let's get married tomorrow!
Now...
Princess-sama...
I can't find someone who is as
big and beautiful as you are!
She must've been kidnapped?
let's continue where we left off.
That annoying faction from the Sun Pirates
- Jimbei's group--is not here-dosun!
It's fine if we end up together.
Hey, what are you doing?!
Wait, wait. I'll fight him-jamon.
My body is bottomless!
But I can't allow you to
live with somebody else!
Neptune, the God of the Sea, and the
brothers; Fukaboshi, Ryuboshi, Manboshi!
No! Don't bother, Neptune-sama!
The gate that connects the Fish-Man
Island and the Ryugu Palace...
Now how much were Mermaids going for?
I'd rather see you dead than
with someone else, Shirahoshi!
No, that man is strong.
Where is the switch to open it?!
Much! If we can bring those 4 under control,
Neptune's army can't stand against us-ch!
If I remember right,
70 million each at auction.
And I don't want anyone else
to get hurt anymore-jamon!
Huh? The switch?
Skeleton, hurry and go back to Neptune-sama!
Your life is either dead or marriage!
I got 3 of them so that'll be...
Let's bite all the soldiers' flesh off!
We have to tell him what is going on here!
Let me present you with an ax with a
rose painted on it just as always!
I have to thank the Straw Hats!
I'll just cut them--whatever
you tell me to do.
We have no choice but to do as we're told.
Because of them, I made it
into the Fish-Man Island
Accept it, Shirahoshi!
As proof of our marriage!
without going through immigration!
They told us the only way
we'll live is if we obey them.
Let's begin.
Go ahead and begin conquering
major towns on your own!
I can hunt these valuable
Mermaids as much as I want!
Well, hurry up and get ready!
This is a treasure island for me!
The Ryugu Kingdom falls today!
Captain? It's way off the target.
Just tell us!
Let's go out, right now!
Who are "they"?
Don't be silly! I don't miss!
And then we will dominate the sea floor!
They're gonna kill us if you don't tell us!
Huh? R-R-Right now?
Ishilly!
Kill you?
B-But I... I mean, I still...
Tell us!
Ishilly!
I suspect.
I'm sure I heard them around here!
I don't know what you're talking about!
It's coming back!
Still what?
A FEW HOURS AGO THE FISH-MAN DISTRICT "NOAH"
It's heading towards the Ryugu Palace!
Ishilly...
I-It's too sudden so I still... Um...
AT THE PRESENT TIME
And now,
at Coral Hill, the port
town in the Ryugu Kingdom...
THE RYUGU KINGDOM
THE PORT TOWN--CORAL HILL
THE ROYAL PALACE OF THE RYUGU KINGDOM
THE RYUGU PALACE
I can't sort my feelings out.
Could you give me a little more time?
Just in time.
What a pain in the ass!
The Straw Hat Pirates?!
Humans are such lowly creatures -
they can't even breathe in the water!
They kidnapped girls from the Mermaid Cove?
Hey, hey, whoa! What's going on?
The Sea Forest...
I wonder what this place is like.
It's just a walk, it's not a big deal.
I'm just a pirate who came
here looking for food!
No, that's not what I meant.
They were all pretty nice.
There's no mistaking her!
Nico Robin of the Straw Hats!
Boy. Don't take too long.
Listen to me!
I don't like you after all.
First of all, they're Camie's friends.
Hey!
Listen, you pirates under
the control of Hordy Jones!
She's loud! What should I do?
Maybe they made a threat against her.
No!
Woman! You and your friends are
suspects in 2 ongoing investigations!
Alright, alright.
I'll wait so just make up your mind.
In fact, at the place at the moment,
Princess Shirahoshi-sama's crying!
You should all be happy! Because you
can be part of this historic mission!
there were only us guards, the Mermaid girls,
--It's from the Hard Shell Tower!
--What are the tower guards doing?!
First, for multiple counts of
Mermaid kidnapping! Second,
the guys from the Fish-Man
District who were beaten,
What?! Why is nobody with her?!
That's Vander Decken
of the Flying Dutchman?!
I'm sorry! The guard shifts were changing!
and the Straw Hats.
you people are suspected of being
What have you guys done?!
The captain of the cursed ghost ship?!
a potential risk to the Fish-Man Island
based on Madam Sharley's prevision!
And now they're gone so who
knows what they're doing.
In any case, get to the tower now!
No matter how I look at it, this is overkill!
A human is... here in the
room... trying to kill me!
Humans have a good reason
to kidnap Mermaids.
Don't worry, I'm his descendant.
I'm not a ghost.
He's right! You should regret your actions!
So we're taking all of the
Straw Hats into custody!
You guys started this fight!
So you're my accomplices, you idiots!
Young Mermaid girls have been
traded at high prices in their world.
Though I am cursed as well. I can't
swim even though I'm a Fish-Man.
Huh? No! Hey! That's not true!
I don't know what you're talking about.
And did you say "prevision"?
We were gonna just intimidate them and run!
But you can't suspect them blindly...
I got this devil power alongside
of the Mark-Mark curse.
I was hungry and I didn't
know that the food was yours!
Don't you know that there
were a lot of pirates
I was just enjoying
sightseeing and shopping.
You people need to get your brains checked...
who got close to Mermaids...
Let me show it to you!
...if you unashamedly believe
in such unscientific things.
...pretending they were
nice only to kidnap them?
What's done is done! Stop complaining!
Alright, you human right there! Step forward.
Madam Sharley's previsions
are accurate! Come with us!
Hmmm...
"What's done is done"?!
Prince Fukaboshi!
Huh?
And Madam Sharley, did you really see the
Stopping by the Fish-Man Island
Hordy!
No thank you. I don't want to miss my bus.
and occupying the palace accidentally
- what are we? Some kind of evil pirates?!
future that you mentioned a while ago?
Ow, ow, ow...
Get her!
Then we should've allowed
ourselves to be beaten?
That the pirate - Straw Hat Luffy
I told you "Let's wait for a
chance and run" many times!
Are you guys serious? Don't be crazy!
will destroy the Fish-Man Island?!
Mil Fleurs!
I don't know the way out
and Luffy is missing!
--It's Hachi-san!
--Hatchan-san!
Madam Sharley, drink some water.
That's right. Luffy is missing!
--It's Hachi-san!
--It's Hatchan-san!
What's that ax?! Where did it come from?!
Where did he go?
Dunno.
Hachi-san...
The Energy Steroids will
do nothing but ruin you!
We really have to go so
don't be mean and tell me!
Yes, I saw the future.
THE MAIN ENTRANCE OF THE RYUGU PALACE
Yeah, where is Luffy...
What's the point of destroying the island?
Oh, boy!
W-We have to report... She... got... away...
It's true that I saw it.
When can we have a banquet?
How long do we have to wait?
Where is the treasure chamber?
Even the people at the Ryugu Palace like us
Don't underestimate the
Great Knight Neptune!
No!
My stomach is growling...
know how accurate your previsions are.
What? Why?
Hachi-san, give me a break.
But I don't have a stomach to growl!
Stop pretending you're naive! Be sensible!
SEA FOREST
It's no good.
I don't want to hear your voice anymore.
I was going to treat them nicely
since they saved my sister's pet, but...
Hey, everybody! When you're
sad, let's sing and be happy!
I can't believe you were an officer
of the pirate group that I admired.
--Hey!
--Yes?
It doesn't look like we're
having a banquet any time soon!
They had information as I thought.
There is a Poneglyph somewhere here.
Come on!
You became a coward.
It's time for a generation change.
Although everything remains uncertain,
It's gonna be alright! It's gonna be alright!
Does this mean that we've
landed ourselves in trouble?
we can't let them be at large!
I think this kingdom holds the
important key to the 100-Year Void!
If it's not,
-- you're gonna die someday anyway, yeah!
We have no choice but to
take them into custody!
What should we do?!
To teach humans a lesson,
we need the Fish-Man Island
I'm sorry that you came all the way
here but we've just received a call!
Shut up already, Soul King!
THE RYUGU PALACE
AROUND THE SAME TIME
Around the same time,
THE RYUGU KINGDOM
THE HIGH-CLASS DISTRICT--FISHVERLY HILLS
Neptune-sama, are you alright?
at the high-class district
of the Ryugu Kingdom -
so Neptune is in our way!
You Straw Hat people, you are suspects
in 2 ongoing investigations.
Fishverly Hills...
I can't believe that this is happening to
King Neptune, the Great Knight of the Sea!
You all taught us that
we're the supreme race!
They're gone.
So who were they after all?
S-Suspects?! What do you mean?!
But Arlong-san lost!
I can't fight when I've thrown out my back...
King Neptune came to pick them up himself
First, for multiple counts
of Mermaid kidnapping!
Decken! Hyouzou! Why are you doing this?!
and invited them to the Ryugu Palace.
We didn't do such...
You even refused
Arlong-san's offer back then
Second, you people are suspected
of being a potential risk...
--What's wrong with these guys?
--One after another...
I-I got old...
Don't fall.
so why are you helping these youths now?!
Neptune!
...to the Fish-Man Island due to
Madam Sharley's prevision!
It's my fault-jamon. I'm sorry.
Why do we always get involved in trouble?
Helping? I'm just in this for the money.
Whale!
Huh? Prevision? You don't know
if that'll happen for real!
We should've broken their bubbles and
made them fight in the water earlier.
Stop whining, Nami! The battle is on already!
Shark! Shark!
Jamon! Jamon!
Arlong was stingy so he couldn't pay me much.
--Shut up!
--What's wrong with them?!
I can't believe we let
them drain all the water...
Jamon! Jamon!
They keep attacking us so we have no choice.
Can't take it!
Is this the right thing to do?
Jamon! Jamon!
I felt sorry for him that he could only
take crappy swordsmen like you with him.
Hey, you bastards!
Therefore, we're here to
take you people into custody!
Shut up, Zoro! We don't wanna get ourselves
into more trouble than we already have!
Neptune!
When the 3 formidable princes
of Neptune's army - Fukaboshi,
Ryuboshi, Manboshi come back,
Catch them at any cost!
We have to protect the Fish-Man Island!
What's wrong with pirates
fighting pirates? There's no crime.
Hachi from the Arlong Pirates?
Oh, sweet memories!
you won't get away with this!
Yeah!
Your captain even tried to make
me work under him at that time.
Boy, he never learns!
Go!
Yeah!
Princess Shirahoshi-sama!
Guys, you're barely clinging to life
- why do you wanna fight so badly?
In any case, we can't
stay here on this island.
That was ridiculous!
I won't work under anybody!
Somebody's coming!
Where's the Sunny? Let's bring
everybody together and sail out soon.
Let's settle this peacefully...
I'm sorry to do this!
Do you think they'll give up that easily?
Hordy understands that.
But the coating on the Sunny came
off when we entered this island.
--Are you alright?
--Did you get hurt?
What is that chant, old
man? It sounds so dumb!
N-No!
Arlong-san had a dream and an ability
to take action that I could respect.
You were crying louder
than usual - we were worried!
The Log Pose hasn't been
working right for a while too.
No, that's rude! Straw, you bastard!
Terrifying! You're terrifying!
The switch for the gateway...
What are you...?!
It has been unstable since we got here.
Who opened this door?!
I can't take it! That Pose is not good
enough to sail across the New World.
Was it an intruder?
If we can't open it, they'll kill us!
But at the same time, he was too
rough and lacked cleverness.
I-I'm sorry to make you worry!
That shark--Megalo is a pet that
my daughter loves so much-jamon!
Kill them!
I think I had a bad dream...
You ignorant pirates!
Kill them!
When you guys were running wild on the sea,
we were all too young to become pirates.
Kill them!
What? This is not good
enough? What do you mean?
Hey...!
--No, I heard somebody for sure!
--No, that's... Um... Well...
She kept crying hysterically
saying "Megalo is not coming back."
I'll tell you if you untie me.
Let me do it too!
We all witnessed what they did
so we plan things more carefully.
My stomach made a noise!
I wasn't aware he was attacked by the Kraken.
Kill them!
A-Are you sure?
Thank you for saving him from danger-jamon!
Who is it?!
Because we've learned from
our predecessors' failure.
You little...!
Megalo! Welcome home!
I will continue where Arlong left off.
We didn't mean to but I'm
glad that you're okay!
Ding dong!
Oh yes! There is something
that I have to tell you.
As a member of the group I admired so much,
They leave me no choice.
It must be Prince Fukaboshi!
So he's the Mermaid Princess' pet?!
Ding dong!
Oh, Pappagu-san? If I'm correct,
It's about Straw Hat Luffy,
the pirate who saved Megalo.
Ding dong!
your opposition is so
discouraging, Hachi-san!
you said you're the best friend
of the Mermaid Princess.
Straw Hat Luffy who shattered
Arlong's dream is here, by the way.
Shh! Shh!
This is weird. What are the guards doing?
Die!
Oh, so that was a lie!
He is suspected in the kidnapping
of some missing Mermaid girls.
Why don't they get it?
Clank.
Anyway, I feel sorry for Sanji-san!
Outta my way!
Hello? Who is it?
Oops!
And due to Madam Sharley's prediction,
But you don't mind at all?
Don't pick it up!
He wanted to see the Mermaid
Princess more than anybody!
He called me his friend even though I'm
a former member of the Arlong Pirates.
all of the Straw Hats are considered
as an uncertain but potential risk
--Prince Fukaboshi!
--Help us!
I wonder what that was.
Shut up, you guys!
so we've decided to lock
them in the palace prison.
I guess he was just born to be unlucky.
All three of you are my friends now!
--Prince Ryuboshi!
--Prince Manboshi!
Luffy-sama.
Why are you so strong?
We took the swordsman who
came to the palace first
Plus, Straw Hat Luffy saved my life.
I wish I could go see him now but...
I think, Brother,
something is going on-la-ti-do!
But a princess who has a
shark as a pet must be...
into custody while he was
sleeping due to intoxication.
I've been training myself since I was a kid.
I agree! Are Father and Shirahoshi alright?
But there were people stronger than me.
I-Is it okay...
I'm too ashamed to face him when somebody
is trying to keep Arlong's dream alive!
It's me, Fukaboshi. What
is going on in there?
The 3 members who just arrived are
probably in custody by now, too.
Oh, there are people even stronger than you?
...for us to go to the Ryugu Palace?
Lower the gate now and let us in.
He said "Your friends can
come-jamon" so it should be okay.
How pathetic of you to
become friends with a human!
What's wrong, Shark? You don't feel well?
But their captain--Straw Hat, who was with
them, might have noticed our intentions
Normally you're not allowed, right?
I'm disgusted by you!
Megalo?
And then what?
Do you have a stomach ache, Shark?
Then, why don't you just enjoy it?
and ran away.
I can't do that.
Hey! What are you saying?!
Just be honest and tell him!
Lock on to you, Hachi!
He is probably hiding somewhere
in the palace so please be careful.
I sent out my sons first but
they haven't come back.
Yeah guys, tie me and Camie up too!
They'll think we're your accomplices.
That was close! Be careful, Shark!
You forgot how pirates do things?
We'll catch the rest of them on the island
If there is something to say,
you have to use violence!
That's why I came.
Zoro-chin's scary!
and defend the country at any cost.
Because I can't wait to see the food at the
--Help us!
--Prince Fukaboshi!
Don't accuse me of cutting
them just because I like it!
banquet so I want to start already-jamon!
I suspect!
But you looked like you were enjoying it.
You're a natural born manslayer!
--I just heard something.
--Did you? Isn't it just your imagination?
I can't wait, either!
Here!
Where is he throwing it?
Hey, you two, quit drooling!
When I touched you just now,
you became my mark.
--No, I'm sure I...
--No, it's just your imagination!
Well then, if you were attacked by pirates,
what would you do? Serve tea?!
Oh, I almost forget. I already
invited one of your friends.
Okay. Anyway,
Are you a member of the Straw Hats?
No matter what I throw or where I
throw it, it's like a living bird,
I feel bad that we have to arrest the
people who saved Megalo's life!
Fukaboshi! That's the Three-Sword
Style swordsman of the Straw Hats -
Well, serving tea and
talking is one way to solve...
He is a swordsman.
He started drinking on his
own before the banquet.
They wouldn't let you!
"Pirate Hunter" Zori!
it will strike you at full speed!
Princess-sama,
you're acting strangely. Are you hiding...
It's more fun to have a banquet
with everybody - he is so selfish.
--It's Zoro!
--Father!
In any case, if you beat them all,
You have Father too!
you won't be able to find
out what they wanted!
Minister of the Right, we have to go.
Like you just heard, we have
Neptune and many other hostages.
--The knife he just threw somewhere else...
--...Flew at the octopus Fish-Man!
I think his name was...
Oh, it's been 5 minutes already.
We're gonna go now.
Is it Zoro?
Stop worrying so much about them.
Must be Zoro...
If you don't want me to kill them,
prepare for us to set sail!
Zori!
Mark-Mark curse...
Something is wrong with this picture...
It's Zoro!
Of course, there are a number
of ways to defend yourself.
Why do most of our crewmembers
tend to act like this?
We need our ship - Sunny,
with a fresh coating on.
My soldiers will find the rest of your
friends and bring them to the palace
Give it a try.
Lock the doors tightly!
--Well, look at our captain.
--Yeah, there's no point in even questioning it.
We don't know where it is
so go find it on your own.
No... You have so many arrows.
so don't worry-jamon.
I knew about your power - I heard the rumors!
And we need the rest of our crew - a gloomy
woman, a robot, a racoon, and a dirty water imp.
Nami, don't you know where they went?
Hey, Hordy, he's trying to kill me!
Thank you very much!
I wonder if Luffy-san has met the Mermaid
Princess already. I wanna see her too!
Stop Decken!
I was being very rude to you
before. Please forgive me!
As he told you, Hachi-san.
Vander Decken is not working under me.
And Zoro, one billion berries in cash.
Looks like a good place to shop!
More importantly, untie me!
Give me back Shirahoshi-jamon!
No, you stop!
There are so many people here.
I didn't know that you were the
one who saved Megalo's life.
"Dirty water imp"... That's funny!
Can't stop laughing!
Maybe it won't take that much
to get some information.
We are allies on equal footing.
Why do you think that we want to
kidnap the Mermaid Princess?!
Stop laughing, you fool!
About Luffy and the others?
And you're annoying me anyway!
May I call you Luffy-sama?
--"Dirty water imp"...
--What about "gloomy woman"...
That, too.
But what I wanna know
the most is the whereabouts of...
I know Straw Hat Luffy did
it-jamon! Shirahoshi!
Uh-huh.
Luffy-sama, you are a pirate does
that mean you are a bad person?
I understand your conditions.
Coward!
...my shipwright master -
Tom-san's relatives.
I'll make an arrangement for you
to leave this country immediately
Damn!
I saw Luffy-san and Shark-san
coming out of the room for sure,
Alright, get him!
This is where he came from.
with all of your friends.
I don't know. You decide.
However,
but I didn't see the Mermaid
Princess with them.
I want all the hostages back alive!
If his family is here, I have
to tell them the way he lived.
Okay.
But she is not the kind of girl who
just sneaks out on her own-jamon.
That's it! Run, run!
Oh, they said that our soldiers
took your friends into custody...
That's fine.
Brother!
But they will chase you, chase you,
We just got back together
but let me do this on my own.
Shirahoshi is as big as myself-jamon.
Someone will notice her if she gets out.
We have no choice.
Yeah but that's fine. You guys can't
keep them under control anyway.
This gateway is the only way to
enter the Ryugu Palace even for us.
chase you and chase you
to the end of the world!
It doesn't seem like
there is any stopping you.
What?! The Mermaid Princess is big?!
Is that so?
I wanna check on something too.
It's impossible to break in elsewhere
Don't worry about it.
Now tell me, what was that ax?
I'm a princess-jamon!
You too, Robin?
If I can get out of here...!
since it's covered with
several layers of bubbles.
There are a lot of ancient
traditions on the Fish-Man Island.
No way...
Who threw it? From where?
Oh yeah-jamon! Maybe, he hid Shirahoshi
in Megalo's mouth and took her out!
There is one more thing, Zoro-kun?
So there must be some
important pieces of history
Yes, now I can get away!
In the water, arrows will...
I know who did it...
I wouldn't normally tell you
this under the circumstances
that haven't been revealed yet.
Important pieces of history...?
but I can't ignore my duty to Jimbei.
Damn! They aren't even slowing down!
His name is Vander Decken-sama.
What is it?
Stop making us laugh under
these circumstances, King.
So we got separated again.
He holds a grudge against
me for refusing to marry him.
Stop following me!
This is from the former Warlord - "First
Son of the Sea" Jimbei to Straw Hat Luffy.
You didn't have any problem either, did you?
Who would do such a thing?
Even if he had the idea...
No... Well, there was a little one.
That gentleman has a Devil's
power called Mark-Mark.
He left 2 messages for me to
give you when you arrived.
Hey, by the way, grandpa...
Jimbei...
He can strike me anytime or
anywhere with a thrown weapon
Call him "God of the Sea - Neptune-sama"!
--Jimbei...
--Boss Jimbei...
My nose is itching too.
Jimbei?!
since he designated me as his mark.
Luffy said that he became
friends with Jimbei!
Luffy-sama, did you catch cold?
This place is at 10,000
meters below sea level
Ah, he was in the newspaper with Luffy-san.
I don't often catch cold.
I wonder what it is.
so why is there light around this island?
Although he's a pirate, he's a big
figure that people on the island trust.
The island itself doesn't
provide any light.
That's why it's too dangerous for
me to leave this Hard Shell Tower...
This is the only place in the deep sea
Luffy is not here but I'll
tell him later. Go ahead.
that has light so Fish-Men started
living here a long time ago.
And that was the beginning
of the Fish-Man Island.
I'm hungry!
Shirahoshi!
First, he says to not fight against Hordy.
I can have two marks - one for each palm!
There are the roots of a giant
tree called the Sun Tree Eve...
In any event, our captain wouldn't kidnap anybody!
You better look for somebody else!
Second, he'll be waiting at the Sea Forest.
...that transfers sunlight from
the surface to the deep sea.
I haven't washed my right hand for 10 years
No, I can't think of anybody else!
If Shirahoshi doesn't come back safely,
Transfers sunlight?
ever since I touched Princess
Shirahoshi and designated her as my mark!
That's all.
You mean there is a tree with
shining roots more than 10,000 meters long?
you can't have your ship
or friends back-jamon!
Yum-yum! Can I eat this?
Yes, indeed.
Do you understand? It doesn't matter
if it's love or a weapon that I throw,
Scientists try to make some senses out of it
Go ahead.
No! You can't do that to us!
Clank.
but it's a mystical tree that transfers
sunlight to its roots-jamon.
they'll both follow
until the furthest hell!
Yummy!
This is my power!
The Sea Forest?
And its respiration supplies
air to the sea floor as well.
He wants to marry you but
he's trying to kill you?
Awesome!
Hordy?
That's why he could continue
stalking her insidiously...
I... I did it!
It's like the boss of the Hustle
Muscle Mangrove at Sabaody?
It doesn't make sense, does it?
...without showing himself or
getting caught by Neptune's army!
It's been 10 years already.
Hairy old man, I'm hungry!
For 10 years?! You must be bored!
That's right!
Looks like those human
pirates pulled it off.
What a sinister guy!
You!
Sinister! Sinister! Sinister!
On top of that, my father made a rule that
soldiers can't stay here more than 5 minutes.
We'll be there soon!
Now you human pirates.
Now that you've seen Decken's power.
And that's what happened.
It's huge!
So I want you to find the Straw Hats' ship
and the rest of them as soon as possible.
Hmmm.
Here is the first stage of the mission.
That's why Megalo is the
only one that I can talk to.
That's the entrance-jamon.
Sunny, are you alright?! You're a super
miracle ship just as I thought!
Roger that.
He's my dear friend.
They say the Ryugu Palace
is impregnable but...
Roger that.
That's why they wanted
to have a banquet for us.
Hey hey, did you hear that?
The Straw Hat Pirates did it!
This place is like a graveyard of ships.
...someone has been able to pierce
the defenses for 10 years
It must be canceled now.
The tide brings sunken ships here.
They took over the Ryugu Palace!
I wonder why they want to put
Megalo's liberators in prison.
and that's him - Vander Decken.
What do they want?!
Isn't it ironic?
Although that's what this place is,
it receives the blessings of the Sun Tree Eve -
No way! They looked like really good people
- I can't believe they did such a thing!
I heard that Madam Sharley-sama's
previsions are unbelievably accurate.
So for this mission,
you'll be thrown by Decken
--Yes?
--It's me-jamon.
corals have grown beautifully
drawing fish and whales here.
I-It must be K-King-sama!
I'll put down the gateway now!
I can't believe it!
--Can't believe it!
--Yes, I can believe it.
That's amazing! There are a lot of whales
and they are so much bigger than the Sunny.
That explains why everyone's afraid, but...
--Maybe I can't either.
--I can't believe it, so what?
and fly to the Mermaid
Princess in the palace.
Oh yeah, take this.
I'm sure they're the ones who kidnapped
the Mermaids and the prediction is true!
What?!
Where you'll be landing is the
solid wall of the tower though.
Anyway, you humans eat a lot
even though you're small!
What's this?
Whales only come to fertile seas.
It's a Bubbly Coral.
You can make a bubble easily with it.
That's how things are progressing!
Most of the palace is filled with sea water.
They finally showed their true colors!
Then, open the gate from inside the palace
That hairy old man said... that we
were gonna have a banquet, but...
I heard the 2 of them are hiding
in the back of the Mermaid Cafe.
This place is wonderful!
You need a good bubble-jamon.
and let us in - that is your duty.
Guards are heading there to catch them!
I've been studying this magical
Sea Forest in the deep sea.
he kept getting scolded...
--No way! If we get thrown...
--...We could die from hitting the wall!
so I couldn't wait any longer...
and I followed the smell.
Yeah, it's hard to believe that
this place is in the deep sea.
By the way, did they call you Princess?
This is handy!
You're right!
--What is this animal?
--He transformed himself!
Alright, let's go.
Yes.
That's why I want you humans to do it
because your lives aren't so important!
Just like the Fish-Man Island.
Are you the Mermaid Princess?
Neptune!
Yes. I am King Neptune's daughter.
Kung Fu Boost!
You humans are less
valuable than slaves here!
Treasure Tree Adam--it is so valuable.
But you built a hell of a ship out of it.
My name is Shirahoshi.
It's fast!
Those of you who survive hitting
the wall carry out your duty.
--Shirasu (Baby sardine)?
--Shirahoshi.
Oh, I can't wait to see the Ryugu Palace!
Sanji just got better! Stay away from him!
Hmmm. That's hard to pronounce.
You think so?
Wh-What should we do, Pappagu?
If you succeed it, I'll set you free.
It's made with the same material as the
King of the Pirates' ship that Tom-san made.
Oh, I wanna eat that too!
As a man who was invited to the Ryugu Palace,
If you refuse to do it, I'll kick
you out of the bubble right now!
"Come to the Ryugu Palace"?
You're trying to catch us, aren't you?
It's my greatest design of all!
I don't think you're such a bad person.
I'll become even more famous.
You lowly creatures!
Your face is twitching.
I'll do the coating. Count on me, completely!
Hey, guys...
N-No way... If we leave the bubble,
we'll drown for sure!
Do you seek adventures since you're a pirate?
Sanji, you should still be in bed!
Oh, thank you... Um... Can I ask your name?
Uh-huh.
In that case, you have no choice but wager
on the possibility you'll survive, right?!
Oh yeah! Have you ever seen the sun?
Here we are.
I'm Den.
There are stars in the
night sky, aren't there?
Den-san. You don't look like him.
Go!
And there are different kinds
of flowers and hairy animals!
You're a Merman--not a cowfish.
THE ROYAL PALACE OF THE RYUGU KINGDOM
THE RYUGU PALACE
I thought you'd look like him
Hey, are you ready?
since you're his brother.
Today, a new history for
the Fish-Men will begin!
DEN (TOM'S YOUNGER BROTHER)
SHIPWRIGHT/RESEARCHER OF THE SEA FOREST
Have you ever been to a green
place called a "forest"?
Let's go out!
I'm sorry. I can't go...
That's how a human would think.
Wait, wait! That's too many
questions! Wait a moment!
Races on earth--family members often
look like one another, don't they?
First, we conquer the Ryugu Kingdom!
Why? You said there's a place
you wanna go, didn't you?
Okay!
Cool! Awesome!
Yeah!
Oh, that's a big cheek pouch!
Fish-Men are a little different.
But if I do something like that,
Pappagu-san's house is
nothing compared to this.
Fish-Men and Merfolk each have different,
ancient genes from their ancestors.
I'm coming to you soon, Shirahoshi!
Push!
it's going to cause a lot of trouble
for everybody in the palace!
Don't compare!
Stop it! What are you doing?!
What a beautiful palace!
If I stayed here for 10 years, I'd go crazy!
P-P-Please...
A MOTHER AND SON
When an octopus Mermaid
gives birth to a shark Merman,
--King Neptune is back!
--We were wondering where you were!
THE NORTHWEST SIDE OF THE RYUGU PALACE
A PASSAGEWAY TO THE HARD SHELL TOWER
And now...
Don't yell at me like that!
It's in return for the
food - I'm coming with you!
that means one of her
ancestors was a shark Merfolk.
Open the gate!
Wait!
Luffy-sama is a scary
man just as I thought...
The gate will open!
Where do you want to go?
No way!
Hurry up, Skeleton, get to the King!
It's not so strange when kids don't look
like their parents on the Fish-Man Island.
Wait... We have to open the gate or...
Well...
Welcome home, King-sama!
...Hordy will kill us!
Whoa, whoa! I didn't do
anything to make you cry! Stop!
That's why we can't understand why you
humans want to discriminate against...
This palace looks fun!
I have never been yelled
at by anyone before...
The Sea...
Hey, I have a question for you guys. Um...
It's my palace-jamon!
Stay as long as you like!
The Sea...
...those who don't look like yourselves.
Sanji, you have to stay in bed!
Boy, you did it again?!
You may be big but you're
a coward and a crybaby!
The Sea Forest!
I mean, at that place called
the Ryugu Palace... Is she there?
Hmm...
You must learn your place!
I don't like you!
You went out of the palace on your own again!
By the way, one of your
ancestors was a robot?
No but it's just a dream.
You know, the Mermaid Princess!
What?!
It's inexcusable to go down to
the lower world without guards!
S-She is there! So what?!
I'm a human.
I can't do such a selfish thing,
I can't just go out...
No one ever said such a
horrible thing to me...
Human? Oh, one of your ancestors
was a humanoid robot.
Then I'll go. Even if it kills me.
Can't take it.
It won't happen again-jamon...
You're going?! You never learn!
If she's beautiful, you'll die!
No, a normal human!
Why are you crying just from
saying where you wanna go?!
How awful you are! Please leave now!
He got yelled at...
It's okay.
It's not okay!
Of course she's beautiful, isn't she?!
It'll be too late once something happens!
I-I'm sorry. It's because I
summoned all my courage to say it.
Oh yeah, she mentioned you and
Iceberg-kun in her letter.
I've never met her but I
heard she's very beautiful.
Don't you know the situation
of this country right now?!
I can't take it anymore!
Please don't get mad!
You are scaring me, Luffy-sama!
So she's beautiful, just as I thought!
Oh, that old bag Kokoro wrote to you?
I'm full! Thank you for the food!
Let's have the banquet already!
I'll go, I'll go, at any cost!
So you've been here for 10 years, huh?
It could make you sick!
Now lead me to the Ryugu Palace!
What a thoughtful old woman.
You're such a pain in the butt!
So I know everything about what happened.
Luffy-sama, please leave now!
--What's wrong with him?
--I don't know but we have to take him.
What is that? That was so loud!
Hey, isn't there anywhere you wanna go?
By the way, I brought the people who
saved Megalo when he got attacked
My brother lived his life completely
like he always did, to the very end!
Is he throwing something again?
You need to be handcuffed if
you're going to the palace!
Huh?
What a sick guy!
by the Kraken-jamon.
Of course, there are a lot
of places that I want to go...
Do whatever you want as long as
I can see the Mermaid Princess!
And you traveled all the way to tell me that.
Now welcome our guests!
He had a good pupil.
Sanji!
That's what I thought.
Then let's get out of here!
No! Wake up!
Where is the Princess?
What is Princess Shirahoshi doing?
Fools!
Stop it!
What's this?
What?
I can't cook for the Mermaid
Princess if you handcuff me!
Well, King-sama,
it happened again a few minutes ago...
Let's go for a walk!
What's this noise-jamon?
Don't tell me it's Decken again!
Oh, so you're a robot!
No... No, I'm not supposed to do that!
No... Well, let's just
say that I'm a pervert.
It's coming from the Hard Shell Tower-jamon!
Shirahoshi must be in danger!
Why? Let's go!
That's the reason?!
I knew you were gonna resist! Cart them off!
Are there guards with her?!
Oh, by the way, somebody has been
sitting there for quite a while.
What?! You have to guard the
Princess to keep her calm!
--You're gonna be okay!
--Huh?
You bastards wanna ruin my chance
to get close to the Mermaid Princess?!
No, they're all tied up here!
If something's thrown at
you again, I'll deflect it!
What?!
Idiots!
Hey, pirates! Go see if the Princess is okay!
Oh, that's Boss Jimbei!
If you go missing when something
like that is happening,
Do you?! Do you?!
can't you see that it'd make everyone in
the palace worry, King?!
Boss?
Huh? What are you talking about?
He said he's expecting somebody.
Boy! How can he sleep under
these circumstances?
Neptune-sama! Then they'll
find out about the Princess!
Hey, Sanji!
In the first place?!
He doesn't wanna enter the
island since he's a wanted man.
Oh no, you beat all the soldiers...
It really won't happen again-jamon...
We have no choice-jamon!
He was drinking like crazy so...
The Hard Shell Tower is on the northeast
side of the palace! You guys, go there now!
He got yelled at again...
--Hurry up!
--Yes, sir!
We didn't do anything wrong but now...
THE ENTRANCE OF THE RYUGU PALACE
And I'm very sorry that you just brought
A lot of activity in the palace.
What's going on?
THE GATEWAY
It's their fault - they tried to handcuff me.
THE RYUGU KINGDOM
THE MINISTER OF THE RIGHT (SEAHORSE MERMAN)
the guests here personally
but there's a serious matter.
Why are we being ordered
around by our hostages?!
--They're part of the Straw Hats...
--Dangerous people...
Usopp-chin! Nami-chin! Brook-chin!
Silence! Shirahoshi is
my only daughter-jamon!
Yes, Prince Fukaboshi just called in and...
THE MAIN GATE
THE RYUGU KINGDOM
THE MINISTER OF THE LEFT (CATFISH MERMAN)
Look, everybody's looking at us coldly
like they're a bunch of deep-sea fish!
Somebody is trying to kill her constantly!
THE PALACE GATE
I really can't take it!
We have intruders!
If something happens to my daughter,
I'll shove you all off the end of an ocean trench!
Catch them!
Fukaboshi did? What was it about?
Stop complaining! What's done is done!
How did you guys get this far?!
They're just 3 humans!
As a matter of fact...
Think before you act!
What're you gonna do?!
Aren't they gonna entertain us yet?
So she is the Mermaid Princess, am I right?!
I can't believe this! I was ready
to start a fight right away
Guys! If you resist more,
you're really gonna become criminals!
You beat the half of them with kung fu!
Oh? Where did Luffy go?
But there is no reason for
us to obey them, Camie-san.
but Neptune and all the soldiers are tied up!
He was here a couple minutes ago.
Then I'll go there as soon as possible!
You were pretty strong...
Don't try to compliment me, you bastard!
That fool can't stay still even for a minute!
And...
I was looking forward to a
banquet at the Ryugu Palace.
He can't just wander around
the holy palace of the Sea God!
...can I ask her to show me her panties?
I didn't expect to see a present like this.
It's the voice of a lady!
They'll just arrest us if we don't resist!
There is a man covered
with blood at the shore!
Hey wait, Brook!
They made an unthinkable
accusation against us first!
What a surprise.
Oh, I can't take it! He's heading
there with lascivious intent!
You're the guy from the Fish-Man District!
What happened?
Call a doctor!
We will fight them forever
if that's what they want!
That guy!
Now she's in a different kind of danger!
Huh? I am a doctor!
Why is he here?!
It's no mistake! I can smell
food in the sea water!
Wait, Skeleton! You don't have
to untie me but take me with you!
The hateful Vander Decken!
You've shown up at last!
--They're so strong even without the captain!
--Can't believe it!
Smells really good!
What? Hachi?
I don't know what we're
gonna do in the future.
And that's...
I have jurisdiction over the tower!
What happened to you?!
Is it this way?
If something happened to the Princess,
I would be beside myself with regret!
But you can't arrest us now
for things we haven't done!
...Hordy Jones from the Fish-Man District!
Hey, Hachi! It's us!
Why are you hurt?! What happened to you?!
Why did he come back here?
The nose guy wasn't ever
that remarkable, was he?!
Oh... It's you guys...
Hordy? That guy is...
Brook-chin and Nami-chin became
stronger than 2 years ago as well!
Good to see you... Is Straw Hat with you?
He was once a decorated soldier in our army.
See? That's the prologue to the
future that has been predicted.
He's not here! Wait for a moment!
I'll treat you in a sec!
I assume... you...
Yeah, right! If you guys didn't start it,
we wouldn't have to fight back in the first place!
Summon all your friends... Hurry...
There's no water here?
...wanna see her too!
--Don't be ridiculous!
--How lecherous!
You guys don't wanna get involved...
Is this some kind of trap?
It's too good to be true.
He's right.
He's wrong!
But this is nothing compared to giant
insects' all-out attack on the Bowin Islands!
Sanji-san, excuse me for seeing her first!
...with this island! Get out of the island!
We've had visitors one after another.
The smell is gone!
It must be through those doors then!
The New Fish-Man Pirates will
come and attack the island soon!
What a lively palace.
I've always wanted to go to the Sea Forest.
Ah-ha! You guys are their accomplices!
You let them in, didn't you?!
Witness the power of my
new weapon - Black Kabuto!
And the Ryugu Kingdom will... fall!
For this 10 years.
Bring it on!
You know what, we wouldn't be
here if you guys didn't invite us!
But everybody is kind enough to tell me that
it's too dangerous to go out of the tower.
Neptune-sama, we need your help!
Neptune-sama!
Maybe this is a banquet room.
There was a kidnapping!
Somebody kidnapped the Princess!
I wonder if it's fair to arrest
somebody based on a prediction.
They look formidable! Who are those people?!
And I am scared of going out, too!
He said Zoro is here already.
--Hey, let us have our arms at least!
--Please, let us fight!
Luffy-sama, are you really
going to take me out of here?
And pirates are falling like
rain at the tower! In any event,
What huge, thick, solid-looking doors!
I need some time to think-jamon!
they're your enemies! They're attacking!
Vander Decken!
Since you've shown up, there is no doubt!
Uh-huh.
Thus,
These walls look very solid too.
Are you really going to protect me?
Kidnapped?! Shirahoshi?! Who did it?!
you need to be in custody for now!
They look like the ones in Impel down.
Count on me! You're gonna be fine!
You're the one who did it!
Give me back my daughter!
They must have really good food inside!
He's formidable!
Somebody's making a
raid now? What should we do?
Take this!
We haven't even got married yet.
It's too soon for you to say that, Father-sama.
Why now?!
We're occupying the palace ourselves!
Zoro!
Don't call me Father-sama!
Whoa-whoa, I'm not gonna take you if you cry.
I thought you'd been captured!
It's dark. This isn't a banquet room.
Where did you take Shirahoshi?!
You'd better tell me she's unharmed!
Wh-What should we do?!
Plus, to be accurate,
you take me since I can't swim.
I heard the sound of this
festival so I let myself out!
No, don't answer!
What are you talking about?
You're talking like the Princess is missing.
But there was delicious food!
I'll cut them.
I said "Don't answer"!
I-I am so sorry. I am too delighted...
Then, is this food storage?
Who cares! I'll have some!
Captain Decken, we're here!
Quit acting dumb!
In order for us to survive...
You really are a crybaby and a coward.
Wait there, Wadatsumi!
Why else would Shirahoshi have
disappeared from her room all of the sudden?!
I'm starving!
THE FISH-MAN DISTRICT "NOAH"
...We have to open the gate at any cost!
Uh-huh, okay!
But once you go out,
everybody will recognize you.
What is this? Such a funny feeling.
Th-They're here!
My Shirahoshi disappeared?!
This way, sir.
Thank you for waiting!
Yes, I'm sorry.
She's my... My daughter-jamon!
So I have an idea!
What is it?
Neptune-sama, don't lose
your temper over his nonsense!
Why don't you come out of Shark now?
Vander Decken-sama is here!
Coral is everywhere on this island.
N-No, I'd rather stay in here still...
Mermaid Princess?! Are you alright?!
Please!
How do you like it out here after 10 years?
What's this? It's so soft!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
We ran into a volcanic eruption.
Hey, Skeleton! Look at the tower!
Calm down, Decken.
My heart is racing! This is very bad...
Look. All of the humans that you threw,
aimed at the Mermaid Princess, are here.
Oh? Did I hear someone?
So you're the notorious Hordy?
How can it be bad? You
just got out of the tower.
I can't believe this!
Those aren't knives or axes like usual!
I suspect?
You're weird!
That means that Princess Shirahoshi
was here at least during that time.
You're notorious, too.
This coral is like pudding!
This is...
Help me...
Nutty Vander Decken.
Plus, it doesn't matter
if they're lying or not
It was the sound of human
pirates hitting the tower!
Is somebody here?
because you know how to
check where she is now.
...what they call an adventure?!
--Nice to meet you.
--Oh, a handshake?
How eccentric! He's not normal,
that man - Vander Decken!
It's no good. Just a minute.
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
What's wrong with you?
Huh?! V-Vander Decken?!
If your heart is racing, that's an adventure!
Check where she is?
Oh, this is no good!
They're getting on their feet!
I'm all set!
You're right! Hordy,
you're a very smart guy! I suspect!
Did you say "the Sea Forest"?
What are you doing on my body?
Never mind!
Does this mean that the
impregnable Ryugu Palace...
What is that? Something fun?
Nice to meet you too, Hordy Jones!
Huh? Is he leaving?
...has been invaded by enemy forces?!
Who are you, sir?!
What is he gonna do?
It's a graveyard.
This is a surprise attack!
The King is in danger!
There is a grave that I haven't
been to since they built it.
We're unbeatable on the seafloor now.
The Princess is in danger!
What?! It was a big
person... I mean, Mermaid!
The worst of the worst coming together!
Alright, you coral, fly to Shirahoshi!
That is the place that I've wanted
to go to the most for 10 years!
The attack stopped, huh?
Decken! Decken! Hordy! Hordy!
You came here to kill me
like the others, didn't you?
Let's go, Coward!
Decken! Decken! Hordy! Hordy!
Y-Yes! We are ready, Megalo!
But I'm not scared!
It's not heading towards the tower!
THE SEA FOREST IN THE DEEP SEA
Decken! Decken! Hordy! Hordy!
Because I am Neptune's daughter!
So I'm not scared...
Decken! Decken!
We've been in love for a decade!
Nothing will tear us apart...
It's been 10 years already.
...Not scared...
Neptune is a nuisance for both of us.
Since her assassination in broad daylight
...except for death!
which threw the Fish-Man
Island in an uproar.
We have the same goal.
...And I had a very big fart!
Time flies.
Beat Neptune's army who take no
pride in being Fish-Men or Mermaids...
Somebody! Father-sama! Brother-sama!
Princes have grown into tough soldiers.
Luffy-sama, that is so
inappropriate to talk about.
...And kill Neptune, the God of the Sea!
Whoa, whoa! I didn't do
anything to you, did I?!
Go, Shark!
Is it?
Princess Shirahoshi is still in the tower.
And...
Megalo?!
Before you become somebody else's,
...We will destroy...
But nobody forgets your ideals.
Luffy-san?!
...The Ryugu Kingdom completely!
I'd rather see you dead with
your blood splattered all over!
To the Sea Forest!
Oh, damn! What's with you?!
Shirahoshi!
Queen Otohime!
Hordy's plans for revenge are underway!
A wall of the royal palace is destroyed
and seawater begins to rush in.
Princess Shirahoshi is a gigantic mermaid.
The Straw Hats are facing the
God of the Sea, Neptune's army.
When Shirahoshi is discovered missing,
the Ryugu Palace is thrown into a panic.
The pirates he has sent lay
siege to the Ryugu Palace,
Hordy attacks Neptune's
army with his full might.
Vander Decken has doggedly pursued her, so she has lived for years in the Hard Shell Tower.
Neptune's soldiers attempt to break
Furthermore, a group of unknown
pirates have infiltrated the palace.
and throw it into a state of panic.
the bubbles protecting Zoro's group
to turn the tables of the battle.
The soldiers risk their lives to
protect Neptune, the God of the Sea
The crew has been caught up in the attack,
These pirates seem driven to attack
the Straw Hats at all costs.
Decken hurls an axe at the tower in an attempt to take Shirahoshi's life.
Meanwhile, unidentified
pirates continue to attack
and the once impregnable Ryugu
Palace gate is breached,
when Zoro stands to face Hordy.
the Hard Shell Tower where
Luffy and Shirahoshi are.
Meanwhile, in Coral Hill, a critically
wounded Hachi appears before Sanji and Chopper!
With the seawater is rising, Zoro will
battle in dramatically unfavorable conditions.
The New Fish-Man Pirates have arrived,
intent on destroying the kingdom!
Meanwhile, Nami's group has been surrounded by soldiers from Neputune's army!
The tension inside the Ryugu
Palace continues to rise!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Ryugu Palace in Shock!
The Kidnapping of Shirahoshi!"
"A Coward and a Crybaby!
The Princess in the Hard Shell Tower!"
"It's an Emergency!
The Ryugu Place Is Occupied!"
"The Battle in the Ryugu Palace!
Zoro vs. Hordy!"
"Hordy's Onslaught! The Retaliatory
Plan Set Into Motion!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!