Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he
ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew returned
to Sabaody Archipelago.
And on their way to the New World,
they reached the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
I'm going to invite you to
the Ryugu Palace-jamon!
"The Ryugu Palace! Taken by
the Shark that They Saved!"
A FEW HOURS AGO
A few hours before...
...Luffy and the others met King Neptune...
THE RYUGU KINGDOM MERMAID COVE
At the Mermaid Cove in the Ryugu Kingdom...
Somebody sealed this very tightly!
--I wonder what's inside.
--Let me guess...
If the barrel is so important to them,
like a treasure chest, it must be
high-quality liquor or something.
It's really tight!
Wait! That's enough!
You loosened it up pretty
well and that's enough for me!
What? There's someone inside?
No way!
Thank you!
I appreciate your help, Mermaids!
Don't try to get away!
Get to the water now!
It's too late!
I'm sinking!
It's a swamp! On rocky ground?!
It's a muddy swamp that you can't escape!
It's a bottomless swamp!
I'm a Devil Fruit eater!
I ate the Swamp-Swamp Fruit
and became a swamp man!
The more you struggle...
No!
...The more you sink!
Help!
Stop calling for help!
I'm not gonna kill you!
Somebody...
I said "Stop," didn't I? You fool!
Ishilly!
I just want you to sleep for a while!
My body is bottomless!
Now how much were Mermaids going for?
If I remember right,
70 million each at auction.
I got 3 of them so that'll be...
I have to thank the Straw Hats!
Because of them, I made it
into the Fish-Man Island
without going through immigration!
I can hunt these valuable
Mermaids as much as I want!
This is a treasure island for me!
Ishilly!
I'm sure I heard them around here!
Ishilly...
AT THE PRESENT TIME
And now,
at Coral Hill, the port
town in the Ryugu Kingdom...
THE RYUGU KINGDOM
THE PORT TOWN--CORAL HILL
The Straw Hat Pirates?!
They kidnapped girls from the Mermaid Cove?
No, that's not what I meant.
They were all pretty nice.
First of all, they're Camie's friends.
Maybe they made a threat against her.
No!
In fact, at the place at the moment,
there were only us guards, the Mermaid girls,
the guys from the Fish-Man
District who were beaten,
and the Straw Hats.
And now they're gone so who
knows what they're doing.
Humans have a good reason
to kidnap Mermaids.
Young Mermaid girls have been
traded at high prices in their world.
But you can't suspect them blindly...
Don't you know that there
were a lot of pirates
who got close to Mermaids...
...pretending they were
nice only to kidnap them?
Hmmm...
Prince Fukaboshi!
And Madam Sharley, did you really see the
future that you mentioned a while ago?
That the pirate - Straw Hat Luffy
will destroy the Fish-Man Island?!
Madam Sharley, drink some water.
Yes, I saw the future.
It's true that I saw it.
Even the people at the Ryugu Palace like us
know how accurate your previsions are.
It's no good.
I was going to treat them nicely
since they saved my sister's pet, but...
Although everything remains uncertain,
we can't let them be at large!
We have no choice but to
take them into custody!
AROUND THE SAME TIME
Around the same time,
THE RYUGU KINGDOM
THE HIGH-CLASS DISTRICT--FISHVERLY HILLS
at the high-class district
of the Ryugu Kingdom -
Fishverly Hills...
They're gone.
So who were they after all?
King Neptune came to pick them up himself
and invited them to the Ryugu Palace.
Don't fall.
Neptune!
Whale!
Shark! Shark!
Jamon! Jamon!
Neptune!
What is that chant, old
man? It sounds so dumb!
No, that's rude! Straw, you bastard!
Terrifying! You're terrifying!
That shark--Megalo is a pet that
my daughter loves so much-jamon!
She kept crying hysterically
saying "Megalo is not coming back."
I wasn't aware he was attacked by the Kraken.
Thank you for saving him from danger-jamon!
We didn't mean to but I'm
glad that you're okay!
So he's the Mermaid Princess' pet?!
Oh, Pappagu-san? If I'm correct,
you said you're the best friend
of the Mermaid Princess.
Shh! Shh!
Oh, so that was a lie!
Anyway, I feel sorry for Sanji-san!
He wanted to see the Mermaid
Princess more than anybody!
I guess he was just born to be unlucky.
But a princess who has a
shark as a pet must be...
I-Is it okay...
...for us to go to the Ryugu Palace?
He said "Your friends can
come-jamon" so it should be okay.
Normally you're not allowed, right?
Then, why don't you just enjoy it?
I sent out my sons first but
they haven't come back.
That's why I came.
Because I can't wait to see the food at the
banquet so I want to start already-jamon!
I can't wait, either!
Hey, you two, quit drooling!
Oh, I almost forget. I already
invited one of your friends.
He is a swordsman.
He started drinking on his
own before the banquet.
It's more fun to have a banquet
with everybody - he is so selfish.
I think his name was...
Is it Zoro?
Must be Zoro...
Zori!
It's Zoro!
My soldiers will find the rest of your
friends and bring them to the palace
so don't worry-jamon.
Nami, don't you know where they went?
Looks like a good place to shop!
There are so many people here.
Maybe it won't take that much
to get some information.
About Luffy and the others?
That, too.
But what I wanna know
the most is the whereabouts of...
...my shipwright master -
Tom-san's relatives.
This is where he came from.
If his family is here, I have
to tell them the way he lived.
We just got back together
but let me do this on my own.
It doesn't seem like
there is any stopping you.
I wanna check on something too.
You too, Robin?
There are a lot of ancient
traditions on the Fish-Man Island.
So there must be some
important pieces of history
that haven't been revealed yet.
Important pieces of history...?
So we got separated again.
You didn't have any problem either, did you?
No... Well, there was a little one.
Hey, by the way, grandpa...
Call him "God of the Sea - Neptune-sama"!
This place is at 10,000
meters below sea level
so why is there light around this island?
The island itself doesn't
provide any light.
This is the only place in the deep sea
that has light so Fish-Men started
living here a long time ago.
And that was the beginning
of the Fish-Man Island.
There are the roots of a giant
tree called the Sun Tree Eve...
...that transfers sunlight from
the surface to the deep sea.
Transfers sunlight?
You mean there is a tree with
shining roots more than 10,000 meters long?
Yes, indeed.
Scientists try to make some senses out of it
but it's a mystical tree that transfers
sunlight to its roots-jamon.
And its respiration supplies
air to the sea floor as well.
It's like the boss of the Hustle
Muscle Mangrove at Sabaody?
Hairy old man, I'm hungry!
You!
We'll be there soon!
It's huge!
That's the entrance-jamon.
--Yes?
--It's me-jamon.
I-It must be K-King-sama!
I'll put down the gateway now!
Oh yeah, take this.
What's this?
It's a Bubbly Coral.
You can make a bubble easily with it.
Most of the palace is filled with sea water.
You need a good bubble-jamon.
This is handy!
Alright, let's go.
Neptune!
It's fast!
Oh, I can't wait to see the Ryugu Palace!
Wh-What should we do, Pappagu?
As a man who was invited to the Ryugu Palace,
I'll become even more famous.
Your face is twitching.
Here we are.
THE ROYAL PALACE OF THE RYUGU KINGDOM
THE RYUGU PALACE
Cool! Awesome!
Pappagu-san's house is
nothing compared to this.
Don't compare!
What a beautiful palace!
--King Neptune is back!
--We were wondering where you were!
Open the gate!
The gate will open!
Welcome home, King-sama!
This palace looks fun!
It's my palace-jamon!
Stay as long as you like!
Boy, you did it again?!
You must learn your place!
You went out of the palace on your own again!
It's inexcusable to go down to
the lower world without guards!
Can't take it.
It won't happen again-jamon...
He got yelled at...
It'll be too late once something happens!
Don't you know the situation
of this country right now?!
Let's have the banquet already!
By the way, I brought the people who
saved Megalo when he got attacked
by the Kraken-jamon.
Now welcome our guests!
Where is the Princess?
What is Princess Shirahoshi doing?
Well, King-sama,
it happened again a few minutes ago...
What?! You have to guard the
Princess to keep her calm!
Idiots!
If you go missing when something
like that is happening,
can't you see that it'd make everyone in
the palace worry, King?!
In the first place?!
It really won't happen again-jamon...
He got yelled at again...
And I'm very sorry that you just brought
THE RYUGU KINGDOM
THE MINISTER OF THE RIGHT (SEAHORSE MERMAN)
the guests here personally
but there's a serious matter.
Yes, Prince Fukaboshi just called in and...
THE RYUGU KINGDOM
THE MINISTER OF THE LEFT (CATFISH MERMAN)
I really can't take it!
Fukaboshi did? What was it about?
As a matter of fact...
Aren't they gonna entertain us yet?
Oh? Where did Luffy go?
He was here a couple minutes ago.
That fool can't stay still even for a minute!
He can't just wander around
the holy palace of the Sea God!
It's no mistake! I can smell
food in the sea water!
Smells really good!
Is it this way?
There's no water here?
The smell is gone!
It must be through those doors then!
Maybe this is a banquet room.
He said Zoro is here already.
What huge, thick, solid-looking doors!
These walls look very solid too.
They look like the ones in Impel down.
They must have really good food inside!
It's dark. This isn't a banquet room.
But there was delicious food!
Then, is this food storage?
Who cares! I'll have some!
I'm starving!
What is this? Such a funny feeling.
What is it?
Coral is everywhere on this island.
What's this? It's so soft!
Oh? Did I hear someone?
This coral is like pudding!
Is somebody here?
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing on my body?
Who are you, sir?!
What?! It was a big
person... I mean, Mermaid!
You came here to kill me
like the others, didn't you?
But I'm not scared!
Because I am Neptune's daughter!
So I'm not scared...
...Not scared...
Somebody! Father-sama! Brother-sama!
Whoa, whoa! I didn't do
anything to you, did I?!
Oh, damn! What's with you?!
Princess Shirahoshi is a gigantic mermaid.
Vander Decken has doggedly pursued her, so she has lived for years in the Hard Shell Tower.
Decken hurls an axe at the tower in an attempt to take Shirahoshi's life.
Meanwhile, Nami's group has been surrounded by soldiers from Neputune's army!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Coward and a Crybaby!
The Princess in the Hard Shell Tower!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!