Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
2 years have passed since
the War of the Best.
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
Luffy and his crew returned
to Sabaody Archipelago
to Sabaody Archipelago.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training.
and on their way to the New World,
they reached the Fish-Man Island
And on their way to the
next stage - the New World,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
And on their way to the New World,
they reached the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
they reached the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level,
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi,
are engaging in secret maneuvers.
But they have yet to gather and are
stirring things up as a fragmented crew!
where the New Fish-Man Pirates, who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
Luffy and the others find
themselves caught up in the turmoil.
We're gonna restore his dream!
Luffy set out from the Ryugu Palace
with Mermaid Princess Shirahoshi.
along with Vander Decken, who is after the
Then, two people rose up on the Fish-Man Island,
to change our hopeless history.
Zoro and the others facing Hordy
and the New Fish-Man Pirates...
Mermaid Princess,
are engaging in secret maneuvers.
We're the New Fish-Man Pirates!
The Straw Hats find themselves caught
up little by little in the turmoil.
...tried to escape after the
tides turned against them
Robin got information about a Poneglyph
that's hidden somewhere
on the Fish-Man Island.
Shark Grip!
but were caught by Hordy whose
strength was multiplied tremendously
Vander Decken blocks Luffy and
Shirahoshi's way to the Sea Forest.
I think this kingdom holds the
important key to the 100-Year Void!
One was Queen Otohime.
by taking the Energy Steroid.
Franky found the Sunny at the Sea Forest
- the resting place for sunken ships.
--No! I tell you this is no good!
--What should we do?!
And the other is the hero who
freed the slaves - Fisher Tiger.
I found you! I suspect!
Meanwhile, Luffy and the others
finally got to the Sea Forest...
Nami-chin?
Shirahoshi!
Camie, do me a favor!
The person who is responsible for setting
Arlong loose into the East Blue was...
I'll do the coating. Count on me, completely!
Let's talk. They were two
monumental figures!
What?
Vander Decken-sama!
Zoro! The water is rising!
But what was their hidden angst?!
Oh, thank you... Um... Can I ask your name?
Why do you wanna interfere with
my business with Shirahoshi?!
"A Hero Who Freed the Slaves!
An Adventurer Tiger!"
...me!
I have a favor to ask!
Let those two get out of here!
I'm Den.
Oh, by the way, somebody has been
sitting there for quite a while.
"The Haunting Ties!
Nami and the Fish-Man Pirates!"
What about you?
Gum-Gum...
No one can get away with
that guy chasing after them!
...Jet...
Oh, that's Boss Jimbei!
...Hammer!
He said he's expecting somebody.
Go Shark!
I'm going to tell you about...
Don't stand in my way of
conquering this country!
Zoro, Usopp, Nami, and Brook who
have unintentionally taken over
Meanwhile, at the Ryugu Palace,
Zoro and the others...
...an incident that made Arlong
rampage through the East Blue.
I'm sure there is a key to the
void in history somewhere here.
Um... Well, uh...
...are fighting an intense battle with
the New Fish-Man Pirates led by Hordy!
the Ryugu Palace by accident...
...came face to face with
Hordy, Vander Decken
I want you especially to know about this.
You found me!
and his rebel forces who are
trying to destroy the kingdom!
Drop dead, you lowly creature!
The missing piece must have been
She's big! Don't tell me that that is...
lying here secretly at this serene
place for several centuries.
Alright.
Oh, no.
My Shirahoshi disappeared?!
They kidnapped the Mermaid Princess!
If I keep going, there'll be...
She's my... My daughter-jamon!
No, Sanji! Don't turn around at any cost!
It all began...
One-Sword Style...
Huh? What's going on?
We've been in love for a decade!
Nothing will tear us apart...
...16 years ago.
...Lion Strike!
If you do, you're gonna die, Sanji!
Here it is!
16 YEARS AGO - THE FISH-MAN ISLAND
...except for death!
"Keep Shirahoshi Safe!
Decken Close Behind!"
"The Straw Hats Defeated?!
Hordy Gains Control of the Ryugu Palace!"
King Neptune...
Don't look back!
Think about what the King did for us!
Outta my way!
Before you become somebody else's,
Thief!
I see the exit!
Somebody, catch him!
I'd rather see you dead with your blood
splattered all over! Shirahoshi!
Yeah!
We made it outside!
He stole a lot of money!
Use the Bubbly Coral!
"The Battle in the Ryugu Palace!
Zoro vs. Hordy!"
Hey, outta my way!
I'm coming! To wherever my Shirahoshi is!
What a disaster!
I-If anyone comes close, you won't
wanna see what I'll do with this girl!
So few soldiers made it out even
after we left the King there!
It's dead or marriage!
Zoro!
We failed!
Stop moaning! It was the King's order!
--Boss!
Your Majesty?
Men, this is not a retreat!
Oh, Your Majesty! Wait!
How could a human move faster
than a Fish-Man in the water?!
We will exterminate the pirates in the
palace and rescue the King at any cost!
Don't get involved with such a thing!
That's an octopus-san!
That's our responsibility!
That's a blowfish-san!
What's wrong with that man?!
First, we need to communicate with
Prince Fukaboshi and the others!
Oh, there is a killifish-chan as well!
--Wait!
--Queen Otohime!
Coward, you only see fish!
I need to breathe now!
Get in touch with the Princes A.S.A.P.
and reorganize the forces...
Who is that?!
P-Princess Shirahoshi has...
Stay away! Or I'll shoot you!
Damn! How dare he cut Boss!
Look, a rice ball and a doughnut!
...and let's go back to the palace!
Don't be afraid! He's just a human!
He can't stay long in the water!
...really been...
I-I warned you!
Yes, sir!
The nearest town from here is...
Meat!
Fishverly Hills, sir!
...kidnapped!
Catch the swordsman!
Luffy-sama, you're only seeing food!
Look out!
FISHVERLY HILLS
Let's take the Energy Steroid!
Meanwhile, at the high-class
district - Fishverly Hills...
Am I?
Hey, Coward! Why did you come out of Shark?!
Jamon! Jamon!
Run!
Did I miss?
--All of you, get in line!
--Hurry up if you don't wanna die!
Dammit! Stay away!
Jamon!
I-I'm sorry! Luffy-sama,
please don't get mad at me!
Th-This is... What do you want from us?!
What is it all of the sudden?
--Step on it!
--What?
F-Father-sama! He must be
worrying about me at the palace now...
--It's a test!
--No way!
He made Princess-sama cry!
What an evil pirate!
Much...
I got you!
Shut up! Captain Hordy's
gonna rule this country-ch!
Screw this! Kill them all
--Neptune's army, too!
Boy, you're such a pain.
I feel terrible... Princess Shirahoshi-sama!
AN OFFICER OF THE NEW FISH-MAN
PIRATES - IKAROS MUCH
Now, step on the image!
Here, Coward!
Damn!
No, I can't...
KING NEPTUNE'S WIFE
QUEEN OTOHIME (GOLDFISH MERMAID)
Step on it now!
Princess...
CANDY FACTORY TOWN
He said "Princess"! Don't tell me that's...
What's this? I sense a great deal of madness!
At Candy Factory Town in the northeast...
Luffy-sama!
It's... Otohime-sama!
No, Sanji!
Why are you laughing?! Swallow her now!
Zoro!
--Ouch!
--Really?!
Hey, just do it already!
Don't turn around at any cost!
--My hand!
--Doctor!
I can't!
Hey, could it be that the
Mermaid Princess is behind me...
Your Highness! Let me see it!
Huh?!
Please forgive me! I can't
tread on the image of her face!
Zoro! Is he okay?! He's not surfacing!
It's a compound fracture.
...if I turn around?
Shut up!
With one hit?!
I can't take it! I'm losing my
strength and I can't take it!
Vander Decken is going after Shirahoshi!
Those who can't do it are human sympathizers.
I don't mind!
AN OFFICER OF THE NEW
FISH-MAN PIRATES - DARUMA
Yes, she's there! That's why I don't
want you to turn around, Sanji!
What's going on?
Queen Otohime!
Which means they're our enemies!
You almost died after seeing
some average Mermaids!
Neptune-sama!
Queen?
Take this!
IN FRONT OF THE FISH-MAN CULTURAL HALL
In front of the Fish-Man Culture
Hall in the southeast...
Beat him up!
I beg you-jamon, you people!
Why have you done such a senseless
thing as robbing someone?!
So if you see the Mermaid Princess,
I'll give you anything you want!
Shut up! You're from a wealthy,
royal family - you don't understand!
you'll lose all of your blood
and it's curtains for you!
Let me go after Decken!
Whoa, whoa! It's easy!
I have 10 kids at home,
who are crying from hunger!
AN OFFICER OF THE NEW
FISH-MAN PIRATES - HYOUZOU
It's either step on this image
or flee from this island.
You can take silver, gold and jewels...
All you can do is defend yourself!
Just give up.
...or my soldiers' lives or anything!
Screw you!
All the more reason to not do it!
Huh?
You're choking already, aren't you?!
No no, King!
Damn! I can't take it anymore!
Mermaid Princess...
Q-Queen-sama! Stop hitting him!
He's gonna catch Shirahoshi!
My treasure--Shirahoshi!
They say even the most beautiful woman
Ah-ha!
in the world - Pirate Empress Boa
Hancock's looks pale in comparison.
You're far more fragile than all of us!
You're desperate, huh?
She is the most gorgeous of all Mermaids.
And now, she's behind my back...
I don't care! I have to do this for him!
How pathetic, Neptune.
But this is the end of the line!
Just do it! If somebody
refused to do either...
I have to teach him even if it
shatters my hand into pieces!
I never thought that the hateful Straw Hats
would help us conquer the Ryugu Palace!
Drop dead!
Don't push your luck, bastard!
No! I beg you! Don't turn around!
...I've been told to slice 'em up!
One-Sword Style Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
MARINE SHOPPING MALL
At the Marine Shopping Mall in the east...
"Hateful"?
Would your children be happy
being raised by stolen money?!
"Leave the country"? Don't be ridiculous!
Chopper.
This is the only place on the
seafloor that has light.
Rather than live a day longer without
grasping at a dream within reach,
And we can't live in the humans' world!
Damn! Now let's just kill them all!
Live a life of which your
children can be proud!
He's got Arlong's mark, too!
See?
Zoro!
You can see how heartlessly the
humans discriminate against others.
This place is going to be filled with water!
I will live out my dream...
You have to hang onto me, too!
Jimbei told me there was something
going on in the Fish-Man District!
...and choose to die!
What?! I thought your dream
was to go to the All Blue!
What is it?! What are you doing?!
However...
I can't believe you, a former proud soldier
of Neptune's army, are the ringleader!
What's going on?
They defeated my strong army very easily.
There is no way that humans
and Fish-Men can get along.
I have to... apologize, as well!
Shame on you, Hordy!
They've got some kind of uncanny strength.
You must submit to King Hordy!
I have to get all my men out of the palace!
No!
I'm sorry!
Shame?
We will reign over humans and change history!
AN OFFICER OF THE NEW FISH-MAN PIRATES - ZEO
Sanji!
Here! Secure some air with this-jamon!
I didn't notice your struggles
I'd feel shame if I had felt any
real pride to be in Neptune's army.
WATERWHEEL TOWN
At Waterwheel Town in the north...
even though I'm your queen and
I'm living in the same country!
Oh, thanks!
Hang onto my body very tightly!
Dosun!
--Now, you're next.
--It's gonna be easy.
Huh?
Got it!
The only reason I joined the army was to
learn fighting skills in actual combat.
Your worries and your pain are killing me!
Th-Th-That is...
I can't!
We don't have time-jamon!
Now I know how poor my imagination is!
Zoro, this way! Hang onto the old man!
And that's all.
AN OFFICER OF THE NEW
FISH-MAN PIRATES - DOSUN
I'm gonna pummel those who
won't step on it-dosun!
--You bastard!
--I became stronger thanks to you.
I hope my strained back can take it!
You must have had some awful
reason to do what you did...
She's magnificent!
Take this!
What do you mean?
You all have failed to notice
what's been going on on the island.
That's quite simply...
I didn't want to do it!
You're... Fukaboshi! Don't get in my way!
But I had no choice!
...a beauty that you can't even draw!
Since I was a child, I've seen Fish-Men
oppressed at the hands of irrational humans.
My store burned down.
Somebody set fire to it and stole all my money!
What do you think you are doing?!
Now, my soldiers! Here is your way out!
He turned to stone!
I lost my job and my debts were increasing.
And my poor kids were starving!
How dare you make people of this country
tread on the image of my late mother!
Abandon the battle and get out of here!
Princess Shirahoshi-sama!
Help me-dosun!
We gotta rescue her!
But they're the Straw Hats who are
strong enough to occupy the palace!
Merman...
We've gone through all the trouble
to get to the Fish-Man Island,
...Combat!
CORAL HILL
So that's why you did it. I understand...
I understand how you feel...
At Coral Hill, after Luffy
and the others left...
why don't we take a Fish-Man back with us?
Zoro! Use this!
--What should we do?!
--We let Vander Decken get away...
Here we go!
--But you can't do that!
--What?!
I thought he'd die from a nosebleed.
L-Let me go-dosun!
Give us back our friend! You kidnappers!
If you do the same thing to others,
it will never stop!
But he turned to stone! That's new.
...and we couldn't stop the Straw Hats
from taking Princess Shirahoshi away!
Neptune's up to something!
I'm sorry!
But I'm sorry! We are guilty
of not being dependable...
Zoro!
Maybe because of his blood donors!
But the Princess said that
she'd be back by dinner.
Do you Fish-Man brats
wanna mess with us humans?
Ultramarine!
You fool! They made her say it!
L-Luffy-sama, I don't know... what to do...
That's very generous...
That's very generous of you to say...
They're worth far less than Merfolk
A group from the Fish-Man District
is rampaging all over the island!
but we can make some extra
money by selling them as a set.
--What?!
--What's going on on the island?!
But you can't do that!
Hey, are you okay?!
I'm sorry!
I can't take it anymore!
In any case, Hachi, who did this to you?!
Mermaid girls are going
missing all around the island!
But you can't!
Ow, ow, ow...
I will change my life!
All soldiers, go!
If they sell the Princess
to the Celestial Dragons...
Thank you for crying for a
good-for-nothing like me, Queen-sama!
They can't even breathe in the water...
Yes, sir!
Ride the current at any cost-jamon!
...but no matter how much we kill them,
these damn humans never go away!
Hey, it seems like another
Mermaid girl went missing!
Damn! They're escaping without fighting us!
Don't mention it. Good luck!
It's already unusual for someone from
the royal family to come out of the palace
I'm scared!
Boss Hordy! You gotta take this now!
Hey, what do you guys want?!
Oh no!
and walk around...
--We caught them!
--The Straw Hats! We did it!
But to slap a citizen and sob over his story!
We're out now! Keep going!
I took her!
I admired Arlong's ambition to
take the arrogance out of them!
Get through the gateway and go inland!
We are sea hunters who risk our lives
to catch the Sea Kings everyday!
That aside, I just saw something great!
Otohime-sama is a very
unconventional queen.
Hey, old man! Don't pass out, please!
A big size Mermaid-san!
She's a woman of boundless compassion.
Look, even kids love her!
Pirates are no match for us!
Don't mess with the sea hunters!
We're gonna restore his dream!
I hate getting old!
--The Sea hunters did it!
--Great!
A human-sized Mermaid is worth 70 million
Otohime-sama!
I can't move even a millimeter-jamon!
We're the New Fish-Man Pirates!
Oh!
so if I can catch a Mermaid
who is 7 or 8 times bigger
You guys are fishermen?! We're not fish!
I will do my best for you children!
What?!
I remember you, too! You're the punk
who used to be in Arlong's group!
I was training myself to become
Arlong's right-hand man one day...
and sell her...
What?!
--King-sama!
--King Neptune!
Your nose is running!
I hit you for your own good!
I'll make a bundle!
Hey hey, what should we do?!
Y-You are...
You're safe now, Princess-sama!
...when he set out to conquer the world
from the East Blue as he planned.
You look like a fool having
snot running out of one nostril.
This is the end-jamon!
Hello.
Turn them over to the Ammo Knights
so they can cut their heads off!
Good afternoon!
It's better to have to come from both sides.
No!
But...
Um... It's not like that, everybody.
Luffy-sama was not...
...unfortunately he was
stopped by some humans.
Whale!
How touching!
Oh, Hoe!
SEA FOREST
Hey guys!
Something's flying towards us! There!
Yeah?
Father-sama!
She was so passionate and
full of love. Queen Otohime...
So these Fish-Men are followers of Arlong?!
Princess Shirahoshi, don't worry.
Great!
Huh? It's no use--we're not gonna be fooled!
Maybe they got the King but
they can't really take his life!
...went down to the island everyday
and addressed the nation.
Thank you. Ow, ow, ow...
I can't even turn my head-jamon.
What?! Hey, something's really flying!
What?! Arlong?!
What? Are you sure?
We have to relocate the
Ryugu Kingdom on earth!
Are you okay?!
Just kidding! I've never had Arlong before...
Good! Well done, Hoe!
Yes. And I will save the King at any cost!
Is it just some coral?
We have a different skin color.
We look different.
Go!
No, somebody's on it.
Can't take it anymore!
Okay. I will be counting on you, Boss-sama!
Oh no! That's...
That's what humans say. And instead of waiting
for the day when they'll understand us,
Ouch! Hey, Usopp-san, why did you kick me?!
...Vander Decken!
Now let me talk to Luffy-kun
and the others for a while.
I found you! I suspect!
we should move closer to
them to understand them!
Just shut up for now!
The seafloor is 10,000 meters from the land.
Shirahoshi!
Enough with chit-chatting
and let's get down to business.
That is also the distance
between our ways of thinking.
Ladies!
What was that?!
Vander Decken-sama!
Stay away!
What's going on?!
Have some tea!
He must've been hiding for a long time
and now he's finally showed himself!
Thanks. Leave it there, Sanji-kun.
Wh-What the...
Don't get the wrong idea!
And we're having a serious
conversation so stop acting like that!
Shark Grip!
The humans who come to this island
are the kind called "pirates."
Princess-sama, run! We'll handle this!
I love you, Nami-san, even
when you're so severe!
I want your answer, Shirahoshi!
If it's "Yes," you can escape death!
And the humans who buy people from
kidnappers are the Nobles who are in power.
Sanji-chin hasn't changed a bit.
Good!
What a strong grip! What
the hell is he doing?!
It's not for you!
We've only known the bad sort of humans.
King-sama!
Now, Jimbei-san.
You have to...
We don't know anything about humans yet.
Oh no! King-sama's been caught by Hordy!
--No! I tell you this is no good!
--What should we do?!
There are so many kind
humans on earth, I assume.
...marry me!
Hordy has been severely wounded, hasn't he?!
What do you mean?
We should relocate the
kingdom under the same sun!
Nami-chin?
You set Arlong loose into the East Blue?
Minister of the Right-sama, let's go back!
If nothing is done, King-sama will...
Camie, do me a favor!
You've been throwing weapons
at her for 10 years to kill her
What?
Let's express our intention to
relocate at the World Summit this year!
No, don't turn back-jamon!
and now you wanna marry her?!
Jimbei-san!
I know.
Stop messing around, Vander Decken!
Is that his own strength?
You have to keep going and...
Yeah, he hasn't taken an Energy Steroid yet.
That's what I heard.
I need you all to sign here!
...bring Fukaboshi and the others!
The Princess must have feared
death for 10 years because of you!
What?
When Luffy and I first heard the
name Jimbei of the Seven Warlords,
Well, even if it's Otohime-sama's idea...
How dare you propose to her!
The walls are broken!
that's what Yosaku told us.
There's no time to lose! Do as he said!
I want your answer, Shirahoshi!
I suspect it's "Yes"!
The idea of moving closer
to humans is... Right?
In exchange for joining the Warlords,
Yes, sir!
Boss Hordy, should we go after them?
Jimbei set loose a terrible
man into the East Blue.
No, just let them go.
Don't say that.
Oh damn! It's a flood!
Soldiers who abandon their
king can't amount to much.
--Was that what he said?
--I bet you don't remember it.
Let's take the first step
instead of doing nothing.
Anyway, tie the stupid king up!
I wonder how Yosaku is doing.
Well?
--Oh this is no good! Especially for me!
--I'm gonna drown!
When I read that you were with
Jimbei 2 years ago in the newspaper,
Yes, sir!
Um...
I'm sorry, you guys!
What do you wanna say?! "Yes"?!
I'm sorry.
But I'm not going to let you down!
Y...
it raised so many questions in my mind.
You're not my type!
Because I thought Jimbei was the key
figure who was pulling Arlong's strings.
It's no use. History has proven it.
--No, water drops!
--Get down! He's gonna do it!
Hey, Jimbei.
If you wanna make excuses, I'll listen.
But you better watch what you say.
What is it?
No idea. Whose skeletonized body is it?
What?
No!
As a matter of fact, this beautiful navigator
- Nami-san here had her home island...
Shark Arrows!
Prince Fukaboshi.
What?! Is that the reason?!
I'm home, kids!
Did you find the Straw Hats' crew?
...taken over by Arlong!
Welcome home, mother-sama!
Yes. I mean, no. Someone from
the store had seen them here
Those water drops are becoming arrows!
And she's been through hell because of it!
but he said Neptune-sama took
Straw Hat Luffy and 4 others away.
Y... Y... Y... Y...
I'm home, Shirahoshi!
You bitch!
Depending on what you have
to say, I might not forgive you!
I think those are the ones
occupying the palace now.
You trampled on my feelings of 10
years and now who will you marry?!
You bastard! How dare you
shoot my soldiers at random!
I think so.
So they're not here. What about the two
from their crew who were in the Coral Hill?
If you don't love me,
your very existence irritates me!
Oh, Shirahoshi, my consolation.
I'm sorry to be late.
--Jimbei-san!
--Hatchin!
Stop it!
Your wounds are gonna
open up again! Don't get up!
I've been trying to reach
them but I can't-mi-re-do.
You fool!
Drop dead, Shirahoshi!
He's right! We gave her so much pain...
Run, Princess Shirahoshi!
I see. I have a bad feeling about this.
--King-sama!
--Don't do that!
Oh, your nose is running
but you're beautiful!
Hurry up! We'll stop him here with our lives!
...that we can't heal no matter
how much we apologize.
No-jamon! You guys are my subjects-jamon!
Moonfish! Shake, shake!
Don't go anywhere! Stay there, Coward!
Neptune-sama!
We were here with her so
she was safe, mother-sama!
I think something happened there.
We better go check.
What an idiot! What kind of a king
becomes a shield for his men?!
What are you saying?!
We can't trust you pirates!
She was safe, she was safe!
Oh, you got a call?
Thank you, my princes.
You don't have what it takes to be king!
You're Decken's accomplice,
aren't you? You want her to die?!
Prince Fukaboshi! Prince Fukaboshi, come in!
Mother-sama, is your hand okay?
--King-sama!
--Damn Hordy!
Brother.
It's nothing.
If you run somewhere, I can't keep you safe!
This is Fukaboshi.
It's awful! He's shooting at the unarmed!
Prince, we have a problem!
I'm in Waterwheel Town.
The future that you four will live in,
And he's way stronger than Arlong!
O-Okay, I'll stay!
I will change it!
Princess-sama!
Waterwheel Town?
Men from the Fish-Man
District invaded the town
WATERWHEEL TOWN
--How dare you scare her!
--You evil pirate!
I’m gonna use my navigation skills
to travel to all the world’s oceans!
and Queen Otohime...
If Otohime-sama wants to make a speech,
she could do it by video.
Sorry guys. I have nothing
against you but you're...
One-Sword Style!
And then I’m gonna make a
world map of everything I see!
Bird Dance!
You shouldn't have done that.
...in my way!
Her strong Observation Haki by
nature makes her the way she is-jamon.
So your map of this island is your
first step toward your dream, then?
Hey wait, Boss Hordy! It's...
What about my mother?! Hey! Answer me!
She prefers to face people to win their hearts
rather than speak from the palace above.
Yeah!
Second Gear!
I'm a fill-in mother for
you two, Nami and Nojiko.
Luffy!
--Let's go to Waterwheel Town!
--Yes, sir!
That's one of Otohime's guiding principles.
And not even I can stop her.
You two are my dear family!
But there are a lot of human
pirates staying on the island.
He did it with his hands tied!
Are they gone?
Yes, to Waterwheel Town I assume.
Why do you wanna interfere with
my business with Shirahoshi?!
She is protected by your friend, the pirate
- Whitebeard's influence to some extent...
Dosun acted too early-ch.
Are you the one who took Shirahoshi out?
There's no point in doing it
unless it's simultaneous.
but you never know what could happen!
She knows that, too.
But that's okay. Alright, let's do this-ch.
Are you the one...
The world that Otohime dreams about is...
Listen, guys! Our dreams
will finally come true!
...that's been throwing things at Coward?!
Pirates, everyone!
...exactly the same as...
Pirates are coming!
I'll kill you both! Let me put you two
together and cut you into quarters!
Be as wild as you like -ch!
That bastard! He shielded
himself with his own man!
Yeah!
You seem to be in excellent spirits,
pathetic humans!
...what our ancestors dreamed about
Hey guys, untie the soldiers!
Try it!
but couldn't make come true
several hundred years ago-jamon.
As of this moment,
What?
L-Let me go!
this village - no,
this island - is now under my control!
The negotiation with the
kingdom has broken down.
Gum-Gum...
What do you mean by that?
...Jet...
We couldn't keep our word to give
them back all the hostages unharmed.
I can't stop Otohime.
100,000 Berries per adult.
50,000 Berries per kid.
...Hammer!
Be sure to keep her safe!
He's so trustworthy.
Yes, sir!
Alright, I got it!
Those who can’t pay… die!
SEA FOREST
Oh, my foot is in the water!
I'm losing my strength!
It's a beautiful place!
Help me, Nami-san!
Hey, fish girl!
So this is the Sea Forest!
Oh? Where is Nami-san?
--Yes?
--Stay here and serve us!
I... always wanted to come here!
Huh? Nami is gone?
I'm sorry. We don't do that sort of thing.
I just can’t say I don’t have a family…
Where did she go? Camie is missing too!
Huh? Don't be such a snob!
Thank you very much, Luffy-sama!
Even… if it costs me my life…
You're just a Fish-Man!
Boy! First Luffy and now Nami?
But we have to untie them first!
Yeah, maybe we’re not related by blood…
Maybe I can treat him carefully here.
Hang on for a minute, Brook!
Mermai-do!
…but we’re a family.
What? Does anyone have something to say?
He's driving my bones too hard...
Why don't you run now?
Mermai-do!
I want to be their parent,
even if it’s only in name.
Th...
That guy...
Sanji...
They’re… my kids.
Please untie the others.
I have no energy left...
Oh, that's the Sunny!
...beat Vander Decken!
Shut your mouth!
Die with your pathetic love.
Yeah, Franky is there too!
Untie the others and take up your arms!
Hey, Franky! I didn't
know that you were here!
Don't let them do a damn thing!
You make my sake taste bad.
He's still moving but we can catch him now!
Nojiko! Nami!
Destroy all of Neptune's
army and the Straw Hats!
Luffy?!
O-Okay...
I love you!
What the hell?!
You're with quite a pin-up girl!
Special Attack--Green Star "Rafflesia"!
THE RYUGU KINGDOM - A SOLDIER OF NEPTUNE'S ARMY
JIMBEI     30 YEARS OLD
Shark! Wake up!
Sanji!
--Whoa! A flower from earth opened up!
--I've never seen such a flower!
You alright?!
Let me introduce you. She's Coward.
He turned to stone a while ago but
he looks happy now. He's conscious!
Take it!
Oh, you're Coward! You have
to get tougher, don't you Sis?
What's this?
Oh, it stinks!
--A sea chart?
--No!
Okay, got it.
Damn! How stupid!
I drew that! It's important
to me! Give it back!
Yes, I'm sorry. My name is Shirahoshi.
Mermaid Princess... Am
I in heaven or paradise?
You drew it?
--How's that?!
--I can't take it anymore...
--Give it back!
--Nami! No!
Franky, no one else is here?
So Otohime-san was a very unusual woman.
Oh? This is quite impressive.
Zoro! The water is rising!
My dream came true! I can die now!
Yeah. Actually Robin came here too but
she said she had to look for something
You're a crybaby just like your mother, huh?
Again, your dream was to go
to the All Blue, wasn't it?
She’s an invaluable
asset! Bring her with us!
I have a favor to ask!
Let those two get out of here!
Well... I-I don't know...
and went into the forest of huge coral.
--Right!
--No!
Let go! Let go! No!
Were you a soldier of the kingdom?
What about you?
Hurry up, Coward!
Hmmm...
No one can get away with
that guy chasing after them!
O-Okay!
There weren't that many options for
a man from the Fish-Man District...
Please don't yell at me.
It makes my heart race.
We have no food for humans!
Shut up and keep drawing maps!
Luffy-kun!
...who knew nothing but fighting.
Jimbei! Oh, Jimbei!
The Fish-Man District?
The people on this island
don't like us for some reason.
That's where you're from, right, Hachi?
Don't stand in my way of
conquering this country!
It's been a while!
We've got to get away from here!
Sounds like a bad neighborhood.
Yes. It used to be a big orphanage where they
housed children without any relatives.
Thank you! Coward! Let's go!
Gather up 100 million
Berries and bring it here.
Okay!
Do so and I’ll let the village
go and give you freedom.
Okay! Nothing has been broken.
P-Princess-sama, why did you untie him?
But the orphanage started
to get out of control
That evil pirate must've scared her again!
Thief! She stole our treasure!
Sorry that I pushed you
so hard all of the sudden.
You look stronger. I hardly recognized you.
and was too much for the
administrators to handle
--She's a kid!
--Who cares! Shoot her!
I am sorry, everybody! I
will be back by dinner!
You can rest here for a while.
They said you weren't here so
I thought I couldn't meet you!
so it became a lawless area that drew
misfits from all over the island.
Do you want me to help you with the coating?
Oh, I thought you came here
because you got my message.
What?
Shit! Go after her!
Go Shark!
No, every man knows his own trade best.
Fisher Tiger was the leader
figure in the Fish-Man District
What's that? I didn't hear about any message.
Okay, thank you!
Hm, that's odd.
but he left the country to chase adventure.
Oh, there you are, Sunny!
Boss Jimbei-sama. It has been a long time.
And I was his lieutenant but
I joined Neptune's army.
70 million more...
70 million more to free the village!
Oh, Princess Shirahoshi-sama,
you're here too! Long time no...
--Robin!
--Is she your friend?
Get away, you shits!
Yeah. Did you finish your business?
Macro and the others became kidnappers
even though they were Fish-Men themselves.
What?! Princess Shirahoshi!
Oh, you're back!
Not yet. I really need to
check something. There it is.
Don't let them get away!
And all the others went
their separate ways as well.
Humph! It seems like you
have nowhere else to go.
Wadatsumi!
Why are you here?!
Hey hey, outsiders should stay out of there!
Welcome home, my dear navigator!
Hey, Franky! Can you help
me with Hachi and Sanji?
But one day...
Thank you for your suggestion.
Yeah!
--Give them back! Please!
--Take them if you want them!
You're the octopus guy!
She's odd, isn't she?
Look who's talking.
What happened to you?
Give them back to her! Do you know
how many signatures there are?
Hachi?! What?!
He looks familiar.
I don't care!
How were you injured?!
He's the Sea Bonze who attacked
the Sunny! He works for Decken!
Before that, why are you
here at the Fish-Man Island?
--I-It's the Great Monk!
--Wadatsumi!
I thought you'd been caught with Arlong!
What can you do with these papers? Huh?!
Sounds like you had a terrible experience.
Stop them!
You were the only one who
could see my arrows earlier.
You bastard! Don't distance yourself!
Hey! Cut it out! You're Arlong from
the Fish-Man District, aren't you?!
Jimbei-san, why are you here?
I got it!
Yes.
Is it because you've seen Arlong's?
Franky, Sanji is next!
It would never make me change
the way I feel about Arlong,
Second Gear!
No, you don't need to do that.
Arlong from the Fish-Man District?
If you've learned how to see them for
the second time, that's impressive.
but until I went to Sabaody
Archipelago 2 years ago,
L-Let go of me!
You're a bit wrong.
Gum-Gum...
But no matter how skillful you are,
no one can beat a Fish-Man in the sea!
THE CAPTAIN OF THE ARLONG PIRATES
ARLONG 25     YEARS OLD
I'm Captain Arlong from the Arlong Pirates!
I never knew that such tough
Fish-Men were persecuted by humans.
...Jet...
Oh, Mermaid Princess!
...Pistol!
I make a living by hunting those lowly
pirates who can't even breathe in water.
I feel like such a bad painter
when I'm standing in front of you!
When Camie was kidnapped
and I was going after her,
I couldn't believe what I saw!
We're doing it on behalf of
all of you - Neptune's army!
My front tooth...
Because I can't depict your splendor
in any of the paint that I have!
It cracked!
The Sabaody Park in front of me looked exactly
like the Arlong Park that Arlong built!
Thank me with your money!
B-Boss Jimbei, don't just watch - help me!
Um...
That's the way he always
acts in front of women!
It hurts! It hurts!
Jimbei?
He's good for nothing!
He's okay now!
Hey, punk! Let go of that rookie soldier.
You can't deflect them in the water!
Your beauty won't fit on my canvas!
We were yearning for it.
Alright!
He is my man, in a way.
And the papers with signatures.
I'm not just saying this
to make you forgive me.
Three-Sword Style! Dragon Twister!
--Yeah, he's back to his old self!
--So I can't draw!
Coward, let's get to the Sea Forest!
Nami! Arlong-san really didn't like humans!
Yes!
I have no interest in them but they're
important for the Queen. So give them back.
It's so noisy. What's going on?
DRAGON
Oh, seems like I can have some fun.
Huh?!
Why is Princess Shirahoshi here?!
Boss Hordy! A pirate girl and a Mermaid
just exited the Ryugu Palace!
He hated them.
--That's Boss Jimbei of Neptune's army!
--Great!
Hey, who the hell are you?!
Why are you on board the Sunny?!
We went too far.
"Boss"? That's a good title.
Who cares?
That's Den-chan, brother of
Tom - my shipwright master...
I don't have much time!
Sounds like you're running a gang!
But ever since we were kids,
If I can get rid of him,
...doing the recoating for us.
CORAL HILL--AT THE SHORE
Do as I say, Arlong!
there will be only an old
fool and a mob to take care of!
we yearned for the world that humans live in.
Oh, okay!
Stay with me! It's gonna be okay!
Alright. Here.
So he's a shipwright who's
coating Franky's brother!
Hurry up and get out of here!
Here!
Shark Arrows!
Don't be mad, brother.
Don't worry about us now!
Just think about yourself...
Me, Arlong-san...
What? Brother?
Yeah, something like that!
It's been a while, huh? I'm your
family from the Fish-Man District!
What?
Everybody...
Princess Shirahoshi-sama,
I know why you wanted to come here but...
What do you guys want?
We want the Mermaids back!
Nami-chin, was it okay to leave
Zoro-chin and the others behind?
I'm not like you.
You're still a pirate, aren't you, scum?
You humans only see us as novelties!
We couldn't escape with everyone.
Ah? What are you talking about?!
That's true, but...
Don't play dumb, you pirates!
--Don't call me "scum," brother!
--How about trash?
We heard that 3 more young Mermaids
disappeared at a beach in the south.
Don't worry! They always make it through!
"Trash"?! I've let you say
what you wanted, but that's...
Again?
Where are those girls?
Hey, everybody! It's the
adventurer - Fisher Tiger-san!
I know they're all tough.
I beat him up so badly but he kept throwing
dozens of things! How persistent he is!
I don't know what you're talking about!
--What?
--Tiger-san's back!
But Hatchin said that Hordy is not only
strong but has dangerous thoughts, too.
Why do you think that we
did it? It's true that...
Look at what you've done.
Why did you bring her here, Luffy-kun?
--Tiger-san!
--How was the trip?
--Brother Tai!
--Big Brother!
But we hurt so many humans!
...I love Mermaid-chans so much
that I wanna take them away!
Don't worry. You know I got your back, right?
Jimbei! Arlong!
Looks like you guys are doing fine!
They've gotten much
stronger in last 2 years.
Yes!
Hachi, don't push yourself!
I'm gonna prepare some medicine so lie down.
But we didn't kidnap them.
It was a long trip, wasn't it?
How careless!
See? You just said that
you wanna take them away!
Yeah, a lot happened.
That aside, what kind of person
is Jimbei, the former Warlord?
Stop by at my ship!
Why are you guys arguing? Be quiet!
Huh?
Maybe later. I need to go
to the Ryugu Palace first.
I heard that Fish-Men and Merfolk were
considered mere fish a long time ago.
I knew humans did it!
So that's the grave she talked about.
Although he is a pirate,
I'll take you then.
He doesn't have use for a pirate!
Get out!
people on the island trust him so he's
allowed to enter the Ryugu Palace.
Ouch!
But 200 years ago, the Ryugu Kingdom became
a member country of the World Government.
Huh? Big Brother wouldn't say such a thing!
I see. But he was in the same pirate
group with Arlong, wasn't he?
She's been at that for a long time.
There's some left in it! Don't waste food!
Guys, don't fight!
They established friendly
relations with humans
Shut up, human!
That is her mother--Queen Otohime's grave.
That guy--Hordy is a follower of Arlong.
Oh? Sanji! Chopper!
and the king was allowed to
participate in the World Summit.
Hey, Sanji! Is your nosebleed stopped now?
Jimbei's message to Luffy was
"Don't fight against Hordy."
Vander Decken's relentless courtship
began right after the Queen's death.
Despite that,
humans kept disliking Fish-Men.
Is that Luffy?! What's that blowfish?
I know what he meant.
The worst time that I experienced was
the beginning of the Great Pirate Era.
Isn't it because it's dangerous?
A human gentleman and...
That's why the Princess couldn't
even attend her mother's funeral
You are going to free the slaves?
I hope Zoro and the others won't make
Hordy mad as they get more involved.
Are you serious?
...a racoon! It looks exactly
the same as in the book!
and has spent last 10 years
in the Hard Shell Tower.
I vividly remember the fear of seeing
human pirates running wild on the island.
In any event, I wanna see Jimbei!
I am serious. I can't take it anymore.
A-Are they your friends, Luffy-sama?
He'll be waiting for Luffy
at the Sea Forest, right?
It's like a living hell
to be a slave isn't it?
They are my crewmembers!
The events happening now
have deep roots in history.
I can't get it off of my mind!
They are?
As we speak now, they are not
being treated like men.
Look! That's their captain!
The things that she
wanted to tell her mother...
They could shake up the whole kingdom!
That straw hat... He's the boss
of the Mermaid kidnappers!
The Fish-Man Island was
taken over by humans.
But...
...kept building up inside
her heart, probably.
I think he knows everything
about what's going on.
My mind is set.
I just wanted to tell you
and the Queen in advance
Boss Jimbei does?
Camie.
And then, the late,
good-old Whitebeard saved us.
I don't want them to see me! Megalo,
close your mouth a little more!
since it will cause you trouble.
Take me to the Sea Forest!
Please don't tell anybody about this.
Luffy!
Uh-huh!
Luffy-chin!
What did you see during your trip?
He claimed the Fish-Man Island as his own
Nami! Camie!
Nami-chin, look!
I'm gonna go down there for a bit!
That's Boss Jimbei who's standing
right by Luffy-chin's side!
What?
and peace returned to the island.
Listen, soldiers!
He came down!
However, it didn't stop humans
from disliking Fish-Men.
I saw humans!
Yes, sir! We'll get rid of Hordy
and his crew immediately!
Hachi! I thought that was you!
Oh?
No-jamon!
Princess Shirahoshi is with them...
I know that you people saw
it at Sabaody Archipelago.
Straw Hat...
Since I can't fight at full power,
you'd be sacrificing your lives for nothing.
What happened to you?! Who did this?!
Shocking!!
Nami! Did the banquet start?
The reality.
He's not saying!
Get off of this island!
--Nami-san!
--H-He's cured completely...
We shall give up the palace for now and
meet up with Fukaboshi and the others
The funny thing is those who seize
power tend to be more afraid of change.
That's all he's been saying!
and wait for a chance to fight back!
But if I'm correct, the pirate--Straw Hat
is occupying the Ryugu Palace now!
Hatchin! What happened to you?!
Give up the palace?
Are you serious, Neptune-sama?!
Even though the Government bridged
the gap between Fish-Men and humans
Camie...
Is that true?! Hordy did it?!
those who held the real power ended up being
much more bigoted than all the others!
They're kidnapping Mermaids! He came to
kidnap more leaving his men at the palace!
Damn Zoro! He thinks he can
beat a Fish-Man in the water?
Uh-huh.
I never thought that such things
could happen at the Ryugu Palace!
Usopp-san, I keep losing my
strength and I'm going to drown soon...
Maybe he's gonna kidnap
Princess Shirahoshi in the end!
And then before long,
something big happened.
The relationship between Fish-Men
and humans remained the same.
What happened to Zoro and the others?!
Don't be ridiculous! That's impossible!
Something's happened!
I don't know. I was gonna
go back as soon as I met you.
You're dead already.
Then, two people rose up on the Fish-Man Island,
to change our hopeless history.
The Princess is a giant
smelt-whiting Mermaid
What is it?!
N-No!
B-Boss Jimbei! T-Tiger-san...
and the God of the Sea--
Neptune's beloved daughter!
That's true...
I can't believe Father-sama
has been caught!
Some people might dream about kidnapping
her, but no one could do it for real.
...attacked the Celestial Dragons!
One was Queen Otohime.
The Celestial Dragons?!
What is that blowfish?
She kept trying to tell the islanders
to live in harmony with humans.
Are you starting to suffer?
Luffy-kun, I'm sorry!
Fisher Tiger's attack on
the Holyland of Marie Jois!
Humans are so disadvantaged under water!
She was Princess Shirahoshi's mother.
I left you the message because I
didn't want to get you into trouble
People called him the hero
who freed the slaves.
And the other is the hero who
freed the slaves - Fisher Tiger.
No!
And at the same time, he became a criminal.
Zoro's gonna pass out!
but I let you get involved already.
Something Tiger... I heard that name before.
Is that what Hordy's up to?
We have to hurry but let me just say,
Calling for parting ways with humans,
he broke an unspoken rule
I'm leaving the army today.
2 years ago when I met Luffy-kun, it was
harder for me to talk about it than it is now.
Jimbei, are you going to
walk away from your mission?!
and invaded the Holyland of Marie
Jois by himself and freed the slaves.
I'm passing out!
Surprisingly, I enjoyed my
role of protecting the island.
Zoro...
I've been feeling very thankful...
Later, he formed the Sun Pirates
with the Fish-Men who were slaves.
...to those people who stopped the Arlong
Pirates running wild in the East Blue.
But sometimes, paying a debt
of honor is more important
than carrying out my mission!
The Sun...?
That was you guys, wasn't it?
What?!
Yes! Me, Arlong, and Hachi joined the...
Big Brother Tai did it at last!
That swordsman's dead!
Thank you! Let me express my gratitude.
How stupid is he? Thinking that a human
can fight against a Fish-Man in the water!
We Arlong Pirates will
join Fisher Tiger now!
And I want to apologize at the same time.
Let's go, guys!
...crew of the Sun Pirates, naturally.
What a pain in the ass. But this is it!
--Oh!
--Huh?!
Jimbei-san...
And that was how the ruffians
from the Fish-Man District
However, having the "Fish-Man Pirates"
who went against the Government...
The person who is responsible for setting
Arlong loose into the East Blue was...
Drop dead, you lowly creature!
who admired him assembled.
Princess Shirahoshi-sama?!
Welcome to the pirates' world!
...made it harder for Queen Otohime to
establish good relations with humans.
Um... Well, uh...
...me!
We'll fight against the world from now on.
Those of you who are ready, come forward!
You found me!
Zoro!
She's big! Don't tell me that that is...
Queen Otohime was trying to weather
great hardships and change the future.
...the Mermaid Princess?
What? Is there anybody behind me?
In order to make it
impossible to distinguish
Fisher Tiger threw his future away
No, Sanji! Don't turn around at any cost!
to save the slaves of his race
who were suffering at the time.
between those who were
slaves and those who weren't,
everybody used the Sun mark to
cover over the mark of slaves...
Huh? What's going on?
No one can say which one was right or wrong.
If you do, you're gonna die, Sanji!
Boss!
One-Sword Style...
Oh, no.
...Lion Strike!
...and the Sun Pirates
were formed by Fish-Men!
Let's talk.
They fought for the future
of Fish-Men and humans.
They were two monumental figures!
They kidnapped the Mermaid Princess!
But what was their hidden angst?!
Angered by the kidnapping
of Princess Shirahoshi,
Queen Otohime tried to
guide the Ryugu Kingdom
Fisher Tiger attacked the
Holyland of Marie Jois
Zoro's group must escape Ryugu Palace
before it fills with water,
Jimbei reveals shocking past events as
Nami recalls her difficult time with Arlong
toward a future where humans and
Fish-Men could live together.
and freed Fish-Man slaves
from the Celestial Dragons.
the terrifying Hammond of
Fish-Man Island captures Luffy.
but the Fish-Men take Energy
Steroids to enhance their strength
Pursued by the Marines, they fight the
humans in battle after bloody battle,
And then, Vander Decken
finally reveals himself!
Things become tense between
the crew and Jimbei.
There was also Fisher Tiger,
a hero who rescued Fish-Man
and gain the upper hand again.
from enslavement by humans.
Can Luffy escape his bonds and safely
take Shirahoshi to the Sea Forest?
until he has a fateful encounter with
a human girl with a painful past.
Jimbei then tells the great
story of two individuals
Meanwhile, Luffy's group has finally
reached Jimbei in the Sea Forest
Their fates intertwined as they imagined
a new future for Fish-Man Island,
And, upon seeing an attractive mermaid,
Sanji is once again in danger!
and he tells them of shocking past events
involving Nami and Arlong.
and an incident that shaped history occurred!
who tried to change the bitter history
between Fish-Men and humans.
And a certain man finally makes his move.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Hero Who Freed the Slaves!
An Adventurer Tiger!"
"The Haunting Ties!
Nami and the Fish-Man Pirates!"
"The Straw Hats Defeated?!
Hordy Gains Control of the Ryugu Palace!"
"Kizaru Appears!
A Trap to Catch Tiger!"
"Keep Shirahoshi Safe!
Decken Close Behind!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!