Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training.
And on their way to the
next stage - the New World,
they reached the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
But they have yet to gather and are
stirring things up as a fragmented crew!
We're gonna restore his dream!
We're the New Fish-Man Pirates!
Shark Grip!
--No! I tell you this is no good!
--What should we do?!
Nami-chin?
Camie, do me a favor!
What?
Zoro! The water is rising!
I have a favor to ask!
Let those two get out of here!
What about you?
No one can get away with
that guy chasing after them!
Don't stand in my way of
conquering this country!
Um... Well, uh...
You found me!
She's big! Don't tell me that that is...
Oh, no.
They kidnapped the Mermaid Princess!
No, Sanji! Don't turn around at any cost!
Huh? What's going on?
If you do, you're gonna die, Sanji!
"Keep Shirahoshi Safe!
Decken Close Behind!"
I'm coming! To wherever my Shirahoshi is!
It's dead or marriage!
P-Princess Shirahoshi has...
...really been...
...kidnapped!
Hey, Coward! Why did you come out of Shark?!
I-I'm sorry! Luffy-sama,
please don't get mad at me!
He made Princess-sama cry!
What an evil pirate!
I feel terrible... Princess Shirahoshi-sama!
Princess...
He said "Princess"! Don't tell me that's...
No, Sanji!
Don't turn around at any cost!
Hey, could it be that the
Mermaid Princess is behind me...
...if I turn around?
Yes, she's there! That's why I don't
want you to turn around, Sanji!
You almost died after seeing
some average Mermaids!
So if you see the Mermaid Princess,
you'll lose all of your blood
and it's curtains for you!
Mermaid Princess...
They say even the most beautiful woman
in the world - Pirate Empress Boa
Hancock's looks pale in comparison.
She is the most gorgeous of all Mermaids.
And now, she's behind my back...
No! I beg you! Don't turn around!
Chopper.
Rather than live a day longer without
grasping at a dream within reach,
I will live out my dream...
...and choose to die!
What?! I thought your dream
was to go to the All Blue!
No!
Sanji!
Huh?
Th-Th-That is...
Now I know how poor my imagination is!
She's magnificent!
That's quite simply...
...a beauty that you can't even draw!
He turned to stone!
Princess Shirahoshi-sama!
We gotta rescue her!
But they're the Straw Hats who are
strong enough to occupy the palace!
I thought he'd die from a nosebleed.
But he turned to stone! That's new.
Maybe because of his blood donors!
L-Luffy-sama, I don't know... what to do...
Hey, are you okay?!
In any case, Hachi, who did this to you?!
Hey, what do you guys want?!
--We caught them!
--The Straw Hats! We did it!
We are sea hunters who risk our lives
to catch the Sea Kings everyday!
Pirates are no match for us!
Don't mess with the sea hunters!
--The Sea hunters did it!
--Great!
You guys are fishermen?! We're not fish!
I remember you, too! You're the punk
who used to be in Arlong's group!
You're safe now, Princess-sama!
Turn them over to the Ammo Knights
so they can cut their heads off!
Um... It's not like that, everybody.
Luffy-sama was not...
Hey guys!
Something's flying towards us! There!
Huh? It's no use--we're not gonna be fooled!
What?! Hey, something's really flying!
Is it just some coral?
No, somebody's on it.
Oh no! That's...
...Vander Decken!
I found you! I suspect!
Shirahoshi!
Vander Decken-sama!
He must've been hiding for a long time
and now he's finally showed himself!
Princess-sama, run! We'll handle this!
I want your answer, Shirahoshi!
If it's "Yes," you can escape death!
You have to...
...marry me!
You've been throwing weapons
at her for 10 years to kill her
and now you wanna marry her?!
Stop messing around, Vander Decken!
The Princess must have feared
death for 10 years because of you!
How dare you propose to her!
I want your answer, Shirahoshi!
I suspect it's "Yes"!
Um...
What do you wanna say?! "Yes"?!
Y...
You're not my type!
What?
No!
What?! Is that the reason?!
Y... Y... Y... Y...
You bitch!
You trampled on my feelings of 10
years and now who will you marry?!
If you don't love me,
your very existence irritates me!
Drop dead, Shirahoshi!
Run, Princess Shirahoshi!
Hurry up! We'll stop him here with our lives!
Don't go anywhere! Stay there, Coward!
What are you saying?!
We can't trust you pirates!
You're Decken's accomplice,
aren't you? You want her to die?!
If you run somewhere, I can't keep you safe!
O-Okay, I'll stay!
Princess-sama!
--How dare you scare her!
--You evil pirate!
Sorry guys. I have nothing
against you but you're...
...in my way!
Second Gear!
Luffy!
He did it with his hands tied!
Why do you wanna interfere with
my business with Shirahoshi?!
Are you the one who took Shirahoshi out?
Are you the one...
...that's been throwing things at Coward?!
I'll kill you both! Let me put you two
together and cut you into quarters!
Try it!
L-Let me go!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
...Hammer!
Th...
That guy...
...beat Vander Decken!
He's still moving but we can catch him now!
Shark! Wake up!
Sanji!
You alright?!
He turned to stone a while ago but
he looks happy now. He's conscious!
Okay, got it.
Mermaid Princess... Am
I in heaven or paradise?
My dream came true! I can die now!
Again, your dream was to go
to the All Blue, wasn't it?
Hurry up, Coward!
O-Okay!
Please don't yell at me.
It makes my heart race.
The people on this island
don't like us for some reason.
We've got to get away from here!
Thank you! Coward! Let's go!
Okay!
P-Princess-sama, why did you untie him?
That evil pirate must've scared her again!
I am sorry, everybody! I
will be back by dinner!
What?
Go Shark!
Get away, you shits!
Don't let them get away!
Wadatsumi!
He looks familiar.
He's the Sea Bonze who attacked
the Sunny! He works for Decken!
--I-It's the Great Monk!
--Wadatsumi!
Stop them!
I got it!
Second Gear!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
...Pistol!
My front tooth...
It cracked!
It hurts! It hurts!
He's good for nothing!
Alright!
Coward, let's get to the Sea Forest!
Yes!
DRAGON
Boss Hordy! A pirate girl and a Mermaid
just exited the Ryugu Palace!
Who cares?
If I can get rid of him,
there will be only an old
fool and a mob to take care of!
Shark Arrows!
Nami-chin, was it okay to leave
Zoro-chin and the others behind?
We couldn't escape with everyone.
That's true, but...
Don't worry! They always make it through!
I know they're all tough.
But Hatchin said that Hordy is not only
strong but has dangerous thoughts, too.
They've gotten much
stronger in last 2 years.
That aside, what kind of person
is Jimbei, the former Warlord?
Huh?
Although he is a pirate,
people on the island trust him so he's
allowed to enter the Ryugu Palace.
I see. But he was in the same pirate
group with Arlong, wasn't he?
That guy--Hordy is a follower of Arlong.
Jimbei's message to Luffy was
"Don't fight against Hordy."
I know what he meant.
Isn't it because it's dangerous?
I hope Zoro and the others won't make
Hordy mad as they get more involved.
In any event, I wanna see Jimbei!
He'll be waiting for Luffy
at the Sea Forest, right?
The events happening now
have deep roots in history.
They could shake up the whole kingdom!
I think he knows everything
about what's going on.
Boss Jimbei does?
Camie.
Take me to the Sea Forest!
Uh-huh!
Listen, soldiers!
Yes, sir! We'll get rid of Hordy
and his crew immediately!
No-jamon!
Since I can't fight at full power,
you'd be sacrificing your lives for nothing.
We shall give up the palace for now and
meet up with Fukaboshi and the others
and wait for a chance to fight back!
Give up the palace?
Are you serious, Neptune-sama?!
Damn Zoro! He thinks he can
beat a Fish-Man in the water?
Usopp-san, I keep losing my
strength and I'm going to drown soon...
You're dead already.
That's true...
Are you starting to suffer?
Humans are so disadvantaged under water!
Zoro's gonna pass out!
Is that what Hordy's up to?
I'm passing out!
Zoro...
That swordsman's dead!
How stupid is he? Thinking that a human
can fight against a Fish-Man in the water!
What a pain in the ass. But this is it!
Drop dead, you lowly creature!
Zoro!
Boss!
One-Sword Style...
...Lion Strike!
Zoro's group must escape Ryugu Palace
before it fills with water,
but the Fish-Men take Energy
Steroids to enhance their strength
and gain the upper hand again.
Meanwhile, Luffy's group has finally
reached Jimbei in the Sea Forest
and he tells them of shocking past events
involving Nami and Arlong.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Straw Hats Defeated?!
Hordy Gains Control of the Ryugu Palace!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!