Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
It's a "guiding light." The entrance to
the Grand Line lies ahead of that light.
In order to find the All Blue!
In order to be King of the Pirates!
In order to become
a master swordsman!
In order to draw a world map!
I-In order...
...to become a brave warrior of the sea!
We're going...
...to the Grand Line!
"Precursor to a New Adventure!
Apis, a Mysterious Girl"
Hey, it's meal time.
Hm?
She's gone?! Hey! Where're you?!
Where're you hiding?!
Hey! It's no use!
It's storming outside!
Just come out!
Ouch!
Ow, ow, ow...
Hey!
I'm telling you, you can't escape.
If you stay put, we won't
do anything to you.
No! Let me go!
--Hey, calm down!
--What're you doing?!
What?! What?!
The girl escaped!
Search the whole ship!
Take her into custody
as soon as you find her!
She's still a child.
Don't be rough on her!
Ow, ow, ow...
There she is!
Capture her!
Hey! Hold it!
--It's dangerous!
--Come down!
We can't have the sail
unfurled like that in this storm!
Please protect me, Grandpa Ryu.
Wh-What're you going to do?!
Ahhh! It's dangerous! Stop it!
Idiots! What is this report?!
That girl may be a clue to the Dragonite
that I've spent years searching for!
Don't you realize how serious this is?!
Y-Yes, sir!
Eric!
I've been here all along.
I can't lose a clue to the elixir of
immortality after I've finally found it.
Go join my fleet and find her
no matter what it takes.
With all due respect,
tracking down someone
wasn't in the contract.
I'll pay you however much you want.
I hired you for a time like this.
Losing a clue now will be a blow
for you as well, will it not?
Now, go!
Understood, Your Excellency,
Commodore Nelson Royal.
Nami! Aren't we in the Grand Line yet?
We just left Loguetown two days ago.
It'll take a few more days.
Wait a little longer.
Okay!
What nice weather!
That storm seems like a dream.
Hm...?
What the heck is that?
Hey! I see a flock of birds to starboard!
--A flock of birds?
--Yeah.
I also see something
kind of big on the water...
I can't see it well.
I wonder what it is.
--Maybe a fish?
--A small boat...?
It could be a big fish, too, but...
I often hear that
seabirds flock above fish.
Fish?!
Luffy! Let's have them for lunch.
Alrighty!
Gum-Gum...
Grab!
Whoa! Now that's a stretch!
His body sure is convenient.
I caught it!
It's pretty big!
Nice, Luffy!
H-Hold on a second...
What're you gonna do now?
Oh... Sorry, Zoro.
Dumbass!!
I'm gonna... cut him down... someday...
Hey, look. That's no fish.
It's a girl!
Oh? Is she a fishperson?
Where's her web?
You idiot. Just how does
she look like a fishperson?
Why was a little girl in
a small boat like that...?
Ouch!
So you've come to?
Seems you're doing
better than I expected.
Does it hurt anywhere?
You must be hungry.
I'm cooking soup right now.
Lucky!
Were you in a ship wreck or something?
You could've been in big trouble.
What's your name?
When you ask someone questions,
you should give your name first.
Good point. My name is Nami.
The one who's cooking soup
in the kitchen is Sanji.
Hi!
The one with a scary face
wearing a bellyband is Zoro.
Shut up.
The one who's unconscious
over there is Usopp. And...
I'm Luffy. I'm the captain
of this pirate ship.
What?!
Pirates?!
We're heading to the Grand Line.
What's wrong?
She isn't moving.
What're we gonna do with this kid?
Ahhh, well, what should we do?
Let's think about it tomorrow.
Why?!
Why? Why? Why? Why in the heck?!
I went through all that trouble and did
scary things to escape from the Navy!
Of all things, why did I get
picked up by a pirate ship?
This isn't funny!
In any case, I'll think about
it after I eat something.
Ouch...
You again?
You never learn no matter
how many times I tell you, Luffy.
Can't you get it
through your thick skull?
Hm? What're you doing?
Yum!
If you ask, I'll make something for you.
So, like I told you,
don't take food without asking.
But I'm hungry.
What's wrong? Aren't you eating?
You didn't eat this afternoon, either.
Why're you holding back?
I'm telling ya, it's not
poisoned or anything.
If you just sit there like that,
he'll finish everything.
If you're not eating, I'll eat it!
--No!
--Huh?
Yum!!
Of course! Sanji's the cook I picked!
I've never eaten anything this good!
--You're finally smiling.
--Oh, Nami-san!
You're eating again, Luffy?!
I didn't eat that much for lunch.
You emptied two pots, didn't you?
I did?
You got scared when you heard
we're pirates, didn't you?
W-Well...
Well, that's a natural reaction
towards pirates these days.
--You're not gonna sell me off?
--No way!
You're all evil-looking, so...
You've got a right
to talk with that face?
What're you doing?!
Ahh! That's enough!
We have more, mademoiselle.
At least, this ship isn't the kind
of pirate ship you're thinking of.
Don't worry.
--Another plate, please!
--As you wish.
--Me, too!
--Do it yourself!
You meanie...
Wo-oah!
--Huh?
--Wh-What happened?
Hey! Just what'd you do?
I was preparing a meal!
What?
Everyone! Breakfast is ready!
Oh, breakfast?!
What breakfast explodes?
--You made this?
--Yep!
It has quite... a unique appearance...
Thanks! I'm digging in!
In addition to rescuing me,
you're feeding me, too.
I'll do anything to help you from now on!
Uh... uhm...
That'll be helpful... Thank you.
Is this really edible?
Stop grumbling and just eat it!
But seriously, is it really safe to eat?
Really? This is good.
That's right. It's possible that
just the appearance is bad.
Really?
W-Was it that bad?
Whoa! That's spicy!
What is this?!
I put in the wrong seasoning!
Well, that's a common mistake.
You'll be fine if you
are careful next time.
Hey, she took the trouble
to prepare it for us.
Eat every crumb!
Shut up! Don't waste this
girl's kindness. This girl's...
Oh, what's your name, by the way?
Apis! My name is Apis!
Apis-chan put her heart into this food!
Plus, I won't allow anyone to waste food!
I'll cook something
for you later, Nami-san.
Thanks.
I'm sorry. I'm not good at cooking...
but I wanted to be helpful!
Don't worry about it.
We really appreciate the thought.
Leave the cooking to me.
There're many other things
that you could help out with.
Okay!
Really? This is good.
You...
I wanna eat barbecue next.
I haven't had it for a while.
Say, why were you
drifting on the sea, Apis?
I escaped from a Navy ship...
From a Navy ship?
...during the stormy
night three days ago...
In that small boat in such a storm...
You're reckless.
So what'd you do in the first place?
What?
You had to escape,
which means you weren't on
their ship as a guest, right?
But then the Navy wouldn't
go after every little villain.
W-Well... uhm...
What? Are you a super villain?
No! There's no way I'd do bad things!
I never did bad things...
but I can't tell you why...
What's that about...?
What's the big deal?
She must have her reasons.
If she doesn't want to say,
then we shouldn't press her.
That's true. But can you at
least tell us where you're from?
What? Oh, yes...
I'm from Warship Island.
Warship Island?
Do you know it?
No. I'll check it out.
Why is it called Warship Island?
It's because the shape of the
island looks exactly like a warship.
Oh, that's interesting.
Ahh! This is the one!
Oh, it's close to the Grand Line.
We're around here right now,
so it's not that far.
--What do you wanna do?
--What?
Do you wanna go
back to Warship Island?
If we keep sailing like this,
we are going to enter the Grand Line.
You were nice enough to save me
and I feel bad burdening you further...
but I want to go back to the island!
I'm sorry. I'm selfish, aren't I?
If you hand me to a ship heading
west on your way if possible,
I'll work things out on my own.
Oh my, that's a real burden!
There's no way that a pirate ship can
get close to another ship so easily.
Yeah, you're right.
But since it's not totally out of our way
and we're not really in a hurry...
--Oh, what the heck?
--What?!
It doesn't matter either way to me.
What should we do, Captain?
Yeah, that sounds fine.
The Grand Line isn't
that far, either, so...
I see. The island looks
like a warship, huh?
--Sounds like they've decided.
--Really?!
Are you really going to stop
by Warship Island for me?!
--Yeah.
--All right! Thank you, Luffy!
All right! All right! I'm so happy!
Thank you very much! Thank you!
Thank you very much, everyone!
To show my appreciation,
I'll prepare lots of dishes every day!
No, that won't be necessary.
Why not?
Reporting!
Ship sighted ahead at 13 o'clock!
It's a mid-size caravel.
I see a flag with a skull
mark on the main mast!
Pirates, huh?
They don't know their own station,
sailing around in the seas
under Commodore Nelson's control.
I'm sure they're just small fries.
Just leave them alone!
No. That flag doesn't
belong to small fries.
If I remember correctly,
that belongs to Straw Hat Luffy,
a man with a 30 million Berry
bounty on his head.
Oh, the ones people have
been talking about lately?
We still can't find the girl
even with this big fleet.
It's possible that someone has her.
Not to mention, pirates of that caliber...
Isn't it going to be a problem if you
leave them be, Lt. Commander?
Capture that ship!
I wonder what this feeling is...
Hey! I see ships
approaching from the rear!
--What?
--Ugh! Oh, man!
--They're Navy ships!
--Navy?!
And it's not just
one or two ships, either!
He's right!
But what's a fleet like that doing here?
What? What? What's going on?
Are they after my head?
That's a lot even for that!
It means that they need that
many to capture me, right?
I'm amazing, aren't I?
How can you be so easygoing?!
Hm...? What's wrong?
Those ships belong to Branch 8!
I escaped from them!
What am I gonna do?
Hm...? There! I found her!
I see the girl on their deck!
What?!
It was just as I said,
wasn't it, Lt. Commander?
Did I hurt your pride?
But if you make a mistake
and lose that girl...
...the clue to the elixir
of immortality, the Dragonite,
I wonder how furious
Commodore Nelson would get.
Prepare the main cannons!
We'll capture that pirate ship!
Ugh! They're firing at us!!
Attention pirate ship!
Stop the ship immediately!
Those were warning shots.
The next shots will hit your ship!
There's no way we'd stop!
What're we gonna do, Luffy? If you
wanna take 'em on, I'm with you.
--Yeah. Why don't we?
--Ahhh! W-Wait a sec!
Why are you guys always like this?!
--What the heck are you
gonna do against that fleet?!
--Apis, go to the cabin downstairs.
--We'll make a raid on them.
--O-Okay...
--A raid isn't gonna work!
--We'll make it work.
--You can't!
We're not saying you have to come.
Back us up with the cannon.
What? So I'm staying on this ship?
Okay, leave it to me!
--And we'll get clear
of them at full speed!
--Hey, Apis. What's the matter?
--You take care of the rest.
--He said a wind is coming.
A strong wind is...
Zoro! Lean the sail towards the south!
Usopp and Sanji-kun,
right rudder full! Hurry up!
--O-Okay.
--Yes, Nami-san!
What's going on?
A gust is coming.
We'll ride it and get out of here.
If we fight them head on,
we'll lose no matter how good we are.
We can take them, though...
This girl...
Their ship shows no signs of stopping.
They're mocking us!
Here goes!
Ahh! The pirate ship sped up
and changed its route!
--What?!
--They're heading south!
South?! How foolish!
Do they know what's in that direction?!
What're you doing, Lt. Commander?!
Go after them! Now!
Whoa! This is fast!
This is a good wind.
Look at that, Luffy!
The Navy's falling behind!
Whoa!
Ha! You guys're slow turtles!
No good! We can't catch up!
A Navy fleet falling behind
such a small ship? Dimwit.
A small ship has better mobility!
I don't wanna hear excuses!
Lt. Commander, this ship will soon...
--Lt. Commander!
--I know!
Stop all the ships!
Prepare to turn around!
Wait, Lt. Commander!
Why are you stopping the ships?
If we keep going,
we'll go into the Calm Belt!
--So what? Go after them!
--No!
You really don't appreciate the
seriousness of this matter, do you?
We can't lose that girl now.
What're you going to say
to Commodore Nelson?!
I'm prepared to take the punishment.
I can't just sit by and let this fleet
and my subordinates
be swallowed by the sea!
No matter what you say,
the chase ends here!
How... foolish...
The Navy isn't following us!
Did Captain Usopp
scare the pants off them?
Amazing! Amazing! Just as
you'd expect from our navigator!
Well done, Nami-san. To think you
detected such a wind beforehand...
Well, it was like an instinct, though.
Oh, Nami-san is lovely
when she's humble, too.
Well then, shall we head
straight to Warship Island?
--Really?!
--Yeah, really.
Okay, then! To Warship Island, let's...
...go!!
What's wrong, Zoro?
You've had a serious look
on your face for a while.
Well, I hope it's just my imagination.
What is?
I feel like this ship hasn't
been moving at all for a while.
What?
Come to think of it, the sail
isn't catching any wind at all...
Ah!
What's wrong, Nami?
Nami-san...?
Dammit...
We've entered the Calm Belt!!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
What's the Calm Belt?
We'll head straight to Warship Island!
Ahhh!
He always makes us do reckless things!
Say, don't you think Apis
has an air of secrecy about her?
Hey, look at that!
Something incredible's there!
Th-That's...!
On the next episode on One Piece!
"Miraculous Creature! Apis's Secret
and the Legendary Island."
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!