Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi,
are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
Then, two people rose up on the Fish-Man Island,
to change our hopeless history.
One was Queen Otohime.
And the other is the hero who
freed the slaves - Fisher Tiger.
Let's talk. They were two
monumental figures!
But what was their hidden angst?!
"A Hero Who Freed the Slaves!
An Adventurer Tiger!"
I'm going to tell you about...
...an incident that made Arlong
rampage through the East Blue.
I want you especially to know about this.
Alright.
It all began...
...16 years ago.
16 YEARS AGO - THE FISH-MAN ISLAND
Outta my way!
Thief!
Somebody, catch him!
He stole a lot of money!
Hey, outta my way!
I-If anyone comes close, you won't
wanna see what I'll do with this girl!
Your Majesty?
Oh, Your Majesty! Wait!
Don't get involved with such a thing!
That's our responsibility!
--Wait!
--Queen Otohime!
Who is that?!
Stay away! Or I'll shoot you!
I-I warned you!
Did I miss?
Dammit! Stay away!
I got you!
KING NEPTUNE'S WIFE
QUEEN OTOHIME (GOLDFISH MERMAID)
It's... Otohime-sama!
--Ouch!
--Really?!
--My hand!
--Doctor!
Your Highness! Let me see it!
It's a compound fracture.
With one hit?!
I don't mind!
Queen Otohime!
Queen?
Why have you done such a senseless
thing as robbing someone?!
Shut up! You're from a wealthy,
royal family - you don't understand!
I have 10 kids at home,
who are crying from hunger!
All the more reason to not do it!
Q-Queen-sama! Stop hitting him!
You're far more fragile than all of us!
I don't care! I have to do this for him!
I have to teach him even if it
shatters my hand into pieces!
Would your children be happy
being raised by stolen money?!
Live a life of which your
children can be proud!
However...
I have to... apologize, as well!
I'm sorry!
I didn't notice your struggles
even though I'm your queen and
I'm living in the same country!
Your worries and your pain are killing me!
You must have had some awful
reason to do what you did...
I didn't want to do it!
But I had no choice!
My store burned down.
Somebody set fire to it and stole all my money!
I lost my job and my debts were increasing.
And my poor kids were starving!
So that's why you did it. I understand...
I understand how you feel...
--But you can't do that!
--What?!
If you do the same thing to others,
it will never stop!
I'm sorry!
But I'm sorry! We are guilty
of not being dependable...
That's very generous...
That's very generous of you to say...
But you can't do that!
I'm sorry!
But you can't!
I will change my life!
Thank you for crying for a
good-for-nothing like me, Queen-sama!
Don't mention it. Good luck!
It's already unusual for someone from
the royal family to come out of the palace
and walk around...
But to slap a citizen and sob over his story!
Otohime-sama is a very
unconventional queen.
She's a woman of boundless compassion.
Look, even kids love her!
Otohime-sama!
Oh!
I will do my best for you children!
What?!
Your nose is running!
I hit you for your own good!
You look like a fool having
snot running out of one nostril.
It's better to have to come from both sides.
How touching!
Yeah?
She was so passionate and
full of love. Queen Otohime...
...went down to the island everyday
and addressed the nation.
We have to relocate the
Ryugu Kingdom on earth!
We have a different skin color.
We look different.
That's what humans say. And instead of waiting
for the day when they'll understand us,
we should move closer to
them to understand them!
The seafloor is 10,000 meters from the land.
That is also the distance
between our ways of thinking.
Don't get the wrong idea!
The humans who come to this island
are the kind called "pirates."
And the humans who buy people from
kidnappers are the Nobles who are in power.
We've only known the bad sort of humans.
We don't know anything about humans yet.
There are so many kind
humans on earth, I assume.
We should relocate the
kingdom under the same sun!
Let's express our intention to
relocate at the World Summit this year!
I need you all to sign here!
Well, even if it's Otohime-sama's idea...
The idea of moving closer
to humans is... Right?
Don't say that.
Let's take the first step
instead of doing nothing.
Well?
I'm sorry.
It's no use. History has proven it.
I'm home, kids!
Welcome home, mother-sama!
I'm home, Shirahoshi!
Oh, Shirahoshi, my consolation.
I'm sorry to be late.
Oh, your nose is running
but you're beautiful!
We were here with her so
she was safe, mother-sama!
She was safe, she was safe!
Thank you, my princes.
Mother-sama, is your hand okay?
It's nothing.
The future that you four will live in,
I will change it!
If Otohime-sama wants to make a speech,
she could do it by video.
Her strong Observation Haki by
nature makes her the way she is-jamon.
She prefers to face people to win their hearts
rather than speak from the palace above.
That's one of Otohime's guiding principles.
And not even I can stop her.
But there are a lot of human
pirates staying on the island.
She is protected by your friend, the pirate
- Whitebeard's influence to some extent...
but you never know what could happen!
She knows that, too.
The world that Otohime dreams about is...
...exactly the same as...
...what our ancestors dreamed about
but couldn't make come true
several hundred years ago-jamon.
What do you mean by that?
I can't stop Otohime.
Be sure to keep her safe!
Yes, sir!
Hey, fish girl!
--Yes?
--Stay here and serve us!
I'm sorry. We don't do that sort of thing.
Huh? Don't be such a snob!
You're just a Fish-Man!
What? Does anyone have something to say?
Shut your mouth!
You make my sake taste bad.
O-Okay...
THE RYUGU KINGDOM - A SOLDIER OF NEPTUNE'S ARMY
JIMBEI     30 YEARS OLD
So Otohime-san was a very unusual woman.
You're a crybaby just like your mother, huh?
Well... I-I don't know...
Were you a soldier of the kingdom?
There weren't that many options for
a man from the Fish-Man District...
...who knew nothing but fighting.
The Fish-Man District?
That's where you're from, right, Hachi?
Sounds like a bad neighborhood.
Yes. It used to be a big orphanage where they
housed children without any relatives.
But the orphanage started
to get out of control
and was too much for the
administrators to handle
so it became a lawless area that drew
misfits from all over the island.
Fisher Tiger was the leader
figure in the Fish-Man District
but he left the country to chase adventure.
And I was his lieutenant but
I joined Neptune's army.
Macro and the others became kidnappers
even though they were Fish-Men themselves.
And all the others went
their separate ways as well.
But one day...
--Give them back! Please!
--Take them if you want them!
Give them back to her! Do you know
how many signatures there are?
I don't care!
What can you do with these papers? Huh?!
Hey! Cut it out! You're Arlong from
the Fish-Man District, aren't you?!
Arlong from the Fish-Man District?
L-Let go of me!
You're a bit wrong.
THE CAPTAIN OF THE ARLONG PIRATES
ARLONG 25     YEARS OLD
I'm Captain Arlong from the Arlong Pirates!
I make a living by hunting those lowly
pirates who can't even breathe in water.
We're doing it on behalf of
all of you - Neptune's army!
Thank me with your money!
B-Boss Jimbei, don't just watch - help me!
Jimbei?
Hey, punk! Let go of that rookie soldier.
He is my man, in a way.
And the papers with signatures.
I have no interest in them but they're
important for the Queen. So give them back.
--That's Boss Jimbei of Neptune's army!
--Great!
"Boss"? That's a good title.
Sounds like you're running a gang!
Do as I say, Arlong!
Alright. Here.
Here!
Don't be mad, brother.
What? Brother?
It's been a while, huh? I'm your
family from the Fish-Man District!
I'm not like you.
You're still a pirate, aren't you, scum?
--Don't call me "scum," brother!
--How about trash?
"Trash"?! I've let you say
what you wanted, but that's...
Hey, everybody! It's the
adventurer - Fisher Tiger-san!
--What?
--Tiger-san's back!
--Tiger-san!
--How was the trip?
--Brother Tai!
--Big Brother!
Jimbei! Arlong!
Looks like you guys are doing fine!
It was a long trip, wasn't it?
Yeah, a lot happened.
Stop by at my ship!
Maybe later. I need to go
to the Ryugu Palace first.
I'll take you then.
He doesn't have use for a pirate!
Huh? Big Brother wouldn't say such a thing!
Guys, don't fight!
You are going to free the slaves?
Are you serious?
I am serious. I can't take it anymore.
It's like a living hell
to be a slave isn't it?
As we speak now, they are not
being treated like men.
But...
My mind is set.
I just wanted to tell you
and the Queen in advance
since it will cause you trouble.
Please don't tell anybody about this.
What did you see during your trip?
I saw humans!
And then before long,
something big happened.
Something's happened!
What is it?!
B-Boss Jimbei! T-Tiger-san...
...attacked the Celestial Dragons!
The Celestial Dragons?!
Fisher Tiger's attack on
the Holyland of Marie Jois!
People called him the hero
who freed the slaves.
And at the same time, he became a criminal.
I'm leaving the army today.
Jimbei, are you going to
walk away from your mission?!
Surprisingly, I enjoyed my
role of protecting the island.
But sometimes, paying a debt
of honor is more important
than carrying out my mission!
Big Brother Tai did it at last!
We Arlong Pirates will
join Fisher Tiger now!
Let's go, guys!
And that was how the ruffians
from the Fish-Man District
who admired him assembled.
Welcome to the pirates' world!
We'll fight against the world from now on.
Those of you who are ready, come forward!
In order to make it
impossible to distinguish
between those who were
slaves and those who weren't,
everybody used the Sun mark to
cover over the mark of slaves...
...and the Sun Pirates
were formed by Fish-Men!
Fisher Tiger attacked the
Holyland of Marie Jois
and freed Fish-Man slaves
from the Celestial Dragons.
Pursued by the Marines, they fight the
humans in battle after bloody battle,
until he has a fateful encounter with
a human girl with a painful past.
And a certain man finally makes his move.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Kizaru Appears!
A Trap to Catch Tiger!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!