Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
I can't stand still, I can't stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
If you want to go to
the unbelievable world
your toughness, that's what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
At any cost, One Piece,
I'll be the first
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
It's important not to wake up
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won't left anyone behind
Keep going forward, that's our pledge
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I'm
aiming at hasn't changed
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
Luffy reunited with Toriko and his friends
when he popped out of a Spring Shark.
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
The group headed to Chinese Tower Island,
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
an island full of healthy
foods and natural cures,
in search of Seafood Fruit to cure
Chopper's illness, Deep Sea Fever.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
They worked together to defeat
the fierce beasts on the island
and found the Seafood Fruit,
which they fed to Chopper.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
However...
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
Chopper's illness
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
was not cured.
and his friends venture into that sea.
Chopper!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
"A Team is Formed! Save Chopper"
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level.
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
where the New Fish-Man Pirates - who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
where the New Fish-Man Pirates
Meeting Jimbei again at the Sea Forest,
Isn't there anything we can do?
who are looking to destroy
the Ryugu Kingdom...
Well, since we don't know what caused it...
Luffy learns about the Fish-Man Island
...assisted by Vander Decken,
who is after Shirahoshi,
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi,
are engaging in secret maneuvers.
along with Nami, Sanji, Chopper,
Franky and the others.
are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
It's okay to cry!
Meeting Jimbei again at the Sea Forest,
If I join the Warlords,
Why...
Don't think that we're like
those stupid Celestial Dragons!
Why is the Sunny here?!
Luffy learns about the
Fish-Man Island along with
Aladdin and the others who
don't want to be pirates...
We flew here with the Coup de Burst.
...can live in this country
without being chased
Nami, Sanji, Chopper,
Franky and the others.
Boss!
These guys said there was a sea
in the middle of the island.
Look closely.
under the amnesty of the Government.
"The Sun Pirates Split! Jimbei vs. Arlong!"
Big Brother is dead!
Coco! Sunny!
We'll go our own way, just like we used to!
"Kizaru Appears!
A Trap to Catch Tiger!"
Rin!
What?
The Sun Pirates split into three groups
We won't kill anybody!
And even Kiss?!
And so that was how the captain of
the Sun Pirates - Fisher Tiger died.
Toriko! I was so worried!
We'll take her...
and went separate ways.
Why are you guys here?
Fisher Tiger's attack on
the Holyland of Marie Jois
My fortune told me that
danger was coming your way.
...to her hometown!
"The Death of the Hero!
A Shocking Truth of Tiger!"
and the Sun Pirates' raid - those events...
I thought it must be about
you or Komatsu-kun, but...
"Shaking Fish-Man Island! A
Celestial Dragon Drifts In!"
The captain's death.
It looks like I was wrong.
...had such impact on Fish-Men's future.
I think you all must know
how painful it was...
The Sunny!
Yay! It's magnificent!
THE FISH-MAN ISLAND
And it flies! Beautiful!
We finally got an Eternal
Pose to Koala's hometown!
12 YEARS AGO - THE GRAND LINE
The name "The Sunny" is truly fantastic!
...for the crew who were left behind.
I'm back!
Nyu! Koala, you can go back to your home!
I still can't believe that this day has come!
We didn't talk much last
time, so I didn't notice,
Um...
15 YEARS AGO
When we were the Celestial Dragons' slaves,
but you're one weird-looking guy.
we were hopeless and all we
had was hatred toward them.
I don't want to hear that from
a guy with swirly eyebrows!
I can't believe my eyes.
You've changed a lot!
I can't believe that he really did it.
We got away from the Celestial
Dragons thanks to Boss Tai
What'd you say?!
KOALA (THE FORMER SLAVE GIRL)
You look like a girl now!
What are you going?!
"Don't kill humans"?!
but still they were looking for us.
I don't normally wear these...
It put the Fish-Man Island
in a bad position again.
I thought being a pirate was
the only way to survive.
See what happens when
you show mercy to them?!
This is... Deep Sea Fever?
You know it?
We won't be welcomed at the
World Summit for a while.
But now we can even go back to
our hometown without hiding!
What? We bought them for you
but you don't like them?
Yes. I heard about it in
Life, the nation of healing.
Brother Tai was a fool!
Now, what should we do?
We are free!
First, you turn cold and
blue, like the deep sea.
You got your hair cut, too.
Your mother will be really happy.
Arlong-san!
But we couldn't stop him that day.
In the terminal stage, you turn
red hot, like the burning sun.
Captain! No, Brother Jimbei!
I...
I'll never forget what you've done for us!
What did you see during your trip?
I should clean.
It peaks at sunrise...
Don't be so dramatic.
Nyu! You need to stop working
when you don't know what to do!
Arlong-san!
I won't, but we know what you did.
And as the sun comes up,
Arlong-san!!
I saw humans!
death comes with it.
You needed the amnesty of the
Government to help free us.
This is not Marie Jois!
Because I could hear that the
scream from his soul so loudly.
Leave her alone.
That's why you joined the Warlords.
I won't forgive them at any cost!
She needs time.
We only have a few hours until sunrise!
THE SHIP'S DOCTOR OF THE SUN PIRATES
ALADDIN
Trauma can't be healed that easily.
It's not as though you wanted to join them.
Quit this chatting and go
to your family already!
This is terrible!
Alright.
You understand her very
well, Brother Aladdin.
Well, there is a way to save him.
You need the legendary Seafood Fruit to—
Look! They're becoming impatient.
Because you were a slave yourself.
We tried that!
--Honey...
--Dad!
Just eating the fruit isn't enough.
But wouldn't you rather kill her right now?
Get ready, you bastards!
--Baby...
--Just go to them.
Extra, extra! Read all about it!
Spring, summer, autumn, winter.
You're the Fish-Man...
She's a human just like
the one who owned you!
He showed up the Celestial Dragons
who no one dares challenge!
He must eat the legendary ingredient
of each of the four seasons together.
--Dad!
--Honey!
Stop it, Arlong!
Fisher Tiger - the hero
of the Fish-Man Island!
Legendary ingredient of each season?
Tell us the truth.
What did your mother tell you?
Yes. The one said to be hardest to obtain
Wow! A Fish-Man changed history!
Aladdin, you were a slave just like them.
So noisy!
Your parents looked down
on Fish-Men, didn't they?
Listen to me, everyone!
But now you can get off of the ship finally.
is the Mango Karin that blooms in spring.
--Oh, that's Queen Otohime!
--Her again?
Mango Karin?!
Jimbei.
We will no longer be chased
as renegade slaves.
A sweet flower that tastes
like mango pudding,
We have been cowering, hiding and running.
That's how human society is!
also called the "spring pudding"
that heralds the coming of spring.
All of us can stay with family without fear.
You're Arlong, aren't you?
But we have learned nothing from it.
They think that they're
the best race in the world.
I hear its sweet flavor works as a
revitalizing tonic that cures exhaustion!
What brought you here?
Why did you come back so...
But just like the mark
of the Celestial Dragons,
If we cut all humans off because of
the actions of only a few bad ones,
Their children are spoiled
by watching their example.
I wanna eat one!
because of our terrible experience as
slaves, our hatred toward humans...
Toriko-san, you're drooling! You're drooling!
It won't stop until somebody destroys them!
there will be no future for the Fish-Men!
It blooms in spring? Wait a minute!
Now, let's live together with humans!
You mean we have to go to Spring
Island and Winter Island now?
THE NAVY HQ VICE ADMIRAL
BORSALINO (FUTURE ADMIRAL KIZARU)
...will never go away!
I suppose you guys have seen it enough
while we were sailing these past 3 years.
Learn about them under the bright sun!
We can't do that in just a few hours!
...nonchalantly?
I'm gonna kill all the people
who betrayed Big Brother Tai!
Of course I understand what
Brother Tai truly meant...
It's all right.
Their disrespectful
contemptuous look when they see us.
--Learn about them?
--Yeah, I feel sorry for her but...
This is Chinese Tower Island,
home of healthy foods and natural cures.
I'm gonna go to that island too!
I don't know what I would've done
to them if the Boss wasn't there.
Let us go verify the legend
handed down on this island!
But...
You two right there!
So you're seeking revenge?
That's right! Fisher Tiger is dead!
I can't believe that Boss Jimbei
Sign here!
I-I can't, Otohime-sama!
Seal
is becoming a tool of the
World Government... or humans!
You lowly creatures killed him!
The whole island is applauding
Tiger-san for what he did.
Are these four ingredients
really in a place like this?
Oh I see, he's dead.
Did he forget who killed Tiger-san?
It might cause a rift
between us and the humans.
That was only a few of them.
But you need to come with me now.
I've lost respect for Boss Jimbei.
Terry, you sense it, too?
But, after all, it's their fault,
of course. So I can't...
I thought so. I can sense powerful
electromagnetic waves here.
--The others didn't look like that.
--Brother Jimbei...
I knew that there were many islanders
Even though it's impossible now,
think about 7 years or 11 years or 15 years from now.
Toriko! This is definitely the place!
Everytime I see them,
they all look terrified to me.
Enraged by Fisher Tiger's death,
who didn't like the idea
of me joining the Warlords.
Okay! We just have to get it out
from under the earth, right?
Arlong lashed out against
humans and he was imprisoned.
Plan for the day that we will be able to
participate in the World Summit again.
Nail Punch!
Is it because we're pirates?
Please! Sign here! Please!
He could've survived if he hadn't
been refused a transfusion.
THE RYUGU PALACE
Why are you so afraid of us?
How great! Fisher Tiger!
THE FISH-MAN DISTRICT
Fisher Tiger didn't have to die
if there was Fish-Man's blood.
Thanks to Jimbei's momentous decision,
He was leader in this town!
now we have a relationship
with the World Government.
Because I don't know you folk.
He made the Celestial Dragons mad!
You humans killed him!
HORDY JONES
In order to use this opportunity to
establish friendly relations with humans,
The Celestial Dragons!
If you don't know someone,
you naturally fear them?
He sure showed those annoying humans!
"Fisher Tiger,
the Captain of the Sun Pirates,
I will keep trying hard!
Arlong-san always said
that humans were all jerks!
We've only known the bad sort of humans.
Dies After Being Denied a
Transfusion of Human Blood."
But even if it's for his friends,
We don't know anything about humans yet.
I can't believe Jimbei took
on such a big burden-jamon.
Not too far from the truth.
They're lowly creatures!
The Sun Pirates are pummeling humans
as they sail around the sea now-dosun!
When he gets an order from
the World Government,
So getting to know someone
would change something?
The cause of his death was related to humans.
This is...
he has no choice but to fight...
Wow!
Arlong told the Navy a lie...
Nyu. Hey, Koala.
Cool-dosun!
It's a huge mushroom tower!
...whether he likes it or not-jamon.
If we were stronger,
we could've gone with them-ch!
What?
The truth was far more tragic.
Guess which hand it's in.
He will put himself in
harm's way and occasionally
I see.
Tiger was betrayed by humans so he
refused their blood because he had
Awesome! It's so cool!
I wanna do it too, someday!
Well, where is it now?
This is "Mush Room."
his blood will be spilled.
Go, Sun Pirates! Kill all the humans!
I know.
Um... This one.
Mushroom?
I won't let Jimbei's sacrifice end up wasted.
hard feelings against them.
Mush Room is a tower divided into four rooms,
Plus, he was a slave.
Winter
Autumn
Summer
Spring
Nope! It's here!
I have to do my best, as well!
Yeah!
If that became public,
it would have stained Boss' honor.
with a different season on each floor.
But don't push yourself too hard.
Alright, one more time.
So we just have to get the seasonal
ingredients from each floor, right?
That's why Arlong told a lie.
Nyu. Get it right this time.
Because I don't want you to
suffer another hangover-jamon!
Boss! Boss! There's an enemy ship-nyu!
Uh-huh.
What's something like this doing underground?
Oh...
Where is it?
Boss! Boss! Boss!
This island's name
Chinese Tower Island
This one.
means "an island of Chinese with a tower."
Boss Tai! We have a crisis!
Wrong again!
And then something happened that would
Captain Jimbei! There is an enemy ship!
Shut up, Hachi!
This tower is the core, the center,
Even without the Boss,
there is no turning back now!
change Queen Otohime's life forever.
of the island.
Why don't you calm down a bit?
But you people certainly are
knowledgeable about foodstuffs.
An uninvited visitor came to the island...
Prepare for action!
How disturbing. Is it the Navy?
How very heartening!
Don't kill anybody!
Nyu! I saw the Navy's banner!
Ryugu Kingdom! Ryugu Kingdom!
Toriko-san, Coco-san, and Sunny-san
Yeah!
This is border patrol speaking!
What should we do, Boss?
are among the Four Heavenly Kings of Gourmet.
A huge wrecked ship is seeking
emergency entry into the country!
They're the cream of the Gourmet Hunter crop!
I start identifying myself as
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei
Four Heavenly Kings?
Then is there not one more?
That's a silly question!
What are you waiting for?!
Accept them already...
There is no mistake!
Those are the Sun Pirates!
and as the captain of the Sun Pirates,
It can't be true!
Zebra is...
Kill Tiger!
I did nothing but fight, day in and day out.
...is prison right now.
A Celestial Dragon is on board!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
THE FISHMAN ISLAND - THE RYUGU PALACE
What?!
You missed!
"I am writing this because..."
King Neptune!
"...I thought that you two deserved
to know the whole truth."
A Celestial Dragon?!
Accept them!
Shoot them!
Nami! Take care of Chopper!
--Send a rescue team immediately!
--Yes, ma'am!
"The Sun Pirates captain - Jimbei."
Right! These two are here,
too, so we'll be fine!
I'll meet them myself!
What are you doing?! Shoot at them!
Otohime-sama!
Leave it to us!
My mind is set.
What is a Celestial Dragon
doing on the seafloor?
But it's hard when they're in the water!
Okay! Ready to go?
I guess Tiger had no choice but
to live the way he did-jamon.
Yeah!
It's a Celestial Dragon's ship!
Now I understand what was going
through his mind that day.
Must've been attacked by
some deep-sea creature.
They look down on us Fish-Men.
How come they were in such deep water?
Just as Koala was fitting in so well.
Hurry up!
That's when we arrived at Foolshout
Island - where she came from.
It's hot...
This is like the tropics!
Damn! They are all dead! What weaklings!
So this is the summer floor, huh?
THE GRAND LINE - FOOLSHOUT ISLAND
Koala, get off of the ship.
Oh no.
I'll be alright! I will not give in!
Bring me a breathing mask now, you fishes!
This is your home island.
But why is it so bright
when there are no windows?
You Fish-Man bastards!
Return all the slaves!
A WORLD NOBLE (CELESTIAL
DRAGON) SAINT MYOSGARD
We shall live under the sun!
Oh, that's because of the Light Mushrooms
growing on the walls and ceiling.
I can't stand this Fish-man's smell!
The day that humans and we
understand each other will come!
Then the charges against you will...
--Where is your home village?
--Huh?
Sign here to show that you want to relocate!
--I'll walk you to the entrance to the village.
--Uh-huh!
R-Rear Admiral-dono!
Th-They're coming from below...
Bring me a mask now!
Komatsu, you okay?
Hurry up and save my life, you fools!
That's impossible, Otohime-sama!
We just can't!
This heat is nothing compared
to Chopper-san's fever!
Don't go, Koala! Come with us!
What?!
Humans refused to help
Tiger-san who saved slaves
He has no respect of us!
You're a good girl even
though you're a human.
That's not how you ask somebody to help you!
of all races without discrimination!
Stop crying, you guys.
You fools!
Banjyan Tiger (Mammal Beast) Capture Level 29
How could we understand them?!
Just give us back the slaves.
What you guys are doing is a serious crime!
Doctor!
I'll tell everybody in the village...
I need a doctor!
S-S-Something jumped out!
--Is a medical team here?
--They're here but...
Another day without any signature.
How dare you turn against humans!
You guys are only Fish-Men!
...that there are so many good Fish-Men!
Oh, a Banjyan Tiger, huh?
...they don't know what to do with "it."
It's said that you can harvest rich,
ripened chili paste from them.
We have to kill him.
What did you say?
Mother-sama!
My sweet babies!
Let's hear...
Thank you, everybody!
They are the scum of the world!
Let's hear you say that again!
Goodbye!
The Banjyan Tiger is the first ingredient.
Mother-sama, are you okay?
The Seven Warlords are nothing!
Oh?
Help...
Are you okay? Are you okay?
I'm not gonna work for the World Government
Poison Rifle!
You look very tired.
Slavery is okay but
freeing slaves is a crime?
Hey, take care of yourself!
or anybody, even if they beg me to!
You're my consolation!
That's our Captain Vander Decken!
And you still want us to give
humans a chance, Queen Otohime?
We don't have much time.
But I'm fine!
Jimbei is no match for me as
a pirate in the first place,
Perhaps we should split up and
visit each floor in groups?
Mother-sama!
I agree!
no match at all, I suspect!
I promise you...
Then I'll head upstairs!
...a great future!
What? You, too?!
Hm? What's going on at the harbor?
You two are so compatible!
Queen Otohime was working
so hard day after day.
Hey.
We are not!
Captain, he said that a
Celestial Dragon is here.
Luffy-san! Everyone! Leave this floor to us!
Celestial Dragon?
Shoot! Shoot!
Looks like his ship has wrecked
and he's asking for help.
Shoot at him! We got a tip!
Rescuing humans from shipwrecks...
I'm sure she'll grow up into a
mean-spirited human like the others.
Why is it chasing me?!
You guys are hiding the former slaves!
Sounds like fun. Let's go see it.
What did you just say?!
--Are you alright?!
--It was pirates again.
And up...
Jimbei!
No way!
--Help me...
--Of course, we will help you.
Is this the autumn floor?
The former slaves?
Arlong, you bastard...
This wasn't how it was supposed to be...
A-Are you a monster?!
Brother Jimbei.
You've changed a lot in last 3 years.
Let's take them to the island!
What?! The Fish-Man slaves
went back to their island?!
Toriko! Leave this one to me!
Teaching the island children
about the world above...
I'll stay here, too!
What?
Why is it, My Daddy?
Think about it. What's the point in her
telling people that Fish-Men are nice?
Like I taught you yesterday, this is
an area with many trees called forest.
You guys really are compatible!
Here is the thing, My Son.
I told you, we are not!
A Fish-Man named Jimbei just
joined the Seven Warlords.
Do you have any proof that
we are hiding the slaves?
Forest? The Sea Forest?
Don't copy me! I'm staying
on this floor with Rin-chan!
It's like Otohime's speeches,
her voice will just ring hollow.
Collecting signatures...
Check all of us. I heard all the
slaves have a mark on their body.
No, no! I decided at the start
that I would stay on this floor!
Jimbei?
Wait!
And the Sun Pirates which he belongs
to were hiding all those slaves
I have a personal interest
in the ingredient here!
It'll only take a minute!
Do you see it?!
What ingredient is that?
It sounds interesting.
L-Let go of me! Stop! What are you doing?!
but their evasion charges were
dropped by the amnesty of the
However...
Okay, we'll leave it to you!
She's back!
Help me!
Government so they went back home, My Son.
He's right! Your daughter is back!
Toriko! It seems the ingredient you
can get on the next floor is sake!
Queen Otohime!
I think the slaves who escaped from
my place are among them, My Daddy.
Oh, you folk are the ones
who signed it, aren't you?
Got it, Rin! Take care of this floor!
--I'm so glad!
--Yeah...
Toriko asked me to take care of it!
Everybody!
Don't worry, I'll let you go.
I'm not like you humans.
I'm sure of it.
Well? What are we gonna see here?
We need to ask you a favor.
Hurry up! She came back!
How many signatures have you got so far?
It makes me sick to think
that they are living a
Huh?
Koala? Koala!
Have you heard of unicorns?
Guys! Take their money,
goods and food, and get back to the ship!
I have been doing this for 5 years
free and easy life now.
Unicorn? You mean the horse with
the single horn on the forehead?
I'm gonna go get them back, My Daddy!
but on about 100 sheets of paper
there are 10 signatures each.
Mom...
Yes. It is beautiful!
Because I've spent a lot of money
to collect those Fish-Man slaves!
Which means there are 1000 supporters.
The unicorn is a mythical
horse of many legends.
You deserve execution.
Being human is itself a sin.
The population of the Fish-Man Island is
5 million so, to be honest, I'd prefer more...
The creature we'll see here is not a unicorn,
Gee! I didn't know that the deep
sea was such a horrifying place.
Wait, Arlong!
Drop dead!
but an eight-horned beast: an Octohorn!
Now, here is what we have to ask you.
Koala!
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Mom! Mom!
I can't wait!
We're afraid we want to withdraw
our signatures - which amount to
Vice Admiral Borsalino.
MARINEFORD--THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
G2 branch - Rear Admiral Kadar's
ship has been defeated.
You mean that thing?
Mom!
about half of what you have.
Oh? Why did they even fight them?
What?
You haven't heard yet?
The pirates who arrived the other day...
Octohorn (Eight-Horned Boar)
(Mammal Beast) Capture Level 29
Mom!
I just wanted to know where they were.
It has an eight-horned herb on its head.
It's been a while, huh? Myosgard.
That is the captain of the Sun Pirates...
It's said if you get
close enough to see them,
...committed a robbery in this
town and got away from the island.
How dare you address me without my title! Oh?
Fisher Tiger!
Wh-What?!
they'll surround you in the
water before you know it.
He's a bad man, isn't he?
Because he's a Fish-Man...
What is this?!
Oh, that's scary! They aren't known as
undersea professionals for nothing.
Shh!
Oh, you were my slaves!
I-It's not what I imagined at all!
It must've been painful
and hard being a slave!
So, what are we up against?
Nah, you just made up that image yourself.
You just have to come home with me!
Queen Otohime...
Queen Otohime!
I didn't give you my permission
to be free, fishes!
Well, it looks like Arlong and his men,
Oh kids! Do you want to hear
about the world above?
But Mom, not everybody was
like the Celestial Dragons!
who are conducting raids around
the Fish-Man island, are among them.
Um... My mom wants the paper
that I signed the other day!
What?
I thought Fish-Men were all terrible
but there were so many nice Fish-Men!
But they're always in water so it's
hard to tell how strong they are.
D-Don't do it, guys!
It's c-c-cold!
He's a Celestial Dragon!
This cold really has a kick!
If you kill him, the
amnesty will become void!
Arlong... Yes, I've heard about him before.
My mom wants it!
It does...
Don't do it, fools! Know your place!
But how is there a blizzard indoors?
That's because you're only a child.
And they said there is a man
Who do you think I am?!
No! I know it because I was with Uncle
Tiger and the others all this time!
There's probably warm air coming
from somewhere, causing convection.
What do you want?
who is as big as Tiger and just as
formidable but we don't even know his name.
I'm... I'm...
I listened to you because you're the Queen...
The Navy admirals will come to the aid of a
Oh, that's not good.
You would think so too
if you'd lived with them!
Celestial Dragon in danger
in the world above.
Is that the cause?
But we have problems with humans...
Ouch!
That's why people are afraid of your folk.
We don't wanna...
So what? It's not so big a deal to get rid
of one or two of those lowly creatures!
But you're on the Fish-Man
Island at the seafloor.
...Hear your speech anymore.
Huh?!
Uncle!
As long as the islanders stay quiet,
whatever happens to you here,
Something's there!
Uncle Tiger!
We are tired of it.
You two are going too far, don't you think?
An orangutan wearing clothes!
they'll think it was an accident.
Thank you for keeping your promise!
Has it adapted human customs?!
We're not a group of killers.
Stop acting like fools!
He's right...
--I won't say anything!
--Me too! Of course!
Wait, it looks like it's drunk!
But Brother Tai - I mean, "Boss!"
They're all trying to kill you!
Welcome home, Mother-sama!
I'll never forget you - Uncle Tiger...
He's barely alive. He's
gonna die soon anyway!
...and Hachi-san,
Aladdin-san and all of the Sun Pirates...
This smell is...
Let him suffer the same
way that you slaves did!
I worked so hard today! I'm home, my angels!
Raochu!
If that's what they want, we might
go a little too far! It makes us mad!
That's the Raochu Spring,
erupting with raochu!
--Kill him!
--Make him suffer!
...for the rest of my life!
I think I overdid it...
Could you leave me alone for today?
Show him no mercy!
If you kill somebody, it's your loss!
Do you want to be like them?
What's going on?
So that's the third ingredient?
Thank you so much!
I thought I was a respected man...
Excuse me, could you share that sake with us?
For the life of me...
This is not revenge for their discrimination.
Neither was what I did at Marie Jois.
I want to believe that when you grow up,
humans and Fish-Men will...
I broke that stupid unspoken rule but I did
so to free all those mistreated slaves.
I can't forgive you!
Toriko-san!
We Sun Pirates are all about liberation
and freedom. There is nothing more to it.
You okay?
I see... That's...
I'm Rear Admiral Strawberry
from the Navy Headquarters.
Hey, don't!
It's my first time seeing one.
--Do it!
--Kill him!
An orangutan whose favorite treat is raochu!
If we start to seek revenge
against the humans as we like,
Someone on this island
informed us of your arrival.
it will only lead them to get back
at us later and that's just tragic.
Don't do it!
You are all liars!!
You stupid fishes!
The elders of this village knew there
might be trouble if we stopped you
Raochutan (Mammal Beast) Capture Level 32
They will look on innocent
future Fish-Men as their enemies.
A Raochutan!
Its favorite treat is sake?
but they approved it.
Then it probably won't be
easy to get it to share.
Don't you see?
On the condition that we wouldn't repossess
the girl who is the rightful property
We'll fight and rob those people who
come after us but don't cross the line.
Otohime-sama! You're on the air
- the whole country heard it!
Be careful.
With all that wobbling,
we can't predict its attacks.
of the Celestial Dragons.
Fisher Tiger, captain of the Sun Pirates.
We won't kill anyone!
It's like drunken boxing!
Shurrup!
You are charged on two counts.
I'm sure you know this already.
Queen Otohime!!
Minister of the Left!
Big Brother! I always wanted
to say one thing to you.
Assault and evasion.
"It will only lead them to get back at us"?
Hang in there, Chopper.
I'm sure the others will
bring back the ingredients.
We could just kill them so
they can't get back at us.
There's no more time.
Kill them brutally and
scare the hell out of them!
It's almost dawn...
Then they wouldn't dare
think about getting revenge!
A-Are you drunk?!
The Queen has been shot!
They don't know how strong
and dreadful we can be!
I'm alright!
You guys!
Shurrup! I'm not... I'm not drunk!
Let it be engraved in
their minds! The terror!
Don't just watch!
Hurry up and catch this thing!
What do you think you're doing?!
Yes, you are!
Just capturing it isn't enough.
--What is that?
--Is that Otohime-sama?
Queen Otohime...
If you don't make the Banjyan Tiger run fast,
What was that? I heard gunshots!
Everybody, drop your gun!
Everybody, listen!
It's from the direction Boss headed!
you can't collect the chili paste.
Looks like it's figured out by instinct
that you're the easiest prey.
Did something happen to him?!
We... We are capable of staying
in the water forever if we want!
Children are watching!
Hey, look at the sea!
Better run hard.
It's the Navy! We're surrounded-choo!
But in the ocean so broad,
Why are they here?
We're trapped!
Aladdin!
That brat was a ploy to lure us here!
and on the seafloor so dark,
Where is the Celestial Dragon
who's ship was wrecked?!
And Big Brother and all
of us took it like fools!
I just got here, myself.
Hey! It turned into chili paste!
we chose to live in this
limited area... Do you know why?!
Boss Jimbei!
See?! That's what humans do!
So all that running around melted it.
Our mother rushed out of the palace!
We did it!
What?
Otohime-sama...
All right. We've got the first ingredient.
Brother-sama, who are the Celestial Dragons?
Isn't it because there is some light and air?
They are humans, Shirahoshi.
Well, this is just what I can do!
Humans?
Is that Jimbei?
There are quite a few humans out
there and they are the scary ones.
Franky Rocket Launcher!
But there is more light above ground,
and the sky is higher!
Damn the Navy!
Arlong is very hot-blooded and
quite a pain in the neck, isn't he?
Boss! Boss Tai is in danger!
I heard some gunshots too.
Arlong!
Let's go.
Can you handle this? We
gotta go save the Boss!
O-Otohime-sama...
So it's got speed, too?
Not bad.
Okay, Brother Jimbei!
It's just a scratch.
I was so excited to see what
beautiful creature would appear...
Why do you protect him?
Why do our children sneak
out to see the Sabaody Park?
I don't blame him.
You have to bring Big Brother back safely!
You don't know what he did to us in the past!
In fact, I have no right to say such a thing.
and yet...
I know! Let's go!
Rin-chan! Are you okay?!
He treated us like we were
animals, not even slaves.
Brother Tai...
Arlong-san, this is not good!
The ship is gonna be wrecked!
There are more beautiful places
than we can imagine in the world!
I'll protect Rin-chan!
Jimbei, what Queen Otohime
is calling for is great.
I can feel your anguish - it's very painful.
Everybody, get off of the ship!
How dare you betray my hopes so deeply?!
Let's hijack one of the Navy ships!
For her, there is no difference
between Arlong and me.
There is no place that we should not go...
Mother-sama!
It stopped moving!
You are just making convenient
excuses to convince yourself
My brother stopped it with his Hair Lock!
I know it's hard but...
What the heck? Looks like that ended easily.
and giving everything up!
...you can't plant your anger and resentment
toward humans in children's mind!
The eight horns are a little cute,
but I don't care about the rest.
Why is he still alive?
What I'm most afraid of is the demon
that is hiding deep in my mind.
He's been shot so many times!
Why is he still standing?!
Have courage!
Sorry my brother made trouble with
you with his made-up expectations.
And go for what you truly want!
They need a chance to meet humans
and figure them out on their own.
Now, I'll just... take these!
I won't forgive you...
Let's get moving!
I won't forgive you!
I won't forgive you, humans!
Your Majesty...
At that time, I couldn't
understand what Boss really meant.
You two really are compatible.
If humans stand in your way,
let's face them together!
Shoot him!
So, please!
We're not compatible at all!
Don't tell the people on the island anything!
Then maybe we can make a difference for
the future of the children on this island,
Nyu! There's a pirate ship!
I think I heard something.
Did you hear anything, Mom?
Neither the tragedy we endured
nor of our anger towards humans!
It's a big one!
They wanna beat us to prove themselves!
No.
Now we have these kinds of enemies, too.
Brother Tai...
even just a small one!
Boss...
Well, if we sink them,
we'll make an example of them!
Boss!
Rear Admiral-dono! The Sun Pirates are here!
We were fighting on a daily basis,
as criminals wanted by the Government
Toriko-san! Luffy-san!
So that must be...
That little...
It's so cold, I can't
move the way I want to...
...Jimbei.
while Queen Otohime was fighting
against the world in her own way, too.
Watch out, Mother-sama!
Don't move!
Sign here!
You all... I'm sorry!
Oh no! Your Majesty!
No, Your Majesty! We don't wanna
live together with humans!
I left my family behind
on the Fish-Man Island.
Boss!
Mother!
The more it drinks, the stronger it gets!
Please!
You're responsible for all of this?!
Hey, they put a bounty on
Boss Tai and Jimbei-san!
That bastard!
The sake isn't the only
thing making it stronger.
My kid and wife... I wonder
how they are doing.
Everything I've done is for justice...
Queen?
There's also that leaf it's drinking out of!
...and to destroy the Sun Pirates!
To a Celestial Dragon like me,
What?!
But you can go home someday.
the Queen of a fish country
is just another commoner...
Wow, 230 million berries!
That's a Mango Karin leaf!
Damn the Navy!
If the leaves are here...
Jimbei-san is 76 million berries!
...or even less!
Does that mean the Mango Karin is nearby?
I'll kill you too!
We former slaves will get
killed if they find us.
What an asshole!
Wanted posters!
The reward has increased again!
Go ahead! I'd like to see you try!
So whether we want it or not, we have to
keep sailing for the rest of our lives.
Mother-sama!
Even the World Government is scared!
We managed to rescue Boss
Destroy the Navy!
I'm sorry! I didn't mean it.
and flee to sea with a Navy
ship that Arlong stole.
You fools! What are you doing?!
Komatsu!
Sign!
Oh, no!
Get me a mask and a doctor! Otherwise...
Let go of me!
THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
So 3 years passed like that and then
we met a young girl on some island.
But...
Are you alright now?
It was awful.
I can't believe that you got beaten so bad.
Boss!
Mister, could you do us a favor?
12 YEARS AGO
What do you mean that you don't
want a transfusion? Boss!
Don't get cocky, now!
Mother-sama!!
Arlong, who was locked up in Impel
down the other day, is nothing.
This girl escaped from Marie Jois like
us 3 years ago when you freed the slaves.
Don't be ridiculous!
You lost too much blood!
You're gonna die if you don't get one!
What?!
The most violent one is Jimbei!
The Boss' blood type is rare! No one
in our crew has the same blood type!
Look.
The blood stock on this Navy ship must be...
But her hometown where her
parents are is far from here.
He was unbelievably strong.
What was that?! It was incredible!
It's too dangerous to have him at large.
We wanna take her home but we don't
think we can cross the ocean safely.
It's Zebra! That was Zebra's Sound Bullet!
...human blood.
Hmm...
He shot a Sound Bullet
from inside the prison!
That's right. But humans
and we share the same blood.
UNCLEAR JUSTICE
My name is Koala. I'm 11 years old.
So we can use human blood to save you!
Let me enjoy this a little longer, Toriko.
Thank you for helping me 3 years ago.
It's the Sea Kings!!
They want me to join the Seven Warlords?!
You figure out how to deal with the rest.
Your bounty was raised
to 250 million berries!
She might be a kid but she's
still a human! Disgusting!
Now let me do this!
This is the power of Zebra-san
of the Four Heavenly Kings...
No!
They figured that you're gonna be an
even bigger threat to the Government.
Why did you invite a human on board?!
I'd rather die than live with their blood!
It's warmer now that the
outside air is coming in!
It's just how things turn out.
Stop smiling! You're an aggravating brat!
I can move really well now!
They finally got it!
Their blood is filthy.
Arlong-san!
Let's turn them down and gain
more notoriety, Captain Jimbei!
They never stop disrespecting us Fish-Men!
Arlong-san!
Let go of me, Hachi! I
wanna pound her into pulp!
Boss...
He's right.
She's constantly smiling and kind of creepy.
No, I think I'm gonna take the offer.
I don't wanna owe them anything!
I don't need mercy from them!
What?!
I don't wanna give in to humans!
What was that?
Welcome back, Jimbei!
I heard about the Seven Warlords.
It didn't look like a coincidence...
Big Brother! Was there something...
between you and the humans?!
If I join the Warlords, Aladdin and the
others who don't want to be pirates...
It grew gigantic!
What are you...?
Shirahoshi... Don't tell me you are...
I'm sorry! I'll work! I'll clean without
taking a break! So please don't hit me!
Could that be...
...can live in this country without being
chased under the amnesty of the Government.
A Mango Karin flower?!
Yeah. There's no doubt.
I didn't wanna tell you this!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
All right! I'll be taking that!
What's the matter, Captain?
More importantly, if I become a Warlord,
Just wait, Chopper!
On my last trip, I...
I'm sorry!
According to the family legend, a long
long time ago, there was a Mermaid...
Third Gear!
--What are you doing?
--I'm sorry!
the Fish-Man can get closer
to the World Government.
It was a long trip, wasn't it?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Armament: Hardening!
Yeah, a lot happened.
...who possessed mysterious power that
could even control the Sea Kings!
For the good of the Queen who
we've caused so much trouble.
--Hey, you're bleeding.
--I'm sorry!
Fifteen-fold...
What did you see during your trip?
Gum-Gum...
I'll never ever cry -
just please don't kill me!
Thank you.
Vander Decken I decided to look into
the legend and headed for the seafloor.
She's not feeling well now.
Elephant Gun!
Nail Punch!
Hey, stop it! Are you afraid of us?
I saw humans!
My ancestors! I finally found her!
And it could make the late
Tiger's dream come true -
liberation and freedom for the Fish-Man!
Yes, I am. But I wanted to see my mother so
I plucked up courage and got on board.
Soon after I set off on my trip,
Shirahoshi is the legendary Mermaid?
But at the same time, I think the amnesty
would cause us some trouble too...
--I was caught.
--What?
You did it, Captain!
If I stop cleaning,
maybe you men are gonna kill me.
All right!
Shh! Don't let anybody hear about it.
I spent several years in Marie Jois.
Amazing! They beat the Raochutan!
I'll serve you well so please don't kill me!
It's a secret legend that only
my family knows, I suspect!
IMPEL DOWN
I was...
She's used to living as a slave.
This is the Mango Karin?
...a slave!
If I can control the Sea Kings as
I wish, I can do anything I want.
No!
The flower isn't blooming!
She must have seen other slaves get killed
when they cried or took a break from cleaning.
--Arlong-san!
--Arlong!
Looks like it's too cold
for it to open completely.
Boss!
I can have anything I want!
What?! So what do we do?!
Arlong-san!
What I saw there was the insanity of humans!
So she has always been afraid that she
might be next and she can't trust anyone.
So, what are we gonna do now?
If it gets some warm light,
like the spring sunlight...
--Arlong-san!
--Arlong-san is back! He's back!
Kidnap Princess Shirahoshi?
You mean light from the sun?
I fled for my life but...
First, I have to marry her.
Arlong-san!
But once the sun comes up,
Chopper will be done for!
...I couldn't just forget about
all those slaves that I saw!
Boss!
What?!
If you've got something to say, just say it!
But she's still a kid now.
What the heck can we do?!
Hmmm... that's the problem!
You're gonna join the Warlords,
huh? Brother Jimbei.
Please! Don't kill me! I'll do anything!
Listen carefully!
I did things the way I wanted and...
You're gonna be the
Government's dog, aren't you?!
Aladdin...
Bring this brat to my room.
...I interfered with Queen
Otohime as a result.
Don't you remember what Brother Tai said?
Let me treat him.
What is he doing?
Don't let resentment and
anger get the better of you!
Thank you.
Lecturing her won't do anything.
She's mentally ill.
I'll treat you next.
But she is right.
You've gotten soft, Brother.
A few weeks later,
Everybody wants peace, of course!
I know I'd be safe if I just
followed you, but I refuse!
when the Celestial Dragon
who's life has been saved was
about to leave for home,
But the only people who can make
a difference on that island...
Boss! What're you doing in there?!
Queen Otohime did an unexpected thing.
Big Brother is dead!
I'll lead the Arlong Pirates again!
...are children of the next generation
like Koala who aren't prejudiced.
That's...
I'll take my men with me.
What? Is it dawn?
So this is it.
No, it's...
Stop the bleeding!
Arlong, you fool...
I may have been rough on her but she couldn't
forget being a slave with that mark on her.
So, please!
A school of Spring Sharks!
If you really wanna stop
me, you better kill me...
Don't tell the people
on the island anything!
I'll get even with you!
Spring Sharks? Like the
one that swallowed me?
Although I'm a respected
World Noble, you insulted me
Hey, are you alive?!
Yeah. They're a highly valuable shark,
but they're called Spring Sharks
Neither the tragedy we endured
nor of our anger towards humans!
...right now!
and harassed me terribly.
You fishes, I'll make you
feel sorry for what you did!
A-Arlong-san!
because, during the spawning
season, they glow!
Oh, you're up!
But Big Brother...
If you can't do it, I'm free to go.
Oh, I passed out.
Arlong!
Is that what we get for saving his life?
And that glow is said to be as warm
and bright as the spring sunlight!
I'm sorry! But I didn't cry
so please don't kill me!
I represent the anger of the Fish-Man!
We provided a ship and
crew for him to go home!
There are so many humans
who are compassionate!
The glow of a whole school rivals
the warm glow of the sun!
I'll never, ever cry so please don't kill me!
How arrogant you are!
How could he say that?!
I know! But...
We shouldn't let him go! It's
dangerous to this island!
It's okay to cry!
...it's funny - the dying leave
only their resentment behind.
Jimbei-san!
Wait a minute!
Don't think that we're like
those stupid Celestial Dragons!
That's great!
You seem like you have more to say.
And even though I know
that there are kind humans,
In that case, I'll come with
you to the world above.
Look closely.
there is a devil inside of me that is...
To the world above?!
That's too dangerous, Otohime-sama!
...clouding my thoughts.
Mother-sama!
Wait-jamon, Otohime! I won't let you do that!
My whole body rejects their blood!
That's...
The Mango Karin!
Jimbei-san!
If you wish to negotiate
with the Nobles, I'll go!
I can't...
Stop it!
So... So beautiful!
I'm sure humans won't catch you
Luffy, it looks like you have great
Food Luck for finding ingredients.
...accept humans!
since you're the King and a Great Knight.
You had already met the last ingredient
you needed to heal Chopper,
Boss! Don't say such a
thing and live! I beg you!
Then let me...
No, there is no point if
it's a strong man like you!
the Spring Shark, once before!
You don't have to die!
What?
We have to show that
Boss! No matter what you say,
even a weak woman can
go there and return home
Seafood Fruit, chili paste
from the Banjyan Tiger,
you're the greatest benefactor to
all the slaves who were freed by you!
Just take him away now!
if we want to prove to our nation
it's totally safe up there.
the eight-horned herb from the Octohorn,
Arlong-san!
raochu from the Raochu Spring,
and the Mango Karin flower.
Don't worry, Jimbei.
I'm physically more fragile than
anyone - that's why it makes
You're a hero to all Fish-Men,
who accomplished such a great feat!
It's finished!
We won't kill anybody!
Seafood Fruit with a sauce made
from the four seasonal ingredients!
more sense for me to go.
I'm so happy...
You two grew up together and
he's like a brother to you.
--Mother-sama!
Here, Chopper-san, eat this.
You're not strong enough!
No wonder you couldn't just kill
him even though you were justified.
Otohime-sama!
What?!
You have to step further. You can't
protect anybody with that punch!
Where are you going, Otohime-sama?
Why can't that fool understand...
Let's go, guys!
Otohime...
Huh? Protect?!
Trust the woman who you chose to be your wife
We'll take her...
...what Brother Tai truly meant?!
Brother!
If there is nobody else
who wants to challenge me,
and the humans.
Wherever he goes, as long as he engages
in violence, the Navy won't leave him alone.
Yum!
I'll become the leader of the
Fish-Man District from today!
...to her hometown!
You're doing that again?
My name is Tiger!
Or if that doesn't work,
let's go and stop him ourselves...
She's just a fish queen - how arrogant!
Since I'm your brother now,
leave everything up to me.
We did it!
Your life is my life!
He's cured!
...at any cost!
Well, well, we'll go our own way,
just like we used to, Captain Jimbei!
I'll keep my men safe!
Thank you all so much!
Mother-sama!
I'll never forget this!
Macro, you...
Toriko! See you again!
Let them go!
Yeah! Let's eat our fill of tasty food again!
Bye!
Jimbei...
No one can stop her.
The food you eat with
your friends is the best!
Boss!
All we can do is trust her and wait.
Damn, he's like a monster...
--Boss!
What's with him?
I guess, in spite of everything,
he's sad to say goodbye.
Your Majesty! Please be careful!
Hachi, let's go.
Goodbye!
Otohime-sama!
The Sun Pirates split into three groups
Mother-sama!
Take care!
Let's meet again,
Boss!
The Sunny!
and went separate ways.
That's what you meant?!
The Straw Hats and Toriko's friends
have the crossover of your dreams!
Otohime brought a single
paper back from the surface.
After a long voyage, Tiger finally
returns Koala to her home.
Fisher Tigers death sent
ripples far and wide.
Because of Jimbei's status
as one of the Seven Warlords,
It represents a light of
hope for Fish-Man Island.
he is able to safely bring the
former slave Fish-Men home.
Chopper has come down with Deap Sea Fever,
Can Fish-Men and humans coexist,
or must they remain separate?
Watching Koala and her mother
in a tearful embrace,
Gathering numerous signatures,
so Luffy and Toriko's groups must find
a mysterious ingredient to save him.
Just as Otohime's ideal future
had seemed one step closer,
As the Fish-Men waver,
Arlong's hatred of humans
her dream becomes the dream
of all of Fish-Man Island.
But Chopper will only last until daybreak!
Tiger sees hope for a new future
for Fish-Men and humans.
a drifting ship arrived.
Fish-Man Island seemed ready to change,
and Jimbei's desire to preserve
Otohime and Tiger's ideals
As the seconds tick by, mighty
beasts rise up to block their way!
But his hopes are cruelly
trampled upon by humans.
when all of a sudden,
On board is a Celestial Dragon
who thinks of Fish-Men as
will bring their convictions into conflict!
a gunshot rings out across
all of Fish-Man Island!
nothing more than slaves!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Sun Pirates Split! Jimbei vs Arlong!"
"Shaking Fish-Man Island!
A Celestial Dragon Drifts In!"
"The Death of the Hero!
A Shocking Truth of Tiger!"
"A Team is Formed! Save Chopper"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
"A Sudden Tragedy! A Gunshot
Shuts Down the Future!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!