Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates - who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi,
are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
Meeting Jimbei again at the Sea Forest,
Luffy learns about the
Fish-Man Island along with
Nami, Sanji, Chopper,
Franky and the others.
"Kizaru Appears!
A Trap to Catch Tiger!"
Fisher Tiger's attack on
the Holyland of Marie Jois
and the Sun Pirates' raid - those events...
...had such impact on Fish-Men's future.
15 YEARS AGO
I can't believe that he really did it.
It put the Fish-Man Island
in a bad position again.
We won't be welcomed at the
World Summit for a while.
Now, what should we do?
But we couldn't stop him that day.
What did you see during your trip?
I saw humans!
Because I could hear that the
scream from his soul so loudly.
Extra, extra! Read all about it!
He showed up the Celestial Dragons
who no one dares challenge!
Fisher Tiger - the hero
of the Fish-Man Island!
Wow! A Fish-Man changed history!
Listen to me, everyone!
--Oh, that's Queen Otohime!
--Her again?
We have been cowering, hiding and running.
But we have learned nothing from it.
If we cut all humans off because of
the actions of only a few bad ones,
there will be no future for the Fish-Men!
Now, let's live together with humans!
Learn about them under the bright sun!
--Learn about them?
--Yeah, I feel sorry for her but...
You two right there!
Sign here!
I-I can't, Otohime-sama!
The whole island is applauding
Tiger-san for what he did.
It might cause a rift
between us and the humans.
But, after all, it's their fault,
of course. So I can't...
Even though it's impossible now,
think about 7 years or 11 years or 15 years from now.
Plan for the day that we will be able to
participate in the World Summit again.
Please! Sign here! Please!
How great! Fisher Tiger!
THE FISH-MAN DISTRICT
He was leader in this town!
He made the Celestial Dragons mad!
HORDY JONES
The Celestial Dragons!
He sure showed those annoying humans!
Arlong-san always said
that humans were all jerks!
They're lowly creatures!
The Sun Pirates are pummeling humans
as they sail around the sea now-dosun!
Cool-dosun!
If we were stronger,
we could've gone with them-ch!
Awesome! It's so cool!
I wanna do it too, someday!
Go, Sun Pirates! Kill all the humans!
Yeah!
Boss! Boss! There's an enemy ship-nyu!
Boss! Boss! Boss!
Boss Tai! We have a crisis!
Shut up, Hachi!
Why don't you calm down a bit?
How disturbing. Is it the Navy?
Nyu! I saw the Navy's banner!
What should we do, Boss?
That's a silly question!
There is no mistake!
Those are the Sun Pirates!
Kill Tiger!
You missed!
Shoot them!
What are you doing?! Shoot at them!
But it's hard when they're in the water!
Oh no.
You Fish-Man bastards!
Return all the slaves!
Then the charges against you will...
R-Rear Admiral-dono!
Th-They're coming from below...
What?!
You fools!
Just give us back the slaves.
What you guys are doing is a serious crime!
How dare you turn against humans!
You guys are only Fish-Men!
What did you say?
Let's hear...
Let's hear you say that again!
Help...
Slavery is okay but
freeing slaves is a crime?
And you still want us to give
humans a chance, Queen Otohime?
Shoot! Shoot!
Shoot at him! We got a tip!
You guys are hiding the former slaves!
No way!
The former slaves?
A-Are you a monster?!
Do you have any proof that
we are hiding the slaves?
Check all of us. I heard all the
slaves have a mark on their body.
Do you see it?!
L-Let go of me! Stop! What are you doing?!
Help me!
Don't worry, I'll let you go.
I'm not like you humans.
Guys! Take their money,
goods and food, and get back to the ship!
You deserve execution.
Being human is itself a sin.
Wait, Arlong!
Drop dead!
Vice Admiral Borsalino.
MARINEFORD--THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
G2 branch - Rear Admiral Kadar's
ship has been defeated.
Oh? Why did they even fight them?
I just wanted to know where they were.
It's said if you get
close enough to see them,
they'll surround you in the
water before you know it.
Oh, that's scary! They aren't known as
undersea professionals for nothing.
So, what are we up against?
Well, it looks like Arlong and his men,
who are conducting raids around
the Fish-Man island, are among them.
But they're always in water so it's
hard to tell how strong they are.
Arlong... Yes, I've heard about him before.
And they said there is a man
who is as big as Tiger and just as
formidable but we don't even know his name.
Oh, that's not good.
Ouch!
So what? It's not so big a deal to get rid
of one or two of those lowly creatures!
You two are going too far, don't you think?
We're not a group of killers.
Stop acting like fools!
But Brother Tai - I mean, "Boss!"
They're all trying to kill you!
If that's what they want, we might
go a little too far! It makes us mad!
If you kill somebody, it's your loss!
Do you want to be like them?
This is not revenge for their discrimination.
Neither was what I did at Marie Jois.
I broke that stupid unspoken rule but I did
so to free all those mistreated slaves.
We Sun Pirates are all about liberation
and freedom. There is nothing more to it.
If we start to seek revenge
against the humans as we like,
it will only lead them to get back
at us later and that's just tragic.
They will look on innocent
future Fish-Men as their enemies.
Don't you see?
We'll fight and rob those people who
come after us but don't cross the line.
We won't kill anyone!
Big Brother! I always wanted
to say one thing to you.
"It will only lead them to get back at us"?
We could just kill them so
they can't get back at us.
Kill them brutally and
scare the hell out of them!
Then they wouldn't dare
think about getting revenge!
They don't know how strong
and dreadful we can be!
Let it be engraved in
their minds! The terror!
What do you think you're doing?!
Is that Jimbei?
Arlong is very hot-blooded and
quite a pain in the neck, isn't he?
I don't blame him.
In fact, I have no right to say such a thing.
Brother Tai...
Jimbei, what Queen Otohime
is calling for is great.
For her, there is no difference
between Arlong and me.
What I'm most afraid of is the demon
that is hiding deep in my mind.
At that time, I couldn't
understand what Boss really meant.
Nyu! There's a pirate ship!
It's a big one!
They wanna beat us to prove themselves!
Now we have these kinds of enemies, too.
Well, if we sink them,
we'll make an example of them!
We were fighting on a daily basis,
as criminals wanted by the Government
while Queen Otohime was fighting
against the world in her own way, too.
Sign here!
No, Your Majesty! We don't wanna
live together with humans!
Please!
Hey, they put a bounty on
Boss Tai and Jimbei-san!
What?!
Wow, 230 million berries!
Jimbei-san is 76 million berries!
Wanted posters!
The reward has increased again!
Even the World Government is scared!
Destroy the Navy!
Sign!
Let go of me!
So 3 years passed like that and then
we met a young girl on some island.
Mister, could you do us a favor?
12 YEARS AGO
This girl escaped from Marie Jois like
us 3 years ago when you freed the slaves.
Look.
But her hometown where her
parents are is far from here.
We wanna take her home but we don't
think we can cross the ocean safely.
My name is Koala. I'm 11 years old.
Thank you for helping me 3 years ago.
She might be a kid but she's
still a human! Disgusting!
Why did you invite a human on board?!
It's just how things turn out.
Stop smiling! You're an aggravating brat!
Arlong-san!
Let go of me, Hachi! I
wanna pound her into pulp!
He's right.
She's constantly smiling and kind of creepy.
What are you...?
I'm sorry! I'll work! I'll clean without
taking a break! So please don't hit me!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
--What are you doing?
--I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
--Hey, you're bleeding.
--I'm sorry!
I'll never ever cry -
just please don't kill me!
Hey, stop it! Are you afraid of us?
Yes, I am. But I wanted to see my mother so
I plucked up courage and got on board.
If I stop cleaning,
maybe you men are gonna kill me.
I'll serve you well so please don't kill me!
She's used to living as a slave.
She must have seen other slaves get killed
when they cried or took a break from cleaning.
So she has always been afraid that she
might be next and she can't trust anyone.
Boss!
Please! Don't kill me! I'll do anything!
Bring this brat to my room.
What is he doing?
Lecturing her won't do anything.
She's mentally ill.
Boss! What're you doing in there?!
Stop the bleeding!
I may have been rough on her but she couldn't
forget being a slave with that mark on her.
Hey, are you alive?!
Oh, you're up!
Oh, I passed out.
I'm sorry! But I didn't cry
so please don't kill me!
I'll never, ever cry so please don't kill me!
It's okay to cry!
Don't think that we're like
those stupid Celestial Dragons!
Look closely.
What?
We won't kill anybody!
Let's go, guys!
We'll take her...
...to her hometown!
The Straw Hats and Toriko's friends
have the crossover of your dreams!
Chopper has come down with Deap Sea Fever,
so Luffy and Toriko's groups must find
a mysterious ingredient to save him.
But Chopper will only last until daybreak!
As the seconds tick by, mighty
beasts rise up to block their way!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Team is Formed! Save Chopper"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!