Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level.
Meeting Jimbei again at the Sea Forest,
Luffy learns about the Fish-Man Island
along with Nami, Sanji, Chopper,
Franky and the others.
It's okay to cry!
Don't think that we're like
those stupid Celestial Dragons!
Look closely.
What?
We won't kill anybody!
We'll take her...
...to her hometown!
"The Death of the Hero!
A Shocking Truth of Tiger!"
We finally got an Eternal
Pose to Koala's hometown!
12 YEARS AGO - THE GRAND LINE
Nyu! Koala, you can go back to your home!
Um...
I can't believe my eyes.
You've changed a lot!
KOALA (THE FORMER SLAVE GIRL)
You look like a girl now!
I don't normally wear these...
What? We bought them for you
but you don't like them?
You got your hair cut, too.
Your mother will be really happy.
I...
I should clean.
Nyu! You need to stop working
when you don't know what to do!
This is not Marie Jois!
Leave her alone.
She needs time.
THE SHIP'S DOCTOR OF THE SUN PIRATES
ALADDIN
Trauma can't be healed that easily.
Alright.
You understand her very
well, Brother Aladdin.
Because you were a slave yourself.
But wouldn't you rather kill her right now?
She's a human just like
the one who owned you!
Stop it, Arlong!
Tell us the truth.
What did your mother tell you?
Your parents looked down
on Fish-Men, didn't they?
That's how human society is!
They think that they're
the best race in the world.
Their children are spoiled
by watching their example.
It won't stop until somebody destroys them!
I suppose you guys have seen it enough
while we were sailing these past 3 years.
Their disrespectful
contemptuous look when they see us.
I don't know what I would've done
to them if the Boss wasn't there.
That was only a few of them.
--The others didn't look like that.
--Brother Jimbei...
Everytime I see them,
they all look terrified to me.
Is it because we're pirates?
Why are you so afraid of us?
Because I don't know you folk.
If you don't know someone,
you naturally fear them?
We've only known the bad sort of humans.
We don't know anything about humans yet.
So getting to know someone
would change something?
Nyu. Hey, Koala.
What?
Guess which hand it's in.
Well, where is it now?
Um... This one.
Nope! It's here!
Alright, one more time.
Nyu. Get it right this time.
Uh-huh.
Where is it?
This one.
Wrong again!
Just as Koala was fitting in so well.
That's when we arrived at Foolshout
Island - where she came from.
THE GRAND LINE - FOOLSHOUT ISLAND
Koala, get off of the ship.
This is your home island.
--Where is your home village?
--Huh?
--I'll walk you to the entrance to the village.
--Uh-huh!
Don't go, Koala! Come with us!
You're a good girl even
though you're a human.
Stop crying, you guys.
I'll tell everybody in the village...
...that there are so many good Fish-Men!
Thank you, everybody!
Goodbye!
Hey, take care of yourself!
I'm sure she'll grow up into a
mean-spirited human like the others.
What did you just say?!
Jimbei!
Arlong, you bastard...
Brother Jimbei.
You've changed a lot in last 3 years.
What?
Think about it. What's the point in her
telling people that Fish-Men are nice?
It's like Otohime's speeches,
her voice will just ring hollow.
She's back!
He's right! Your daughter is back!
--I'm so glad!
--Yeah...
Everybody!
Hurry up! She came back!
Koala? Koala!
Mom...
Koala!
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
That is the captain of the Sun Pirates...
Fisher Tiger!
He's a bad man, isn't he?
Because he's a Fish-Man...
Shh!
It must've been painful
and hard being a slave!
But Mom, not everybody was
like the Celestial Dragons!
What?
I thought Fish-Men were all terrible
but there were so many nice Fish-Men!
That's because you're only a child.
No! I know it because I was with Uncle
Tiger and the others all this time!
You would think so too
if you'd lived with them!
Uncle!
Uncle Tiger!
Thank you for keeping your promise!
I'll never forget you - Uncle Tiger...
...and Hachi-san,
Aladdin-san and all of the Sun Pirates...
...for the rest of my life!
Thank you so much!
I want to believe that when you grow up,
humans and Fish-Men will...
I'm Rear Admiral Strawberry
from the Navy Headquarters.
Someone on this island
informed us of your arrival.
The elders of this village knew there
might be trouble if we stopped you
but they approved it.
On the condition that we wouldn't repossess
the girl who is the rightful property
of the Celestial Dragons.
Fisher Tiger, captain of the Sun Pirates.
You are charged on two counts.
I'm sure you know this already.
Assault and evasion.
What was that? I heard gunshots!
It's from the direction Boss headed!
Did something happen to him?!
Hey, look at the sea!
It's the Navy! We're surrounded-choo!
Why are they here?
We're trapped!
That brat was a ploy to lure us here!
And Big Brother and all
of us took it like fools!
See?! That's what humans do!
Damn the Navy!
Boss! Boss Tai is in danger!
Arlong!
Can you handle this? We
gotta go save the Boss!
Okay, Brother Jimbei!
You have to bring Big Brother back safely!
I know! Let's go!
Arlong-san, this is not good!
The ship is gonna be wrecked!
Everybody, get off of the ship!
Let's hijack one of the Navy ships!
Why is he still alive?
He's been shot so many times!
Why is he still standing?!
I won't forgive you...
I won't forgive you!
I won't forgive you, humans!
Shoot him!
I think I heard something.
Did you hear anything, Mom?
No.
Boss...
Boss!
Rear Admiral-dono! The Sun Pirates are here!
So that must be...
...Jimbei.
You all... I'm sorry!
Boss!
You're responsible for all of this?!
Everything I've done is for justice...
...and to destroy the Sun Pirates!
Damn the Navy!
I'll kill you too!
Go ahead! I'd like to see you try!
We managed to rescue Boss
and flee to sea with a Navy
ship that Arlong stole.
But...
Boss!
What do you mean that you don't
want a transfusion? Boss!
Don't be ridiculous!
You lost too much blood!
You're gonna die if you don't get one!
The Boss' blood type is rare! No one
in our crew has the same blood type!
The blood stock on this Navy ship must be...
...human blood.
That's right. But humans
and we share the same blood.
So we can use human blood to save you!
Now let me do this!
No!
I'd rather die than live with their blood!
Their blood is filthy.
They never stop disrespecting us Fish-Men!
Boss...
I don't wanna owe them anything!
I don't need mercy from them!
I don't wanna give in to humans!
Big Brother! Was there something...
between you and the humans?!
I didn't wanna tell you this!
On my last trip, I...
It was a long trip, wasn't it?
Yeah, a lot happened.
What did you see during your trip?
I saw humans!
Soon after I set off on my trip,
--I was caught.
--What?
I spent several years in Marie Jois.
I was...
...a slave!
No!
Boss!
What I saw there was the insanity of humans!
I fled for my life but...
...I couldn't just forget about
all those slaves that I saw!
Listen carefully!
I did things the way I wanted and...
...I interfered with Queen
Otohime as a result.
But she is right.
Everybody wants peace, of course!
But the only people who can make
a difference on that island...
...are children of the next generation
like Koala who aren't prejudiced.
So, please!
Don't tell the people
on the island anything!
Neither the tragedy we endured
nor of our anger towards humans!
But Big Brother...
Arlong!
There are so many humans
who are compassionate!
I know! But...
...it's funny - the dying leave
only their resentment behind.
And even though I know
that there are kind humans,
there is a devil inside of me that is...
...clouding my thoughts.
My whole body rejects their blood!
I can't...
...accept humans!
Boss! Don't say such a
thing and live! I beg you!
You don't have to die!
Boss! No matter what you say,
you're the greatest benefactor to
all the slaves who were freed by you!
You're a hero to all Fish-Men,
who accomplished such a great feat!
I'm so happy...
You're not strong enough!
What?!
You have to step further. You can't
protect anybody with that punch!
Huh? Protect?!
Brother!
If there is nobody else
who wants to challenge me,
I'll become the leader of the
Fish-Man District from today!
My name is Tiger!
Since I'm your brother now,
leave everything up to me.
Your life is my life!
I'll keep my men safe!
Boss!
--Boss!
Fisher Tigers death sent
ripples far and wide.
Can Fish-Men and humans coexist,
or must they remain separate?
As the Fish-Men waver,
Arlong's hatred of humans
and Jimbei's desire to preserve
Otohime and Tiger's ideals
will bring their convictions into conflict!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Sun Pirates Split! Jimbei vs Arlong!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!