Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil
caught up in the turmoil.
The Straw Hats find themselves
On their way to the New World,
and Zoro, Usopp and Brook got
caught by Hordy at the Ryugu Palace.
On their way to the New World,
--Mother-sama!
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
Otohime-sama!
I'm gonna go to the Ryugu Palace to save
my crew and kick that Hordy guy's ass!
Where are you going, Otohime-sama?
"Back to the Present!
Hordy Makes a Move!"
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
I said "Don't do it"!
Otohime...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
Trust the woman who you chose to be your wife
"Something Has Happened to Hordy!
The True Power of the Evil Drug!"
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
and the humans.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
This country will soon be destroyed.
Uh, everybody on the Fish-Man Island.
And it will be rebuilt under a new king.
It's time for the decisive battle!
Mother-sama!
Can you hear me?
Well, as soon as we cut the King's head off,
the morale of his army will be shattered
Namely, me!
Mother-sama!
I'm the captain of the New Fish-Man
Pirates from the Fish-Man District,
Citizens of Fish-Man Island!
Otohime-sama!
and then it's over!
It's time to say goodbye...
Which means we'll have a new king soon!
Your Majesty! Please be careful!
Hordy Jones!
...to the old Ryugu Kingdom!
I can't wait!
Three hours from now, at Conchcorde Plaza,
Mother-sama!
"The Kingdom in Shock!
An Order to Execute Neptune Issued!"
I'm going to cut this
incompetent King's head off!
Straw Hat Pirates!
All right. Next!
I'll show you something good.
Meanwhile, at Candy Factory
Town in the center of the island...
CANDY FACTORY
"A Sudden Tragedy!
A Gunshot Shuts Down the Future!"
Next!
I know you are somewhere on
the island watching this.
Jimbei!
Damn! Who shot our queen?!
Next!
You people shattered Arlong's dream
- he was a symbol of Fish-Men's anger.
Daruma-san, w-what are you...?
Look for the shooter!
Queen Otohime's voyage was to determine
the fate of the Fish-Man Island.
Leave no stone unturned!
Zoro! Usopp! Brook!
--He's chewing the wall of the factory...
--W-What powerful jaws!
You won't step on it?!
--What fools...
--I can't believe they got caught!
Brother Tai! Queen Otohime! I... I...
Of course, we were all worrying
but it was nothing compared to
I'm sure Queen Otohime would forgive us.
--It's water!
the burden of the Neptune family.
If I refuse, they'll kill
me! I have no choice!
That room will be filled with water by
the time we finish executing the King.
The whole Ryugu Kingdom was restless.
I'm sorry, Queen Otohime!
Okay, you pass! Next!
What should I do with this anger?!
You lowly creatures can't
survive that, can you?
But all we could do was pray
for the Queen's safety.
My fangs itch!
Shark! Take me to the Ryugu Palace!
This is boring! Surprisingly,
they're all just stepping on it.
Shit! Dammit!
I said "Wait," Luffy-kun!
What? A Tamate Box?
You fools!
There he is! We found the shooter!
I don't want some trendy cappuccino
and cake for my happy snack time!
Huh?
Otohime was not that
well-respected after all!
Yes, Captain. I heard that they
have one at the Ryugu Palace.
You people shouldn't fight Hordy!
Go! Get to the rooftop now!
Daruma-san, Captain Hordy is on the air now!
Jimbei! They have my crew!
And it makes anyone grow older?
Do I look like a yuppie?!
I-I'm sorry, Daruma-san!
And I got to do something about Hordy
before my friends get into real trouble!
That's what they say.
Huh?
Is he the shooter?!
Do you want me to bite your flesh off?!
For instance, a small brat like her...
He had a gun in his hand. There is no doubt.
You're impossible!
--So he is the one who is behind all of this!
--He made us step on the picture!
Just shut up!
My favorite snack is the bones of
big fish! And don't ever forget it!
What?
...would become a sexy mature woman?
Stop me if you can!
Where is he?!
Jimbei-san! We just killed him.
I shouldn't let my guard down
just because we fought together.
Y-Yes, I'll be careful from now on!
Hey, wasn't he the one who killed
the assassin of Otohime-sama?
I think so.
That's okay. I'm gonna go chew up the
royal family and their soldiers now!
Great! Problem solved!
Who was it?
Well...
I almost forgot that
you're that man's brother.
In that case, I can get married to
Shirahoshi right away, I suspect!
Yes, his name is Hordy Jones!
I'm sure it was him!
See you at Conchcorde Plaza!
It's a...
Wasn't he a soldier of Neptune's army?
Go steal that Tamate Box thing now!
We all have to be there! Don't be late!
You ready to do this?
There is something I want
to tell all citizens of...
SEA FOREST
...human!
Wait a minute. There is no way
to break in to the Ryugu Palace.
What should we do about the citizens?
Kid?
...the Ryugu Kingdom.
Weren't you listening to what Boss said?
"A Rift Opens Up!
Luffy vs. Jimbei!"
This country will soon be destroyed.
Hide the body!
What? Boss Jimbei!
--But if you get married to Shirahoshi first...
--You can go in and out as you please.
He said "No more stepping on her picture."
And it will be rebuilt under a new king.
You guys are smart!
It will ruin the Queen's efforts!
Leave them alone!
They know what's waiting for them!
Namely, me!
Shirahoshi is not bad-looking.
She won't be able to rest in peace like this!
If she grows older by 10 to 20 years,
she will be really hot!
But she'll get even bigger.
People called me The Submarine
of the East Blue when I was a kid.
She'll look just fine! I like big women!
But it is what it is.
What is he talking about?!
CORAL HILL
Who does he think he is?! Cut the crap!
No, because he was a pirate!
I can easily swim even an 82-foot pool!
She's the legendary Mermaid
Princess who can control the Sea Kings.
--Where is he broadcasting from?
--What happened to the King?
It doesn't matter if he was a pirate or not.
The New Fish-Man Pirates have...
I can run that far!
I heard the Straw Hats occupied
the palace - what happened to them?
...4 shark Fish-Man officers including Hordy,
When I become her husband
and seize that power,
No, Hordy! Don't do it!
I can't swim but I can run!
and 1 giant squid Fish-Man.
What's going on in this country?
our dream will come true!
Hey, Brook! Let's see which one
of us is faster sometime soon!
Plus, they have a blue-ringed
octopus Merman as a bodyguard,
The new Fish-Man Island over which I will
rule is going to be strict in discipline.
It's the dream of all the ancestors
of Vander Decken family!
Listen, everyone!
You can't beat me! I'm going
to run beyond the horizon!
who is the best swordsman on the island.
It was a human...
Our only hope is the Neptune brothers.
Those of you who hope for
friendly relations with humans,
Alright, I'll start writing
an invitation to our wedding.
...who killed our queen!
Anyway, it doesn't look good, does it?!
get packing and leave this country!
I believe in the Princes!
You have to propose to her first!
No, it doesn't! The surface of
the water is getting closer!
Humans are weak and they
don't know their place.
Oh, I don't have any friends!
Queen Otohime was killed by a human!!
They don't deserve any help
from us strong Fish-Men.
Kotsun...
--Look, look! The water is...
--It's coming! It's coming!
At Waterwheel Town in
the north of the island...
WATERWHEEL TOWN
There had been no word
from the Queen for days.
Shut up!
Instead, we will have new residents
from the Fish-Man District soon.
WE NEED YOUR SIGNATURE FOR
THE FUTURE OF THE ISLAND!
And worries kept growing.
--The Princes are heading to Conchcorde Plaza!
--What's gonna happen to this country?
What's your problem?!
How can you be so calm?!
I wanna hear her speeches again.
Yeah! Do you have any ideas?!
They hate humans and hope to
change this island like us.
I don't know. All we wanted was
friendly relations with humans.
She didn't deserve it!
Nope.
Please come back safe!
--Don't be so honest!
--That's so clear, I like it. Yeah...
Why should our lives be threatened?
A human...
They're in the same camp as us.
Hey, Boss. Where is Otohime-sama?
What? New residents?
...killed the Queen who wanted
nothing but peaceful coexistence
WATERWHEEL TOWN
I can't believe they're
gonna execute the King.
If only I had my sword.
When will she come back?
All those outlaws will come and live with us?
Keep faith in her and wait.
and broke our hearts just when we were
inspired by her words and about to...
Sword? But...
Can't we stop them by taking
these guys as hostages?
She embarked on a voyage to make
the future better for you kids.
I have no choice.
I have to do it in front of you two...
I bet you all witnessed how your
beloved Queen Otohime died.
Hostages?
...extend our friendship!
No, that's not gonna work.
Boss Hordy is a ruthless man-kotsun.
What is "it"?
Dorororororo...
Your Majesty, please be safe.
He took our beloved one's life!
She was so selfless and tried so hard to
build a bridge between Fish-Men and humans.
Bone, bone, bone, bone...
Even if you try it, he'll just cut
us off and go on as planned-kotsun.
Even by taking your life,
Otohime-sama can never come back, human!
Hey Brook, what are you doing?
But who killed her?!
Bone, bone, bone, bone...
Mother-sama...
Is there no justice in this world?!
This is not good. Because he
got beaten by the Princes,
It was a human.
Hey! Brook!
If you trust them and meet halfway
in friendship, they'll disappoint you again!
Dosun-san's power level
went down to "kotsun."
Bang!
It's so sad! Unbelievably sad!
She will be fine-jamon.
He needs the Energy Steroid.
Why can't you see it?!
Let's trust in her and wait-jamon.
All right.
He's always been like that-kotsun.
Boom!
That one week felt like 100 days.
I'm out!
That bastard!
Duped by the Neptune family, you are
all heading down the path of death.
What?!
Okay, see you!
He has too much pride-potsun.
And then...
Their high-sounding
dream is just unfeasible.
Hey, w-wait, wait, wait!
You got some explaining to do!
Is the King still in the Hard Shell Tower?
"Potsun"?
It's a lie that will lead you to perdition.
He doesn't like Fish-Men who do
business with human pirates-posun.
You can do something like that now?
Minister of the Left!
No!
Yes, I can make my soul leave my body.
Can you hear that? He's lost all control.
Look at this!
That's just like a real dead person.
"Posun"?
That's...
Father-sama!
Those Fish-Men who transfused
blood to wounded humans,
Yes, you're right.
Father-sama!
It happened when I was on
my world tour as Soul King...
Father!
King-sama!
he punished them by attacking
them in the dark-tosun.
Lock the door!
The Great Knight Neptune
got old like anyone else.
Don't open it while I have
this urge to kill someone!
I was in quite a slump
at that time for a while.
"Tosun"?
Humans' blood is tainted-tosun.
There is no future for the Fish-Man
Island if the old guard remains in power.
TDS SALES PLUMMET----
CONCERT TICKETS REMAIN UNSOLD
Sales of TDs and concert
tickets were dropping.
Both giving them blood
and getting their blood...
And I didn't know what to do.
...degrades our Fish-Man blood-dosun!
Unfortunately the King
was captured because of us...
Today's concert was not so great.
He's back to "dosun"!
Yeah! Otohime-sama!
He's not making great music lately.
Those Fish-Men who support
the horrible humans are...
...or Zoro.
I couldn't feel his soul!
Don't worry, Nami-san.
It's all that Moss Head's fault.
Your Majesty!
...getting in the way of...
What happened to you, Brook?
Write a new song that will sell!
We are so happy just to see you alive!
What did you people do?!
King-sama, it's me.
Be quiet!
B-B-But, Boss Jimbei!
It's not that easy to make a hit song...
Welcome back!
...Our noble intentions-dokan!
Soldiers of Neptune's army attacked
Nami-chin and the others first!
Your Majesty!
Minister of the Left.
He exceeded "dosun"!
The shooter had a gun in his hand so
one of our soldiers shot him dead.
After a few days of convincing,
Queen Otohime finally succeeded...
Music is something much more sublime.
He broke the chain!
Neptune's army?
Citizens of Fish-Man Island!
Maybe... Maybe, the God of Music
doesn't love me anymore.
You bastard!
...in calming down the Celestial Dragons and
she brought back with her a sheet of paper...
It was a human.
It's time to say goodbye...
I would have killed him
even if he were unarmed.
One more time... Just one more song is fine!
The soldiers got blown away!
...to the old Ryugu Kingdom!
...which held the fate
of the Fish-Man Island.
CONCHCORDE PLAZA
Damn Fukaboshi!
I'll get even with you-bokan!
God! God of Music!
Three hours from now, at Conchcorde Plaza,
But Otohime would not allow that.
Everyone, the World Nobles
are very influential...
Bless me with a melody that will
shake everybody to their soul! God!
I'm going to cut this
incompetent King's head off!
I'll beat you to within an inch
of your life next time-zugan!
I don't know when this
cycle of revenge started.
...in the World Summit - the Summit of Kings.
The Great Pirate Era began...
But if I kill somebody, I would
only perpetuate that cycle.
Listen to what they wrote
on this sheet of paper.
...when they executed a human -
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates.
Witnessing my actions would
make children's eyes cold
"To foster friendship between
the Fish-Men and humans,
Let's go, guys-bagon!
and they would harbor
hatred and become bitter,
That era saw humans grow
to persecute Fish-Men.
To Conchcorde Plaza,
the execution ground-gaban!
we will pledge our endorsement
of their duly signed petition."
Boom!
What?! What is going on?!
the cycle of revenge spiraling on.
So this time, by executing Neptune,
I'll start the Great Fish-Man Era...
That means if we can submit a petition
with many signatures at the Summit,
I could relate to what Otohime was saying...
Since I got this ability,
I noticed what's missing in my songs.
In front of the Fish-Man Cultural
Hall in the south of the island...
FISH-MAN CULTURAL HALL
this one sheet of paper will
give us all the support we need.
...where Fish-Men will dominate humans.
...as long as it was somebody else's problem!
I found a way out of my slump!
As you may know by now, I'm at the Ryugu Palace
as I speak. And we found something good.
But...
--What was it?
--Well...
We can relocate!
Who did you say is drunk?
...why shouldn't I kill the man
who shot my wife to death?!
You are, Hyouzou-san!
--The Celestial Dragons will support the petition?
--I have mixed feelings about it.
Get yourself back together!
You can't fight like that!
If you had the ability to pass
undetected through walls...
It's the letter from the Celestial Dragons
that Queen Otohime got 10 years ago,
So what I need now is more signatures.
I can't understand that-jamon...
No worries, no worries! This is my treat!
Any able-bodied male
understands the potential, right?
All I can do is wait for
you to make a decision.
What are you talking about?!
As a soldier, I have taken many
lives in reprisal for my friends.
at the risk of her life!
We have to fight Neptune's army
which is being led by Fukaboshi now!
Express your intention...
I'm jealous, Zoro! I wish I were him!
If I destroy that letter, it's over.
You won't get another one.
In the worst-case scenario,
the infamous Jimbei will be there too!
...to relocate to the world above and
live together with the humans!
I killed many humans who besieged us!
Shut up!
Oh, the water got that high!
And,
Hey! Stand on your feet!
That is why I thought I have no place
helping Otohime in what she was doing
in this big box,
It's no good. He's as
slippery as a sea cucumber.
Do something already!
there are signatures from
the majority of this country.
so I just stood by and watched.
Why should an innocent one like
her die and a man like me still live?!
I can't believe how many degrees
your head can spin around.
Please! Sign!
I need your signature!
It's not spinning! You're too drunk!
I couldn't believe my eyes!
I can't take over her quest
because my hands are sullied
Boy! I bet you can't even hold your sword!
There are so many fools who
want to befriend humans!
Luffy-chin! Boss Jimbei!
No, I can!
by what I have done in the past-jamon.
Luffy! Jimbei! Hold on a second!
What are you guys doing?!
Hey, stay away from him!
Those of you who have signed your
name would oppose my new kingdom.
B-But we all change and we all
are full of contradictions.
Hyouzou will slice into
anyone when he gets drunk!
I'm gonna go to the Ryugu Palace to save
my crew and kick that Hordy guy's ass!
You children, you aren't going to go back
on your pledge after raising my hopes?
So this is actually...
We Fish-Men, and humans too. And there are
things that only soldiers can protect.
I said "Don't do it"!
He will... slice?
...a list of traitors!
Hey hey, why do you have to fight now?
We won't! My mom said she will sign too.
No more stepping on her picture.
Cut it out, guys!
It would be easy to pretend
you don't mind stepping on it.
Luffy-sama! Boss Jimbei-sama!
He sliced his friend!
A FEW DAYS LATER
Shark! Take me! To the Ryugu Place!
But these signatures will tell
who is my enemy and who is not.
I said "Wait"!
King-sama!
Outta my way!
Fish-Man Karate--Shark Brick Fist!
It's hard evidence!
Thank you all.
I will take care of those enemies one by one.
It's my own wife's funeral
- I have to attend it-jamon.
First...
--What?!
--Luffy-chin!
Father-sama! Father-sama!
Huh?!
Luffy-sama!
Shirahoshi...
Togare from Coral Hill.
No, I... I'm not... I...
That wasn't enough!
Next, Gotan from Waterwheel Town.
I wanna cut more!
Ow... Ouch!
Otohime-sama,
this small box won't be enough.
What?
Father...
It worked?! He's supposed to be immune
to blows like that as a rubber man!
My sons.
Luca from Mermaid Cove.
H-Hyouzou-san!
Don't you know the
population of this country?
I'm glad to see you.
Go to the plaza now and slice up the
Neptunes to your heart's content!
The Fish-Man Karate is all about
manipulating the water around you!
Here, here, here! Put
them in here from now on!
Garcia from Fishverly Hills.
Oiaiyonohoniaiu!
I'm sorry to make you feel so left alone.
The shock wave can travel
through water vapor in the air
Meverly from the Coral Apartment.
Those of you who support the Queen's passion,
put your signature in here!
and through to the water
within your target's body!
What are you talking about?!
There are a lot more!
Every living thing is made up of water.
So even a rubber man can't escape the impact!
Um... Father-sama, look at this.
TO SHIRAHOSHI
Stop!
At the Marine Shopping Mall
in the east of the island...
MARINE SHOPPING MALL
What is it?
I won't let you hurt my folk!
These letters keep flying in wherever I go.
We're former soldiers of Neptune's army!
We won't let you do whatever you want!
Well, enough for now.
We don't have time anyway.
There are already 5 of them, Father-sama!
It's...
Lastly...
...a love letter!
But Shirahoshi is only 6 years old.
I'M IN LUV WITH YOU. I SUSPECT.
MARRY ME. VANDER DECKEN
What?! He disappeared!
Damn you!
Who is Vander Decken?
What the...
Straw Hat Pirates!
I won't let you go, Luffy!
That is the name of a pirate family.
Second gear!
I'll show you something good.
Take this!
Gum-Gum...
The Fish-Men and humans.
He disappeared again! How can he do that?!
My children won't attend the funeral!
We were trying to ignore
the history of racism.
...Jet Stamp!
What?
I know you are somewhere on
the island watching this.
There could be an accomplice
still lurking around.
You people shattered Arlong's dream
- he was a symbol of Fish-Men's anger.
But the Queen took the first
step herself and now we have hope.
And catch this pirate named Decken now!
What can you civilians do now? Nothing!
Yes, sir!
Zoro! Usopp! Brook!
Is this all you learned from your training?
If she can get enough signatures,
the future of the island could change for real.
--What fools...
--I can't believe they got caught!
Zeo-san can change his skin color like
a chameleon and camouflage himself!
Don't bet on it!
It's even hard for us to
figure out where he is!
Do it.
Yes, Boss!
It would have helped Arlong if
he could have understood better...
Enough.
Do it.
Robin!
...about Queen Otohime's firm belief.
Robin-chan!
I-It's impossible for
us to beat a guy like that!
Hey, move aside, Robin!
Who are you?! Move!
Your only hope is...
--Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh?
--Wh-What's going on?!
I wish Brother Tai were here to see this.
Robin-chan's in danger!
...the Neptune brothers.
But they'll die soon just like the others.
Th-This is so high!
Which means you folk have...
Mother! Signatures keep coming
in from all over the country!
Oh, a bug!
--It's going well, isn't it?
--Yes, it's like a dream.
Kill it!
--What's this noise?
--It's like a roar...
It's because of your courage!
Everyone!
Courage?
Don't fight.
Look at the monitor!
I got encouraged at that very moment,
that this island would change for sure.
--It's water!
I don't know the reason but
you two are friends, right?
--Prince Fukaboshi!
--Prince-sama!
Huh?! Why did Robin come out of the forest?!
That room will be filled with water by
the time we finish executing the King.
What happened? He stopped talking.
That moment?
Fukaboshi...
WATERWHEEL TOWN
Yes, the moment that the Sea Kings
came and stared at the island.
Is the cockroach dead?
You lowly creatures can't
survive that, can you?
Yeah, it's flattened.
Take this!
That was surprising!
Citizens of the Fish-Man Island.
Straw Hat Luffy with a 400
million berry bounty!
Shirahoshi called them.
There is something I
want to tell you all today.
What?
Your people's heads will serve perfectly
as a lesson to humans above ground.
We Merfolk can communicate
with fish and talk to them, right?
Wh-Which means you folk have nowhere to run.
So please give me your attention.
J-Just give up! You guys can't win!
Now, let's start cleaning
up the old Ryugu Kingdom!
There's nowhere to run!
But no one can talk to those great Sea Kings.
He kept his nobility! He's not known as the
Noble of the Fish-Man District for nothing!
In her last moment, my mother said happily,
No way. Didn't you see
Boss Hordy's broadcast?
Is he pretending as if nothing happened?
This country will be destroyed.
And Neptune is gonna die!
Bury the embarrassing past and shift
the helm towards the great future!
Even your father Neptune who can talk to whales,
doesn't know how to talk to them.
"We are almost there at that
place under the real sun."
It's like a revolution.
What did you say?!
Later today, at Conchcorde Plaza,
No!
The Fish-Man Island will win
back its pride in three hours!
We have decided to take over
But according to our royal family's legend,
once in several hundred years,
Don't kill them.
our mother's dream and dedicate
our lives to seeing it through.
If you do so, you'll be no better than them!
the Neptune family will die
and the new king will rise.
one with an ability to communicate
with the Sea Kings, will be born.
Princes...
B-But...
Ryuboshi, Manboshi, take them into custody.
You probably are not going to be
ready for the World Summit in 2 years.
Now, let's go to the plaza!
--I got it-so-la-ti-do!
--Count on it!
--With those giant Sea Kings?!
--And Shirahoshi is the one?
I-I can't believe it!
Yes, and she will meet someone who will guide
her and her power in the right direction
But there will be another one in
6 years and another in 10 years.
Captain Hordy! Wh-What's the matter?!
You're as indulgent as before-dosun.
--It's nothing.
--But...
Does indulgence run in the
Neptune family's blood?
and it will cause a major change the world.
I'm sure this tragedy made you
change your view of humans.
Hey, bring it to me now! As much as we have!
You are not just getting back at
humans but hurting your fellow beings.
It? No way!
And that is the whole story.
So I will get rid of all the
signatures that were left unburned.
The world?
If it's true, there will be a
major change on this island too.
You better not take more Energy Steroid!
Doesn't it pain your heart?!
That's too much!
We won't let them do that!
Any Fish-Man who sides with
humans deserves death-dosun!
Let's start from the beginning!
Could it help what you're doing?
Yes, it could.
And when your emotional
wounds heal someday,
Do you want your head to
get smashed?! Just shut up!
It's a power of love that can save thousands
of lives if only the bearer wishes to.
Lead the way for your
father--towards death! Fukaboshi!
Captain! We got King Neptune already!
But with the wrong intentions, that power
could sink the whole world into the ocean.
Screw you!
Victory is within our grasp!
So you don't have to do that!
let's dream about the sun together again!
It is one of the most
fearsome powers in the world.
He's right! Don't push yourself too hard!
Shirahoshi doesn't know that she
has that power and she doesn't know
Now, issue an order to Daruma
and the others to assemble.
how to control it yet.
If something were ever to shock her,
It's gonna get busy.
Yes, Boss.
she could unintentionally
drive the Sea Kings berserk.
I'll make your execution a big show.
So that all citizens of the
Fish-Man Island will be afraid of me.
What?
The Fish-Man Island would be flattened
like a pancake! What should we do?!
Shit!
How could you be so selfish?
You can't govern a country like that!
Dammit!
Don't worry! I can take care of it for now.
They did it!
They got the New Fish-Man Pirates!
But the three of you will have to
become strong warriors someday
And for the decade that followed,
not just Fukaboshi, Ryuboshi and Manboshi
All kings are selfish.
Only the 3 great royal brothers could do it!
You were a selfish king to us.
I'm running out of time!
I said "Get out of my way"!
but also the King and the Princess spoke
to the nation through the monitor
and as her brothers and as warriors,
Prince Fukaboshi-sama!
Leave the rest up to us.
protect your baby sister with your lives!
You and Otohime's dream made me sick
ever since I was a soldier in your army.
I won't! I said "Leave it up to me"!
Thank you.
all while signatures kept mounting up again.
Let's get to Conchcorde
Plaza to save our father!
Why can't you understand
even after I've explained it?!
--Yes!
--Of course!
Shut up!
Thank you.
When the leader changes,
a country will change, too.
So that was how we have been fighting against
discrimination for the last 16 years
I don't give a damn about the history
between Fish-Men and humans
But then the unexpected happened...
All right. Let's go!
I will be the "law" from now on!
when my friends are in danger!
and the beginning of the Fish-Man Pirates.
That is why! That is why I want you to wait!
Okay, let's go to the execution ground.
Damn! The water level keeps rising!
Arlong, who did horrible
things to your hometown,
Do you want some of us to
stay here at the palace,
They both wanna help the
country and their friends.
Usopp-san, I just got dry.
I don't wanna soak in sea water again!
Boss Hordy?
Why do they have to fight?!
was like a brother to me.
No, I don't think so.
Me neither!
This Ryugu Palace is impregnable.
Signatures were mounting up at a rapid pace.
Do something, Zoro-kun!
Leave some men to open the
gate when we come back.
If he engaged in violence, we were willing to
go anywhere in order to stop him ourselves
How long will it take to Conchcorde Plaza?
"WATERWHEEL TOWN" TO "CONCHCORDE PLAZA"
All right. Then...
The islanders still didn't trust humans
Less than an hour!
We don't want the new
king getting locked out!
...untie me.
Got it!
It's not the actions of a sane
man to go through the trouble of
but they were hoping to see
the beginning of a new era.
but he always paid off the
Navy soldiers around him...
I feel it! I feel my psychic power!
Chains, come off! Chains, come off!
We sure don't!
That'd be nonsense-jamon!
executing the King at the plaza!
Queen Otohime!
...to keep his actions secret from the Navy.
I think they just wanna lure you Princes out!
You can't win citizens'
hearts with violence!
Chains, come off! Come
off, chains! Come off...
We brought our signatures again!
As a result, I made you
and many others suffer.
I don't care!
That's against the rules!
Each person can only vote once!
I am looking forward to it, rather.
I won't let them hurt my father!
You have only a little
life left. Say what you want.
...or not!
W-We're sorry...
It's no good. I don't have any psychic power.
And I won't let our people's minds close again,
not after they were just opening up!
But it means a lot to me that you did so.
Hey hey, did you see it?
This hurts.
The look on those Fish-Men's
faces when I moved.
Now I know why Jimbei
always had his eyes on Hordy!
I feel responsible!
That stupid swordsman cut me there.
Thank you so much.
Your efforts finally paid off.
The drug is wearing off.
Hey, give me the Energy Steroid.
And they are the reason we haven't seen
human pirates around the island these days!
Oh yeah?
Y-Yes.
Then why don't you cut your own belly?!
I wonder if Shirahoshi is
still in the Hard Shell Tower.
He isn't moving. Is he dead?
Sanji...
Pay her with your life!
I can't help worrying because we don't
hear anything about her-fa-so-la-ti-do!
I should stay dead.
I still won't forgive you but it
could relieve Nami-san of her pain!
Brother Fukaboshi-sama,
what do you think about the Straw Hats?
What should we do with
these skeletal remains?
The pain is gone!
Stop, Sanji-kun!
Get away! Fire!
Is it okay to take that much at once?
How did they even get here?
Madam Sharley said they
will destroy this country.
But Nami-san, what they
have done to you was...
I-I don't know.
I guess they flowed in with the water when
Captain Hordy broke the wall of the palace.
--How could the box catch fire?
--Water! Water!
Boss, what should we do
about those 3 Straw Hats?
That's a different story!
This man didn't mean to hurt us.
Put out the fire now!
They did not seem like they had bad intent.
I can't believe it!
They're just humans.
They'll drown if we leave them like that.
Let's pull them up onto the bridge.
The signatures we collected!
Great!
That's what I thought.
Run now!
Nami-san...
Brook can free us later if he
keeps pretending to be dead.
Straw Hat is Jimbei's friend and the Mermaids
at the cove didn't speak badly of them.
No matter who is coming to save them,
no one can break into the palace.
O-Otohime-sama!
Put out the fire! We have
to save the signatures!
I will take any punishment!
If it makes you happy...
Those Mermaids sure have an eye for people!
That aside, how are the new residents
from the Fish-Man District doing?
He was adrift at sea. I feel sorry for him.
No! It's too dangerous!
Stop!
But this is not the time to
think about those things!
They are very important! I have to save them!
Stop. The only one I hate is Arlong.
He must've been dead for 50 years or so.
They're doing fine.
That's correct!
Yeah, that's right-la-ti-do!
Your Majesty!
They're already moving.
Summon all soldiers from all over the country!
We will save the King at any cost!
We can't let them burn!
They are everyone's dream!
You got it right!
H-He's moving!
That's good.
There'll be empty houses for them.
Anyway, I'm glad that you are not the
mastermind of the Arlong Pirates.
Yes, I'm a dead skeleton--Brook!
They are the future of the Fish-Man Island!
Yes, sir!
Much!
Some will leave the country
and the others will die.
At Fishverly Hills in the
northeast of the island...
FISHVERLY HILLS
Because you're Luffy's friend, aren't you?
Yes, ma'am!
Save the signatures now!
They can just move into those houses.
Yes, sir!
It's true that I've gone through
hell because of the Arlong Pirates
Please save yourself!
Leave the rest up to us!
Wait!
Damn!
but I met my friends in
that horrible turmoil.
We'll make a great country in which
all citizens can look down on humans.
I can't believe that we are still
struggling against just one sea monster!
Nice, Brook!
There is something not
right with this sea monster!
One thing led to another
and I am who I am today.
Touch my bones!
I found it! The ray of hope!
I'm not gonna hate you
because you're a Fish-Man.
Here, here, here! Here!
You damn fools, it serves
you right! Good job, Sea Bear!
Those Fish-Men that we saw earlier are
all gone and nobody is here in the palace
That's enough!
So don't pity me because of my life!
but they left Pappagu-san behind.
The Energy Steroid worked too well!
It's not so bad because I'm
enjoying it in the present!
All right then, Brook,
ask Pappagu to find the key to unchain us.
C-Calm down, Sea Bear! That's enough!
Damn.
Those soldiers are barely alive.
So it's over, Sea Bear!
--And the keys to this cage and this room...
--Wait a minute, fool!
So it doesn't matter who did this...
Use this! Sea monsters don't like fire.
Oh, I can't stop laughing
just thinking about it!
Huh?
One of my swords is enough.
Just bring my sword.
Stop!
Don't get angry on my behalf.
We got caught because of you!
Much?
I'll cut them all!
Help! They're gonna kill me!
Wow, you're so reliable!
Don't tell the people
on the island anything!
Otohime-sama has been shot!
Oh, I'm already dead.
All right, I'll go ask Pappagu-san!
Neither the tragedy we endured
nor of our anger towards humans!
Who did it?!
The shooter must be here somewhere!
Protect the royal family!
Well, at least Nami and the others got away.
--Mother!
--Mother-sama!
They can bring Luffy and the others here.
Don't worry, Jimbei.
It's dangerous here! Get on the gondola now!
You two grew up together and
he's like a brother to you.
What if they don't come?!
Ikaros-san's body is contorting!
Princes!
Robin would say,
I-I'm scared!
No wonder you couldn't just kill
him even though you were justified.
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Is it some kind of curse?
"I hope Nami hasn't been
eaten by a deep-sea fish."
What the hell? I thought we
were just invited to a banquet.
Put out the fire-ch, you fool!
--Your Majesty!
--Otohime-sama!
Oh, crackle, crackle...
Sounds exactly like her!
Fire? What about the fire?
Oh no, Princess, this is pretty serious...
I wonder if those Straw Hats are doing okay.
I'm gonna become a piece of dried squid-ch!
I don't deserve such words of kindness!
Pappagu-san...
--Who're you?!
--Oops!
No way, fool!
--Stay away from the Princess!
--Stop!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Thank you!
I know you were trying to roast me and
eat me with sake. I'll kill you-ch!
--Mother-sama! Mother!
--Mother!
This is different from any of
Poneglyphs than I've seen before.
M-Mother!
Who would do that, fool?!
Nami!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Huh? Huh?
Ikaros-san once had a best
friend who was a giant squid.
This is like a letter... A letter of apology.
Dammit! Who the hell did it?!
--Pappagu-san...
--What? What?
--Didn't an emergency team arrive yet?!
--Mother! Mother!
One day, he went too close to the sun
and became a giant dried squid!
Boss Jimbei-sama...
I found you!
Who are you apologizing to? And who are you?
Oh! I know how hard it is to be a big brother!
You're the man, Jimbei!
Open your eyes!
This can't be forgiven! I'll make him pay!
That's why when Ikaros-san sees fire, he...
"Joy Boy."
Boom!
Daidalos!
I'm here!
I like Tiger and Otoshime
and everybody very much!
He's a Fish-Man. He's not
gonna be like his friend.
Mother!
Daida...
Stay near me, my angels.
A ghost!
Shut up, Franky!
He must've been feeling so much pain...
Don't lose your temper.
Wait!
My guard was down. Because I was
thrilled that everybody was signing.
Be careful hereafter-ch!
It's a ghost--I'm scared!
Oh no!
Pappagu-san! It's me!
That Dried Squid Spear is always waiting for
its chance to turn back into a normal squid.
I don't have much time! I need the
key... I mean, the sword! Hey, wait!
I was so happy!
Hey.
What?
So once it gets stuck in someone,
it'll suck all fluid out of his body!
Luffy?
Prince Fukaboshi, I should
be the one who is frustrated.
He said I'm worth 400 million!
When did they raise it?
No, stay away!
Your Majesty, you need treatment now!
Ika!
--No!!
--What do you mean "No"? Listen to me! Wait!
What?!
This is no time for that!
Ika, Ika, Ika, Ika, Ika, Ika, Ika...
Hey, wake up!
So it doesn't matter who did this...
Obviously, they want to fight us.
That's awful!
He's pummeling that guy who got dried out!
The War of the Best at Marineford
made you infamous instantly.
That was a good nap.
I can't believe it! I thought it was
unusual for you to listen so quietly.
Don't get angry on my behalf.
Ikaros-san, that's enough!
When it goes over 300 million,
it's not easily increased again.
Don't we have to go to the plaza already?!
Huh? Jimbei, are you crying?!
Don't let resentment or hatred
get the better of you for my sake.
Much! You're right!
It's too late.
He already became a dried squid.
Are you okay, you two? And Sanji?
What are you saying? I am not crying!
But if somebody wants
to fight me, I'll fight!
Minister of the Right! Look up!
Think about it, Luffy!
Hey wait, Luffy-kun!
Why is that?
Cut it out! I said I am not crying!
What will happen if you guys resort to
violence now on the Fish-Man Island?
Is that Hordy and the others?
Father-sama...
Hmmm... Oh, well!
I don't see Hordy but I see some
men from the Fish-Man District!
Everytime Fish-Men tried to open their
hearts to humans, humans disappointed them.
They're heading to the plaza!
And Jimbei, what did happen to the
thief that Coward's mother caught?
Father-sama!
M-Mother-sama...
Father-sama! Father-sama!
Damn, those bastards!
Look! The King-sama is on board!
You must've been sleeping most of
the time! That was the very beginning!
"Humans are very violent."
"Humans hate and look down on Fish-Men."
Megalo!
King Neptune-sama!
Shirahoshi, keep your senses.
--Was it?
--It was!
Help us!
Hey, so your name is Shirahoshi?
What happened in the past planted those
twisted ideas in Fish-Men's minds.
I have to go save him!
Great Knight, perform a miracle to save us!
Wait, Princess Shirahoshi!
N-Nami-chin, she's the Princess!
You can't say "Hey"...
Don't call me Great Knight.
Stop, Megalo!
I can't save my citizens--look at me!
In the case of Arlong,
Yes. Oh, excuse me.
If something were ever to shock her...
Wait!
many Fish-Men believe that humans
hunted him because he was a Fish-Man.
How pathetic!
Boss Jimbei-sama! But...
I was crying remembering my mother.
King-sama!
Luffy-kun, Princess-sama,
both of you have to wait!
We are the King's army but we
can't even protect the King?!
She was quite a woman, wasn't she?
If you, the people who beat
Arlong, fight Hordy now,
This is just like...!
Yes!
Then, what are we here for?!
Princess, I don't think you should go either.
what do you think will happen?
Ikaros-san! There are only 2
hours left until the execution!
So you are Nami-chin-sama.
No, Mermaid Princess-sama!
Hachi-sama...
Even if it helps the island
overcome this crisis,
Shirahoshi, no!
Come with us to Conchcorde Plaza!
Nami-chin is like her nickname.
Her real name has no "chin."
What Hordy is most afraid of
in the Ryugu Kingdom now is...
What happened to Captain Hordy-ch?!
I know he's there-ch!
Hey, Shirahoshi!
witnessing you people knocking down
Hordy who is standing against humans...
It feels like I have known you since I was a
kid although we just met for the first time...
...Princess Shirahoshi's ability!
Why doesn't he even come out-ch?! Much!
Well...
...would make the islanders to think
that things will never change.
Even if he reshapes the Fish-Man
Island exactly the way he wants,
I feel comfortable with you.
Yeah? Maybe that's because we've
been through similar things.
Moonfish mambo! Moonfish mambo!
once she controls the Sea Kings
to attack the island, it'll be gone.
That drug enhances your strength
but takes years off your life.
Moonfish mambo! Moonfish mambo!
You shouldn't take it in
the first place-jamon.
He took the King hostage
to use him as a shield.
Look, Shirahoshi!
Moonfish mambo! Moonfish mambo!
Shut up!
Now, excuse me.
--It's fun! It's fun!
--Shake, shake! Shake, shake!
Captain Hordy said he got cut by
the pirate swordsman and it hurts!
I took too much time. I need to know
who is still at the Ryugu Palace now.
So what they're really going
for is Shirahoshi-chan.
But, Jimbei,
--It's nothing! Let's sing Shirahoshi!
--Moonfish mambo! Shake, shake, shake!
we have to rescue our crew.
Cut? The Boss got cut?!
Hordy and his crew invaded the palace
and captured the King and his soldiers.
Hordy is not planning to capture
her and get control of her power.
We three will always be
there for you-la-ti-do!
And if nothing is done,
Hordy will rule the Fish-Man Island.
So he kept taking the Energy
Steroid to kill the pain!
He prefers her power didn't exist at all.
And you don't know what
happened to four of your crew.
We have so many friends on the island.
Mambo dance is fun!
And he ended up... I mean,
we told him to stop!
That's why he teamed up with Decken
who is capable of killing her.
That's all the information we have so far.
Hey, Hachi.
You've been trying so hard
to hide who did that to you
Jimbei-san.
It's fun!
Hordy wants to get rid of everything
that could stand in his way.
If things are going as Hordy planned,
It's fun-do-re-mi-fa!
Captain Hordy!
the whole country might be
in a terrible state by now.
but you said a while ago...
P-Princes, what are you doing?!
He is right.
...that Hordy attacks those Fish-Men
who are sympathetic to humans.
I can't... breathe!
--Stop them!
--That's not appropriate!
Rushing to the plaza is just what
Hordy wants Princess-sama to do!
Do you know what his plan is?!
My body is gonna explode!
Mother, look, we're fine!
Did you get beaten by them
because you spoke up for us?
I have been told about my power but...
Much! Is it a side-effect-ch?! So that
drug could kill you as I thought-ch!
I suspected he was up to something
in the Fish-Man District
We will protect our baby sister
like this forever-la-ti-do!
after retiring from the army,
...I have never communicated
with the Sea Kings-sama.
but he never revealed it to me.
Stop it! Can't you see
the Queen's situation?!
I don't even know if I really
have that kind of power...
Yeah, I know.
Hachi!
Hordy hates humans more
than Arlong-san did.
But even so, I'm sure that
Hordy will try to kill you.
Mother-sama!
Hatchin, is that true?
Hordy and his crew did that to you?
We will collect the signatures
that burned away again.
He has been living on the resentment and
anger of the Fish-Men, and nothing else.
I can't...
And we shouldn't let Hordy know
that you can't control the power.
Jimbei!
We three will become great
warriors like our father...
I think part of the reason Luffy wants
to fight is because this is your home.
It's good that he is afraid of it.
And there is something about him
clearly different from Arlong-san.
Is that all? Then I'll get going.
...and protect Shirahoshi
with our lives as we promised!
I heard that you helped our captain
when he had his back against the wall.
Arlong-san would look down on humans
but he would never hurt other Fish-Men.
Shark! Take me to the Ryugu Palace!
So please...
Sanji, take care of Coward!
Yeah! Count on it.
But Hordy will attack those Fish-Men
who are sympathetic to humans...
Please don't worry!
I said "Wait," Luffy-kun!
Huh?
We can't thank you enough for that.
You people shouldn't fight Hordy!
Th-That's...!
...without mercy!
Why are you trying to stop me?
Is it because we're humans?
And if Luffy wants to fight,
we will go along with him!
This year is the World Summit which
takes place every four years.
You two shouldn't say that!
It makes things more complicated!
That's right! You humans shouldn't do that!
Since they gathered enough signatures,
We can't just leave the island like this.
The surviving Fish-Men
will hate humans again!
Hey, what's wrong, Sea Bear?!
King Neptune will express his
intention to the world finally,
We have reason to fight!
He's acting strange!
Although all these sea monsters
are under Captain Hordy's control,
to relocate the Fish-Man Island.
You have to leave it to me.
I've never seen them get so scared!
Don't tell me he is planning to block it!
Jimbei! They have my crew!
No, he wants more than that.
And I got to do something about Hordy
before my friends get into real trouble!
--C-Captain Hordy?!
--Are you all right?!
The reason is...
Luffy-chin...
Straw Hat.
Camie-chan's here!
Why shouldn't I be all right?
And Shirahoshi-chan's here!
Wh-What is that?!
Why can't you see it?!
Yes! This country is the
Mermaid paradise of my dreams!
--I'm going.
--You're impossible!
That's a big Transponder Snail!
Just shut up!
We are almost there!
It's a Video Transponder Snail!
Stop me if you can!
Captain Hordy!
At that place under the real sun!
Luffy.
Why is it here?
Look! It's activated!
I shouldn't let my guard down
just because we fought together.
Oh, it's projecting something on the bubble!
Get out of my way, Jimbei!
You gotta let me go!
Oh, I see some soldiers from the army!
No, I won't! Leave it up to me!
I almost forgot that
you're that man's brother.
That's...
Water Shot!
He's the...
If you're not going to
listen to me, I have no choice!
Nami-san, do you know him?
You bastard!
Whoa... Whoa!
Then I'll just beat my way past you!
Hordy!
What?! That's him?!
I'll fight you as many times as
I have to till you understand!
Hatchin!
Uh, everybody on the Fish-Man Island.
What did you say?!
Cut it out, guys!
Can you hear me?
I'm the captain of the New Fish-Man
Pirates from the Fish-Man District,
You ready to do this?
Kid?
Hordy Jones!
After Otohime's death, Fish-Man
Island is consumed by rage.
Hordy broadcasts his ambition
across all of Fish-Man Island.
Luffy and Jinbei's emotional
battle has begun!
Neptune's execution draws ever closer.
Facing the destructive power of Hordy's new form,
His shocking intention is
to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom
Hordy's powerful allies are mobilizing.
Is this the end for her ideal?
Neptune's army is defeated.
Luffy faces the overwhelming force
of Jimbei's Fish-Man Karate.
and establish himself as the new king.
The New Fish-Man Pirates are overrunning
every part of Fish-Man Island.
After relating the subsequent
events on Fish-Man Island,
The citizens have only one hope remaining...
The citizens of Fish-Man Island
had been deeply unsettled already,
and finishing his story, Jimbei
again apologizes to Nami.
The three Neptune brothers!
Their duel is interrupted,
and takes an unexpected turn!
But then, just as his ambition
is coming to fruition,
They rise to face Hordy, and their battle begins!
but Hordy's announcement has
further filled them with dread!
But Nami's reply was utterly unexpected!
an terrifying change befalls Hordy!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Rift Opens Up!
Luffy vs. Jimbei!"
"The Kingdom in Shock!
An Order to Execute Neptune Issued!"
"The Battle is on!
At Conchcorde Plaza!"
"Back to the Present! Hordy Makes a Move!"
"Something Has Happened to Hordy!
The True Power of the Evil Drug!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!