Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil
and Zoro, Usopp and Brook got
caught by Hordy at the Ryugu Palace.
I'm gonna go to the Ryugu Palace to save
my crew and kick that Hordy guy's ass!
I said "Don't do it"!
"Something Has Happened to Hordy!
The True Power of the Evil Drug!"
It's time for the decisive battle!
Well, as soon as we cut the King's head off,
the morale of his army will be shattered
and then it's over!
Which means we'll have a new king soon!
I can't wait!
Meanwhile, at Candy Factory
Town in the center of the island...
CANDY FACTORY
Daruma-san, w-what are you...?
--He's chewing the wall of the factory...
--W-What powerful jaws!
My fangs itch!
You fools!
I don't want some trendy cappuccino
and cake for my happy snack time!
Do I look like a yuppie?!
I-I'm sorry, Daruma-san!
Do you want me to bite your flesh off?!
My favorite snack is the bones of
big fish! And don't ever forget it!
Y-Yes, I'll be careful from now on!
That's okay. I'm gonna go chew up the
royal family and their soldiers now!
See you at Conchcorde Plaza!
We all have to be there! Don't be late!
What should we do about the citizens?
Weren't you listening to what Boss said?
He said "No more stepping on her picture."
Leave them alone!
They know what's waiting for them!
The New Fish-Man Pirates have...
...4 shark Fish-Man officers including Hordy,
and 1 giant squid Fish-Man.
Plus, they have a blue-ringed
octopus Merman as a bodyguard,
who is the best swordsman on the island.
Our only hope is the Neptune brothers.
I believe in the Princes!
Kotsun...
At Waterwheel Town in
the north of the island...
WATERWHEEL TOWN
--The Princes are heading to Conchcorde Plaza!
--What's gonna happen to this country?
I don't know. All we wanted was
friendly relations with humans.
Why should our lives be threatened?
I can't believe they're
gonna execute the King.
Can't we stop them by taking
these guys as hostages?
Hostages?
No, that's not gonna work.
Boss Hordy is a ruthless man-kotsun.
Even if you try it, he'll just cut
us off and go on as planned-kotsun.
This is not good. Because he
got beaten by the Princes,
Dosun-san's power level
went down to "kotsun."
He needs the Energy Steroid.
All right.
He's always been like that-kotsun.
He has too much pride-potsun.
"Potsun"?
He doesn't like Fish-Men who do
business with human pirates-posun.
"Posun"?
Those Fish-Men who transfused
blood to wounded humans,
he punished them by attacking
them in the dark-tosun.
"Tosun"?
Humans' blood is tainted-tosun.
Both giving them blood
and getting their blood...
...degrades our Fish-Man blood-dosun!
He's back to "dosun"!
Those Fish-Men who support
the horrible humans are...
...getting in the way of...
Be quiet!
...Our noble intentions-dokan!
He exceeded "dosun"!
He broke the chain!
You bastard!
The soldiers got blown away!
Damn Fukaboshi!
I'll get even with you-bokan!
I'll beat you to within an inch
of your life next time-zugan!
Let's go, guys-bagon!
To Conchcorde Plaza,
the execution ground-gaban!
In front of the Fish-Man Cultural
Hall in the south of the island...
FISH-MAN CULTURAL HALL
Who did you say is drunk?
You are, Hyouzou-san!
Get yourself back together!
You can't fight like that!
No worries, no worries! This is my treat!
What are you talking about?!
We have to fight Neptune's army
which is being led by Fukaboshi now!
In the worst-case scenario,
the infamous Jimbei will be there too!
Hey! Stand on your feet!
It's no good. He's as
slippery as a sea cucumber.
I can't believe how many degrees
your head can spin around.
It's not spinning! You're too drunk!
Boy! I bet you can't even hold your sword!
No, I can!
Hey, stay away from him!
Hyouzou will slice into
anyone when he gets drunk!
He will... slice?
He sliced his friend!
That wasn't enough!
I wanna cut more!
H-Hyouzou-san!
Go to the plaza now and slice up the
Neptunes to your heart's content!
Oiaiyonohoniaiu!
What are you talking about?!
At the Marine Shopping Mall
in the east of the island...
MARINE SHOPPING MALL
We're former soldiers of Neptune's army!
We won't let you do whatever you want!
What?! He disappeared!
What the...
Take this!
He disappeared again! How can he do that?!
What can you civilians do now? Nothing!
Zeo-san can change his skin color like
a chameleon and camouflage himself!
It's even hard for us to
figure out where he is!
I-It's impossible for
us to beat a guy like that!
Your only hope is...
...the Neptune brothers.
But they'll die soon just like the others.
Which means you folk have...
Oh, a bug!
Kill it!
What happened? He stopped talking.
Is the cockroach dead?
Yeah, it's flattened.
Wh-Which means you folk have nowhere to run.
There's nowhere to run!
He kept his nobility! He's not known as the
Noble of the Fish-Man District for nothing!
Is he pretending as if nothing happened?
It's like a revolution.
Later today, at Conchcorde Plaza,
the Neptune family will die
and the new king will rise.
Now, let's go to the plaza!
Captain Hordy! Wh-What's the matter?!
--It's nothing.
--But...
Hey, bring it to me now! As much as we have!
It? No way!
You better not take more Energy Steroid!
That's too much!
Do you want your head to
get smashed?! Just shut up!
Captain! We got King Neptune already!
Victory is within our grasp!
So you don't have to do that!
He's right! Don't push yourself too hard!
I'm running out of time!
I said "Get out of my way"!
I won't! I said "Leave it up to me"!
Why can't you understand
even after I've explained it?!
Shut up!
I don't give a damn about the history
between Fish-Men and humans
when my friends are in danger!
That is why! That is why I want you to wait!
They both wanna help the
country and their friends.
Why do they have to fight?!
How long will it take to Conchcorde Plaza?
"WATERWHEEL TOWN" TO "CONCHCORDE PLAZA"
Less than an hour!
It's not the actions of a sane
man to go through the trouble of
executing the King at the plaza!
I think they just wanna lure you Princes out!
I don't care!
I am looking forward to it, rather.
I won't let them hurt my father!
And I won't let our people's minds close again,
not after they were just opening up!
Now I know why Jimbei
always had his eyes on Hordy!
And they are the reason we haven't seen
human pirates around the island these days!
I wonder if Shirahoshi is
still in the Hard Shell Tower.
I can't help worrying because we don't
hear anything about her-fa-so-la-ti-do!
Brother Fukaboshi-sama,
what do you think about the Straw Hats?
Madam Sharley said they
will destroy this country.
They did not seem like they had bad intent.
That's what I thought.
Straw Hat is Jimbei's friend and the Mermaids
at the cove didn't speak badly of them.
Those Mermaids sure have an eye for people!
But this is not the time to
think about those things!
Yeah, that's right-la-ti-do!
Summon all soldiers from all over the country!
We will save the King at any cost!
Yes, sir!
Much!
At Fishverly Hills in the
northeast of the island...
FISHVERLY HILLS
Damn!
I can't believe that we are still
struggling against just one sea monster!
There is something not
right with this sea monster!
You damn fools, it serves
you right! Good job, Sea Bear!
The Energy Steroid worked too well!
C-Calm down, Sea Bear! That's enough!
Those soldiers are barely alive.
So it's over, Sea Bear!
Use this! Sea monsters don't like fire.
Stop!
Much?
Ikaros-san's body is contorting!
Is it some kind of curse?
Put out the fire-ch, you fool!
Oh, crackle, crackle...
Fire? What about the fire?
I'm gonna become a piece of dried squid-ch!
No way, fool!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I know you were trying to roast me and
eat me with sake. I'll kill you-ch!
Who would do that, fool?!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Ikaros-san once had a best
friend who was a giant squid.
One day, he went too close to the sun
and became a giant dried squid!
That's why when Ikaros-san sees fire, he...
Daidalos!
He's a Fish-Man. He's not
gonna be like his friend.
Daida...
Be careful hereafter-ch!
Oh no!
That Dried Squid Spear is always waiting for
its chance to turn back into a normal squid.
So once it gets stuck in someone,
it'll suck all fluid out of his body!
Ika!
Ika, Ika, Ika, Ika, Ika, Ika, Ika...
That's awful!
He's pummeling that guy who got dried out!
Ikaros-san, that's enough!
Don't we have to go to the plaza already?!
Much! You're right!
It's too late.
He already became a dried squid.
Minister of the Right! Look up!
Is that Hordy and the others?
I don't see Hordy but I see some
men from the Fish-Man District!
They're heading to the plaza!
Damn, those bastards!
Look! The King-sama is on board!
King Neptune-sama!
Help us!
Great Knight, perform a miracle to save us!
Don't call me Great Knight.
I can't save my citizens--look at me!
How pathetic!
King-sama!
We are the King's army but we
can't even protect the King?!
Then, what are we here for?!
Ikaros-san! There are only 2
hours left until the execution!
Come with us to Conchcorde Plaza!
What happened to Captain Hordy-ch?!
I know he's there-ch!
Why doesn't he even come out-ch?! Much!
Well...
That drug enhances your strength
but takes years off your life.
You shouldn't take it in
the first place-jamon.
Shut up!
Captain Hordy said he got cut by
the pirate swordsman and it hurts!
Cut? The Boss got cut?!
So he kept taking the Energy
Steroid to kill the pain!
And he ended up... I mean,
we told him to stop!
Captain Hordy!
I can't... breathe!
My body is gonna explode!
Much! Is it a side-effect-ch?! So that
drug could kill you as I thought-ch!
Th-That's...!
Hey, what's wrong, Sea Bear?!
He's acting strange!
Although all these sea monsters
are under Captain Hordy's control,
I've never seen them get so scared!
--C-Captain Hordy?!
--Are you all right?!
Why shouldn't I be all right?
Captain Hordy!
Oh, I see some soldiers from the army!
Water Shot!
Facing the destructive power of Hordy's new form,
Neptune's army is defeated.
The citizens have only one hope remaining...
The three Neptune brothers!
They rise to face Hordy, and their battle begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Battle is on!
At Conchcorde Plaza!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!