Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
On their way to the New World, Luffy and
his crew reached the Fish-Man Island,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates
who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom,
are engaging in secret maneuvers.
and his friends venture into that sea.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Friends or foes? That's something...
On their way to the New World,
...you'll have to decide on your own!
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
"A Big Clash! The Straw Hats vs.
A Hundred Thousand Enemies!"
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil
caught up in the turmoil.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil
caught up in the turmoil.
S-So he's the Straw Hat Luffy who
invaded the Navy HQ twice, 2 years ago!
while Zoro, Usopp and Brook get
captured by Hordy at the Ryugu Palace.
--We've been waiting for you, Straw Hat!
--H-He really came!
Get out of my way, Jimbei!
You gotta let me go!
There are 30,000 human slaves we've
caught in the sea over the past month.
A pirate ship is here, too!
She broke... She broke my heart!
Luffy-sama, what did you just call me?
So are all the Straw Hats!
No, I won't! Leave it up to me!
Oh yeah.
You were calling me "Coward
(Yowamushi)" before.
You bastard!
And 70,000 Fish-Men who know how to use arms.
Then I'll just beat my way past you!
Yeah, it's not like I know everything but
you're not as timid as I thought you were.
What's wrong?
I'll fight you as many times as
I have to till you understand!
I got an idea!
They moved here from the
closed Fish-Man District.
What don't I just destroy
everything altogether?!
So I'll call you Yowahoshi from now on!
What did you say?!
Behold...
Boy, he gave me a lot of trouble...
...100,000 outlaws altogether!
All pirates will fall down on their knees
before us--the New Fish-Man Pirates!
Take care of Hachi, Camie!
Y-Yes.
Look at these human pirates with
confidence in their ability to fight!
Look how powerful I am!
Go, Megalo!
Silly Straw Hat! I can't believe
he was hiding in the shark's mouth!
This is the power that I'm talking about!
You will all be like them, Straw Hat!
I thought that skeleton and the others
were captive in the Ryugu Palace.
I started this whole thing 10 years ago.
So that was the true power of the drug!
I'll be the one who becomes
King of the Pirates!
--We've been waiting for you, Straw Hat!
--H-He really came!
Let me tell you something.
Concerning the late Queen of the Ryugu
Kingdom, who you fools still love!
The King of the Pirates?
Madam Sharley! The pirate
with a hat just showed up!
Oh, I see some soldiers from the army!
We have 100,000 on our side!
He saved the King and the Princes!
Otohime was killed by...
"A Surprising Confession! The Truth
Behind the Assassination of Otohime!"
Water Shot!
Straw Hat boy...
Hey, Luffy!
...me!
That 400 million berry prize is mine!
Did I do okay, Jimbei?
No, mine!
No way!
It wasn't so disastrous,
considering it was Luffy.
We are almost at the plaza! Hurry up, Megalo!
What?!
Your mother was not murdered by a human!
Mm-hm. Although it did not
go exactly as we had planned...
Kill him!
Father-sama...
Hey! I'm here-jamon!
I, her kinsman, did it!
A FEW HOURS AGO--SEA FOREST
Boss Jimbei-sama! Megalo!
Outta my way!
No, I won't let you go!
"The Battle is on!
At Conchcorde Plaza!"
Hey! I'm here-jamon!
Luffy-chin... Boss Jimbei...
I, standing in front of you now, killed her!
What's going on here?!
I'm so happy to see you!
Hey, that's enough already!
E-Excuse me, but they are
going to kill Father-sama!
Father-sama!
He didn't do anything but
so many of us got knocked out!
I said "Outta my way"!
I'm gonna go kick those guys' asses!
I'm coming!
You're Hordy, right?
I guess I have to kick your ass.
No, wait!
How many times do I have to tell you?
I said "Wait"! Let me finish!
I already knew it.
Father-sama!
You can become king of whatever
you want in any country.
Shirahoshi!
Captain Hordy is awesome-ch!
How would you describe our relationship?
I can't believe that he was just writhing in
agony from an Energy Steroid overdose-ch!
We're friends!
But there can only be
one King of the Pirates!
That's right.
What?
It's such a simple relationship but the
Fish-Men and humans couldn't establish it
Please stop!
Princess Shirahoshi!
"Deadly Attacks One After Another!
Zoro and Sanji Join the Battle!"
"Shirahoshi's Tears!
Luffy Finally Shows Up!"
If you don't wanna see the
Princess get hurt, freeze!
and have been struggling to do so for years.
When I left you the message
"Don't fight against Hordy,"
L-Let me go!
I meant "Don't fight him recklessly."
Don't rush!
Alright, let's take her!
If you just go and beat Hordy up,
people on the island will think that you
are just another violent human bully.
CONCHCORDE PLAZA
What do you mean you already knew that...
N-Neptune's army's been beaten!
Instead,
I want you to become the hero who
will save the Fish-Man Island!
No way!
...I killed your mother, Shirahoshi?!
They got wiped out!
Exactly how strong is Hordy?!
We have quite an audience.
Hero?
No!
Minister of the Right-dono!
What?!
Minister of the Left-dono!
We're pirates!
Damn!
I love heroes but I don't wanna be one!
Neptune-sama!
Father! Are you all right?!
What a view!
King-sama!
Stay with us!
Do you know what heroes are?
Prince Mamboshi!
Prince Ryuboshi!
Shirahoshi!
Say there is a chunk of meat.
Let's go to Conchcorde Plaza!
Prince Fukaboshi-sama!
Pirates will have a banquet and eat it
--Oh, what...
--...Extraordinary power!
How did the pirates manage that?!
A few years after it happened,
but heroes will share it with other people.
Oh no, Neptune-sama!
The Princes were winning by far!
Megalo told me secretly.
I want all the meat!
So he's the Straw Hat Luffy!
Suddenly, the tables
have turned against them!
Megalo?!
Is that how he defines a hero?
He did?!
Oh, I wanna fight some more-zugon!
So it all comes back to meat again.
I will let you have your meat
just as long as you do as I tell you!
Much! Don't get so heated up! Or I'm gonna
become a piece of dried squid-ch!
Is that true, Megalo?!
Neptune-sama!
Okay.
Soldiers of the army. The ministers.
What?! That easy?!
He's out of our league!
In the simplest terms, I will call for
your help so I want you to respond.
And the royal family. There is no one
left in this country, who can fight us now!
Where do you think you're going?
If you run from your enemy on this historic
day for the Fish-Men, you deserve death.
No...
We were almost...
Help you?
What unbelievable power!
Yes, first, Megalo and I will get caught
voluntarily and enter the plaza.
...almost there!
I'm sorry, Father!
We may have lost 50,000.
You don't have to be!
Those powers are fake-jamon!
Your efforts were expected to bear
fruit at the World Summit this year!
While they are paying attention to us,
But...
That doesn't really matter if it
enables them to take over the country!
Megalo was owned by
Neptune's army back then.
...we are still 50,000 strong!
Captain Hordy, let's put them to death!
one of you sneak out of
Megalo's stomach and...
Queen Otohime!
--Burn them alive!
--No, impale them!
And he witnessed everything that day!
But then they started this all of a sudden!
The Straw Hats always shatter
our dreams. They're our...
I wish a terrible death on those who lack
pride and look to coexist with the humans!
Out of his stomach?
Please save him!
If nothing is done, they will kill King-sama!
...worst enemy!
Let's show the audience!
They will have the letter
from the Celestial Dragons.
Mother! Mother!
Let's just kill them!
Please! Please save the King!
Kill them! Kill them!
What letter?
Oh yeah.
And Jimbei!
Luffy was sleeping so he
missed most of Jimbei's story.
Kill them! Kill them!
He lives Otohime's dream
and befriends humans!
Kill them! Kill them!
It is...
...something Queen Otohime acquired
10 years ago, at the risk of her life
But that's not the future we Fish-Men want!
Kill them!
Silence.
and it will define the future of this island!
He's right! Straw Hat is nothing!
He's just a human!
Mom!
I can't believe it.
I haven't heard from Decken's crew yet,
with regards to Shirahoshi's death.
And they will also have
the key to free the King.
Princess Shirahoshi, why didn't you...
And Jimbei betrayed the Fish-Men!
Let's kill them both!
If I told anyone...!
We need to get our hands on those 2 things.
There is no point in doing
this if we can't lure her here!
Who is up to it?
Someone would hold a grudge
against Hordy-sama, I thought.
I'm good at stealing! I can do it with Robin.
Don't do anything to our sister!
She won't fight!
What's gonna happen to this country?!
Yeah.
Luffy! I wish you left more
than 50,000 of them for me.
All right. Once you free the King,
I will call for Luffy-kun's help.
She wouldn't harm you in any way!
And that is not what Mother-sama wanted!
Oh, sorry.
You think that I don't know anything?
Don't get so excited.
And once Luffy-kun emerges gallantly,
out of Megalo's body,
Huh?
I'll go for 30,000! Okay, Moss Head?
She's the Mermaid with that troublesome
power so I want to be rid of her the most.
people will notice that Luffy-kun
and I are working together.
Shut up, Mr. Nosebleed.
Huh?
Princess-sama, you wait somewhere
completely safe outside of the plaza.
That was the last promise we made with her.
You audience babies!
Hordy!
Captain Hordy!
And after we pass you the letter,
flee with the freed King and the Princes.
Okay! Let me do one song for
the beginning of the battle!
She told us that no matter who did it to her,
We got them!
Captain! Hey Captain!
Captain Decken,
things will start looking up soon.
Meanwhile, the rest of you, get to the
Ryugu Place now and save your friends.
we should not get angry or hate anybody!
You fool! I don't need you to comfort me!
Princess Shirahoshi and
Jimbei got caught in a trap!
And then, hurry to the plaza with them.
You guys don't know how painful
it is to be broken-hearted!
They're not here to see you.
So it doesn't matter who did this...
Shirahoshi!
Now--about how to rescue your
friends in the Ryugu Palace...
I mean, Shirahoshi was
just a kid when we first met.
Father-sama! Brothers-sama!
As always, Robin-san's so cool!
Don't get angry on my behalf.
How lucky I am!
And I decided to marry her to
fulfill my ancestors' dream!
They weren't listening at all, were they?
Figure it out yourself!
Don't let resentment or hatred
get the better of you for my sake.
You don't care about us, do you?!
Okay! Super count on it!
That's because I whispered it!
We caught the two that I
concerned about most, all at once.
And how did it all turn out?
--What?!
--He has too much pride.
We have the Sunny!
Shirahoshi, you...
This is too good to be true!
We'll figure it out!
Don't tell me that you...
Mm-hm.
Kill them!
I-I am very sorry!
Once this is all set into motion, how do
you think the citizens will respond?
You did as Mother said
to do 10 years ago and...
--Let's show them...
--...How great Fish-Men are!
You wouldn't have to go through
this if I hadn't been fooled...
Both the citizens of the Fish-Man Island
You're not my type!
What's done is done so never mind.
...you have been keeping this to yourself all
this time, alone in the Hard Shell Tower?!
and the outlaws of the Fish-Man
District respect Jimbei-san.
So you're here as I thought, Jimbei.
"Not my type" she said When the words came
to my ears I felt my true love grow, I suspect.
Uh-huh. So if they find out that Boss trusts
Luffy-chin with his life, to save the King,
Let's do it!
I liked you back when you were a wild man.
Third Gear!
A haiku with extra syllables.
By Vander Decken IX.
What happened to you, Hordy?
You look so different from before.
they'll root for you, Luffy-chin!
I don't care if there're
thousands of you! Just bring it on!
She broke... She broke my heart!
She tried not to harbor hate for
the one who killed her mother?
Straw Hat.
It's Boss Jimbei!
Gum-Gum...
I thought he left the island
after he quit the Warlords!
Luffy-sama.
--Here he comes!
--What's wrong with his hand?!
Even though it was her dying mother's wish,
I was dumped so I cut my hair!
I heard that Princess Shirahoshi had
been kidnapped by Straw Hat Luffy.
I am only doing this because
you asked me to, Jimbei!
...Giant Pistol!
it's almost unthinkable someone
would be able to keep such a promise!
It's uncomfortable having
everybody cheer me on.
Did Boss Jimbei rescue her?
Only the top?!
I wanted to kill her but she's still alive!
She is such an obedient, admirable girl!
Yeah, we're not used to that treatment.
Now, everyone that I wanted to see is here.
I know it because I still
can throw things at her!
Who else could have done such a thing?!
All right, let's join him.
I'd fight the king of the devils himself
if the Mermaids-chan cheered for me!
It was easier than I thought.
That Straw Hat fool must be protecting her!
That fool didn't wait for us again.
Thank you!
My only concern now is
what the Straw Hats will do.
I've got to do this, after seeing
tears in Shirahoshi-chan's eyes.
That settles it.
Stop laughing, you fool!
Okay, let's do it!
I can't help it! Hey, Megalo?
But I assume they're desperately looking
for a way in to the Ryugu Palace now.
Oh yeah.
You must have been trying
so hard to protect...
Is there something else?
...that small "sprout"
single-handedly, day after day.
If you had cried out right there,
you could've drawn everybody's attention
Should we pick a codename
for this operation?
What's wrong?
Even if they make it here after
they find their friends dead,
But let us protect it for you this time.
Who cares!
I got an idea!
Alright, let's hurry up!
and let them know that I
was the one who did it.
What don't I just destroy
everything altogether?!
we're totally ready to ambush them!
So you saved your friends at the
Ryugu Palace successfully.
So thank you for shutting your mouth!
It's gonna be great!
And thank you for confiding
only in this dumb girl!
Straw!
Men who can't wipe away the tears
from women's eyes aren't real men.
Pappagu! I'm happy to see you again!
Let's wreck these guys!
If it were anybody else,
we couldn't have come this far!
But, but, I've had quite a few brushes
with death because of them!
When this is over, let's have a drink
at the Mermaid Cafe, Shirahoshi-chan!
Straw Hat Luffy is a human and a pirate
THE OUTSKIRTS OF CONCHCORDE PLAZA
Drop dead!
You know, Shirahoshi,
what you did was pretty stupid!
but he's on our side, right?
Princess Shirahoshi called for his help!
That's what we call those
actions in this world!
It looks like he came to save
this country with Boss Jimbei!
Because you tried to stymie your
hate for me, this kingdom will fall.
Straw Hat!
Collier Shoot!
Because of you,
They love you so much.
your father, your brothers, the citizens,
and you yourself are all going to die!
I won't let you destroy
this Mermaid paradise!
There are 30,000 human slaves we've
caught in the sea over the past month.
But you only saved the King
temporarily so don't push your luck!
You're just a human pirate!
Shirahoshi!
They'll either give up or be wiped out.
Mermaid Princess-san, you're so beautiful!
No, don't listen to him, Princess-sama!
You did nothing wrong!
108...
Let King-sama go, Hordy!
...Pound Phoenix!
Excuse me, could I look at your panties?
And 70,000 Fish-Men who know how to use arms.
No, it was definitely foolish!
Don't ask the Princess that!
Then, show me yours.
Why should I?!
Shark Arrows!
We're all together again finally!
King! Princes!
Stop! Or we'll open fire!
They're ignoring you!
Well, that's because I
said it in a small voice!
What are you looking at, woman?!
There are some important historical
resources here on the Fish-Man Island!
Nami-san! I rescued those idiots!
Stop! Please stop!
You can't just rampage
around destroying things!
--Do you love me now?
--Yeah, yeah.
Run, soldiers! Don't die a
meaningless death-jamon!
You fool! We got to the exit on our own.
Wh-What the...
I won't let them get away-ch! Sea Bear!
Whether it's the citizens
or the kingdom or the history.
Uh-huh.
And you couldn't have
done it without my help!
Trienta Fleurs...
Pappagu helped them?!
No, before that, Brook became a ghost and...
They moved here from the
closed Fish-Man District.
What's this?!
...Clutch!
Ghost?
That's right.
Behold...
My newfound ability helped us!
They're so excited!
...100,000 outlaws altogether!
It's a nice day to do a concert!
Father-sama! Brothers-sama!
I don't have much time!
I need the key... I mean, the sword!
Dammit!
I don't have time...
Stay away, Ghost!
Look how miserable they are!
Everybody say "ho"!
No...
Pappagu-san!
We are doomed!
Huh?
Great warriors?! Pathetic!
They're barely alive now!
Today's audience is awesome!
How did the ghost know my name?
It's because Captain Hordy is so strong-ch!
It's me!
They can't make it until
the time of execution-ch!
I don't have any ghost friends!
I got him!
You're the Bone, aren't you?
That's not good. They must
be executed by beheading.
There are a few female and child slaves
who can't fight, outside the plaza.
Kung Fu Boost!
Finally, you're here! I got tired of waiting!
Hyouzou-san, we're here!
Hey, I need a sword.
We will take care of them later.
H-He transformed himself!
Don't get too close! He'll cut you!
Our only concern was Jimbei and
Shirahoshi, and we got them now.
But we'll soon have more human slaves!
I don't care how many at
once - just bring it on!
I'm here as you wish-dokan!
There is no reason for us to wait
until the appointed time now.
Th-The racoon shape-shifted!
So, 100,000 of you islanders!
You folk have nowhere to... run!
The water is here finally!
I'm not a racoon!
You fools are a dishonor to our
race so vacate your houses!
What are you doing, Brook?! It's too late!
Special Attack--Green Star "Devil"!
I'm going to execute these
worthless creatures...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You can either drop dead or run.
Think about what you want!
Oh, welcome back.
...of the royal family!
It's gonna eat me!
Take this! Green Stars at random!
Here, your sword!
Horsing around in public...
You kids have no class at all!
Yeah! Kill them!
How's that? I'm a Pop Green master!
People call me Usopp'n-sama!
They deserve death!
Don't push your luck!
Kill them! Kill them!
We can't get in! The entrance
to Conchcorde Plaza is locked!
Hordy Jones.
Kill them! Kill them!
Good job, Zoro-san!
I haven't seen you for a
long time. What do you want?
Huh?
Neptune-sama!
Alright, Zoro, let's get out of here!
No! They're really gonna kill
Neptune the Great Knight!
Let's climb the wall!
Maybe we can see inside.
--Three-Sword Style!
--What?!
I just wanted to say one thing to you
since you're at the height of your glory!
Thanks, Nami!
It's hell on earth!
I thought you got stronger
but some things never change!
They have 100,000 outlaws on their side.
Madam Sharley?!
This is it for our country!
According to my prevision, a man
will destroy the Fish-Man Island.
Super it's getting
pretty exciting, isn't it?!
Madam Sharley!
I may be the one.
There are 50,000 enemies. This is the
perfect opportunity to unveil them!
Children...
You cut too much!
Tell me! When will the pirate with
a hat come to destroy the island?!
Oh yeah?
Was it me that you saw?
Them?!
What are they, Franky?!
I can't swim anymore!
No.
There are 2 new weapons on the Sunny!
I-I need to breathe!
Tell me! When will it be?!
The man who will destroy the island is...
Damn!
I-I'm gonna die!
Who wants to ride along?
...Straw Hat Luffy!
What?! New weapons?!
I don't know. All I know is what
will happen in the future.
--Super! Super! I'm super!
--Hey, hey! What are they?
Zoro! Usopp! Brook!
What?!
Super we're here to pick you up!
It could be tomorrow or a year from now.
I can't tell what the Straw Hat
boy will do specifically.
Can I ride it?
Is it safer to be onboard than out here?
We made it.
I want them to come now...
Well, you'll see! You can set
your expectations very high!
That's how it went.
What is your point?
Brook's new ability sounds awesome! Anyway...
If they create havoc here now,
My point is that it's not you!
we might be in trouble but those
villains would be too, right?
You are all amazing!
That's all I can say.
Those guys got their
captain beaten by Luffy.
What are you guys doing?! How pathetic!
The one who determines the
fate of the Fish-Man Island is...
I want them to come now, too!
I don't want them to kill the King!
How come they don't seem worried?
You're right. That's odd.
Me neither!
Try and save the giant Mermaid...
...not you, Hordy.
Oh, I see! Madam's previsions are accurate!
...in the middle of the plaza,
That means Hordy will never
reign over the island!
if you can!
You're right, children.
Water Shot!
It's better if they came now.
Boy, he gave me a lot of trouble...
Yes, yes...
We've wasted so much time.
Let's go, Princess-sama.
Here you go.
Okay!
It's the letter from the Celestial Dragons.
Oh, I didn't have to worry.
Take care of Hachi, Camie!
Hey! Straw Hat Luffy!
Thank you all!
Y-Yes.
This is the hope of the Fish-Man Island,
that Mother-sama left behind.
Go, Megalo!
If you want to destroy the island,
why don't you do it now?!
What?!
Madam Sharley!
But I think it's not safe for Yowahoshi.
Do your worst - right here, right now!
Mm-hm, her capture was
not a part of our plan.
Yeah! Can you hear us, Straw Hat?!
Neither was asking her to escape on her own.
If you're hiding somewhere
on the island, come here now!
Luffy-sama, what did you just call me?
Straw Hat!
Straw Hat! Straw Hat!
You were calling me
"Coward (Yowamushi)" before.
Straw Hat! Straw Hat!
Yeah, it's not like I know everything but
you're not as timid as I thought you were.
Straw Hat! Straw Hat!
--Madam!
--How could he do this?!
So I'll call you Yowahoshi from now on!
Straw Hat! Straw Hat!
He deflected Captain Hordy's
destructive Water Shot...
That's nonsense!
It's understandable why someone would
hate those who they think wronged them.
Straw Hat! Straw Hat!
What do you mean by that, Sharley?
What do you have against me?!
...with his own Water Shot?!
Straw Hat! Straw Hat!
That man is a monster, too!
That man who insulted you...
I'm not like your brother.
Straw Hat! Straw Hat!
That's exactly what he's doing.
I don't know how you've
attained that much power
Well, when I was a kid,
everybody in the Fish-Man District
but your Fish-Man Karate is very unskilled!
But a coward couldn't have been so strong
may have looked
up to your brother Arlong.
He was the first Fish-Man
to join the Seven Warlords!
and borne such hardship
on her own for this long.
I thought you soldiers had
to protect this country!
But then we seized power.
She is right.
And after he resigned,
his bounty exceeded 400 million berries!
Princess Shirahoshi, it must have
been hard for you through the years.
In fact, the name "Arlong Pirates" is
nothing but a symbol to unite us now.
How can we fight a guy like that?!
I'm sorry.
Soldiers...
I caused you trouble
because I kept it secret.
Straw Hat! Straw Hat!
Shut up and bring it on!
We don't even need the
name "Arlong" anymore!
You have to kill us all in
order to kill the Princess!
Straw Hat! Straw Hat!
It's okay. I like you
just the way you are now.
Hordy!
The only man who can break the whole country
to its foundation and rebuild it, is...
Straw Hat! Straw Hat!
No passing on hatred to the next generation.
Why are you hesitating?!
How pathetic!
They're literally clutching at straws!
That's what those brave
heroes were trying to teach us.
There is nowhere for you to run!
That soldier is up to something.
...me! Because I have enough power to do so!
Don't tell the people
on the island anything!
Which one?
Sharley's previsions were always
accurate but this time, it's bullshit!
He's gonna launch a suicide attack
to kill anyone around him-bokan!
Don't let resentment or hatred
get the better of you for my sake.
N-No way!
Look how powerful I am!
How boring.
How meaningless...
I'm gonna become a piece of
dried squid if he does-ch!
This is the power that I'm talking about!
Those fools must be out of their minds.
Let's bring them to their senses.
There is a small "sprout"
that bloomed in your heart.
How rude.
I started this whole thing 10 years ago.
Before the Princes gets here,
Hold your tongue until you've beaten
the formidable line of defense...
If all people on the island share it
and think the same way as you do one day,
if I can kill at least one of their officers!
Listen, you stupid citizens!
Let me tell you something.
I'm going to proceed with the execution
of the former king, Neptune - now!
there will be no more
fighting and the conflict
Concerning the late Queen of the Ryugu
Kingdom, who you fools still love!
Oh no, he's gonna...
...of the New Fish-Man Pirates!
between Fish-Men
and humans will be over.
Water Shot.
I don't think the years you
suffered through were meaningless.
We'll even smash that sword you're proud of!
Father...
Watch very closely!
Otohime was killed by...
Go, Iron Shell Squad!
As I cut former king Neptune's head off!
You must have been trying
so hard to protect...
...me!
...that small "sprout"
single-handedly, day after day.
Then, this half-assed king without a
drop of racial pride will be gone forever
But let us protect it for you this time.
Please!
Train me as a swordsman!
What's that? How far can it go?
What?!
and the new kingdom of Fish-Men will rise,
which will dominate the pathetic humans!
No...
I'll put an end to the
shameless Ryugu Kingdom!
What about the human then?
How could you not notice it, idiots?!
The day before that fateful
day 10 years ago...
Y-Yes!
MERMAID COVE
They're really just copying
what "Hawk-Eye" does!
I don't know who you are but...
--What is that?
--Huh?
Thank you very much!
...I would do anything if I
can make some big money.
I hear something.
It's a pain in the ass to
fight all these weaklings!
She may not be a coward
but she sure is a crybaby!
Here we go again - just like that time!
Is this real money?!
Straw Hat! Kick the crap out of them!
How regrettable!
That's just a half of it. You can have
the rest after you finish the job.
I... I swore to become stronger, didn't I?!
Farewell!
Vander Decken was so useless!
Alright, I'll do it!
Just this is enough to drink
all day for quite some time.
I needed him to get rid of Shirahoshi.
Luffy-sama...
Captain Hordy!
The Energy Steroid is
still working as I thought.
I will never lose again!
Luffy-sama!
And what do you want me to do?
It's so easy. Even a child can do it.
No wonder. He took a lot of them.
Three-Sword Style!
Please save Father-sama!
However, don't let anyone notice.
Captain's back!
Luffy-sama!
Hey, I thought the Water Shot
was fairly weak, wasn't it?
And on that day...
Black Rope Dragon Twister!
She's the legendary Mermaid
Princess with that troublesome power.
I know you took a lot of Energy
Steroid but still, that was great-ch!
So I needed to take out Shirahoshi
as soon as possible, but...
What?!
Get away! Fire!
He cut through their iron
shells as if they were fruit!
Your hair turned white
and you've gained muscle.
Megalo?
--Put out the fire!
--Run!
What was that attack?! It looked like the
Grim Reaper's scythe or something!
--Protect the royal family!
--Put out the fire now!
...you people duped me completely.
How do you feel, Captain?
Jimbei.
Couldn't be better!
I-It's still going on!
I should have noticed when you
gave in without resistance.
--It won't stop!
--It's like a cyclone of blades!
--Run! Or you're gonna get cut!
--Don't come after us!
You're quite taken with
these humans, aren't you?!
Otohime-sama has been shot!
I despise your kind the most!
It'll chase you to hell's end!
Hey, give me the rest of that money now!
Fisher Tiger who you grew up together
with in the Fish-Man District
Use your brains, fools!
I set fire to those
signatures like you told me to!
and Arlong who was like a brother to you,
were both beaten or killed by humans!
Use your bubbles to float!
I wanna make a run for it
already so give me the money!
The soldiers...
Why didn't they wait for us?
But instead of seeking revenge for them,
you joined hands with humans!
Let's hit them from the sky!
Kill Princess Shirahoshi!
You are as gutless as Neptune!
What?!
What's going on here?
How sneaky.
You stupid human.
Th-That's...
Outta my way!
When I become king of the island,
I'll change everything!
Shit! Dammit!
We'll impale you all!
This year's World Summit
is a perfect opportunity!
Go, Harisenbon!
...Straw Hat Luffy!
Fukaboshi! Ryuboshi! Manboshi! Be careful!
It's the Sea Urchin Spike Unit
led by Commander Harisenbon!
He really showed up!
I'm gonna kill the human kings from
all over the world at Marie Jois
All the sea monsters and the
Fish-Men have taken the drug!
It was a human...
Impale that kick-fighting guy!
and the legend of a terrifying
underwater kingdom will begin!
Hey, did you see that? He saved King Neptune.
I thought Neptune's army
...who killed our queen!
wouldn't be beaten so easily as long
as playing field was level-re-mi-fa!
Hari, sen, bon!
Yeah! And right before that,
Princess Shirahoshi cried for his help!
Queen Otohime was killed by a human!!
We'll save you, Father!
We'll drag all humans in the world
into the water and enslave them!
Now, you have nowhere to hide!
Sanji-san, watch out!
Luffy-sama!
Eventually, no one will be able
to stand against Fish-Men.
How can you act so relaxed?! Hey!
Did he come out of the shark?
Was he hiding in its stomach?! But why?!
Everybody got fooled completely!
Even in the world of pirates!
You're out already... But I
guess you had no choice!
All pirates will fall down on their knees
before us--the New Fish-Man Pirates!
Damn! It was him!
He killed Queen Otohime!
It's been a while already...
Hurry up, you all!
Sanji-kun!
Hordy, you bastard!
Look at these human pirates with
confidence in their ability to fight!
Much! What the... Who is he talking to-ch?!
Don't worry! We were ready
from the beginning!
Why don't you understand, Hordy Jones?!
I ran.
You will all be like them, Straw Hat!
Wait, candy-chan!
Father!
You folk are the weakest on this island!
Because we knew that Luffy would never...
No way, screw you!
Hordy, stop!
I'll be the one who becomes
King of the Pirates!
I brought my favorite dress for you!
Father!
The other islanders were trying to ignore
the history of discrimination by humans
...sit tight as we had planned!
--Put it on!
--You don't need to be shy!
The King of the Pirates?
and to forgive the murder of their hero
and queen who died at the hands of a human.
She was annoying.
Don't you think so, Shirahoshi?
Mirage, release!
I said I won't wear it! I'm not being shy!
A woman appeared all of a sudden-ch!
You're just a band of 10 half-assed
pirates. You can't do anything!
They endured their pain in
order to change the future
In the rain, in the snow,
She begged everyone not to
seek revenge against humans
Is this it, Jimbei-chan?
The letter from the Celestial Dragons?
and signed their names.
We have 100,000 on our side!
but to become friends with them instead.
That's it! Good job!
in the rolling thunder, I ran and ran...
--Prince!
--Fukaboshi-sama!
No way! Whoa! The letter is gone!
When did she take it?!
She was bugging me because she
almost accomplished her goal.
Th-There are so many of them.
Straw Hat and Boss Jimbei have only
10 people. Are they gonna be okay?
What were you doing, idiot?!
Go to hell, kick-fighting guy!
I knew I wouldn't be satisfied
with just killing her.
Why can't you appreciate the boldness
and kindness of their decision?
And I handed the key over to Robin!
If they lose, Hordy will take
over the Fish-Man Island!
You silly boy!
To me, your mother was...
No, don't tell me...
Kindness?
Do you think you can escape us forever?!
The key's gone!
What were you doing?!
It's a meaningless gesture.
...someone who deserved death!
And we will be kicked out of our home!
You all want to be fooled by the humans?!
Sanji-kun!
Don't say such a thing to the Princess!
Beat them up! Straw Hat! Boss Jimbei!
It's unlocked!
I shouldn't have trouble
dealing with these fools!
How dare you?!
Who did this?
And then I came up with an idea
to make the best of her death.
Straw Hat!
Sanji-kun!
Kill them all, New Fish-Man Pirates!
Merman Combat!
Robin-sama?
Spear of the Ages!
Damn you!
Is this...
Seven Great Treasures!
Which would allow me to stoke
the hatred towards humans,
Father! Are you all right?!
Here come 100,000 enemies!
How can we fight them?!
Stop! Sanji!
Dragon Tower Gate!
Hey, look up! What's that?
It's impossible!
This is why I don't wanna
get involved with you guys!
that citizens of the
Fish-Man Island once had
That's...
Do I forget what happened
at Sabaody, already?!
A whale and a lion?
Th-They beat the sea monsters!
Before we fight, we could get squashed.
and destroy the islanders' stupid
dream along with Otohime - all at once!
No, wait! That's...
Sanji-kun!
Squash?! No!
You folk are just seeking your
revenge out of your own hatred!
100,000 enemies?! I'm so
stunned - my eyes will pop out!
Gaon Cannon!
What I need to do now is to
get all the Vital Recipes
I'd point the finger at a
human for killing Otohime.
But I won't let you take the King's life,
or the island that belongs to our citizens...
from the grand masters of the New Kama Kempo!
You fools will...
But I don't have eyes to pop out!
Sanji-kun!
It's a pirate ship!
...or the Ryugu Kingdom!
If I blamed it on a human, I knew that the
islanders will get pissed off at humans again.
Fire!
You let your guard down, candy boy!
100,000 is nothing! Let's do this!
What?
Don't hide behind us while you say that!
Sanji-kun!
And it turned out that you all got
fooled by my trick exactly as I wanted!
They're so strong! After all,
they're the strongest men in the Kingdom!
You're already surrounded by New Kamas!
Here I go! My time has come!
Super Armored Me!
Now is your chance! Go, Whale!
Sanji-kun!
She was worth killing! Right, Shirahoshi?
Sanji-kun-kun!
All right! Bring it on!
You think you win because
you beat the sea monsters?
Sanji-kun-kun-kun!
There are 10 of us.
Hoe?
Princes! Take the King and go!
So we each have to beat 10,000 of them.
Your mother was not murdered by a human!
We won't lose! Because we were
given the great power from above!
Then one day, I finally got cornered and...
They outnumber us but it
doesn't mean they're stronger.
I, her kinsman, did it!
Okay!
I won't let you do that! Wait-zugan!
That power will allow us to
rule the real Fish-Man country!
It's not like they're elite Navy soldiers.
So don't shit yourself.
I, standing in front of you now, killed her!
Oh no, it took the King and the Princes!
What did you say, you stupid Moss Head?!
We'll beat you all and lead the way to
peaceful coexistence with the humans!
Damn! Give us back the royal family-gaban!
Bring it on, you Bloody-nosed, Two-bit Chef!
If we let you have your way,
What happened?
Fish-Men and humans won't get another
chance at friendship for hundreds of years!
Hey, Luffy!
L-Luffy-kun!
I ran...
I think Jimbei hatched a
plan with the Straw Hats.
Luffy-sama?
Ouch, ouch! Ow, ow, ow...
Huh? Where did he go?
Say whatever you like! But after all,
this country will be ruled by...
That 400 million berry prize is mine!
No, mine!
...the winner, right?
No way!
I already knew it.
Kill him!
Shirahoshi!
I ran...
Sanji-kun!
I can't believe that he really came.
And I...--
What?
Hey, look! That's...
...ended up...
A long time ago, everyone on the
Fish-Man Island came together
...flying!
Wow! Look how many people there are!
and built a mysterious
giant ship called Noah.
Oh no, are they all our enemies?!
He's up there!
I think so. It looks like
there are 70,000 or 80,000...
Sky...
The reason remains a mystery.
...Walk!
No, 100,000 of them, maybe.
Cool! Sanji is in the air!
Like those people in the past!
It's just a leftover from the past now.
That's a little tough!
You can go take a nap or something
if you want. I'll take care of them.
They look strange!
Let me touch it with my right hand.
Captain Decken, what are you up to?
What do you mean, you fool?!
What's going on here?!
Here they come!
That's the Moon Walk of CP9's!
Wh-What the...
I can't wait!
Let's go wild, guys!
Too slow.
Hey, you guys!
--What?!
--He's flying!
Look, the members of the Straw
Hats are coming out of the ship!
If you wanna talk to Shirahoshi-chan,
you need to talk to me first!
Wh-What is it? What's going on?!
I'm the notorious knight...
The pain of heartbreak will never go away.
...here to protect you!
Sanji-chin-sama!
He didn't do anything but
so many of us got knocked out!
Don't push your luck too far!
Hey, stand up, guys!
Hey! Straw Hat Luffy!
Damn! He beat half of us in a single moment!
Let's cook these small fries!
Are you really going to destroy the island?!
Diable Jambe...
That means 50,000 people
in an instant? What did he do?!
Why did you occupy the Ryugu Palace?!
Do you want to kill the royal family too?!
...Poele a Frire...
It's moving!
What's going on?
...Spectre!
--Wh-What's going on?!
--Run!
Wh-What? What just happened?
Was it you guys who kidnapped the Mermaids?!
He's so strong. That Straw Hat boy...
I'm throwing the Noah...
Hey! Answer us!
...at Shirahoshi!
The Straw Hat pirate did it?!
Hurry up, Megalo!
Are you people friends or
foes to the Fish-Man Island?!
Cool, Straw Hat!
What?!
The ship is half the size
of the Fish-Man Island!
That was Haki!
Father-sama, please be safe!
He's gotten much stronger in just 2 years.
Answer, Straw Hat!
That means if it hits the island,
not just Shirahoshi
He will be fine! It's going to be alright!
That was Conqueror's Haki?
So he was capable of that, as I thought.
but the whole island will be shattered!
Hey, you!
That's what I needed from my captain.
Otherwise, he needs to step down.
She can't run or hide from me anymore!
Shirahoshi has no choice but to
stay with me in my heart forever!
Friends or foes? That's something...
That was amazing! Luffy-sama!
It's gonna be over soon so just stay still!
You're Hordy, right?
I guess I have to kick your ass.
So that was the true power of the drug!
Burn in hell with the island!
Goodbye my sweet Shirahoshi!
Doesn't matter if there
are 100,000 or 1,000,000!
You can become king of whatever
you want in any country.
We'll just beat them all!
Goodbye Fish-Man Island!
But there can only be
one King of the Pirates!
...you'll have to decide on your own!
The Straw Hats have begun their all-out
battle against the New Fish-Man Pirates.
Shirahoshi continues to fulfill her
promise to her mother, Otohime.
Attempting to free Neptune,
Shirahoshi and Jimbei
Brooke and Robin use the
The Straw Hats have gathered
in the Conchcorde Plaza.
exquisite techniques
learned in their two years
But Hordy proclaims that he will
become King of the Pirates,
Hordy ridicules her and
commences Neptune's execution.
of training to defeat their opponents.
Surrounded by Hordy's superior numbers,
but they are caught in Hordy's trap.
But the New Fish-Man Pirates' Deadly
Venom Squad begin a counterattack,
they must protect Shirahoshi
from the relentless assault.
and sends the vast force of the New
Fish-Man Pirates to attack Luffy's crew.
The despairing citizens call out
the name of their last hope.
Displaying his prisoners, Hordy affirms
his complete control of Fish-Man Island.
And the new attacks developed over two years
things start getting dangerous
Ten pirates will battle to decide
the fate of Fish-Man Island!
when Franky, Usopp and Chopper
and reveals a surprising, long-hidden truth!
by Zoro and Sanji will erupt!
And their voice resounds
throughout Fish-Man Island!
bring out a wondrous new weapon!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Shirahoshi's Tears!
Luffy Finally Shows Up!"
"A Surprising Confession! The Truth
Behind the Assassination of Otohime!"
"Deadly Attacks One After Another!
Zoro and Sanji Join the Battle!"
"A Big Clash! The Straw Hats vs.
A Hundred Thousand Enemies!"
"Unveiled! The Secret
Weapons of the Sunny!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!