Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
There are 30,000 human slaves we've
caught in the sea over the past month.
And 70,000 Fish-Men who know how to use arms.
They moved here from the
closed Fish-Man District.
Behold...
...100,000 outlaws altogether!
Look how powerful I am!
This is the power that I'm talking about!
I started this whole thing 10 years ago.
Let me tell you something.
Concerning the late Queen of the Ryugu
Kingdom, who you fools still love!
Otohime was killed by...
...me!
What?!
Your mother was not murdered by a human!
I, her kinsman, did it!
I, standing in front of you now, killed her!
I already knew it.
Shirahoshi!
What?
"Shirahoshi's Tears!
Luffy Finally Shows Up!"
What do you mean you already knew that...
...I killed your mother, Shirahoshi?!
Father! Are you all right?!
Stay with us!
Shirahoshi!
A few years after it happened,
Megalo told me secretly.
Megalo?!
He did?!
Is that true, Megalo?!
No...
Megalo was owned by
Neptune's army back then.
And he witnessed everything that day!
Mother! Mother!
I can't believe it.
Princess Shirahoshi, why didn't you...
If I told anyone...!
Someone would hold a grudge
against Hordy-sama, I thought.
And that is not what Mother-sama wanted!
That was the last promise we made with her.
She told us that no matter who did it to her,
we should not get angry or hate anybody!
So it doesn't matter who did this...
Don't get angry on my behalf.
Don't let resentment or hatred
get the better of you for my sake.
Shirahoshi, you...
Don't tell me that you...
You did as Mother said
to do 10 years ago and...
...you have been keeping this to yourself all
this time, alone in the Hard Shell Tower?!
She tried not to harbor hate for
the one who killed her mother?
Even though it was her dying mother's wish,
it's almost unthinkable someone
would be able to keep such a promise!
She is such an obedient, admirable girl!
Who else could have done such a thing?!
Stop laughing, you fool!
I can't help it! Hey, Megalo?
If you had cried out right there,
you could've drawn everybody's attention
and let them know that I
was the one who did it.
So thank you for shutting your mouth!
And thank you for confiding
only in this dumb girl!
If it were anybody else,
we couldn't have come this far!
You know, Shirahoshi,
what you did was pretty stupid!
That's what we call those
actions in this world!
Because you tried to stymie your
hate for me, this kingdom will fall.
Because of you,
your father, your brothers, the citizens,
and you yourself are all going to die!
Shirahoshi!
No, don't listen to him, Princess-sama!
You did nothing wrong!
No, it was definitely foolish!
Shark Arrows!
King! Princes!
Stop! Please stop!
Father-sama! Brothers-sama!
Look how miserable they are!
No...
We are doomed!
Great warriors?! Pathetic!
They're barely alive now!
It's because Captain Hordy is so strong-ch!
They can't make it until
the time of execution-ch!
That's not good. They must
be executed by beheading.
Hey, I need a sword.
Our only concern was Jimbei and
Shirahoshi, and we got them now.
There is no reason for us to wait
until the appointed time now.
I'm going to execute these
worthless creatures...
...of the royal family!
Yeah! Kill them!
They deserve death!
Kill them! Kill them!
No! They're really gonna kill
Neptune the Great Knight!
It's hell on earth!
They have 100,000 outlaws on their side.
This is it for our country!
Madam Sharley!
Children...
Tell me! When will the pirate with
a hat come to destroy the island?!
Tell me! When will it be?!
I don't know. All I know is what
will happen in the future.
It could be tomorrow or a year from now.
I want them to come now...
If they create havoc here now,
we might be in trouble but those
villains would be too, right?
I want them to come now, too!
I don't want them to kill the King!
Me neither!
You're right, children.
It's better if they came now.
Yes, yes...
Hey! Straw Hat Luffy!
If you want to destroy the island,
why don't you do it now?!
Do your worst - right here, right now!
Yeah! Can you hear us, Straw Hat?!
If you're hiding somewhere
on the island, come here now!
Straw Hat!
Straw Hat! Straw Hat!
How pathetic!
They're literally clutching at straws!
Sharley's previsions were always
accurate but this time, it's bullshit!
How meaningless...
Those fools must be out of their minds.
Let's bring them to their senses.
Listen, you stupid citizens!
I'm going to proceed with the execution
of the former king, Neptune - now!
Father...
Watch very closely!
As I cut former king Neptune's head off!
Then, this half-assed king without a
drop of racial pride will be gone forever
and the new kingdom of Fish-Men will rise,
which will dominate the pathetic humans!
I'll put an end to the
shameless Ryugu Kingdom!
How regrettable!
Farewell!
Luffy-sama...
Luffy-sama!
Please save Father-sama!
Megalo?
What?!
Th-That's...
...Straw Hat Luffy!
He really showed up!
Hey, did you see that? He saved King Neptune.
Yeah! And right before that,
Princess Shirahoshi cried for his help!
Luffy-sama!
Did he come out of the shark?
Was he hiding in its stomach?! But why?!
You're out already... But I
guess you had no choice!
Hurry up, you all!
Much! What the... Who is he talking to-ch?!
Don't worry! We were ready
from the beginning!
Because we knew that Luffy would never...
...sit tight as we had planned!
Mirage, release!
A woman appeared all of a sudden-ch!
Is this it, Jimbei-chan?
The letter from the Celestial Dragons?
That's it! Good job!
No way! Whoa! The letter is gone!
When did she take it?!
What were you doing, idiot?!
And I handed the key over to Robin!
No, don't tell me...
The key's gone!
What were you doing?!
It's unlocked!
Who did this?
Robin-sama?
Is this...
Father! Are you all right?!
Hey, look up! What's that?
That's...
A whale and a lion?
No, wait! That's...
Gaon Cannon!
It's a pirate ship!
Fire!
Now is your chance! Go, Whale!
Hoe?
Princes! Take the King and go!
Okay!
I won't let you do that! Wait-zugan!
Oh no, it took the King and the Princes!
Damn! Give us back the royal family-gaban!
What happened?
I think Jimbei hatched a
plan with the Straw Hats.
I can't believe that he really came.
Hey, look! That's...
Wow! Look how many people there are!
Oh no, are they all our enemies?!
I think so. It looks like
there are 70,000 or 80,000...
No, 100,000 of them, maybe.
That's a little tough!
You can go take a nap or something
if you want. I'll take care of them.
What do you mean, you fool?!
I can't wait!
Let's go wild, guys!
Look, the members of the Straw
Hats are coming out of the ship!
Hey! Straw Hat Luffy!
Are you really going to destroy the island?!
Why did you occupy the Ryugu Palace?!
Do you want to kill the royal family too?!
Was it you guys who kidnapped the Mermaids?!
Hey! Answer us!
Are you people friends or
foes to the Fish-Man Island?!
Answer, Straw Hat!
Friends or foes? That's something...
...you'll have to decide on your own!
The Straw Hats have gathered
in the Conchcorde Plaza.
But Hordy proclaims that he will
become King of the Pirates,
and sends the vast force of the New
Fish-Man Pirates to attack Luffy's crew.
Ten pirates will battle to decide
the fate of Fish-Man Island!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Big Clash! The Straw Hats vs.
A Hundred Thousand Enemies!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!