Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
--We've been waiting for you, Straw Hat!
--H-He really came!
Luffy-sama, what did you just call me?
You were calling me "Coward
(Yowamushi)" before.
Yeah, it's not like I know everything but
you're not as timid as I thought you were.
So I'll call you Yowahoshi from now on!
All pirates will fall down on their knees
before us--the New Fish-Man Pirates!
Look at these human pirates with
confidence in their ability to fight!
You will all be like them, Straw Hat!
I'll be the one who becomes
King of the Pirates!
The King of the Pirates?
We have 100,000 on our side!
Hey, Luffy!
That 400 million berry prize is mine!
No, mine!
No way!
Kill him!
What's going on here?!
He didn't do anything but
so many of us got knocked out!
You're Hordy, right?
I guess I have to kick your ass.
You can become king of whatever
you want in any country.
But there can only be
one King of the Pirates!
"Deadly Attacks One After Another!
Zoro and Sanji Join the Battle!"
--Oh, what...
--...Extraordinary power!
So he's the Straw Hat Luffy!
He's out of our league!
Where do you think you're going?
If you run from your enemy on this historic
day for the Fish-Men, you deserve death.
We may have lost 50,000.
But...
...we are still 50,000 strong!
The Straw Hats always shatter
our dreams. They're our...
...worst enemy!
And Jimbei!
He lives Otohime's dream
and befriends humans!
But that's not the future we Fish-Men want!
He's right! Straw Hat is nothing!
He's just a human!
And Jimbei betrayed the Fish-Men!
Let's kill them both!
Luffy! I wish you left more
than 50,000 of them for me.
Oh, sorry.
Don't get so excited.
Huh?
I'll go for 30,000! Okay, Moss Head?
Shut up, Mr. Nosebleed.
Huh?
You audience babies!
Okay! Let me do one song for
the beginning of the battle!
They're not here to see you.
As always, Robin-san's so cool!
They weren't listening at all, were they?
That's because I whispered it!
--What?!
--He has too much pride.
Kill them!
--Let's show them...
--...How great Fish-Men are!
Let's do it!
Third Gear!
I don't care if there're
thousands of you! Just bring it on!
Gum-Gum...
--Here he comes!
--What's wrong with his hand?!
...Giant Pistol!
All right, let's join him.
That fool didn't wait for us again.
I've got to do this, after seeing
tears in Shirahoshi-chan's eyes.
You must have been trying
so hard to protect...
...that small "sprout"
single-handedly, day after day.
But let us protect it for you this time.
Men who can't wipe away the tears
from women's eyes aren't real men.
Let's wreck these guys!
When this is over, let's have a drink
at the Mermaid Cafe, Shirahoshi-chan!
Drop dead!
Collier Shoot!
I won't let you destroy
this Mermaid paradise!
They'll either give up or be wiped out.
108...
...Pound Phoenix!
What are you looking at, woman?!
There are some important historical
resources here on the Fish-Man Island!
You can't just rampage
around destroying things!
Whether it's the citizens
or the kingdom or the history.
Trienta Fleurs...
What's this?!
...Clutch!
They're so excited!
It's a nice day to do a concert!
Everybody say "ho"!
Today's audience is awesome!
I got him!
Kung Fu Boost!
H-He transformed himself!
I don't care how many at
once - just bring it on!
Th-The racoon shape-shifted!
I'm not a racoon!
Special Attack--Green Star "Devil"!
It's gonna eat me!
Take this! Green Stars at random!
How's that? I'm a Pop Green master!
People call me Usopp'n-sama!
Huh?
Thanks, Nami!
I thought you got stronger
but some things never change!
Super it's getting
pretty exciting, isn't it?!
There are 50,000 enemies. This is the
perfect opportunity to unveil them!
Them?!
What are they, Franky?!
There are 2 new weapons on the Sunny!
Who wants to ride along?
What?! New weapons?!
--Super! Super! I'm super!
--Hey, hey! What are they?
Can I ride it?
Is it safer to be onboard than out here?
Well, you'll see! You can set
your expectations very high!
You are all amazing!
What are you guys doing?! How pathetic!
Try and save the giant Mermaid...
...in the middle of the plaza,
if you can!
Water Shot!
Oh, I didn't have to worry.
What?!
He deflected Captain Hordy's
destructive Water Shot...
...with his own Water Shot?!
That man is a monster, too!
I don't know how you've
attained that much power
but your Fish-Man Karate is very unskilled!
He was the first Fish-Man
to join the Seven Warlords!
And after he resigned,
his bounty exceeded 400 million berries!
How can we fight a guy like that?!
Shut up and bring it on!
You have to kill us all in
order to kill the Princess!
Why are you hesitating?!
There is nowhere for you to run!
N-No way!
How boring.
How rude.
Hold your tongue until you've beaten
the formidable line of defense...
...of the New Fish-Man Pirates!
We'll even smash that sword you're proud of!
Go, Iron Shell Squad!
Please!
Train me as a swordsman!
They're really just copying
what "Hawk-Eye" does!
It's a pain in the ass to
fight all these weaklings!
Here we go again - just like that time!
I... I swore to become stronger, didn't I?!
I will never lose again!
Three-Sword Style!
Black Rope Dragon Twister!
What?!
He cut through their iron
shells as if they were fruit!
What was that attack?! It looked like the
Grim Reaper's scythe or something!
I-It's still going on!
--It won't stop!
--It's like a cyclone of blades!
--Run! Or you're gonna get cut!
--Don't come after us!
It'll chase you to hell's end!
Use your brains, fools!
Use your bubbles to float!
Let's hit them from the sky!
Kill Princess Shirahoshi!
How sneaky.
Outta my way!
We'll impale you all!
Go, Harisenbon!
It's the Sea Urchin Spike Unit
led by Commander Harisenbon!
Impale that kick-fighting guy!
Hari, sen, bon!
Now, you have nowhere to hide!
Sanji-san, watch out!
How can you act so relaxed?! Hey!
It's been a while already...
Sanji-kun!
I ran.
Wait, candy-chan!
No way, screw you!
I brought my favorite dress for you!
--Put it on!
--You don't need to be shy!
I said I won't wear it! I'm not being shy!
In the rain, in the snow,
in the rolling thunder, I ran and ran...
Go to hell, kick-fighting guy!
You silly boy!
Do you think you can escape us forever?!
Sanji-kun!
I shouldn't have trouble
dealing with these fools!
Sanji-kun!
Damn you!
Stop! Sanji!
Do I forget what happened
at Sabaody, already?!
Sanji-kun!
What I need to do now is to
get all the Vital Recipes
from the grand masters of the New Kama Kempo!
You fools will...
Sanji-kun!
You let your guard down, candy boy!
What?
Sanji-kun!
You're already surrounded by New Kamas!
Sanji-kun-kun!
Sanji-kun-kun-kun!
Then one day, I finally got cornered and...
I ran...
Ouch, ouch! Ow, ow, ow...
Huh? Where did he go?
I ran...
Sanji-kun!
And I...--
...ended up...
...flying!
He's up there!
Sky...
...Walk!
Cool! Sanji is in the air!
Like those people in the past!
That's the Moon Walk of CP9's!
Hey, you guys!
--What?!
--He's flying!
If you wanna talk to Shirahoshi-chan,
you need to talk to me first!
I'm the notorious knight...
...here to protect you!
Sanji-chin-sama!
Don't push your luck too far!
Let's cook these small fries!
Diable Jambe...
...Poele a Frire...
...Spectre!
Hey, you!
It's gonna be over soon so just stay still!
Doesn't matter if there
are 100,000 or 1,000,000!
We'll just beat them all!
Brooke and Robin use the
exquisite techniques
learned in their two years
of training to defeat their opponents.
But the New Fish-Man Pirates' Deadly
Venom Squad begin a counterattack,
things start getting dangerous
when Franky, Usopp and Chopper
bring out a wondrous new weapon!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Unveiled! The Secret
Weapons of the Sunny!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!