Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
where the New Fish-Man Pirates  who are
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
where the New Fish-Man Pirates  who are
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
caught up in the turmoil
The Straw Hats find themselves
and involved in an all-out war!
Super it's getting
pretty exciting, isn't it?!
and involved in an all-out war!
The Noah is turning away. It's
not gonna crash into the island!
Now, set off the fireworks!
Surume!
There are 50,000 enemies. This is the
perfect opportunity to unveil them!
Princess-sama saved us
by drawing the ship away!
If I am the only one who you want to kill,
please do not harm the other people...
So you were doing everything he says
in order to save your brother's life?
Them?!
What are they, Franky?!
--Princess Shirahoshi!
--Please escape!
Okay, I cut you already.
There are 2 new weapons on the Sunny!
I know how you feel.
Quinto Tierce Fantasia!
...of the Ryugu Kingdom!
Is it your younger brother or older brother?
Who wants to ride along?
I have to go out to the sea in order
to keep the Noah away from the bubble!
What?! New weapons?!
Let me try to save his life too!
Come and get me!
Three-Sword Style!
Mil Fleurs...
I'll give you one last chance, Shirahoshi!
Did you forget?
...Gigantesco Mano...
If you say "Yes," I'll spare your life!
I'm your friend!
...Stomp!
Black Rope Dragon Twister!
The Soldier Dock System!
Have mercy, Decken-sama!
Second Gear!
Marry me!
Channel 4!
You're not my type!
--It won't stop!
--It's like a cyclone of blades!
Then go to hell!
--Run! Or you're gonna get cut!
--Don't come after us!
Damn Yowahoshi! I told her to stick with me!
FR-U 4!
We're not gonna let her marry a guy like you!
It'll chase you to hell's end!
Huh? Where did he go?
She's our only baby sister! We're
not gonna let you hurt her, Decken!
I'll take care of it!
Sky...
...Walk!
Brother Mamboshi-sama! Brother
Ryuboshi-sama! Hoe-sama!
"The Noah Closing in! The Fish-Man
Island Facing Destruction!"
Cool! Sanji is in the air!
Diable Jambe...
The new number! Channel 5!
I'm sorry that we suspected you...
Don't mess with me, Vander Decken!
...Poele a Frire...
Don't mention it. Take me to the deck!
Brachio-Tank 5 is here!
...Spectre!
But I like this idea!
Come on out, Kraken!
I can't believe it! That's...
Oh, Hordy Jones!
There are only 10 of them!
Just crush them all!
Doesn't matter if there
are 100,000 or 1,000,000!
...the Ship of Promise! "Noah"!
I'll be counting on you to save
my beloved Shirahoshi-chan!
What happened to Neptune? Did you kill him?
We'll just beat them all!
Then it'll finally be over!
You ready, Luffy?!
I'm tormenting Shirahoshi with the Noah now.
"Unveiled! The Secret
Weapons of the Sunny!"
Oh, hey, Surume!
Don't you think it's a good idea?
Go ahead!
Huh, Bro?!
It's me! Surume!
"Hurry up, Luffy! Shirahoshi's
Life in Jeopardy!"
I have a good idea too!
The Kraken betrayed us!
What is it? Let me hear it.
Listen, Surume! Stay here
and protect Yowahoshi!
If you die now...
Um, thank you for doing this, Surume-sama!
"Iron Pirate!
Here Comes General Franky!"
What'll happen to this ship?
Th-The Noah is...
Decken!
W-Why...
"The Fierce Fight Begins! Luffy vs. Hordy!"
Why is it moving?!
The Noah is turning away. It's
not gonna crash into the island!
Who is doing it and how?!
They're pushing their luck too far!
Th-This is no good!
Princess-sama saved us
by drawing the ship away!
I'll make them pay for this!
What's the matter, Father?
How annoying...
--Princess Shirahoshi!
--Please escape!
It's a bit strange,  but
why are you so upset?
It's not over yet, Moss Head!
You can't top me, Nosebleed!
It's just a relic from history.
It serves no purpose.
Where are you going, Shirahoshi?
There's no way for you to run!
Why are they competing against each other?
No! We can't let anything
happen to that ship-jamon!
Shirahoshi!
Where am I?
Until the proper day comes, no one
is allowed to move that ship-jamon!
You're in Conchcorde Plaza.
Don't you remember?
Ignore them. They're always like that.
I have to go out to the sea in order
to keep the Noah away from the bubble!
Honestly, that side of
them hasn't changed a bit!
Everybody's getting
pretty warmed up, aren't they?
Maybe it's time for them!
The bubble can't take any more damage!
--By them, you mean...
--Finally, the new weapons?!
Captain Hordy!
I thought he took a lot of Energy
Steroids and became a monster!
But the main entrance is too far from here.
That's right! Follow me!
No, look!
We've been waiting for this!
If I am correct, Luffy-sama's friends were
the last ones who left the Ryugu Palace.
Oh, hey, wait!
G-Guys! Don't leave me alone!
Hordy! You... squirt!
Then maybe the gateway is still open.
You're bugging me! Go somewhere else!
Looks like they have some good swordsmen!
My left hand...
You go!
Straw Hat!
...touched you.
Don't push your luck, you bastards!
He's pretty tough.
What are you doing, you bastard?!
Get out of my way!
--Shut up!
Damn! Isn't there anything that we can do!
We found Shirahoshi!
Don't cut me! Hyouzou-san!
You betrayed me first, Decken.
Over here!
Our princess is risking
her life to save us all!
Um... What do you three want?
Honestly, I panicked a little when this
ship covered up the sky over the island.
We can't let you live!
They're too strong...
It's not her fault that Decken is after her!
We have to kill you!
Not only is Decken on that ship but now
Hordy is climbing aboard one of the chains!
But it was a good idea to break the bubble.
Get away!
What did you just say?
Run!
Nothing!
Princess Shirahoshi's life is in danger!
The Fish-Man Island would be washed away
Surume!
Oh? What's going on?
but we'd still have the Fish-Man District.
He betrayed me, that lunatic - Decken!
The humans are "too strong"?
They're trying to escape from us!
Surume-sama, you are very strong!
If you die here and now, your Mark-Mark
power will become ineffective
But he can still be useful.
How dare you call yourself a Fish-Man?
I guess they're scared of us!
C-Captain!
Protect Yowahoshi!
and this ship will fall onto
the Fish-Man Island again...
Let's take out their
officers while they're gone!
Be careful for Hordy, Luffy!
I-I'm sorry!
Straw Hat!
Don't disappoint me.
Yeah! Advance!
Do you know what Fish-Man Karate is?!
Fish-Men are way stronger
than humans in the water!
I don't need a soldier who is afraid of...
Then it will destroy everything.
His head is gone!
...stupid humans!
He did it with a single blow!
Got it!
Now, more than anything, I want all of
those annoying Straw Hats to be gone.
I can't let him pierce the
bubble and go out to sea.
There is one of them right in front of us!
It's not gonna work. Because
I'm made of rubber!
Prepare to fire!
I have to do it carefully -
not too strong, not too weak.
Roger! Preparing to fire!
Thousands of my men will die too
Your skill is nothing compared to Jimbei's!
but I can just get more human
slaves, as many as I like, later.
Sanji!
Of course! That's why you
shouldn't depend on fake power!
Armee de L'Air Assault...
Oh? He's gone!
Why don't you kill Shirahoshi already?
Cookie Cutter!
...Gum Shoot!
Head; Hardening!
Iron Shell Squad!
There he is! Prepare to fire!
Thousands will die, huh?
Yes, sir!
I'll get him this time...
Oh, he's gone again!
You fool! Your head's gonna crack open!
That's good. But first,
you...
It's awesome down here!
There! Fire!
...drop dead!
Gum-Gum...
What?! Oh, he's gone again!
Did you change something?
No, there he is!
...Bell!
Damn! He moves so quickly!
You fool! Don't do it!
There wasn't a "5" or a "6" before!
What a big chain!
His head was harder than iron!
You're right! And "0" is gone!
Hey, Commander Chopper!
Am I in between the bubbles?
It's rattling! Is there something wrong?!
It's been renovated!!
I remodeled "0" to  create "5" and "6."
What? What?! What?!
Hordy! He's still under the bubble.
Armament; Hardening!
It's a sink hole!
The new weapons are in "4"
which was empty before
Pull! Pull!
and in the newly made "5."
What?!
That serves you right!
Special Attack - Daruma Drop!
We don't have stop it! We only have
to slow it down a little bit...
Okay, hurry up! I wanna see
the new weapons already!
Become a martyr for the New Fish-Man Island.
...before it catches up with Princess-sama!
Alright, alright!
Ouch!
--Pull!
--Don't let the Noah go any farther!
Take a look and be surprised!
Here they are!
I just dug a web of tunnels
underground with my fangs!
Princess-sama! Get somewhere safe
while we're slowing it down!
Cool!
Let's finish this up already-dosun!
Hey! What happened?!
Damn! Stop!
Shark Arrows!
Artillery Unit!
Usopp! Chopper!
Those fools!
Kill Shirahoshi!
Everybody!
They must be out of their minds!
Now, I'm gonna take care
of that stupid biker too...
I do not like it!
They can't move it even a millimeter!
How senseless is that?!
He doesn't get hit at all!
You want to hurt the world's
favorite Mermaid Princess?!
Does he know when they come?!
Amazing, Luffy-sama!
What?
Hey, quit it!
Party music!
That's the Observation Haki!
Oh no!
Shark Arrows!
A sink hole!
Worthless scum!
Gum-Gum...
Because of cowards like you guys, humans
think they can make fools of Fish-Men!
What?! Is he dumb?!
You'll die soon.
Ow, ow, ow...
...Bullet!
Then the ship will start falling again and
it will fall onto the Fish-Man Island.
What's going on? It got dark all of a sudden.
Hey! Are you okay, guys?!
Bastard! Super I won't forgive him!
Your lives mean nothing to me!
Since I'm a kind man, I'll
make your dream come true,
It's nice to have you along
on this festival night!
You guys, get out!
Why?!
the very least I can do, before you die.
What the...
Are they splitting up?!
I'll kill Shirahoshi for you!
Hey, what are you doing, Franky?!
People like you just keep bringing
shame to Fish-Men. Drop dead already!
Captain Hordy!
How dare you kick the commander out!
He stabbed Decken! What kind
of relationship do they have?!
Because it's gonna turn
into a single-seater!
This is no time to think about
that. Hordy's gonna come this way!
Let's get perverted!
You're already a pervert!
We're gonna stop him!
Out of my way, you fools!
Black Rhino FR-U 4!
Everybody...
That bastard!
Luffy-sama, he is unbelievably strong!
Princess-sama, escape! H-Hurry...
You stupid interlopers!
He's great! Straw Hat Luffy!
So that's how strong the
world-renowned pirate is!
I have to keep going!
Brothers-sama!
Is this...
Shirahoshi! Get away at full speed!
...An amusement park?
I was right! The entrance
to the palace was left open!
Hey, let's dance!
Hey, stay with me! Damn Hordy!
Stand by!
Now you're out of the Hard Shell
Tower - it's so easy to kill you.
Oh, it perverted!
That's not it!
Princess Shirahoshi is going...
Brachio-Tank 5!
...out to sea through the gateway!
What's going on?!
--The Noah is going after her!
--Princess-sama, go farther!
Huh? Were we just dreaming?
Head change!
Now, set off the fireworks!
What is it?
Oh, it's going up!
It's no use!
Brachio-Tank 5!
This is fun!
Black Rhino FR-U 4!
Docking!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
The Merfolk may be the
What?! Docking?!
Oh no, the chain!
fastest swimmers in the world but
I'm way faster than you right now!
It's beautiful!
Hey! I said "Kill the Princess"-bokan!
But...
How inconvenient it must be to be a human!
Dosun-san, we're enjoying
today's joyous festival...
Okay, I cut you already.
You all act so tough on the ground
Brother-sama!
What?
Quinto Tierce Fantasia!
but you couldn't even win a fight
with a Fish-Man child in the sea!
Iron Pirate!
Shirahoshi!
Hordy!
That's how weak you are!
General Franky!
I'll make you regret standing against me!
Huh?
Gum-Gum...
Awesome!
Ganging up on a weak woman?
You people are a bunch of brutes.
...Snake Shot!
Hordy!
What?! I-Is that...
What the hell is that?!
Cool!!
...the Noah of the Fish-Man District?!
Mil Fleurs...
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
The transforming robot of our dream!
Why is the Noah in the air over the island?!
It's heading towards this plaza!
...Gigantesco Mano...
Where do you think you are?!
It's almost broken through
the bubble around the island!
Legs?!
You're not on the ground!
Once the bubble pops, the island is
finished! We're all gonna get washed away!
...Stomp!
Luffy-sama! Brother Fukaboshi-sama!
Humans become powerless in the water
--What is that?!
--The Noah?!
but for a Fish-Man like me, this is where I
--Straw Hat!
--B-Brother!
Sorry!
Sorry to be late. I was
caught up in strategizing.
can use my true ability to the full extent!
The mad genius Vegapunk
who I haven't met yet.
--People are screaming outside.
--What's going on?
It was very fortunate for me
that Shirahoshi went out to sea!
You bastard!
Super big!
Hey guys, get out! It's too tight!
I realized his old dream...
Once the ship hits, the whole
island will be destroyed!
You have no interest in the
new weapons! You get off!
CONCHCORDE PLAZA
Meanwhile, at Conchcorde Plaza
on the Fish-Man Island...
...after trial and error
for the last 2 years.
Who's operating it?!
I'm here because I'm scared!
I don't think it has an engine!
I don't wanna be alone, either!
Captain Vander Decken-sama abandoned me!
Shark Arrows!
Franky, do we have to wait much longer?!
--What is that?!
--It's gigantic!
By using the shape-memory
alloy called Wapometal,
I need you to become a
Don't know what's happening
but we're all dead!
sacrifice upon Shirahoshi's
death, along with the island!
Don't rush it!
I wonder if the sea will turn red
if we all get smashed at once.
I finally did it!
Devil Fruit eaters fare no better than
ordinary people in the water.
Don't say things like that! Stop it!
D-Don't be intimidated by its looks!
Why don't you fight, Sea Bonze!
It's all set!
Maybe worse.
--Evacuate!
--Get into the water off the island!
Please! Do something about the Kraken!
Isn't it ironic, Straw Hat?
--Beat him up, Kraken!
--You're strong!
I'm getting excited too!
Wait a minute! I need to
operate this thing so...
Pathetic and powerless!
That's how you truly are!
They're both huge but he doesn't
seem like he wants to fight.
The Kraken will defeat him!
Oh, so strong!!
No matter how big you talk!
It got more spacious!
Hey, Great Monk! You must have misheard him!
There is more to come!
What's going on in here?!
You humans can't even breathe in the water...
F-Folks?
Look at this! This is
the "plunderer's sword"!
Straw Hat, a piece of trash like you
will never become the ruler of the sea!
What Decken said to you was "I'll
leave the plaza up to you!"
Alright, here are the new weapons
on the Soldier Dock of the Sunny!
It's...!
Franken!
--I'm excited!
--What's gonna happen?!
He has a sword!
What?
It's time to unveil!
You ought to regret what
you did and beg for mercy!
That means he wasn't
gonna destroy the island!
General...
You can't even do that now, can
you? You pathetic, lowly creature!
But he said "Become a sacrifice."
...Watch-Your-Step!
He wanted you to fight hard as though
you were going to sacrifice yourself.
Deadly Venom Squad, go!
Rot in hell, Straw Hat!
Striking below the belt!
It's unmanly but effective!
Ouch! I slipped!
Do you think so?
Even if you got giant legs or arms,
The cannons in these shoulders
will get you while you're jumping!
Yes. Isn't that right, guys?
you're dead meat once
you're stung by our venom!
You're Wadatsumi - working for Decken!
Huh? Y-Yeah... he's right!
What?!
How lucky to be trusted
by your captain that much.
Hold it right there!
What?! Cannons in its shoulders?!
Damn you!
Captain Vander Decken! I fell off!
--You're amazing!
--It's time for you to man up!
Franky Cannon!
Oh, that's what it was!
Stop the ship! I don't wanna die!
The Soldier Dock System!
Are you okay, Straw Hat?
No, it wasn't.
Channel 4!
Oh, the cannons are in your shoulders!
Now, take this
B-Brother-hoshi!
Decken?! What's going on here?
--But...
That stupid hanger-on -
what a useless gesture.
and beat the Straw Hats up with us!
--...you're so cool!
--Oh yeah!
Captain Hordy, are you all right?!
You can't get away from me, Straw Hat!
Oh, how awesome!
--The door opened!
--Destroy that stupid ship!
Um, is this one of your strategies?!
It looks like Decken is operating the ship!
The Energy Steroid!
No way. It's not gonna
work on that giant body!
Dammit!
Black Rhino...
Shut up, you good-for-nothings!
He's so tricky!
Damn, Straw Hat!
I've got more new weapons!
Huh?
Watch out!
How tough can he be?! I attacked
him with the Armament Haki!
...FR-U 4!
It's working tremendously well!
Come on! New weapons!
What?!
General...
...Weight!
Did you say Decken? That crazy pirate!
It's so heavy!
This is not a part of the plan!
Pull! Pull!
Surume!
--You're so cool, General!
--Weight! Weight!
We don't have stop it! We only have
to slow it down a little bit...
Captain Decken! I'm sorry
that I didn't trust you!
The Soldier Dock System!
What's so cool about that?
Oh!
Channel 4!
...before it catches up with Princess-sama!
Yeah! He beat the hell out of the Kraken!
Here is a weak one!
--Pull!
--Don't let the Noah go any further!
--What happened? Are you all right?!
--It's no good! He passed out!
Princess-sama! Get somewhere safe
while we're slowing it down!
Are you guys my enemies too?!
How dare you say I'm
weak! I'm just a chicken!
Shirahoshi!
I-In order to save the people
of the Ryugu Kingdom,
He's like a different person!
Black Rhino...
Sorcery Climate Baton!
Accept my love!
I have to draw the Noah
away from the island...
Leave it all up to me!
Watch out for a gust of wind.
...as far as possible!
Gust Sword!
...FR-U 4!
Shirahoshi!
How do you like your freedom?
Do you understand now?
You no longer have those
walls of the Hard Shell
It's Weatheria's science of weather!
Tower that were protecting
you for last 10 years!
You have a choice of bleeding to death
or being crushed by the giant ship - Noah!
Cool! It's a cy-bike!
Did you hear me, Shirahoshi?
Don't underestimate it!
Where is my enemy?
What is it?! Looks so tough!
I'll give you one last chance, Shirahoshi!
Th-That guy right there, Wadatsumi!
That must be...!
What did you say about venom?
Princess Shirahoshi!
Is that him?
If you say "Yes," I'll spare your life!
Don't tell me Decken threw the Noah
like he threw those letters and axes!
All right!
What the hell?!
Watch out, Jimbei-chan!
Have mercy, Decken-sama!
Sting it if you can! This steel monster!
Fish-Man Karate!
I've been loving you for 10 years
since you were just a little kid.
Marry me!
7000 Brick...
You're not my type!
There is no one who could love you
like I do in all the wide world!
...Roundhouse Kick!
Oh? Huh?
Where did Chopper go?
Gee...
It's super cool, isn't it?!
Let's get that guy!
It's my love! Love, love!
Damn! I got kicked out of the tank after all!
Stop that guy!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
All right!
Steel on steel!
L-O-V-E!
All right...
I have no other choice but to fight.
Then go to hell!
I'll take care of it!
Why can't you just accept it?!
How could he do such a giant
creature that much damage?!
Drop dead and live in my heart forever!
But I'm not scared!
Things that I throw with
my Mark-Mark Fruit power...
Because I'm not the same
person that I used to be!
Here! Take this!
...won't stop until they crash into
something or hit their target!
As my beloved wife!
Special Attack - Green Star!
Noah the giant ship! It embodies
my love for you! Accept it!
Now!
We're not gonna let her marry a guy like you!
Bamboo Javelin!
And drop dead along with all the
Fish-Man Island, Shirahoshi!
She's our only baby sister! We're
not gonna let you hurt her, Decken!
Master Heracles'n!
Nami-san!
Brother Mamboshi-sama! Brother
Ryuboshi-sama! Hoe-sama!
Oh no! The wind blast brought Nami-san down!
I'll never forget those 2 years that I
spent in the deadly Swindling Forest!
Hey!
Get up, you bastard!
Brothers-sama!
It begins now!
The new number! Channel 5!
We're not your brothers!
Ouch! Who is it this time?!
The second chapter of "The
Adventures of the Real Man Usopp"!
Captain Decken! What about me?!
Brachio-Tank 5 is here!
You big shit!
Brothers-sama! Some people at the
plaza tried to save me and...
What would happen if you
so much as make a scratch
It's like a dinosaur! I want it!
Wadatsumi! It's too late! It's
impossible for me to save you!
or two on our beautiful navigator?
I'll make sink holes all over the plaza!
Shirahoshi! Don't cry now!
It's amazing!
Unbelievable! His kick worked too!
No! Brother-sama got mad...
Did you see my great shooting skill?
So I need you to become a sacrifice upon
Shirahoshi's death, along with the island!
Doesn't matter if it's a cool robot or
something else! Once it falls down, it's all over!
How strong is his leg that it
can hurt a giant like him?!
I bet this thing can do a lot more.
I'm not mad!
According to Father, we can't even
let the ship get damaged-la-ti-do!
Oh no!
No!
I thought he was a shipwright.
What is that?!
Somebody else is digging too!
So we have to return it to the seafloor
without letting it hit anything!
This is it! The bubble is gonna pop!
I am Commander Chopper!
I got messy.
We're doomed!
I see some enemies at 9 o'clock!
Here it comes!
That wasn't my fault!
Hey, where did Princess Shirahoshi go?!
Fire!
Oh no! In any case, you shouldn't swim
near undersea mountains or trenches!
Oh? She's not there!
What?! Princess! Princess Shirahoshi!
Fire!
The Noah will get damaged!
I will fight you, Great Monk!
Then where should I go,
Brother Mamboshi-sama?!
Fire!
Pay with your life, you Jumbo Steamed Bun!
What? Shirahoshi disappeared?!
Daruma-san got blown out!
Go up! There are too many
obstacles down here!
N-No way!
How strong can they get?!
You're so cool, Commander!
I am over here!
Wh-Who is it?!
Okay!
Mil Fleurs!
Hey, you! Fight!
We'll go beat Decken!
It's me!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Wow! They're so strong!
There are only 10 of them but they're
kicking the asses of 100,000.
You will never get away from the Noah
and my unending love, Shirahoshi!
Horn Boost!
The Straw Hat Pirates...
I'm good at digging too!
Maybe, they can save us all and
the Fish-Man Island for real!
Help us, Hyouzou-san!
Chopper!
Cool! You can turn into a stag beetle now?!
Go, Straw Hat!
Old man, can I get a wasabi octopus?!
Beat Hordy!
It's not a stag beetle!
No, you're not in a bar! Plus,
you shouldn't eat octopus!
You're doing great, Straw Hat!
--Princess Shirahoshi!
--When did she go up there?!
I strengthened 7 of my transformation
boosts in the last 2 years!
Thank you for saving me!
Boss Jimbei!
If you win, I'll let you eat as
much as you want at my restaurant!
You got hurt before - are you okay?
Yowahoshi...
I only need the Rumble
Ball for just one boost now!
Don't be mean!
Members of the royal family, soldiers,
citizens... all of them got hurt or died.
Mermaid Princess!
You can drink as much as
you want too, at my bar!
Shirahoshi! Why did she do that?!
So I can turn into any other
forms whenever I want!
--Straw Hat!
--We're counting on you!
Because that ship is flying towards her!
And even Shirahoshi is trying so hard
to save the Ryugu Kingdom while injured!
It's no use! He's completely drunk!
Boss Jimbei!
What a pain-in-the-ass coral guy!
How pathetic!
What? Then she...
Don't push your luck!
I'll bite your flesh off!
These are not coral - they're horns!
So this is not the time for me to
suffer from such minor injuries!
If you can prove yourself now,
it's your chance to become
an officer in one move.
And I'm a pain-in-the-ass monster for you!
Come on out, Kraken!
I need to ask you a favor.
Maybe not now.
They all seem so full of
life when they're fighting!
The Merfolk are the greatest
swimmers in the world!
Like they've been waiting
to fight for so long!
That's the girl that I love!
But to me, they look like stop motion!
I knew a little surprise
attack like this wouldn't do.
I thought you wanted to take just my life!
That bastard!
Shark Slicer!
Who are you?
I'm the soon-to-be No.1 Fish-Man
swordsman - Nuru-sama!
How many of them have we killed?
No...
If I am the only one who you want to kill,
please do not harm the other people...
It's huge!
N-None, sir.
There are only 10 of them!
Just crush them all!
What?
We're dead once it hits us!
Then it'll finally be over!
...of the Ryugu Kingdom!
--What's wrong?
--Is it a hangover?
Should I chop both of you up and
feed you to the little fishes?
Come and get me!
Oh no! They got the
mythical monster - Kraken!
Hyouzou-san!
--Princess-sama!
--Princess!
The pirate with a 400 million bounty
and the prince of the Ryugu Kingdom.
Watch out!
What exquisite food for them!
Even though the Straw Hats are strong,
Kraken!
He's coming!
Good job, considering it was you.
they're finished once they
get crushed by that thing!
Although his power is phony, he's fast!
You gained their favor so
slickly and caught Shirahoshi!
Oh, it's the Kraken! He'll do
whatever Captain tells him to!
Hang on tight!
He's as strong as hell!
Now, squeeze her to death!
See how formidable this
deep-sea creature is!
Hey, that's...
Look! The Noah is changing its course!
You're not too bad!
Your brother at the North Pole...
You're weak.
What are you doing?!
It's heading towards
Princess Shirahoshi-sama!
I know exactly where he is.
Can you say the same thing after this?!
We can just go there and
kill him whenever we want.
Kill them already!
Shirahoshi!
I brought you here all the way from
the North Pole! You're my slave!
So bright!
You brothers are mythical creatures.
Don't do this, Shirahoshi-chan!
If you can't see, you can't
defend yourself from my sword!
You have to work for me!
Even dead, I can sell you for a good price.
You can do it, can't you?
Take this!
He's pretty strong in the
sea! Almost like Zoro!
Don't tell me that's what you want.
So, that crazy Decken bastard...
You're not supposed to be
impressed at a time like this!
Kraken?
He was gonna crush us all
along with the island.
I can't believe this.
No matter where you go, you can't get
away from the Shark Slicer's blade!
He was obeying Hordy because his
brother was taken as a hostage!
How dare he betray us!
W-Wait a moment!
Is he trying to escape in the cloud of dust?
What?
Don't try to help us!
Fall back!
I'll tell you one last time!
Can we do something to save her?!
You only use your eyes to
see. That's why you're weak.
Squeeze Shirahoshi to death!
Hey, if I remember right, that's...
Go train some more and come back!
I don't think there are many others!
Huh? You two know him?!
How amazing!
Huh?
How amazingly beautiful you are,
Shirahoshi! Even your mind!
I didn't expect to see him here.
Surume-sama, y-you're hurting me!
The Noah is...
That was just dumb luck!
You're trying to take the
matter into your own hands
I'm gonna be the No.1 Fish-Man
swordsman, I won't lose...
Oh, hey, Surume!
in order to save the country,
aren't you, Shirahoshi?!
Shirahoshi!
It's me! Surume!
--Shirahoshi!
--Hey, go to the deck of the ship!
Shirahoshi!
Damn Decken!
Oh? Don't you remember me?
Is that what you wanted to
ask me before? But why there?
Surume!
Who is No.1?
How could you forget?!
Shira... hoshi...
You became my pet for a
while. I'm your friend!
Because of what Jimbei told me.
So you were doing everything he says
in order to save your brother's life?
Stop!
Do you think the ship is
filled with water, Jimbei?
You're eligible to become Vander
Decken IX's wife as I thought!
I don't know but I know Decken
is a Devil Fruit eater.
Hyouzou-san, we're on your side!
Oh no, the Sea Bonze is...
I know how you feel.
Which means there must be air for him!
You better die while you're still
beautiful and live in my heart forever!
--He looks strange.
--That's not how he gets drunk usually!
Is it your younger brother or older brother?
Alright, that's enough. Stop!
It'll be easier for me to fight there.
He's much stronger!
I wanna kick the crap out of Hordy
and the guy who throws things!
Shirahoshi!
Let me try to save his life too!
Tottering Hash!
I promised Yowahoshi when we left the
tower, that I was gonna protect her!
--Princess-sama!
--How could you do that!
Good job!
Did you forget?
I'm your friend!
--Don't do that!
--Run, Princess!
I can't believe it!
You really tamed the monster octopus?
Speaking of promises...
We three will become great
warriors like our father...
Sh-Shields don't work!
Yeah, I'm gonna use him like
experienced people do! Right, Surume?
He was writhing in agony without
any injury until a while ago!
...and protect Shirahoshi with
our lives as we promised!
Are you kidding? This is like what
happened when Hordy-san changed.
Surume-sama!
I have a promise to keep too!
Let me ride on you again!
We were defeated by that cheap
hoodlum who relies on some
Hyouzou-san has become a monster, too?!
fake power from the Energy Steroid!
It feels great! I feel a surge of energy!
Straw Hat is coming this way!
What a shame!
I'm sorry that we suspected you...
Kill him!
He did it!
Oh, I wanna cut more people!
Luffy-sama!
Don't mention it. Take me to the deck!
You guys are no match for him-dogon!
Let me cut you!
You wanna go to the deck?
Let us take care of him-ch!
Run! Somebody, stop him! There's
no way to defend ourselves!
Hordy!
I can take care of Straw Hat anytime.
Damn Yowahoshi! I told her to stick with me!
But there is something that
needs to be done right now.
It could be anybody!
That tickles! Stop! Surume!
Straw Hat! Captain Hordy!
--Go after him already!
--No, wait, Straw Hat!
Straw Hat!
Oh? Where did Hordy-san go?
I found one!
Why?!
We won't let you come any
closer to our captain-ch!
I'm sure you know it by now.
Look! He's up there!
All right, Surume! Let's go!
Hordy has an advantage in the
water since he is a Fish-Man.
Drop dead!
He's heading for the Noah!
H-Hyouzou-san got stopped!
--If nothing is done...
--What should we do?
We won't let you guys...
...Get in his way!
I have an idea!
The Kraken betrayed us!
Go up! Go up!
Stop Straw Hat!
You look tougher than the
anglerfish I just beat.
Like I said, it's no use, Shirahoshi!
Stop Kraken!
Second Gear!
Don't mess with me, Vander Decken!
You stupid octopus!
As long as my Mark-Mark Curse is in effect,
Where did he go?!
Zoro!
But I like this idea!
Sorry. I'm gonna take this guy.
What?!
there is no way for you
to get away from the Noah!
This will be a nice warm-up
before we go to the New World.
Go Surume!
Help me, Captain!
Kraken, go that way!
I don't know why but I'm full of fight now!
Damn! What's going on?!
Oh, Hordy Jones!
The Kraken is totally bonded to Straw Hat!
It gets less powerful in water as I thought.
What happened to Neptune? Did you kill him?
Awesome!
"Less powerful"?
How did he get there?! I couldn't see him!
I'm tormenting Shirahoshi with the Noah now.
Stupid lowly creature!
That bastard! How dare
he hurt Shirahoshi-chan!
Don't you know where you
are?! You're in the deep sea!
Listen, Surume! Stay here
and protect Yowahoshi!
Don't you think it's a good idea?
Sanji, wait!
Huh, Bro?!
A human like you has no
chance to win a fight!
I'll go up there! You stay here
and take care of the plaza!
That's...!
I have a good idea too!
On top of that,
All right!
everything will come to an end soon.
But Luffy, the ship is in the water!
Whether it's Shirahoshi or the
Fish-Man Island or your friends!
What is it? Let me hear it.
Do you think the ship is
filled with water, Jimbei?
I can't believe you knew the Kraken!
I don't know but I know Decken
is a Devil Fruit eater.
A fool like you can't protect anything!
If you die now...
I'm so impressed! You have so many friends!
Which means there must be air for him!
No.
Yeah?
Take this with you!
Um, thank you for doing this, Surume-sama!
It's a coral that produces bubbles!
Thanks!
I can't believe it!
What'll happen to this ship?
I'll be counting on you to save
my beloved Shirahoshi-chan!
There are still a lot of them.
That's...
You ready, Luffy?!
I'll protect them all!
...the Ship of Promise!
All right! Let's go!
Decken!
Go ahead!
That's what I worked for...
...those 2 years!
"Noah"!
The Straw Hats are battling the
Attempting to save Fish-Man Island.
Hordy suddenly attacks Decken.
As Luffy and Hordy begin their battle,
Using their new weapon, Franky, Usopp
Shirahoshi lures the Noah away.
officers of the New Fish-Man Pirates.
His terrifying plan was to
destroy Fish-Man Island!
suddenly, directly above
the Conchcorde Plaza,
and Chopper were making good progress,
After Luffy follows her,
The new, stronger attacks the crew has
learned in their two years of training
until they fell into the trap Daruma,
the massive form of Noah appears
and terrifies the citizens.
he's cornered into an underwater battle
at a severe disadvantage against Hordy.
an officer of the New
Fish-Man Pirates, had laid.
Hordy then attacks Shirahoshi
to complete his ambition!
continue to be revealed.
As everyone begins to lose hope,
Far above them,
But then, the second of Sunny's
new weapons commences its docking!
Then, Shirahoshi
the Noah is getting closer by the second,
Shirahoshi places herself in front
of the Noah to save Fish-Man Island.
But then, Luffy's new attack
is unleashed on Hordy!
in order to finish things!
as it descends to destroy Fish-Man Island.
A wondrous robot emerged!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Iron Pirate!
Here Comes General Franky!"
"The Noah Closing in! The Fish-Man
Island Facing Destruction!"
"A Massive Confused Fight! The Straw
Hats vs. The New Fish-Man Pirates!"
"Hurry up, Luffy! Shirahoshi's
Life in Jeopardy!"
"The Fierce Fight Begins! Luffy vs. Hordy!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!