Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates  who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil
and involved in an all-out war!
Surume!
So you were doing everything he says
in order to save your brother's life?
I know how you feel.
Is it your younger brother or older brother?
Let me try to save his life too!
Did you forget?
I'm your friend!
Second Gear!
"The Noah Closing in! The Fish-Man
Island Facing Destruction!"
I can't believe it! That's...
...the Ship of Promise! "Noah"!
W-Why...
Why is it moving?!
Who is doing it and how?!
Th-This is no good!
What's the matter, Father?
It's a bit strange,  but
why are you so upset?
It's just a relic from history.
It serves no purpose.
No! We can't let anything
happen to that ship-jamon!
Until the proper day comes, no one
is allowed to move that ship-jamon!
Captain Hordy!
I thought he took a lot of Energy
Steroids and became a monster!
No, look!
Straw Hat!
He's pretty tough.
We found Shirahoshi!
Over here!
Um... What do you three want?
We can't let you live!
We have to kill you!
Surume!
Surume-sama, you are very strong!
Protect Yowahoshi!
Straw Hat!
Do you know what Fish-Man Karate is?!
His head is gone!
He did it with a single blow!
It's not gonna work. Because
I'm made of rubber!
Your skill is nothing compared to Jimbei's!
Of course! That's why you
shouldn't depend on fake power!
Head; Hardening!
Iron Shell Squad!
Yes, sir!
You fool! Your head's gonna crack open!
Gum-Gum...
...Bell!
His head was harder than iron!
Armament; Hardening!
What?!
Shark Arrows!
He doesn't get hit at all!
Does he know when they come?!
Amazing, Luffy-sama!
That's the Observation Haki!
Gum-Gum...
...Bullet!
Captain Hordy!
Luffy-sama, he is unbelievably strong!
He's great! Straw Hat Luffy!
So that's how strong the
world-renowned pirate is!
What's going on?!
What is it?
What?! I-Is that...
...the Noah of the Fish-Man District?!
Why is the Noah in the air over the island?!
It's heading towards this plaza!
It's almost broken through
the bubble around the island!
Once the bubble pops, the island is
finished! We're all gonna get washed away!
--What is that?!
--The Noah?!
Super big!
Once the ship hits, the whole
island will be destroyed!
Who's operating it?!
I don't think it has an engine!
--What is that?!
--It's gigantic!
Don't know what's happening
but we're all dead!
I wonder if the sea will turn red
if we all get smashed at once.
Don't say things like that! Stop it!
--Evacuate!
--Get into the water off the island!
F-Folks?
It's...!
Ouch! I slipped!
You're Wadatsumi - working for Decken!
Captain Vander Decken! I fell off!
Stop the ship! I don't wanna die!
Decken?! What's going on here?
Captain Hordy, are you all right?!
Um, is this one of your strategies?!
It looks like Decken is operating the ship!
Shut up, you good-for-nothings!
Damn, Straw Hat!
Huh?
How tough can he be?! I attacked
him with the Armament Haki!
Did you say Decken? That crazy pirate!
This is not a part of the plan!
Shirahoshi!
Accept my love!
Did you hear me, Shirahoshi?
That must be...!
Princess Shirahoshi!
Don't tell me Decken threw the Noah
like he threw those letters and axes!
I've been loving you for 10 years
since you were just a little kid.
There is no one who could love you
like I do in all the wide world!
It's my love! Love, love!
L-O-V-E!
Why can't you just accept it?!
Things that I throw with
my Mark-Mark Fruit power...
...won't stop until they crash into
something or hit their target!
Noah the giant ship! It embodies
my love for you! Accept it!
And drop dead along with all the
Fish-Man Island, Shirahoshi!
Captain Decken! What about me?!
Wadatsumi! It's too late! It's
impossible for me to save you!
So I need you to become a sacrifice upon
Shirahoshi's death, along with the island!
No!
This is it! The bubble is gonna pop!
We're doomed!
Hey, where did Princess Shirahoshi go?!
Oh? She's not there!
What?! Princess! Princess Shirahoshi!
What? Shirahoshi disappeared?!
N-No way!
I am over here!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
--Princess Shirahoshi!
--When did she go up there?!
Yowahoshi...
Mermaid Princess!
Shirahoshi! Why did she do that?!
Because that ship is flying towards her!
What? Then she...
That's the girl that I love!
I thought you wanted to take just my life!
If I am the only one who you want to kill,
please do not harm the other people...
...of the Ryugu Kingdom!
Come and get me!
--Princess-sama!
--Princess!
Look! The Noah is changing its course!
It's heading towards
Princess Shirahoshi-sama!
Shirahoshi!
Don't do this, Shirahoshi-chan!
So, that crazy Decken bastard...
He was gonna crush us all
along with the island.
How dare he betray us!
Don't try to help us!
Can we do something to save her?!
How amazing!
How amazingly beautiful you are,
Shirahoshi! Even your mind!
You're trying to take the
matter into your own hands
in order to save the country,
aren't you, Shirahoshi?!
Shirahoshi!
Shira... hoshi...
You're eligible to become Vander
Decken IX's wife as I thought!
You better die while you're still
beautiful and live in my heart forever!
Shirahoshi!
--Princess-sama!
--How could you do that!
--Don't do that!
--Run, Princess!
Damn Yowahoshi! I told her to stick with me!
Straw Hat! Captain Hordy!
Oh? Where did Hordy-san go?
Look! He's up there!
He's heading for the Noah!
Don't mess with me, Vander Decken!
But I like this idea!
That bastard! How dare
he hurt Shirahoshi-chan!
Sanji, wait!
I'll go up there! You stay here
and take care of the plaza!
All right!
But Luffy, the ship is in the water!
Do you think the ship is
filled with water, Jimbei?
I don't know but I know Decken
is a Devil Fruit eater.
Which means there must be air for him!
Take this with you!
It's a coral that produces bubbles!
Thanks!
I'll be counting on you to save
my beloved Shirahoshi-chan!
You ready, Luffy?!
Go ahead!
Attempting to save Fish-Man Island.
Shirahoshi lures the Noah away.
After Luffy follows her,
he's cornered into an underwater battle
at a severe disadvantage against Hordy.
Then, Shirahoshi
in order to finish things!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Hurry up, Luffy! Shirahoshi's
Life in Jeopardy!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!