Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Hey, Apis! Who're you talking to?
Sickle-Sickle...
...Whirlwind!
It's coming!
Shoot it, quickly! Shoot it!
No! Don't come here!
We're out! We're out!
Oww!
Make chase at once!
Awesome! Nami! Check it out!
A wind slash!
Didn't Lost Island sink
a long long time ago?
Here they come! Here they come!
O-One other thing, Lt. Commander!
While in pursuit of them,
Eric-sama also reappeared
Now!
and has just returned to ship!
Grandpa Ryu says that the
island will surface again.
Look at 'em come! Look at 'em come!
The pirate ship!
The Going Merry is faster and more agile,
But he doesn't seem to remember
clearly where it is and there's no clue.
I won't let you escape...
but what are we going to do
when we get to Warship Island?!
Hey! I see an island below that light!
Yahoo!
Grandpa Ryu!
--We'll be okay!
--How will we be okay?!
We're going to land there!
He was separated from
his friends and lost his energy.
We just need to find
the dragons' nest first
Why've you not reported to me after
finding the Millennial Dragon?!
Grandpa Ryu! Hang in there!
so Grandpa Ryu can get better, right?!
Okay! Set sail for Lost Island!
I want to take him back to his
home no matter what it takes.
Doesn't look like that's
going to be an option...
Our main forces will now
head for Warship Island!
He always tells me that he'll
get his energy back for sure
Grandpa Ryu!
All ships, move out!
once he goes back to the dragons' nest.
Stupid Nami makes the
men do all the work...
So I'll definitely find it for him.
The small fries have leapt forth...
"Through the Sky They Soar!
The 1,000-Year Legend Lives Again!"
Hey, you! Less complaining
and more pushing!
"A Solitary Island in the Distant Sea!
The Legendary Lost Island"
Okay then! I'll take him...
Open to the left and right!
Crane Wing Formation!
Don't start getting cocky, you!
...to Lost Island!
Luffy! Were you listening?!
Lost Island sank into the sea!
Contacting all squad captains!
What now?! They have us blocked off!
Assemble on the deck of Ship #1!
Jump onto a ship, kick the guys off,
and cut the links!
Hang in there!
But since the legendary
Millennial Dragon actually exists,
Where's the resource manager?!
What happened to going to the
dragons' nest?! Try hard to live!
--Turn the yard this way!
--No, no! To the right!
That's the only choice, obviously!
I'm sure Lost Island also exists somewhere!
Finally made it...
Doesn't sound too bad to me!
Go get repair planks
from the other ships!
An island that's not even on a map?
Grandpa Ryu...
Okay! Let's go!
Yeah, that's why we're going!
--Grandpa Ryu!
--Damn those guys!
Repair Team!
Get to work repairing Ship #1!
Alright!
--This is bad!
--Yeah. He can't swim, huh?
"Eric Attacks! Great Escape
from Warship Island!"
Those damn pirates...
They're quicker at running
than I expected.
"Luffy, Completely Surrounded!
Commodore Nelson's Secret Strategy"
No worries. It'd be best to
let them go for now, anyway.
It's hot!
What do you mean?
They went to such dangerous lengths
to escape from this island.
Hm? Wh... What the heck is that?!
We're alive... right?
Why do you think that is?
The Navy again?!
Yeah, it seems that way...
Have you forgotten
this island has a legend?
Whew, what a scare...
It suddenly came right for me...
What's that?
Hey everyone! This is so cool!
The story about the dragons'
nest on Lost Island...
What's going on here...?
Commodore! The Millennial
Dragon is starting to sink!
What is this?
What? Are you saying they...?!
And, the 1,201st King was...
Don't fret! We'll still make it in time!
Fire a harpoon and drag it in!
It's only a guess.
"Showdown in the Ruins!
Tense Zoro vs. Eric!"
But if so, they'll wind up
being the perfect guides there.
Geez... The story isn't over yet?
Hey, listen to me.
Ugh!
What? Is it morning already?
Wow! What a huge picture!
Reporting to Commodore Nelson?
What's it of?
Yes...
I dozed off since the old
man's story was so long...
It looks like some
sort of map... Oww...
Target the Millennial Dragon!
There will be no need for that.
Okay! Fire!
But it's too worn out
to make any sense of.
Sir! But...!
Yes, sir!
But what is this place, anyways?!
Th-There's a problem!
Bokuden-san! Where's Apis?!
Wasn't this supposed
to be the dragons' nest?
Marvelous! A truly marvelous view!
Dunno.
The Dragonite I seek...
The elixir of immortality...
What's the matter?
Well, Apis?
Ah, you guys're pirates, right?
A Navy Fleet started blocking the harbor!
I don't know.
Listen, now! Do not let
the attacks falter even a bit!
As if I'd ever hand it over
to the likes of Nelson Royal!
Grandpa Ryu says he doesn't
know what this place is, either...
What?!
It can't be... Just to capture Apis...?
Man! He's always just a useless old guy!
Yes, sir!
But do not hit the raft!
I will have it!
Why are they after a girl like that?
To become a flawless
Eric the Whirlwind!
He's what?!
What are you doing?!
But it's the truth!
Yes, Commodore!
Hey! Everyone, come with me!
Then how exactly are you being useful?!
You've no idea of the value of the
thing you're standing on right now!
Certainly, Nami-san!
--Me?!
--Hey, guys! Look at this!
Why?
For so many years I've sought
the Millennial Dragon...
Just do it!
The ceiling picture's fallen down!
What do we do with the old man?
What's taking so long?!
And I've finally found it!
Looks like he's sound asleep,
so let's let him be.
All I want are the
Millennial Dragon's bones!
--Yikes!
--It's huge!
Whoa, talk about dangerous!
The elixir of immortality,
the Dragonite, is now as good as mine!
Commodore, sir! Please have this!
Hey, when Bokuden-san wakes up,
Once I have its Dragonite,
I can attain everlasting life!
please tell him that we'll protect Apis.
This whole building's ready to fall apart!
That's not what I mean!
O-Okay.
If we dilly-dally around here,
we'll be in danger, too!
--Commodore Nelson Royal!
--Oh! It's about time!
Let's get the heck outta this place!
But this might be the dragons' nest!
You have a report from Eric, I assume?
Their ship is on the starboard bow!
Why, you...!
No. It's a message from a soldier
working at Warship Island.
I don't see any dragons
around here, do you?!
Hold on a second!
Okay! The landing unit will
come to Warship Island with me!
What is it, Nami-san?
"Eric has located the
legendary Millennial Dragon."
This might not be Lost Island...
The rest of the crew
is to seize their ship!
He goes on to say that all ships
are presently busy repairing damage
Sir! The commodore's flagship
says his plan has succeeded!
See!
that the flagship received.
He says his attack is still ongoing!
You don't even know the reason why!
Quit making stuff up!
Curse you, Eric...
How can you tell that, Nami?
Looks like our mission is over now.
Why've you not reported to me
after finding the Millennial Dragon?!
Look up.
Up?
Are you planning to take the
Dragonite all for yourself?!
Grandpa Ryu isn't a thing!
He's our friend!
At the ceiling picture?
Look closely. It's a map that marks
the location of Lost Island.
Hi everyone!
He's a dear friend
who's on a journey with us!
You're nothing more than a hired soldier.
If they fall into
Nelson Royal's hands now...
This is the Millennial Dragon
Grandpa Bokuden was talking about.
That island with a
dome-shaped building on it...
What utter nonsense!
See?! Isn't he cool?!
In that case, you can sink
into the sea with your friend!
That's this island.
That dome is this building.
Hold on, Lt. Commander!
Don't talk like he's yours!
How dare you try to harpoon me?!
Our main forces will now
head for Warship Island!
It does look just like it...
When you get closer to the Grand Line
you run into things like this, huh?
Fire at that brat!
And the people around the island
are the people who once lived here.
Do you still want something?
All ships, move out!
Prepare one paddleboat
and three proficient seamen.
B-But, if we do that, we'll blow
the Millennial Dragon up, too!
Since there're Sea Kings as well,
I guess this is possible...
I'd wager they're probably Apis' ancestors.
No matter!
Bone fragments will do just fine!
A paddleboat?! What for?!
I-Is he really harmless?!
Our ancestors?
Y-Yes, sir! Aim the
sub-cannons out to sea!
Say, do you remember what
old man Bokuden told us?
Because a mast would get in the way.
Yes, sir!
Nope! I was asleep!
Don't tell me you're going
into the enclosed area?!
Come on, now! He said
the people of Warship Island
Ah! He can be senile sometimes,
so if he acts like you're food, get away!
Lost Island, huh?
had traveled there from another island.
Just do it already.
The map doesn't have any islands
in the waters around Warship Island
You're fine staying here?!
What kind of wimpiness is that?!
He did?
Come to think of it,
he did say something like that...
It's too late!
that fit the bill...
You still haven't
accomplished your goal!
But it doesn't hurt, right?
Then does that mean the dynasty
he kept blabbing on about
Hey! Grandpa Ryu!
Which way should we go?!
What happened to going to your nest?!
was on this island?
Don't give up by saying
you're staying here!
I guess you call it soft-mouth?
Probably.
So what had me wondering
Wh-Wh-What're you saying?!
He's not a puppy.
Of course I will!
Don't worry about Apis!
Apis! It's dangerous! Go back inside!
were all the dragon statues
and paintings on the way here.
Let him eat you like that!
Just think about yourself now!
Zoro!!
I think they might've been used
by the people living on this island
I can't leave Grandpa Ryu all by himself!
Don't! He'll have food poisoning.
to worship the Millennial Dragon as a god.
Hey, you! Wait!
What'd you say, you damn love cook?!
I bet the Millennial Dragon used
to fly over this island long ago.
That's dangerous! Get back here!
It's your fault if you fall!
Untie these ropes!
Hey.
What the Navy is after
is this Millennial Dragon.
I see!
Grandpa Ryu!
That would lower the chance of the
dragons' nest being on this island.
--I gotta go to Grandpa Ryu!
--What's that?!
Just hang in there a little longer!
I think he went to sleep again!
Frankly, the reason I brought you here
I gotta save Grandpa Ryu!
I promise I'll take you
to the dragons' nest!
But...! If so, then where's the real one?!
L-Leave Grandpa Ryu to Luffy!
is that we'd like to bring this
Millennial Dragon back to Lost Island.
Man, she's brave!
Wouldn't it be that island
with the dragon drawn on it?
No, no, no!
I gotta go! I gotta go!
Dammit! That moves me to tears!
Sorry for the wait, everyone!
Wh-What're you saying?!
The Navy is closing in on us!
If anyone, he'll manage somehow!
That's right!
Alright!
The food's ready!
There's an island ahead of where
this island's people are praying.
I'll break through the front lines
and take you to the dragons' nest!
We're gonna have enough
trouble just getting away,
Did she cook again?!
The entire sea is shaking!
how in the heck could we
take such a big creature...?
No one was waiting for her food!
What is this?! What's happening?!
Grandpa Ryu... wants to go home...
That's the real Lost Island!
The dragons' nest must be there, too!
So...
Oh! Sanji!
But...
Don't tell me, Luffy,
Whew, what a relief!
that you promised her, like,
"Yeah! I'll bring him home"...
Wait a minute!
That island is shaped like...!
So you made today's meal--?!
Oww!
Yeah, I promised and said,
"I'll bring him home."
Yeah.
Hey! We've been hit from behind!
Assuming the map is correct,
the dragons' nest is on Warship Island.
Don't do that! We don't know
where that island is, right?!
Grandpa Ryu!
Hey! Sanji! We've been hit! Sanji!
Eat lots, okay?
Oh! Food!
How are we supposed to get there?!
We're done for! We're sunk!
But I thought there were no places
on Warship Island that fit the bill?!
Food!
What the...?!
What the...?! What the...?!
If we go, it'll work out somehow.
Pipe down! We ain't been hit.
As if!
Hot!
But that's what the map says!
Eh? Seriously?
I thought Grandpa Ryu would get his
energy back once he goes home...
Why, you...!
Yeah.
Or are you saying the people
long ago just drew random nonsense?!
I'm saved!
Who the hell thought
of this plan anyway?!
Yeah, you guys!
Nami-san'd never say
anything that's wrong!
Grandpa Ryu!
Animals have a migration instinct.
It was you.
Really? So that's it!
This means it's somewhere on that island!
Hot!
This Millennial Dragon may know something.
That's it! That's it! Go!
Grandpa Ryu!
We'll figure it out if we go check it out!
Apis!
Yeah. Let's find Lost Island!
What is happening?!
But... It could also have sunk
to the bottom of the ocean...
There shouldn't be any underwater
volcanoes in these waters!
But...
Grandpa Ryu!
Well, things will probably
work out, don't you think?
No, that's actually much more likely.
Zoro...
No matter! Fire! Fire! Fire!
That would explain why
nobody's ever found it yet.
That's fine, but what
are we gonna do with him?
Just bringing him down the mountain
alone will be a lot of work.
Hey! A ball's coming this way!
Apis?
I can't do any more than this!
Do something on your end!
Grandpa Ryu!
First, build a cart!
Think back, Grandpa Ryu!
Where is the dragons' nest?!
A big enough one for Grandpa Ryu to ride.
Okay! I'll do something!
We thought it was this place,
but there's nothing here!
Gum-Gum...
Ahhh...
...Balloon!
There's only a painting, Grandpa Ryu!
Grandpa Ryu!
All right!!
Are you okay?
Does the painting bring
back any memories?!
Gum-Gum Gatling!!
Our only hope now is that you
remember something, Grandpa Ryu!
No way...!
Come on! Please!
Remember, Grandpa Ryu!
No way!
Sheesh. I made all that food
and it goes to waste!
I see!
You impudent bastards!
Can't you just make some more, then?
How dare you damage one of my warships?!
The point is we shouldn't waste food!
You have dear friends of your own, too!
What are you doing?!
Hit them with the Super Giant Cannon!
Yes, sir!
What is it?
--Grandpa Ryu!
--What's he bellowing for?
There's no escape!
There's no escape for you!
He's calling...
Lost Island...
Calling?
Prepare to fire the Super Giant Cannon!
The dragons' nest...
It's east of Warship Island...
He's telling Millennial Dragons
all around the world that it's "time"...
So that's where Lost Island is?!
Grandpa Ryu said he just remembered!
Is this enough?
It's "time"?
Yeah. A-Okay!
What's that mean?
We know where!
Since you did all this,
I guess I have no choice...
Lost Island is east of Warship Island!
The pirate ship has
been trapped up ahead!
I'll do it. All right, I'll do it!
Grandpa Ryu said so!
Ready to fire!
Hey! W-What's that?!
That's right!
Usopp! Take the wheel!
What is that?!
A direct hit from that and our
ship'll be blown to shreds!
You got it!
Phew! I guess this is it.
We'll be okay!
I'll just bounce it back again!
Alright! Let's rush
straight for Lost Island!
This thing won't break even
when Grandpa Ryu rides it!
Don't be stupid!
I'll turn the ship about;
Yeah!
you guys work the rear sail!
But the harbor is blocked
by the Navy, right?
--Hurry!
--Yeah!
What will we do with the ship?
An eye for an eye!
I got a shot ready for you, too!
Isn't it gonna work out?
Dammit! You better eat all of that!
S-So many Millennial Dragons!
No, it won't.
Here we go!
Yep! Leave it to me!
Shall we make a raid?
--These're Grandpa Ryu's friends!
--Yeah!
Eat this!
Yeah, good idea.
They've changed course?
That's not gonna work
since we have Grandpa Ryu.
--What the...?!
--Where the hell'd they come from?
Yes, sir! The pirate ship appears
to be headed for the waters
--Fire!
I have an idea about how
we can carry him out of here.
east of Warship Island!
T-Those are...!
By the way,
I want the Going Merry
So they're making their move...
Dragonite!
It's a mother lode of Dragonite!
to be brought to
the rear of the island.
Okay! It's the precious ship
that Kaya gave us. I'll do it.
Turn the bows eastward!
Full speed ahead!
What just happened?!
He's so cool!
We're now going to close
in on the Straw Hat Pirates!
However... Zoro comes with me!
An enemy cannonball hit
our main cannon perfectly!
Shoot them! Shoot them down!
Me too?!
W-What?!
Cannoneers to the gun batteries!
Then I'll leave it to you guys.
W-We can't! Our cannons
can't reach that high!
All ships, prepare for Level 3 combat!
Okay! So...
Hurry and lift me up!
...how about we wait until nightfall?
Grandpa Ryu!
Our destination...
Alright! So the dragons' nest
really is on Warship Island, then?!
No!
Yes, sir!
...is Lost Island.
Howdya like that?!
All ships, move out!
This is what happens when
Usopp-sama gets serious!
Eh?! How did you know
what he said, Luffy?!
Bring the ship to the edge of the cape
that looks like Usopp's nose.
I just did!
Not too shabby, for a fluke.
Grandpa Ryu!
You're right.
Grandpa Ryu said he remembered!
You're so full of it.
--What?! I can do that anytime!
--Wow... He hit it!
--Here, Zoro.
--Yeah.
You're right! That's Usopp's nose.
He says the dragons' nest
You're cool, Usopp!
So what're we gonna do?
Just bringing the ship won't...
--Here you go, Zoro.
--Yeah.
is on an island east of a peak
that looks like a warship...
Don't worry about it.
Yeah! I know!
I promise I'll tell Apis!
Man! Why does he say that
--Here, Zoro.
--Yeah.
Yeah!
I don't think they'd find
this place so easily...
only after we went through
all that hardship to get here?!
--Zoro.
--Yeah.
...but in any case, hurry up.
I'm sorry...
What?! Doing things on a
hit-or-miss basis like that isn't...
It'll be okay! Don't worry!
I'm sorry for dragging
you all the way out here
Here, Zoro.
Sanji-kun, Luffy!
Put Grandpa Ryu on the cart.
Can't you hand 'em
to me without talking?
You just keep Apis safe!
for something that might've
already sunk into the ocean...
--Okay!
--Okay, Nami-san!
--Who're you talking to?!
--Grandpa Ryu.
It was all for nothing...
Huh?
Lost Island is at the
end of this great ocean!
Not necessarily!
Now's our chance!
Let's act quickly and
cut some links to open a path!
Who knows? The dragons' nest
could be somewhere unexpected!
What kind of island could it be?!
Hey, old man!
Where are you hiding this girl?
Right, Nami-san!
Hey!
--Luffy.
--Leave it to me!
And there's no telling for sure
without checking it out, right?!
Usopp! See anything?!
Gum-Gum...
Hey!! Wake up!!
That's right!
Nope, nothing!
...Bridge!
Being discouraged this
easily isn't like you, Apis!
No?
Oh... Did I already talk
about the 1,201st King?
Gum-Gum...
Man, we've come a long way, but
there's no sign of an island at all...
You'll never get anything done
if you're afraid of failure.
...Rocket!
Alright!
Wh-What are you talking about?
There's nothing wrong with
living a roundabout life...
Grandpa Ryu! Just hold on!
Gonna borrow your neck!
Lt. Commander!!
Are we sure about this?
Yeah...
...And...
There're tracks from something
being dragged in the backyard!
Everyone...
And then there's Grandpa Ryu...
Here goes!
I wish he'd remember
some more details or something...
...Battle-Axe!
So, let's go! Grandpa Ryu won't
get any better if we just stay here!
Eric! Did you find anything?!
Oh! I know!
Right?!
--Sorry, Zoro.
--Why, you...!
Let's bonk Grandpa Ryu
in the head with this!
Yeah!
These tracks must've been made by them.
What?!
Think maybe then the shock'll
help him remember something else?
Thank you!
Report! What are they doing?!
They should be hiding
somewhere in the mountain.
Knock it off!
Yes, sir!
Three people from the pirate ship
have boarded portside Ship #1!
Okay! We'll track them down!
Huh?! Say what?!
Ahhh... This is why I suggested
that we wait until night.
Is something wrong, Zoro?!
Someone's here.
With bloodlust.
What're you doing?!
Steel chains, huh?
What was that?!
Hey! Grandpa Ryu! We're almost there!
--Think you can cut 'em?
--There's nothing I can't cut!
Thanks for the explanation.
We're almost to Lost Island!
Now I know where to find
Dragonite and the dragons' nest...
Really? Then they're all yours.
And it's there, right? The dragons' nest?
And if you go to the dragons' nest,
you'll get better, right?!
You again?!
But there's no point if it's
at the bottom of the ocean...
What?
So it would seem my only option
is to take your Millennial Dragon.
You're so goofy, thanking me!
No!
I'll go on ahead.
Besides, we don't know if their
nest is on the ocean bottom or not!
We're not even there yet!
Talk about coming out of the woodwork...
--I like it when things are lively!
--Sure, whatever.
He said he had Sickle-Sickle
Fruit powers, if I recall...
--I leave the small fries to you.
--Yeah!
That's one nasty guy we got here...
Hm...? Ahhh!
Sickle-Sickle Fruit?!
He has Devil Fruit powers?!
In the name of the Nelson Fleet,
we won't let you break through here!
Ahhh! Meh mound me!
--Hey...
--Luffy.
--It's them!
--Don't let him escape! Fire!
You go on ahead and take
Grandpa Ryu to the ship!
They followed us, huh?
I'll catch up with you later.
Zoro!!
What's that? Smoke?
Got it!
W-W-Whoa, now! The ship?!
What?!
Th-There was another one?
We don't even know
where the exit here is!
Stop! Stop!
What was that?!
Then we can just... make one!
Stop! Or we'll fire!
The commodore's been beaten!
You're not seriously gonna--!
Oh, well! We'll see when we get closer!
Stop!!
Yeah! That's it! That's it!
You're so wonderful!
Urgh!
That's not true! I don't think
you're troubling me at all!
Keep it up!
Chop those things up good!
Wh... What?! Are they going to ram us?!
What's your problem?!
Huh? I thought that would
bust it open, but...
--It turned into an argument at some point.
--Hey! Grandpa Ryu!
Troops sure are weak once
their bosses are taken out.
Curse you! How dare you
lousy pirates try to break my links?!
--It turned into an argument at some point.
--Hey! Are you listening?
--It looks more like Apis is
--Pretending to sleep isn't fair!
Oh, geez...
Maht?! Mis is mad!!
Are they just gonna reel in
their chains and run away?
--the only one who's angry, though...
--Pretending to sleep isn't fair!
Capture them, at all costs!
--the only one who's angry, though...
--Hey, say something!
We better get goin' too.
--Do you think we should stop her?
--Hey, say something!
Or else I'll maroon
every last one of you!
It's gonna ram us!
Gum-Gum...
Furl the sails!
It's too late now!!
They're circling around...
What's going on?
...Gatling!
A... ship?
Hey! Let's go!
But something's definitely
not right about it...
Yeah!
The chains!
It's open! It's open!
--You idiots! What're you doing?!
--We're gonna crash!
It worked out! It worked out!
Let's go, Apis!
He's less than a caveman...
Oh, no, you don't!
Here they come! Here they come!
That's really somethin'!
Nami-san! I'm back!
Awesome! Nami! Check it out!
--Just get on already!
--Where's Luffy?
I already am...
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
...Slingshot!
Look! Look at me!
Sorry to bother you again!
Hiyaaaaaah!
Prepare to set sail!
Dammit, Luffy! Get going already!
Yes, sir!!
--Yo!
--Don't give me, "Yo!"
Oh! My bad!
Hoist the anchor!!
Can't you come back more quietly?!
You're gonna wreck the ship!
--The pirate ship!
--This can't be real!
Furl the sails!!
What the--?!
I-It vanished!
Grandpa Ryu...
What's going on?!
Wow...
Go after that pirate ship!!
Hey! What just happened?!
Why did they disappear?!
--An earthquake?
--Again?!
Yes, sir!!
I didn't know they were like this...
Grandpa Ryu...
I-I have no idea!
I wasn't able to keep my
promise to you, Grandpa Ryu...
--All ships, full stop!
--Yes, sir!
Tell everyone to wait on
standby until my next orders!
There's only one chain left!
Let's get moving!
Yes, sir!
I wasn't able to take
you to the dragons' nest...
So fast! So fast!
Continue moving forward.
Aye-aye, sir!
You can't be serious! There's no
telling what's in the waters ahead!
No, no! Someone stop them!
No, Grandpa Ryu's wish came true.
It's too risky!
That again?
W-We always make it out alive, don't we?!
It's not for certain that we'll
live through this! That idiot!
Can't you hear the
Millennial Dragons' voices?
Then have them prepare a small craft.
This makes going back a cinch!
You're not seriously going to...!
That's right. I'm going on my own.
W-What the...?!
Damn you! Get in my way
and you'll pay!
What's with these earthquakes?!
T-This one's big!
Here they come!
So let's see how you plan
on making me pay!
Hey! Look!
T-The sea's pulling way back!
Oh! Eric!
Huh? It's just fog...
Well done! Now the
Millennial Dragon is mine!
W-We've got trouble!
I thought Nami was in
big trouble again or something...
The bird said that the
Navy is getting close!
What in the world's going on?!
What was that?
Oh... They came sooner than I thought...
Our own ship was right in front of us...
Hey, what're you going to do now?
And then we went right through it... right?
Ahh, you don't have to worry
I can't see anything at all!
because we have these two.
That scared me--!
It was almost like... a mirage...
You're the Sicko Sicko Fruit guy!
So that's what it meant!
A mirage? That's it!
What is it, Nami-san?!
Once the Going Merry
is at Usopp's Nose Cape,
I read about this a long time ago!
The dragons' nest really is here!
Not "Sicko." The Sickle-Sickle Fruit!
It said temperature differences
between warm and cold ocean water
we'll go all the way down.
They're not called "Millennial Dragons"
because of their life spans!
can create mirages at sea!
I'm pretty confident that right now
Girl! It's time to hand
over the Millennial Dragon!
we're the fastest moving
things in this world!
It's because they come to this
island only once every 1,000 years!
What kind of thing is that to brag about?!
No! I'll never give you Grandpa Ryu!
Luffy! Do something!
That brat is up there.
We're gonna wind up in pieces
before we get to the ship!
Hand it over like a good little girl!
No!
It's okay! It's okay!
Wh-What's that?
Millennial Dragons are migratory!
How are we okay?!
Is this a mirage, too?
I-It's a monster!
I can chop you into pieces with
wind slashes at any time, you know.
Urgh! What's the deal with this sea?!
And it's by no coincidence that
they've all flocked here now!
Sickle-Sickle Wind Slash!
Stop right there!
It's no wonder they call it Lost Island!
What was that?!
I finally found Dragonite,
the elixir of immortality!
Lay a hand on the kid and you'll pay!
You can't run away from me!
Because it only surfaces
once every 1,000 years!
Y-Yeah! I, Usopp-sama,
won't sit by quietly either!
I have no time to be playing with you.
Dammit! What're you doing?!
Don't panic!
So of course no one today
remembers the last time it surfaced!
That's the Millennial Dragon
we've been looking for!
Shut up! I can't help it,
you damn bastard!
My only goal is that Millennial Dragon!
Fools.
We'll get closer to them without being
noticed and capture it in one shot!
Sanji-kun! Zoro!
I made that wind slash
just now miss on purpose...
And now... this very moment...
Get back here!
Let's raise the sails! Undo the ropes!
Yes, sir!!
Yes, Nami-san!
...is when the dragons' nest has appeared!
You stay in the cabin!
No! I'm going to stay
by Grandpa Ryu's side!
Dammit! After we went through
all that trouble to escape...!
You idiot! There's nothing you
can do by staying with him!
Get in my way,
and this time I won't miss!
I'm sure he's feeling lonesome!
I hafta hurry to him!
I'll blow your entire ship apart!
Are they alright?!
We haven't yet.
Hey!
What's wrong?
Ahhhh!
Just sit down and shut up!
Don't let them get away!
Capture them without fail!
--It's him.
--Huh? What's he doing?
Hey! Will Zoro really be alright?!
Yeah! He'll be fine!
--Tie the raft to our boat!
--It's him.
--Huh? What's he doing?
--Tie the raft to our boat!
--Looks like he's planning to take
Apis hostage and steal the dragon.
Ahhh! Zoro! Zoro! Zoro! Zoro!
T-T-Take care of the sail!
But he's up against a guy
with Devil Fruit powers!
--Yes, sir!
--Looks like he's planning to take
Apis hostage and steal the dragon.
He doesn't stand a chance,
no matter how strong he is!
That's bad!
Got it! Leave it to me!
Stop! If you lay a hand on him,
Hurry! We need to hurry back
down and get out of danger!
He'll still be alright!
he'll take out Apis and Nami
and the others with his technique!
Dammit! Their ship is big, but it's fast!
Oh! Right!
For some reason it seems...
Luffy! Ahead! Ahead!
Then I'll use my foot!
Whoa...
...like this sea's trying
to push the ship back.
This isn't good...
--Huh?!
--Listen better!
Don't give us that!
I'm taking the Millennial
Dragon now! Nothing personal!
Do something!
No!! Don't shoot Grandpa Ryu!
Grandpa Ryu!
You fight dirty! Give Apis back!
Apis!
Don't worry! This storm is no big deal at--!
Eric! Well done! Now, bring it here!
Grandpa Ryu!
No thanks. This isn't for you.
Eh?! What did you say?!
As I thought, that brat had something
to do with the Millennial Dragon...
Over there, eh?
The only reason I obeyed you
was to use the Navy's
information-gathering capabilities.
...although I didn't think that I'd be
able to encounter a real live dragon.
No!
Sorry. I can't let you pass here.
What?!
It's not like you were any different.
You tried to use me, too.
I no longer care about that brat.
Whatever. It's up to me
whether I pass or not!
Zoro!
Say, is that what I think it is?
That dragon is the elixir of
immortality that we've been looking for!
I hired you for a great sum of money!
Yeah! It must be the dragon nest
Grandpa Ryu wanted to go back to!
Out of the way!
I think I've worked off
that chump change by now.
Fire!
I have no obligation to obey
a sea lion like you anymore!
Grandpa Ryu! No! What are you saying?!
This is?
Stop it!
S-Sea lion?
You're calling me a sea lion?!
We will save you! Don't give up!
I'm going to use the Dragonite
I get from the Millennial Dragon
Damn! That nimble bastard!
--H-Hey! Apis!
--Apis!
to make myself perfect!
No use!!
We promised we'd go
to your nest together!
--Why'd she suddenly run off?
--Grandpa Ryu.
You'll pay! You'll pay for this!
Wh-What the heck...?!
Gum-Gum...
Shoot that backstabber!
Shoot him! Shoot him!
Grandpa Ryu is here...
Th-The bullets definitely...!
...Lasso!
So you have powers of a devil fruit.
Grandpa Ryu!
Nami-san! There's light over there!
That's right. I'm a rubber person.
That's the eye of the typhoon!
R-Rubber person...!
Hey! I see an island below that light!
D-Devil fruit...?
Grandpa Ryu! Grandpa Ryu!
What's that?
They're starting again!
We're going to land there!
--Use...
--Use swords!
Grandpa Ryu!
Guns don't work against rubber!
Luffy!
Don't worry! Leave it to me!
Sanji-kun!
If you don't want to
get blasted into pieces,
We're taking him to
the dragons' nest, right?!
Yes, Nami-san!
you'd better start rowing!
I told you I'm not letting you pass.
Yeah!
Just by coincidence,
the place Grandpa Ryu sunk
Just stay right there!
Gum-Gum Gatling!
was where the dragons' nest was...
Stop...
Do you suppose that might
help him rest in peace better?
Stormy seas surround the island...
Stop!
It's okay! He said his wish
came true when he was sinking!
Luffy! There's another dead-end!
I'm begging you! Please don't
harass Grandpa Ryu any more!
It's almost like they're trying
to keep people away from it...
You call yourselves the Navy?
--Wanna bust it down?
--No!
So this is the dragons' nest?
Look at all these weird rocks...
Really, you guys are good for nothing.
He hasn't done anything wrong!
That must be why nobody's
ever found it before, huh?
I'm pretty sure that up ahead is
the cliff we followed on our way up!
Hm?
Be quiet.
I think they're probably
made of Dragonite...
If we do that, we'll fall over it
head-first and then we're goners!
But it seems more like a castle
that's sunk into the sea than an island...
I have to take him to
the dragons' nest right away!
Huh?!
Look at this rock here.
Doesn't it look just like a dragon?
So please stop this!
--What was that?
--A knife?
Oh, now that you mention it...
But why are the rocks dragons?
--Think we can fly?
--No!
What're you doing?!
Let go! Let go, I said!
Whoa! Check it out!
Doesn't that seem shaped like a dragon?!
Because they were on the ocean floor
for a thousand long years.
Listen, girl. You're a hostage.
This must be where the
Millennial Dragon lives after all!
The materials in their bodies fossilized.
And I'm taking the Millennial Dragon.
Wow! Dragons sure are skillful!
Oh, I see!
I'll never let you have
Grandpa Ryu! Never! Never!
--Do you really get it?
--Nope! Not at all!
You idiot! It was obviously
humans who made this building!
They say when elephants are about to die,
I've had enough, girl!
Well, whatever.
they hide themselves
in their elephant graveyard.
Any more shouting
and I'll chop you apart!
We made it to Lost Island!
My name is Eric the Whirlwind.
Maybe the same is true here.
This might be a dragon graveyard...
Oww!
I'm a mercenary hired by Nelson Royal.
A dragon graveyard?
Let go!
But does anyone even live here anymore?
No! It's not!
We don't have any business
with you pirates.
I told you not to get in my way!
Grandpa Ryu said going back
to his nest would make him better!
The whole place has been
swallowed up by Mother Nature...
We have some business
with that Millennial Dragon.
Now die like a good little boy!
Say, where do you suppose
the dragons' nest is?
Damn kid, giving me trouble...
If you stand in my way,
This can't be a graveyard!
I'll make you a victim of my wind slash,
the power of the Sickle-Sickle Fruit.
Hey!
Grandpa Ryu!
I'm talking to you, Grandpa Ryu!
Apis...
Hey! What are you running for?!
--Hey, he said Sicko Sicko...
--Surprised?
--I have the power of a devil fruit, too.
Grandpa Ryu was
a lost Millennial Dragon...
--Sicko?
--I have the power of a devil fruit, too.
Sheesh! We're at the dragon nest
island now! Come on, wake up!
It looks like we somehow
managed to make it...
Get back here!!
--What should we do?
--I have the power of a devil fruit, too.
--What shall we do?
Man, we seriously have
incredible luck or something...
Luffy?
Nami!
He was all alone,
for a thousand years...
Do we have to keep going?
A little bit longer!
But he made friends with you, Apis.
Nami-san's lovely even when
she looks at the distant ocean.
Alright! We made it, right?
Dammit!
What did he say?
Get ready to set sail! Let's go!
Just hurry up.
He says he's not sure...
Hey! You bastards!
Are you listening to me?!
No more, please...
He says this might not be Lost Island...
Damn bastard...
You're totally... gonna pay!
He said out of the
1,000 years he was alive,
You're Eric the Sicko, right?
We're listening.
--What?!
--You can't be serious!
this last year with
you was his happiest.
We went all the way through
that stormy sea just to get here!
That's not right!
Grandpa Ryu!
You want some of this? It's yummy!
I didn't say sicko, I said sickle,
like the one that slices!!
Apis!
Hey, Grandpa Ryu!
Eat lots and get better soon, okay?!
We're sicko talking about this!
Just kidding!
Luffy... You understand
the dragons' language?
Look at the top there!
Luffy!
We could look down at the
whole island from up there!
I just somehow know.
He says... He says Zoro's in trouble!
Geez, talk about half-baked...
Yeah! Trying to figure things
out here won't get us anywhere!
That's so cute!
It really suits you, Grandpa Ryu!
Hope you don't regret making me angry.
But there's no doubt about it!
What do we do?! We gotta help him!
You liar...
--Let's go have a look!
--Okay!
Sickle-Sickle...
Alright! Let's go!
Die!
You're such a liar, Grandpa Ryu!
If this is the dragons' nest...
Whirlwind!
Zoro!
If you've made it back to the dragons' nest,
then open your eyes again!
Ow!
Stupid Nami makes
the men do all the work...
Talk to me!
What was that?
I see. A wind slash, huh?
Get better!
It's like, "Try pushing it yourself!"
Hey, you! Less complaining
and more pushing!
The winds I create are as sharp
as legendary swords.
--Bingo!
--Awesome!
Don't start getting cocky, you!
No, not this pattern...
No matter how trained you are,
Quit complaining and push!
it's easy for me to tear you apart.
Ah! Nami-san is so nice
when she's snappy!
--Here we go!
--I told you to stop doing this!
Grandpa Ryu wasn't lying at all!
If only!
Aren't we going yet?
No. Not yet!
He said that Millennial Dragons
return to the nest every 1,000 years
Oh. My bad.
Now, out of my way!
Hand over the Millennial Dragon!
I swear, someday
I will chop this guy up!
and are reborn again.
I can't stand this!
No way!
Damn!
Do you wanna experience the
Sickle-Sickle Whirlwind again?
Grandpa Ryu said that?
It's a city...
I refuse to let you escape me!
Oww! My ears!
There!
Aren't we going yet, Nami-san?!
Wow! Everything is broken everywhere!
Grandpa Ryu let out a sound...!
Here they come! They're here!
Did people really used to live here?
Now! Sanji-kun! Luffy!
Obviously, given all of these houses.
Okay, Nami-swan!
--We're out! We're out!
--That's definitely weird...
--What?!
--We'll be right there!
Then why's there no one here now?
Who knows? Maybe they found
a better island to live on.
What?! They did?!
Nami-san! I'll be your love catapult!
A baby Millennial Dragon?!
Yes, sir! They're on their
way to Warship Island again,
Oww...
with the Millennial Dragon in tow!
Then make chase the moment
we're ready! On the double!
Grandpa Ryu!
The Millennial Dragon's mark...
You can move! That's great!
Did the Millennial Dragon play
with children here on this island?
I won't let you escape!
Y-Yes, sir! A-And one other
thing, Lt. Commander!
Gum-Gum...
That's great!
While in pursuit of them,
Eric-sama also reappeared
Sickle-Sickle...
Pistol!!
and has just returned to ship!
What?
Hey! Are you guys friends
of the Millennial Dragon too?
Whirlwind!!
What a bunch of useless clods.
We should just sink the lot of 'em...
Come on, Apis. Don't get left behind!
Sir?
I won't let you escape.
Nothing! Thank you for the report!
Guess what?!
These birds told me something!
Really?!
I'm glad to see you've
returned to the ship unharmed.
They said there's a building
on the summit with a dragon mark!
Did you get the Dragonite?
--What the...?!
--You don't suppose he's...
For reals?!
We're gonna run into a rock!
It might be the dragons' nest!
Luffy!
Gum-Gum... Gatling!
Yeah! You can do it,
Grandpa Ryu! You can fly!
If you have time for sarcastic remarks,
then go after them already!
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
Nami! Hurry up!
You're flying!
You're flying, Grandpa Ryu!
Look at 'em come! Look at 'em come!
Wait for me!
No! If the Millennial Dragon
is just going to escape,
They'll never catch up with us!
The Going Merry is faster and
more agile than bulky Navy warships,
then I don't care if we kill it!
What is this?!
All I need is its Dragonite, anyway!
Fire! Fire! Fire like mad!
That's how I do it.
but what are we going to do
when we get to Warship Island?!
Dumbass!!
--We'll be okay!
--How will we be okay?!
Ready... go!
You know, Apis.
We just need to find
the dragons' nest first
This isn't just a
Millennial Dragon graveyard.
so Grandpa Ryu can get better, right?!
That was close...
Stop!
We finally made it... I can't go on...
I think it's a place
that connects to new life.
Grandpa Ryu! Run! Run to where
the cannons can't reach you!
Easier said than done!
Thanks for showing us the way!
Their nest could be
at the bottom of the ocean!
We just need to search the
bottom of the ocean then!
--Thank you, everyone!
--Eh?
Yoo-hoo!
That's big talk for
someone who can't swim...
We've sure come up a long ways.
For bringing Grandpa Ryu
back to the dragons' nest.
That's it! Shoot him down, quickly!
Anyways, we need to get back
as fast as we can!
Good work, everyone!
Yoo-hoo!
I realize it now, too.
Yep! Good work!
I realize what kind of place this is,
We don't have time to be
messing with the navy!
Stop that!
and why Grandpa Ryu
wanted to return here so badly.
Nami-san. It doesn't look like
that's going to be an option...
This painting is of the
Millennial Dragon, right?
Apis...
Yoo-hoo!
Yeah, it is.
It's an amazing place, isn't it?
This building is the dragons' nest?
Now I understand why my ancestors
went so far as to build a temple...
This place?
Now's your chance to run, Grandpa Ryu!
Hold on! Where's the entrance?
How do we get inside?
Nami said to come to the
edge of that cape, right?
What are you doing?!
Attack it with this ship, too!
Wow! Cool!
This is the door!
Yeah.
You're so stupid!
Thank you, Luffy!
It's like a gargoyle!
--Yes, sir!
--It must be shot down!
There's no handle
or keyhole anywhere!
Hey, now!
Darn. We couldn't get rid of them.
How're you supposed to open it?!
Okay! Let's go back to the village!
Yeah.
Everyone there must be worried,
and probably surprised, too!
Well, after all, we have no choice
but to make a raid... Yikes!!
The small fries have leapt forth...
Now is the time!
Yeah!
H-Hey!
Open to the left and right!
Crane Wing Formation!
Alright! Let's hurry back to
the ship and leave the island!
Apis! That pendant... You don't mean...
Go! Go!
Grandpa Ryu!
Go!
It's actually a key that opens
the door to the dragons' nest?
Yoo-hoo!!
No! Don't go that way!
Yeah!
Whew, I'm starving!
Sanji! Make me some food!
Yeah.
--Yeah!
--Meat! Make meat!
I'll have sauted veggies
with lots of bean sprouts!
What?! It's coming this way!
Shoot it down, quickly!
Is this for reals?!
Where've I heard that before?
Just how many ships
does the damn navy have?!
Huh?
Man, these rocks are cool!
Listen, now!
These all used to be
Millennial Dragons?
Connect all ships by chain links
to create a complete wall
I can't reach...
Yeah, it looks that way.
Even if they are Dragonite,
there's no way to extract it like this.
--You're so little, Apis!
--So what?!
that won't allow even a
single small fry to escape!
Alright! Leave it to me!
Then the whole elixir
of immortality thing...
What a crazy plan that was!
...was nothing but a
dream within a dream.
What now?! They have us blocked off!
Huh?
It's coming!
Shoot it, quickly! Shoot it!
Huh?!
Even if we took these
coral-covered fossils back with us,
Well, it worked out!
Jump onto a ship, kick the guys off,
and cut the links!
we'd never get an elixir from them.
Exactly.
That's the only choice, obviously!
Yeah, huh?
Wow! You can do that, Usopp?!
Go after them! Go after that ship!
Meaning those Navy bastards
did all that work for nothing.
We can't move because
the sail is in our way!
Go! Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
I thought as much.
What?!
Doesn't sound too bad to me, though!
Eh?! But, are you serious?!
I think this will do.
There's no way you could
survive if you tried that!
That was fun.
Fools! As if I would ever
kick the bucket so easily!
That was fun!
It's okay, Apis. Things'll work out.
Apis! Are you okay?
I must pay you back
for what you've done!
Yep!
But make it quick, you guys!
Luffy, we can leave any time now.
But first...!
You can count on me, Nami-san!
Alright! Let's go!
Okay!
Millennial Dragons!
Set sail... for Lost Island!!
All ships, take aim!
The target is the pirate ship!
We're alive... right?
With this many, I can have
all the Dragonite I want!
Yeah, it seems that way...
But do not hit the raft behind the ship!
But which way?
Grandpa Ryu!
Hmmm, that way? Or, maybe this way?
Say, what was that about it
being a key just a minute ago?
It must not be damaged
in even the slightest!
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Are we gonna be okay
when you're so unreliable?
Move.
Here!
Well, we'll just have to go.
Eric! Look!
A flock of Millennial Dragons!
Grandpa Ryu! Hang in there!
It's not on the sea chart, either, so...
Stop the ships.
Well, in any case, we're inside now.
You're lovely, Nami-san,
even when you're decisive.
I'll pay you money!
What do you say to another deal?!
All ships, full stop!
We can make elixirs of immortality
from living Millennial Drag--!
Hey, now! What are you saying?!
Don't talk about dying!
It worked out!
You know...
But... what is this place?
Get out of my way!
Nelson Royal...
Yeah... What is it?
I had you pegged as a fatty
who can do nothing but eat,
Yeah. I know. I will save Apis!
but when you're on the sea,
it's as if you've been reborn...
And take you to the dragons' nest!
A mere commodore,
but a commodore nonetheless, huh?
So try hard to stay alive!
What is this?
Our destination is Lost Island!!
This feels great!
Grandpa Ryu!
Alright! Let's go!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
--That's Eric!
--Man, he's stubborn!
Hang in there, Grandpa Ryu!
Which direction is Lost Island?
Ah! We're done for!
Hey, now! Is this really Lost Island?!
What happened to going to
Lost Island?! Try hard to stay alive!
They're gonna take us down!
Who knows. Grandpa Ryu is sleeping, so...
--I'll handle him.
--No, I will!
Who the hell thought
of this plan anyway?!
See! Look at that! This means...
Ahh. You're so irresponsible...
--Damn those Navy guys!
--This isn't good.
Get lost!
It was you!!
Look out!
Lost Island, huh?
It's sad to leave it now.
That bastard!
He followed us all the way here?!
I don't see it on the sea chart.
The ride's about to get rough!
Hang on to something!
Luffy can't swim, right?
Ahhh! A ship has appeared
right in front of us!!
Alright! Set sail! The Grand Line,
at last! Isn't this great?!
Alright, Nami-san!
Alright! Let's fight! You too, Zoro!
Hold on! What is this?!
The whole sea is shaking!
That's the Going Merry!!
Oh, that round is gonna hit us.
I said stop already!
Quit your blabbing and do something!
What in the world's happening?!
Hey, could this place be...
Oh, no! Now there's a huge armada!
Yeah, I can't wait!
H-H-Hey, now! What's that?!
It's coming this way!
Yo, I'm on it!
Is this the legendary island?
--There it is!
--So that's the Red Line!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy, Completely Surrounded!
Commodore Nelson's Secret Strategy"
"Showdown in the Ruins!
Tense Zoro vs. Eric!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Solitary Island in the Distant Sea!
The Legendary Lost Island"
"Through the Sky They Soar!
The 1,000-Year Legend Lives Again!"
"An Angry Showdown!
Cross the Red Line!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!