Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates  who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil
and involved in an all-out war!
The Noah is turning away. It's
not gonna crash into the island!
Princess-sama saved us
by drawing the ship away!
--Princess Shirahoshi!
--Please escape!
I have to go out to the sea in order
to keep the Noah away from the bubble!
I'll give you one last chance, Shirahoshi!
If you say "Yes," I'll spare your life!
Have mercy, Decken-sama!
Marry me!
You're not my type!
Then go to hell!
We're not gonna let her marry a guy like you!
She's our only baby sister! We're
not gonna let you hurt her, Decken!
Brother Mamboshi-sama! Brother
Ryuboshi-sama! Hoe-sama!
I'm sorry that we suspected you...
Don't mention it. Take me to the deck!
Oh, Hordy Jones!
What happened to Neptune? Did you kill him?
I'm tormenting Shirahoshi with the Noah now.
Don't you think it's a good idea?
Huh, Bro?!
I have a good idea too!
What is it? Let me hear it.
If you die now...
What'll happen to this ship?
Decken!
"The Fierce Fight Begins! Luffy vs. Hordy!"
Hordy! You... squirt!
My left hand...
...touched you.
What are you doing, you bastard?!
You betrayed me first, Decken.
Honestly, I panicked a little when this
ship covered up the sky over the island.
But it was a good idea to break the bubble.
The Fish-Man Island would be washed away
but we'd still have the Fish-Man District.
If you die here and now, your Mark-Mark
power will become ineffective
and this ship will fall onto
the Fish-Man Island again...
Then it will destroy everything.
Now, more than anything, I want all of
those annoying Straw Hats to be gone.
Thousands of my men will die too
but I can just get more human
slaves, as many as I like, later.
Thousands will die, huh?
That's good. But first,
you...
...drop dead!
You fool! Don't do it!
Become a martyr for the New Fish-Man Island.
You'll die soon.
Then the ship will start falling again and
it will fall onto the Fish-Man Island.
Since I'm a kind man, I'll
make your dream come true,
the very least I can do, before you die.
I'll kill Shirahoshi for you!
He stabbed Decken! What kind
of relationship do they have?!
This is no time to think about
that. Hordy's gonna come this way!
We're gonna stop him!
Out of my way, you fools!
You stupid interlopers!
Brothers-sama!
Shirahoshi! Get away at full speed!
Now you're out of the Hard Shell
Tower - it's so easy to kill you.
It's no use!
The Merfolk may be the
fastest swimmers in the world but
I'm way faster than you right now!
Brother-sama!
Shirahoshi!
Hordy!
Gum-Gum...
...Snake Shot!
Luffy-sama! Brother Fukaboshi-sama!
--Straw Hat!
--B-Brother!
Sorry to be late. I was
caught up in strategizing.
You bastard!
CONCHCORDE PLAZA
Meanwhile, at Conchcorde Plaza
on the Fish-Man Island...
Captain Vander Decken-sama abandoned me!
I need you to become a
sacrifice upon Shirahoshi's
death, along with the island!
Why don't you fight, Sea Bonze!
Please! Do something about the Kraken!
--Beat him up, Kraken!
--You're strong!
They're both huge but he doesn't
seem like he wants to fight.
The Kraken will defeat him!
Hey, Great Monk! You must have misheard him!
What Decken said to you was "I'll
leave the plaza up to you!"
What?
That means he wasn't
gonna destroy the island!
But he said "Become a sacrifice."
He wanted you to fight hard as though
you were going to sacrifice yourself.
Do you think so?
Yes. Isn't that right, guys?
Huh? Y-Yeah... he's right!
How lucky to be trusted
by your captain that much.
--You're amazing!
--It's time for you to man up!
Oh, that's what it was!
No, it wasn't.
Now, take this
and beat the Straw Hats up with us!
The Energy Steroid!
No way. It's not gonna
work on that giant body!
It's working tremendously well!
What?!
Surume!
Captain Decken! I'm sorry
that I didn't trust you!
Yeah! He beat the hell out of the Kraken!
--What happened? Are you all right?!
--It's no good! He passed out!
Are you guys my enemies too?!
He's like a different person!
Leave it all up to me!
Where is my enemy?
Th-That guy right there, Wadatsumi!
Is that him?
All right!
Watch out, Jimbei-chan!
Fish-Man Karate!
7000 Brick...
...Roundhouse Kick!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
How could he do such a giant
creature that much damage?!
Nami-san!
Oh no! The wind blast brought Nami-san down!
Get up, you bastard!
Ouch! Who is it this time?!
You big shit!
What would happen if you
so much as make a scratch
or two on our beautiful navigator?
Unbelievable! His kick worked too!
How strong is his leg that it
can hurt a giant like him?!
Oh no!
I got messy.
That wasn't my fault!
I will fight you, Great Monk!
Pay with your life, you Jumbo Steamed Bun!
How strong can they get?!
Mil Fleurs!
Help us, Hyouzou-san!
Old man, can I get a wasabi octopus?!
No, you're not in a bar! Plus,
you shouldn't eat octopus!
Don't be mean!
It's no use! He's completely drunk!
How pathetic!
If you can prove yourself now,
it's your chance to become
an officer in one move.
I knew a little surprise
attack like this wouldn't do.
Who are you?
I'm the soon-to-be No.1 Fish-Man
swordsman - Nuru-sama!
What?
--What's wrong?
--Is it a hangover?
Hyouzou-san!
You're not too bad!
You're weak.
Can you say the same thing after this?!
So bright!
If you can't see, you can't
defend yourself from my sword!
Take this!
What?
You only use your eyes to
see. That's why you're weak.
Go train some more and come back!
That was just dumb luck!
I'm gonna be the No.1 Fish-Man
swordsman, I won't lose...
Who is No.1?
Stop!
Hyouzou-san, we're on your side!
--He looks strange.
--That's not how he gets drunk usually!
He's much stronger!
Tottering Hash!
Sh-Shields don't work!
He was writhing in agony without
any injury until a while ago!
Are you kidding? This is like what
happened when Hordy-san changed.
Hyouzou-san has become a monster, too?!
It feels great! I feel a surge of energy!
Oh, I wanna cut more people!
Let me cut you!
Run! Somebody, stop him! There's
no way to defend ourselves!
It could be anybody!
I found one!
H-Hyouzou-san got stopped!
You look tougher than the
anglerfish I just beat.
Zoro!
Sorry. I'm gonna take this guy.
This will be a nice warm-up
before we go to the New World.
It gets less powerful in water as I thought.
"Less powerful"?
Stupid lowly creature!
Don't you know where you
are?! You're in the deep sea!
A human like you has no
chance to win a fight!
On top of that,
everything will come to an end soon.
Whether it's Shirahoshi or the
Fish-Man Island or your friends!
A fool like you can't protect anything!
No.
I'll protect them all!
That's what I worked for...
...those 2 years!
The Straw Hats are battling the
officers of the New Fish-Man Pirates.
The new, stronger attacks the crew has
learned in their two years of training
continue to be revealed.
Far above them,
the Noah is getting closer by the second,
as it descends to destroy Fish-Man Island.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Massive Confused Fight! The Straw
Hats vs. The New Fish-Man Pirates!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!