Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
Luffy and his crew reached
the Fish-Man Island
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
located 10,000 meters below sea level,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates
where the New Fish-Man Pirates  who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
who are looking to destroy
the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find
themselves caught up in the
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in
the turmoil and involved in an all-out war.
turmoil and involved in an all-out war.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in
the turmoil and involved in an all-out war.
Now, Hordy's merciless plot puts the
Fish-Man Island in unprecedented danger!
Straw Hat!
Now, Hordy's merciless plot puts the
Fish-Man Island in unprecedented danger!
Straw Hat! Please!
You wanna stop the Noah, don't
you? Then you have to beat me.
Everything will come to an end soon.
We don't need the past!
Otherwise, you can't save
the Fish-Man Island!
Reset our history to zero!
My axe! Hit Hordy!
Whether it's Shirahoshi or the
Fish-Man Island or your friends!
The giant ship, Noah, has just lost its power
Wipe out those phantoms who shut
the island away from the sun!
and is starting to fall
towards the island again!
A fool like you can't protect anything!
Hordy, what's with you?!
Bring the Fish-Man Island back...
What?!
...to zero!
No.
About Hordy Jones...
You even abandoned the ones you grew
up with in the Fish-Man District!
I'll protect them all!
Brother-hoshi.
The Noah is falling!
That's what I worked for those 2 years!
Don't you realize what you are doing?!
I found out who he really is!
As long as you let me handle
it my way, don't worry.
"A Massive Confused Fight! The Straw
Hats vs. The New Fish-Man Pirates!"
Hordy is...
Our minds were made up when
we arrived at the plaza that,
...a monster who was brought
to life by our environment!
Just in time!
along with Jimbei, we wouldn't
let anyone harm the island!
The New Fish-Man Pirates are a group of
monsters created from an ancient grudge!
Or is your hatred for humans so
deep that makes you lose your mind?
Leave it all up to us, Brother-hoshi!
The Fish-Man Island...
...is in danger!
We're friends, right?
What did you go through in the past?!
"Luffy Loses the Fight?!
Hordy's Long-Awaited Revenge!"
What happened to you?
Did humans beat you?!
Answer me, Hordy!
What did humans do to you?!
Did humans kill your loved
ones or someone dear to you?!
You can't get away from me!
Protect them all? Don't make me laugh!
Hordy-sama!
Nothing.
What did you go through in the past?!
You've got such a big mouth,
haven't you, Straw Hat?
Yowahoshi!
Stay with me! I promise
I won't let you be hurt!
Answer me, Hordy!
What did humans do to you?!
Okay!
We were chosen by heaven to punish humans...
I can't believe he'd even harm Decken!
"Luffy's All-out Attack! Red Hawk Blasts!"
Shirahoshi! Get away!
...and granted powers!
Draw the Noah away from the island!
Their hatred is...
It's too late.
...not rooted in their
experience or true beliefs.
This is the Air Tank. We met you a while ago.
They have no substance!
Oh, it's you guys.
We've been listening to  what's
been going on out there.
What did he mean by "too late"?
So he's dead finally!
Oh? Huh?
They are completely "empty"!
And we see the Noah falling
towards the island.
Now, Vander Decken's
power became ineffective
Wait a minute!
I lost him.
He just beat Decken, right?
We're getting ready as planned.
and the Noah will crash
into the Fish-Man Island!
"Back to Zero! Earnest Wishes for Luffy!"
The guy in stripes.
What would happen to the Noah if
Decken dies or loses consciousness?
Enough with the difficult
stuff and just do it!
Go to hell, Straw Hats!
Where did he go?
Luffy-san, please save the island!
And all those people who stand
in the way of our vengeance!
Hey, Straw Hat. Can you hear me?
--The Fish-Man Island...
--...Will be no more!
Their hatred is not rooted in
their experience or true beliefs.
Fool! I'm here!
They have no substance! They
are completely "empty"!
You're gonna be dead before you notice!
We have to stop the ship somehow!
Empty? What does he mean by that?
Take this!
Straw Hat!
Camouflage Carpet!
Hey, you guys, you got to keep
moving! Get off of the island!
You wanna stop the Noah, don't
you? Then you have to beat me.
Huh?
Decken's power would become ineffective!
I heard a voice around here!
Listen carefully.
You can see the shadow of the
Noah up in the sky already!
Otherwise, you can't save
the Fish-Man Island!
And the Noah would fall...
About Hordy Jones...
Z-Zeo-san got...
...Stabbed!
...onto the island!
You bastard!
If the Noah crashes into the Fish-Man
Island, it will be the end of everything.
I found out who he really is!
Why did you kick me?! It hurts!
How was that, Skeleton?
Both the kingdom and the Noah's purpose
That bastard!
My weapon-destroying technique
called Body Sword Crush made...
that has been protected
for hundreds of years!
Shut up or I'll kick your fat ass again!
--Hurry up! It's gonna come within range soon!
--I'm hurrying!
Listen, my sons.
Even Captain Decken wouldn't
kick me for no reason at all!
...the tip of your sword crumble...
That ark - the Noah is not just
a relic from history-jamon.
How much longer? How much
inflation do we have so far?!
I stabbed you.
He still has too much pride!
"A Shocking Fact! The
True Identity of Hordy!"
87%!
You damn Steamed Bun bastard! How dare you...
Make it in time! Make it!
Just think that way and get defatted...
Hundreds of years ago, a promise
was made to a great man
Get defeated!
...bring Nami-san down with the wind blast!
This time, he...
...Stumbled.
This is my payback to you!
Hurry up, Yowahoshi!
Shh! Don't say that.
and that ship has been kept on the
seafloor until the appointed day comes.
You just fumbled your words.
Hey!
--This is for...
--Huh?
Before the Noah started to fall...
Hordy-sama looks even more
terrifying than before!
The ship has not served
its purpose yet-jamon.
You dumbhead!
...the wind blast that Nami-san took!
Ouch!
Now, we don't even know
how they made that ship.
Oh? Oh?! I lost him again! Where did he go?!
Humans are lowly creatures.
The Noah cannot be damaged
until the day comes!
Oh no!
Remember, Hordy.
Watch out for the wind blast, Nami-san!
Understood, Father.
They are evil.
We will go and find out why
it moved and take care of it.
A wind blast, again?! Please!
Hidden Flail...
I have to save both the kingdom
and the Noah at any cost!
Keep your guard up! Look out!
...66 Neck!
Something came out from that stick earlier!
Straw Hat, you have neither
a strategy to stop the Noah
Black Ball!
Ouch!
nor a chance to beat me!
Damn you!
--What is it this time?!
--Is she a magician?
This is it! We're doomed!
Now I'm mad!
What's the matter? If nothing is done,
No, don't call me a magician!
Since the Pirate Era began, we've kept
losing our friends day after day!
your friends will have no choice
Call me a charmer!
Just you wait and see!
but to be swallowed by the sea,
along with the Fish-Man Island!
I learned something...
Humans have kidnapped some young Mermaids
Intimidation Mega Monk!
Were you fooling yourself when you said
you'd protect them all, Straw Hat?!
...in the last 2 years,
and sold them to the Human Shoppe!
Although it's not really a
charm. It's based on science!
about the true power of
the Revive-Revive Fruit.
We're all doomed! The
Fish-Man Island will fall!
I will stop it!
I'm gonna break it to pieces
before it gets to the island!
You can't do that, Straw Hat!
Even if you could do so,
Clouds?
He was very big already!
--Damn humans!
--We have to kill them all!
Storm Cloud Rod!
as I told you, the Noah has
When people die,
Kill them! Kill them! Kill them all!
a long history and will serve
a purpose in the future!
their souls must go to the next world.
Then how can we save the island?!
But my soul,
We don't have time!
Is that necessary?
in order to keep its existence in this world,
That's all I can think of!
Damn! Humans!
Ouch!
Help me!
Decken could still be alive.
How is this? Are you surprised?
Stay away! I don't wanna
become a dried squid-ch!
radiates a strong energy almost
like other corporeal beings.
If we can wake him up, maybe we
can change the course of the ship.
They get on my nerves!
I'm a tiger blowfish Fish-Man. Scared?
--Damn that woman!
--Hey, Ikaros.
Oh, you got stronger-ch!
What if he's dead? Then what are
we gonna do? We gotta destroy it...
Not at all. Anyway, why
are you talking so fast?
That guy in the black suit was overreacting
because that woman got hurt.
Wow!
It enables me to rock a crowd
It's great! We have a hero!
of people better than anybody
else when I play music.
Because I'm gonna deflate if I don't.
I said "Wait"!
He blew up the Human Shoppe sacrificing
his life! Pay him your respects!
I can draw them into my world and
even create illusions for them.
Are you guys splitting? While you're arguing,
I think that woman may be
the Straw Hat's weak link.
The Kraken is bigger than you.
What?!
look, the Noah is falling towards the island!
Then, how's this?!
Really?
Let's not forget his death!
I'll hold her legs and you
kill her with your spear!
Blowfish!
Even when my soul leaves my
body, people can see me clearly.
--So annoying!
--I don't wanna get crushed!
I got it-much!
--Help me!
--Hey, Wadatsumi-san, no!
Wait, Noah! There are people
who I love on the island!
Well, if you don't wanna
get burned, leave me alone!
I certainly exist in this world.
Hero?
You're squashing the people on your side!
Still smaller than the Kraken.
Decken-sama! If you are alive,
please make it come after me!
What?! Then, how's this?!
What?
I can't move my feet!
Please don't harm the Fish-Man Island!
I did it!
That's enough!
That serves you right, humans!
I took down one of the Straw Hats!
You're gonna become a dried squid-ch!
Drop dead now and watch it from beyond
the grave, as the Ryugu Kingdom falls!
Your Majesty!
This is awesome!
W-W-Wait a minute!
Yeah.
Why can't I move my feet?! Somebody!
Are you all right?!
Heroes are cool-ch!
Dosun!
Fish-Man Karate!
I'm sorry that we couldn't protect you!
Shirahoshi!
Sea Drums!
Nami-san! Oh yeah!
No, you didn't.
Arlong-san sank another human pirate ship!
We are such useless vassals!
Take this! The Squid Spear!
That is okay. More importantly,
did you see the Noah?
Brother Mamboshi-sama!
What keeps me alive in this world
is neither bodily organs...
This is a crusade!
Mamboshi!
Yes.
Could I look at your panties...
Ages ago, the filth we call "humans"
envied the chosen and gifted Fish-Men
I can't believe it's moving.
It's your turn now!
...nor muscles.
No!
Damn Decken! If the Noah had crashed
into the Princess and the island,
Is he on their side?
It's my...
Fish-Man Karate!
Hordy!
Why don't you dry up?
Become a dried squid-ch!
and feared our existence.
Straw Hat!
...soul!
everything would have been destroyed-jamon!
Second Gear!
And...
Huh?
We didn't know what was going on. We tried
to order an evacuation to all citizens
Gum-Gum...
Hm? What's wrong-ch?
...they decided to persecute us.
What?!
Suck all the fluid out of
his body and dry him up-ch!
Luffy-sama!
Humans were everywhere in
the world, like maggots.
...Jet Pistol!
but I guess all the communications centers
were seized by the New Fish-Man Pirates!
Oh! I've got a lot of spunk! All right!
So they exploited their only
advantage - their number,
Hey, Squid! What's up?
What's wrong? Why? Why? Why? Why? Why? Why?
He's pretending he wasn't surprised!
and drove us down to the seafloor.
We have been trying to reach the
border guards out at sea but...
Damn! I can defend myself
with the Armament Haki
Did you get it?
Why?!
Listen, everyone! Never forget
our grudge against the humans!
Ring, ring, ring...
--Get ready to shoot the bubble now!
--Hurry up!
So, in other words, as long
as my bones don't get damaged,
but my Haki is not good enough
for these kind of attacks yet!
Humans know and fear that
their reckoning day will come!
Excuse me.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
I'm pretty dried up already.
your attack can't pierce me to the bone.
What?!
And that's when we'll make them pay!
Why aren't they picking up?
In any case, take the King somewhere safe!
I shouldn't be fighting in the water.
I don't believe you-ch!
And,
In order to beat him, I need...
It's a long story. How I
became a dried-up skeleton.
No.
this sword cane which the Longarm
Tribe sharpened for me -
I'm going to wait for the Princes.
Never forget our history.
I don't believe you-ch!
Feel the disappointment of the dead.
--No, believe me. It was over 50 years ago...
--Help me!
it's called Soul Solid!
Take over their resentment.
Hey hey, isn't there anybody
who is strong enough to fight?!
What the...
Hold a grudge against humans!
Its soulful slash will make you feel
He wants to fight on the
falling ship, doesn't he?
Tell me what is going on, guys!
Huh?
the cold air from the land of the dead!
But what he really wants is...
Why are there so many pirates?!
There is this human named Rayleigh
who I knew for a long time
...the air on its deck!
Well...
Are you all right?
and he's different!
It's the "Freezing Sword"!
He doesn't make a face
even when he sees me...
Who are you-ch?!
If I could get in there, I can
beat Hordy with a single blow!
Have a good look!
It's me!
Hordy?
The Straw Hats!
--I don't know you-ch!
--What?! You don't know this super robot?!
That's awesome, Brook!
I don't like your story, Hachi-san.
I knew he was going to do it!
The Freezing Sword - how cool is that?!
Those bubbles are susceptible
to large gashes!
It makes me sick.
Hm? You must be one of their officers, huh?
Jimbei!
That's my Soul King!
Humans are afraid.
Princess-sama?!
Then I bet you have backbone.
Oh, thank you very much.
Hordy! Decken!
Take over the resentment. Okay, Hordy?
Though I'm a squid, I'm still
a Fish-Man! I have backbone!
Damn! The air on the deck is gone!
So that is what happened...
Oh! Oh no! Dammit!
Remember, Hordy.
Oh, he has a backbone
even though he's a squid!
They are evil, lowly creatures.
I lost him again!
All right! I understand everything now!
Sympathy!
That's not what he meant.
Hey, Skeleton, get out of there already.
Hate humans.
All soldiers! Go to the plaza!
Hate them. Hate them! Hate them!!
I have to keep it up too!
Follow Jimbei and the Straw Hats!
Huh? Why?
It's so easy to render you humans helpless!
Everybody's gained skills
to go on to the New World!
Your foot! Your foot!
What about my foot?
You should realize you're
no better than us Fish-Men!
If they can handle the strong ones for
us, the rest are just average fighters.
This is terrible!
You're stepping on him!
Tiger-san, the hero who freed the
slaves, has been killed by humans!
Concerning your friends?
Not only can you not stop the
Noah but you can't even beat me!
The pirates who we mistrusted and falsely
charged are fighting for our country.
Huh? What is he?! I couldn't
move because of him?!
Don't worry!
What?!
I'll make sure you all get
drowned in the deep sea!
Drop dead, Straw Hat!
We should be ashamed of ourselves.
Special Attack!
Gum-Gum...
Um... Who are you?
So Tiger was not the chosen hero.
Fireball Cutter!
The least we can do is
offer them our support!
...Snake Shot!
Green Star!
Yes, sir!
Whoa! Ouch, ouch, ouch!
How did you like it?!
It's Neptune's army!
What?
--We can handle them!
--Kill them all!
Screw you!
Getting a head-butt to
the bottom of your foot!
Do you think I'm stupid enough
to get hit by the same attack twice?
Green Star!
It's time to show our strength!
--What?
--Huh?
Green Star!
I wonder which comes first - your friends
It may take some time for
you to feel the pain!
You bastard!
being shattered to death
along with the island
He's a human!
Who are you people?! Go away!
What?!
or your last breath! Can't wait to see!
He doesn't wanna admit
that  he got stepped on!
Looks like you're a burden to the Straw Hats!
I heard you gave your blood to humans.
Sorry that I stepped on your face!
Oh no! He's gonna break my bubble again!
Go slaves!
Don't say that!
So what?! There was a
human who was dying so...
You didn't hit me at all!
Fight for us if you don't wanna die!
You dullard!
This technique allows me to give you a
head-butt to the bottom of your foot!
It's called Super Sole Head-Butt!
Dad!
Luffy-sama!
Shirahoshi!
He named it!
Brother Fukaboshi-sama!
Don't rush around, mole shark.
Listen to me very carefully.
Advance, "Slave Tank"!
I'm a cookie-cutter shark!
Where did you go, Coral
Head?! I'll bite you good!
I want you to handle Straw Hat.
I just...
Go that way!
...finished setting a trap!
Handle Luffy-sama?
I'm going to stop Hordy at any cost!
Even the members of the royal
family are crazy in this country.
No one can beat me in the
ground. I can move freely!
Oops!
You are good for nothing! Just drag him!
You have to trust me no matter what
happens and stay close to the Noah!
She wants to forgive humans.
Daruma-san!
Luffy-sama!
Don't make too many tunnels in the ground!
Screw that!
No matter what happens! Understood?
How weak!
Hordy-sama is coming!
Somebody, take his place!
We're all gonna fall into them!
Did you hear about Jimbei-san
joining the Seven Warlords?
Yes.
You wouldn't let anyone harm the island?
How terrible.
Give it your best shot!
Only the Arlong Pirates keep
the purity of the Fish-Men.
That is like...
Nico Robin.
Yes!
Chopper! Did you finish it?
Second Gear!
Do you think you can free those human slaves?
Gum-Gum...
Come out this way!
There's no way I can miss now!
Even with my eyes closed!
Are you sure it's wise?
...Jet...
I'm sure they're holding a grudge
against the Fish-Man Island.
What a fool! That guy is off his guard-dogon!
We need a hero.
If those human pirates come against
me, I will just beat them up.
Oh no!
...Bazooka!
I'm gonna beat him up!
This is it!
Hey, Chopper? Can't he hear me?
But they can hardly be
called "humans" now anyway.
This country...
Get squashed and go to hell-zugan!
I can't stand watching Hordy and the
others copying the Celestial Dragons.
Wh-What happened?
...needs a hero.
Luffy-sama.
I'm sorry.
Usopp! Get down!
Yowahoshi!
Brother Fukaboshi-sama asked me to do this.
It's not working!
Otohime-sama has been shot!
All right! I'll do it!
Horn Cannon Elf!
Luffy-sama!
Thanks.
Brother-hoshi!
You see? That's what humans do!
Hordy! What's wrong with you?!
Nice, Chopper! Did you
connect all the tunnels?
It's no use, Straw Hat.
They show no mercy even to someone like
Hey! You guys are too slow!
Yes, it's nice and ready!
There are so many lives on
that island! How could you?
All right! Here we go!
We were granted power from heaven!
the Queen who was so friendly to them!
What's wrong with you?!
If the royal family won't
seek revenge out of pride,
Special Attack - Green Star!
You three Princes are the
strongest in the Ryugu Kingdom?!
Dammit! Son of a bitch!
we'll never trust this country again!
Give it up! You can't stop the Noah now!
After all, you are sons
of that stupid Otohime.
We don't need such a spineless country!
And you will lose everything!
She had no pride in being a
Fish-Man and died a dog's death
Skull Bombgrass!
The leader of those disgraceful
ones has been punished by heaven!
The cuffs came off!
No, I'm gonna finish the
whole thing with this one!
trying to become friendly with humans.
Hey, what are you doing?!
Those villains who want to
forgive humans must die-dosun!
Who uncuffed the slaves?!
You can't finish anything!
You three are worthless Princes who
can't even save your own country!
Drop dead!
How did you like that?!
You're a member of the
Straw Hats, aren't you?
We fought a ground digger
once in Alabasta already!
Hey, turn around already!
Second Gear - Armament!
Brother-hoshi!
Brother Fukaboshi-sama!
What's wrong, you slaves!
Our experience gave us the upper hand!
Even your power is fake,
The cuffs...
Yeah!
--Did you do it?
--Why did you save us?
I admit that I couldn't fight back
because I'm not strong enough.
Damn you coral monster!
I'll never...
I can't turn down a request
from a handsome man.
...let anyone die again!
Is this all your doing?
But there is still hope!
I'll show you my extraordinary power!
You can thank Boss Jimbei for that.
Merman Combat!
Jimbei asked you to?
Ultramarine!
Speaking of power, I have
one up my sleeve, too.
It's time for our revenge!
You can't just do that!
Gum-Gum...
I'm gonna bite your nose off!
Heaven chose us finally and granted us power.
Trawl Net!
Try it if you like!
I'm gonna bite your arm off!
Back me up, Chopper!
Don't you get it?!
--Don't tell me it's...
--That legendary drug-ch?!
I got you!
You can't beat me with
those crappy attacks now!
...Red Hawk!
Hey, back me up!
I can't believe you got it-dosun!
Why, Hordy?!
Can you make a lot of it, Zeo?
Oh?
What is it that you want
badly enough to sacrifice
Cuerpo Fleurs!
Chopper?
I'll try.
How did you get behind me?!
The people of the Fish-Man District who are
Now, it's my turn!
so many innocent fellowmen's lives?!
disappointed with the
country will come together!
This is a crusade! Get ready!
How can you do such a horrible thing?!
Wh-What the...
Prepare to kill as many humans
as you can until your own death!
It won't take long. Relax.
Hordy! Ultra...
Shark Slicer!
We were chosen...
Let go of me! Who are you?!
...Marine!
Go to hell!
...to inherit the duty of vengeance!
You! How are there two of you?!
The reckoning day will come!
Double Clutch!
Brother Fukaboshi-sama!
Evil lowly creatures - humans!
--Hammond-san!
--That bitch!
We're devoting our life to this vengeance!
--Thank you, Sis!
--You bastards really treated us like shit!
Damn you! You made me angry!
You guys can't beat us on earth!
I won't forgive you even if you say sorry!
The human slaves are...
I'm gonna beat you up!
...rising in revolt!
Luffy-sama!
Great! That's how a swordsman should be!
Straw Hat!
You're strong!
It was too late!
I don't know when but we lost
contact with the Fish-Man District
Ring, ring, ring... Ring,
ring, ring... Clank!
and they've become something like an
isolated, dark side of the Fish-Man Island!
He...
This is one of the border guards.
Is this the Minister of the Left?
He did it!
We pretended not to see the twisted hatred
building up in that lawless ditch...
Yes, I is. I have been trying to
reach you - why didn't you pick up?
Forgive me! But I have no
time to go into detail now!
Straw Hat Luffy-san defeated...
How pathetic, you piss-poor Prince!
...in the deep water!
...Hordy, the captain of
the New Fish-Man Pirates,
Please warn the whole kingdom!
--Hey you! Where are you going?!
--Let me go! The Noah is...
This power is a gift from heaven!
The giant ship, Noah, has just lost its power
No way!
finally!!
I filled my mother's shoes
and collected signatures
Now, it's your turn, you two.
and is starting to fall
towards the island again!
but I was only dealing
with superficial matters.
It's not over yet!
Damn!
Yowahoshi, take me to the Noah!
But I thought I was making a progress!
Okay!
What?!
The Noah is falling again?
I know it's hard but...
--Help me...
--Are you okay? I'll treat you right away!
At your full speed!
...you can't plant your anger and resentment
Where are you now?
Okay!
You can't beat me with that fake power!
At the Air Tank control tower.
--Honey, stay with me!
--Daddy!
What?! No way! Captain Hordy lost?!
toward humans in children's minds!
That's good. Then, you need to
warn everybody about the crisis.
It was too late!
Drop dead already!
Treat him now!
What's gonna happen to the Noah?!
People like them are the ones
that my mother feared the most!
Damn Hordy! He can't do
this to unarmed citizens!
None of the communication centers
on the island are working.
Hordy, what's with you?!
I know you can reach the
state-operated Transponder Snails
You petitioned for vengeance against
the humans to Fish-Men, but now
This is it! For the island and all of us!
Brother-sama!
Is the Princess okay?
all over the country from there!
We should have fought within ourselves first!
Run!
Hurry up!
I don't know...
you're trying to take those fellow
Fish-Men's lives along with the island!
Yes, sir!
But I'm sure she's still fighting for us!
We should have fought our
own feelings toward humans!
Madam Sharley!
You even abandoned the ones you grew
up with in the Fish-Man District!
To all citizens of the kingdom--
from the Air Tank above the island.
What's gonna happen to the island?!
Is it really gonna fall?!
Don't you realize what you are doing?!
Mother was...
An emergency evacuation
order has been issued!
That Straw Hat pirate guy will
save the island, won't he?
Mother was killed by the grudge
growing on the Fish-Man Island!
Zeo-san, please! You know this island is...
The giant ship - Noah is
falling onto the island again!
Won't he, Madam Sharley?!
Please leave the island immediately!
Don't be fooled!
Captain Hordy was chosen by heaven!
Or is your hatred for humans so
deep that makes you lose your mind?
--Let's pray.
--What?
All we can do now is pray for the
safety of the Princess and the others.
Some loser human could never beat him!
What happened to you?
B-But if the Noah destroys the island,
we're getting nothing anyway!
Did humans beat you?!
It was too late! People like them are...
Pray that they will save the Fish-Man Island!
Did humans kill your loved
ones or someone dear to you?!
Death is another way to get revenge.
The giant ship - Noah is
falling onto the island again!
...the ones that my mother feared the most!
Hate humans even in death!
We should have fought within ourselves first!
Please leave the island immediately!
What did you go through in the past?!
Tragedies will become our flesh and blood.
What?!
CORAL HILL
We should have fought our
own feelings toward humans!
And our grudge will never go away.
Answer me, Hordy!
Look!
What did humans do to you?!
It's the shadow of the Noah!
Somebody will take it over
and get our revenge for us!
WATERWHEEL TOWN
Decken did it?
Mother was...
That's what I heard.
Mother was killed by the grudge
growing on the Fish-Man Island!
That damn stalker! I can't
believe he threw it!
There he is.
Captain Hordy and all
you officers are insane!
Maybe she knew it!
The bubble's gonna break!
FISHVERLY HILLS
The island will be destroyed!
Hurry up! Forget about your suitcase!
So it doesn't matter who did this...
Humans made us insane!
B-But...
Get out to the sea!
Don't get angry on my behalf.
Stop running!
Go further! More!
Everybody, escape from the island!
CORAL APARTMENT
Don't let resentment or hatred get
the better of you for my sake.
Direct all of your anger toward humans-bogon!
I heard Princess Shirahoshi was drawing
the ship away from the island.
She's desperate!
Stay away from the island!
Humans are responsible for every single
disaster that Fish-Men meet-zugan!
But a part of me held that resentment
Yeah, we can't just run and
leave her alone like that!
Noah!
Shirahoshi!
But the Noah is falling onto the island!
If the Noah falls,  everything
will be destroyed!
and hated humans for killing my mother!
Well...
You wanna just stay here and have
Princess-sama's effort wasted?!
Are humans that terrible?
--Oh no! She couldn't hear us!
--Don't go up!
Prince...
--We've got to leave the island!
--To the sea!
Dead people take their regret to the grave.
That's ridiculous!
Turn to the side! You have
to change your course!
Brother Fukaboshi-sama!
I mean, when you look at history,
So a grudge is an illusion that the living
create and they alone cultivate it!
Hurry up, everyone!
No! That thing is gonna come back?!
humans did horrible things to Fish-Men...
They noticed!
Stop!
Are we gonna be alright, Luffy?!
Because I hated humans - even
a bit, I overlooked the
Shirahoshi!
Madam Sharley!
What happened to Princess Shirahoshi?
Shark Slicer!
See it with your own eyes!
resentment in the Fish-Man District
Decken, again?! That crazy pirate!
and when I finally noticed, it had
become too powerful and beyond control!
We have to run, too! It's too dangerous!
In the plaza and up in the sky,
Brother!
Ryuboshi!
That bastard!
Don't mess with my plan!
humans are fighting against the
pirates from the Fish-Man District!
Yowahoshi! Brother-hoshi
is in trouble! Let's go!
Leave Hordy and the others up to us.
If nothing is done, the
Fish-Man Island will...
Brother! Stay with me!
What are you doing?! Hey! Yowahoshi!
All you spectators leave here
and get off of the island!
Decken's power must have
become ineffective by now.
...destroy itself through its
own hatred toward humans!
That's why I stabbed him.
Is he a human, too?
Where are you going, Yowahoshi?!
What are you doing? Hurry up!
I see!
There are some strange ones but...
No!
If she just keeps going up, the
ship could fall onto the island!
...you have to see it with your own eyes!
You have to trust me no matter what
happens and stay close to the Noah!
Be careful!
Wh-What?
Unlike the bubble protecting the
island, this one can overshoot the ship!
If you don't, you have no
right to say something!
Especially women and children. Go now!
Then, Yowahoshi's effort to draw
the ship away means nothing!
It has to surround the
Noah! It can't go too far!
No matter what happens! Understood?
No!
The Straw Hats are human pirates but
they're fighting for the island!
Brother-hoshi, let's catch up with Yowahoshi!
No matter what happens,
Straw Hat! Please!
Yowahoshi...
Alright!
you have to look at things
with an impartial eye.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Shirahoshi!
We can't just run out on them!
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Yowahoshi!
Straw Hat Luffy-san, this is the
Air Tank. We met you a while ago.
We don't need the past!
Reset our history to zero!
He's right! We were the ones
who asked them for help!
Those of you who won't fight
to the death will get
You can't go any further!
Wipe out those phantoms who shut
the island away from the sun!
Oh, it's you guys.
I can't do anything but I
want to share their fate!
killed by me in order to leave
your hatred toward humans behind!
AIR TANK
The Fish-Man Island will be destroyed
along with all the islanders!
We've been listening to what's
been going on out there.
--Me too!
--Me too, Minister of the Right!
And we see the Noah falling
towards the island.
CONTROL ROOM
And Straw Hat,
Be quiet!
I'll make sure that all
of your friends are dead!
We're getting ready as planned.
Okay, now!
Listen, here is your duty!
You can't do that to your own people!
That's what Brother-hoshi was talking about.
You have to make sure to tell all
the other spectators what I said!
Are you all right?
You wanna go to the deck?
Oh, that was close! Thank you, Skeleton Mask!
Shirahoshi!
Hordy!
Turn to the side!
--Go after him!
--No, wait, Straw Hat!
Understood?
It's you again.
Shirahoshi!
Go!
I'm sure everyone has their
own reasoning and ideas.
Why?!
Bring the Fish-Man Island back...
You've never died before so don't
talk like you know all about it!
If you want to stay here, suit yourself!
I'm sure you know it by now.
...to zero!
Hordy has an advantage in the
water since he is a Fish-Man.
Get killed and leave hatred
behind? How ridiculous!
Nothing is left behind when you die!
Bring it on, outlaws!
--If nothing is done...
--What should we do?
All you can leave behind is your bones!
Shut up, Fukaboshi!
I have an idea!
The Fish-Men's grudge will last forever!
Very persuasive!
Shirahoshi!
Thank you!
Hey, where are you going?! Brother-hoshi!
Yowahoshi!
I don't like people who
devalue the lives of others!
Straw Hat Luffy-san.
Stupid Mermaid!
THE MAIN ENTRANCE OF THE FISH-MAN ISLAND
Brother-hoshi.
That little shit!
This is the Air Tank. We met you a while ago.
I can't even stand their smell!
Prince Fukaboshi?
--She heard you!
--She turned to the side!
As long as you let me handle
it my way, don't worry.
What brought you here, Prince?
Even though I don't have a nose!
Listen, we might need a
large amount of air soon.
How annoying!
H-Hey! Those guys fighting against
Hordy's crew at the plaza are...
Straw Hat? What are they broadcasting?
You can't do that!
Make preparations!
We've been listening to  what's
been going on out there.
Wait!
It's you guys who are devaluing lives.
Yes, sir!
--Yes, it's the Straw Hats!
--And Boss Jimbei!
It's fine. There is some air on the deck.
And we see the Noah falling
towards the island.
It's so impressive that none
of you is trying to escape
What?!
Then I can beat him up there.
Let go of me!
--Luffy-chan's voice!
--Oh yeah!
Luffy-sama! What should I do about the Noah?
I won't let you go after her!
Aside from Decken,
but you humans will die once
the Noah hits the island!
do you think Hordy would leave the
bubble so you can fight there?
Damn you!
What are they doing?!
Although I can't tell if
you're a human or not!
They are broadcasting their conversation
across the country by mistake!
I want you to take this Baby
Transponder Snail just in case.
Noah! Come this way!
Our captain - Luffy will become
the King of the Pirates someday.
Hey, hello? How can we get air from you?
We need to be well-prepared. Let's go!
I can't hold on...
If we make a bubble and shoot
all the air from the Air Tank,
Noah! Come after me!
And he said it clearly.
Yes! It's in the bubble!
That he wouldn't let anyone
harm the island and
Luffy-sama! What should I do about the Noah?
maybe we can surround the Noah.
--Let's go!
--Yeah!
we can leave it all up to him!
Shirahoshi! Straw Hat!
Brother Fukaboshi-sama told me
to stay close to the Noah along
Damn you, Decken! Drop dead already!
Our minds were made up when
we arrived at the plaza that,
I believe in him so there
is nothing to worry about.
I'm afraid you'll have to take it from there!
with Luffy-sama, no matter what happens!
along with Jimbei, we wouldn't
let anyone harm the island!
So that's what Brother-hoshi...
Now, I'll do my part.
Dammit.
Enough with the difficult
stuff and just do it!
Hordy that bastard, I won't forgive him!
Leave it all up to us, Brother-hoshi!
H-Hey, hello?  How can we get air from you?
I won't let you disappear
in front of my eyes again!
It's Luffy! I'm glad to hear him!
He sounds all right!
We can shoot all the air from the Air Tank.
Although I don't have eyes!
Well, I wasn't worrying
much since it's Luffy!
What is the Air Tank?
We're friends, right?
It's an air conditioning facility that's
providing air to the Fish-Man Island.
What are they talking about? I
heard Princess-sama's voice too!
Noah! I'm right here!
How's this? Surprised?
If we make a bubble and shoot it,
maybe we can surround the Noah.
--Straw Hat is the serial kidnapper, isn't he?
--He's a human.
The ship's starting to go sideways!
Yeah, that's enough. Oh, I'm so surprised!
But the bubbles neutralize ascending forces
Good! Keep going, Yowahoshi!
Luffy-san, please save the island!
Shirahoshi!
so it's not going to make the Noah float.
Oh yeah?
Keep going!
Why is the border guard
counting on the human pirate?
Now, shall we finish this up, Jimbei?
That means we can't stop it from falling.
On top of that, we have to use all the air
I touched Hordy with my left hand.
--Is the human trying...
--...To handle the Noah?
Yes, let's do it.
we have in order to engulf that giant ship.
You're my target! Don't forget it!
In other words, there is only one chance.
Hey, wait! I've lost my swords.
I cannot believe we suspected
a human like him!
If we don't shoot it at the exact moment
I'll drive you into the ground physically
and mentally, until you die!
that the Noah comes right beside us,
Hey, Straw Hat.
How can I fight now?
Hey, what's wrong? Don't stop!
there will be no second chance.
Can you hear me?
So basically, it's a hit-or-miss situation.
Don't ask me.
Prince Fukaboshi!
Noah!
About Hordy Jones...
Shirahoshi! Keep going - a little bit more!
We have to run! Hey!
Y-Yes. And I'm afraid you'll
have to take it from there!
--I'm gonna stay on the island!
--What?!
There is no point if it
doesn't fall onto the island!
I found out who he really is!
Me too!
I'll hunt you down... to the ends of hell!
Again, I can't emphasize enough that...
--Me too!
--I'm not gonna run either!
Enough with the difficult
stuff and just do it!
I won't let you go!
Me too!
I can handle anything
as long as there is air!
All right. We'll do our best!
How annoying!
I'm gonna end this fight by
using a daring technique!
--Luffy-sama! There is air on the Noah now!
--Yeah!
Hordy!
Luffy-san, please save the island!
One, two...
Straw Hat! Shirahoshi!
You can't get away from me!
On the third step, you will get
shot by me and that'll be it!
Brother-hoshi, so who is Hordy?!
What can they accomplish by
swimming alongside the Noah?
Hordy-sama!
They are only a human and a Mermaid Princess!
Yowahoshi! Stay with me! I
promise I won't let you be hurt!
Don't talk nonsense!
A little more to go, Yowahoshi!
Shark Slicer!
Okay!
Stop dreaming your stupid dream!
Decken!
I will... kill you!
Straw Hat!
You weakling! Are you crying sour grapes?!
Screw this!
Hordy is...
I'll pass through by force!
Oh boy, I'm losing my edge.
Armament Hardening!
…a monster who was brought
to life by our environment!
You can't!
I used to bluff better in the past.
My axe! Hit Hordy!
Straw Hat!
Our environment?
What does he mean?
But now, I can actually do these things.
Shark Slicer!
Luffy-sama!
The New Fish-Man Pirates are a group of
I will protect!
monsters created from an ancient grudge!
Take this! The Wings of Ikaros!
Wings?
What the hell is that monster?!
Was it here before?!
The grudge was born from their ancestors
That's not tsubasa (wings).
Oh, that's...
in the shadow of the Fish-Man Island.
That's tsuba (spit)!
And they fear that the
grudge will be forgotten
Squid!
Chopper!
and their anger against the
humans will be dispelled.
Th-That little guy got bigger suddenly!
Ink?
That's why they are so impatient.
Hey! Whoa, whoa!
It's too bad for you-ch!
And they want humans to be evil
That was my alter ego made from squid ink!
so they can justify themselves
for their crusade!
He's putting up quite a fight!
Don't underestimate us officers of...
They just want to see bloodshed
Franky Fireball!
You didn't have to go out of control!
Oh, I don't wanna become a dried squid-ch!
and they don't even want
peace for the Fish-Men!
Hey, Human! Give it up, Human!
Yes! General Franky's new attack!
It makes me sick to my stomach
just looking at you people!
He shot a fireball from his stomach!
Huh?
Even if it shortens my life and even
if it comes at the ultimate price,
I'm okay, Usopp.
You breathed it?!
How could you drop your guard-gaban?!
What did you go through in the past?!
Weight Boost!
I will execute my revenge on you humans!
T-shot!
Answer me, Hordy!
Heavy Gong!
What did humans do to you?!
That bastard!
He stopped my hammer with his bare hand?!
Nothing.
Ow... Maybe this transformation is not
suited for a fight against a hammer!
What's wrong?
Did you just say "Nothing"?!
Don't miss it! You don't
have a second chance!
L-Look at that!
Hey, Chopper!
That was the form that gave you the most
If you miss it, the
Fish-Man Island will be...
H-Hordy is...
human-like look but now
you look like a monster!
We were chosen by heaven to punish humans...
I don't care now.
I wanted to look like a human
because I wanted friends.
Hey, Straw Hat. Can you hear me?
Now I wanna become a monster
who is helpful to Luffy!
I can't believe it!
It's Brother Fukaboshi-sama!
...and granted powers!
Brother-hoshi, are you okay?!
I see.
Smiles make me wanna slice!
The Noah is falling!
Luffy-sama!
I see!
Let's go!
Barely alive. Anyway, listen carefully.
Now I see everything!
There is air!
Bring the strongest swordsman
on the Fish-Man Island!
About Hordy Jones...
Just in time!
Their hatred is...
The Fish-Man Island...
You're not even able to kill my boredom.
I found out who he really is!
...not rooted in their
experience or true beliefs.
...is in danger!
Straw Hat!
No!
I win!
It's all over now!
They have no substance!
Weren't you listening?
They are completely "empty"!
I won't let anyone harm the Fish-Man Island!
It's finally time...
Hordy has become consumed by
his deep hatred of humans.
The Noah begins to fall again,
As the Noah once again draws near,
The Straw Hat crew finally
demonstrates its true power...
...for the climax of the Straw
Hats' battle in Conchcorde Plaza.
Fish-Man Island is in chaos
as the citizens evacuate.
and Luffy tries to stop it
to save Fish-Man Island,
His dangerous emotions...
...and attempts to overpower
the New Fish-Man Pirates.
And on the Noah, Hordy, transformed
into a living weapon...
...are directly fueling his assault on Luffy.
but underwater, he's at a
disadvantage as he battles Hordy,
The Straw Hats continue to
believe in Luffy and fight on.
The only thing that can help Luffy in his
desperate struggle on the airless Noah...
...mercilessly attacks Luffy.
Neptune's army finally
joins the battle, as well.
and can't get the upper hand.
Meanwhile, Hordy, having derived
immeasurable power from the Energy Steroids...
Furthermore, the last air
on the Noah's deck is lost,
In order to fulfill his
promise to Fukaboshi...
The battle at the Conchcorde
Plaza is unfolding rapidly,
...is air from the Air Tank.
...and the severely wounded Luffy...
...Luffy puts everything he's got into
his fists in order to crush Hordy!
making Luffy's demise eminent!
All hope is placed...
as a new truth further
shakes up the citizens!
...in a single last-ditch shot!
...grapple in a final battle!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy's All-out Attack! Red Hawk Blasts!"
"Luffy Loses the Fight?!
Hordy's Long-Awaited Revenge!"
"Coming to an End! The Final
Decisive Battle against Hordy!"
"A Shocking Fact! The
True Identity of Hordy!"
"Back to Zero! Earnest Wishes for Luffy!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!