Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates  who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in
the turmoil and involved in an all-out war.
Straw Hat!
You wanna stop the Noah, don't
you? Then you have to beat me.
Otherwise, you can't save
the Fish-Man Island!
Hordy, what's with you?!
You even abandoned the ones you grew
up with in the Fish-Man District!
Don't you realize what you are doing?!
Or is your hatred for humans so
deep that makes you lose your mind?
What happened to you?
Did humans beat you?!
Did humans kill your loved
ones or someone dear to you?!
What did you go through in the past?!
Answer me, Hordy!
What did humans do to you?!
This is the Air Tank. We met you a while ago.
Oh, it's you guys.
We've been listening to  what's
been going on out there.
And we see the Noah falling
towards the island.
We're getting ready as planned.
Enough with the difficult
stuff and just do it!
Luffy-san, please save the island!
Hey, Straw Hat. Can you hear me?
Listen carefully.
About Hordy Jones...
I found out who he really is!
That bastard!
"A Shocking Fact! The
True Identity of Hordy!"
Before the Noah started to fall...
Ouch!
Damn you!
Now I'm mad!
Just you wait and see!
Intimidation Mega Monk!
He was very big already!
Is that necessary?
How is this? Are you surprised?
I'm a tiger blowfish Fish-Man. Scared?
Not at all. Anyway, why
are you talking so fast?
Because I'm gonna deflate if I don't.
The Kraken is bigger than you.
What?!
Then, how's this?!
Blowfish!
--So annoying!
--I don't wanna get crushed!
--Help me!
--Hey, Wadatsumi-san, no!
You're squashing the people on your side!
Still smaller than the Kraken.
What?! Then, how's this?!
That's enough!
Your Majesty!
Are you all right?!
I'm sorry that we couldn't protect you!
We are such useless vassals!
That is okay. More importantly,
did you see the Noah?
Yes.
I can't believe it's moving.
Damn Decken! If the Noah had crashed
into the Princess and the island,
everything would have been destroyed-jamon!
We didn't know what was going on. We tried
to order an evacuation to all citizens
but I guess all the communications centers
were seized by the New Fish-Man Pirates!
We have been trying to reach the
border guards out at sea but...
Ring, ring, ring...
--Get ready to shoot the bubble now!
--Hurry up!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Why aren't they picking up?
In any case, take the King somewhere safe!
No.
I'm going to wait for the Princes.
What the...
Tell me what is going on, guys!
Why are there so many pirates?!
Well...
The Straw Hats!
Jimbei!
Princess-sama?!
Hordy! Decken!
So that is what happened...
All right! I understand everything now!
All soldiers! Go to the plaza!
Follow Jimbei and the Straw Hats!
If they can handle the strong ones for
us, the rest are just average fighters.
The pirates who we mistrusted and falsely
charged are fighting for our country.
We should be ashamed of ourselves.
The least we can do is
offer them our support!
Yes, sir!
It's Neptune's army!
--We can handle them!
--Kill them all!
It's time to show our strength!
He's a human!
Go slaves!
Fight for us if you don't wanna die!
Advance, "Slave Tank"!
Go that way!
Oops!
You are good for nothing! Just drag him!
How weak!
Somebody, take his place!
How terrible.
That is like...
Nico Robin.
Do you think you can free those human slaves?
Are you sure it's wise?
I'm sure they're holding a grudge
against the Fish-Man Island.
If those human pirates come against
me, I will just beat them up.
But they can hardly be
called "humans" now anyway.
I can't stand watching Hordy and the
others copying the Celestial Dragons.
All right! I'll do it!
Thanks.
Hey! You guys are too slow!
Dammit! Son of a bitch!
The cuffs came off!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Who uncuffed the slaves?!
You're a member of the
Straw Hats, aren't you?
Hey, turn around already!
What's wrong, you slaves!
The cuffs...
--Did you do it?
--Why did you save us?
I can't turn down a request
from a handsome man.
You can thank Boss Jimbei for that.
Jimbei asked you to?
You can't just do that!
Trawl Net!
I got you!
Cuerpo Fleurs!
How did you get behind me?!
Wh-What the...
It won't take long. Relax.
Let go of me! Who are you?!
You! How are there two of you?!
Double Clutch!
--Hammond-san!
--That bitch!
--Thank you, Sis!
--You bastards really treated us like shit!
You guys can't beat us on earth!
The human slaves are...
...rising in revolt!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring,
ring, ring... Clank!
This is one of the border guards.
Is this the Minister of the Left?
Yes, I is. I have been trying to
reach you - why didn't you pick up?
Forgive me! But I have no
time to go into detail now!
Please warn the whole kingdom!
The giant ship, Noah, has just lost its power
and is starting to fall
towards the island again!
What?!
The Noah is falling again?
Where are you now?
At the Air Tank control tower.
That's good. Then, you need to
warn everybody about the crisis.
None of the communication centers
on the island are working.
I know you can reach the
state-operated Transponder Snails
all over the country from there!
Hurry up!
Yes, sir!
To all citizens of the kingdom--
from the Air Tank above the island.
An emergency evacuation
order has been issued!
The giant ship - Noah is
falling onto the island again!
Please leave the island immediately!
The giant ship - Noah is
falling onto the island again!
Please leave the island immediately!
What?!
CORAL HILL
Look!
It's the shadow of the Noah!
WATERWHEEL TOWN
Decken did it?
That's what I heard.
That damn stalker! I can't
believe he threw it!
The bubble's gonna break!
FISHVERLY HILLS
The island will be destroyed!
Hurry up! Forget about your suitcase!
B-But...
Get out to the sea!
Everybody, escape from the island!
CORAL APARTMENT
I heard Princess Shirahoshi was drawing
the ship away from the island.
Yeah, we can't just run and
leave her alone like that!
But the Noah is falling onto the island!
Well...
You wanna just stay here and have
Princess-sama's effort wasted?!
--We've got to leave the island!
--To the sea!
Hurry up, everyone!
No! That thing is gonna come back?!
Are we gonna be alright, Luffy?!
What happened to Princess Shirahoshi?
Decken, again?! That crazy pirate!
We have to run, too! It's too dangerous!
Leave Hordy and the others up to us.
All you spectators leave here
and get off of the island!
What are you doing? Hurry up!
No!
Wh-What?
Especially women and children. Go now!
No!
The Straw Hats are human pirates but
they're fighting for the island!
We can't just run out on them!
He's right! We were the ones
who asked them for help!
I can't do anything but I
want to share their fate!
--Me too!
--Me too, Minister of the Right!
Be quiet!
Listen, here is your duty!
You have to make sure to tell all
the other spectators what I said!
Understood?
I'm sure everyone has their
own reasoning and ideas.
If you want to stay here, suit yourself!
Bring it on, outlaws!
Straw Hat Luffy-san.
This is the Air Tank. We met you a while ago.
Straw Hat? What are they broadcasting?
We've been listening to  what's
been going on out there.
And we see the Noah falling
towards the island.
Luffy-sama! What should I do about the Noah?
What are they doing?!
They are broadcasting their conversation
across the country by mistake!
Hey, hello? How can we get air from you?
If we make a bubble and shoot
all the air from the Air Tank,
maybe we can surround the Noah.
Shirahoshi! Straw Hat!
I'm afraid you'll have to take it from there!
Enough with the difficult
stuff and just do it!
It's Luffy! I'm glad to hear him!
He sounds all right!
Well, I wasn't worrying
much since it's Luffy!
What are they talking about? I
heard Princess-sama's voice too!
--Straw Hat is the serial kidnapper, isn't he?
--He's a human.
Luffy-san, please save the island!
Why is the border guard
counting on the human pirate?
--Is the human trying...
--...To handle the Noah?
Hey, Straw Hat.
Can you hear me?
Prince Fukaboshi!
About Hordy Jones...
I found out who he really is!
Brother-hoshi, so who is Hordy?!
Hordy is...
…a monster who was brought
to life by our environment!
Our environment?
What does he mean?
The New Fish-Man Pirates are a group of
monsters created from an ancient grudge!
The grudge was born from their ancestors
in the shadow of the Fish-Man Island.
And they fear that the
grudge will be forgotten
and their anger against the
humans will be dispelled.
That's why they are so impatient.
And they want humans to be evil
so they can justify themselves
for their crusade!
They just want to see bloodshed
and they don't even want
peace for the Fish-Men!
What did you go through in the past?!
Answer me, Hordy!
What did humans do to you?!
Nothing.
Did you just say "Nothing"?!
We were chosen by heaven to punish humans...
...and granted powers!
I see!
Now I see everything!
Their hatred is...
...not rooted in their
experience or true beliefs.
They have no substance!
They are completely "empty"!
Hordy has become consumed by
his deep hatred of humans.
His dangerous emotions...
...are directly fueling his assault on Luffy.
The only thing that can help Luffy in his
desperate struggle on the airless Noah...
...is air from the Air Tank.
All hope is placed...
...in a single last-ditch shot!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Back to Zero! Earnest Wishes for Luffy!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!