Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
where they faced the New Fish-Man Pirates
who were looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom
and his friends venture into that sea.
and instigated an all-out war.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
The Sea Kings stopped the Noah from
falling onto the Fish-Man Island.
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
Please help me!
where the New Fish-Man Pirates  who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
I cannot stop Luffy-sama's bleeding!
where they instigated an all-out war
against the New Fish-Man Pirates,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates
where the New Fish-Man Pirates  who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
who are looking to destroy
the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken,
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
who were holding a grudge against humans
and looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom.
Take my blood.
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
who is after Shirahoshi, are
engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil and...
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in
the turmoil and involved in an all-out war.
It's F.
Luffy finally defeated Hordy, the captain of
the New Fish-Man Pirates, in a fierce fight
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in
the turmoil and involved in an all-out war.
You can have as much as you need.
The Noah is already...
Hey, Jimbei.
Now, Hordy's merciless plot puts the
Fish-Man Island in unprecedented danger!
and thwarted his plot.
...stopped!
Sea Kings? Why?
2 years ago at a Sky Island,
I read a Poneglyph indicating where
one of the ancient weapons is.
Luffy-sama! The wound is opening up again!
What's wrong?
Weren't you listening to what I said?
L-Look at that!
Join...
You are bleeding a lot!
The Mermaid Princess who lived
around the same time as Joy Boy...
I will save the Fish-Man
Island and Shirahoshi...
...my crew!
Well... Well... That's good...
I can't believe it!
"The Secret Revealed! The Truth
about the Ancient Weapon!"
...was known by a specific name, wasn't she?
Luffy-sama...
...and keep my promise to a friend.
...as long as the ship is stopped.
The ancient weapon...
Straw Hat...
There is air!
I'm glad
...Poseidon!
I'll protect...
"The Straw Hats Stunned! The
New Fleet Admiral of the Navy!"
The royal family came to a decision!
everybody's...
...everything!
...safe.
Song of Scratches, Blizzard Slice!
Yeah! We are free!
Impact Wolf!
Damn Hordy! Look at yourself!
Cloven Rose, Palm!
"To the Future! The Path to the Sun!"
Franky...
I thought I was gonna be a slave forever!
Squid! Squid! Squid!
Straw Hats! I owe you one!
...Radical Beam!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Vagabond Drill!
Huh?! That's a bit...
I do not know their purpose
Hell Memories!
"Coming to an End! The Final
Decisive Battle against Hordy!"
What? I-I'm gonna become king...
but a long time ago, there were powerful
entities that could destroy the world.
Finally I can set sail for the New World!
Purgatory...
...Onigiri!
Princess Shirahoshi.
Gum-Gum...
We have been waiting for you
to be born for a long time.
Are you sure about releasing
Hordy's human slaves?
They were 3 Ancient Weapons
given the names of gods.
...Elephant Gun!
I will stop the Noah!
Pluton, Uranus, and Poseidon.
For me?
Their anger against Hordy could
turn towards all Fish-Men.
This ship is designed to be pulled by us.
Keep falling, Noah!
That is a different story.
And she is one of them.
Since very early times, the
duty has been passed on.
This island has always been a place
for pirates to travel and rest.
Kill all the pride-less Fish-Men!
Indeed.
And since they meant no harm to us,
Is that why the Noah is so big?
We can't let anyone know about this.
That toughness should put
his worth over 100 million.
there is no reason to hold them here-jamon.
Yes.
Every powerful group in the world would
want Princess Shirahoshi's power.
Once in many centuries,
Now, for the rest of the
New Fish-Man Pirates...
our queen comes into the
world in the form of Mermaid.
This wound...
The Government--even pirates.
--Don't cut my head off!
--P-Please!
I wonder why.
Luffy-sama...
The Ancient Weapons?
We didn't even know that
Hordy killed the Queen!
I wonder why as well.
Gum-Gum...
They could destroy the world?!
Ever since you were born,
...Elephant Gatling!
They're all nuts, really!
--He's right!
--It's Hordy's fault!
you have been our queen.
I won't let you interfere
with my plan, Straw Hat!
"Stop, Noah! Desperate Elephant Gatling!"
We're not responsible!
I got all their treasure
and I was about to leave
You can't lay a finger on the ship!
but this is even bigger news!
Brother!
Yeah, I think Shirahoshi is...
The Fish-Man Island is
doomed to fall like this!
I see. So that Mermaid Princess is...
She is talking with the Sea Kings.
I order you all to live on this main island!
I can't believe it!
Second Gear!
What is going on, guards?
How did the Noah stop?
Gum-Gum...
What?!
...Jet Pistol!
Whew, I want seconds!
What?! Are you telling us
to live law-abiding lives?
Well, actually a group of
Sea Kings showed up here
You already ate it all?!
It sounds better than working under Hordy.
It's so good--I could eat this forever!
around the island, out of the blue.
No way, King-sama! We
don't want them among us!
Especially this candy!
It seemed like they came
to protect the Noah...
Even those demon-like officers are a joke
to them. That's how strong they are!
We can't let our kids walk the streets!
...from getting destroyed by Luffy-san.
It's as good as meat. I
want hundreds of them!
Of course, I meant they need
to do their time and work
I-I'm afraid we are running out of that one.
I wonder if the Noah is something
very important to them.
under the supervision of my army-jamon.
We can bring other things if you want!
You're too slow, Straw Hat!
I will give you all jobs to use
up your overflowing energy.
Neptune-sama?!
Sea Kings...
All right!
From today on, the Fish-Man District
It awakes finally-jamon.
will be sealed off since it
is out of our control-jamon!
Luffy-sama...
Let me ask you, Luffy.
The power that could destroy the world!
Luffy-sama!
What do you know about the
state of the world now?
The dark side of the Fish-Men was exposed
Huh? What are you asking all of a sudden?
Look,
along with the real killer of Queen Otohime.
the bubble is getting absorbed by the island.
Gum-Gum...
Looks like you know nothing. You're
out of the loop--that's not good.
A pirate - Hordy Jones attempted
to take over the Fish-Man Island...
...Jet Bazooka!
The human can't survive in the deep sea.
Yeah?
You better go and save him.
...but his plans
Here's the food!
were foiled by human pirates who
were just stopping by the island.
Stay alert!
Let's go somewhere else to talk.
Look up! You're in danger!
Luffy-sama! Oh no!
Okay. One sec.
Armament Hardening!
What?!
Hey, where is Straw Hat Luffy-jamon?
I'll take a light snack.
--Wadatsumi is...
--...Falling toward us!
Well... He escaped.
Gum-Gum...
We should go capture Hordy and the others.
Escaped?!
Yeah.
...Red Hawk!
We have to hurry!
Noah... I wonder what
secrets that ship holds.
Oh, you guys are here too!
I drank too much! I'm trying to sober up!
Why did you have to leave the plaza
as though you were running away?
You should've dropped him
elsewhere, you worthless chef!
Shut up! I'll make someone
fall onto you next time!
I ate too much!
Am I imagining things?
Sanji Mermaid-ed too much.
Can't you see? We had to fight
with a lot of spectators watching.
What?
That human with the hat noticed our voice.
It's like heaven! The Mermaid Island!
If we stayed, they'd treat
us like heroes or something.
I doubt it.
That was amazing, Sanji.
What?! Akainu and Aokiji had a big fight?!
Something like this happened not so long ago.
Just the thought of it makes me shudder.
That's what I thought.
These fangs aren't fake!
Becoming a hero is not a good thing?
You didn't even know about that, did you?
Yes, I remember.
Hey Chopper! Could you shrink
yourself a little bit?
I know you're in pain, Straw Hat!
Let me tell you something.
A hero is someone who will share
his own sake with other people.
I didn't hear about anything
during my training.
You're upstaging the giant robot!
Rayleigh, did you just hear that voice?
Rayleigh is terrible.
Franky, I loved the beam!
What are you talking about?
I knew about it! I knew!
But I wanna drink it all by myself!
It's really quiet down here.
That robot was totally useless.
Again, that's not how you define a hero!
Are you serious?!
Who are you, talking in such deep sea?
Damn! He's pretty tough! Red Hawk
worked much better a while ago.
Why can't you join us, Jimbei?!
Oh! Nami-san!
Come on an adventure with us!
To the sea! It's gonna be fun!
Right after the war 2 years ago,
Fleet Admiral Sengoku resigned.
Hey, show yourself!
What?
Please wear a miniskirt.
This is the power I was granted by heaven,
Yeah, join us, Boss!
Shut up!
It's nice to have  a former Warlord with us!
Sengoku recommended Aokiji
to be his successor since he was
very popular among his own men
to destroy you evil lowly creatures - humans!
--I wonder why.
--I wonder why as well.
And Luffy,  you need a complete rest!
That's just what I'd expect
from Luffy-kun's friends.
but a lot of people at the
highest level favored Akainu
As I said, I can't join you right now!
I bet you thought you could gain the
upper hand fighting where you can breathe
I wonder if Straw Hat
and the others are okay.
and so he became a major contender.
I'm grateful that you asked me.
They're strong, aren't
they? Then they're fine.
but it's no use.
Nobody can best this righteous power!
Normally, Aokiji doesn't show his passion
I know it'd be fun to sail
the sea with you all.
Uh-huh, we have to trust them, Hatchin.
And nobody can stop me from getting revenge!
but he hated the idea of Akainu
becoming a Fleet Admiral.
He did it!
But I still have things that need to be done.
You're right.
They stood against each other and the
first-ever feud between the Admirals...
I have my current responsibilities which
Hordy.
This time for sure! Luffy-san beat Hordy!
I'm just taking a break from right now.
I'm sure that he is now beyond
his physical capacity.
...erupted into a battle
on an island somewhere.
When I fulfill my duties
and am free from them,
But he became a real
monster due to his grudge
--Did you hear that?
--Yeah...
Like the saying "Dead men tell no tales,"
S-Sea Kings?!
whoever lost had to withdraw his candidacy.
I promise I will come to see you all again.
toward humans and the Energy Steroid.
They're pulling the Noah!
The winner would lead the Navy.
They're gonna eat us!
Straw Hat.
And if you haven't changed your mind,
Luffy-san is losing.
As all the world now knows, their
deadly struggle lasted for 10 days.
The Straw Hats defeated
the New Fish-Man Pirates!
Hordy Jones... Is he invulnerable?
The ship is falling apart.
can I take you up on your offer then?
Can it be fixed?
They were comparable in their
strength but it came to an end.
I repeat.
You swear?!
Does it still work?
The giant ship - Noah is still
falling toward the Fish-Man Island
I don't know.
Akainu won!
In order to fix it, we need
help from "them" but...
Sakazuki is the new Fleet Admiral.
and on the deck of the Noah, Luffy-san
is engaging in battle with Hordy!
Whoa whoa, when a man talks about
his "duty," you can't press him.
Hey.
The Noah!
...times are changing.
He likes Jimbei so much!
Akainu!
--The Noah is gonna crush us!
--Can't we do anything?!
I got you!
Can it be fixed?
Straw Hat!
I hope it can be fixed...
Luffy thinks so highly of you! So
we're all gonna wait for you, Jimbei!
...by the appointed time.
Did you hear that? Our captain is doing fine.
The Noah is right there!
Did Aokiji die?
Our cause was right after all.
We were chosen by heaven!
They were both severely wounded
All right. Thank you!
and though Akainu is
pitiless, he showed mercy
Now what are we gonna do?
Head for the New World?
Run!
It's gonna destroy us along with the island!
It's a one-in-a-million chance for
your captain to win the fight!
This is the Ryugu Palace!
to his former comrade
who couldn't even stand.
Minister of the Left, you
might want to hear this!
What? Are you going to leave the island?!
If we stay here any longer, Neptune's
army will bar us in the plaza!
But Aokiji refused to work for Akainu
What is it?
We found the Mermaids who
had been kidnapped...
I couldn't thank you properly
and didn't get to talk to you!
Hurry up! Those crazy officers are gone now!
so he left the Navy.
No.
He's not a Navy soldier now, is he?
Like I said, I believe in him.
...inside the palace!
All right! Let's stay at the
Mermaid Cafe for a week or two!
Oh my goodness! How is the evacuation going?!
What?!
No, he is not. I wonder where he
is and what he is thinking now.
Are they all right?
Our captain will never lose!
That'd be just up your alley, wouldn't it?
Yes, they are. They say
they still feel groggy
Only a few citizens have escaped to the sea.
It was a big loss for the Government, too.
But I wanna go, too!
Most people are still here on the island!
but they remember the
kidnapper's face clearly!
Hey, wait!
Joke around while you can!
Who is it?
Of course. The Admirals were
the Navy's greatest powers.
Also, the treasure chamber's been emptied.
A soldier of Neptune's army?
Please wait, Straw Hats!
There isn't even a single
piece of treasure left.
Chopper, what do you mean you're okay?
But what the Government
did to cover their loss...
King Neptune! I caught up with them!
Now, I can fight like this for
3 minutes with the Rumble Ball.
Not to mention the national
treasure--the Tamate Box!
Good.
Are you okay?
Luffy-kun, why did you leave?
I wanted to thank you...
...gave the Navy unexpected power.
Is it too late?!
King-sama! S-Somebody robbed
the palace while we were gone!
I'm not the same person that I used to be.
I don't wanna be a hero!
I know. Let's just have a banquet!
I won't cause you guys trouble anymore.
Can't you do anything, Straw Hat?!
Forget about the treasure thief.
Listen. You all need to know
the two biggest changes...
The banquet we could not have before-jamon.
I can't believe it!
We almost lost the whole
country just now-jamon.
A banquet?! Then I'll
be right there! Banquet!
Straw Hat!
We can really depend on you
if you can control that power!
...which have occurred in the New World.
--Meat, meat! I wanna eat!
--Boy! Then why did we leave?
Instead, let the whole nation know
that those Mermaids were okay.
The threat of rebellion is now gone but...
We can't say no to a banquet.
Y-Your compliment doesn't make
me happy at all, you bastard!
First, the Navy Headquarters
led by Sakazuki...
All right! Let's go pick up Hachi and Camie!
I know it's too late
...has become an even more
powerful force for justice.
but we need to clear Straw Hat
and the others' name-jamon.
This is it!
No, not yet!
That's creepy!
What?
And second,
We did them wrong.
the Blackbeard Pirates have advanced.
You pissed me off-dosun!
The Fish-Man District was sealed
off right away by Neptune's order.
We shouldn't be here!
No matter how big you get, I'll blow
you away to the end of the sea-gogan!
He is not...
Hurry up!
Blackbeard?
They'll catch and kill us!
We met them in Mock Town.
Let's go! We humans have nothing
to do with this battle!
They destroyed my hometown once.
Hordy, the officers of the New Fish-Man
Pirates, and Vander Decken...
...giving up yet!
I'm not gonna be blown away to anywhere.
Where are you going?
The new era they're talking about is crap!
Let us go!
...were placed in the Prison Tower.
Straw Hat Luffy-san is...
Let's fly over him with bubbles.
Now, bring it on!
The era where pirates have dreams
will be over, they say?! Huh?!
Water Shot!
Chopper!
You fool!
THE MAIN ENTRANCE OF THE FISH-MAN ISLAND
I will shoot you down if you
try to fly over me with those!
What's going on?
Talking to a friend while fighting?
You don't know your place!
...trying his best...
Go, Kraken! Take him somewhere far!
You're just a burden to the Straw Hats!
...to destroy...
Wadatsumi, you don't fit into
any of the cells in the prison!
Dammit!
I beg you, Boss! Let us go!
People's dreams... have no end!!
We forbid you from entering
this country again!
...the Noah!
I'm gonna take care of you already!
We were just afraid of Hordy and the others!
CORAL HILL
Did you catch it?
Isn't that right?!
We have nothing to do with this
civil war because we're humans!
I told you I finished setting it up.
Yeah!
So you're...
Let's prepare these and
take them to the palace!
...Blackbeard?!
I thought this island was a tourist spot
Now, bring it on! I'll put
on an awesome magic show!
Oh yeah, I never gave you my name.
They'll have a big banquet
with the Straw Hats!
largely depending on us
human pirates for money!
Count on us!
Let us get out through the exit!
Much! How funny! Did you say you're
gonna end this with one shot?!
I heard they like sea monster meat.
No one says that you all are
going to get your heads cut off.
Long time no see, Straw Hat!
Let's take snacks and cakes, too!
Destroy the Noah?!
Maybe the Squid Spear didn't work on you
Trying to destroy it?
CANDY FACTORY TOWN
I heard they eat a lot. Take all we have!
He was once a long-time member
of the Whitebeard Pirates.
Wait for Neptune royal family's decision.
Destroy that giant ship?!
but I have another one that
will cut through anything-ch!
Do they have enough sake?
Really?! That's impossible!
He knows their territory very well
I want them to have our highest quality sake!
Prepare for the worst, guys!
There is something that we would
like all islanders to know.
and he conquered it in an instant
after the good old man died.
Welcome to the palace-jamon,
Luffy-kun, everybody.
Yeah. Let's just stand by him.
Emit light! Light Bright Spear!
Let's talk later during the banquet.
The Straw Hats were not involved in
the kidnap of the Mermaids at all.
Using the Tremor-Tremor Fruit power
that he got from the good old man.
RYUGU PALACE
The long flounders will take
you to the banquet hall!
I will beat you with one shot instead-ch!
Luffy-san!
--Whew! These rays are huge!
--They're flukes.
I'm gonna cut a hole through your cockpit-ch!
The world already counts him among...
We admit that we made a mistake
in our fact-checking process
He just said "flounders."
..."Red-Haired," Kaido,
That looks kind of cool but...
and we take full responsibility
- we want to apologize.
and Big Mam,
...it's not gonna work! You're
less than an ordinary squid...
and considers him as one
of the Four Emperors.
It's a dark room filled with water.
Luffy-sama!
I didn't think the Straw Hats did it.
So he took Whitebeard's place successfully.
Are we really allowed in? I'm nervous!
...before my ultimate weapon!
I knew it wasn't them the whole time.
What a dirty rat!
I've never entered the palace before.
If he can destroy the Noah before it
hits the island, we'll be okay but...
Yes, he is annoying.
I can't fight with my bare
hands. What should I do?
Don't lie!
We all thought that they were the kidnappers!
What's this place? What happened
to the meat and banquet?
Rumor has it that they are  on
the hunt for Devil Fruit eaters.
...if he can't,
Oh, here comes the heroes!
the Fish-Man Island will fall!
I won't cut a man without the
fighting spirit! Go away, Froggy!
--N-No, we trusted them, didn't we?
--Y-Yeah.
They can somehow acquire a Devil Fruit
eater's power after killing them.
Oh, it's filled with soldiers down there!
--Liars!
--Hey!
Give it everything you got, Luffy!
Frog?
Thank you for saving the Fish-Man Island!
That's not fair!
I don't know what he is talking about.
He's right!
--Luffy-san!
--We're counting on you, Luffy!
We'll never forget what you did for us!
They keep looking for
stronger Devil Fruit powers.
Admit it.
Luffy!
He doesn't know that my
deadly poison will kill him!
We didn't trust them.
Be careful!
We didn't trust them because they're humans.
Luffy-kun!
They'll get me!
No one wants your Human-Human Fruit power.
Heroes! Heroes! Heroes! Heroes!
That's how we've always treated humans...
What?!
What's wrong?!
Especially you, Luffy-kun.
I'm not gonna run!
Shut up! Stop calling us
"heroes"! I wanna eat meat!
Don't be ridiculous! Can't you see the Noah?!
There is a lot of bad blood between
you and Blackbeard--Teach.
I know! I know, but...
Finish this up? That's my line.
He's right! I wanna drink sake!
So take extra care...
Super...
...Straw Hat's heroic actions
bring back memories of...
Don't think that I inflated myself just
because I got taken in by you fools!
...Afro!
You idiots...
...what happened 20 years
ago when I was a kid!
--Franky-san, that's so cool!
--Isn't it super?
Luffy-sama! There is a stage
right in front of you!
Luffy! Are you even listening?!
I'm gonna roll around and squash
your friends in the plaza!
Hey Chopper, are you alright?
There was one human that the people of
this kingdom thanked with all our hearts!
Yeah... I'm fine...
I thought you were the captain!
A stage?
Whoa!
You have to know a little
bit of information at least!
Ladies and gentlemen! Let's start
the banquet with the Straw Hats!
--Thanks.
--Oh boy...
Don't worry, Jimbei.
We were listening.
Are you listening?!
When I use the Monster Boost,
First,
I thought captains normally
don't listen to other people!
I can't even walk for a
couple hours from fatigue.
we present you the greatest
diva of the deep sea!
Sorry, I was thinking about something else.
Captains are responsible for their
crew's safety, aren't they, Luffy?!
What a haul!
Maria Napole!
Thinking about something else?!
But I can still treat you.
Hey wait!
Yeah, I was thinking how should I
cook an unnecessarily big blowfish.
No!
Is anyone hurt?
Hey Jimbei, take it easy! I
like taking chances anyway!
Who are you?! Do you wanna die?!
Look who's talking!
What?! Do it if you can!
Everybody looks okay.
Robin-chan! I used a daring
technique and I'm exhausted too!
You got to be kidding me! Why is he...
Blowfish!
It must be hard to work for him.
Let me put my head in your lap, too! Please!
...taking the Fish-Men's side?!
Yeah...
--Put your stupid head somewhere else!
--You do it!
Luffy-chin!
All right...
Neptune helped me when we
were young and we exchanged
There you are!
Luffy...
You shouldn't be here. You're
the life of the banquet.
cups of sake as a pledge of friendship!
There they are! Hey!
Camie!
I haven't seen Yowahoshi.
Prince!
Don't kill me! I promise I'll never
kidnap Mermaids and Fish-Men!
Everybody!
Princess-sama said she's
tired and she wanted to rest
It's the Princes!
so she went to her room.
I'm glad that they're okay!
Don't mess with my friend's country!
Luffy-sama! You are bleeding!
Can't you see it? There
is nothing you can do!
You wet-nosed brats!
--Hordy!
--Vander Decken!
Hey, Zoro!
You will never beat me!
Sanji!
I declare that this island
is my territory now!
I think there is a wild animal
or something in this palace.
Father! We are sorry to make you worry!
You're right.
I feel it, too.
I am glad that you are all okay-jamon.
Weren't you listening to what I said?
THE HARD SHELL TOWER
Are you talking about Whitebeard?!
Well done!
Are you saying you trust them like
you trusted the great pirate?!
I will save the Fish-Man
Island and Shirahoshi...
Thank you!
And the Swing Jazz Orchestra!
I did not know it's such fun
to party with everybody!
Because,
Luffy-sama...
...and keep my promise to a friend.
to be honest, I don't even like humans
and this is the Fish-Men's kingdom,
Straw Hat...
I'll protect...
but they...
Our minds were made up when
we arrived at the plaza that,
...everything!
Wow! What a sweet voice!
along with Jimbei, we wouldn't
let anyone harm the island!
Wow! Maria-sama!
Everybody! No worries!
She is rocking my soul! Oh yeah!
Leave it all up to us, Brother-hoshi!
We won't allow them to make trouble again!
We're friends, right?
He said such things and they're
all risking their lives...
We can live without fear now!
And the special guests!
I can't believe there was such an awful
guy so nearby in the Fish-Man District.
D-Don't tell me...
--C-Captain Hordy!
--He looks like a monster!
Seems like you humans have
to die in order to realize...
Their beauty takes your breath away!
This is great!
...how arrogant you are
even though you're so weak!
Straw Hat...
Hey, that's...
Then I'm gonna make you realize!
They are back!
Luffy-san!
Hey, Luffy!
It's Straw Hat Luffy and Princess Shirahoshi!
The Mermaid Cafe Dancers!
I have no time! Let's wrap this up already!
Please help me!
I cannot stop Luffy-sama's bleeding!
Beat me if you can!
--Yowahoshi, stay away!
--Y-Yes!
Help!
Shhh!
Fish-Man Jiu-Jitsu - Water Heart!
Please stop! Who are you?!
Shark Pack!
Don't lose, Straw Hat!
Yeah, Straw Hat, we're supporting you!
Somebody! Help!
Hang in there, Straw Hat!
--You're a human and you're fighting for us!
--We're not gonna run!
Shut up!
Don't look so resentful, Princess-san!
Hey Luffy, stay with us!
You can't get away!
Go, Big Bro Straw Hat!
Luffy!
Don't worry! I'm not gonna
hurt you or make you suffer!
You're gonna die, Sanji!
Luffy-sama pushed himself
so far in order to save us!
I was content with taking the treasure.
It became a pain to sell those Mermaids
Their beauty can't be captured
in a picture! No. 1!
Go to hell!
Straw Hat!
but you're an exception!
Please save the Fish-Man Island, Straw Hat!
This is bad!
I just need you to be
unconscious for a while!
There are hemostatics in my backpack!
--I'm losing my strength...
--Oh no!
Go, Straw Hat!
--Awesome!
--Fascinating!
We believe in you!
--Get it for me, Robin.
--Okay.
I just got word from my
brother and the others
Straw Hat!
This makes me worried about how
you'll fight from now on, Doc!
they've arrived at a port on this island!
Camie!
Straw Hat!
Luffy-sama...
Ishilly! I'm glad that you're okay!
Okay, go ahead!
Come to the New World with us!
Straw Hat!
-I'll help you move.
--We have an odd doctor here!
Luffy-chan!
Hey.
Come on! Why don't you laugh?
A little bit to the left.
Here it comes! There's no
having a banquet without it!
Will Luffy-sama be all right?!
Nyah, nyah, nyah, nyah, nyah, boo!
I can stop the bleeding but he
already lost a lot of blood!
--Super I've been waiting for this!
--That's how the Ryugu Palace should be!
Straw Hat!
Hey!
What do you want, Straw Hat?
I'm having fun here so go away!
Straw Hat!
He's lacking blood!
Thank you.
Luffy-sama!
Luffy is the only one  with
blood type F among us.
Thanks.
Straw Hat!
Nyah, nyah!
Thank you!
Straw Hat!
Mermaid-chan!
Oh no!
Nyah, nyah, nyah! Nyah, nyah, nyah... Nya...
There must be somebody in the plaza!
Straw Hat!
Somebody!
Hey!
--Straw Hat!
Thank you very much!
Is there someone with blood type F here?!
Now, King, will you give a toast?
--Straw Hat!
He needs blood!
Stop, Noah!
What?
Can somebody donate blood?!
Straw Hat?!
Stop!
Luffy-sama!
Before I give a toast, I really want
to express my gratitude briefly-jamon.
Stop!
Really? Nobody?
Third Gear!
My blood type is F.
Mine is F but...
Dad, your blood type is F, isn't it?
Armament Hardening!
I didn't know he was still around.
Well, I mean...
Luffy-sama!
Oh yeah! Donating blood to humans
is prohibited in this country!
I only broke half of it so far!
Drop dead already!
It was scary!
What?!
All of you Straw Hats!
Gum-Gum...
You're so lucky, Luffy!
I should have kicked him!
What kind of law is that?!  That's horrible!
Thanks to you...
...Elephant Gun!
Luffy-sama!
It's banquet time!
I beg you! Luffy is dying!
He was the pirate that
we captured in the sea.
Cheers!
The wound is opening up...
I haven't seen him since we
entered the Fish-Man Island.
M-My blood type is not F but mine's red too!
Cheers!
Stay away!
All right! Let's drink!
I forgot about him.
Stay there and watch!
It's no good?!
It's no use!
That was close! Thank you again!
I need to keep destroying this thing now!
Yes but thank you for offering!
I know, I know. Nobody
wants to hear me-jamon.
You puny humans could never stop me...
Princess Shirahoshi...
Don't mention it!
Bring the food!
I can't believe the treasure
thief was still here.
Oh yeah! There are human pirates!
...from taking revenge!
Stop, ship!
Meat!
We usually don't even let
a tiny fish into the palace
Hey please! If nothing is
done, Luffy is gonna...
I will stop the Noah!
Eat! Sing! Drink! Dance!
but the gate was left open in
the confusion of the battles.
Luffy is gonna die!
--Straw Hat!
Look! That tower on the right
has been sliced clean through.
Luffy, go for it!
I assume the thief did it
while we were not here.
Break it into pieces!
Super!
Yummy!
We have plenty more.
No, this guy cut the tower.
Oh yeah? Thanks!
When they escaped from the cage,
he cut bars, walls... everything!
I need more obviously!
You eat a lot!
Why did you have to tell him
that, you stupid starfish?!
Come on, sisters, dance with me! Here we go!
Keep falling, Noah!
What?! As they say, lying and
stealing are next-door neighbors!
I'm sorry, Father.
Let's dance.
--I'll dance.
--I won't.
Take my blood.
Destroying the Noah is the only way.
Wait a minute, Minister of the Right-chan!
--Maybe I'll dance.
--I'll dance, so what?
Kill all the pride-less Fish-Men!
It's F.
Chan?
Did you say "treasure thief"?
You can have as much as you need.
Straw Hat!
Yum! You have great snacks on this island!
Yes, he stole all the
treasures in the palace.
Jimbei!
The Ship of Promise...
Jimbei-chan!
But it's against the law...
But it cannot be helped.
People's lives are the most important.
I am a pirate!
What?! He did?!
This island's sake is so good!
I am sorry. I cannot keep the promise-jamon,
I have a bad feeling!
Boss! I'm so glad!
Aren't they national treasures?
You're not gonna go after him?
I already had it once!
Jimbei-san!
Joy Boy!
After seeing my people's lives be
saved, treasures mean nothing to me.
I heard you got caught for that!
Thank you!
Jimbei, you...
No, they're worth something!
It is okay-jamon.
Gum-Gum...
Forget about those little things!
What if we get them back?!
K-King-sama!
...Elephant Gatling!
Bone...
What is so wrong with it?
Are you okay, Hero-san?
You can keep them all.
It would be wonderful if people who
saved the country had them-jamon.
That old law is also...
That bastard, I didn't think of that!
Just a little more to go!
...a curse-jamon.
Are you sure?!
This is my space, skeleton man.
I'm dying-bone!
You fools! Why did you kick him out?!
Sanji!
Okay, let me prepare for the procedure.
If you enter this circle, I'm gonna
break your bones into pieces!
Why didn't you just punch
him and tie him up here!
I'm fine now. I can move for a while.
Please...
You can't push yourself like that, young man!
I love it even when you...
Let me help with something.
OK, thanks.
I think you're gonna die soon.
What are you gonna do now?!
Go find him now!
Nobody cares about me-jamon...
Stop.
The hairy old man doesn't look happy.
K-King-sama!
Hey, Straw Hat-san! Don't
be rude to the King!
Something wrong with Hordy and
the others! Their cuffs came off!
Luffy-chin! Luffy-chin!
Luffy, raise your glass!
What?!
THE PRISON TOWER
Okay, I'm sorry but...
Who is it?!
You too, hairy old man!
...I got into the circle and cut you already.
Uh-huh.
But I want to express my gratitude briefly...
Damn humans! Our grudge against
you will never go away...
Luffy-sama! Please stop!
It's going to be cold. Take care of yourself.
Luffy-sama, you have to stop!
Our time to avenge will come again...
Father-sama!
When did you get in?!
Shirahoshi.
Jimbei, it may hurt a little bit.
Song of Scratches, Blizzard Slice!
Cheers!
Move, Yowahoshi! I need to
destroy it to save the island!
Bring Straw Hat here! I'll kill him!
I don't mind.
Cheers-jamon! Oh, whatever-jamon!
It's okay now!
Cheers to you guys, too!
It's not okay! Everybody's on the island!
Let me read a haiku.
Cheers!
It's very good. I wonder if
it's because of the water.
The Noah is already...
The blood-freezing wind from
the far land of the dead...
Oh, you can tell the difference, young lady?
...stopped!
...Please, blow up some skirts!
I want more!
Why do you look so pale?! It's empty!
Drop dead!
Am I drunk?
I-I can't believe it.
I feel pain in my joints!
Sea Kings? Why?
What is it?!
Green Star - Humandrake!
I got old on purpose.
I'll get back at the Straw Hats-fosun...
Luffy-sama is angry!
This plant has human-shaped roots
which attack things flying over,
Hey, this is no time for crying!
totally entwining them!
Moonfish! Shake, shake!
What is it this time?!
We are the ones who will punish humans.
I don't quite understand, either.
Dance more, everybody!
Green Star - Trampolia! It'll blow
away all approaching enemies!
What is going on here?
Eat, drink and make some
noise-mi-fa-so-la-ti-do!
Is that Hordy and his clan?
But the Noah is stopped now!
And now you're up high in the air
- there's nothing you can do!
Don't think that you can keep me
in jail, you stupid royal family!
If you hurt somebody...
Special Attack - Green Star!
What happened?!
Th-These bars are nothing...
What's going on here? The
Sea Kings stopped the ship!
Captain Hordy!
A monster from aboveground?!
I'll bite it off!
What do you want to talk
to me about, pirate girl?
...or if somebody hurts you,
Luffy-sama! The wound is opening up again!
You better not.
What is going on here?!
I'm sorry. I thought this was my only
chance to talk to you in private.
The bulb on its nose
I knew it! The Energy Steroid
that you guys were taking...
You are bleeding a lot!
will release a powerful shockwave
3 meters in diameter.
What?!
I-I will tell you now!
...was the legendary pill that
was kept in the Tamate Box!
I have a wife named Otohime
who I swore to love forever!
the same red blood will be shed.
Well... Well... That's good...
Tamate Box?
Although she is dead, I am
not going to cheat on her...
It was national treasure that had been
passed down for generations-jamon.
Who is Joy Boy?
...as long as the ship is stopped.
Impact Wolf!
Dosun! Dogan! Bogan!
10 years ago, somebody stole
the contents of the Tamate Box.
I'm glad everybody's...
Now, get blown away to the end
of the world-gadon-megagon!
It hardly seems like a path...
...safe.
We couldn't find who did it
and by the King's decision,
I read the Poneglyph in the Sea Forest.
Luffy-sama!
Papara-Hammer!
we closed the case before
it became a scandal.
Who is he apologizing to?
He's fine.
Cloven Rose, Palm!
Come to think of it, that was
when you left the army, Hordy.
You can read it?
...because it's a very thin and narrow
tube - but it makes its way through...
I'm a survivor of Ohara.
Pi... pikon.
You don't have to tell me
everything if you don't want to.
Boy, what a human!
That's right! I stole it!
Squid! Squid! Squid!
He is a very strong one, isn't he?
You idiots!
Chew on this - the spear that will cut
through even an undersea mountain!
No.
The legendary pill had unclear effects.
...the prejudice that makes
people fear each other...
If we were late, we could
still have saved the island
Franky...
I will tell you everything I know.
One explanation says it
gives you tremendous power.
but the Noah would have
been completely destroyed.
Squid! Squid! Squid!
...Radical Beam!
I trust you people.
Another explanation says
it just makes you old.
Joy Boy was a person from
above ground who lived
I'm glad that we made it!
Dried squid!
It is an odd national treasure.
during the Hundred Year Void-jamon.
I'm glad that Princess Shirahoshi called us!
...and blood feuds...
What?!
That means more than 800 years ago.
I assumed they guarded the power drug closely
L-Laser beam?!
What? I didn't do anything
and I was just sad...
That message was written
to a Mermaid Princess
in order to seal off its dangerous effect.
Cool!!
who was on this island at that time-jamon.
...so very easily.
No, you were moved by Straw
Hat boy's strong determination
You folk opened the box
that should not be opened
It's a letter of apology for not
keeping his promise to the island.
and dreamed a foolish dream
of gaining some power-jamon.
This is a path towards a very real sun,
and prayed.
Promise?
I do not know the details of his promise
Shut up, Neptune!
not some empty wish.
but they say somebody will come and
fulfill it on behalf of Joy Boy someday.
You wished strongly to
help him save the island.
Fish-Man Karate technique!
Seems like they no longer get their revenge.
That is the story handed
down in our royal family.
Vagabond Drill!
Shut up!
So we believe the day will come
We're chosen avengers!
and have continued
We will kill all humans...
looking after the Noah for generations
just as we promised him.
What?!
Water blasted through his body!
...and you!!
When the day comes, the Noah will be put
The air will leak...
to its true use for the first time-jamon!
I feel sorry for them now.
Our power is your power.
I will consider giving them clemency.
I heard when all the battles
came to an end today,
Jimbei...
How do you like it up here, Balloon Blowfish!
Wait, Neptune!
We helped him because you called us.
the half-destroyed Noah was
taken to the Sea Forest...
Luffy-sama, you came to life again!
That human is flying!
Fukaboshi, you're a dishonor to our race!
Luffy!
You scared the guts out of me!
...by the Sea Kings!
--Luffy!
--Luffy-san!
What is it?
I wonder if Joy Boy had power to
Remember, over the past 2 years...
I didn't know that you were awake.
control Sea Kings since he
was going to use the Noah.
The Fish-Man Island will change.
Sanji-kun!
No,
Straw Hat!
Why did I have to go through such hell?!
You killed my mother but I will
not hold a grudge against you.
the former Mermaid Princess was
the one who had such power-jamon.
Luffy!
He's on fire!
So please. Just shut your mouth!
That's what I thought.
I want to burn those memories!
A-All people of the kingdom.
Then, Princess Shirahoshi
has that same power?
Hell Memories!
Wh-What just happened here was beyond words
Yes.
I don't want the children
on the island to hear you.
I think it awoke completely today.
but it happened for sure!
Scared the guts out of you?
You saved me the trouble then.
The Noah is stopped!
Because when I cook blowfish,
Minister of the Left!
I have to remove the toxic parts carefully.
The ship didn't get destroyed completely
Mr. Pekoms and Baron Tamago
arrived at the Candy Factory!
Take these swords coated with my venom!
I am not happy about it.
Cut it out, Froggy.
I know how you feel.
and the Fish-Man Island has been saved!
They were sent by Big Mam.
This is not a good time!
2 years ago at a Sky Island,
I'm not a frog!
I'm the best octopus eight-sword
style swordsman...
I read a Poneglyph indicating where
one of the ancient weapons is.
Straw Hat did it!
Where are our sweets? Grr!
...on the Fish-Man Island! My
name is Hyouzou! Don't forget it!
We are back to zero now!
--Straw Hat!
--So we're safe, aren't we?
It was pointing at this island.
Purgatory...
Mama is waiting for them-soir!
Yeah!
...Onigiri!
Straw Hat!
Mother!
The Mermaid Princess who lived
around the same time as Joy Boy...
I'm so sorry.
I'm so relieved!
I thought that you were a frog.
A big frog in a small pond.
...was known by a specific name, wasn't she?
We don't have any sweets
to pay them for this month.
--Yeah!
--Oh, he did it!
Hordy and the others destroyed the factory
Luffy did it!!
Since Princess Shirahoshi has the same
power, she will inherit that name.
and the undamaged sweets have
been sent to the banquet
since everybody wanted the
Hey, Jimbei.
Straw Hats to have them!
Another name for her will be...
He...
He did it!
I wonder if we can explain the situation.
She is like a monster who would
destroy a whole country for sweets!
This time for sure!
...the ancient weapon...
He beat Hordy!
One of the Four Emperors...
Join...
...Poseidon!
...my crew!
Big Mam!
Fish-Man Island is saved.
Jimbei reveals speaks about
two important matters.
Luffy and the others are caught up trying
to reclaim the treasure of Fish-Man Island.
However, in his fight to achieve this...
The Noah falls toward Fish-Man Island,
as if inheriting Hordy's grudge.
After Whitebeard's death, distribution of
...Luffy is in critical condition
with a multitude of wounds.
power among pirates in the
New World was decided...
The crew of Big Mam, one of
the Four Emperors, shows up.
Yet the Fish-Men, still bound
by the island's past...
Just when the insurmountably huge mass...
...by none other than one
of the Four Emperors.
And a fierce and epic battle
occurred within the Navy.
Just as Fish-Man Island faces
destruction yet again...
...causes everyone to lose hope,
...hesitate to come to his aid.
Its shocking conclusion...
Luffy alone...
Just when Luffy is almost out of time...
...at the hands of one of the
overwhelmingly powerful Four Emperors...
...pushes his life to the limit
and stands against the Noah!
...becomes a big obstacle for
Luffy as he enters the New World.
...a single man's actions
alter the course of history.
...Luffy takes a stand!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Stop, Noah! Desperate Elephant Gatling!"
"The Straw Hats Stunned! The
New Fleet Admiral of the Navy!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Secret Revealed! The Truth
about the Ancient Weapon!"
"She Loves Sweets! Big Mam
of the Four Emperors!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
"The Secret Revealed! The Truth
about the Ancient Weapon!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!