Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates  who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in
the turmoil and involved in an all-out war.
Now, Hordy's merciless plot puts the
Fish-Man Island in unprecedented danger!
What's wrong?
L-Look at that!
I can't believe it!
There is air!
"Coming to an End! The Final
Decisive Battle against Hordy!"
That toughness should put
his worth over 100 million.
This wound...
Luffy-sama...
I won't let you interfere
with my plan, Straw Hat!
You can't lay a finger on the ship!
The Fish-Man Island is
doomed to fall like this!
Second Gear!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Pistol!
You're too slow, Straw Hat!
Luffy-sama...
Luffy-sama!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Bazooka!
Armament Hardening!
Gum-Gum...
...Red Hawk!
These fangs aren't fake!
I know you're in pain, Straw Hat!
Damn! He's pretty tough! Red Hawk
worked much better a while ago.
This is the power I was granted by heaven,
to destroy you evil lowly creatures - humans!
I bet you thought you could gain the
upper hand fighting where you can breathe
but it's no use.
Nobody can best this righteous power!
And nobody can stop me from getting revenge!
Hordy.
I'm sure that he is now beyond
his physical capacity.
But he became a real
monster due to his grudge
toward humans and the Energy Steroid.
Straw Hat.
Luffy-san is losing.
Hordy Jones... Is he invulnerable?
I repeat.
The giant ship - Noah is still
falling toward the Fish-Man Island
and on the deck of the Noah, Luffy-san
is engaging in battle with Hordy!
--The Noah is gonna crush us!
--Can't we do anything?!
Straw Hat!
Did you hear that? Our captain is doing fine.
Our cause was right after all.
We were chosen by heaven!
It's a one-in-a-million chance for
your captain to win the fight!
No.
Like I said, I believe in him.
Our captain will never lose!
Joke around while you can!
Chopper, what do you mean you're okay?
Now, I can fight like this for
3 minutes with the Rumble Ball.
I'm not the same person that I used to be.
I won't cause you guys trouble anymore.
I can't believe it!
We can really depend on you
if you can control that power!
Y-Your compliment doesn't make
me happy at all, you bastard!
That's creepy!
You pissed me off-dosun!
No matter how big you get, I'll blow
you away to the end of the sea-gogan!
I'm not gonna be blown away to anywhere.
Now, bring it on!
Chopper!
You fool!
Talking to a friend while fighting?
You don't know your place!
You're just a burden to the Straw Hats!
I'm gonna take care of you already!
I told you I finished setting it up.
Now, bring it on! I'll put
on an awesome magic show!
Much! How funny! Did you say you're
gonna end this with one shot?!
Maybe the Squid Spear didn't work on you
but I have another one that
will cut through anything-ch!
Emit light! Light Bright Spear!
I will beat you with one shot instead-ch!
I'm gonna cut a hole through your cockpit-ch!
That looks kind of cool but...
...it's not gonna work! You're
less than an ordinary squid...
...before my ultimate weapon!
I can't fight with my bare
hands. What should I do?
I won't cut a man without the
fighting spirit! Go away, Froggy!
Frog?
I don't know what he is talking about.
He doesn't know that my
deadly poison will kill him!
Finish this up? That's my line.
Don't think that I inflated myself just
because I got taken in by you fools!
I'm gonna roll around and squash
your friends in the plaza!
Are you listening?!
Sorry, I was thinking about something else.
Thinking about something else?!
Yeah, I was thinking how should I
cook an unnecessarily big blowfish.
What?! Do it if you can!
Blowfish!
All right...
Luffy-sama! You are bleeding!
Can't you see it? There
is nothing you can do!
You will never beat me!
Weren't you listening to what I said?
I will save the Fish-Man
Island and Shirahoshi...
Luffy-sama...
...and keep my promise to a friend.
Straw Hat...
I'll protect...
...everything!
Seems like you humans have
to die in order to realize...
...how arrogant you are
even though you're so weak!
Then I'm gonna make you realize!
I have no time! Let's wrap this up already!
Beat me if you can!
--Yowahoshi, stay away!
--Y-Yes!
Fish-Man Jiu-Jitsu - Water Heart!
Shark Pack!
You can't get away!
Go to hell!
Luffy-sama...
Straw Hat!
Luffy-sama!
Third Gear!
Armament Hardening!
Drop dead already!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
It's no use!
You puny humans could never stop me...
...from taking revenge!
I will stop the Noah!
Keep falling, Noah!
Kill all the pride-less Fish-Men!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gatling!
This is my space, skeleton man.
If you enter this circle, I'm gonna
break your bones into pieces!
What are you gonna do now?!
Okay, I'm sorry but...
...I got into the circle and cut you already.
It's going to be cold. Take care of yourself.
When did you get in?!
Song of Scratches, Blizzard Slice!
Let me read a haiku.
The blood-freezing wind from
the far land of the dead...
...Please, blow up some skirts!
Drop dead!
What is it?!
Green Star - Humandrake!
This plant has human-shaped roots
which attack things flying over,
totally entwining them!
What is it this time?!
Green Star - Trampolia! It'll blow
away all approaching enemies!
And now you're up high in the air
- there's nothing you can do!
Special Attack - Green Star!
A monster from aboveground?!
I'll bite it off!
You better not.
The bulb on its nose
will release a powerful shockwave
3 meters in diameter.
Impact Wolf!
Dosun! Dogan! Bogan!
Now, get blown away to the end
of the world-gadon-megagon!
Papara-Hammer!
Cloven Rose, Palm!
Pi... pikon.
Squid! Squid! Squid!
Chew on this - the spear that will cut
through even an undersea mountain!
Franky...
Squid! Squid! Squid!
...Radical Beam!
Dried squid!
What?!
L-Laser beam?!
Cool!!
Fish-Man Karate technique!
Vagabond Drill!
What?!
Water blasted through his body!
The air will leak...
How do you like it up here, Balloon Blowfish!
That human is flying!
You scared the guts out of me!
Remember, over the past 2 years...
Sanji-kun!
Why did I have to go through such hell?!
He's on fire!
I want to burn those memories!
Hell Memories!
Scared the guts out of you?
You saved me the trouble then.
Because when I cook blowfish,
I have to remove the toxic parts carefully.
Take these swords coated with my venom!
Cut it out, Froggy.
I'm not a frog!
I'm the best octopus eight-sword
style swordsman...
...on the Fish-Man Island! My
name is Hyouzou! Don't forget it!
Purgatory...
...Onigiri!
I'm so sorry.
I thought that you were a frog.
A big frog in a small pond.
He...
He did it!
This time for sure!
He beat Hordy!
The Noah falls toward Fish-Man Island,
as if inheriting Hordy's grudge.
Just when the insurmountably huge mass...
...causes everyone to lose hope,
Luffy alone...
...pushes his life to the limit
and stands against the Noah!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Stop, Noah! Desperate Elephant Gatling!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!