Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where they faced the New Fish-Man Pirates
who were looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom
and instigated an all-out war.
The Sea Kings stopped the Noah from
falling onto the Fish-Man Island.
Please help me!
I cannot stop Luffy-sama's bleeding!
Take my blood.
It's F.
You can have as much as you need.
Hey, Jimbei.
Join...
...my crew!
"The Secret Revealed! The Truth
about the Ancient Weapon!"
The royal family came to a decision!
Yeah! We are free!
Damn Hordy! Look at yourself!
I thought I was gonna be a slave forever!
Straw Hats! I owe you one!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Huh?! That's a bit...
What? I-I'm gonna become king...
Finally I can set sail for the New World!
Are you sure about releasing
Hordy's human slaves?
Their anger against Hordy could
turn towards all Fish-Men.
That is a different story.
This island has always been a place
for pirates to travel and rest.
And since they meant no harm to us,
there is no reason to hold them here-jamon.
Now, for the rest of the
New Fish-Man Pirates...
--Don't cut my head off!
--P-Please!
We didn't even know that
Hordy killed the Queen!
They're all nuts, really!
--He's right!
--It's Hordy's fault!
We're not responsible!
I order you all to live on this main island!
What?!
What?! Are you telling us
to live law-abiding lives?
It sounds better than working under Hordy.
No way, King-sama! We
don't want them among us!
We can't let our kids walk the streets!
Of course, I meant they need
to do their time and work
under the supervision of my army-jamon.
I will give you all jobs to use
up your overflowing energy.
From today on, the Fish-Man District
will be sealed off since it
is out of our control-jamon!
The dark side of the Fish-Men was exposed
along with the real killer of Queen Otohime.
A pirate - Hordy Jones attempted
to take over the Fish-Man Island...
...but his plans
were foiled by human pirates who
were just stopping by the island.
Hey, where is Straw Hat Luffy-jamon?
Well... He escaped.
Escaped?!
Why did you have to leave the plaza
as though you were running away?
Can't you see? We had to fight
with a lot of spectators watching.
If we stayed, they'd treat
us like heroes or something.
Just the thought of it makes me shudder.
Becoming a hero is not a good thing?
Let me tell you something.
A hero is someone who will share
his own sake with other people.
But I wanna drink it all by myself!
Again, that's not how you define a hero!
Why can't you join us, Jimbei?!
Come on an adventure with us!
To the sea! It's gonna be fun!
Yeah, join us, Boss!
It's nice to have  a former Warlord with us!
And Luffy,  you need a complete rest!
As I said, I can't join you right now!
I'm grateful that you asked me.
I know it'd be fun to sail
the sea with you all.
But I still have things that need to be done.
I have my current responsibilities which
I'm just taking a break from right now.
When I fulfill my duties
and am free from them,
I promise I will come to see you all again.
And if you haven't changed your mind,
can I take you up on your offer then?
You swear?!
Whoa whoa, when a man talks about
his "duty," you can't press him.
He likes Jimbei so much!
Luffy thinks so highly of you! So
we're all gonna wait for you, Jimbei!
All right. Thank you!
Now what are we gonna do?
Head for the New World?
What? Are you going to leave the island?!
I couldn't thank you properly
and didn't get to talk to you!
All right! Let's stay at the
Mermaid Cafe for a week or two!
That'd be just up your alley, wouldn't it?
But I wanna go, too!
Hey, wait!
Who is it?
A soldier of Neptune's army?
Please wait, Straw Hats!
King Neptune! I caught up with them!
Good.
Luffy-kun, why did you leave?
I wanted to thank you...
I don't wanna be a hero!
I know. Let's just have a banquet!
The banquet we could not have before-jamon.
A banquet?! Then I'll
be right there! Banquet!
--Meat, meat! I wanna eat!
--Boy! Then why did we leave?
We can't say no to a banquet.
All right! Let's go pick up Hachi and Camie!
The Fish-Man District was sealed
off right away by Neptune's order.
Hordy, the officers of the New Fish-Man
Pirates, and Vander Decken...
...were placed in the Prison Tower.
THE MAIN ENTRANCE OF THE FISH-MAN ISLAND
Go, Kraken! Take him somewhere far!
Wadatsumi, you don't fit into
any of the cells in the prison!
We forbid you from entering
this country again!
CORAL HILL
Did you catch it?
Yeah!
Let's prepare these and
take them to the palace!
They'll have a big banquet
with the Straw Hats!
Count on us!
I heard they like sea monster meat.
Let's take snacks and cakes, too!
CANDY FACTORY TOWN
I heard they eat a lot. Take all we have!
Do they have enough sake?
I want them to have our highest quality sake!
Welcome to the palace-jamon,
Luffy-kun, everybody.
Let's talk later during the banquet.
RYUGU PALACE
The long flounders will take
you to the banquet hall!
--Whew! These rays are huge!
--They're flukes.
He just said "flounders."
It's a dark room filled with water.
Are we really allowed in? I'm nervous!
I've never entered the palace before.
What's this place? What happened
to the meat and banquet?
Oh, here comes the heroes!
Oh, it's filled with soldiers down there!
Thank you for saving the Fish-Man Island!
We'll never forget what you did for us!
Heroes! Heroes! Heroes! Heroes!
Shut up! Stop calling us
"heroes"! I wanna eat meat!
He's right! I wanna drink sake!
You idiots...
Luffy-sama! There is a stage
right in front of you!
A stage?
Ladies and gentlemen! Let's start
the banquet with the Straw Hats!
First,
we present you the greatest
diva of the deep sea!
Maria Napole!
And the Swing Jazz Orchestra!
Wow! What a sweet voice!
Wow! Maria-sama!
She is rocking my soul! Oh yeah!
And the special guests!
D-Don't tell me...
Their beauty takes your breath away!
The Mermaid Cafe Dancers!
Shut up!
You're gonna die, Sanji!
Their beauty can't be captured
in a picture! No. 1!
--I'm losing my strength...
--Oh no!
--Awesome!
--Fascinating!
Camie!
Ishilly! I'm glad that you're okay!
Here it comes! There's no
having a banquet without it!
--Super I've been waiting for this!
--That's how the Ryugu Palace should be!
Thank you.
Thanks.
Thank you!
Mermaid-chan!
Thank you very much!
Now, King, will you give a toast?
Before I give a toast, I really want
to express my gratitude briefly-jamon.
All of you Straw Hats!
Thanks to you...
It's banquet time!
Cheers!
All right! Let's drink!
I know, I know. Nobody
wants to hear me-jamon.
Bring the food!
Meat!
Eat! Sing! Drink! Dance!
Yummy!
We have plenty more.
Oh yeah? Thanks!
I need more obviously!
You eat a lot!
Come on, sisters, dance with me! Here we go!
Let's dance.
--I'll dance.
--I won't.
--Maybe I'll dance.
--I'll dance, so what?
Yum! You have great snacks on this island!
This island's sake is so good!
I already had it once!
I heard you got caught for that!
Forget about those little things!
Bone...
Are you okay, Hero-san?
That bastard, I didn't think of that!
I'm dying-bone!
Sanji!
You can't push yourself like that, young man!
I think you're gonna die soon.
Nobody cares about me-jamon...
The hairy old man doesn't look happy.
Hey, Straw Hat-san! Don't
be rude to the King!
Luffy-chin! Luffy-chin!
Luffy, raise your glass!
You too, hairy old man!
Uh-huh.
But I want to express my gratitude briefly...
Father-sama!
Shirahoshi.
Cheers!
Cheers-jamon! Oh, whatever-jamon!
Cheers to you guys, too!
Cheers!
It's very good. I wonder if
it's because of the water.
Oh, you can tell the difference, young lady?
I want more!
Why do you look so pale?! It's empty!
I-I can't believe it.
Moonfish! Shake, shake!
Dance more, everybody!
Eat, drink and make some
noise-mi-fa-so-la-ti-do!
What do you want to talk
to me about, pirate girl?
I'm sorry. I thought this was my only
chance to talk to you in private.
What?!
I-I will tell you now!
I have a wife named Otohime
who I swore to love forever!
Although she is dead, I am
not going to cheat on her...
Who is Joy Boy?
I read the Poneglyph in the Sea Forest.
Who is he apologizing to?
You can read it?
I'm a survivor of Ohara.
You don't have to tell me
everything if you don't want to.
No.
I will tell you everything I know.
I trust you people.
Joy Boy was a person from
above ground who lived
during the Hundred Year Void-jamon.
That means more than 800 years ago.
That message was written
to a Mermaid Princess
who was on this island at that time-jamon.
It's a letter of apology for not
keeping his promise to the island.
Promise?
I do not know the details of his promise
but they say somebody will come and
fulfill it on behalf of Joy Boy someday.
That is the story handed
down in our royal family.
So we believe the day will come
and have continued
looking after the Noah for generations
just as we promised him.
When the day comes, the Noah will be put
to its true use for the first time-jamon!
I heard when all the battles
came to an end today,
the half-destroyed Noah was
taken to the Sea Forest...
...by the Sea Kings!
I wonder if Joy Boy had power to
control Sea Kings since he
was going to use the Noah.
No,
the former Mermaid Princess was
the one who had such power-jamon.
That's what I thought.
Then, Princess Shirahoshi
has that same power?
Yes.
I think it awoke completely today.
I am not happy about it.
I know how you feel.
2 years ago at a Sky Island,
I read a Poneglyph indicating where
one of the ancient weapons is.
It was pointing at this island.
The Mermaid Princess who lived
around the same time as Joy Boy...
...was known by a specific name, wasn't she?
Since Princess Shirahoshi has the same
power, she will inherit that name.
Another name for her will be...
...the ancient weapon...
...Poseidon!
Jimbei reveals speaks about
two important matters.
After Whitebeard's death, distribution of
power among pirates in the
New World was decided...
...by none other than one
of the Four Emperors.
And a fierce and epic battle
occurred within the Navy.
Its shocking conclusion...
...becomes a big obstacle for
Luffy as he enters the New World.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Straw Hats Stunned! The
New Fleet Admiral of the Navy!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!