Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Sickle-Sickle...
...Whirlwind!
Oww!
A wind slash!
Here they come! Here they come!
Now!
I won't let you escape...
Yahoo!
Okay! Set sail for Lost Island!
"A Solitary Island in the Distant Sea!
The Legendary Lost Island"
Contacting all squad captains!
Assemble on the deck of Ship #1!
Where's the resource manager?!
--Turn the yard this way!
--No, no! To the right!
Go get repair planks
from the other ships!
Repair Team!
Get to work repairing Ship #1!
Those damn pirates...
They're quicker at running
than I expected.
No worries. It'd be best to
let them go for now, anyway.
What do you mean?
They went to such dangerous lengths
to escape from this island.
Why do you think that is?
Have you forgotten
this island has a legend?
The story about the dragons'
nest on Lost Island...
What? Are you saying they...?!
It's only a guess.
But if so, they'll wind up
being the perfect guides there.
Reporting to Commodore Nelson?
Yes...
There will be no need for that.
Sir! But...!
The Dragonite I seek...
The elixir of immortality...
As if I'd ever hand it over
to the likes of Nelson Royal!
I will have it!
To become a flawless
Eric the Whirlwind!
What's taking so long?!
Commodore, sir! Please have this!
That's not what I mean!
--Commodore Nelson Royal!
--Oh! It's about time!
You have a report from Eric, I assume?
No. It's a message from a soldier
working at Warship Island.
"Eric has located the
legendary Millennial Dragon."
He goes on to say that all ships
are presently busy repairing damage
that the flagship received.
Curse you, Eric...
Why've you not reported to me
after finding the Millennial Dragon?!
Are you planning to take the
Dragonite all for yourself?!
You're nothing more than a hired soldier.
Our main forces will now
head for Warship Island!
All ships, move out!
Lost Island, huh?
The map doesn't have any islands
in the waters around Warship Island
that fit the bill...
Hey! Grandpa Ryu!
Which way should we go?!
Hey.
I think he went to sleep again!
Sorry for the wait, everyone!
The food's ready!
Did she cook again?!
No one was waiting for her food!
Oh! Sanji!
Whew, what a relief!
So you made today's meal--?!
Grandpa Ryu!
Eat lots, okay?
Oh! Food!
Food!
Hot!
Why, you...!
Grandpa Ryu!
Apis!
Are you okay?
Sheesh. I made all that food
and it goes to waste!
Can't you just make some more, then?
The point is we shouldn't waste food!
What is it?
Lost Island...
The dragons' nest...
It's east of Warship Island...
So that's where Lost Island is?!
Grandpa Ryu said he just remembered!
We know where!
Lost Island is east of Warship Island!
Grandpa Ryu said so!
That's right!
Usopp! Take the wheel!
You got it!
Alright! Let's rush
straight for Lost Island!
Dammit! You better eat all of that!
Yep! Leave it to me!
They've changed course?
Yes, sir! The pirate ship appears
to be headed for the waters
east of Warship Island!
So they're making their move...
Turn the bows eastward!
Full speed ahead!
We're now going to close
in on the Straw Hat Pirates!
Cannoneers to the gun batteries!
All ships, prepare for Level 3 combat!
Our destination...
...is Lost Island.
All ships, move out!
--Here, Zoro.
--Yeah.
--Here you go, Zoro.
--Here, Zoro.
--Yeah.
--Zoro.
Here, Zoro.
Can't you hand 'em
to me without talking?
Lost Island is at the
end of this great ocean!
What kind of island could it be?!
Hey!
Usopp! See anything?!
Nope, nothing!
No?
Man, we've come a long way, but
there's no sign of an island at all...
Are we sure about this?
Yeah...
And then there's Grandpa Ryu...
I wish he'd remember
some more details or something...
Oh! I know!
Let's bonk Grandpa Ryu
in the head with this!
Think maybe then the shock'll
help him remember something else?
Knock it off!
Hey! Grandpa Ryu! We're almost there!
We're almost to Lost Island!
And it's there, right? The dragons' nest?
And if you go to the dragons' nest,
you'll get better, right?!
What?
You're so goofy, thanking me!
We're not even there yet!
They followed us, huh?
What's that? Smoke?
Oh, well! We'll see when we get closer!
Urgh!
That's not true! I don't think
you're troubling me at all!
What's your problem?!
--It turned into an argument at some point.
--Hey! Grandpa Ryu!
--Hey! Are you listening?
--It looks more like Apis is
--Pretending to sleep isn't fair!
--the only one who's angry, though...
--Hey, say something!
--Do you think we should stop her?
A... ship?
But something's definitely
not right about it...
Awesome! Nami! Check it out!
I already am...
Look! Look at me!
--The pirate ship!
--This can't be real!
What the--?!
I-It vanished!
What's going on?!
Hey! What just happened?!
Why did they disappear?!
I-I have no idea!
--All ships, full stop!
--Yes, sir!
Tell everyone to wait on
standby until my next orders!
Yes, sir!
Continue moving forward.
You can't be serious! There's no
telling what's in the waters ahead!
It's too risky!
That again?
Then have them prepare a small craft.
You're not seriously going to...!
That's right. I'm going on my own.
Huh? It's just fog...
I thought Nami was in
big trouble again or something...
What in the world's going on?!
What was that?
Our own ship was right in front of us...
And then we went right through it... right?
I can't see anything at all!
It was almost like... a mirage...
A mirage? That's it!
I read about this a long time ago!
It said temperature differences
between warm and cold ocean water
can create mirages at sea!
Is this a mirage, too?
Urgh! What's the deal with this sea?!
Dammit! What're you doing?!
Shut up! I can't help it,
you damn bastard!
Sanji-kun! Zoro!
Let's raise the sails! Undo the ropes!
Yes, Nami-san!
You stay in the cabin!
No! I'm going to stay
by Grandpa Ryu's side!
You idiot! There's nothing you
can do by staying with him!
I'm sure he's feeling lonesome!
I hafta hurry to him!
Hey!
Just sit down and shut up!
Hurry! We need to hurry back
down and get out of danger!
For some reason it seems...
...like this sea's trying
to push the ship back.
Grandpa Ryu!
Don't worry! This storm is no big deal at--!
No!
Zoro!
Grandpa Ryu! No! What are you saying?!
We will save you! Don't give up!
We promised we'd go
to your nest together!
Gum-Gum...
...Lasso!
Nami-san! There's light over there!
That's the eye of the typhoon!
Hey! I see an island below that light!
We're going to land there!
Luffy!
Don't worry! Leave it to me!
We're taking him to
the dragons' nest, right?!
Yeah!
Stormy seas surround the island...
It's almost like they're trying
to keep people away from it...
That must be why nobody's
ever found it before, huh?
But it seems more like a castle
that's sunk into the sea than an island...
Whoa! Check it out!
Doesn't that seem shaped like a dragon?!
This must be where the
Millennial Dragon lives after all!
Wow! Dragons sure are skillful!
You idiot! It was obviously
humans who made this building!
Well, whatever.
We made it to Lost Island!
But does anyone even live here anymore?
The whole place has been
swallowed up by Mother Nature...
Say, where do you suppose
the dragons' nest is?
Hey!
Grandpa Ryu!
I'm talking to you, Grandpa Ryu!
Sheesh! We're at the dragon nest
island now! Come on, wake up!
What did he say?
He says he's not sure...
He says this might not be Lost Island...
--What?!
--You can't be serious!
We went all the way through
that stormy sea just to get here!
Apis!
Look at the top there!
We could look down at the
whole island from up there!
Yeah! Trying to figure things
out here won't get us anywhere!
--Let's go have a look!
--Okay!
Alright! Let's go!
Stupid Nami makes
the men do all the work...
It's like, "Try pushing it yourself!"
Hey, you! Less complaining
and more pushing!
Don't start getting cocky, you!
Quit complaining and push!
Ah! Nami-san is so nice
when she's snappy!
If only!
It's a city...
Wow! Everything is broken everywhere!
Did people really used to live here?
Obviously, given all of these houses.
Then why's there no one here now?
Who knows? Maybe they found
a better island to live on.
The Millennial Dragon's mark...
Did the Millennial Dragon play
with children here on this island?
Hey! Are you guys friends
of the Millennial Dragon too?
Come on, Apis. Don't get left behind!
Guess what?!
These birds told me something!
They said there's a building
on the summit with a dragon mark!
For reals?!
It might be the dragons' nest!
Nami! Hurry up!
Wait for me!
Ready... go!
We finally made it... I can't go on...
Thanks for showing us the way!
We've sure come up a long ways.
Good work, everyone!
Yep! Good work!
This painting is of the
Millennial Dragon, right?
Yeah, it is.
This building is the dragons' nest?
This place?
Hold on! Where's the entrance?
How do we get inside?
This is the door!
You're so stupid!
There's no handle
or keyhole anywhere!
How're you supposed to open it?!
H-Hey!
Apis! That pendant... You don't mean...
It's actually a key that opens
the door to the dragons' nest?
Yeah.
Huh?
I can't reach...
--You're so little, Apis!
--So what?!
Alright! Leave it to me!
Huh?
Huh?!
We're alive... right?
Yeah, it seems that way...
Say, what was that about it
being a key just a minute ago?
Here!
Well, in any case, we're inside now.
It worked out!
But... what is this place?
Yeah... What is it?
What is this?
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Hey, now! Is this really Lost Island?!
See! Look at that! This means...
Look out!
That bastard!
He followed us all the way here?!
Alright! Let's fight! You too, Zoro!
I said stop already!
Oh, no! Now there's a huge armada!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Showdown in the Ruins!
Tense Zoro vs. Eric!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!