Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates, once
attained everything this world has to offer.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner (･∀･)
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m aiming at hasn’t changed
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
Finally!
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Finally, the Great Pirate Era is coming to an end!
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Master Z!
Meanwhile, the Straw Hats have left the Fish-Man Island and are headed for the New World.
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where they instigated an all-out war
against the New Fish-Man Pirates,
against the New Fish-Man Pirates.
where they instigated an all-out war
against the New Fish-Man Pirates,
"Z's Ambition!
Lily the Little Giant!"
who were holding a grudge against humans
and looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom.
Luffy finally defeated
Hordy in a fierce fight
Luffy finally defeated Hordy, the captain of
the New Fish-Man Pirates, in a fierce fight
and thwarted his plot.
Luffy finally defeated Hordy, the captain of
the New Fish-Man Pirates, in a fierce fight
and thwarted his plot.
Wh-What's going on here?!
All right! Spread the sail!
Are they really the Navy?!
There's the Sunny!
and thwarted his plot. However...
Franky's there!
Here, there, everywhere! 360 degrees!
and thwarted his plot.
Let's set sail!
Looks like he's ready to go!
We're totally surrounded!
Have it your way, instead
of the Fish-Man Island,
Take me out for a fun stroll again!
Listen. You all need to know
the two biggest changes...
Only the Navy could accomplish this. They know every move that we make.
Here we go finally!
I'll have my vengeance against you all!
"Finally Time to Go!
Goodbye, Fish-Man Island!"
I want to go to a real forest above ground!
...which have occurred in the New World.
We're totally surrounded. There is nowhere to run.
Monkey D. Luffy. I know your name now.
You two, stop talking in such a cool manner!
Okay, fine!
First, the Navy Headquarters
led by Sakazuki...
I'll take you there next time!
The weather...
They're closing in on us!
...has become an even more
powerful force for justice.
Come to the New World!
What are we gonna do, Luffy?!
We promise!
Oh? Where did he go?
THE FISH-MAN ISLAND--CORAL
HILL "MERMAID CAFE"
And second,
Madam Sharley,
Sure, wait for me there.
Luffy-chin and his friends
are leaving the island.
the Blackbeard Pirates have advanced.
Once we pass through this deep sea,
There's some business I want
to settle with you, too.
we'll get to the ultimate sea!
Oh yeah? Why don't you go and send them off?
Go forward!
Let's go!
Okay!
I can't leave it in your
hands - that's too dangerous!
Let's keep moving forward like this!
Madam! Can we go, too?!
You fools! Why did you kick him out?!
Guys!
I'll kick your ass all over the New World...
Why didn't you just punch
him and tie him up here!
Guys!
What? We'd need to close the cafe then.
To the New World!
They outnumber us!
I love it even when you...
There's no time to argue!
Tourists will start coming back
since that stupid Hordy is gone.
...and make the Fish-Man Island my territory!
Go find him now!
Usopp, get ready to fire at them! Chopper, fill the tank with cola!
"To the New World! Heading
for the Ultimate Sea!"
So I need you to give your best
for the cafe like before, girls.
I don't care anymore!
They were sent by Big Mam.
This is not a good time!
You insolent brat!
You can count on us, Madam!
I'll take the front!
Leave the sides to us!
"Many Problems Lie Ahead! A Trap
Awaiting in the New World!"
We don't have any sweets
to pay them for this month.
I'll handle the rear!
Bring it on!
Hordy and the others destroyed the factory
We're ready!
Usopp, wait!
and the undamaged sweets have
After leaving the Fish-Man Island,
There's no need to fight.
What? The crystal ball?
been sent to the banquet
since everybody wanted the
the ship ascends toward the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
Why not?
Don't worry. I won't need it again.
Third Gear!
Straw Hats to have them!
--Here you go.
--Oh, thank you!
I will never again try to see the future.
Gum-Gum...
It's kelp tea - a special
product of the Fish-Man Island.
...Giant Pistol!
It aids in digestion so do
your stomach a favor with it.
I wonder if we can explain the situation.
Straw Hat destroying the Fish-Man Island...
--It's going very well!
--Yeah, almost too well.
She is like a monster who would
destroy a whole country for sweets!
Oh?
The warships are vanishing one by one!
It stopped raining too!
I never wanted to see such a horrible future.
I'm starting to get hungry. Let's do it now!
It's good! How thoughtful of
you, Minister of the Right!
I thought so.
One of the Four Emperors...
What's going on?
Big Mam!
Wait until I finish making this, Luffy.
What we're seeing was a mirage only found in this area.
You are treating us most graciously
- I hope we're not imposing!
I'll be so happy if my prevision
is not accurate this time.
"She Loves Sweets! Big Mam
of the Four Emperors!"
A mirage?!
No, no!
I'm so relieved!
There are no words to express
my thanks to you all, so...
Don't drop your guard yet.
She is more afraid than anybody because
she knows it was always accurate.
If I'm...
...right...
The future she saw may not happen soon.
We have to say goodbye to this island soon.
After the banquet reaches its
climax, it comes to an end.
How nice!
What the hell is that?!
It could be a year from now or more.
It's called Shower Tempo.
Do you wanna use it?
What?! They'll give us their treasure?!
Huge raindrops!
Do not mention saying goodbye, "Nose"pp-sama!
There is no reason to
believe it wasn't accurate.
Oh? Me?
Wow!
What's this weather?!
That's really nice!
I'm okay. I just brushed myself 2 days ago.
But, Madam, Luffy-chin and his
friends would never do such...
We're in the Maubeugemour Sea!
No, don't cry! I'm sorry!
I wonder if Luffy-sama and the others
are doing okay, Nami-chin-sama.
Momemomejuban?!
And my name is Usopp.
By the way, doesn't that
cloud look like cotton candy?
Camie!
No, "Maubeugemour"! Also known as the "Ill-Tempered Sea"!
Oh, where did Franky go?
They're fine!
Forgive me for suspecting your friends.
We're finally gonna become
a rich pirate group!
He left to learn how to operate the ship.
You can't eat it!
Home to weather conditions you've never seen or heard of before!
Seems like  he needs to learn
a little trick to ascend.
Oh yeah? It's not sweet, sweet cotton candy?
Things in life usually aren't that easy...
I know what you want to say. I can
trust the Straw Hat boy, right?
What? There is something sweet
and yummy in the bathroom?
Hey Usopp, do you wanna go look for him too?
So... this is the list of treasures
that were stolen from the chamber.
Oh yeah! Looks pretty sweet and yummy!
--Hail?
--It's such a dangerous sea!
No, we better not. I did some research
Uh-huh!
Nami-san, please! Turn around!
It's gonna hit us!
and found out that his
There are so many! The Tamate Box, again...
THE FISH-MAN ISLAND - THE OUTSKIRTS
OF CORAL HILL NEAR THE CANDY FACTORY
360...
bounty is over 200 million.
What?! Mine's only 50 berries...
...Pound Phoenix!
Chopper, step away from the cloud.
Tamate Box?
Damn!
Hey look, Zoro, Sanji!
There he is! That was easy!
IN THE VICINITY OF THE CANDY FACTORY TOWN
These are some gifts! Take them!
Oh, cotton candy?
He got knocked out cold already
by your punch. How pathetic!
Yeah, thanks!
Now there's an avalanche from the sky!
How scary!  I don't wanna
eat that cloud anymore!
Damn Straw Hat!
Mil Fleurs!
Luffy-sama and everybody, are
you really going to leave now?!
Gigantesco Mano!
There is so much treasure
scattered around here.
I can't believe he kicked me out!
Is that furry king really
going to give us all of this?
It's so relaxing!
Nice, Robin!
We just became friends! Stay
here at least one more day!
But,
My first bath on the Sunny in 2 years!
I have so much treasure in my belly.
Cool! We can buy lots of meat!
It started raining hard!
No! A week!
I can't believe he was storing
all of this in his gloopy body!
I'm gonna buy, like, 100 pirate ships and
kill the Straw Hats in the New World...
I hope it's just rain!
It's so luxurious with a view of the deep
sea - it's as beautiful as the night sky.
No! Just one more year!
You've been crying since the
first time we met, Yowahoshi!
What is it this time?!
D-Don't tell me...
Don't they need you on the deck?
I-I am sorry!
The water split!
It's okay. I'll go up before
we ride an upward current.
T-T-The treasure!
1, 2, 3!
I will stop being a crybaby!
So pretty much anything goes here?
It's all gone!
We're sinking!
If a sea monster strikes,
they can take care of it.
If nothing is done, we're gonna end up back in the deep sea!
--Alright! Let's go back to the palace!
--How?
I can't even buy a hard candy now!
I never thought the day like this would come!
No, we'll hit a rock and drown before that.
We need a flying fish.
Oh my treasure-chan!
--Which way is the town, Zoro?
--That way.
Hurry up, Usopp!
The Mermaid Princess of the Fish-Man Island
Don't say it so casually!
Where is it?!
who I've dreamed about is
crying as we're leaving!
Just one minute.
--Okay, let's head in the opposite direction.
--Hey!
What an amazing phenomenon!
We want a giant fish so
the ropes gotta be strong!
Now's not the time to be impressed!
Sanji-kun!
How do we escape?!
I wanna live here for a year or two!
Punch.
--Cut.
--Kick.
Okay, I think this is good.
Alright!
No, that won't do!
How is everything-jamon, Jimbei?
Yes, me too!
All right, Minister of the Left?
Leave it to the Sunny!
Finished!
I sing about a dream life on the
Fish-Man Island on my latest single!
Are the members of the
Sun Pirates doing well?
Please show us mercy!
Ta-dah!
Coup de...
Oh? You guys are having fun.
It was all unexpected! Hordy and the
others destroyed the factory and...
...Burst!
Yes. In fact, they have too much energy
and they are a bit out of control.
When you wake up in the morning you
say "Good mor-ningyo (mermaid)!"
I hadn't even thought about it
on our way to the Fish-Man Island
That's none of our concern! Grr!
--In the cafe at the night, you say "Good eve-ningyo!"
--Oh, my Mermaids!
because I was excited to see the island
But I cannot believe they accepted it.
Yeah!
I was planning on snatching some
for myself so I'm very hungry!
but if we catch a deep-sea fish
now, Sanji can cook it for us!
--Cool!
--He did it!
Even I was surprised when
I heard about it-jamon.
That's a good idea!
I hope it'll go with cola!
You pay us with sweets once a month.
Why don't you stay here, Nosebleed-kun?
I had never expected the Sun
Pirates becomes Big Mam's allies.
Cook, huh? That's a good idea!
And we allow you to use Mama's name.
PEKOMS-- A MEMBER OF THE BIG MAM PIRATES
What did you just call me, Moss Head?!
Can't wait to have a drink in
celebration of entering the New World!
That was the agreement, wasn't it? Grr!
Who are you calling Moss Head, you fool?!
Is it going well?
Now, which one should we catch?
Now, I don't want to say this to you
seeing as how we're business partners
It's baking hot now.
Your Majesty.
I have to say that while she is not a
reasonable person she lets us
I want something that looks yummy!
--It's sweltering...
--That was close.
We have to tell them.
That one would taste good
fried up with some salt!
do what we like.
but you know how scary Mama can be!
If you make her mad, she will...
About the Tamate Box that
they gave to Big Mam.
But I'm impressed, Nami-san. You know about the weather in the New World.
Well, I was worried because it must be hard
A fried fish with salt sounds good!
When someone opens it, there
will be a huge explosion!
for a man like you to work under somebody...
I studied as much as I could about the New World over the past 2 years.
...destroy you all!
How about slicing it in half and grilling it?
He's cute when he does that!
...other than Fisher Tiger.
Like an eel, huh?
I want a beer when it's hot.
Now, what are you gonna do?! Grr!
You don't have to worry.
Oh! That one looks good too! It
would be yummy with some mayonnaise!
--I'm hungry!
--Me too.
But, look at that!
I don't mind working for someone.
Look - a crowd.
Oh yeah! We caught a deep-sea fish!
Plus, in the New World,
Which one?
Oh, this is the Candy Factory!
Pappagu told me about it!
the best you can do to protect your crew is
Unfortunately, most of it was ruined by the horrible weather.
No, it doesn't look good at all.
We're doomed! One of the Four
Emperors wants to kill us!
Yeah?
ally yourself with one of the Four Emperors.
No matter how you cook
it, it won't taste good.
I hope we can find a flying fish here.
We're gonna go to the New World just to die!
What?!
I guess they're making
those yummy sweets here!
You think so? Well, whatever's fine with me!
But I had already set aside some.
Oh yeah? It seems to me like you
Do you think she'll forgive us
Hey, Candy Factory!
are doing it for the benefit
of the Fish-Man Island.
Just give me some time and I'll cook something.
Second Gear!
if we send all the treasures
that we get from now on?!
Even after Whitebeard's death,
I'm sure Sanji can cook up any fish!
Straw Hat Luffy!
First, I'll just whip up some carpaccio.
Luffy-san, is the banquet over already?!
this island remained safe under
Big Mam's name because you
We cannot tell them that they
already sent her a bomb!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Pistol!
Today's soup will be deep-sea fish bouillabaisse. What should I make for the main dish?
Luffy-kun, why are you here?!
connected us to her.
Yeah, I ate a lot!
I knew you wanted that one!
But those explosives are 10 years old.
No, it's just a coincidence.
The meat was good but those sweets
Hey, isn't it a little too big?!
We are supposed to protect the island
Maybe they won't explode,
Minister of the Right.
Okay, it's done! Come and get it!
from the Fish-Man Island were unbelievable!
Hurry, hurry! Catch it!
Yeah!
Your Majesty, you are so positive!
but we are wanted pirates so...
Special Attack - Capture Star!
Looks great!
Yes, the Ryugu Palace is very humid
Food! Food! Food! Food!
What?!
However, Your Majesty!
and we don't even know if Big
Mam is going to open it herself!
No, Straw Hat-san!
Yeah!
Let's eat!
We got a deep-sea fish!
I am thinking about breaking
away from Big Mam.
Don't talk about them!
Eat it and wait. It's deep-sea fish carpaccio.
Then let's just hope for their safety!
Oh, old Mr. Catfish, it's you!
I wanna eat it already!
Are you sure it's a fish?
Looks like an old man!
Oh, are you going to accept
Luffy-kun's invitation?
What are you two whispering about?
--There's nothing here!
--No, it's on the platter.
Did he say "sweets"?! Who are they?!
An old man?
There is a platter here but nothing is on it!
Hey, Jimbei.
What is this?
What are you talking...
It got eaten!
It's a Log Pose for the New
World. Take it with you.
Oh yeah, he's Straw Hat Luffy! Definitely!
Join...
It's gone!
Oh? Huh?
...my crew!
--Boo! Boo!
--Did you guys eat it already?!
What is that notorious pirate doing here?
Hey, hey, not again! They keep coming!
I cannot believe you were going to
go there with a single-needle one!
Yes. I've made up my mind.
No, we didn't!
Well, um...
Then who did?!
Reel it in already, Usopp!
Hey brat! Which sweets
are you talking about?!
Oh, what's that?
But the pirates' world is all
about obligation and honor.
Maybe the Maubeugemour Sea is haunted!
I can't, I can't! The
ship is gonna flip over!
A new Log Pose? Wow, that's cool!
Our contracts are made by exchanging cups of
Well, Mr. Pekoms, let me explain...
I can't believe this! Is it a Russian doll?
sake and a verbal agreement - no documents.
Who are you?!
Yummy!
Do you think something happened?
You're not a Fish-Man, are you?
So we have to be really determined
when we terminate a contract.
There are 3 needles. Why?
The ship is shaking and  I
hear them yelling on the deck.
You came to buy sweets?
I just finished stuffing myself full of them!
Look at the Log Pose that
you have been using.
A ghost!
I shouldn't have trusted them!
My concern is that there is a chance
The soup is all gone!
What?!
that Big Mam will turn her
anger toward this island.
What?!
One-Sword Style - 360 Pound Phoenix!
What's that?! Something came out!
What's going on here?!
He just said he ate them!
A bug?
It's still moving a little bit! I thought
it gathered enough logs already.
A bug ghost!
--Did the bug eat it?!
--No way.
W-Well... There is an explanation...
Nice, Zoro!
Boy... You do not have to feel responsible
for everything-jamon, Jimbei.
It did. And from now on, it would
take only half a day to record logs.
What's going on here?
Oh?! A talking lion!
Hey Sanji, look at that!
But I guess that's not such a big
deal. We've got something similar.
On the first half of the Grand Line,
The strawberries are gone!
If that is going to happen,
so be it. I have a plan-jamon.
you let the Log Pose record the
magnetic waves of the next island
I see! That's great!
Atchoo!
Whoa, what's wrong? Did you catch a cold?
--What?! The corn is gone!
--Really?!
A deep-sea fish, huh? Can't wait to cook it!
and navigated your ship as it told you.
Maybe somebody's talking about me.
We just welcomed 70 thousand rowdy
Dammit! This is unforgivable!
Well, first of all, how did you get burned?
You're popular.
But on the second half of
Luffy, it went outside!
fellows as new soldiers from
the Fish-Man District today.
the Grand Line, on top of the
sea current and the climate,
I have a bad feeling.
Listen to this! You won't believe it!
This lion's got an unique face!
there are some islands that change their
--The fridge is empty!
--What?!
There are 2 more fish inside that one!
So do not worry about us-jamon.
magnetic waves, the only thing
you can normally count on.
What?! Are you messing with me?!
Where did it go?! I lost it!
But, is the ship really moving forward?
--What's going on?
--We found a bug ghost!
And for some islands, the
magnetic waves just disappear.
And if we lose Big Mam's
Jolly Roger as protection,
It feels like we're sinking...
And a food thief!
No way!
Yuck! You fool!
What?! Then we can't reach those islands!
What is that?!
Pekoms.
there is another one that I want to use!
What do you mean "thief"?!
If you only have one
needle, you will get lost.
What?
Making such threatening faces doesn't
help us in collecting the sweets.
A skull with a straw hat on-jamon.
But what if you have 3 needles?
I just ate what I found sitting around.
It's a giant sea snake! No!!
Huh? Me?
One of them is moving just
like the old one but...
I see! I like that Jolly Roger too!
That's what we call a "thief"!
Alright, get closer! Let's eat that too!
What?! Why are you doing this to me, Luffy-san?!
Let's settle this peacefully-soir.
The tea party is 4 days from now-bon.
…the other two look settled.
We have too much to carry already!
It got out!
They each record the magnetic
waves from different islands.
Wait! Don't tell me it's...
--Where?
--Oh? Where did it go?
We can make it on time if we
leave here tomorrow morning-jour.
All the food in the fridge is gone too! The booze as well!
King-sama!
That means you can choose whichever
your gut tells you and advance.
Whitestrom!
There's another odd one! Who are you?
W-W-We have a problem!
What?!
It's a giant whirlpool that appears
out of the blue in the deep sea,
Where did it go?!
Whether you live or die hangs on that point.
King-sama!
like a living dragon!
Bon to meet you, you half-boiled pirates.
You're...
What is it, Minister of the Right?
Why are you in such a rush?
What?
...a human?!
A good navigator can tell
I just remembered something serious!
My name is Baron Tamago-soir!
A whirlpool in the deep sea?!
How dare you steal my food!
BARON TAMAGO-- A MEMBER OF THE
BIG MAM PIRATES (LONGFEET TRIBE)
which way is safer to go
Relating to giving all the treasures
to Luffy-kun and the others.
What the hell is that?! This
is dangerous, isn't it?
Here it is!
by looking at slight
movements of the needles.
Tamago (egg)?!
Oh?
What it basically tells you is
the wilder the needle moves,
Damn!
If they find them, could you to
tell them to return the Tamate Box!
Remember my name at least-s'il vous plait!
--Hey, catch her, Franky!
--I got it!
Damn, those fools!
the more dangerous the island is!
I can't get caught now!
What?! Oh no! It must be the Whitestrom!
What are you saying?!
Something is happening on the island
Stop!
I will not tell them to return
something I already gave them!
that is causing the change
in its magnetic waves.
When a ship gets caught up in the whirlpool,
Now, you gentlemen...
it'll end up somewhere far
off usually missing its crew.
But...
What?! I don't like this! I'd
rather not know about it!
She took Franky down! She's strong!
Did you just say you ate the sweets
from this factory-c'est si bon?
What?! That means the crew
all died, doesn't it?
What?! It will explode if someone opens it?!
You'll see if it's dangerous?!
Looks like we gotta go all out.
No way! Break that Log Pose!
Why did you rig it with explosives?
This is dangerous! Let's get away!
He looks like a compass.
Yes, I did! I wanna have
some more if they have any!
Why? You have to navigate
safely in order to stay alive.
Well...
A ship will end up somewhere far off?
After the contents of the Tamate
Box were stolen 10 years ago,
I have no choice!
They don't. That's why we
don't know what to do-bon!
Take the Mini-Mini Full Rebound!
So it's like the wormhole of my dreams?!
I thought, in case another thief
comes, we have to teach him a lesson.
Let's see.
No, it's not, you fool!
D-Dammit!
That big mark on the factory is...
Guys! We have to get away
from that whirlpool now!
So we set up a box-full of explosives
to explode when someone opens it.
No!
...the Jolly Roger of the great pirate
and our boss- Charlotte Lingling-soir.
There! Our navigator's back! Let's go, fools!
The one in the middle is wobbling a
lot! That must be where the party is!
Oh, wow!
It claims this island as Big Mam's territory
- she is one of the Four Emperors.
Augh! What is that fish doing there?!
Since I am in charge of the treasure
chamber and the Tamate Box...
H-H-He was listening!
She's...
Oh, we caught it!
What do you think you're doing?! We
can't advance if we're pulling that!
Which means, the Fish-Man Island is
protected under Big Mam's name-bon!
All right. All right.
Gigantic!
Luffy! You stay quiet!
If Luffy-kun and the others
come back with the treasures,
How cool is that!?
See? The fish got caught in the whirlpool!
I'll choose which way to go from now on!
Sounds like a nice person! I wanna
meet your boss! Big Mam, huh?
You're amazing, mega young girl!
--No! Get it back!
--Yeah!
give them the reason and ask
them to return it to us.
No way! I'm the captain!
No! We're gonna cut it loose!
Run!
Please Captain! Listen to what
the navigator has to say!
I am sorry.
Now, come to me!
Don't mistake our arrangement.
We have a business arrangement.
What?! We wanted to eat the deep-sea fish!
But what if they open it
before they get here...
--Oh no!
--She's gonna stab us!
Which is more important to
you - the fish or your life?!
In exchange for 10 tons of sweets a month,
That is my concern, too.
Nami-san's so cute when she gets frightened!
No hard feelings!
How could you get in this much trouble
while I was away for only 10 minutes?!
King-sama, Minister of the Right!
Luffy-sama and the others just came back.
I'll fight you!
we allow them to use the mark-bon.
So cute! So cute...
Alright! Here I go!
The B-side of the single
is "The Requiem for Us"!
Franky, Coup de Burst?!
Oh, so they are okay?!
--10 tons?
--That's right.
No, it's super too late for that!
What?
All right, guys!
I am so relieved. I guess I
was just worrying too much.
Mama loves sweet candies
more than anything-soir.
We're ready to go!
Nice, he lifted her up!
--Huh?
--Stop "Huh?"-ing me!
Gum-Gum Propeller!
What's going on?!
Sweets from the Fish-Man
Island are her favorite.
We're gonna get caught in the whirlpool!
What?!
Propeller Wind-Down!
Den-san taught me how to ascend too!
We're in big trouble!
All the treasures?!
So we'll wait until tomorrow morning.
Oh no!
Shall we go?
To Big Mam?!
You gave them away?!
No, Baron, I already told you.
--It's too late!
--I don't wanna die!
Okay!
She said she was gonna destroy the
island if she couldn't get her sweets!
Let's go!
The factory's giant cooking
machines are broken
Hold onto the ship!
Wh-What? She can't swim?
Can you believe how crazy she is?! I mean
- if it were meat, I could understand!
and we need at least 2 weeks to repair them!
Luffy-chin!
Young girl, I'm coming for you!
Straw!
But don't worry!
I'm gonna help with repairing the factory!
Are you gonna be okay without a guide?
That's not acceptable-soir.
I really stood up to her!
Maybe, she's a Devil Fruit eater.
Hey Tamago! Why can't you wait?!
You stood up to one of the Four Emperors?!
Dad, I'm sorry...
Is your boss's mind as small as his balls?
He's one of the Four Emperors, isn't he?
We're fine! We had a lot
of fun on our way here!
You talked back to Big Mam?!
I don't think I can make it...
How fun!
Yeah, he's right! We don't need a guide!
This is super not good!
Wow! You are so tough, Luffy-sama!
It's not "he." Mama is a great
woman pirate-vous plait.
Even the Sunny can't endure
a whirlpool this wild!
Why is she shrinking?
Man's journey always ends up in hell!
That's not the point!
I don't think she has balls-jour.
I blame Luffy and the rest of you!
Yeah, yeah! We want a war, you bastard!
My head is spinning!
Oh, she's a madam.
"Nose"pp-sama is scary!
How desperate.
Everybody! Come visit someday!
My name is Usopp!
Dad! Dad!
I love sweets!
Can't we get out of the whirlpool somehow?!
Okay, I'm sorry!
I'll come back!
I'll save you at any cost!
And I love you too since you can make them!
Boy, that's not good.
You're the "All Blue" of my heart!
There are no records of someone
escaping the Whitestrom! Because...
Wait for me, Dad!
I have to break away from Big
Mam before it gets complicated.
What a cheap dream.
What's gonna happen if you
can't have them on time?
No one has ever survived!
Dad!
All I want to say is "Thank you"!
You guys should not do anything
to make Big Mam angrier!
Oh, good.
In that case...
Instead of the New World,
we're all going to hell!
--She woke up.
--Young girl, you okay?
I will pray for your safe trip!
The deal is off!
We won't! We're all gonna get killed
since she's one of the Four Emperors!
Hey, you!
Uh-huh!
Luffy! Don't use violence against a lady again!
Vicious members of the
Big Mam Pirates will...
Next time we see you, we will lead
the strongest army on the seafloor!
Hey, this is pretty bad,
Minister of the Right!
You can grow and shrink! That's awesome!
...descend on the island and
destroy it  in no time-vous plait!
I can't believe it!
Ooh mambo!
If they gave the Tamate Box to Big
Mam and if she opens it herself,
He's right!
Destroy the island?!
We will become greater than the
Great Knight Neptune-mi-fa-so-la-ti-do!
I-I was born a Giant but I ate the Mini-Mini Fruit and...
Are you guys nuts? You can't
destroy a country over candies!
she will take it as Luffy-kun's
challenge to her!
This island has just been saved!
Can't wait!
That is a big problem-jamon!
You're a Giant?!
Yes, but this is my usual size now.
Well, he had no choice though.
Um, where is he?
However, I can shrink myself down to 5 millimeters and enlarge myself to the size of the Giants.
What's done is done.
There you are!
I guess it was a tit-for-tat situation
so you couldn't help fighting with her.
Hmmm... You're interesting!
Jimbei!
--Am I?
--Yeah!
You're right! No matter who she was, I'd...
And you're strong too! Although you're small, you took Franky down!
It stopped.
Even when I'm small, I still have the power of the Giants.
The Sunny was not destroyed.
That was easy!
WHOLE CAKE ISLAND SOMEWHERE IN THE NEW WORLD
We hit something and got
bumped out of the whirlpool.
Like this!
You look happy, Mama.
Nami-san...
You're strong!
Why...
In any case, we're alive!
He totally forgot that she ate all of our food.
...did you give all the treasures away?!
ONE OF THE FOUR EMPERORS-- - THE GREAT
PIRATE "BIG MAM" CHARLOTTE LINGLING
I can't wait for the tea party
Where are we?
That's what you're focused on?!
Boy, they're having fun.
four days from now because...
--I'll punch you!
--You already did!
Is there anything else you can do?
What's this black wall?
Yes, I have another technique.
All right! Leff's go thew the New World!
It doesn't seem like the Red Line.
I can get smaller and slip into my enemy's body
We have no future ahead of us!
...I'll get my hands on those delicious
sweets from the Fish-Man Island!
All right! Spread the sail!
This is it! We're doomed!
then expand myself to break him into pieces!
I can't wait and my stomach is
already producing so much acid!
No way!
That way, I can become a Giant!
A ghost!
Meanwhile, near the Candy Factory...
Can't wait! Can't wait! The
sweets from the Fish-Man Island!
Let's set sail!
What do you mean by that?
What is it?
Dammit! Somebody took all the
treasures before I knew it!
Luffy is a rubber man. So instead of breaking into pieces, he stretches.
You guys can't wait either?
It's gonna eat us!
Of course, we can't! They are so good!
Who did this? I'm gonna
kill him at any price!
I can't believe it! You're right, how interesting!
Then why don't you wait for
them inside of my stomach?!
By the way, young girl, what's your name?
With a mountain of treasures
and the secret of the Mermaid
Princess as presents,
My name is Lily Enstomach. People call me "Lily the Glutton"!
I know that person will like me!
I eat a lot for a woman, right?
A monster!
Straw Hat!
Oh, a crowd!
Lily, why are you aboard this ship?
Who are those two carrying heavy loads?
"Why"?
See you, Fish-Man Island!
What is that?!
Straw Hat Luffy! How dare he challenge Mama!
I was waiting for someone
when your ship flew out of the water all of a sudden!
Alright, here we go!
Mama must be really mad-soir.
Who were you waiting for in the middle of nowhere like this?
I wonder what's going to happen-vous plait.
The tea party is 4 days from now.
I was waiting for my dad...
It's going away!
Let's stop by at some island and
get something really sweet. Grr!
Thank you, Straw Hat!
A fin? Don't tell me it's...
I shouldn't be wasting my time like this!
Mama!
Come to eat sweets and meat anytime!
We have to ease her anger
even if just a little bit.
I'm home! Boyoyon!
I can hear it singing. It must be...
I like humans now!
I think that's the best we can do-soir.
Oh! How did it go, Bobbin?
Racoons and robots too!
Luckily, we have so many
treasures-vous plait.
I beat them up and burned the place!
Like I give a damn, you jerk!
How lovely!
Those are my treasures! I'm sure!
Huh? Oh? What about bones?
That country had the best baked goods!
Who the hell are they?!
I will bury them alive!
Take care, Luffy-chin and everybody!
It must have smelled so good
as it burned to the ground!
I stole those treasures!
Give them back to me!
Come to eat octopus balls again!
What's the matter, Lily-chan?
It's a shame but we had no choice.
Calm down! The size of your head doesn't match your body anymore!
You guys! I love you all!
--That's...
--He looks familiar to me. Grr!
Because they couldn't reach
their quotas on time.
The bottle was shattered! What should I do?!
Wow, it's a pod of whales!
1, 2, 3!
Oh, here he is!
We like bones too!
Can I have some snacks?
I finally made it this far by sneaking aboard some Navy boats and warships!
Oh, those scars!
His name is "Wet-Haired"
Caribou. A rising rookie.
We have to kill them if
they don't give us sweets!
Thank you for your concern!
I can't get to my dad!
We'll come back to see you again.
Oh, he's got a 200 million berry bounty.
I don't like people who
don't keep their promises!
Dad? Are you looking for your father?!
When I come back, let's fight again!
H-He's worth 200 million berries?
What kind of man is your father?
Just like I don't like bitter candies!
It's too late to beg for your life!
My dad is the greatest pirate chef in the New World!
Oh yeah! I heard the Fish-Man Island
may not have sweets to pay this month.
Laboon?!
Swamp-Swamp...
A pirate chef? Lily-chan, what's your father's name?
...Gatling Gun!
It's Panz Fry.
I just got word from Pekoms. Do
you want the Fish-Man Island
Princess-sama!
Yeah, I know his name!
to be burned down too?
Is he that famous?
Laboon! Wait for us! We'll come
back here for sure...! For sure!!
He's a top volcano cooking chef!
Luffy-sama!
Volcano cooking?! What's that? Is it delicious?!
Yowahoshi!
Shirahoshi-chan!
I'll fill you with holes!
Oh yeah! I'm getting excited just by thinking about it...
I can't have the sweets
from the Fish-Man Island?!
Laboon! You got so much bigger!
It's my favorite food - churrasco sea monster!
Get them on the Transponder Snail now!
If I can see you again someday,
Rare herbs that only grow around volcanoes
Don't be ridiculous! Laboon should be
in the first half of the Grand Line.
and million-year-old salt crystals  from between molten rocks.
I promise I won't be a crybaby!
He's gigantic! He can't fit
through the hole in the Red Line!
All sprinkled on sea monster meat and stewed in a volcano
Amazing!
It's like a miracle to come
across a pod of Island Whales.
to cook it up quick!
Take me out for a fun stroll again!
Some of them have scars like Laboon.
Sounds yummy!
Destroy the island?!
Mr. Pekoms!
That's not all! The best one is...
A stroll? Do you wanna go to
your mother's grave again?
Are you guys nuts?
Go on!
Yeah, the scars look the same! I can't
believe it! But it's not Laboon?!
A frying pan filled with an assortment of foods from the sea and mountains...
You can't destroy a country over candies!
No. I want to go somewhere further next time!
This island has just been saved!
Gather up all of the crew!
Time to ship out Binks's Brew!
...all cooked over a volcano! It's called Thousand-Person Paella!
I want to go to a real forest above ground!
Laboon! Stop! Listen to me!
Just one taste and...
What is that?!
It's me from the Rumbar Pirates! Brook!
ﾉit's like slipping into a dream!
Oh yeah, you've never been
out of the sea, have you?
It's just like running  through a field of flowers in heaven!
Come to your senses!
That's a different whale!
A turtle?
Okay, fine!
I wanna eat it! I wanna run in heaven!
I'll take you there next time!
Laboon!
We're not on a whale watching crew!
Heavenly food! Yeehaw!
It's still dangerous out here!
No, I don't have time for this!
Now, let me call the roll to make sure
no one got lost in the whirlpool!
You started it!
I've heard about Panz Fry before too.
--Nami-san!
--Yes!
You're a Devil Fruit eater!
Robin-chan!
Here.
Okay, we gotta get out of here now.
He steals food from the Government, the Navy, and other pirates
Of course I am!
Will you promise?
Yeah, trust me!
I can't believe it-bon.
The ship will be destroyed if
those giant whales crash into us!
and likes nothing better than to cook for starving people.
But you're just Zoan type, aren't you?
I promise!
They aren't even half-boiled, they are raw.
Why didn't you call our names?
Hey, Luffy! We have to help
you keep that promise.
Sanji-kun! Six more of us
are alive and well here too!
Drop dead!
What should I do with those
fearless rookies-jour?
He sounds like...
Luffy-san, a promise is something
you have to keep at any cost.
Nami-san, what should we do?!
...a hero!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Let's not do anything.
A Hero? I'm flattered!
Yeah, we shouldn't do anything,
fools! Let's watch the whales now!
Then, Shirahoshi, I promise you too!
I have no time to be flattered!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Nami-chin-sama!
What's wrong with you?!
Enough with that. Tell us what's going on.
Me too!
Since they're such giant whales,
they're creating a current.
Okay. I was pirating around with Dad for a long time
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Okay, me too!
Me too!
It must be Mama! Grr! I told them
what was going on a while ago.
It'll be dangerous to go against it!
Me too!
Me too, of course!
but he went missing all of a sudden a couple weeks ago.
Tighten the sails!
B-Big Mam is calling in person?!
We all promise her so...
Turn the ship in the direction
that the whales are heading!
...We won't let her down!
Okay!
They say the Navy took him.
Oh yeah! This is where Laboon came from.
I was asking around going island to island
We promise!
Are any of you related to him?
then I read in the paper that he'll be taken to Impel Down.
E-Everybody!
Be careful, Brook!
Is anyone looking for a calf
who got lost 50 years ago?
Impel Down?
Logia Devil Fruit eaters who think
they're invincible often die young.
Why is that? He's a hero!
So don't cry anymore!
Don't worry! He's doing okay
on the other side of the world!
Because Dad has a 320 million berry bounty.
Half-boiled challengers
always disappoint me-soir.
Over 300 million?! Really?!
Okay!
According to Luffy-san, he's very big now.
He kept stealing food from the Government and the Navy so the price went up before he knew it.
Let's go home-bon, Pekoms. Mama is waiting.
So please don't worry!
I think Laboon would...
He beat a guy with a 200 million
bounty in a single blow!
And I managed to get this far but...
Hey, Pekoms!
As I recall, Mr. Pekoms has
a 330 million berry bounty.
...the ship I was on was wrecked by this weather.
Why don't you pick it up? Grr!
I don't wanna get yelled at!
Catch the stream!
Okay!
And I didn't know what to do.
Over 300 million?
That is how strong the pirate group led
by the one of the Four Emperors can be?
You're a good girl! You love your dad so much!
Clank!
--Hello?
--Hey!
Will Luffy-san and the others be okay?
We're okay now.
But of all places - Impel Down...
We'll stick with the whales for a while.
That prison has no mercy. I almost died there.
That's kind of nice.
Are you Big Mam?!
I wasn't planning on going there.
Oh? Brook?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
What about your dad?!
Yo ho ho ho… Yo ho ho ho…
Well, when I was hiding in a warship, I heard them talking.
We're traveling across the Maubeugemour Sea carrying Panz Fry.
You're not Tamago, are you? Nor Pekoms.
Yo ho ho ho… Yo ho ho ho…
The ship carrying Dad will pass through here!
We are totally heroes now!
Who are you?
I'm Monkey D. Luffy! I'm gonna
become the King of the Pirates!
Do not ever forget their kindness.
You mean the Navy is coming?!
There's the Sunny!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Franky's there!
Of course!
Gather up all of the crew!
Time to ship out Binks's Brew!
If they see us, it's not gonna be pretty!
Looks like he's ready to go!
--Luffy-kun!
--Straw Hat-san...
Yeah. But I have to save Dad at any cost!
Hey, Franky!
Sea wind blows to where, who knows?
The waves will be our guide!
O'er across the ocean's tide,
the sunset is goin' wild
Before they take him to Impel Down,
Monkey D.?
Here we go finally!
See the sky! Birds singing
in circles passing by!
Hey, Dad, Dad!
this is my last chance to save him!
Lily-chan...
Bid farewell to weaver's town!
Say so long to port renowned!
Buy me a straw hat! I wanna
pretend I'm the hero!
I'm sorry for everything.
Meanwhile, on the sea near the
Red Line in the New World...
I don't want to cause you guys trouble anymore.
Sing a song, it won't be long
before we're casting off!
You're Garp's grandson!
What? They only sell it above ground!
Now I remember!
If you just give me an empty bottle, I'll get off of this ship.
Cross the gold and silver waves,
changin' into water sprays!
Buy one above ground then!
You were the brat who meddled
in the war 2 years ago.
No way!
You guys better get away from here.
Sailing out on our journey
to the ends of the sea!
There are horrible humans
who hate Fish-Men above...
An urgent report from the headquarters!
The sweets are gone!
Several coated ships are emerging
from the seafloor at high speed!
Lily.
Gather up all of the crew!
Time to ship out Binks's Brew!
What?
I ate them all!
Let me...
Oh, I mean, I heard some
of them are like that...
So it's true that they don't have any!
...help you!
Everyone, man your posts now!
Pirates we, we'll divide
and conquer all the seas!
I wanna try that heavenly food that only your dad can make!
They must have 10 tons of them!
Of course, there are good and
strong humans like Straw Hat, too.
I repeat!-- Everyone, man your posts now!
I ate 10 tons of them!
With the waves to rest our heads,
ship beneath us as our bed!
And besides, he's a hero!
I wanna see the hero!
Hoisted high up on the mast
our Jolly Roger flies!
Straw Hat-san, that's too...!
But that's too...
Oh, Boss Jimbei! You came at the right time!
That's...!
That's what we do. So don't worry, Lily-chan.
Why is he saying that?
Somewhere in the endless sky,
a storm has started comin' by!
I heard what you were talking about.
We have no choice!
I will tell a merchant to get
his hands on some of those.
If we don't help her now, it's a dishonor to our pervert name!
Waves are dancing having fun,
it's time to sound the drums!
Hey, you're giving us a ride?
If we let blow winds of fear,
then the end of us is near!
Let him take us!
Really?!
Our first fight in the New World will be against the Navy! I can't wait!
A-A pirate ship!
Yes, what you want is that hero's hat, right?
Looks like they're gonna go upward too!
Even so, tomor-row the sun will rise again!
It must be karma!
Uh-huh!
You guys! Are you sure about this?
Yo ho ho ho… Yo ho ho ho…
Yeah! Count on us!
Luffy! Everybody!
When we rescue him, let me have some of that heavenly volcano food!
Yo ho ho ho… Yo ho ho ho…
Fire!
You fool! Stop lying!
Yeah! Of course!
You're covering up for Fish-Men, aren't you?
I'll make sure you have enough until your stomach bursts!
Hurry up! There's one more at two o'clock!
I had a wonderful time!
But it's true that I ate them!
It's the New World, the final sea
of the Grand Line, up above us!
Pirate ships are emerging one after another!
The Mermaid Paradise!
Shuzo-san! Come in! Shuzo-san!
I didn't know they had to go to you!
Now everybody, pull yourself together!
What do you want? Our commander is unavailable.
What's going on?
I can't wait!
There is no safe place once we sail out!
I'll take your message.
Luffy?
We have a lot of treasure with us here.
We have to pass though the dark water again.
All ships were required to turn out today. Why aren't you here yet?
You can have it all! In
compensation for the sweets!
Treasure?!
Hey, what's wrong? Answer me! Where are you now?
I can't eat treasure!
What is that, Franky?
Don't try to gain her favor like that!
That's it!
I'm gonna make the ship float with
buoyant square logs of hollow Banyan.
I know you are there.
What I want is sweet candies!
Finally!
Shut up! Go away!
Hey, wait a minute! Is that all treasure?
Ain-san?
I just got freed from hell at
last! I don't wanna die here!
I can adjust the speed by how many I put out.
You're there, aren't you, Shuzo?
Yes, it is.
Here comes a big one!
The captain is in danger!
What's the matter, Luffy?
I'm gonna embrace her to keep her safe!
Mama, this is Tamago! Let's think about this.
We're heading there.
Let me take that important task!
A few days ago, that brat - Captain
Kid sank two of our allies' ships-bon!
Hey!
We'll get to the Maubeugemour Sea soon.
Why are you taking such a long way round?
Not again!
If we ascend here,
Kid?
You obviously don't understand how important this plan is.
we'll be at the sea where Shanks is!
It's that guy!
The rookie who's worth over a 100
million that we met at the Sabaody!
No, I understand very well.
Nice! That's my Captain-chan!
--Then why...
--I heard...
What beautiful swordplay!
...that a ship carrying Panz Fry, that big-shot pirate, will pass through the Maubeugemour Sea soon.
It was a huge loss
I wanna see him!
and to be honest, we've been
in need of money lately-bon.
It's not just the swordplay that's beautiful!
In that case...
You guys, be serious!
...I'll leave this hat with you.
So how about we save the fun of
eating sweets for a couple of weeks
It's dear to me.
We don't wanna miss this opportunity and let him continue to live in Impel Down.
You all know how to ward off bombshells!
and take the treasure and forgive them?
I think it's the best plan for us-jour.
Come bring it back to me someday!
If you don't use that skill
now, when are you gonna...
Once you've become a great pirate!
Captain, you're talking to a mast!
All pirates in the New World must be exterminated!
If you want candies,
I cleaned your glasses!
we could get something sweet
and delicious on our way back.
Thank you.
I thought that was what we Neo Navy really want!
There is one thing that makes me wanna stay.
She's so cute! She's like
a flower in the filthy G-5!
I will die for you, Captain-chan!
We can't give the Navy onto our plan by letting you do whatever you want.
That is my desire to see
you fulfill your dream.
Me too! Me too!
Screw that, Tamago!
We're in a battle! Stop fooling around!
But I'm sure that you can do it!
Otherwise, you'll get killed!
You better come here now.
How could you say such
an embarrassing thing!?
Don't worry.
I'm sick of the G-5!
NAVY GRAND LINE 5TH BRANCH
"G-5" CAPTAIN--TASHIGI
Pirates shouldn't compromise
on what they want!
If we sink him with the Navy and all, there'll be no evidence.
I can't believe you guys are Navy soldiers!
Because you're my brother!
I-I'm sorry-soir!
Don't just think about the ones you've lost!
Don't take me lightly
just because I'm a woman!
Let's do it, guys!
I'll pull off this operation...
You can't get back what you've lost!
We're not taking you lightly!
10, 9, 8, 7, 6...
Having said that,
We're just falling for Captain
Tashigi's cuteness...
What is it that you still have?!
...and prove that  I will be a better right-hand man to him...
...5, 4, 3, 2...
There! You're taking me lightly!
That brat who stood up to
me has piqued my interest.
Rise to the top!
You have to realize that you're Navy...
...than you!
...1!
Luffy-san! Do you know what they call
the second half of the Grand Line?
Shut up, Tashigi!
Have it your way, instead
of the Fish-Man Island,
If you fail... You know the consequences.
I'm interrogating someone here.
I'm sorry, sir!
I'll have my vengeance against you all!
Yes.
I see.
People call the final sea beyond
the Red Line by another name.
Clank!
So you all were captured by Hordy
Jones, a pirate from the seafloor.
--We're out!
--In the New World!
Brat.
--We did it!
--We finally made it!
Listen, all of you!
That explains why
Let's make the foolish Navy realize how formidable we Neo Navy are!
there was no rookie passing by
the Fish-Man Island for a month.
"The New World."
But it's not time to celebrate yet!
Captured? No, he enslaved us!
Luffy-sama and the others are not back yet.
"The New World."
Get ready to surface!
It's the sea where pirates who will open
the way to the next generation gather.
Are you sure they are going
to be okay, Nami-chin-sama?
But when Hordy and his clan started a civil
war, a group of pirates defeated them
Yes, sir!
Oh, the whales!
Yeah, it's taking so long.
Whoa, what's going on with the weather now?
The pirate who conquers the sea will
become the King of the Pirates!
We'll tell Laboon about
you all if we see him!
and freed us!
Boy! I wonder what they're doing!
A mirage, again?
A group of pirates?
I think it's just fog.
I won't forgive them if they
can't get the treasure back!
Yeah, but I'm not gonna
tell you who they were!
Visibility is going down.
Laboon's relatives! Take care of yourselves!
It'll be harder to find your dad.
Idiot! Just tell them!
Monkey D. Luffy. I know your name now.
Once we pass through this deep sea,
Yeah.
Thank you for everything!
They're not just Navy
soldiers - they're the G-5!
Hey, Lily, look!
we'll get to the ultimate sea!
They'd fish for sharks using a pirate as bait
Come to the New World!
Finally! I'll cut everything away!
I had heard about it but
it's more than I expected!
or make a bonfire using pirates as kindling!
Wait for me, Laboon! One more half to go!
They're the Navy's craziest outlaws
It's the Navy!
Count on me! I'll navigate
you anywhere you want!
who won't even obey orders
from the headquarters!
The New World has...
Luffy-kun!
You have no idea what they're gonna do to us!
That's right! The Sunny can do it!
…really bad weather!
I'll heal you no matter how wounded you are!
And of all men, we were...
Sure, wait for me there.
Dad!
The sky is filled with thunder!
Is that him?
You'll never go hungry while I'm here!
The wind is so strong!
There's some business I want
to settle with you, too.
...caught by the infamous
"White Chase" Smoker!
The sea is very rough!
You've got the warrior of the sea here too!
The needle is going crazy!
NAVY GRAND LINE 5TH BRANCH "G-5" VICE ADMIRAL
"WHITE CHASE" SMOKER
I can't leave it in your
hands - that's too dangerous!
Vice Admiral Smoker! Can I take them?
Let's go!
SIN
I see some ships!
I'll kick your ass all over the New World...
No, don't!
Guys!
Pirates are having a party!
I'll tell you! So help me!
No, those are warships!
Couldn't ask for anything better!
The group of pirates who beat
Hordy and his clan was...
All right, guys!
...and make the Fish-Man Island my territory!
...the Straw Hats!
Let's go and take Lily's dad back!
To the New World!
The Navy?
I know.
Yeah!
You insolent brat!
Fool!
Fish-Man Island's treasure,
Nami's plan to rescue Lily's father is put into action.
The Straw Hats depart Fish-Man Island
and rise up out of the sea.
the Tamate Box, hold a surprising secret.
With both excitement and uncertainty...
The Straw Hats finally
make it to the surface.
...the journey to the New
World is finally underway.
One that further intensifies the conflict...
But events take an unexpected turn...
But it's the harshest
ocean of the Grand Line.
They encounter many grueling trials...
The Straw Hats acquire a new Log Pose...
...and escalate into a full-scale war between the Straw Hats and the Navy.
On the voyage up to the New World...
...between Luffy and Big
Mam of the Four Emperors.
...including a mysterious girl small
enough to fit in the palm of you hand.
...and say their goodbyes
to Shirahoshi and Jimbei.
...they come across hardship after hardship.
Uncertainty grows concerning the
Straw Hats' next destination.
Just as the fierce battle concludes and the rescue appears successful...
As the crew is tossed about...
However...
To fulfill his promise to Shanks...
...by a killer underwater whirlpool...
...it also brings to light a conspiracy...
On the oceans of the New World...
...both the Straw Hats and Navy are attacked...
...than man whose fate is
closely tied to theirs...
...Luffy finally sets off...
...between pirates and the
Navy of the New World!
...an unimaginable sight appears before them.
...on a new voyage.
...by a new enemy.
...makes a move.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Finally Time to Go!
Goodbye, Fish-Man Island!"
"Z's Ambition!
Lily the Little Giant!"
"Many Problems Lie Ahead! A Trap
Awaiting in the New World!"
"To the New World! Heading for the Ultimate Sea!"
"Z's Ambition! A Dark and Powerful Army!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!