Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where they instigated an all-out war
against the New Fish-Man Pirates,
who were holding a grudge against humans
and looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom.
Luffy finally defeated Hordy, the captain of
the New Fish-Man Pirates, in a fierce fight
and thwarted his plot.
Listen. You all need to know
the two biggest changes...
...which have occurred in the New World.
First, the Navy Headquarters
led by Sakazuki...
...has become an even more
powerful force for justice.
And second,
the Blackbeard Pirates have advanced.
You fools! Why did you kick him out?!
Why didn't you just punch
him and tie him up here!
I love it even when you...
Go find him now!
They were sent by Big Mam.
This is not a good time!
We don't have any sweets
to pay them for this month.
Hordy and the others destroyed the factory
and the undamaged sweets have
been sent to the banquet
since everybody wanted the
Straw Hats to have them!
I wonder if we can explain the situation.
She is like a monster who would
destroy a whole country for sweets!
One of the Four Emperors...
Big Mam!
"She Loves Sweets! Big Mam
of the Four Emperors!"
After the banquet reaches its
climax, it comes to an end.
What?! They'll give us their treasure?!
Wow!
That's really nice!
I wonder if Luffy-sama and the others
are doing okay, Nami-chin-sama.
They're fine!
We're finally gonna become
a rich pirate group!
Things in life usually aren't that easy...
Hey Usopp, do you wanna go look for him too?
No, we better not. I did some research
and found out that his
THE FISH-MAN ISLAND - THE OUTSKIRTS
OF CORAL HILL NEAR THE CANDY FACTORY
bounty is over 200 million.
What?! Mine's only 50 berries...
Hey look, Zoro, Sanji!
There he is! That was easy!
He got knocked out cold already
by your punch. How pathetic!
There is so much treasure
scattered around here.
Is that furry king really
going to give us all of this?
Cool! We can buy lots of meat!
I can't believe he was storing
all of this in his gloopy body!
1, 2, 3!
--Alright! Let's go back to the palace!
--How?
We need a flying fish.
--Which way is the town, Zoro?
--That way.
--Okay, let's head in the opposite direction.
--Hey!
All right, Minister of the Left?
Please show us mercy!
It was all unexpected! Hordy and the
others destroyed the factory and...
That's none of our concern! Grr!
I was planning on snatching some
for myself so I'm very hungry!
You pay us with sweets once a month.
And we allow you to use Mama's name.
PEKOMS-- A MEMBER OF THE BIG MAM PIRATES
That was the agreement, wasn't it? Grr!
Now, I don't want to say this to you
seeing as how we're business partners
but you know how scary Mama can be!
If you make her mad, she will...
...destroy you all!
He's cute when he does that!
Now, what are you gonna do?! Grr!
Look - a crowd.
Oh, this is the Candy Factory!
Pappagu told me about it!
Yeah?
I hope we can find a flying fish here.
I guess they're making
those yummy sweets here!
Hey, Candy Factory!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Luffy-san, is the banquet over already?!
Luffy-kun, why are you here?!
Yeah, I ate a lot!
The meat was good but those sweets
from the Fish-Man Island were unbelievable!
What?!
No, Straw Hat-san!
Don't talk about them!
Oh, old Mr. Catfish, it's you!
Did he say "sweets"?! Who are they?!
Oh yeah, he's Straw Hat Luffy! Definitely!
What is that notorious pirate doing here?
Well, um...
Hey brat! Which sweets
are you talking about?!
Well, Mr. Pekoms, let me explain...
Who are you?!
You're not a Fish-Man, are you?
You came to buy sweets?
I just finished stuffing myself full of them!
What?!
What's going on here?!
He just said he ate them!
W-Well... There is an explanation...
Oh?! A talking lion!
But I guess that's not such a big
deal. We've got something similar.
Atchoo!
Whoa, what's wrong? Did you catch a cold?
Maybe somebody's talking about me.
You're popular.
This lion's got an unique face!
What?! Are you messing with me?!
Yuck! You fool!
Pekoms.
Making such threatening faces doesn't
help us in collecting the sweets.
Let's settle this peacefully-soir.
The tea party is 4 days from now-bon.
We can make it on time if we
leave here tomorrow morning-jour.
There's another odd one! Who are you?
Bon to meet you, you half-boiled pirates.
My name is Baron Tamago-soir!
BARON TAMAGO-- A MEMBER OF THE
BIG MAM PIRATES (LONGFEET TRIBE)
Tamago (egg)?!
Remember my name at least-s'il vous plait!
Now, you gentlemen...
Did you just say you ate the sweets
from this factory-c'est si bon?
He looks like a compass.
Yes, I did! I wanna have
some more if they have any!
They don't. That's why we
don't know what to do-bon!
That big mark on the factory is...
...the Jolly Roger of the great pirate
and our boss- Charlotte Lingling-soir.
It claims this island as Big Mam's territory
- she is one of the Four Emperors.
Which means, the Fish-Man Island is
protected under Big Mam's name-bon!
Sounds like a nice person! I wanna
meet your boss! Big Mam, huh?
Don't mistake our arrangement.
We have a business arrangement.
In exchange for 10 tons of sweets a month,
we allow them to use the mark-bon.
--10 tons?
--That's right.
Mama loves sweet candies
more than anything-soir.
Sweets from the Fish-Man
Island are her favorite.
So we'll wait until tomorrow morning.
No, Baron, I already told you.
The factory's giant cooking
machines are broken
and we need at least 2 weeks to repair them!
That's not acceptable-soir.
Hey Tamago! Why can't you wait?!
Is your boss's mind as small as his balls?
He's one of the Four Emperors, isn't he?
It's not "he." Mama is a great
woman pirate-vous plait.
I don't think she has balls-jour.
Oh, she's a madam.
I love sweets!
And I love you too since you can make them!
What's gonna happen if you
can't have them on time?
In that case...
The deal is off!
Vicious members of the
Big Mam Pirates will...
...descend on the island and
destroy it  in no time-vous plait!
Destroy the island?!
Are you guys nuts? You can't
destroy a country over candies!
This island has just been saved!
WHOLE CAKE ISLAND SOMEWHERE IN THE NEW WORLD
You look happy, Mama.
ONE OF THE FOUR EMPERORS-- - THE GREAT
PIRATE "BIG MAM" CHARLOTTE LINGLING
I can't wait for the tea party
four days from now because...
...I'll get my hands on those delicious
sweets from the Fish-Man Island!
I can't wait and my stomach is
already producing so much acid!
Can't wait! Can't wait! The
sweets from the Fish-Man Island!
You guys can't wait either?
Of course, we can't! They are so good!
Then why don't you wait for
them inside of my stomach?!
Mama!
I'm home! Boyoyon!
Oh! How did it go, Bobbin?
I beat them up and burned the place!
How lovely!
That country had the best baked goods!
It must have smelled so good
as it burned to the ground!
It's a shame but we had no choice.
Because they couldn't reach
their quotas on time.
Can I have some snacks?
We have to kill them if
they don't give us sweets!
I don't like people who
don't keep their promises!
Just like I don't like bitter candies!
Oh yeah! I heard the Fish-Man Island
may not have sweets to pay this month.
I just got word from Pekoms. Do
you want the Fish-Man Island
to be burned down too?
I can't have the sweets
from the Fish-Man Island?!
Get them on the Transponder Snail now!
Destroy the island?!
Are you guys nuts?
You can't destroy a country over candies!
This island has just been saved!
I can't believe it-bon.
They aren't even half-boiled, they are raw.
What should I do with those
fearless rookies-jour?
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
It must be Mama! Grr! I told them
what was going on a while ago.
B-Big Mam is calling in person?!
Hey, Pekoms!
Why don't you pick it up? Grr!
I don't wanna get yelled at!
Clank!
--Hello?
--Hey!
Are you Big Mam?!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
You're not Tamago, are you? Nor Pekoms.
Who are you?
I'm Monkey D. Luffy! I'm gonna
become the King of the Pirates!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
--Luffy-kun!
--Straw Hat-san...
Monkey D.?
You're Garp's grandson!
Now I remember!
You were the brat who meddled
in the war 2 years ago.
The sweets are gone!
I ate them all!
So it's true that they don't have any!
They must have 10 tons of them!
I ate 10 tons of them!
Straw Hat-san, that's too...!
Why is he saying that?
You fool! Stop lying!
You're covering up for Fish-Men, aren't you?
But it's true that I ate them!
I didn't know they had to go to you!
We have a lot of treasure with us here.
You can have it all! In
compensation for the sweets!
Treasure?!
I can't eat treasure!
What I want is sweet candies!
Hey, wait a minute! Is that all treasure?
Yes, it is.
Mama, this is Tamago! Let's think about this.
A few days ago, that brat - Captain
Kid sank two of our allies' ships-bon!
Kid?
It's that guy!
The rookie who's worth over a 100
million that we met at the Sabaody!
It was a huge loss
and to be honest, we've been
in need of money lately-bon.
So how about we save the fun of
eating sweets for a couple of weeks
and take the treasure and forgive them?
I think it's the best plan for us-jour.
If you want candies,
we could get something sweet
and delicious on our way back.
Screw that, Tamago!
How could you say such
an embarrassing thing!?
Pirates shouldn't compromise
on what they want!
I-I'm sorry-soir!
Having said that,
That brat who stood up to
me has piqued my interest.
Have it your way, instead
of the Fish-Man Island,
I'll have my vengeance against you all!
Luffy-sama and the others are not back yet.
Are you sure they are going
to be okay, Nami-chin-sama?
Yeah, it's taking so long.
Boy! I wonder what they're doing!
I won't forgive them if they
can't get the treasure back!
Monkey D. Luffy. I know your name now.
Come to the New World!
Luffy-kun!
Sure, wait for me there.
There's some business I want
to settle with you, too.
I can't leave it in your
hands - that's too dangerous!
I'll kick your ass all over the New World...
...and make the Fish-Man Island my territory!
You insolent brat!
Fish-Man Island's treasure,
the Tamate Box, hold a surprising secret.
One that further intensifies the conflict...
...between Luffy and Big
Mam of the Four Emperors.
Uncertainty grows concerning the
Straw Hats' next destination.
On the oceans of the New World...
...than man whose fate is
closely tied to theirs...
...makes a move.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Many Problems Lie Ahead! A Trap
Awaiting in the New World!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!