Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates, once
attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner (･∀･)
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m aiming at hasn’t changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
we go!
WE GO!
Finally!
Finally, the Great Pirate Era is coming to an end!
Master Z!
Meanwhile, the Straw Hats have left the Fish-Man Island and are headed for the New World.
"Z's Ambition!
Lily the Little Giant!"
Wh-What's going on here?!
Are they really the Navy?!
Here, there, everywhere! 360 degrees!
We're totally surrounded!
Only the Navy could accomplish this. They know every move that we make.
We're totally surrounded. There is nowhere to run.
You two, stop talking in such a cool manner!
The weather...
They're closing in on us!
What are we gonna do, Luffy?!
Oh? Where did he go?
Go forward!
Let's keep moving forward like this!
Guys!
They outnumber us!
There's no time to argue!
Usopp, get ready to fire at them! Chopper, fill the tank with cola!
I don't care anymore!
I'll take the front!
Leave the sides to us!
I'll handle the rear!
Bring it on!
We're ready!
Usopp, wait!
There's no need to fight.
Why not?
Third Gear!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Pistol!
Oh?
The warships are vanishing one by one!
It stopped raining too!
I thought so.
What's going on?
What we're seeing was a mirage only found in this area.
A mirage?!
I'm so relieved!
Don't drop your guard yet.
If I'm...
...right...
What the hell is that?!
Huge raindrops!
What's this weather?!
We're in the Maubeugemour Sea!
Momemomejuban?!
No, "Maubeugemour"! Also known as the "Ill-Tempered Sea"!
Home to weather conditions you've never seen or heard of before!
--Hail?
--It's such a dangerous sea!
It's gonna hit us!
360...
...Pound Phoenix!
Damn!
Oh, cotton candy?
Now there's an avalanche from the sky!
Mil Fleurs!
Gigantesco Mano!
Nice, Robin!
It started raining hard!
I hope it's just rain!
What is it this time?!
D-Don't tell me...
The water split!
So pretty much anything goes here?
We're sinking!
If nothing is done, we're gonna end up back in the deep sea!
No, we'll hit a rock and drown before that.
Don't say it so casually!
What an amazing phenomenon!
Now's not the time to be impressed!
How do we escape?!
Punch.
--Cut.
--Kick.
Alright!
No, that won't do!
Leave it to the Sunny!
Coup de...
...Burst!
Yeah!
--Cool!
--He did it!
It's baking hot now.
--It's sweltering...
--That was close.
But I'm impressed, Nami-san. You know about the weather in the New World.
I studied as much as I could about the New World over the past 2 years.
I want a beer when it's hot.
--I'm hungry!
--Me too.
Oh yeah! We caught a deep-sea fish!
Unfortunately, most of it was ruined by the horrible weather.
What?!
But I had already set aside some.
Just give me some time and I'll cook something.
First, I'll just whip up some carpaccio.
Today's soup will be deep-sea fish bouillabaisse. What should I make for the main dish?
Okay, it's done! Come and get it!
Yeah!
Looks great!
Food! Food! Food! Food!
Let's eat!
Eat it and wait. It's deep-sea fish carpaccio.
--There's nothing here!
--No, it's on the platter.
There is a platter here but nothing is on it!
What are you talking...
It's gone!
Oh? Huh?
--Boo! Boo!
--Did you guys eat it already?!
No, we didn't!
Then who did?!
Maybe the Maubeugemour Sea is haunted!
Yummy!
A ghost!
The soup is all gone!
What?!
What's that?! Something came out!
A bug?
A bug ghost!
--Did the bug eat it?!
--No way.
The strawberries are gone!
--What?! The corn is gone!
--Really?!
Dammit! This is unforgivable!
Luffy, it went outside!
I have a bad feeling.
--The fridge is empty!
--What?!
Where did it go?! I lost it!
--What's going on?
--We found a bug ghost!
And a food thief!
What do you mean "thief"?!
I just ate what I found sitting around.
Huh? Me?
That's what we call a "thief"!
What?! Why are you doing this to me, Luffy-san?!
It got out!
--Where?
--Oh? Where did it go?
All the food in the fridge is gone too! The booze as well!
What?!
Where did it go?!
You're...
...a human?!
How dare you steal my food!
Here it is!
Oh?
Damn!
--Hey, catch her, Franky!
--I got it!
I can't get caught now!
Stop!
She took Franky down! She's strong!
Looks like we gotta go all out.
I have no choice!
Take the Mini-Mini Full Rebound!
Oh, wow!
She's...
Gigantic!
How cool is that!?
You're amazing, mega young girl!
Run!
Now, come to me!
--Oh no!
--She's gonna stab us!
No hard feelings!
I'll fight you!
Alright! Here I go!
What?
Nice, he lifted her up!
Gum-Gum Propeller!
What's going on?!
Propeller Wind-Down!
Wh-What? She can't swim?
Young girl, I'm coming for you!
Maybe, she's a Devil Fruit eater.
Dad, I'm sorry...
I don't think I can make it...
Why is she shrinking?
Dad! Dad!
I'll save you at any cost!
Wait for me, Dad!
Dad!
Oh, good.
--She woke up.
--Young girl, you okay?
Hey, you!
Luffy! Don't use violence against a lady again!
You can grow and shrink! That's awesome!
I-I was born a Giant but I ate the Mini-Mini Fruit and...
You're a Giant?!
Yes, but this is my usual size now.
However, I can shrink myself down to 5 millimeters and enlarge myself to the size of the Giants.
Hmmm... You're interesting!
--Am I?
--Yeah!
And you're strong too! Although you're small, you took Franky down!
Even when I'm small, I still have the power of the Giants.
That was easy!
Like this!
You're strong!
He totally forgot that she ate all of our food.
Boy, they're having fun.
Is there anything else you can do?
Yes, I have another technique.
I can get smaller and slip into my enemy's body
then expand myself to break him into pieces!
No way!
That way, I can become a Giant!
What do you mean by that?
Luffy is a rubber man. So instead of breaking into pieces, he stretches.
I can't believe it! You're right, how interesting!
By the way, young girl, what's your name?
My name is Lily Enstomach. People call me "Lily the Glutton"!
I eat a lot for a woman, right?
Lily, why are you aboard this ship?
"Why"?
I was waiting for someone
when your ship flew out of the water all of a sudden!
Who were you waiting for in the middle of nowhere like this?
I was waiting for my dad...
I shouldn't be wasting my time like this!
What's the matter, Lily-chan?
Calm down! The size of your head doesn't match your body anymore!
The bottle was shattered! What should I do?!
I finally made it this far by sneaking aboard some Navy boats and warships!
I can't get to my dad!
Dad? Are you looking for your father?!
What kind of man is your father?
My dad is the greatest pirate chef in the New World!
A pirate chef? Lily-chan, what's your father's name?
It's Panz Fry.
Yeah, I know his name!
Is he that famous?
He's a top volcano cooking chef!
Volcano cooking?! What's that? Is it delicious?!
Oh yeah! I'm getting excited just by thinking about it...
It's my favorite food - churrasco sea monster!
Rare herbs that only grow around volcanoes
and million-year-old salt crystals  from between molten rocks.
All sprinkled on sea monster meat and stewed in a volcano
to cook it up quick!
Sounds yummy!
That's not all! The best one is...
Go on!
A frying pan filled with an assortment of foods from the sea and mountains...
...all cooked over a volcano! It's called Thousand-Person Paella!
Just one taste and...
ﾉit's like slipping into a dream!
It's just like running  through a field of flowers in heaven!
I wanna eat it! I wanna run in heaven!
Heavenly food! Yeehaw!
No, I don't have time for this!
You started it!
I've heard about Panz Fry before too.
He steals food from the Government, the Navy, and other pirates
and likes nothing better than to cook for starving people.
He sounds like...
...a hero!
A Hero? I'm flattered!
I have no time to be flattered!
Enough with that. Tell us what's going on.
Okay. I was pirating around with Dad for a long time
but he went missing all of a sudden a couple weeks ago.
They say the Navy took him.
I was asking around going island to island
then I read in the paper that he'll be taken to Impel Down.
Impel Down?
Why is that? He's a hero!
Because Dad has a 320 million berry bounty.
Over 300 million?! Really?!
He kept stealing food from the Government and the Navy so the price went up before he knew it.
And I managed to get this far but...
...the ship I was on was wrecked by this weather.
And I didn't know what to do.
You're a good girl! You love your dad so much!
But of all places - Impel Down...
That prison has no mercy. I almost died there.
I wasn't planning on going there.
What about your dad?!
Well, when I was hiding in a warship, I heard them talking.
We're traveling across the Maubeugemour Sea carrying Panz Fry.
The ship carrying Dad will pass through here!
You mean the Navy is coming?!
If they see us, it's not gonna be pretty!
Yeah. But I have to save Dad at any cost!
Before they take him to Impel Down,
this is my last chance to save him!
Lily-chan...
I'm sorry for everything.
I don't want to cause you guys trouble anymore.
If you just give me an empty bottle, I'll get off of this ship.
You guys better get away from here.
Lily.
Let me...
...help you!
I wanna try that heavenly food that only your dad can make!
And besides, he's a hero!
I wanna see the hero!
But that's too...
That's what we do. So don't worry, Lily-chan.
We have no choice!
If we don't help her now, it's a dishonor to our pervert name!
Our first fight in the New World will be against the Navy! I can't wait!
It must be karma!
You guys! Are you sure about this?
Yeah! Count on us!
Luffy! Everybody!
When we rescue him, let me have some of that heavenly volcano food!
Yeah! Of course!
I'll make sure you have enough until your stomach bursts!
Shuzo-san! Come in! Shuzo-san!
What do you want? Our commander is unavailable.
I'll take your message.
All ships were required to turn out today. Why aren't you here yet?
Hey, what's wrong? Answer me! Where are you now?
I know you are there.
Ain-san?
You're there, aren't you, Shuzo?
We're heading there.
We'll get to the Maubeugemour Sea soon.
Why are you taking such a long way round?
You obviously don't understand how important this plan is.
No, I understand very well.
--Then why...
--I heard...
...that a ship carrying Panz Fry, that big-shot pirate, will pass through the Maubeugemour Sea soon.
We don't wanna miss this opportunity and let him continue to live in Impel Down.
All pirates in the New World must be exterminated!
I thought that was what we Neo Navy really want!
We can't give the Navy onto our plan by letting you do whatever you want.
You better come here now.
Don't worry.
If we sink him with the Navy and all, there'll be no evidence.
I'll pull off this operation...
...and prove that  I will be a better right-hand man to him...
...than you!
If you fail... You know the consequences.
Yes.
Clank!
Brat.
Listen, all of you!
Let's make the foolish Navy realize how formidable we Neo Navy are!
Get ready to surface!
Yes, sir!
Whoa, what's going on with the weather now?
A mirage, again?
I think it's just fog.
Visibility is going down.
It'll be harder to find your dad.
Yeah.
Hey, Lily, look!
It's the Navy!
Dad!
Is that him?
SIN
All right, guys!
Let's go and take Lily's dad back!
Nami's plan to rescue Lily's father is put into action.
But events take an unexpected turn...
...and escalate into a full-scale war between the Straw Hats and the Navy.
Just as the fierce battle concludes and the rescue appears successful...
...both the Straw Hats and Navy are attacked...
...by a new enemy.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Z's Ambition! A Dark and Powerful Army!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!