Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
The Straw Hats have left the Fish-Man Island
The Straw Hats have left the
and finally reached the New World.
The Straw Hats have left the Fish-Man Island
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
Fish-Man Island and finally
reached the New World.
But not before entering the
treacherous Maubeugemour Sea.
and finally reached the New World.
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
But not before entering the
treacherous Maubeugemour Sea.
They met a Giant girl named Lily
who ate the Mini-Mini Fruit
What's this weather?!
We're in the Maubeugemour Sea!
and decided to help her save her father
Arriving there, they met a Giant
girl who ate the Mini-Mini Fruit.
Momemomejuban?!
However, no one has ever fully explored it
- Panz Fry from the Navy's ship. However,
No, "Maubeugemour"!
My name is Lily Enstomach.
Also known as the "Ill-Tempered Sea"!
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
a mysterious group called the Neo
Navy threw the situation into chaos.
Home to weather conditions you've
never seen or heard of before!
People call me "Lily the Glutton"!
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
I eat a lot for a woman, right?
After finally rescuing Panz Fry, Shuzo and
The ship carrying Dad will pass through here!
Arriving there, they met a Giant
girl who ate the Mini-Mini Fruit
his clan are hot on the Straw Hats' tails!
You mean the Navy is coming?!
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
and decided to help her save her father
- Panz Fry from the Navy's ship.
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Rescue mission accomplished!
If they see us, it's not gonna be pretty!
Yeah!
and his friends venture into that sea.
But I have to save Dad at any cost!
Yeah. But I have to save Dad at any cost!
Now, bring that food here!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Before they take him to Impel Down,
I'll make them my heavenly food!
Really?! Thanks, frying pan pops!
After surviving a fierce battle,
this is my last chance to save him!
After surviving the fierce
battle at the Fish-Man Island,
this is my last chance to save him!
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
Lily.
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
Let me help you!
Lily.
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
I wanna try that heavenly food
that only your dad can make!
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
I wanna try that heavenly food
that only your dad can make!
It's erupting again!
It's right there! Who
cares about the needles?!
Navigating the treacherous Maubeugemour Sea,
However, a mysterious
group called the Neo Navy
They decided to help Lily save her father
Shuzo-san, I found them!
They're hiding behind a reef!
they met a Giant girl named Lily
who ate the Mini-Mini Fruit
Hey, what's this? The
Transponder Snail is crying!
- Panz Fry from the Navy's ship. However...
is trying to kill her father.
and got fired up to help
her save her father -
Hey, what's wrong?! You have a stomachache?
How annoying! All ships, prepare for battle!
Fool! That's an emergency signal.
...a mysterious group called the
Neo Navy is trying to kill him.
Panz Fry from the Navy's ship. However,
Somebody's calling for help.
Let's blow them up along with the reef!
Dad!
If I pick it up, can we hear them?
a mysterious group called the
Neo Navy was trying to kill him.
I-I'm afraid we used up all our
torpedoes in the battle earlier
Wait, Luffy!
I heard a ship carrying Panz
Fry, that big-shot pirate,
Consider that our greeting.
More than 50 percent of
emergency signals are fake!
Surface and finish them off at once!
will pass through the Maubeugemour Sea soon.
and we're almost out of bombshells too.
Help me!
Yes, sir!
No, we still have a torpedo.
My colleagues are getting
cut one after another!
You're responsible for all
the raids on pirates?!
We can use this submersible as a torpedo!
It's the Navy!
And a three-way battle erupted
between the Straw Hats,
The samurai are gonna kill us!
Yes, I am! I'm gonna cut
this guy's head off too!
We are the proud soldiers of
the Neo Navy's flying squad!
Samurai?
the Navy and the Neo Navy.
Hey you, what's your name?! Where are you?!
--Dad!
--Is that him?
We trusted in Master Z and
Shuzo-san and got this far!
And a three-way battle heated up between the
Somebody please help me! I'm on...
Another bomb?!
"Z's Ambition! A Dark and Powerful Army!"
Gum-Gum...
Shuzo-san! Let us fight with you! Please!!
Straw Hats, the Navy and the Neo Navy.
...Balloon!
...Punk Hazard!
Move!
You worthless pirates are no match for me!
A man?!
Outta my way!
I'm proud of you guys! I'll
care for you to your deathbed!
It's hot!
This is the place. The name matches.
Fight to your heart's content
as a Neo Navy soldier!
So this is Punk Hazard...
Gum-Gum...
All torpedoes, go!
Damn!
I won't let you do whatever
you like on this ship
...Giant Jet...
Those were probably not people's houses.
while it's under the control of the Navy!
SIN
Finger Pistol Ten!
I think there were some kind
of Government facilities here.
...Spear!
Pops' heavenly food is...
They deployed 4 ships just
to transport a pirate?
...all mine!
"Z's Ambition! Luffy vs. Shuzo!"
What's wrong, Luffy?
"Z's Ambition! A Great and
Desperate Escape Plan!"
And they were able to bring down
the menacing enemy - Shuzo!
I guess Lily's dad is really a big-shot.
Is that...
But this was just the first foray into
the New World for the Straw Hats.
Dad...
Is that the only reason?
That security is a strange choice
but I wonder why they chose to pass through
What?!
--Pops!
--Dad!
All right, let's go!
this dangerous area on
their way to Impel Down.
Huh? Does it actually exist?!
Yeah!
What?! What?!
--It's them!
--I can't believe this!
Alright! Let's raid them already!
No, it's a mythical creature!
There's no way that it's real!
No way! Don't be ridiculous!
But look at those features...
Ch-Charge!
Listen. Our priority is
to save Lily's father!
"Arriving! A Burning Island - Punk Hazard!"
I don't think it could be anything else!
If we make a raid without
any plan, he could get hurt!
Invade the ship!
We won't let you!
You bastard!
She's right, Luffy!
If anything happens to her father,
Go!
we wouldn't be able to eat
that heavenly volcano food!
"A Battle in the Heat! Luffy
vs. The Giant Dragon!"
Hey, hey, hey!
Then what should we do?
Kill the pirates!
--That's not a torpedo!
--It's a manned ship, isn't it?
Whoa, whoa! Are we gonna be okay?
Can I take charge of this operation?
Long live the Neo Navy!
The Sunny will be fine!
What do you say?
Yes, I want you to do it, Nami-sa!
Uh-huh, all right!
What's that?
What?! That's impossible!
A 400 million berry bounty,
huh? Are you a pirate too?
Aw...
Awesome!!
First, we need a diversion team.
Yeah.
A red sea?!
Then to hell with you too!
You take the Mini-Merry and divert
their attention from a distance...
Look! The volcano's erupting!
What's wrong with them?!
Leave it up to me.
...to set up the infiltration team.
Let's go to that island!
They're launching themselves like torpedoes!
How cool is that!
What?!
They must be nuts!
Second Gear!
The members of the team are
Chopper as boat operator,
D-Don't be so impressed!
Gum-Gum...
Luffy, Robin, and Brook.
Wait a minute, Luffy!
...Jet Gatling!
A diversion?  That means
I can kick their asses?!
Just as I thought.
Iron Body!
None of the needles point to that island.
Cool!!
No, you can't!
I'm outta here!
Robin and Brook will create a diversion!
Let's go to that island!
Wow! I like how he snarls, too!
You just have to wait in case
something really goes wrong!
I said "Wait"!
Why?! There is a volcano! It looks like fun!
What a strange technique.
Did you eat a Devil Fruit?
Cool! So cool!
Don't do anything before!
Who could resist?
I'm a rubber man.
Listen to me, Luffy!
Now, the infiltration team.
But that wasn't strong enough
to break my Iron Body!
None of the 3 needles is
pointing at the island!
Who are you?
You take the Shark Submerge and sneak
onto the raft without being
seen by the Navy soldiers.
Oh yeah?
It's too peculiar even
in the strange New World!
Then cut the chain and release Lily's father.
I said I won't let you do
whatever you like on this ship!
It's erupting again!
It's right there! Who
cares about the needles?!
Nice to see you again, accursed pirates.
The members are Zoro, Sanji-kun...
Let's just go there!
You can't get away!
Count on me!
It's that guy! How did he find us?!
Roronoa Zoro!
...Usopp, and Lily - can you do it?
No way! We can't get any closer!
Thank you for waiting. Let's
pick up where we left off!
Don't come after me!
I used this!
Uh-huh!
Because the sea is on fire!
That sounds like more fun.
A Vivre Card?!
When you were taking off,
I threw it onto the raft!
I don't understand you!
All right?
Advance! Kill the pirates!
The point is how to bring
such a giant man back safely.
It's perfect.
Party Table Kick Course!
Hey, that's the Giant
Shellfish Panz Fry gave us.
What're you doing, you fool?!
You're right. It'll draw their
attention since he's so big.
Hey!
I thought we could cook
this in that sea of fire.
The dragon just talked!
It'd be nice if we could
steal one of their ships
Ochenta Fleurs!
but it'd take too much time and energy.
No way! You're hearing things!
Get ready to open fire!
Sanji! Now isn't the time for that!
So what we're gonna do instead is detach
You think so?
the raft from the ship and whisk
it away with Coup de Burst.
He's an easy target.
--Sparks!
--The ship will catch fire too!
Franky, you stay on the Sunny and
wait somewhere they can't see you.
I-I'm not even sure it's a dragon!
Dad!
No!
I won't allow them to die in vain!
The Sunny is super not gonna let us down!
Prepare for Coup de Burst.
Treinta Fleurs Strangle!
That's not the point!
Is it really a dragon?
There's something wrong with this sea!
I got it!
Look at those fish bones, bones, bones!
What about you, Nami?
Yes, it's hard to believe but...
Me? I'll spy on their movements
with the White Hobby Horse
Robin-chan!
Huh? Did you just call me?
...it has a lizard-like
body with giant wings.
and take command of this mission.
He's super crazy!
It looks exactly how it's described in myths.
Who on earth are they?!
Don't forget that we're
in the Maubeugemour Sea.
You damn pirates are the reason
that the New World is corrupted.
Wh-What's that?!
So all we want is...
Oh no! It's a big mess!
Watch out for a sudden change in weather.
Now let's do it!
Hey, Nami!
Okay!
...to exterminate you all!
No way!
I know!
I'm trying to think of the best
way to bring back Lily's father!
Hey, what's this? The
Transponder Snail is crying!
No! If you move too much, your wound will...
Come to think of it, we are all
Devil Fruit eaters in this team.
Oh no!
Hey, what's wrong?! You have a stomachache?
You're right.
Fool! That's an emergency signal.
So if we fall into the sea,
we're pretty much finished.
Somebody's calling for help.
What?!
If I pick it up, can we hear them?
Iron Body!
I hope we don't drown
and get eaten by sharks.
Wait, Luffy!
Dad!
More than 50 percent of
emergency signals are fake!
No! You're making us scared, Robin!
It could be a Navy trap - one they use often.
Since we're deploying on the open sea,
If the line is tapped, they
will find out where we are.
Lily!
I placed all Devil Fruit
eaters except for Lily
That's our Robin!
in the diversion team to be safe.
No, stop!
Hey, Luffy, you have to be careful...
See you!
Clank.
H-He breathed fire!!
Hello? My name is Monkey D. Luffy!
No! Is that the Thrust Up Stream?!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Where is Luffy?
You picked up too fast and said too much!
This creature is unreal! Am I dreaming?!
I told him to get on board the Mini-Merry!
Help me!
He took the Shark Submerge
instead and left earlier.
What happened?
Bastard! Gum-Gum...
It's cold... Is this the Boss?!
You escaped death earlier!
What?
How exciting!
No, I'm not the Boss. Is it cold there?
Well, he came with us saying that
the diversion sounded boring.
But it's come for you again!
My colleagues are getting
cut one after another!
The samurai are gonna kill us!
Dad!
It's my turn!
Lily, I can't wait to see your dad!
Samurai?
Hey you, what's your name?! Where are you?!
Uh-huh!
Both Luffy-san and Zoro-san
are on the defensive.
How selfish!
Second Gear!
Somebody please help me!
Hey, Luffy, are you listening?!
I'll fight you!
Those two must be very strong!
I'm on...
Don't you dare sneak onto the raft!
Gum-Gum...
--Luffy-sa!
--Go, Luffy!
Take this, you monster!
...Punk Hazard!
It will screw up the whole plan!
...Jet...
Hey you!
Bullet!
Alright!
Even though I'm a soul without a body now,
I won't let you hurt that old man!
By the way, both you and your dad came
from Elbaf like other Giants, right?
He got killed!
I'm not happy to be shot at!
Th-That was...
A rubber man? Oh right.
You're a pirate too and I'll
kill you sooner or later anyway.
Usopp-sa, you know Elbaf?
It didn't work!
Do I know it? Yes, of course!
He's well-armored!
I smell trouble...
The brave warriors of the
sea - Dorry and Broggy...
Then why don't I kill you first? As you wish!
He got killed - of course there is trouble!
There's no mistaking it! Damn! Not now!
...are our close friends!
Somebody just cut him!
Behind you!
What?! Have you met those
legendary pirate bosses?!
The New World is scary!
Thank you for waiting! Nami!
Maybe he was acting and it's a trap.
Franky! We have a problem!
How level-headed!
Yeah, we have!
The weather's gonna change drastically again!
Come on, Robin-san!
I can't believe it! I've never even met them!
Gum-Gum...
Luffy!
It's not safe here!
Speaking of samurai, Brook...
What?!
...Jet Gatling!
My dad has been friends with
them since they were kids.
Everybody, listen carefully!
The Thrust Up Stream is coming soon!
Really?!
Yes, what you think is right.
Yeah. He told me about them all the time.
--The Thrust Up...
--...Stream?
That's that name of the swordsmen
from the Wano Kingdom.
He's looking at us!
Gum-Gum...
What's that?
Finger Pistol!
Sounds like they're having fun!
Come on!
The Wano Kingdom - closed
off to the outside world.
...Jet Whip!
Is it something like the Knock Up Stream
Let's have fun here too!
Don't provoke him!
--Gum-Gum...
--Shave!
that we rode to get to the Sky Island?!
Yeah!
It's not even affiliated
with the World Government.
...Jet Bazooka!
The song is "Let's Go to the Rescue"!
They say those swordsmen
called samurai are so strong
Yeehaw!
Yes, it is! But it's not that big!
Moon Walk!
Go, go, let's go! To the Ill-Tempered Sea!
even the Navy can't approach.
Oh good!
Shut up!
I sense your presence-bu!
But it could easily blow away a warship!
You got us in trouble, Brook!
This great sword - Shusui was once
carried by a legendary samurai.
Sorry! I'm really sorry!
What?
What?!
And once it starts erupting, it
could appear anywhere around us!
Armament!
If you become its owner,
the sword will be pleased.
Gum-Gum...
So return to the Sunny immediately!
Don't get in my way!
...Pistol!
Luffy was right!
R-Roger!
That dragon just said something!
--Yeah!
--He did it!
I let this samurai's
body... take the beating.
Move out of my way!
Three-Sword Style!
I feel bad.
Armament Hardening!
Gum-Gum...
Ultra Tiger Hunt!
Iron Body!
I've never heard of that country.
Don't you get it yet? Iron Body!
I've never heard of a pirate who
But he said Punk Hazard,
not the Wano Kingdom.
...Jet Bazooka!
so brazenly boarded a Government-owned
cargo ship before.
Your Haki is not strong enough to beat me!
Did he mean the island of fire right there?
Why did you do it?
What? Haki?!
What?!
--He uses Haki as well, huh?
--This is going to be difficult.
If he was using a Baby Transponder Snail,
I just wanted to take back
what you took from them!
that's about how far the signal can reach.
One-Sword Style!
All right! Let's go help that guy!
Since you Navy people killed Whitebeard,
the New World is in disorder.
360 Pound Phoenix!
No!
Luffy, think again! I think it's too late!
That island where the Government's ship was
Samurai are scary!
I'm scared too!
moored was not an exception.
His hands are annoying!
Damn! He's so strong and durable!
The islanders were on
the brink of starvation.
I guess that's all you got!
Franky! The anchors!
But the crew on that ship took away
all food that they had stored,
Third Gear!
Hey you, what's your name?! Where are you?!
Roger!
Somebody please help me! I'm on...
to provide for the World
Nobles' nightly feasts!
Luffy!
You brat!
...Punk Hazard!
Take this!
You have some nerve.
I'm a cook!
I have to provide food for hungry people!
Smoker-san, that was...
You too!
Did he say Punk Hazard?
So you boarded the ship
to steal food for them?
Damn!
The islands are in disorder
because of you pirates.
How could they have gotten there?
Sanji-kun! Lily!
Nami-san! I guess she's worrying about me.
Don't shift the blame!
The battle at the Fish-Man Island,
the incident after that...
You haven't collapsed yet?
Luffy!
It's not safe here!
Something like the Knock Up Stream is coming!
I heard him talking!
If we plot the course they took from there...
See?!
What?!
I heard it too! But how?
Did the anchors dig into the raft?!
After all, we remain as far apart as ever.
Yeah!
Punk Hazard... It's possible they're there.
Then, get away on the Sunny now!
Don't do it! I'll do anything!
We'll never be of the same mind!
--Okay!
--Uh-huh!
I'll do whatever you ask me to!
How did you like the Haki-wrapped bombshell?
You're right.
Then get charred!
Somebody is raiding pirates these days.
My lovely partner - Beast Cannon Alpacacino!
What happened?!
Oh no!
He's a bazooka that ate a Devil Fruit!
Stop it, you guys! Stop bullying pirates!
Luffy! Silly swordsman!
Since we have a pirate on our
ship, we are possible targets.
Let's get away from here with
Coup de Burst and her dad in tow!
Tashigi! Let's head for Punk Hazard!
Be on the look-out and shoot
anything that moves on the sea!
Finger Pistol Five!
But Smoker-san,
Alright!
--I won't let you...
--...Do that!
Punk Hazard
Yes, sir!
He's flying!
has been deserted since they sealed it
off after what happened 4 years ago!
Guys, are you ready?
There shouldn't be anybody there!
Anytime.
Luffy!
You're right.
I don't think any living thing
can live there now but...
Cool!!
I defeated your captain!
We're in position. We're ready too!
...it'd make sense to go check.
Usopp!
Bu! Are you people allies
of the Seven Warlords too?
We are setting out for Punk Hazard, men!
Oh no, Luffy and the others!
Luffy!
Thank you all!
Luffy-san!
I couldn't even sneak onto their
ship if I were all by myself!
Huh? Vice Admiral Smoker,
it's a restricted area.
Don't get in my way!
That bastard!
Don't you know that?
Don't thank us yet.
The Seven Warlords?!
Don't tell me about the law, you scum!
We haven't saved anybody yet.
What're you talking about?
D-Don't do it!
He's right!
Okay...
Th-Th-That was scary!
He's gonna breathe fire!
Ready?
Yo, super welcome back!
He's right above us! We can't get away!
Roger.
Cien Fleurs!
Usopp!
Okay, my turn.
Clutch!
And who's going to the island?
Dad!
Since there is uncertainty,
we shouldn't all go.
Usopp-sa, could you do me a favor?
Fling me into that guy's body!
What happened?!
I-It's a ghost!
--Franky, I need the Mini-Merry!
--Okay!
Franky, use Coup de Burst now!
What?!
Wait! Are you gonna go by yourself?
I'm afraid I can't!
I'll expand myself in his body
and break him into pieces!
Huh? Why?
Do you have a problem with that?
I didn't notice until I got
closer but the raft is too big.
Yes, I do!
I am not a ghost! I am a soul!
If we let you go by yourself, you'll
disappear without telling us!
Okay, I'll do it!
Ready?
What the hell... Oh, what should I do?
Huh?
Okay, he needs some company but
not the random belly-warmer guy.
Yeah!
Alright, go!
What do you mean by that?!
I'll cut you, kinky cook!
What's going on?
Now! Sneak in!
Yeah! That just might work!
It's hot!
Roger! Go!
Company? I'll go with him!
What?! Use the eruption of the
Thrust Up Stream to catapult us?!
Yeah, sounds like fun.
Luffy-sa! No!
Hey, maybe we'll pass
on this one. Is it okay?
Luffy-sa!
Wait for me, Nami-san!
There's no other way!
I have no choice.
I'll keep making good desserts for you!
But you don't know if it'll
erupt at the right moment...
I knew your plan all along! So stupid!
How about this?
We'll draw straws. No complaints, right?
Shut up!
Sanji-kun, are the anchors still holding?
What a pain! I'll go even if I lose.
Yeah!
Zoro! If I'm picked, go instead of me!
Hang on tight now! You
have to fly on the raft!
All of you, go to hell!
Oh yeah!
Let's change our perspective.
They say "Good luck lies in odd numbers"!
H-Hey!
I'll stake all my life on this one!
Pretend that you're in a sauna.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Not yet.
What?
Oh, Sanji-san, good job.
I am breaking out in a super sweat of cola!
Damn! That was a little off!
It's going well! We finished
the initial phase!
Another one's coming.
It's not over yet!
#%=/+$!!!
No way!
Nami, not yet?
Huh?!
You fool!
No!
All right, his companions are...
Us!
Not yet.
Can't wait!
I can't see his face like that.
Not yet.
Can't take it!
You won? How lucky!
You're...
Now, Franky!
I... I'm gonna kick your ass and...
...Straw Hat Luffy!
It's strange.
I lost!
Chicken Voyage!
Please trade!
The sky above the island is divided.
...eat that old man's heavenly food!
One half is burning hot and
the other is freezing cold.
Hey, frying pan pops!
I wonder why.
Luffy-sa, here we go!
I hope Luffy and the others are not melting.
D-Dad!
Lily?
Coup de Burst!
Hey, Luffy, we cut the chains off!
"Pirate Hunter" Zoro?!
Here. I made a special
Giant Shellfish lunch box.
Not just Straw Hat! And that's...
Can't wait!
Luffy!
A flying ship?!
Who is that?!
I'm Sanji! Sanji from the Straw Hats!
Milky Road!
Huh? What was that?
What?!
You can't get away from me!
Where did they come from?!
Whoa-whoa!
What's wrong?
Cool! You created a path of clouds.
Rescue mission accomplished!
I don't know. I feel faint...
We saw the same thing at the Sky Island.
Yeah!
Look what he's done.
Now you can make it?
I feel lightheaded...
But I assumed something like this
Now, I get to eat that heavenly food!
Maybe it's heat stroke...
Since it's made of clouds, you
have to take it while it's stable.
would happen once I heard Luffy
was on the Shark Submerge.
Okay!
Oh wow!
Um... Don't forget about me!
Franky, get over here now!
Is this...
It's super!
...what they call de-cola-ration?
There's been a change in plan!
Forget about the raft!
All right!
We'll put a rope around her father and split!
Let's go, recon team! Here we go, Mini-Merry!
Y-You guys!
Roger!
Good luck, guys!
Oh? I'm losing it too...
Lily, go!
You guys are so lucky!
Uh-huh!
I'm sure we'll have a chance to go later.
Straw Hat!
--Take care!
--Usopp, you can do it!
I won't let you get away this time!
That was close!
Please trade!
He's a vice admiral?
This Giant Shellfish is yummy!
Yeah, he's pretty strong!
Are you eating your lunch already?!
Oh yeah?
He got away again.
Looks like we can't avoid
an all-out battle, huh?
What's this? I got horns on my head!
Oh, we're going over the flames!
Once we set our sights on
someone, he can't get away.
This is fun!
Dad!
What happened to you guys? You got smaller!
I can say the same for you guys
since you know our secret now!
Lily! Are you all right?!
We'll get across the sea of fire.
Are these clouds gonna be
here when we come back?
Uh-huh! Dad, I missed you so much!
I'm glad that it stopped raining.
No, you got bigger, Luffy!
--It's a nice day to scout an island!
--But it's hot!
Go to hell!
Lily slipped into your
body and expanded herself!
Nami-san, do those clouds reach the island?
She did?!
That's right, Luffy-sa!
I don't know.
Oh, there you are!
But even if they don't,
Luffy will find a way.
I was wondering where your
voice was coming from!
Nami-san's so reckless!
Giant Luffy! How cool is that?
I'm glad that I didn't get picked to go.
We've wasted too much time here.
I can't stand the heat.
Let's go after them!
Yeah! I became a Giant!
But letting him go by
himself wasn't an option.
They'll come back as soon as
they find out there's no one.
I didn't know you planned it out so well.
How absurd! Even if you get bigger,
You're so kind, Nami-san!
Dad!
It's hot!
you're the same despicable pirate!
I'll make you a cold dessert
with the Giant Shellfish!
It's hot and that dragon
said something again!
You must be kidding! What's going on?!
Yeah!
Are you okay?!
You guys want it too?!
--Yeah!
--I want it!
Oh, I forgot about you guys!
What?!
Oh, there is the erupting island!
How could you?!
He said "the Seven Warlords."
Damage report!
See? I told you there should be an entrance.
Does he have something against them?
You bastard!
What a fight! It's been
going on for 5 hours now!
Consider that our greeting.
Like I said, maybe somebody
was living here in the past
Surface and finish them off at once!
Don't get carried away!
--They're equal in strength?
--No, Shuzo-san has an advantage.
but no one can live here now!
Oh no!
Giants are too slow - I don't think
you can keep up with my speed!
Yes, sir!
It broke the hull and we're taking on water!
The emergency signal earlier must
have come from somewhere far!
--Where is the enemy ship?!
--We can't find it yet!
Right, Robin?!
Second Gear!
It didn't look good but I like the taste.
Estimate their location from
the track of the torpedoes and
She doesn't have enough strength left.
You two are eating lunch too?
concentrate fire there!
Yes, sir!
I know you're suffering.
Let me finish this for you!
You're not gonna eat yours?
Luffy! Leave him up to me!
I don't feel like it now!
--Luffy, do you want this one?
--Yeah!
--Hey! What's going on?!
--It's a fast, hot wind!
Prepare to fire! Go, Alpacacino!
I'll cut him up this time!
Here.
Did I miss?! No worries. I'll
get you with the next one!
All right!
He's an excellent cook!
What?!
Sanji-kun outdid himself again!
In that case...
Damn you Devil Fruit eater!
Ow, ow, ow!
I can't believe it!
The disorder I had 2 years ago is recurring!
The battle is over.
Let me knock him down first!
The winner is Ain!
Hey guys, the truth is, I have
a Fear-of-unknown-islands-osis.
I know.
After that practice match,
Ain became Master Z's aide
You pirates are worthless!
I know.
Are they the pirate raiders?
Oh, I got a headache all of a sudden!
Why are they firing at us Navy?!
I feel a tightness in my chest too!
And your worthlessness is no match for me!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
and I became leader of this flying squad.
I have a stomachache!
But soon, he will find out
which one of us is more suited
His body is hot!
It's hot!
to be his right-hand person.
Gum-Gum...
This is the place.
PUNK HAZARD ISLAND ENTRANCE
The name matches.
So this is Punk Hazard...
Hey, pops! Are you alright?!
...Giant Jet...
Let's beach the Merry!
Bu! It's strange but it's cool here!
I'm okay! Where's Lily?!
Finger Pistol Ten!
Do you think the emergency
signal came from inside?
Dad! I'm here!
Looks like we got away
from the Maubeugemour Sea.
Bu! The flames are cool-bu!
Another bomb?!
Seems like no one's allowed
to enter this island.
The weather is really different
from before. It's quiet here.
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Oh, Luffy, look at that!
Oh no, not there! It tickles-bu!
Move!
A man?!
"Danger" "Keep out"?
Yeah, we've come so far! I don't
see any ship coming after us!
Outta my way!
...Spear!
There are marks of the World
Government and the Navy!
Stop it!
Of course, you don't! That was
an extra-large Coup de Burst!
That's enough-bu!
That means even if somebody's here,
he belongs to the Government.
That's what I thought!
No one can follow us - even
with a high-speed craft.
Hey!
What a wasted trip! Let's go back!
You're not gonna believe this!
Luffy-sa!
We can hide behind these reefs
and catch our breath for now.
Somebody's stuck in the dragon's back!
Damn!
Th-That was too much!
Huh?! What's going on up there?!
Uh-huh! How's it going there?
I almost died!
Usopp! Luffy, fell into the sea!
H-Hey, Zoro, what are you doing?
Then the talking voice was...
What?! I got it!
Don't tell me...
That was unexpected.
Who is that?
He's got a deep wound but...
You're... Shuzo!
Luffy! Lily!
but he's gonna be alright if
he rests for a couple days.
Oh, it's you! It's been quite a while!
Good, it's open.
Thanks, Lily!
Thank you, Chopper-sa! I appreciate it!
Don't mention it.
Open...
You bastard!
I didn't know you were on board, Momonga...
I'm so happy that I could help you!
B-Being thanked doesn't make
me happy at all, you bastard!
Thank you, Luffy-sa!
You're a vice admiral now, aren't you?
Eat your own wing!
All right! Now I can have
pops' heavenly food!
Too hot!
Don't tell me...
...you're responsible for
all the raids on pirates!
Anyway, I'm glad that he's okay.
Uh-huh!
You guys! Trespassing is a crime!
So can you make the heavenly food, like now?
Yes, I am! I'm gonna cut
this guy's head off too!
But we pirates are criminals anyway.
Th-The food is ruined!
I won't let you do that!
Are you a monster?!
Take a look around!
Keep me out of it!
You can't complain because you did it.
Huh?
Do you wanna challenge the Government?!
Why?! Chopper said he's gonna be okay...
--Let's go.
--No! Food!
Oh, we already did!
Fool!
We'll get some food on our way and head
You weren't listening to me, Luffy!
Oh, hey, wait!
for a volcano somewhere. What do you say?
I said he needs to rest!
It's too hot, really.
What? What about the heavenly food?
Sounds good.
Zoro! Here he comes!
All right! Let's go!
Boy, even if Lily-chan's father were okay,
Everything is on fire.
What should we do about his raft?
We can't load it on the ship.
But it doesn't seem like the
island has been burning forever.
we don't have anything to
make heavenly food out of!
--Seems like it's not a problem.
--Oh.
So was there a disaster? Or an accident?
Super!
Usopp!
Oh, I got some food!
I think he made something.
All right!
Just give him over to us. If you don't...
What?
Where? Lily, where is it?!
The great shipwright - Franky! Thank you!
Wait... Luffy!
Special Attack - Green Star!
Why?!
There, look!
Don't mention it! Super!
You were a great Navy soldier.
Why are you doing this?
Oh, there it is! When did you get it?!
Trampolia!
When the warship blew away
earlier, food was raining down.
That was close!
Do you wanna know?
I'll tell you then.
I thought "What a waste!" and
picked up as much as I could!
Hey, Luffy!
We're the Neo Navy, concerned
about today's New World.
Excellent work!
But under those circumstances? How greedy!
We banded together to kill
all pirates in the New World!
One-Sword...
Oh yeah!
Dad, Luffy-sa and the others were
in danger! What was I thinking?!
Those were probably not people's houses.
How absurd to take a villain to Impel
Down and let him continue to live!
You bastard! You survived?!
I think there were some kind
of Government facilities here.
How did you find me?!
...Style!
I got some sake too.
Like you did to the Straw Hats,
Excellent work.
In the name of Master Z, I'm gonna kill
the pirate - Panz Fry, right here!
They shut this island
down because it started
Hey!
we secretly put this on Panz Fry's body.
burning and became dangerous?
But even if we have food, frying
pan pops can't cook, can he?
Lion Strike!
Did you say Z?!
Or these facilities were
hazardous from the beginning?
It's a method of tracking pirates that
I learned from a teacher long ago.
The fact that the Log Pose didn't
point to this island troubles me.
Of course not!
You should not tell him that, Shuzo-san!
I'll cook for...
What are you doing?! I told you to rest!
It's inexcusable for you
to drag us Navy soldiers
Hey!
I forgot about that.
in for the purpose of killing all pirates!
The guy from earlier - are you there?!
Ow, ow, ow... It's just for
a little while. I'll be fine.
He did it!
Well, I don't care!
We'll take you all to Impel Down.
We're here to help you!
It doesn't matter that
you know our secret now
Impel Down?! No way!
Dad! Do as Chopper-sa says!
because all of you Navy people are
gonna die here among those pirates!
We're not gonna tell you anything no matter
Your name is Luffy, isn't it?
This dragon looks yummy!
how much you torture us!
Hey! Come out!
If you wanna kill us, just
do it here in the New World!
How could you do that to Dad and Luffy-sa!
We can grill it with the fire on the island!
Yeah!  I'm gonna become
the King of the Pirates!
Samurai!
That sounds great!
Don't call them! They're murderers!
Ow, ow, ow...
--Now you have an appetite?
--It's stress eating!
Dad!
No, it's up to the law to decide.
Cien Fleurs!
Listen, Lily.
Dad?
That's how the Navy's justice works!
Luffy wants so badly  to
eat the food that I make.
Lily-chan!
You know I've been thinking.
What are Luffy and the silly swordsman doing?
The man on the Snail said
"It's cold," didn't he?
What an honor for a cook!
Who are you now?
It's cold... Is this the Boss?!
W-Well, I understand that. But...
Me?! I'm Panz Fry's
daughter - Lily Enstomach!
You're right.
Nami-san!
On top of that, they saved our lives.
It's really hot here but he said it was cold.
So you're a pirate?! Then you die, too!
This time I made a cold crepe
with the Giant Shellfish!
Maybe he's stupid.
If I don't return the favor, I should
be ashamed of myself as a cook... No.
No way, Sherlock!
Is there a cold place on this burning island?
It'll pair nicely with champagne...
As a Giant!
Huh?
Iron Body!
Or that he had a chilling experience?
Dad!
Three-Section Lariat!
Oh? Are they sleeping?
Robin, you're scaring me!
Now, bring that food here!
Lily-chan!
I'll make them my heavenly food!
Another disturbance? I'm sick of this!
Really?! Thanks, frying pan pops!
What is it? What is it?
No, I have to thank you
instead. Thank you, Luffy!
What is that noise?!
How dare you try to hit a lady!
You worthless piece of crap!
Oh, that's...
Fog?
You...
--Who the hell are you?!
Lily-chan! I'll make something too!
Shuzo-san, I think he's "Black
Foot" Sanji of the Straw Hats!
It's yummy, Sanji!
Okay, I'll help him too! I'll
carry those bags of food!
No, it's not!
I thought I was gonna melt in the heat.
Luffy-sa! Everybody! Thank you!
He looks very different
from the wanted poster!
Damn! I inhaled too much!
Me too!
Sake! Sake!
It's cooling me down!
I assume he's had cosmetic surgery!
I'll never forget what you did for us!
You go and help them too.
Ow, I feel a sharp pain!
The gas made them sleep!
No, I haven't!
He's a pirate? What is his bounty?
Is it a natural phenomenon,
indigenous to the New World?
Uh-huh! I will!
Are my teeth sensitive?
Don't make a big deal out of it.
It's 77 million berries!
You guys only get to eat it
because there are leftovers.
See you! Thank you for the food!
Or did somebody sneak into the ship?
--Humph! He's a nobody.
--What did you say?!
Thank Nami-san!
But he's a pirate too. Sink
them all into the sea!
Don't push yourself too
much, you heroic chef!
Oh, there are a lot for you, Nami-san!
I hope those four
Yes, thank you! The great doctor - Chopper!
Nami, what's the matter?
that went to the island took a
Baby Transponder Snail with them.
Roger!
Augh! We're in big trouble!
The great doctor? Me?
Shuzo-san, I found them!
They're hiding behind a reef!
Yeah, the clouds...
Now, Lily-chan, shrink down!
Compliments like that don't impress me!
I have to let them know... somehow...
I just noticed there's something strange
about the sky above the island.
Lily! Let's fight together again as Giants!
Uh-huh!
How annoying! All ships, prepare for battle!
The far side looks like the Arctic sky.
Uh-huh! You were the strongest
Giant I've ever known!
Let's blow them up along with the reef!
No way!
I-I'm afraid we used up all our
torpedoes in the battle earlier
See you again!
I don't want to fight for pirates but...
and we're almost out of bombshells too.
All right, let's go!
A Giant?!
...I won't let you do whatever
you like on this ship
All right. Then...
No,
No, we still have a torpedo.
Yeah!
it's bigger than a Giant!
while it's under the control of the Navy!
No, we don't.
You're very sensible for a Navy soldier.
So it was the noise of the wind.
We can use this submersible as a torpedo!
Praised by a pirate?
We are the proud soldiers of
the Neo Navy's flying squad!
What I feared most has happened.
That is why I'd say today's Navy is useless.
SHUZO WILL BE PLACED IN IMPEL DOWN
What's wrong, Luffy?
We trusted in Master Z and
Shuzo-san and got this far!
Shame on you!
Shut up, you backstabber!
I should have made myself clearer to him.
Shuzo-san! Let us fight with you! Please!!
Is that...
I'm sorry!
Do you think the Navy found
out what we are up to?
Me too!
Pirate blah-blah... Navy blah-blah...
What?!
Huh? Does it actually exist?!
Don't worry.
But...
Two humans...
They won't say anything no matter
how horrible the torture.
No, it's a mythical creature!
Enough with this bullshit!
I'm proud of you guys! I'll
care for you to your deathbed!
...one cyborg.
Straw Hat!
There's no way that it's real!
And their pet.
But look at those features...
Pops' heavenly food is...
Fight to your heart's content
as a Neo Navy soldier!
After all, isn't he a member
of our indomitable Neo Navy?
I don't think it could be anything else!
...all mine!
Tie them all up!
He's a pirate with a 400 million
berry bounty - Straw Hat Luffy!
Alright!
You're right.
It's good that they're pirates.
All torpedoes, go!
Master Z. We will arrive
at the First Island soon.
Oh, 400 million, huh?
No one will care if they go missing.
Now, it's finally time to
fight! Let's terrify them all!
Great! I'll kill you all at once!
The last day of the New World is nigh.
We will kill all pirates
with our own bare hands!
I'm not gonna let you get away this time!
A dragon?!
Damn pirates!
Let's take them to the Master!
The Straw Hats have begun fighting the Marines
As the Straw Hats sail the Maubeugemour Sea,
Luffy and crew have saved
someone from the dragon...
The Neo Marines have launched a surprise attack
A legendary creature has suddenly appeared. A dragon!
as well as the mysterious Neo Marines.
and the Straw Hats begin their final battle against Shuzo.
the first island of the New World appears before them.
But they are extremely shocked
when they see his bizarre appearance.
It breathes fire and has razor-sharp fangs.
Both sides deal blows
They fight each other to a draw.
As the crew marvels at its bizarre appearance,
until Shuzo reveals his ultimate weapon
It's amazing destructive power
Meanwhile, Sanji and the others
have been captured by someone
Then, as Maubeugemour reveals
its unimaginable wrath
they receive an emergency distress call
proves difficul for even Luffy and Zoro to handle.
and unleashes it on Luffy.
and rescuing Panz Fry seems impossible...
and are locked in a mysterious room.
and then head toward the island.
As the shockwave hits the Straw Hats,
Then, the dragon says something
It is there that they see an unbelievable sight!
But that will lead them into a battle larger than any they have ever faced!
Lily takes fate into her own hands
and makes her decision!
The Straw Hats pull off something incredible!
which is even more shocking!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Arriving! A Burning Island - Punk Hazard!"
"The Straw Hats Stunned! Enter: A
Samurai's Horrifying Severed Head!"
"Z's Ambition! A Great and
Desperate Escape Plan!"
"Z's Ambition! Luffy vs. Shuzo!"
"Arriving! A Burning Island - Punk Hazard!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!