Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
The Straw Hats have left the
Fish-Man Island and finally
reached the New World.
But not before entering the
treacherous Maubeugemour Sea.
Arriving there, they met a Giant
girl who ate the Mini-Mini Fruit.
My name is Lily Enstomach.
People call me "Lily the Glutton"!
I eat a lot for a woman, right?
The ship carrying Dad will pass through here!
You mean the Navy is coming?!
If they see us, it's not gonna be pretty!
Yeah. But I have to save Dad at any cost!
Before they take him to Impel Down,
this is my last chance to save him!
Lily.
Let me help you!
I wanna try that heavenly food
that only your dad can make!
They decided to help Lily save her father
- Panz Fry from the Navy's ship. However...
...a mysterious group called the
Neo Navy is trying to kill him.
I heard a ship carrying Panz
Fry, that big-shot pirate,
will pass through the Maubeugemour Sea soon.
It's the Navy!
--Dad!
--Is that him?
"Z's Ambition! A Dark and Powerful Army!"
SIN
They deployed 4 ships just
to transport a pirate?
I guess Lily's dad is really a big-shot.
Dad...
Is that the only reason?
That security is a strange choice
but I wonder why they chose to pass through
this dangerous area on
their way to Impel Down.
Alright! Let's raid them already!
No way! Don't be ridiculous!
Listen. Our priority is
to save Lily's father!
If we make a raid without
any plan, he could get hurt!
She's right, Luffy!
If anything happens to her father,
we wouldn't be able to eat
that heavenly volcano food!
Then what should we do?
Can I take charge of this operation?
What do you say?
Yes, I want you to do it, Nami-sa!
Uh-huh, all right!
First, we need a diversion team.
You take the Mini-Merry and divert
their attention from a distance...
...to set up the infiltration team.
The members of the team are
Chopper as boat operator,
Luffy, Robin, and Brook.
A diversion?  That means
I can kick their asses?!
No, you can't!
Robin and Brook will create a diversion!
You just have to wait in case
something really goes wrong!
Don't do anything before!
Now, the infiltration team.
You take the Shark Submerge and sneak
onto the raft without being
seen by the Navy soldiers.
Then cut the chain and release Lily's father.
The members are Zoro, Sanji-kun...
Count on me!
...Usopp, and Lily - can you do it?
Uh-huh!
That sounds like more fun.
All right?
The point is how to bring
such a giant man back safely.
You're right. It'll draw their
attention since he's so big.
It'd be nice if we could
steal one of their ships
but it'd take too much time and energy.
So what we're gonna do instead is detach
the raft from the ship and whisk
it away with Coup de Burst.
Franky, you stay on the Sunny and
wait somewhere they can't see you.
Prepare for Coup de Burst.
I got it!
What about you, Nami?
Me? I'll spy on their movements
with the White Hobby Horse
and take command of this mission.
Don't forget that we're
in the Maubeugemour Sea.
Watch out for a sudden change in weather.
Now let's do it!
Okay!
Come to think of it, we are all
Devil Fruit eaters in this team.
You're right.
So if we fall into the sea,
we're pretty much finished.
What?!
I hope we don't drown
and get eaten by sharks.
No! You're making us scared, Robin!
Since we're deploying on the open sea,
I placed all Devil Fruit
eaters except for Lily
in the diversion team to be safe.
See you!
Where is Luffy?
I told him to get on board the Mini-Merry!
He took the Shark Submerge
instead and left earlier.
What?
Well, he came with us saying that
the diversion sounded boring.
Lily, I can't wait to see your dad!
Uh-huh!
How selfish!
Hey, Luffy, are you listening?!
Don't you dare sneak onto the raft!
It will screw up the whole plan!
Alright!
By the way, both you and your dad came
from Elbaf like other Giants, right?
Usopp-sa, you know Elbaf?
Do I know it? Yes, of course!
The brave warriors of the
sea - Dorry and Broggy...
...are our close friends!
What?! Have you met those
legendary pirate bosses?!
Yeah, we have!
I can't believe it! I've never even met them!
My dad has been friends with
them since they were kids.
Really?!
Yeah. He told me about them all the time.
Sounds like they're having fun!
Let's have fun here too!
Yeah!
The song is "Let's Go to the Rescue"!
Yeehaw!
Go, go, let's go! To the Ill-Tempered Sea!
Shut up!
You got us in trouble, Brook!
Sorry! I'm really sorry!
Don't get in my way!
Move out of my way!
I've never heard of a pirate who
so brazenly boarded a Government-owned
cargo ship before.
Why did you do it?
I just wanted to take back
what you took from them!
Since you Navy people killed Whitebeard,
the New World is in disorder.
That island where the Government's ship was
moored was not an exception.
The islanders were on
the brink of starvation.
But the crew on that ship took away
all food that they had stored,
to provide for the World
Nobles' nightly feasts!
I'm a cook!
I have to provide food for hungry people!
So you boarded the ship
to steal food for them?
The islands are in disorder
because of you pirates.
Don't shift the blame!
After all, we remain as far apart as ever.
We'll never be of the same mind!
You're right.
Somebody is raiding pirates these days.
Since we have a pirate on our
ship, we are possible targets.
Be on the look-out and shoot
anything that moves on the sea!
Yes, sir!
Guys, are you ready?
Anytime.
We're in position. We're ready too!
Thank you all!
I couldn't even sneak onto their
ship if I were all by myself!
Don't thank us yet.
We haven't saved anybody yet.
He's right!
Ready?
Roger.
Cien Fleurs!
Okay, my turn.
Clutch!
What happened?!
I-It's a ghost!
I am not a ghost! I am a soul!
What's going on?
Now! Sneak in!
Roger! Go!
Oh, Sanji-san, good job.
It's going well! We finished
the initial phase!
Huh?!
I can't see his face like that.
You're...
...Straw Hat Luffy!
Hey, frying pan pops!
D-Dad!
Lily?
Hey, Luffy, we cut the chains off!
"Pirate Hunter" Zoro?!
Not just Straw Hat! And that's...
Who is that?!
I'm Sanji! Sanji from the Straw Hats!
What?!
Where did they come from?!
Look what he's done.
But I assumed something like this
would happen once I heard Luffy
was on the Shark Submerge.
Franky, get over here now!
There's been a change in plan!
Forget about the raft!
We'll put a rope around her father and split!
Roger!
Lily, go!
Uh-huh!
Straw Hat!
I won't let you get away this time!
That was close!
He's a vice admiral?
Yeah, he's pretty strong!
Oh yeah?
Looks like we can't avoid
an all-out battle, huh?
Dad!
Lily! Are you all right?!
Uh-huh! Dad, I missed you so much!
Dad!
You must be kidding! What's going on?!
Are you okay?!
What?!
Damage report!
Consider that our greeting.
Surface and finish them off at once!
Yes, sir!
It broke the hull and we're taking on water!
--Where is the enemy ship?!
--We can't find it yet!
Estimate their location from
the track of the torpedoes and
concentrate fire there!
Yes, sir!
Prepare to fire! Go, Alpacacino!
Are they the pirate raiders?
Why are they firing at us Navy?!
Hey, pops! Are you alright?!
I'm okay! Where's Lily?!
Dad! I'm here!
Another bomb?!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Move!
A man?!
Outta my way!
Luffy-sa!
Damn!
Usopp! Luffy, fell into the sea!
What?! I got it!
That was unexpected.
Who is that?
You're... Shuzo!
Oh, it's you! It's been quite a while!
I didn't know you were on board, Momonga...
You're a vice admiral now, aren't you?
Don't tell me...
...you're responsible for
all the raids on pirates!
Yes, I am! I'm gonna cut
this guy's head off too!
I won't let you do that!
Take a look around!
Just give him over to us. If you don't...
Why?!
You were a great Navy soldier.
Why are you doing this?
Do you wanna know?
I'll tell you then.
We're the Neo Navy, concerned
about today's New World.
We banded together to kill
all pirates in the New World!
How absurd to take a villain to Impel
Down and let him continue to live!
In the name of Master Z, I'm gonna kill
the pirate - Panz Fry, right here!
Did you say Z?!
You should not tell him that, Shuzo-san!
I forgot about that.
Well, I don't care!
It doesn't matter that
you know our secret now
because all of you Navy people are
gonna die here among those pirates!
How could you do that to Dad and Luffy-sa!
Lily-chan!
What are Luffy and the silly swordsman doing?
Who are you now?
Me?! I'm Panz Fry's
daughter - Lily Enstomach!
So you're a pirate?! Then you die, too!
Iron Body!
Three-Section Lariat!
Lily-chan!
Another disturbance? I'm sick of this!
How dare you try to hit a lady!
You worthless piece of crap!
You...
--Who the hell are you?!
Shuzo-san, I think he's "Black
Foot" Sanji of the Straw Hats!
He looks very different
from the wanted poster!
I assume he's had cosmetic surgery!
No, I haven't!
He's a pirate? What is his bounty?
It's 77 million berries!
--Humph! He's a nobody.
--What did you say?!
But he's a pirate too. Sink
them all into the sea!
Roger!
Augh! We're in big trouble!
Now, Lily-chan, shrink down!
Uh-huh!
I don't want to fight for pirates but...
...I won't let you do whatever
you like on this ship
while it's under the control of the Navy!
You're very sensible for a Navy soldier.
Praised by a pirate?
That is why I'd say today's Navy is useless.
Shame on you!
Shut up, you backstabber!
Pirate blah-blah... Navy blah-blah...
Enough with this bullshit!
Straw Hat!
Pops' heavenly food is...
...all mine!
He's a pirate with a 400 million
berry bounty - Straw Hat Luffy!
Oh, 400 million, huh?
Great! I'll kill you all at once!
The Straw Hats have begun fighting the Marines
as well as the mysterious Neo Marines.
They fight each other to a draw.
Then, as Maubeugemour reveals
its unimaginable wrath
and rescuing Panz Fry seems impossible...
The Straw Hats pull off something incredible!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Z's Ambition! A Great and
Desperate Escape Plan!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!