Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving the fierce
battle at the Fish-Man Island,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
Navigating the treacherous Maubeugemour Sea,
they met a Giant girl named Lily
who ate the Mini-Mini Fruit
and got fired up to help
her save her father -
Panz Fry from the Navy's ship. However,
a mysterious group called the
Neo Navy was trying to kill him.
Surface and finish them off at once!
Yes, sir!
You're responsible for all
the raids on pirates?!
Yes, I am! I'm gonna cut
this guy's head off too!
And a three-way battle heated up between the
Straw Hats, the Navy and the Neo Navy.
You worthless pirates are no match for me!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Jet...
Finger Pistol Ten!
...Spear!
And they were able to bring down
the menacing enemy - Shuzo!
But this was just the first foray into
the New World for the Straw Hats.
All right, let's go!
Yeah!
"Arriving! A Burning Island - Punk Hazard!"
Go!
Hey, hey, hey!
Whoa, whoa! Are we gonna be okay?
The Sunny will be fine!
What's that?
What?! That's impossible!
A red sea?!
Look! The volcano's erupting!
Let's go to that island!
What?!
Wait a minute, Luffy!
Just as I thought.
None of the needles point to that island.
Let's go to that island!
I said "Wait"!
Why?! There is a volcano! It looks like fun!
Who could resist?
Listen to me, Luffy!
None of the 3 needles is
pointing at the island!
It's too peculiar even
in the strange New World!
It's erupting again!
It's right there! Who
cares about the needles?!
Let's just go there!
No way! We can't get any closer!
Because the sea is on fire!
I don't understand you!
It's perfect.
Hey, that's the Giant
Shellfish Panz Fry gave us.
I thought we could cook
this in that sea of fire.
Sanji! Now isn't the time for that!
--Sparks!
--The ship will catch fire too!
No!
The Sunny is super not gonna let us down!
That's not the point!
There's something wrong with this sea!
Look at those fish bones, bones, bones!
Huh? Did you just call me?
Wh-What's that?!
Hey, what's this? The
Transponder Snail is crying!
Hey, what's wrong?! You have a stomachache?
Fool! That's an emergency signal.
Somebody's calling for help.
If I pick it up, can we hear them?
Wait, Luffy!
More than 50 percent of
emergency signals are fake!
It could be a Navy trap - one they use often.
If the line is tapped, they
will find out where we are.
That's our Robin!
Hey, Luffy, you have to be careful...
Clank.
Hello? My name is Monkey D. Luffy!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
You picked up too fast and said too much!
Help me!
What happened?
It's cold... Is this the Boss?!
No, I'm not the Boss. Is it cold there?
My colleagues are getting
cut one after another!
The samurai are gonna kill us!
Samurai?
Hey you, what's your name?! Where are you?!
Somebody please help me!
I'm on...
...Punk Hazard!
He got killed!
Th-That was...
I smell trouble...
He got killed - of course there is trouble!
Somebody just cut him!
The New World is scary!
Maybe he was acting and it's a trap.
How level-headed!
Come on, Robin-san!
Speaking of samurai, Brook...
Yes, what you think is right.
That's that name of the swordsmen
from the Wano Kingdom.
The Wano Kingdom - closed
off to the outside world.
It's not even affiliated
with the World Government.
They say those swordsmen
called samurai are so strong
even the Navy can't approach.
This great sword - Shusui was once
carried by a legendary samurai.
If you become its owner,
the sword will be pleased.
I let this samurai's
body... take the beating.
I feel bad.
I've never heard of that country.
But he said Punk Hazard,
not the Wano Kingdom.
Did he mean the island of fire right there?
If he was using a Baby Transponder Snail,
that's about how far the signal can reach.
All right! Let's go help that guy!
No!
Luffy, think again! I think it's too late!
Samurai are scary!
I'm scared too!
Hey you, what's your name?! Where are you?!
Somebody please help me! I'm on...
...Punk Hazard!
Smoker-san, that was...
Did he say Punk Hazard?
Damn!
How could they have gotten there?
The battle at the Fish-Man Island,
the incident after that...
If we plot the course they took from there...
Punk Hazard... It's possible they're there.
Don't do it! I'll do anything!
I'll do whatever you ask me to!
Then get charred!
Stop it, you guys! Stop bullying pirates!
Tashigi! Let's head for Punk Hazard!
But Smoker-san,
Punk Hazard
has been deserted since they sealed it
off after what happened 4 years ago!
There shouldn't be anybody there!
You're right.
I don't think any living thing
can live there now but...
...it'd make sense to go check.
We are setting out for Punk Hazard, men!
Huh? Vice Admiral Smoker,
it's a restricted area.
Don't you know that?
Don't tell me about the law, you scum!
Okay...
And who's going to the island?
Since there is uncertainty,
we shouldn't all go.
--Franky, I need the Mini-Merry!
--Okay!
Wait! Are you gonna go by yourself?
Do you have a problem with that?
Yes, I do!
If we let you go by yourself, you'll
disappear without telling us!
Huh?
Okay, he needs some company but
not the random belly-warmer guy.
What do you mean by that?!
I'll cut you, kinky cook!
Company? I'll go with him!
Yeah, sounds like fun.
Hey, maybe we'll pass
on this one. Is it okay?
I have no choice.
How about this?
We'll draw straws. No complaints, right?
What a pain! I'll go even if I lose.
Zoro! If I'm picked, go instead of me!
They say "Good luck lies in odd numbers"!
I'll stake all my life on this one!
#%=/+$!!!
All right, his companions are...
Us!
Can't wait!
Can't take it!
You won? How lucky!
I lost!
Please trade!
Here. I made a special
Giant Shellfish lunch box.
Can't wait!
Milky Road!
Cool! You created a path of clouds.
We saw the same thing at the Sky Island.
Now you can make it?
Since it's made of clouds, you
have to take it while it's stable.
Okay!
All right!
Let's go, recon team! Here we go, Mini-Merry!
Good luck, guys!
You guys are so lucky!
I'm sure we'll have a chance to go later.
--Take care!
--Usopp, you can do it!
Please trade!
This Giant Shellfish is yummy!
Are you eating your lunch already?!
Oh, we're going over the flames!
This is fun!
We'll get across the sea of fire.
Are these clouds gonna be
here when we come back?
I'm glad that it stopped raining.
--It's a nice day to scout an island!
--But it's hot!
Nami-san, do those clouds reach the island?
I don't know.
But even if they don't,
Luffy will find a way.
Nami-san's so reckless!
I'm glad that I didn't get picked to go.
I can't stand the heat.
But letting him go by
himself wasn't an option.
They'll come back as soon as
they find out there's no one.
I didn't know you planned it out so well.
You're so kind, Nami-san!
I'll make you a cold dessert
with the Giant Shellfish!
Yeah!
You guys want it too?!
--Yeah!
--I want it!
Oh, there is the erupting island!
See? I told you there should be an entrance.
Like I said, maybe somebody
was living here in the past
but no one can live here now!
The emergency signal earlier must
have come from somewhere far!
Right, Robin?!
It didn't look good but I like the taste.
You two are eating lunch too?
You're not gonna eat yours?
I don't feel like it now!
--Luffy, do you want this one?
--Yeah!
Here.
He's an excellent cook!
Sanji-kun outdid himself again!
I can't believe it!
The disorder I had 2 years ago is recurring!
Hey guys, the truth is, I have
a Fear-of-unknown-islands-osis.
I know.
Oh, I got a headache all of a sudden!
I feel a tightness in my chest too!
I have a stomachache!
It's hot!
This is the place.
PUNK HAZARD ISLAND ENTRANCE
The name matches.
So this is Punk Hazard...
Let's beach the Merry!
Do you think the emergency
signal came from inside?
Seems like no one's allowed
to enter this island.
Oh, Luffy, look at that!
"Danger" "Keep out"?
There are marks of the World
Government and the Navy!
That means even if somebody's here,
he belongs to the Government.
What a wasted trip! Let's go back!
H-Hey, Zoro, what are you doing?
Don't tell me...
Good, it's open.
Open...
Too hot!
You guys! Trespassing is a crime!
But we pirates are criminals anyway.
Keep me out of it!
Do you wanna challenge the Government?!
Oh, we already did!
Oh, hey, wait!
It's too hot, really.
Everything is on fire.
But it doesn't seem like the
island has been burning forever.
So was there a disaster? Or an accident?
Wait... Luffy!
That was close!
Hey, Luffy!
Those were probably not people's houses.
I think there were some kind
of Government facilities here.
They shut this island
down because it started
burning and became dangerous?
Or these facilities were
hazardous from the beginning?
The fact that the Log Pose didn't
point to this island troubles me.
Hey!
The guy from earlier - are you there?!
We're here to help you!
Hey! Come out!
Samurai!
Don't call them! They're murderers!
--Now you have an appetite?
--It's stress eating!
You know I've been thinking.
The man on the Snail said
"It's cold," didn't he?
It's cold... Is this the Boss?!
You're right.
It's really hot here but he said it was cold.
Maybe he's stupid.
No way, Sherlock!
Is there a cold place on this burning island?
Or that he had a chilling experience?
Robin, you're scaring me!
What is it? What is it?
What is that noise?!
Oh, that's...
It's yummy, Sanji!
I thought I was gonna melt in the heat.
It's cooling me down!
Ow, I feel a sharp pain!
Are my teeth sensitive?
You guys only get to eat it
because there are leftovers.
Thank Nami-san!
Oh, there are a lot for you, Nami-san!
Nami, what's the matter?
Yeah, the clouds...
I just noticed there's something strange
about the sky above the island.
The far side looks like the Arctic sky.
No way!
A Giant?!
No,
it's bigger than a Giant!
So it was the noise of the wind.
What's wrong, Luffy?
Is that...
What?!
Huh? Does it actually exist?!
No, it's a mythical creature!
There's no way that it's real!
But look at those features...
I don't think it could be anything else!
A dragon?!
A legendary creature has suddenly appeared. A dragon!
It breathes fire and has razor-sharp fangs.
It's amazing destructive power
proves difficul for even Luffy and Zoro to handle.
Then, the dragon says something
which is even more shocking!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Arriving! A Burning Island - Punk Hazard!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!