Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
However, no one has ever fully explored it
and his friends venture into that sea.
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
and his friends venture into that sea.
Responding to an emergency signal,
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others went to Punk
Hazard and there, they faced...
After surviving a fierce battle,
Bu! It's strange but it's cool here!
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,--
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
entered the New World,--
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
-- the harshest sea ruled
by the Four Emperors.
You're not gonna believe this!
Responding to an emergency
signal, Luffy and the
Then help us!
After receiving an emergency signal,
they landed on Punk Hazard Island.
Somebody's stuck in the dragon's back!
others were heading to the
other side of the island.
What does he mean?
He's torn in half! I'm sorry!
You have to help us! Please!
It was a strange island divided
One-Sword...
You fool! Sorry isn't enough! You killed him!
Meanwhile, Nami and the
others were held captive
into two parts; the Burning
Lands and the Ice Lands.
Please!
...Style!
After being taken to a
in a mysterious facility
on Punk Hazard Island...
Lion Strike!
mysterious facility by an
unknown group of people,
They came across a strange lower-half man.
To rescue Nami and the others
who are held captive,
I came to this island to rescue my son!
Nami and the others encountered
strange children.
Meanwhile, Nami and the others were...
Luffy's group headed to the Ice Lands.
A centaur?
I don't mind cutting thousands
if they get in my way!
Tie them all up!
Let's help these children!
But they were unaware that some
How funny!
Alright!
--There!
--Shoot! Don't let them get away!
former acquaintances were also on the island.
What are you saying, Nami-san?!
It's good that they're pirates.
Meanwhile, Nami and the others held
captive in an unknown building...
We don't know for sure they need saving!
Oh no, that'll be far enough!
No one will care if they go missing.
We just met them and we don't
know what's going on here!
What brought you here - to my vacation home?
These are all parts of my face.
Weapons Left!
It's not our job to help every single person!
Could I ask you to put them back together?
White Chase-ya!
Let's take them to the Master!
What's wrong with them?!
I understand what you're saying but...
I think there is something
wrong with the chin and the
"The Warlord! Trafalgar Law!"
top part but it's okay.
"The Straw Hats Stunned! Enter: A
Samurai's Horrifying Severed Head!"
...you can't turn your back
on a child crying for help!
Thank you!
A severed-head just talked!
You just noticed?
Who are they?
There you are, intruders!
All right! Let's go!
PUNK HAZARD ISLAND
Giant children?!
Ch-Children?!
Huh?!
THE BURNING LANDS
I won't let you get away! Wait, you bastards!
What's going on here?
Now, what should we do about him?
You have...
Oh no!
...those...
That centaur again!
...legs!
"Save the Children! The
Straw Hats Start to Fight!"
Boss!
Let's pull him out!
They are so cool!
The intruders are going that
way! Please finish them off!
Hey, who are you?!
Get your hands off of me-bu!
Hello? Did you find them?
Hey! I'm helping you! Stay calm!
THE ICE LANDS - A MYSTERIOUS FACILITY
Is that the Boss?
Yes, we found them.
Here we go!
We were about to kill them.
I see a man with swords.
Wow, he's completely stuck
in the dragon's body.
There are four intruders.
BISCUIT ROOM SANJI'S GROUP
So is that the samurai who cut our people?
I see.
How is that possible?
His upper body is stuck but
he's talking normally.
That's exciting.
Trafalgar! I know you're a Warlord but
we need you to ask you to step aside.
Snow! Snow! I love playing with snow!
Please be careful!
Why isn't he suffocating?
Move out of the way!
Roger.
Ta-dah! Snowmen!
Who the hell is he?
We know somebody else is here on the island!
It looks like me!
"Startling! The Secret of the
Island is Finally Revealed!"
I-I-It's missing!
Oh?
INSIDE OF DR. VEGAPUNK'S FORMER
LABORATORY NAMI'S GROUP
Dad! Mom!
Hey! Hey!
What's missing?
Who are these kids?
Who the hell...
Is this the island's day-care or something?
What?
Hey, you said "We are not sick
anymore" earlier, didn't you?
Whaaat?!
Sliced up by your enemy and...
They're so big but are they Giants?
He's torn in half! I'm sorry!
...Alive without your body?
You fool! Sorry isn't
enough!  You killed him!
Did we come to an island of Giants?
Uh-huh.
How? I don't get it!
What kind of sickness did you have?
"A Swordplay Showdown! Brook vs.
the Mysterious Torso Samurai!"
But there are not-so-big ones too.
That's like Buggy. How weird.
None of you look sick to me.
Then it's a multi-racial nursery?
I don't know. But they
told us that we were sick
I wish I could cut my belly
and die in obscurity but...
Oh, I'm finally separated from it-bu!
There are no adults.
What?!
and we'd get better in a year.
...there is something that I need
The lower body just talked! What's going on?!
to do even if I have to live in disgrace!
Hey, who are you?
I don't know any of them.
A zombie! A monster!
Get better in a year?
Oh, you must be the ones who got frozen!
Uh-huh.
Did you escape?
Wait a minute.
--Frozen?
--What is she talking about?
And people who were asked
This is strange.
By the way, do you know
where this is, old man?
The mystery of the island deepens.
There is no upper half here.
to treat me by my dad and
mom took me to this place.
Old man?!
What do you mean?
Women can't talk to warriors like that!
That means your parents
sent you to this place?
No matter how far we go, all
we see is a wall of ice.
He didn't have an upper
body from the very start?
Not really, those people told
me that out of the blue in
Women have to walk three steps behind men
There is no point in protecting ourselves
from the gas if we can't land.
Oh, this is too freaky!
and talk modestly and humbly!
Isn't that...
Don't give up yet. Keep searching.
front of my house and took me here.
He's kind of big.
They said they didn't want my
dad and mom to get infected.
It's no use.
...A robot?!
What did you say, you jerk?!
Who is there and what are you doing?
So I couldn't even say goodbye.
Wh-What's going on?
You're just a severed-head!
An eruption?!
It's a robot!
That's what happened to you all?
I sense your presence but
I don't have eyes or ears.
How awesome!
How could you say that to
someone who helped you?!
--Un-huh.
--Me too.
--I love robots!
--They're the best!
No way! It seems they were kidnapped!
G-Get your hands off of me!
You're bizarre!
Huh? The best?
You still wanna act like that?! You...
Some strangers took them here
I don't know who you are
but get out of my way-bu!
Stop it, young woman!
Around here, it feels like...
Oh? Sanji-kun?!
without letting them see their parents?
Robot! Robot! Robot!
What?
What?!
...we are being watched by Akainu and Aokiji.
That could only mean...
I cannot die here!
Robot! Robot! Robot!
...you're really very sick!
What country are you from?!
You kids. So you really love...
What are you, stupid?!
Oh, he took off!
--Oh, that's scary!
--Let's go back!
You're so rude and brash!
I'm not going to let them get away!
Are you all doing okay?
...my armored self?!
But I assume somebody ripped off
your clothes and you're hurt.
That goddamn Warlord!
If any of you can't run,
I'll carry you on my back.
Hey, tell me about "the ones who got frozen."
You have my sympathy.
They all look fine.
Hey, wait! Why don't you join my...
Look! There's a stuffed animal!
Yes, we are! The Master has been treating us.
Nobody ripped off my clothes!
No, Luffy!
It's a stuffed racoon!
Stop the ship.
I'm a reindeer!
I'm gonna go catch him!
The Master?
Lovely!
What happened?
Uh-huh, the Master.
This is the way I dress!
Can you grill the dragon for me?!
Cute!
There.
How obscene! All you have is a breast-band!
--Help me!
--I want it!
Master!
What?
Wait, legs!
Prepare to fire!
Franky is so popular among boys.
Oh, you don't like it?
Fire!
Luffy is so whimsical.
--Master!
No, I love it!
You bastard!
Why does he like that monster so much?
Spiral eyebrows!
Shut up, you brat!
It troubles me that he
mentioned the Seven Warlords.
But it's been over a year, hasn't it?
--You're right!
--So weird!
Stop!
Does it mean one of the Seven
Warlords is here on this island too?
A stag-beetle robot!
You were leering at her!
Chopper, why don't you examine them later?
I can change my hairstyle as I want!
Yeah, okay.
See?
Oh no! That's too much trouble!
Breaking the surface won't help...
See?
We don't wanna face the Warlords!
Here is another hand!
It's not too late!
With this I can...
Can we go back?
...pick my nose!
Oh no! This door is locked!
We have nowhere to go!
That was a trap!
Hey!
His skull must be broken. Doesn't it hurt?
Super!
Wait, legs!
What?
--They are coming!
--What are you gonna do?
Hey, somebody, listen to me!
Ouch... Ow... No, it doesn't hurt!
Super!
I have to hurry!
It itches!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Nami, step aside!
It's itchy!
He's trying to act tough!
What is he doing?
Boy...
One more! Hi-ya!
Hey!
I didn't know women from other
countries only wear a breast-band.
There's a wall!
It's open. Wachaa.
Hey, children!
There's a river!
Who is it?!
I like it.
--So strong!
--You became very powerful!
Stop calling it a "breast-band"!
That was cool, Racoon-chan!
By the way, who are you people?
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
No, I'm not a racoon!
Do you know a child named Momonosuke?!
I heard that you were taken from a ship.
Hey hey, that was amazing, Smo-yan!
But you look like one now.
Why did you do it-bu?
He's a boy!
I guess you're right!
I can't believe it!
Let's go, kids!
How did you know there was a
river behind there, Smo-yan?
Who is it?
We're pirates.
I'm scared!
I know someone's after me.
It's freezing! Chopper,
can I borrow your fur?
--Yeah, Smo-yan?!
--I didn't notice it at all, Smo-yan!
The severed-head talked!
Pirates?!
But for some reason,
Run!
Oh, sure.
I don't feel any hostile intent.
You people are pirates?!
Hey kids, tell me about this facility...
I mean, no way!
What is this place?
He's fast.
Wait!
Is it outside? Or is it a freezer?!
No wonder you people are barbaric!
Bu! I don't know who you are but
what do you want from me-bu?
You fool, shut up!
I don't like pirates! You make me sick!
You can tell by looking at the sea current!
It's too dark. I can barely see anything.
We can't get any information out of them!
You're scaring them!
If you stand in my way, I'll fight you!
You have to pay attention!
It's perfect for me!
You ought to check your own behavior too.
Stand in your way?
Yeah, but you're from a Winter Island.
The door to the Biscuit Room is open!
What are you talking about?
Cut that crap and join my crew!
But it's strange.
Isn't this a path? It's
too dark and I can't...
I was thinking about escaping
with you since we met here
Yeah.
They're coming! Let's run to the back!
Oh, I see it! There's a door!
on this island of ice by chance.
Bu! What are you doing-bu?!
The important thing is not the
fact that there was a river.
It must be those pirates!
Don't let them get away!
Oh yeah!
But it's too bad that you're pirates.
Let's go! It's not a dead end!
Gotcha!
It is whether the ice that
was blocking the river mouth
Let me go-bu!
Okay!
Sis! I don't like this place! I'm scared!
Hey hey, did you say "this island of ice"?
Now, why don't you join...
was natural or man-made.
...my crew?!
What?
I thought it was a burning island.
Do you mean  somebody was
hiding the river on purpose?
What kind of facility is this? Tell me!
--What's wrong, kids?
--Let's go! They're coming!
He's right!
This place is on fire - even
the sea is burning around here.
I'm looking for a boy named Momonosuke!
Who would wanna live on such an
island filled with the poison gas?
When I first got here, I
walked through this place!
No, wait!
Keep your mouth shut!
Are you sure?!
That's ridiculous! No one
wants to live with a mask on!
That means it'll lead us to the exit!
I got hit by a woman!
Old man.
It's really cold but hang on! Let's go!
Sorry!
This is a dishonor to a samurai!
But the man on the Snail
mentioned the island.
I should commit ritual suicide!
So you say it's an island of ice.
Go ahead! Just stop whining!
You male chauvinist pig!
You probably misheard it, Tashigi-chan!
No!
But didn't you hear those eruptions?
Not even a Transponder
Snail could survive here!
--Those damn escapees!
--You can't go anywhere!
I mean...
Oh, that was surprising!
I heard some explosions but
Hey legs, are you alright?
That's right!
I entered the island of ice
straight from an icy sea.
Wait!
Easy! We're not allowed to
use guns and explosives.
If you have time for laughing,
break up more ice!
When you look around...
What the...?!
Don't talk to me anymore, you damn pirates!
Use as few gas canisters as possible!
And you ended up like that?
I thought I saw a wintry sky from the ship.
Around?
If we hit a child, the
Master will be furious!
Yep, that's right.
--What the hell?!
--A wall of ice?!
It wasn't just in my head.
There is something in the wall...
Oh, this dragon meat is yummy!
If we collide into it,  even
this warship would sink!
The burning island that Luffy and
the others went to has a cold side.
Hey.
What do you call someone like this, Usopp?
--Oh no!
--We gotta destroy it!
Do you really wanna cross this lake, Luffy?
THE BURNING LANDS LUFFY'S GROUP
That means they took us to
the other side of the island!
Huh?
Shoot!
Um...
Yeah!
But how do we cross it?
I think it's called...
We need to find out who took us and
why by getting out of this room.
...a centaur, maybe?
Some parts are burning but
there are ice flows as well.
PUNK HAZARD ISLAND - THE
MIDDLE LAKE LUFFY'S GROUP
A centaur?
The temperature could be just right.
But Nami-san, this door is
unbreakable. We can't get out...
We're all sweaty so let's swim!
How funny!
This path scares me because there
are frozen people all around!
No way!
--Move aside!
--What?
Robin and I can't swim so...
First, he was stuck to the
dragon's body and now Luffy's?
Huh?! What's going on here?!
I'm filled up with cola!
What's wrong with him?
They are...
Dead bodies in ice?!
How do you like it?
There are more up there!
Are you implying I should carry you?!
Boss! Please take care of them!
Damn! I'm stuck in something again-bu!
Down there, too!
Why should I do it?
Let me go-bu!
Stop looking at me like that!
N-N...
Hey hey, wait a minute!
I'm sure Zoro wouldn't wanna...
That's vulgar, Luffy.
No!!
Is it?
Franky...
Be ready!
He's already stretching for it!
No, Sis, wait! Don't leave us!
I, Brownbeard-sama,
...Radical Beam!
What's this?!
THE BOSS – BROWNBEARD - AN ALLIGATOR CENTAUR
(A FORMER PIRATE,  BOUNTY: 80 MILLION 60 THOUSAND BERRIES)
Having said that, if we don't cross
it, we have to go all the way around.
will kick your asses all the way to hell!
Okay, I think I'm done.
See? He's not gonna just go along with you.
INSIDE OF THE LABORATORY -
BISCUIT ROOM SANJI'S GROUP
Hey, you blocked their path already.
I have no choice. All right!
There's no such creature!
That should be enough!
I bet his upper half is looking for him.
Okay, let's do it!
Let's go! I just felt
Nami-san's inner scream!
They're all centaurs!
Give him back to his owner!
Special Attack - Green Star!
I wonder if they wanna join us too!
Maybe she wants to tell me that she loves me!
I'm sure they don't!
Where's your sense of adventure, Usopp?
They're obviously prepared to fight us!
Fan Grass!
By the way, what are those people?
He was born like this. Right?
What's this plant?
They're colleagues of the man who sent
out the emergency signal, aren't they?
Boaty Banana!
Oh, so he's naturally a
half-body... No, I don't buy it!
They're half sheep.
It's open. Let's go.
You don't have that bizarre body for nothing.
I think there was a mythical
creature like this.
What's your name?
Yeah, they must be!
Oh, it's a boat! That's awesome, Usopp!
I wish I could shoot a beam like that!
Don't bother to think about them now.
Hey, I know you're gonna eat most
We have to clear the air
before they start to fight!
of this dragon meat so
why don't you carry it?!
We have to get the whole picture first.
I'm sure there are irrelevant points
of being a robot too, though.
Hey!
And we can use this Fan Grass as an oar!
We're here to help you
people! Let's talk first!
Let's go save Nami-san now!
You have many kinds of seeds!
Wait! Leave me here! I want to stay here!
That's wonderful!
You're lying through your teeth!
There were a whole bunch of weird
plants on the Bowin Islands.
My boy was not among those children.
Hey, guys! Come and take a look at this.
You're with the samurai!
So there's no doubt that you're intruders!
Oh, Zoro! Is the samurai
and the guy who got cut?
There must be other rooms so I'll stay and...
The deeper I went into the dangerous areas,
What are you gonna do?
Samurai?
the more handy plants I found.
You can't even move on your own!
You said you wanted to escape with us before
Look.
I survived on that islands for two years!
He's talking about you!
If we leave you here, we would
feel like we're abandoning you!
No, he's not a samurai - he's a swordsman!
you knew we were pirates, didn't you?
There is no difficulty
that I can't overcome...
What is it?
And that's not a great feeling!
--Get on board already, Usopp!
--Or we'll leave you.
Shut up and leave, pirate!
He's a dumb meathead who picks fights
without thinking sometimes but...
But I'm here to rescue my boy!
What?! S-Snowcapped mountains?!
You can't make it by yourself
- all you got is your head.
Hey, I'm the one who supplied the boat!
Don't irritate me!
All right! Let's go!
...he's not the one who attacked your people!
Why don't you just ask me to find your body?!
What are you doing?!
Who did you call "dumb"?!
No, are those mountains of ice?
To the land of snowcones!
Huh, samurai from the Wano Kingdom?!
Where is it?!
Help! He's gonna kill me!
Why aren't you rowing, too?!
I don't wanna owe anything to pirates!
There is a big lake in the middle
and there are snowcapped
What?! Samurai?! Is he?!
--I'm not gonna kill you! Stop saying that!
--They're having a falling out.
It's so windy!
I wouldn't ask you even if it kills me!
--There's a headwind!
--No wonder.
mountains on the other side!
This is a typical Wano Kingdom hairstyle.
What a pathetic ploy!
But on this side, there is an active
volcano and it's burning hot!
There is a big difference in
temperature on this island.
H-However, if you want to look for my body...
We can't let them go any further! Shoot them!
What kind of island is this?!
It makes for strong winds.
Does it mean he is the killer samurai
that the guy on the Snail mentioned?!
The water is boiling around here.
Understood!
So one of the mysteries is solved.
If we were swimming, it
would've been horrible!
Huh? Oh yeah, the man on
the Snail said he was cold!
I won't stop you.
Scary!
You're just a severed-head!
Don't be so arrogant!
I heard an explosion!
--It's so slow!
--Why don't you row then?!
Let's go! Was it those pirates?!
THE ICE LANDS - INSIDE OF THE
MYSTERIOUS FACILITY NAMI'S GROUP
Help me!
Are you gonna use violence against me?!
What happened?
Huh? Did they notice already?
I won't let you get away! Wait, you bastards!
I have no regrets!
It's cold... Is this the Boss?!
I'm not gonna beg a thug for my life!
My colleagues are getting
cut one after another!
Oh no!
Sanji-kun, let's go! They're coming!
Hey, stop.
That centaur again!
You're not gonna feel better by
smashing a helpless severed-head.
Hey!
The samurai are gonna kill us!
This way, kids! Run if you wanna get away!
Did you change your mind
and decide to join us?
It means the killer samurai and
the victims are on the other side!
We came here because we received
an emergency signal from
When you took him out of the room,
you already gave in to him, Sanji!
Were you recruiting again?!
You're on fire, Chopper!
Stop asking strange creatures to join us!
Of course!
Sanji entrusted me with
the important mission of
But...!
one of your victims, samurai!
protecting the kids and
getting them out of here!
This island is so interesting!
He's pissing me off!
There is snow on those mountains, huh?
I was so stupid to be moved
by his determination!
I'll do it!
It's so hot here - I wanna eat a snowcone!
I'll carry it through!
I don't wanna help him!
Is that a horn?
We're not gonna go there! It's too cold!
Sanji, we gotta go!
Now, I'm not even capable of
fighting back if someone hits me
Boss!
Leave the scary samurai here!
Why are those kids running?!
Boss?
And it's a long way. Let's
go back to the ship for now.
The guy on the Snail said "Boss," too.
so you can carry me if you want to.
I don't cut people if it disgraces me!
Oh no, it's gonna be cold this time.
It's cold... Is this the Boss?!
If there are animals, we
could make coats from pelts.
But it's gonna be okay.
The intruders are going that
way! Please finish them off!
Damn! We'll settle this once
you get your body back!
No, it's not gonna be okay!
I came to this island to rescue my son!
How can you guys go along with this?!
I'm a man! Leave it up to me!
Snowcone!
I don't mind cutting thousands
if they get in my way!
You show no mercy even on
a severed-head like me.
Hey, I said "Wait"! Luffy!
Something appeared on the other side.
I better watch my mouth.
Oh, you two are going too?!
You're amazing, racoon bro!
I wonder if Nami found the way out!
I'm not a raccoon - I'm a reindeer! Hi-ya!
I'm not going at any cost!
Let's find them!
I'm really... itchy!
There's no immediate threat to
my life here but over there,
But where should we go?
I'll freeze to death.
That's something you need
to figure out. Wachaa!
I'm not gonna...
Is that the Boss?
PUNK HAZARD ISLAND - THE
MIDDLE LAKE LUFFY'S GROUP
Boy...
Sis, are we going to be okay?
So the emergency signal
was meant for that Boss?
--There!
--Shoot! Don't let them get away!
Of course! We've been though
situations like this lots of times!
Then he shouldn't mean us any harm!
I got you, intruders!
So just relax and follow us!
No, he sliced it.
Oh no, that'll be far enough!
Uh-huh!
Weapons Left!
Take a good look.
I see a man with swords.
They're so dull.
So is that the samurai who cut our people?
How did they get out from that room?
Good job, Zoro-kun! I have to compliment you!
THE MYSTERIOUS FACILITY -
BISCUIT ROOM SANJI'S GROUP
Call the Master now!
Hey, I got Leg-maro too!
--He cut the shell in half?!
--Damn samurai!
What's wrong with them?!
Weapons Left!
Sanji-kun!
Don't hesitate! Fire!
You brought him?! He's dangerous!
Now kids, move out of the way.
I'll take responsibility!
We can't clear the air!
--Stay out of the way.
--It's dangerous.
They look like they're dumb, so...
A monster!
Super!
Hey, Robot-san! Did you come
from outside the island?
We should be friends!
There's a door!
He has weapons all over his body!
Gum-Gum Leg-maro Balloon!
Yes, of course! But I'm
a cyborg, little guy...
No!!!
He's the one who broke the door!
He's doing something again-bu!
Oh? You guys wanna know more about me?
Leg-maro has nothing to do with it!
Do you have a ship?
Ouch! What're you...
Oh yeah, our ship - the Sunny is the best...
I saw... I saw a monster!
A bird! No, a human!
Okay! I'll spend as much
time with you as you want!
Then help us!
What?! He repelled them all!
A bird or a human, which was it?!
Load the poison gas canisters!
There are no kids in here!
What does he mean?
Huh? What are you talking
about? Nobody's there!
What's wrong with his body?!
Help us! Please!
He's a Devil Fruit eater.
Why is he saying that?
Fire at will!
Then this is not a day-care?
Then I know what to do!
Sis!
Prepare to fire!
You have to help us! Please!
Huh?
They're gonna shoot again.
Why don't you take off your mask
and smoke some poison gas with us.
Please!
Gee! Hey, let's go!
They'll never learn. I'll
be counting on you guys!
No, believe me! There was
somebody just a minute ago!
Nami-san, don't stop!
You bastard!
Wait.
Take us out of here!
Don't get so mad.
Please!
They're aiming at the water!
Believe me!
Nami-san, let's go!
They're gonna try to sink the boat!
What?! We have two Devil
Fruit eaters on board!
Who are they?
What?!
Take good aim!
--He ripped off our masks!
--He broke our air tanks too!
We'll let them fall into the water!
Giant children?!
We are not sick anymore! We are all fine now!
Don't use gas canisters!
Ch-Children?!
Rot in hell, Devil Fruit eaters!
What's going on here?
What are they?!
Sick? What kind of sickness?
Sheep?
There are a bunch of kids!
Damn!
What's this place?!
Fire!
What are you doing?
Here they come!
This one is different from the others!
Who is he? He's proving an able opponent!
Damn brats!
I'm here to report, Master.
Again, what are you talking about?
We seized intruders.
Well, that's what's going on with my torso!
I assume they are pirates.
PUNK HAZARD ISLAND--THE BURNING LANDS
Oh, that is perfect.
IN FRONT OF THE MYSTERIOUS FACILITY BROOK
So all of your friends have
cool hind legs like these?
We were running low on guinea pigs.
Damn brats!
Hey! What's going on?!
I wanna see them!
Yeah! I'm sure they'll be surprised
when they see your legs!
Wh-Wh-Who are you?!
Hey, kids!
Let's get behind an iceberg!
Come see them!
They are all scary people! You
need to stay away from them!
Where is your head and legs?!
All right, Hyoutauros!
All right!
Let's race to that burning
tower to cement our friendship!
Is it true? They didn't seem like bad people!
You're scaring me! Please say something!
Ready, go!
That was close.
They fooled you.
Why aren't you rowing?
Then the stag-beetle robot is a villain?
That's right.
--Same for Racoon-chan?
--Yes.
They totally go together!
Shoot! Shoot!
And the man with the spiral eyebrows?
What?! You can't find Nami and the others?!
Yes, so let us protect you all.
Are you all by yourself?!
When you woke up, you were
surrounded by snow and ice?!
Devil Fruit eaters can't fight in the water!
Well, well... They all look
unique and interesting.
We will protect you sick kids.
That's right!
Sink to your death, Devil Fruit eaters!
I was as surprised as a bone in thunder!
A SNOW-CAPPED MOUNTAIN
NEAR THE LABORATORY BROOK
They're gonna be good test subjects.
We will put them to sleep
with our cloud guns.
Yes, I thought  you would
especially like this cyborg.
Oh? No no, like thunder in a duck?
Gross! So gross!
We'll reach the end of the river soon.
Oh no, like a duck in bone?
Oh, what a rare find!
Who cares.
What's wrong with that ghost?!
I wonder what will be there!
He is worth testing. You're
right. I can't wait.
Suddenly attacking me!
Oh, excuse me!
Why do I have to get attacked?!
Those people who tried to steal things
from the Sunny - who were they?
I think I know.
Will this be all?
He's kind of strong too!
It seems there was another man who
looked like one of them but...
I assume they had a falling
out and he was murdered.
I hear something in the distance.
Well, I have no idea at all.
All that remained was his skeleton.
I don't have ears though.
Shoot! Shoot!
Such brutality is not so unusual for pirates.
Huh? No, wait, you guys! Don't be so rash!
You are so persistent!
I see. All right.
I want you to lock them in a room
and make sure they can't escape.
--Huh?
--Did he vanish?!
I have no choice! I'll fight you!
Where did he go?!
Are you a ghost, by any chance?!
Boy... If you had something to say,
If so, you gotta obey the rules!
I would've listened over
a cup of tea or something.
Don't come out during the day!
There he is!
I didn't do anything wrong!
I'll forget I saw it.
But I cut you already.
I just set foot on the
island to make snowmen!
What?
Oh, I don't have eyes anyway.
Three-Pace Hum... Notch Slash!
Oh, would you like to join
me and make one, too?
THE MAIN ENTRANCE OF THE LABORATORY
Let's see what they have here.
We can make a snow sculpture as well...
Look for food or something usable.
By the way, who are you people?
Yes, sir.
Hello? My name is Monkey D. Luffy! I'm
gonna become the King of the Pirates!
I was just kidding!
Oh? What was I doing?
That's how it was.
What's wrong with him?!
I cut them before I asked them who they were.
You picked up too fast and said too much!
How can he attack me with such precision?!
Where are Nami-san and the others?
Help me!
They all have a gas mask
kind of thing on them.
Who are those people?
He doesn't have eyes!
What happened?
Please... Wait...
It's cold... Is this the Boss?!
Gas mask?
It was very hot before
Then maybe they released some
kind of gas that knocked you out.
No, I'm not the Boss.
Oh yeah! I don't have eyes, either!
I want to...
but it became extremely
cold while I was sleeping.
My colleagues are getting
cut one after another!
And they probably moved the Sunny
to the other side of the island.
I want to go home!
The samurai are gonna kill us!
Wait!
Who is it?!
I lost! Damn!
Are you one of those pirates?!
Where are you?!
Somebody please help me! I'm on...
You're fast!
It's bone-chillingly cold, isn't it?
Dammit! Brats!
Scary! He's strong! Scary!
Please wait!
Well, you did well too!
...Punk Hazard!
Oh, I'm a skeleton - that's why.
Get us out of here!
Sis, please! Help us!
All right! Let's do it one more time!
Th-The skeletonized body said something!
The name of the island and
the fact he said "It's cold."
--Ha! No matter how many times we...
--Ring, ring, ring...
Now, kids, you need to stop!
I don't know who you are but do you know
--Clank.
--Hello?
There is almost no doubt that this
man sent the signal from this island.
What do you want?!
Sorry! I have to run now!
Why are you fooling around?
where Nami-san and the others went?
Well, I can't find them.
S-Shoot! Shoot!
Can't you just tell me
why you wanna fight me?!
Huh? No, wait, you guys! Don't be so rash!
Are there really intruders?
Aubade Coup Droit!
You know Straw Hat Luffy, don't you?
All I found is a guy with
weird hind legs that talks.
Gum-Gum...
He is one of the intruders!
...Balloon!
Repel!
Come on! Let's do it!
Two-Sword Style?!
What's going on?
Room.
Hey, let's take them with us!
Enough already!
What?!
Shambles.
Crazy! We don't even know
how to save ourselves!
I wonder where Nami-san and the others went.
Scary! Scary! Gross!
I've been killed!
If there wasn't a note,
maybe they were abducted.
There's no way we can take that many kids!
When the incident involving the Roswalds,
But what is this?! I have a feeling
- something tragic is gonna happen.
Oh yeah! They thought you were dead
since you're a skeleton, probably.
a Celestial Dragon family,
happened on Sabaody 2 years ago,
Sanji, what are you messing around with?
Kid, Straw Hat and you fought together.
Oh, I see. That's why they
didn't take me. I was lucky!
Oh, you're up.
And during the War of the Best...
Can't you see?
They think they left no one on the ship.
Oh no, Franky! We are locked up!
Put Straw Hat-ya on my ship!
Do you see any building or person?
Master!
I'm gonna help him get out of here.
Wow, Robin-san, you sound
like you can see it yourself!
Did you catch the escapees?
Let me take care of him for now!
No, I have news about G-5.
When Akainu was after Straw Hat,  you...
Hey, what's this place?! Where are we?!
Then,
Oh, them!
come back later and help us!
In fact,
...helped him get away!
The poison gas didn't work.
there is.
I was eating a Giant Shellfish
dessert on the deck and...
And it's quite an impressive building.
I can't remember anything after that!
I knew! Even if I've never
been out of this building!
What do you want?
I assume that somebody used sleeping gas
It doesn't look like a restaurant.
I know you Navy people are good at
forging those emergency signals.
Brook, we'll head there
so can you wait for us?
There is nothing on this island, right?!
and seized us once we fell asleep.
Roger!
There is no city! There is no one else!
Oh, Robin-san, could I see
your underwear when...
I'm afraid it wasn't a trap that we set.
What?
The ship was, in fact, filled with gas.
That's why nobody comes to help us!
Clank.
Oh yeah?
I'm sorry.
I want to see my father and my mother!
Currently, they are breaking
through ice floes with a cannon
But I don't know anything so there's
nothing more to talk about.
I wish I could've noticed it a little sooner.
Are we facing allies of the Government?
I don't know but it's better if
they're human because compared
Cut that crap.
Sis, please come back!
and slowly forcing their way into the island.
Let us see inside the laboratory.
to what we've seen so far...
They'll reach the laboratory in time!
Come to help us later!
It's my vacation home now. I refuse!
A fire-breathing dragon!
Why?
What's wrong with me - a pirate staying
on an island you people abandoned?
The bottom half of a man!
Why do they want to come
into the island so badly?
A bird woman!
I'm the only one here!
What should we do?
Do they know something?
If Straw Hat comes, I'll
chop his head off for you.
And a centaur who just
became Luffy's friend...
Are they gonna sell us?!
Are they abducting humans?!
Who is in charge?
Vice Admiral Smoker.
If that's all you have to say, go home!
But if they took all of us
on the ship, where's Brook?
Smoker?
--Why didn't you tell me?!
--What?! What's up so suddenly?!
Nami-san, come on!
I don't know.
Of all others, that pain in the neck?
There are only four of us in here.
You bastard!
If they're abducting humans,
they wouldn't need a skeleton.
Conceal all the ships moored at the front.
I dropped my guard thinking
you were one of us.
You're not a human either.
Who's gonna deal with them?
Neither are you! That's enough!
No one's allowed to be here.
Why can't I be one of you?!
You guys.
So scary! Those frozen people!
We're friends now, don't attack me!
Don't let them find you at any cost.
Did anybody say something?
I've had it with this place!
Then you'll deal with them?
Go to hell, intruder!
Don't be ridiculous! I can't
just show myself like that!
No, it wasn't us.
But look! There's a door! We can get out!
There's one more!
Yeah!
But there is no one else who can stop them!
Do you guys like hanjimono?
Cien Fleurs!
That means "puzzles" in a foreign language.
Do you want me to do it?
There is somebody else in there!
Bellflower!
Was it this thing that just talked?
I made it out!
Let's help these children!
Outside?! It's freezing!
What is it?
We made it!
What are you saying, Nami-san?!
I got out of the building! I can go home!
Don't call me an "it"!
We don't know for sure they need saving!
Who are you?
They said those kids are sick
so this could be a hospital!
I can see my dad and mom again!
It's...
It's cold!
A panther and a giraffe, huh?
What? A bug?
Get out of my way, kids!
We just met them and we don't
know what's going on here!
A new kind of Transponder Snail?
There are many kinds of
centaurs! How interesting!
There are eight of them! I hadn't noticed!
It's not our job to help every single person!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, Franky!
It's a mythical horse! It can't be real!
I'm not a bug!
I understand what you're saying but...
Hey, hey, hey, hey, Tank!
You guys don't seem like bad people.
What happened?
We finally made it!
Clear the way, clear the way, Super the way!
He suddenly attacked me
after talking to somebody.
I thought I was gonna die!
These are all parts of my face.
I'll run over you if you stand in my way!
We've only just landed on the island. Get up!
...you can't turn your back
on a child crying for help!
Could I ask you to put them back together?
But I avoid running over flowers!
Don't be so harsh!
I'm kind of sweet - Franky Tank!
Look at this Baby Transponder
Snail! It says "CC"!
Your face?
We did our best so be kind to us!
Oh yeah, this is a mouth.
Sis!
Don't be such a baby!
All right! Here we go, everybody!
They're not wild centaurs.
And this is an eye.
Like this?
Yeah!
They belong to some kind of organization.
Smoker-san?
--How is it?!
--Yeah, looks like a face now!
One, two, three...
Calm down.
--"CC"?
--So they're our enemies?
Super!
--They'll get away if nothing is done!
--Those brats are in the way!
No no, you left out some parts!
Anyway, even if we go
back to the sea of fire,
Who cares! Shoot the brats too!
the Sunny is not there!
I think it's like this!
--But the Master will...
--Better than letting them go!
The only option we have now
is to go to the ice lands!
How about this?
The Straw Hats?! Children?!
It's completely wrong!
Nami, Sanji, Franky, and Chopper are missing!
No no, this is better.
I don't know where to begin!
I thought so.
A big racoon, a woman in bikini
in the winter, giant kids,
Alright, that's fine.
No! No!
They were abducted most likely.
a robot, and a severed-head...
I wanna try it too!
It's too late!
You guys! Stop playing with my face!
Am I dreaming?!
--There is no gas.
--What?
I hope they're not riddled with bullets.
--Tank treads!
--Cool!
--Awesome!
--A tank!
Stop!
It's done!
The best!
It's hard to believe but she's right.
We could get there faster if we
had landed on the other side.
Bad roads won't trouble me!
Looks like a human face now!
Then why was there poison gas earlier?
Nami-san! I'm glad that you're okay!
Then we wouldn't have gotten to
eat the dragon or meet Leg-maro!
I think there is something
wrong with the chin
Somebody who doesn't want to
welcome us released it probably.
Sanji-kun!
I like the way you shiver
in the cold but I don't want
Spiral Bro!
and the top part but it's okay.
Who's Leg-maro?
Do you really think so?
Diable Jambe Collier...
Thank you!
you to get sick so take my jacket!
I named my hind legs.
Let's find out.
A severed-head just talked!
Thank you, Sanji-kun!
Bu! What happened this time-bu?
You just noticed?
...Strike!
How can you live like
that?! Are you possessed?!
What's going on-bu?!
Is that...
You look familiar!
What are we gonna do, Luffy?
Yes, Dr. Vegapunk's laboratory.
That's amazing!
Yeah, he was there at Sabaody!
I don't know. I didn't
wish to become like this.
We can rescue them if we can
get to the other side, right?
That guy is very strong!
Former laboratory, I mean.
Are you the one who locked
up these children?!
Damn!
It should be abandoned and empty.
You brute! You can't take them back!
Then we have no choice!
That bastard... He used
some kind of weird magic!
All right! Let's go! The plan has changed!
Kung Fu Boost!
Oh, you're...!
I thought I was dead when he cut
me but I ended up like this.
Let's go to the ice lands
to rescue our friends!
I was wondering who this
villainous guy was! Smoker!
I wonder if they're selling
winter clothes on the way.
And you, cutie!
To be kept alive after
being sliced apart is...
There is still power.
Racoon-chan!
This is not good! The Navy's here!
Seriously, we're gonna
die from cold like this!
Who is living here?
...a dishonor to a warrior!
Strong Right!
We can't escape from here!
Let's look for another exit!
What should we do?
Hey! Come on out!
Get inside!
What's taking you so long?!
Are you afraid of us?!
I see. They broke this impenetrable door!
Hurry up, kids! Go to the back!
It seems like crossing the lake
We don't have to ring a doorbell and wait!
There should be a backdoor!
is the only way to get to the other side.
A rocket punch!
We can just break the door with
the cannon of the ship, Smo-yan...
Master!
What brought the Navy to such a place?!
But how do we cross the lake?
I don't know! Just run!
This burn mark...
Smoker-san...
Th-They...
I don't know if we can live long enough
to get to the lake in the first place.
--Hey! Answer!
--Just open it!
Oh? I thought the Navy were good people.
Who the hell are they?
...stopped running!
Why don't you go to them, then?
I thought they were the only
ones who could generate lasers.
You hear me?
It's hot!
No, they look like gangsters!
No one is allowed to be here on this island!
Snowcone!
She's kind to kids.
Whoever you are, you're under arrest, fool!
Vegapunk's Goddamn Pacifistas!
I wonder how Luffy can be so high-spirited.
You lied! You weren't the only one here!
I mean, she's only kind
to kids but I like it.
Come on out now!
Snowcone! Snowcone! Snowcone!
Seems like I wasn't. I'm also surprised.
They haven't caught the
escapees yet, have they?
Ignoring us? Okay, bring the cannon here!
I'm falling for her even more!
--Let's put a big hole in it!
--Hey!
They're trying to corral
them into the Biscuit Room.
Everybody, let's catch the Straw Hats!
The Biscuit Room?
Chopper, you go ahead with Nami-san.
All right, let's go! Follow Captain-chan!
Who goes there?!
Master, are you there?!
There you are, intruders!
Yeah, I'll protect her!
It opened!
No, wait!
Now you're giving up? We're the Navy!
Yes, I'm here.
Room.
Hey, brats!
A G-5's Navy ship is approaching
the northwest shore!
Huh?!
Follow the beautiful lady
and the Kung Fu Racoon!
I will fight our pursuers!
A Navy ship?! Turn them away at any cost!
--Ouch!
--Are you alright?
You have...
But don't get me wrong!
Release large amounts of the poison gas!
...those...
I'm just doing this to answer Nami-san's
beautiful wish to help you kids.
...legs!
Don't kill them--we don't want any trouble!
Those fools... They brought trouble!
They are so cool!
Yes, sir!
Takt!
In fact, I don't like you all
precisely because Nami-san
What brought you here - to my vacation home?
Oh, I'm sorry!
cares about you so much!
I was looking for intruders and
I saw some unfamiliar faces so...
Spiral Bro, thank you!
What's making that noise?
White Chase-ya!
Shut up, brat! Just run already!
Oh, okay! You surprised me!
No way!
Vice Admiral Smoker, it's impossible!
Let's go now!
THE NORTHWEST SHORE
He is...
Everybody, follow us!
I-I can't breathe...
By the way, your legs are cool too!
He used to be a rookie with a 440
million berry bounty and now,
The gas is still leaking!
Damn! They're taking the kids!
he is among them...
Be careful! You don't wanna
inhale even a single breath!
Yeah! Your hind legs are a little different.
You don't have to do this, Franky.
..."Hawk-Eye" Mihawk, Pirate
Empress Boa Hancock,
Put a gas mask on!
You think so?
What a dangerous island! Punk Hazard!
Letting down Armored Franky
fans is not an option for me!
and Don Quixote Doflamingo.
Where am I-bu!
Ever since the failure
of that accursed old man
Hey, calm down!
Pirates backed by the World Government -
Vega Punk's chemical weapon test 4 years ago,
Your hind legs can talk?!
the Seven Warlords!
No way!
this island has rotted to the core!
Yeah!
We will fight you!
Awesome! None of my friends
have legs like that!
First of all, I don't see Straw
Hat Luffy's pirate ship anywhere!
Bring it on!
Trafalgar Law!
And no one can enter the island since
--I've never seen it before!
--Yeah?
there is still poison gas everywhere!
So, Luffy made an odd friend again.
Snow! Snow! I love playing with snow!
Let's go back, Smoker-san!
No.
IN FRONT OF THE MYSTERIOUS FACILITY BROOK
A panther centaur?
I don't want anything to do with him!
It's not natural that it's
still generating so much gas.
It's a great way to kill time!
The warship is in the air!
One, two...
You know what he did!
Robin-san told me to wait here
but what's taking them so long?!
What do you mean?
Along with the bottom of the river!
2 years ago, there was no fire or ice here.
What's going on here?!
...three...
To become a member of the Warlords...
...and four.
It was nothing but a ruined island.
Ta-dah! Snowmen!
I can't let you leave the island now.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Surprisingly, most of the
toxic substances were gone.
I'm sorry that I said no one's here.
Let's rearrange its eyes and nose!
Clank.
Hello? Did you find them?
That's why Akainu and Aokiji
chose Punk Hazard...
I knew he was dangerous!
It looks like me!
Yes, we found them. We
were about to kill them.
...he delivered the hearts of one
hundred pirates to the headquarters!
Step back.
Oh?
...as the place for their showdown!
There are four intruders.
You guys are no match!
He's crazy!
Hey! Hey!
He'll chop off your hands and feet!
What a creep!
Hey, who is it? Why are you doing this?!
I see.
That's exciting.
Why are you here?
Who the hell...
Please be careful!
Go, Smo-yan!
No one, not even pirates
or Government allies,
Roger.
Clank.
What?
is allowed to be here on this island, Law!
--Kick his ass!
--Show him the true power of G-5!
They chose it as a stage
for their big match -
Whaaat?!
That means you people
are not allowed, either!
one powerful enough even to
send the weather into chaos!
J...
Just a torso?!
A mysterious group of children become
uproarious after meeting Sanji and the others.
Law's power, capable of lifting even warships...
Nami and Chopper frantically push through
Luffy and the crew face a new crisis
Law stands in Smoker's way,
...overwhelms the Navy's G-5.
while they cross the burning lands.
the mysterious facility to save the children.
and neither will yield a single step.
During the continuous attacks
by Master's subordinates,
Sanji and Nami's group also ends up...
After Sanji and the others hear what
the bodiless samurai has to say,
As the situation reaches its boiling point,
While Sanji and Franky fight for their lives,
they escape together from their cell.
...in an unprecedented situation because of Law.
the children begin speaking an astonishing truth!
the Straw Hat Pirates suddenly
appear with the children in tow.
Brook is at the mercy of the powerful torso samurai,
While being pursued, they wander into a room,
Meanwhile, Luffy's group comes
upon a lake in the frozen lands...
Nami hears their desperate pleas
It was then that Law does something that causes
and discover a terrifying
secret hidden on the island!
until finally, the two begin their duel.
...and encounters a crisis of its own!
the situation to move immediately!
and her decision moves the entire crew!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Swordplay Showdown! Brook vs.
the Mysterious Torso Samurai!"
"Save the Children! The
Straw Hats Start to Fight!"
"In a Real Pinch! Luffy Sinks
into the Ice-cold Lake!"
"Startling! The Secret of the
Island is Finally Revealed!"
"A Swordplay Showdown! Brook vs.
the Mysterious Torso Samurai!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!