Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
Responding to an emergency signal,
Luffy and the others went to Punk
Hazard and there, they faced...
Bu! It's strange but it's cool here!
You're not gonna believe this!
Somebody's stuck in the dragon's back!
One-Sword...
...Style!
Lion Strike!
Meanwhile, Nami and the others were...
Tie them all up!
Alright!
It's good that they're pirates.
No one will care if they go missing.
Let's take them to the Master!
"The Straw Hats Stunned! Enter: A
Samurai's Horrifying Severed Head!"
PUNK HAZARD ISLAND
THE BURNING LANDS
Now, what should we do about him?
Let's pull him out!
Hey, who are you?!
Get your hands off of me-bu!
Hey! I'm helping you! Stay calm!
Here we go!
Wow, he's completely stuck
in the dragon's body.
How is that possible?
His upper body is stuck but
he's talking normally.
Why isn't he suffocating?
Who the hell is he?
I-I-It's missing!
What's missing?
He's torn in half! I'm sorry!
You fool! Sorry isn't
enough!  You killed him!
Oh, I'm finally separated from it-bu!
What?!
The lower body just talked! What's going on?!
A zombie! A monster!
Wait a minute.
This is strange.
There is no upper half here.
What do you mean?
He didn't have an upper
body from the very start?
Oh, this is too freaky!
He's kind of big.
Who is there and what are you doing?
I sense your presence but
I don't have eyes or ears.
You're bizarre!
I don't know who you are
but get out of my way-bu!
What?
I cannot die here!
Oh, he took off!
I'm not going to let them get away!
That goddamn Warlord!
Hey, wait! Why don't you join my...
No, Luffy!
I'm gonna go catch him!
Can you grill the dragon for me?!
Wait, legs!
Luffy is so whimsical.
Why does he like that monster so much?
It troubles me that he
mentioned the Seven Warlords.
Does it mean one of the Seven
Warlords is here on this island too?
Oh no! That's too much trouble!
We don't wanna face the Warlords!
It's not too late!
Can we go back?
Hey!
Wait, legs!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
What is he doing?
Hey!
There's a wall!
Who is it?!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Why did you do it-bu?
Who is it?
I know someone's after me.
But for some reason,
I don't feel any hostile intent.
He's fast.
Bu! I don't know who you are but
what do you want from me-bu?
If you stand in my way, I'll fight you!
Stand in your way?
What are you talking about?
Cut that crap and join my crew!
Bu! What are you doing-bu?!
Gotcha!
Let me go-bu!
Now, why don't you join...
...my crew?!
Sorry!
Oh, that was surprising!
Hey legs, are you alright?
What the...?!
And you ended up like that?
Yep, that's right.
Oh, this dragon meat is yummy!
What do you call someone like this, Usopp?
Huh?
Um...
I think it's called...
...a centaur, maybe?
A centaur?
How funny!
First, he was stuck to the
dragon's body and now Luffy's?
What's wrong with him?
How do you like it?
Damn! I'm stuck in something again-bu!
Let me go-bu!
That's vulgar, Luffy.
Is it?
What's this?!
See? He's not gonna just go along with you.
There's no such creature!
I bet his upper half is looking for him.
Give him back to his owner!
Where's your sense of adventure, Usopp?
He was born like this. Right?
Oh, so he's naturally a
half-body... No, I don't buy it!
What's your name?
Hey, I know you're gonna eat most
of this dragon meat so
why don't you carry it?!
Hey, guys! Come and take a look at this.
Oh, Zoro! Is the samurai
and the guy who got cut?
Look.
What is it?
What?! S-Snowcapped mountains?!
No, are those mountains of ice?
There is a big lake in the middle
and there are snowcapped
mountains on the other side!
But on this side, there is an active
volcano and it's burning hot!
What kind of island is this?!
So one of the mysteries is solved.
Huh? Oh yeah, the man on
the Snail said he was cold!
Help me!
What happened?
It's cold... Is this the Boss?!
My colleagues are getting
cut one after another!
The samurai are gonna kill us!
It means the killer samurai and
the victims are on the other side!
This island is so interesting!
There is snow on those mountains, huh?
It's so hot here - I wanna eat a snowcone!
We're not gonna go there! It's too cold!
And it's a long way. Let's
go back to the ship for now.
Oh no, it's gonna be cold this time.
If there are animals, we
could make coats from pelts.
But it's gonna be okay.
No, it's not gonna be okay!
How can you guys go along with this?!
Snowcone!
Hey, I said "Wait"! Luffy!
Oh, you two are going too?!
I'm not going at any cost!
There's no immediate threat to
my life here but over there,
I'll freeze to death.
I'm not gonna...
A monster!
No!!!
Ouch! What're you...
I saw... I saw a monster!
A bird! No, a human!
A bird or a human, which was it?!
Huh? What are you talking
about? Nobody's there!
Huh?
Gee! Hey, let's go!
No, believe me! There was
somebody just a minute ago!
Believe me!
I'm here to report, Master.
We seized intruders.
I assume they are pirates.
Oh, that is perfect.
We were running low on guinea pigs.
Well, well... They all look
unique and interesting.
They're gonna be good test subjects.
Yes, I thought  you would
especially like this cyborg.
Oh, what a rare find!
He is worth testing. You're
right. I can't wait.
Will this be all?
It seems there was another man who
looked like one of them but...
I assume they had a falling
out and he was murdered.
All that remained was his skeleton.
Such brutality is not so unusual for pirates.
I see. All right.
I want you to lock them in a room
and make sure they can't escape.
Let's see what they have here.
Look for food or something usable.
Yes, sir.
Oh? What was I doing?
Where are Nami-san and the others?
Who are those people?
It was very hot before
but it became extremely
cold while I was sleeping.
Who is it?!
Are you one of those pirates?!
It's bone-chillingly cold, isn't it?
Oh, I'm a skeleton - that's why.
Th-The skeletonized body said something!
I don't know who you are but do you know
where Nami-san and the others went?
S-Shoot! Shoot!
Huh? No, wait, you guys! Don't be so rash!
Sanji, what are you messing around with?
Oh, you're up.
Can't you see?
Oh no, Franky! We are locked up!
Hey, what's this place?! Where are we?!
I was eating a Giant Shellfish
dessert on the deck and...
I can't remember anything after that!
I assume that somebody used sleeping gas
and seized us once we fell asleep.
What?
The ship was, in fact, filled with gas.
I'm sorry.
I wish I could've noticed it a little sooner.
What should we do?
Are they gonna sell us?!
Are they abducting humans?!
But if they took all of us
on the ship, where's Brook?
I don't know.
There are only four of us in here.
If they're abducting humans,
they wouldn't need a skeleton.
You're not a human either.
Neither are you! That's enough!
You guys.
Did anybody say something?
No, it wasn't us.
Do you guys like hanjimono?
That means "puzzles" in a foreign language.
Was it this thing that just talked?
What is it?
Don't call me an "it"!
It's...
What? A bug?
A new kind of Transponder Snail?
There are eight of them! I hadn't noticed!
I'm not a bug!
You guys don't seem like bad people.
These are all parts of my face.
Could I ask you to put them back together?
Your face?
Oh yeah, this is a mouth.
And this is an eye.
Like this?
--How is it?!
--Yeah, looks like a face now!
No no, you left out some parts!
I think it's like this!
How about this?
It's completely wrong!
No no, this is better.
Alright, that's fine.
No! No!
I wanna try it too!
You guys! Stop playing with my face!
It's done!
Looks like a human face now!
I think there is something
wrong with the chin
and the top part but it's okay.
Thank you!
A severed-head just talked!
You just noticed?
How can you live like
that?! Are you possessed?!
I don't know. I didn't
wish to become like this.
That bastard... He used
some kind of weird magic!
I thought I was dead when he cut
me but I ended up like this.
To be kept alive after
being sliced apart is...
...a dishonor to a warrior!
It seems like crossing the lake
is the only way to get to the other side.
But how do we cross the lake?
I don't know if we can live long enough
to get to the lake in the first place.
It's hot!
Snowcone!
I wonder how Luffy can be so high-spirited.
Snowcone! Snowcone! Snowcone!
Who goes there?!
There you are, intruders!
Huh?!
You have...
...those...
...legs!
They are so cool!
Oh, I'm sorry!
I was looking for intruders and
I saw some unfamiliar faces so...
Oh, okay! You surprised me!
By the way, your legs are cool too!
Yeah! Your hind legs are a little different.
You think so?
Where am I-bu!
Hey, calm down!
Your hind legs can talk?!
Yeah!
Awesome! None of my friends
have legs like that!
--I've never seen it before!
--Yeah?
So, Luffy made an odd friend again.
A panther centaur?
One, two...
...three...
...and four.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Hello? Did you find them?
Yes, we found them. We
were about to kill them.
There are four intruders.
I see.
That's exciting.
Please be careful!
Roger.
Clank.
Luffy and the crew face a new crisis
while they cross the burning lands.
After Sanji and the others hear what
the bodiless samurai has to say,
they escape together from their cell.
While being pursued, they wander into a room,
and discover a terrifying
secret hidden on the island!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Startling! The Secret of the
Island is Finally Revealed!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!