Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
-- the harshest sea ruled
by the Four Emperors.
He's torn in half! I'm sorry!
You fool! Sorry isn't enough! You killed him!
They came across a strange lower-half man.
A centaur?
How funny!
Meanwhile, Nami and the others held
captive in an unknown building...
These are all parts of my face.
Could I ask you to put them back together?
I think there is something
wrong with the chin and the
top part but it's okay.
Thank you!
A severed-head just talked!
You just noticed?
There you are, intruders!
Huh?!
You have...
...those...
...legs!
They are so cool!
Hello? Did you find them?
Yes, we found them.
We were about to kill them.
There are four intruders.
I see.
That's exciting.
Please be careful!
Roger.
"Startling! The Secret of the
Island is Finally Revealed!"
Sliced up by your enemy and...
...Alive without your body?
How? I don't get it!
That's like Buggy. How weird.
I wish I could cut my belly
and die in obscurity but...
...there is something that I need
to do even if I have to live in disgrace!
By the way, do you know
where this is, old man?
Old man?!
Women can't talk to warriors like that!
Women have to walk three steps behind men
and talk modestly and humbly!
What did you say, you jerk?!
You're just a severed-head!
How could you say that to
someone who helped you?!
G-Get your hands off of me!
You still wanna act like that?! You...
Stop it, young woman!
What?!
What country are you from?!
You're so rude and brash!
But I assume somebody ripped off
your clothes and you're hurt.
You have my sympathy.
Nobody ripped off my clothes!
This is the way I dress!
How obscene! All you have is a breast-band!
Oh, you don't like it?
No, I love it!
You bastard!
You were leering at her!
That was a trap!
His skull must be broken. Doesn't it hurt?
Ouch... Ow... No, it doesn't hurt!
It itches!
It's itchy!
He's trying to act tough!
I didn't know women from other
countries only wear a breast-band.
I like it.
Stop calling it a "breast-band"!
By the way, who are you people?
I heard that you were taken from a ship.
We're pirates.
Pirates?!
You people are pirates?!
No wonder you people are barbaric!
I don't like pirates! You make me sick!
I was thinking about escaping
with you since we met here
on this island of ice by chance.
But it's too bad that you're pirates.
Hey hey, did you say "this island of ice"?
I thought it was a burning island.
He's right!
This place is on fire - even
the sea is burning around here.
No, wait!
Old man.
So you say it's an island of ice.
But didn't you hear those eruptions?
I heard some explosions but
I entered the island of ice
straight from an icy sea.
Don't talk to me anymore, you damn pirates!
I thought I saw a wintry sky from the ship.
It wasn't just in my head.
The burning island that Luffy and
the others went to has a cold side.
That means they took us to
the other side of the island!
We need to find out who took us and
why by getting out of this room.
But Nami-san, this door is
unbreakable. We can't get out...
--Move aside!
--What?
I'm filled up with cola!
Hey hey, wait a minute!
Franky...
...Radical Beam!
It's open. Let's go.
You don't have that bizarre body for nothing.
I wish I could shoot a beam like that!
I'm sure there are irrelevant points
of being a robot too, though.
What are you gonna do?
You said you wanted to escape with us before
you knew we were pirates, didn't you?
Shut up and leave, pirate!
You can't make it by yourself
- all you got is your head.
What are you doing?!
Huh, samurai from the Wano Kingdom?!
What?! Samurai?! Is he?!
This is a typical Wano Kingdom hairstyle.
Does it mean he is the killer samurai
that the guy on the Snail mentioned?!
Scary!
I heard an explosion!
Let's go! Was it those pirates?!
Huh? Did they notice already?
Sanji-kun, let's go! They're coming!
We came here because we received
an emergency signal from
one of your victims, samurai!
Sanji, we gotta go!
Leave the scary samurai here!
I don't cut people if it disgraces me!
I came to this island to rescue my son!
I don't mind cutting thousands
if they get in my way!
--There!
--Shoot! Don't let them get away!
Oh no, that'll be far enough!
Weapons Left!
How did they get out from that room?
Call the Master now!
What's wrong with them?!
Sanji-kun!
You brought him?! He's dangerous!
I'll take responsibility!
There's a door!
Who are they?
What?!
Giant children?!
Ch-Children?!
What's going on here?
There are a bunch of kids!
What's this place?!
PUNK HAZARD ISLAND--THE BURNING LANDS
So all of your friends have
cool hind legs like these?
I wanna see them!
Yeah! I'm sure they'll be surprised
when they see your legs!
Come see them!
All right, Hyoutauros!
Let's race to that burning
tower to cement our friendship!
Ready, go!
They totally go together!
What?! You can't find Nami and the others?!
Are you all by yourself?!
When you woke up, you were
surrounded by snow and ice?!
That's right!
I was as surprised as a bone in thunder!
Oh? No no, like thunder in a duck?
Oh no, like a duck in bone?
Who cares.
Oh, excuse me!
Those people who tried to steal things
from the Sunny - who were they?
Well, I have no idea at all.
Shoot! Shoot!
Huh? No, wait, you guys! Don't be so rash!
--Huh?
--Did he vanish?!
Where did he go?!
Boy... If you had something to say,
I would've listened over
a cup of tea or something.
There he is!
But I cut you already.
What?
Three-Pace Hum... Notch Slash!
By the way, who are you people?
That's how it was.
I cut them before I asked them who they were.
They all have a gas mask
kind of thing on them.
Gas mask?
Then maybe they released some
kind of gas that knocked you out.
And they probably moved the Sunny
to the other side of the island.
I lost! Damn!
You're fast!
Well, you did well too!
All right! Let's do it one more time!
--Ha! No matter how many times we...
--Ring, ring, ring...
--Clank.
--Hello?
Why are you fooling around?
Well, I can't find them.
Are there really intruders?
All I found is a guy with
weird hind legs that talks.
He is one of the intruders!
Come on! Let's do it!
What?!
I wonder where Nami-san and the others went.
If there wasn't a note,
maybe they were abducted.
Oh yeah! They thought you were dead
since you're a skeleton, probably.
Oh, I see. That's why they
didn't take me. I was lucky!
They think they left no one on the ship.
Do you see any building or person?
Wow, Robin-san, you sound
like you can see it yourself!
In fact,
there is.
And it's quite an impressive building.
It doesn't look like a restaurant.
Brook, we'll head there
so can you wait for us?
Roger!
Oh, Robin-san, could I see
your underwear when...
Clank.
Are we facing allies of the Government?
I don't know but it's better if
they're human because compared
to what we've seen so far...
A fire-breathing dragon!
The bottom half of a man!
A bird woman!
And a centaur who just
became Luffy's friend...
--Why didn't you tell me?!
--What?! What's up so suddenly?!
You bastard!
I dropped my guard thinking
you were one of us.
Why can't I be one of you?!
We're friends now, don't attack me!
Go to hell, intruder!
There's one more!
Cien Fleurs!
Bellflower!
Who are you?
A panther and a giraffe, huh?
There are many kinds of
centaurs! How interesting!
It's a mythical horse! It can't be real!
What happened?
He suddenly attacked me
after talking to somebody.
Look at this Baby Transponder
Snail! It says "CC"!
They're not wild centaurs.
They belong to some kind of organization.
--"CC"?
--So they're our enemies?
Anyway, even if we go
back to the sea of fire,
the Sunny is not there!
The only option we have now
is to go to the ice lands!
Nami, Sanji, Franky, and Chopper are missing!
They were abducted most likely.
I hope they're not riddled with bullets.
Stop!
We could get there faster if we
had landed on the other side.
Then we wouldn't have gotten to
eat the dragon or meet Leg-maro!
Who's Leg-maro?
I named my hind legs.
Bu! What happened this time-bu?
What's going on-bu?!
What are we gonna do, Luffy?
We can rescue them if we can
get to the other side, right?
Then we have no choice!
All right! Let's go! The plan has changed!
Let's go to the ice lands
to rescue our friends!
I wonder if they're selling
winter clothes on the way.
Seriously, we're gonna
die from cold like this!
What should we do?
I see. They broke this impenetrable door!
Master!
This burn mark...
Who the hell are they?
I thought they were the only
ones who could generate lasers.
Vegapunk's Goddamn Pacifistas!
They haven't caught the
escapees yet, have they?
They're trying to corral
them into the Biscuit Room.
The Biscuit Room?
Master, are you there?!
Yes, I'm here.
A G-5's Navy ship is approaching
the northwest shore!
A Navy ship?! Turn them away at any cost!
Release large amounts of the poison gas!
Don't kill them--we don't want any trouble!
Yes, sir!
Vice Admiral Smoker, it's impossible!
THE NORTHWEST SHORE
I-I can't breathe...
The gas is still leaking!
Be careful! You don't wanna
inhale even a single breath!
Put a gas mask on!
What a dangerous island! Punk Hazard!
Ever since the failure
of that accursed old man
Vega Punk's chemical weapon test 4 years ago,
this island has rotted to the core!
First of all, I don't see Straw
Hat Luffy's pirate ship anywhere!
And no one can enter the island since
there is still poison gas everywhere!
No.
It's not natural that it's
still generating so much gas.
What do you mean?
2 years ago, there was no fire or ice here.
It was nothing but a ruined island.
Surprisingly, most of the
toxic substances were gone.
That's why Akainu and Aokiji
chose Punk Hazard...
...as the place for their showdown!
They chose it as a stage
for their big match -
one powerful enough even to
send the weather into chaos!
A mysterious group of children become
uproarious after meeting Sanji and the others.
During the continuous attacks
by Master's subordinates,
the children begin speaking an astonishing truth!
Nami hears their desperate pleas
and her decision moves the entire crew!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Save the Children! The
Straw Hats Start to Fight!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!