Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,--
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
Then help us!
What does he mean?
You have to help us! Please!
Please!
After being taken to a
mysterious facility by an
unknown group of people,
Nami and the others encountered
strange children.
Let's help these children!
What are you saying, Nami-san?!
We don't know for sure they need saving!
We just met them and we don't
know what's going on here!
It's not our job to help every single person!
I understand what you're saying but...
...you can't turn your back
on a child crying for help!
All right! Let's go!
I won't let you get away! Wait, you bastards!
Oh no!
That centaur again!
Boss!
The intruders are going that
way! Please finish them off!
Is that the Boss?
I see a man with swords.
So is that the samurai who cut our people?
Snow! Snow! I love playing with snow!
Ta-dah! Snowmen!
It looks like me!
Oh?
Hey! Hey!
Who the hell...
What?
Whaaat?!
"A Swordplay Showdown! Brook vs.
the Mysterious Torso Samurai!"
No matter how far we go, all
we see is a wall of ice.
There is no point in protecting ourselves
from the gas if we can't land.
Don't give up yet. Keep searching.
It's no use.
An eruption?!
Around here, it feels like...
...we are being watched by Akainu and Aokiji.
--Oh, that's scary!
--Let's go back!
Stop the ship.
What happened?
There.
What?
Prepare to fire!
Fire!
Breaking the surface won't help...
There's a river!
Hey hey, that was amazing, Smo-yan!
I can't believe it!
How did you know there was a
river behind there, Smo-yan?
--Yeah, Smo-yan?!
--I didn't notice it at all, Smo-yan!
You can tell by looking at the sea current!
You have to pay attention!
You ought to check your own behavior too.
But it's strange.
Yeah.
The important thing is not the
fact that there was a river.
It is whether the ice that
was blocking the river mouth
was natural or man-made.
Do you mean  somebody was
hiding the river on purpose?
Who would wanna live on such an
island filled with the poison gas?
That's ridiculous! No one
wants to live with a mask on!
But the man on the Snail
mentioned the island.
You probably misheard it, Tashigi-chan!
Not even a Transponder
Snail could survive here!
That's right!
If you have time for laughing,
break up more ice!
--What the hell?!
--A wall of ice?!
If we collide into it,  even
this warship would sink!
--Oh no!
--We gotta destroy it!
Shoot!
PUNK HAZARD ISLAND - THE
MIDDLE LAKE LUFFY'S GROUP
They are...
Boss! Please take care of them!
Be ready!
I, Brownbeard-sama,
THE BOSS – BROWNBEARD - AN ALLIGATOR CENTAUR
(A FORMER PIRATE,  BOUNTY: 80 MILLION 60 THOUSAND BERRIES)
will kick your asses all the way to hell!
They're all centaurs!
I wonder if they wanna join us too!
I'm sure they don't!
They're obviously prepared to fight us!
They're colleagues of the man who sent
out the emergency signal, aren't they?
Yeah, they must be!
We have to clear the air
before they start to fight!
Hey!
We're here to help you
people! Let's talk first!
You're lying through your teeth!
You're with the samurai!
So there's no doubt that you're intruders!
Samurai?
He's talking about you!
No, he's not a samurai - he's a swordsman!
He's a dumb meathead who picks fights
without thinking sometimes but...
...he's not the one who attacked your people!
Who did you call "dumb"?!
Help! He's gonna kill me!
--I'm not gonna kill you! Stop saying that!
--They're having a falling out.
What a pathetic ploy!
We can't let them go any further! Shoot them!
Understood!
THE ICE LANDS - INSIDE OF THE
MYSTERIOUS FACILITY NAMI'S GROUP
This way, kids! Run if you wanna get away!
You're on fire, Chopper!
Of course!
Sanji entrusted me with
the important mission of
protecting the kids and
getting them out of here!
I'll do it!
I'll carry it through!
Why are those kids running?!
I'm a man! Leave it up to me!
You're amazing, racoon bro!
I'm not a raccoon - I'm a reindeer! Hi-ya!
But where should we go?
That's something you need
to figure out. Wachaa!
Boy...
Sis, are we going to be okay?
Of course! We've been though
situations like this lots of times!
So just relax and follow us!
Uh-huh!
THE MYSTERIOUS FACILITY -
BISCUIT ROOM SANJI'S GROUP
Weapons Left!
Super!
He has weapons all over his body!
He's the one who broke the door!
Oh? You guys wanna know more about me?
Okay! I'll spend as much
time with you as you want!
Load the poison gas canisters!
There are no kids in here!
Fire at will!
Why don't you take off your mask
and smoke some poison gas with us.
You bastard!
Don't get so mad.
--He ripped off our masks!
--He broke our air tanks too!
Don't use gas canisters!
What are they?!
Sheep?
What are you doing?
This one is different from the others!
Who is he? He's proving an able opponent!
Again, what are you talking about?
Well, that's what's going on with my torso!
IN FRONT OF THE MYSTERIOUS FACILITY BROOK
Hey! What's going on?!
Wh-Wh-Who are you?!
Where is your head and legs?!
You're scaring me! Please say something!
Shoot! Shoot!
We'll reach the end of the river soon.
I wonder what will be there!
I think I know.
Are you a ghost, by any chance?!
If so, you gotta obey the rules!
Don't come out during the day!
I didn't do anything wrong!
I just set foot on the
island to make snowmen!
Oh, would you like to join
me and make one, too?
We can make a snow sculpture as well...
I was just kidding!
What's wrong with him?!
How can he attack me with such precision?!
He doesn't have eyes!
Oh yeah! I don't have eyes, either!
Scary! He's strong! Scary!
What do you want?!
Can't you just tell me
why you wanna fight me?!
Aubade Coup Droit!
Two-Sword Style?!
Enough already!
Scary! Scary! Gross!
Master!
Did you catch the escapees?
No, I have news about G-5.
Oh, them!
The poison gas didn't work.
Currently, they are breaking
through ice floes with a cannon
and slowly forcing their way into the island.
They'll reach the laboratory in time!
Why?
Why do they want to come
into the island so badly?
Do they know something?
Who is in charge?
Vice Admiral Smoker.
Smoker?
Of all others, that pain in the neck?
Conceal all the ships moored at the front.
Who's gonna deal with them?
No one's allowed to be here.
Don't let them find you at any cost.
Then you'll deal with them?
Don't be ridiculous! I can't
just show myself like that!
But there is no one else who can stop them!
Do you want me to do it?
We finally made it!
I thought I was gonna die!
We've only just landed on the island. Get up!
Don't be so harsh!
We did our best so be kind to us!
Don't be such a baby!
Smoker-san?
Calm down.
I thought so.
--There is no gas.
--What?
It's hard to believe but she's right.
Then why was there poison gas earlier?
Somebody who doesn't want to
welcome us released it probably.
Do you really think so?
Let's find out.
Is that...
Yes, Dr. Vegapunk's laboratory.
Former laboratory, I mean.
It should be abandoned and empty.
There is still power.
Who is living here?
Hey! Come on out!
What's taking you so long?!
Are you afraid of us?!
We don't have to ring a doorbell and wait!
We can just break the door with
the cannon of the ship, Smo-yan...
Smoker-san...
--Hey! Answer!
--Just open it!
You hear me?
No one is allowed to be here on this island!
Whoever you are, you're under arrest, fool!
Come on out now!
Ignoring us? Okay, bring the cannon here!
--Let's put a big hole in it!
--Hey!
It opened!
Now you're giving up? We're the Navy!
What brought you here - to my vacation home?
White Chase-ya!
No way!
He is...
He used to be a rookie with a 440
million berry bounty and now,
he is among them...
..."Hawk-Eye" Mihawk, Pirate
Empress Boa Hancock,
and Don Quixote Doflamingo.
Pirates backed by the World Government -
the Seven Warlords!
Trafalgar Law!
Let's go back, Smoker-san!
I don't want anything to do with him!
You know what he did!
To become a member of the Warlords...
...he delivered the hearts of one
hundred pirates to the headquarters!
He's crazy!
What a creep!
Why are you here?
No one, not even pirates
or Government allies,
is allowed to be here on this island, Law!
That means you people
are not allowed, either!
Law stands in Smoker's way,
and neither will yield a single step.
As the situation reaches its boiling point,
the Straw Hat Pirates suddenly
appear with the children in tow.
It was then that Law does something that causes
the situation to move immediately!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Swordplay Showdown! Brook vs.
the Mysterious Torso Samurai!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!