Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
After receiving an emergency signal,
they landed on Punk Hazard Island.
It was a strange island divided
into two parts; the Burning
Lands and the Ice Lands.
To rescue Nami and the others
who are held captive,
Luffy's group headed to the Ice Lands.
But they were unaware that some
former acquaintances were also on the island.
What brought you here - to my vacation home?
White Chase-ya!
"The Warlord! Trafalgar Law!"
Trafalgar! I know you're a Warlord but
we need you to ask you to step aside.
Move out of the way!
We know somebody else is here on the island!
INSIDE OF DR. VEGAPUNK'S FORMER
LABORATORY NAMI'S GROUP
Dad! Mom!
Hey, you said "We are not sick
anymore" earlier, didn't you?
Uh-huh.
What kind of sickness did you have?
None of you look sick to me.
I don't know. But they
told us that we were sick
and we'd get better in a year.
Get better in a year?
Uh-huh.
And people who were asked
to treat me by my dad and
mom took me to this place.
That means your parents
sent you to this place?
Not really, those people told
me that out of the blue in
front of my house and took me here.
They said they didn't want my
dad and mom to get infected.
So I couldn't even say goodbye.
That's what happened to you all?
--Un-huh.
--Me too.
No way! It seems they were kidnapped!
Some strangers took them here
without letting them see their parents?
That could only mean...
...you're really very sick!
What are you, stupid?!
Are you all doing okay?
If any of you can't run,
I'll carry you on my back.
They all look fine.
Yes, we are! The Master has been treating us.
The Master?
Uh-huh, the Master.
Master!
--Master!
But it's been over a year, hasn't it?
Chopper, why don't you examine them later?
Yeah, okay.
Oh no! This door is locked!
We have nowhere to go!
What?
--They are coming!
--What are you gonna do?
I have to hurry!
Nami, step aside!
One more! Hi-ya!
It's open. Wachaa.
--So strong!
--You became very powerful!
That was cool, Racoon-chan!
No, I'm not a racoon!
But you look like one now.
I guess you're right!
Let's go, kids!
It's freezing! Chopper,
can I borrow your fur?
Oh, sure.
I mean, no way!
What is this place?
Is it outside? Or is it a freezer?!
It's too dark. I can barely see anything.
It's perfect for me!
Yeah, but you're from a Winter Island.
Isn't this a path? It's
too dark and I can't...
Oh, I see it! There's a door!
Oh yeah!
Let's go! It's not a dead end!
Okay!
Sis! I don't like this place! I'm scared!
What?
--What's wrong, kids?
--Let's go! They're coming!
When I first got here, I
walked through this place!
Are you sure?!
That means it'll lead us to the exit!
It's really cold but hang on! Let's go!
No!
I mean...
When you look around...
Around?
There is something in the wall...
This path scares me because there
are frozen people all around!
Huh?! What's going on here?!
Dead bodies in ice?!
There are more up there!
Down there, too!
N-N...
No!!
No, Sis, wait! Don't leave us!
Okay, I think I'm done.
INSIDE OF THE LABORATORY -
BISCUIT ROOM SANJI'S GROUP
Hey, you blocked their path already.
That should be enough!
Let's go! I just felt
Nami-san's inner scream!
Maybe she wants to tell me that she loves me!
By the way, what are those people?
They're half sheep.
I think there was a mythical
creature like this.
Don't bother to think about them now.
We have to get the whole picture first.
Let's go save Nami-san now!
Wait! Leave me here! I want to stay here!
My boy was not among those children.
There must be other rooms so I'll stay and...
You can't even move on your own!
If we leave you here, we would
feel like we're abandoning you!
And that's not a great feeling!
But I'm here to rescue my boy!
Don't irritate me!
Why don't you just ask me to find your body?!
Where is it?!
I don't wanna owe anything to pirates!
I wouldn't ask you even if it kills me!
H-However, if you want to look for my body...
I won't stop you.
You're just a severed-head!
Don't be so arrogant!
Are you gonna use violence against me?!
I have no regrets!
I'm not gonna beg a thug for my life!
Hey, stop.
You're not gonna feel better by
smashing a helpless severed-head.
When you took him out of the room,
you already gave in to him, Sanji!
But...!
He's pissing me off!
I was so stupid to be moved
by his determination!
I don't wanna help him!
Now, I'm not even capable of
fighting back if someone hits me
so you can carry me if you want to.
Damn! We'll settle this once
you get your body back!
You show no mercy even on
a severed-head like me.
I better watch my mouth.
I wonder if Nami found the way out!
Let's find them!
I'm really... itchy!
PUNK HAZARD ISLAND - THE
MIDDLE LAKE LUFFY'S GROUP
I got you, intruders!
No, he sliced it.
Take a good look.
They're so dull.
Good job, Zoro-kun! I have to compliment you!
Hey, I got Leg-maro too!
--He cut the shell in half?!
--Damn samurai!
Don't hesitate! Fire!
We can't clear the air!
They look like they're dumb, so...
We should be friends!
Gum-Gum Leg-maro Balloon!
He's doing something again-bu!
Leg-maro has nothing to do with it!
What?! He repelled them all!
What's wrong with his body?!
He's a Devil Fruit eater.
Then I know what to do!
Prepare to fire!
They're gonna shoot again.
They'll never learn. I'll
be counting on you guys!
Wait.
They're aiming at the water!
They're gonna try to sink the boat!
What?! We have two Devil
Fruit eaters on board!
Take good aim!
We'll let them fall into the water!
Rot in hell, Devil Fruit eaters!
Damn!
Fire!
Here they come!
Let's get behind an iceberg!
All right!
That was close.
Why aren't you rowing?
Devil Fruit eaters can't fight in the water!
Sink to your death, Devil Fruit eaters!
A SNOW-CAPPED MOUNTAIN
NEAR THE LABORATORY BROOK
Gross! So gross!
What's wrong with that ghost?!
Suddenly attacking me!
Why do I have to get attacked?!
He's kind of strong too!
I hear something in the distance.
I don't have ears though.
You are so persistent!
I have no choice! I'll fight you!
I'll forget I saw it.
Oh, I don't have eyes anyway.
THE MAIN ENTRANCE OF THE LABORATORY
Hello? My name is Monkey D. Luffy! I'm
gonna become the King of the Pirates!
You picked up too fast and said too much!
Help me!
What happened?
It's cold... Is this the Boss?!
No, I'm not the Boss.
My colleagues are getting
cut one after another!
The samurai are gonna kill us!
Where are you?!
Somebody please help me! I'm on...
...Punk Hazard!
The name of the island and
the fact he said "It's cold."
There is almost no doubt that this
man sent the signal from this island.
You know Straw Hat Luffy, don't you?
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Repel!
Room.
Shambles.
I've been killed!
When the incident involving the Roswalds,
a Celestial Dragon family,
happened on Sabaody 2 years ago,
Kid, Straw Hat and you fought together.
And during the War of the Best...
Put Straw Hat-ya on my ship!
I'm gonna help him get out of here.
Let me take care of him for now!
When Akainu was after Straw Hat,  you...
...helped him get away!
What do you want?
I know you Navy people are good at
forging those emergency signals.
I'm afraid it wasn't a trap that we set.
Oh yeah?
But I don't know anything so there's
nothing more to talk about.
Cut that crap.
Let us see inside the laboratory.
It's my vacation home now. I refuse!
What's wrong with me - a pirate staying
on an island you people abandoned?
I'm the only one here!
If Straw Hat comes, I'll
chop his head off for you.
If that's all you have to say, go home!
So scary! Those frozen people!
I've had it with this place!
But look! There's a door! We can get out!
Yeah!
There is somebody else in there!
I made it out!
Outside?! It's freezing!
We made it!
I got out of the building! I can go home!
I can see my dad and mom again!
It's cold!
Get out of my way, kids!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, Franky!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, Tank!
Clear the way, clear the way, Super the way!
I'll run over you if you stand in my way!
But I avoid running over flowers!
I'm kind of sweet - Franky Tank!
All right! Here we go, everybody!
Yeah!
One, two, three...
Super!
The Straw Hats?! Children?!
I don't know where to begin!
A big racoon, a woman in bikini
in the winter, giant kids,
a robot, and a severed-head...
Am I dreaming?!
--Tank treads!
--Cool!
--Awesome!
--A tank!
The best!
Bad roads won't trouble me!
Nami-san! I'm glad that you're okay!
I like the way you shiver
in the cold but I don't want
you to get sick so take my jacket!
Thank you, Sanji-kun!
You look familiar!
Yeah, he was there at Sabaody!
Are you the one who locked
up these children?!
You brute! You can't take them back!
Oh, you're...!
I was wondering who this
villainous guy was! Smoker!
And you, cutie!
This is not good! The Navy's here!
We can't escape from here!
Let's look for another exit!
Get inside!
Hurry up, kids! Go to the back!
There should be a backdoor!
What brought the Navy to such a place?!
I don't know! Just run!
Oh? I thought the Navy were good people.
Why don't you go to them, then?
No, they look like gangsters!
You lied! You weren't the only one here!
Seems like I wasn't. I'm also surprised.
Everybody, let's catch the Straw Hats!
All right, let's go! Follow Captain-chan!
No, wait!
Room.
--Ouch!
--Are you alright?
Those fools... They brought trouble!
Takt!
What's making that noise?
No way!
The warship is in the air!
Along with the bottom of the river!
What's going on here?!
I can't let you leave the island now.
I'm sorry that I said no one's here.
I knew he was dangerous!
Step back.
You guys are no match!
He'll chop off your hands and feet!
Go, Smo-yan!
--Kick his ass!
--Show him the true power of G-5!
Law's power, capable of lifting even warships...
...overwhelms the Navy's G-5.
Sanji and Nami's group also ends up...
...in an unprecedented situation because of Law.
Meanwhile, Luffy's group comes
upon a lake in the frozen lands...
...and encounters a crisis of its own!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"In a Real Pinch! Luffy Sinks
into the Ice-cold Lake!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!