Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner (･∀･)
Wanted->means Winner :D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled
by the Four Emperors.
After receiving an emergency
signal, they landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts,
one burning, the other frozen.
A branch of the Navy - G-5 - led by Smoker
reached the island while
chasing after the Straw Hats
and got into a fight with Trafalgar
Law who appeared out of nowhere.
It's you! Do you remember me?
Thank you for your help the other day!
Shambles!
What did he just do?
If there is some mastermind behind Law
and if "CC" are his initials,
I think I know who it is.
He is the former colleague of Dr.Vegapunk.
He is a scientist named Caesar Clown!
"The Worst in the World!
A Scientist of Terror - Caesar!"
Caesar Clown?
Who is that?
Um, I have something on my mind, too.
If I remember correctly,
there were a lot of child abduction
cases taking place around here recently.
Child abduction?!
That's right.
By the way, I can't get used seeing
you like that, Captain-chan!
It can't be helped!
You have to deal with it for now!
Hey, Tashigi! What are you talking about?
I haven't heard about
any child abductions!
Please button up, Smoker-san!
I like how open that Captain-chan
is but she's scary inside!
Shut up!
All I know is accidents at sea
happen frequently in this area.
But in fact, I was wondering why accidents
involving children are so prevalent here.
Oh yeah, that's true, isn't it?
Yeah!
I actually go to the
communication department often...
Oh, I don't have glasses...
And I've heard the G-5 gets
many child abduction reports.
But when it appears in the
newspaper, it's often labeled
an accident at sea or the work of pirates...
…or simply a child gone missing.
Of course, it could be the
reporter's mistake but...
I... I thought maybe it's
possible that they were really...
Is it hard to say, Tashigi?
If that's what you think,
just say it clearly!
We saw a bunch of kids earlier
and you're thinking maybe there
really have been many abductions.
And you think the
kidnapper is on this island.
But if that's the case,
those news articles were false...
...meaning somebody in the G-5 covered
up those child abduction cases.
What?
Does it mean somebody among us
is working for the kidnapper?
Wh...
What?!
Hey, Smo-san, don't insult us!
Maybe we are a spoiled group in the Navy
but we take pride in being Navy soldiers!
He's right! None of us is doing that!
Shut up!
So scary!
You fools are not even worth suspecting!
What?!
But, all of you guys,
don't expect too much from the Navy.
As long as it consists of a group of people,
there is no organization that is perfect.
If you assume too much,
you'll miss the enemy.
Don't be fooled by appearances.
Roger, Captain-chan!
Never mind, fools.
I-I'm the Captain!
Oh yeah!
We got fooled by their appearances!
Smoker-san, I'm not so sure
about my theory though.
That's okay.
We'd better keep it in mind anyway.
But since my heart and
body are in Law's hands,
I can't leave this island.
One third of you should leave
here by ship, to make a report.
What are you talking about, Vice Admiral?
Our warship's been destroyed.
I said I saw their ship.
Steal it.
Oh yeah! I hadn't thought of that!
You're a bad person!
Be careful! Before it gets too late,
I'll try to take back my heart and body,
and reveal who's really behind this!
VEGAPUNK'S FORMER THIRD LABORATORY
I finally got through to him.
Clank.
We have permission to kill.
The Straw Hats, G-5, and Foxfire Kin'emon.
No matter who dies on this island,
Joker will make it look
like an accident at sea.
Catch as many of them as possible!
The more guinea pigs, the better.
Yes, Master.
But you can just kill the ones
who can't be taken with poison.
Where did Law go?
He left the room a few minutes ago.
All right.
One of the enemies has a
400 million berry bounty.
Don't push yourself too much.
The other members are in a broad
range of 120 million to 50 berries each.
All of them are wanted pirates
and their bounties are 800
million 50 berries in total.
But they have been inactive
over the past two years
so their bounty hasn't moved up.
They could be more powerful
than the numbers show.
You always study hard, Monet.
Master!
Oh, what happened to you? It's extremely
cold and you didn't wear a coat?!
We were robbed by some pirates.
More importantly, they took
Boss Brownbeard with them!
Please help him!
Oh really? I'm sorry to hear that!
Don't worry about Brownbeard.
We'll get him back at any cost.
Go to the backroom now!
You're so lucky.
We just made a new medicine.
It will warm up your body
and heal your wounds.
Really?! That'd be nice!
Please help the others, too!
Of course, I will.
But first, you have to get treated.
Thank you very much.
What the hell is this, Usopp?!
It's kind of super!
I don't care anymore...
Thanks, Usopp!
It spoils Nami-san's beauty!
Cut the crap!
We get confused if nothing is done.
Brownbeard?
Yes. I'm sure you heard that name before.
That was what I used to go by.
No idea.
Are you kidding, you fool?
Go away, brats!
What happened to you?
You were clammed up a while ago
but now you're talkative.
You guys are done for!
Law's gonna come to save me!
I despise pirates from your generation
but Law is an exception.
What do you mean our generation?
Don't you know anything, fool?
Eleven rookies with
bounties over 100 million
who arrived at Sabaody at
the same time two years ago
plus Blackbeard...
People call you twelve
"the Worst Generation."
You twelve are troublemakers...
...who were born at the change of the era
and hold the key to the future
of this war-torn world.
After Whitebeard died, you all came
to the New World and raised havoc.
When something big happened,
there was always somebody
from your generation involved.
Blackbeard! Kid! Law! Drake! Hawkins!
Basil Hawkins was the one who
shattered my pirate group.
I lost both of my legs and ended my
career as a pirate thanks to him.
My crew were annihilated.
I fled for my life and arrived here...
...on Punk Hazard.
Do you know what this place is?
This place... This island...
...used to be a lush green
treasure house of life.
Really?
It's nothing like that now.
And it housed a laboratory
of Dr.Vegapunk, a Government scientist.
They were experimenting with and
developing weapons and chemicals here.
Instead of going to prisons,
they brought some prisoners here
and performed experiments on
them like they were guinea pigs.
But four years ago,
Vegapunk's chemical
weapon test went wrong!
And two of the three
laboratories exploded!
This is the remains of that laboratory.
THE REMAINS OF VEGAPUNK'S FORMER
FIRST AND SECOND LABORATORY
I see. So there was a huge explosion.
That's why this place is a mess.
The explosion belched intense
heat and toxic substances,
and killed each and every
living thing on the island.
But in that critical situation,
the Government left those
guinea-pig prisoners
and escaped from the island
then shut it down completely.
The prisoners stayed
in the Third Laboratory,
the only building that remained intact,
and sheltered themselves from the
poison gas that was all over the island.
Even those who survived were
paralyzed mainly in their lower body
because of the nerve gas
and lost hope in their future.
But...
...a year later,
our merciful Master came to the island!
He purified the gas all over the
island with his special ability
and gave those prisoners who couldn't
walk mechanical means to move
and took them on as his lackeys.
Master!
Master-san!
I landed here a year later after that,
two years ago.
There were still some toxic
substances left in the air
and I felt nauseous when I breathed in.
Just when I thought I had no energy
left to live and this was the end...
I saw the prisoners who
lost their legs like I did
and the Master!
His kindness saved my
life as it did to the others.
Vegapunk was a devil because
he paralyzed my comrade's legs
but the Master was our
warm-hearted savior!
Master!!
And then a few months ago,
the second savior--
Trafalgar Law who had
gained the title of Warlord...
...came to the island.
Using his special ability,
he gave those of us who
couldn't walk as we wished, legs.
The legs of living animals!
We thought we would never walk again
so we couldn't stop crying from happiness!
What a touching story!
So the Tra-guy is a good guy as I thought!
He saved my life, too!
Vegapunk is a horrible person!
That's why there were those
half-sheep people at the laboratory.
Centaurs and the bird woman, too.
It all makes sense.
But wait. What about the dragon?
Oh, did you see the dragon?
That's an artificial being that
Vegapunk created to guard the island.
It can adapt itself to
any kind of environment.
I heard some Celestial Dragon
liked it and named it.
I forgot the name but if
you see it, you better run.
It's extremely aggressive.
All right.
We already ate it.
Anyway, now you know who rules the island.
No one wants to come near it.
Punk Hazard is our Master's property now!
Rejoice!
The Master is still doing research
today for the future of mankind!
He needs only a few guinea
pigs and you can become one!
You can't get away!
Hm? What's the matter?
Master!
Master! I can't breathe!
What kind of...
...medicine is this?
Master!
Master...
Get me out of here!
You need to hang on.
How do you feel now?
Feeling nauseous and coughing, huh?
That's good.
Do you have a headache?
It hurts!
Feels like it's gonna split open!
Uh-huh, I see.
What? It wasn't Vegapunk?
Then, Smo-san,
who caused that huge explosion?
The one who made the weapon
and
let it go off accidentally...
...was Caesar Clown!
Caesar Clown was
the second-in-command in the
science department at that time
but since he had an inhumane streak,
he was always butting heads with Vegapunk.
M-Master...
H-Help me...
How are your eyes?
Do you see anything?
Huh?
Oh... there is... a giant snake in the room!
No way!
All right, that's good. Goodbye!
When the accident happened,
Vegapunk's name came up only
because he was a person in charge.
Of course,
it was a crime to develop a mass-killing
weapon that belches poison gas.
And since it had been brought
to light by the accident,
Caesar got arrested.
But with his formidable ability,
he managed to escape from a prison ship
and had been missing ever since.
If Caesar is still doing
research on this island,
we must stop him now!
He's gonna do something horrible again!
"Not good."
Another failure?
Failure?
Watch your tongue!
A FORMER GOVERNMENT SCIENTIST
BOUNTY: 300 MILLION BERRIES MASTER CAESAR CLOWN
My experiments never fail!
Even what happened four years ago!
Everyone talks nonsense as usual!
A failed experiment?
I "killed" the whole
island with the weapon!
It wasn't a failure, World Government!
I'm capable of killing more
enemies than anyone else.
I carefully document my
victims until their final moment.
You just wait!
I'll make them realize who is the
greatest scientist in the world!
"One Piece," "Toriko," and "Dragon Ball"
have a miraculous collaboration.
The World's Best Eating Competition is
held in search for the legendary ingredient.
With the dream collaboration
between Luffy, Toriko, and Goku,
the crowd's enthusiasm explodes.
But then a mysterious being suddenly appears
and the situation takes an unprecedented turn.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"History's Strongest Collaboration
vs. Glutton of the Sea"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!