All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
However, no one has ever fully explored it
and his friends venture into that sea.
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
After landing on Punk Hazard; an island with
two parts, one burning, the other frozen,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
the Straw Hats learned about
the hideous experiments
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
performed by Caesar Clown, the Master,
and headed off to investigate
but as things got going,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy was unexpectedly
approached by Trafalgar Law.
We're gonna form an alliance
with the Heart Pirates?!
After surviving a fierce battle,
After landing on Punk Hazard;
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen,
So what we're gonna do is
kidnap the Master, right?
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
the Straw Hats learned about
the hideous experiments
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
-- the harshest sea ruled
by the Four Emperors.
This is the last chance
for you to reconsider.
performed by Caesar Clown, the Master,
They landed on Punk Hazard;
After receiving an emergency signal,
they landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen,
They landed on Punk Hazard;
and headed off to investigate.
That's okay. We're with you.
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen.
an island with two parts,  one
and regrouped at Dr. Vegapunk's
former laboratory.
What?
An alliance?
A branch of the Navy - G-5
- led by Smoker reached
I have a plan...
Luffy learned about the hideous experiments
What?! The samurai left?!
How does it feel to be loose after so long,
the island while chasing after the Straw Hats
...to bring down one of the Four Emperors!
performed by Caesar Clown, the Master,
--Yes.
--Damn!
Smiley?!
and got into a fight with Trafalgar
Law who appeared out of nowhere.
and headed off to investigate.
When I said I saw a torso earlier,
So the clan split up. However...
"Formed! Luffy and Law's Pirate Alliance!"
What are they?
he asked me where in detail.
They are footprints, aren't they?
"Capture M!
The Pirate Alliance's Operation Launches!"
Boy, that fool!
Is it an animal? If it's a
human, he must be a Giant.
Scalpel!
Sanji, Brook, and Zoro
headed to the lake looking
for the missing samurai.
I sense something.
THE MOUNTAIN BEHIND THE LABORATORY
PRESENT
My heart!
Two beast-looking creatures.
An alliance?
What's wrong, Synd?
What're we gonna do?!
Are you saying that if we work together,
we can take down an Emperor?
Maybe from when I fell?
Looks like I hit my head.
Are you in pain?
Where are they?!
Law? The Master?
Mocha!
No, we're on a snow-capped
mountain so it must be them!
How absurd!
Oh, maybe I did, too. I have a huge headache!
I don't know what he wants but don't
listen to this jerk's fast-talk, Luffy!
The Master was our warm-hearted savior!
What happened, everybody?!
The Snow Mountain Killers - stalking
out from deep in the snowstorm!
NHC10.
We've wasted so much time.
I wonder if the samurai is okay.
I detected it in their body.
Master!!
You made us take this side trip.
Punk Hazard is our Master's property now!
You're Brownbeard, aren't you?
Although it was just a trace amount, it's...
I thought we all wanted to do this!
I'm not saying we can beat
the Emperor straight away.
Your name is also on our kill list.
...a drug!
It's a shame that we couldn't find the Yeti.
All I'm saying is we'd get a chance
if we advance the plan step by step.
The candy...
Rejoice!
The Master is still doing research
today for the future of mankind!
But I'll never forget
the shadows that we saw!
Straw Hat bro!
You guys, you didn't harm
my friends, did you?!
Are you gonna go get me the candy?
What do you say, Straw Hat-ya?
That wasn't it. Don't fool yourself.
He needs only a few guinea
pigs and you can become one!
No, I can't! If Chopper says "No," I can't!
You said it was an enemy attack.
Which of the Four Emperors
are you talking about?
No, I didn't.
You can't get away!
He is our doctor. Trust him!
Yes, you did.
Hey Luffy, why are you interested?!
No, I didn't!
You said you're gonna go get it for me!!
I don't believe it exists.
We can't trust this guy!
Oh? Where did he go?!
I believe it exists.
Special Attack - Sleep Star!
I just want to talk about whether
it exists or not forever.
"Chopper's Fury! The Master's
Inhumane Experiment!"
They took Nami with them!
THE REMAINS OF THE FIRST
AND SECOND LABORATORY
I'm impressed a little.
You're kind of mature.
The Emperor's name is...
Master!
"Save Nami! Luffy's Fight on
the Snow-Capped Mountains!"
What a great guy!
I'm very old, you know.
Yes, the Master is a wonderful person.
All right! They are all sleeping now.
I don't like that indecisive attitude.
They kidnapped Nami?!
The Master is super!
It was my fault.
Even though they were very big,
--He's merciful!
--The human race's last hope!
Hey! Samurai-san!
Luffy decided to take the
children back to their parents
We don't know him that well.
I didn't notice they were there until
Hey, are you listening?
Where are you?!
they appeared in front of my eyes.
and set out looking to find the "Master"
--We!
--Love!
First, it was centaurs and now, beast men?!
If only we could find traces
of his wooden clogs.
Master... Wow!
who is responsible for the experiment.
There are a bunch of strange creatures here!
What the hell?!
What about Straw Hat-ya's group?
So heavy!
Maybe they were waiting for their
chance to attack us somewhere.
Since Monet told me to be
careful with the Straw Hats,
My breasts are heavy when I run!
I got puffed up!
A fuzzball!
I thought you wanted to save that samurai!
That's Guard Boost! You can
turn into six forms at will.
They didn't come here to save Brown-gator?!
I sent those two just to make sure.
Oh no!
I see.
--What an unstable body!
--Get used to it.
How romantic!
It seemed like their main purpose
was to kill us and take the kids.
Okay, let's do it!
You fools! Stop playing with my body!
No, fool!
What?!
I don't care if you fall down!
But first, they killed Brownbeard
at the Master's command.
What?!!
What?! The samurai left?!
"To Annihilate the Straw Hats!
Legendary Assassins Descend!"
They were supposed to be on the same side.
Hey, you two! Take a look at this!
Yes.
Brownbeard admired him so much.
THE STRAW HATS' ENCAMPMENT
Damn! I thought he was too quiet!
The Master was our warm-hearted savior!
There is a footprint!
What?!
When I said I saw a torso earlier,
We're gonna form an alliance
with the Heart Pirates?!
A trace of his wooden clogs?
It's nothing like that!
Luffy!
Then, it must be some centaur's footprint.
This Master guy is a very twisted person.
he asked me where in detail.
You just went out to reclaim Nami!
I told him I lost it around the
lake and he went storming off.
No!
So how did you come back with
such an eccentric idea?!
I can't let these kids go
back to such an evil person!
PUNK HAZARD THE REMAINS OF THE
FIRST AND SECOND LABORATORY
Th-This is...
I wasn't paying attention being
fascinated with Nami-san's sexy body!
Listen...
They could come after us at any moment.
I can't help worrying about
Nami in Franky's body, too!
If we ally ourselves with this
creep who gives me the chills,
Look at this! Doesn't this look like
the legendary Yeti's footprint?!
So please come back as soon as possible.
Why does it matter to you?
We don't know what they're gonna do to her!
I won't be able to sleep in peace at night!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Yes, I'll get her back at any cost!
--Hey hey, don't be ridiculous.
He was only a head and couldn't move.
See, Luffy? Everybody's against it.
Control your strength! You're a robot now!
You guys, look after those kids!
Let's not do it. It's too risky.
Wait, Luffy!
I'm the one who brought him with us.
Wow, is this for real?! There are
mysterious footprints in the snow!
I hope this Master guy will just
come clean about those children.
We wanna travel at our own pace.
It's my body that they took!
I couldn't leave him alone
so I'm responsible for him.
She's right, Luffy!
Chopper, I can't fight like this!
Besides, it's too early to even
think about the Four Emperors!
They're huge, aren't they?!
I can't believe it!
If he doesn't, I will force him to.
If something happens to him, it's my fault.
Give me the bean that you
eat when you transform
I'll shove my finger into his nose
and make his back teeth rattle!
And they look fresh!
We can't fight them yet!
I see. Although he is a samurai,
yourself into a monster!
Hey, treat this racoon.
If we follow them, we will find...
It's not a bean!
he can't use a sword without his
torso so all he can do is run.
Franky, please don't talk!
The Rumble Ball is a power drug!
Forget about some racoon now!
I don't think you can control it.
Huh?
All right! Let's go now!
What?!
I can handle it with my super spirit!
It's me!
Good luck!
Do you wanna go honor your responsibility?
…one of nature's greatest mysteries!
Z-Zuber...
Take care!
Just give it to me! There's no time to argue!
Boy, that fool!
Luffy, I'll be right back, okay?
By the way,
What happened?! My body!
why is he sleeping, too?
I have no choice.
Yeah, okay!
What?
I'll show you the way so...
can I see your panties?
Luffy.
I'm gonna go along with your decision
Of course! Oh yeah, let's get a camera!
Just one, okay?
Really?! It was in this
pocket the whole time?!
It's me.
but alliances between pirates
are often marked by betrayal.
Wait, you fools!
We just took care of three
of them for starters.
Of course it was. It's Chopper's.
What?
Maybe it's dangerous for you
since you are so trusting.
A dead end?
Listen. You can become a monster
for just three minutes.
Pirate Hunter Zoro.
Zoro, you gotta go with them!
Huh? Are you gonna betray me?
Cat Burglar.
If Zoro is there, Sanji-kun will
be arguing with him all the time!
You can't fight after that.
No.
Oh! Look! There are huge shadows behind us!
Soul King.
So if possible, transform into Kung
Fu Boost like I did earlier and...
Hey, have at least a little doubt!
We left their bodies at the bottom
of the cliff in district F-16.
Anyhow, a pirate alliance
sounds like fun, doesn't it?
Because you're such an idiot,
Don't tell me they're the Yeti...
What?!
I was forced to go look for the
stinking samurai, too, you perv!
Can you recover them?
I think Tra-guy is a good man but...
--D-Did you kill them?
--Do you have a problem with that?
Buber!
That's way too early!
...even if he isn't, don't worry!
Do you think I wanted this?!
W-Well, I mean...
What is this gas?!
I don't wanna be with a dumb-ass who
I can't share this happiness with!
If you don't want them
dead, then don't call us!
Because I have you guys who spent
the last two years training!
All of a zudden, I can't zpeak clearly
az if I kot drunk. I'm tired.
Let's go, Franky! This way!
No, I'm sorry! The Master
said dead or alive so...
She only hit me.
What?!
Luffy, you're...
Are you all worrying if my bones got broken?
Whoa whoa, don't get so heated up.
Iz it an enemy attack?!
No, the only thing that was broken
is my will to see panties.
D-Don't mention it! Luffy,
you're making me blush!
Oh, I can't believe I lost it.
These KYP gas canisters
make you drunk and drowsy regardless of
whether or not you're a heavy drinker.
Let's stay cool.
Yeah, I know we're zuper dependable but...
Why're you attacking me?!
They look so happy.
We will be counting on you.
Down below the cliff is district F-16
filled with terrible Ice Spikes!
CAESAR CLOWN'S LABORATORY
We just do what we got to do!
Yeah, they're full of energy.
You're not flattering me, you fool!
Oh no! He's out of control as I thought!
They don't look like they're sick at all.
Did you hear that?
A-Alright, Luffy! You can count on us!
Three of them are dead already, Monet!
So is there much point to Franky going?
Three, for a starter.
Yeah?
If Zoro and the others wimp
out, I'll convince them!
After running wild, he won't
be able to move for a while
That's disappointing.
The Straw Hats are a part of the
Worst Generation; as is Law.
I'm counting on you guys!
so he's not gonna be helpful at all.
Instead, he's going to be in the way.
I'm gonna look into their sickness.
The Government is keeping its eye
on them as well as Blackbeard.
CAESAR'S LABORATORY
Spikes?!
Is there anything I can do?
And there was a scintillating
newspaper article
There is. I need samples of their sweat.
Hey, guys!
with the title "They're Back in Force"
Room.
I don't know where he got it but
this "Cyborg" Franky guy has...
so I thought they were stronger.
Can you collect some for me?
Shambles.
What do you think, Law?
...Vegapunk's laser weapon
mounted in his body.
You know them well, don't you?
All done!
I'll make good use of Vegapunk's invention.
Two years ago, at Sabaody and Marineford,
Sis.
THE STRAW HATS ARE BACK
I got it back! My great body!
Mocha.
Do you think I'm gonna get better?
That was close...
you got involved with the Straw Hat twice.
After I chop his body up and
take the laser system out,
I knew I liked myself the best when I'm me!
Do you think I can see my dad and mom?
What?
Super!
he will be useless. Get
the incinerator ready!
Don't worry.
I will take you back to
your family at any price.
I'm happy for you, Franky!
Yes, sir.
Don't ever take Chopper's body again. Ever.
You didn't summon them here, did you?
What's going on with the Navy
idiots who came to steal the ship?
Uh-huh.
I told you that I didn't know they were
Ah, yes.
I'm...
held captive in the lab until I
ran into them at the entrance.
We ambushed them successfully but...
...back to myself, too, but...
Now, let's talk about what we are gonna do.
Why are there cuts and
bruises all over my body?!
We left their bodies at the bottom
of the cliff in district F-16.
If I knew, I would have warned you...
First of all, get us back to
normal as soon as possible!
What did you guys do to it?!
...that locking them up
in a room wasn't enough.
I don't wanna be a pervert anymore!
--I'm sorry. It's his fault.
Can you recover them?
Hey, hey, you're overpraising me!
--What are they?!
--Humans?! No, horses?!
Why?! You went out of
control in Chopper's body
Don't ever smile like that
with Chopper's face! Ever!
Kill them all!
so I had no choice but to stop you!
I wasn't able to drive the Navy
out thanks to your carelessness.
We won't get beaten that easily!
But you didn't have to use
the same technique you used
But what should we do with those brats?
Look behind you!
to beat the Kraken!
They're such a pain in the ass!
I blame both of you!
You know it's bad news for me, too,
What?!
--I'm sorry!
Franky, I don't want you to say a
single word while you're in his body.
if anybody finds out about this place.
You should be happy just being
back to yourself, Chopper.
Why do I have to be in
someone else's body again?
Ever!
Master!
First, it was Franky and now, Sanji-kun!
Not now. I'm doing an experiment.
Here we come!
But it's a Warlord!
We arrived at district F-16.
There are more!
Nami became Sanji!
--This is no good!
--Nowhere to go!
We found three of the Straw Hats as
informed. We'll recover their dead bodies.
What did you say?
Let's have a snowball fight, Synd!
You're looking good!
You wanna stay on Punk Hazard?
We have to change tactics!
Let's try to seize the ship in full force!
Who are you calling dead?!
It was a pain getting here since Log
Poses don't work for this island
It wouldn't be funny if it happened to you!
What's the matter? Are you okay?
What?! She's alive!
It can't be helped.
because there was the
Government's secret facility.
She's just a girl - she can't fight us...
Chopper and Franky could
It doesn't matter if
there're hundreds of you!
Why do you want to stay?
I can't breathe...
go back to themselves because
their bodies were here
You underlings!
Since this used to be Dr.
Vegapunk's laboratory,
but since Sanji went out looking
for the samurai in Nami's body,
I assume there are traces leading
up to today of Government activity.
you have no choice but take Sanji's body.
Captain-chan... I mean, Smoker-san!
I have to be careful.
What's wrong? Synd, you're acting strange.
Nami-san's body is delicate.
The battle is out of control now.
Can't you do something about it?!
All I'm asking for is free roam within
the laboratory and the island.
No...
You mean...
I can't do anything without your body here.
I should avoid getting even a single bruise.
...we're having a hard fight.
This can't be!
I mean...
How is it going, Racoon-chan?
I can help you with something if you want.
These are the children?
Excuse me for having one, Nami-san.
Well, we'll see soon.
Yeah, I wanna help them.
I have an idea!
And we'll stay out of each other's business.
But it means you can't tell
anybody that I'm here.
What?! This is...
Not even "Joker."
M-Master?
Now...
What's wrong, Synd?
Wake up, you idiots!
Are you in pain?
I'm giving them this drug candy everyday.
We're dealing with the Navy.
You know a lot. How did
you know all those things?
It's the perfect opportunity to test it!
Are you okay?
They're such a pain - just forget about them.
Do you prefer to have an
amateur who doesn't know
What? What?
I heard they're drugged.
anything over me?
In any case, hunting for
nature's mysteries is over.
Yeah, that's great! Let's do that!
We know! Because I tested them!
I can't breathe!
Should the samurai be around here?
Chopper, he's saying he can't breathe.
I see what you mean.
We're birds of a feather.
I just wanna take them home
I think so. He's probably still looking
for his torso around the lake.
Help him.
Although I can't trust you, perhaps
there's no harm in what you ask.
Contact the centaurs who are on patrol now.
but it'll take a while for them to recover
Mocha!
and most importantly, they are so big.
What do you think, Monet?
We almost made it to the lake.
Yes, sir!
What happened, everybody?!
Tell all the other soldiers
evacuate if they want to survive.
Boy, I can't believe somebody's
doing such a horrendous experiment.
Samurai-san!
He is from the North Blue.
Dolan, too?!
They're collapsing! Mostly the giant ones!
Hey, samurai!
The Surgeon of Death.
Turning people into giants is a
project that has been underway for
An Op-Op Fruit eater.
What's going on?!
Samurai, come on out!
Chopper, what was it? Are they really sick?
So you're a doctor, huh?
hundreds of years by the World Government.
There are a whole bunch
THE MOUNTAIN BEHIND THE LABORATORY
of former prisoners who were
paralyzed by poison gas.
Samurai!
No.
The Government? For what purpose?
What?
Synd, is there something you want now?
Did you get your ass kicked already?!
Let me go! Let me go, you fools!
Military might, probably.
Can you treat them?
What's wrong with you guys?! You perverts!
What do you usually do at this time of day?
If they can produce an infinite
amount of giant soldiers,
What're you gonna do to me?!
Come on out! Are you alright?! Samurai!
they'll become invincible.
Usually?
I know I'm pretty and have a good figure
Samurai-san! We're calling you!
We have a checkup and...
so you couldn't help kidnapping me!
Caesar wants to achieve the goal first
Well,
...after that...
What is this guy talking about?
you would've been wiser about it if you
I wonder how far he went.
What do you do after that?
and outsmart the Government and Vegapunk
wanted to summon your friends here.
He must be a queer. That's cool.
You became a Warlord intentionally
I get a candy.
but I don't think it's that easy.
Maybe he found his torso already
and went looking for his son.
You're gonna pay for this!
Luffy won't tolerate it!
by kissing the Government's
ass and came to this island.
A candy?
It tastes good.
I hope you two get your asses kicked!
I don't think you would do
something to mess that all up.
Do you really wanna help them?
We all love that candy.
Oh?! He's here!
You don't even know who they are.
I'm sorry.
And it's fun, too.
Be quiet for a moment. Noisy
people like you are...
What?!
Yes, I do. Although I don't know them well,
You said...
I can't believe it! He's frozen!
What?
...those kids will have an urge to come
Because smoke comes out of it.
...Not cool.
back here even if you don't do anything.
they asked me to help
with tears in their eyes.
1, 2, 3!
But the weapons that are
mounted in your body are...
What do you mean by that?
Oh yeah... When I eat that candy...
Oh.
It seems like the Master tricked
them and brought them here
...Cool.
If we give them to the Master,
our reward will be...
That's because I'm giving them
this drug candy everyday.
but they already know there is
something wrong with this place.
When I eat that candy,
I... I feel happy so...
When you eat it, it's sweet and fizzy!
...So cool!
Hey hey, are you alright?
And gas fills up your mouth.
Did someone kick your ass?
...that might help me now!
Until I know that they are safe,
I won't leave this island!
It causes instant addiction!
ROCK
If they go back to their homes,
they won't be able to have it.
It's cold today as always.
I was mysteriously paralyzed
and thought I was gonna die.
Was your name Brownbeard?
Are you willing to stay here alone?
What do you know about this?!
SCOTCH
You just got caught in a snowstorm
and froze solid, didn't you?
You're a sick man. You remind me of somebody.
My body's cool!
I'm not gonna leave my friend behind.
These children are not sick!
THE SNOW MOUNTAIN KILLERS
THE YETI COOL BROTHERS
No! I don't feel cold at all...
If that's what Nami and
Chopper want, I want it, too.
What are you saying?
Then put some clothes on!
I work outside so I don't know much
about what's going on in the laboratory
Aren't you gonna fight the Navy?
Our rifles are like cannons to you people.
And Sanji wants to stick the
samurai's body together.
Don't be so stubborn!
Call me if you need me.
but those brats have an intractable disease!
You got to help us if you
wanna team up with us!
Warriors don't feel cold!
I'll cut whoever's head for you.
We have poison gas canisters, too.
Nobody can beat us because
we don't show ourselves.
Kids, stay with us!
He's such a pain.
Hey Chopper, even the smaller
ones are suffering now!
Get yourself some clothes!
You have an ability to do that!
You said your friend will come?
I thought so. You have no idea.
It's hard dealing with a smart guy.
I'm sure he'll come. We
set a trap to lure him.
What the hell is this Master guy thinking?!
You think an alliance is...
People can't help following
footprints in the snow.
...a cooperative relationship just
for some common goal, don't you?
What do you mean by that?
Do you have a problem with our Master?
T-To tell you the truth,
I wonder how far Zoro went.
because of that magic, I have a weakness.
The merciful Master was
kind enough to take them in
He's with Sanji and Brook so I don't think
Of course, I do.
Listen. Luffy's idea of an alliance
is a little different from yours.
he's lost in the snow-capped mountains.
I-I became not capable of swimming...
and try to save them with
his medicinal skills!
Footprints! Footprints! How helpful!
It's like being friends, isn't it?
You can't swim, right?! We know that!
They are pretty easy to follow!
He's a scientist of love!
If you're thinking of taking control,
it won't be that easy, either.
--I can't breathe!
--Ally!
Wh-What I'm trying to say is my torso is...
Wh-What happened?!
That's what they say.
Look! In fact, they're suffering now
because they left the laboratory
Once he feels sure about
something, he won't back down.
Hey, Franky, I said stop!
...p-probably soaking in the water!
Again! What's going on?!
It's a pain in the ass!
Oh?
and they haven't gotten
their treatment for today!
This is not an earthquake or anything!
His selfishness is as formidable
as the Four Emperors.
The water?
I-In fact,
We're under attack!
You're wrong!
it feels like the upper half
of my body is in the water.
That must be hard.
Chopper, did you find out something?!
The footprints end there...
But what your friends want has
nothing to do with us at all...
NHC10.
I see. That's why you couldn't even
move and you were frozen here.
What are they?
I detected it in their body.
They are footprints, aren't they?
Hey! Don't throw your booger at me, fool!
Huh?
If your body's in the water,
you can't use the power.
Although it was just a trace amount, it's...
Is it an animal?
Luffy and Chopper... No, Franky?!
Oh, sorry!
If it's a human, he must be a Giant.
Speaking of water, Brook, his torso
may have fallen into the lake.
...a drug!
Nami!
I can't move right now!
Sorry, sorry!
A drug?!
Watch out! They're around!
Maybe. I heard that lake is
actually filled with seawater.
Okay, I understand. There is not much time.
Only select doctors in a few
countries are allowed to use it!
He's still alive here so I don't think
it has become food for sharks yet.
You guys have to take care of the samurai.
--Are those bomb blasts?
--That's from the direction we came from.
Shall we, Scotch?
I knew about it because
Doctrine was using it.
Okay! He didn't notice there
was a cliff. He is so careless!
I'll look into the drug
that the kids were taking.
But we don't know what's in that lake.
Even for its intended
purpose - to cure diseases,
Does it have something to
do with these footprints?
Who is your ship's doctor?
We better pull it out as soon as possible.
it's used sparingly because
it's highly addictive!
There are spikes at the bottom!
He's got to come with me and help
me research it behind Caesar's back.
Yes, we have to hurry.
--Die in vain.
--Get skewered by the Ice Spikes!
I sense something. Two
beast-looking creatures.
I-I have to ask you to... um,
go under the water for me...
These children were taking a
small amount of it everyday
Okay, this is good.
Let's go back! Nami and
the others are in danger!
Armament Hardening!
I'm sorry but I can't walk
right now so, thanks!
We know! You can't swim,
right? What a crappy samurai!
Y-Yeah!
and became chronically addicted.
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
They crave another dose to ease the pain.
I thought you people were pirates!
And I'm a total stranger to you!
Oh no!
If it collapses, the kids are...
D-Don't drop him, Tra-guy!
Why are you helping me so much?!
Sorry! I shouldn't laugh! But...
Why is he doing this to
these little children?!
Luffy! Everybody! Come back!
Super cute!
There's no time!
We have to handle this on our own!
So they can't get out of the lab?!
Good luck, Chopper.
Because I'm responsible for you!
Count on me!
What does your "savior" want to do...
I see. He's a little
trickier than the others.
...with these poor children?!
But when you get your whole body back,
THE BURNING LANDS
you have to fight me! I'll kick your ass!
Hey, stop slandering our
Master or I'll beat you up!
1, 2, 3!
Those two from before!
Do you see anybody?
I...
Chopper! What should we do?!
I accept it!
How many are there? What do they look like?
The kids are collapsing one after another!
1, 2, 3!
Second Gear!
The candy...
Well...
Gum-Gum...
Do you want a candy?
Do you want me to go get it from the lab?
...Jet...
Nobody's out there!
...Pistol!
No!
We can never let them eat that candy again!
No way!
Thank you!
I guess they were ingesting the
drug like that without knowing!
Alright, it's unlocked!
Oh great! Now you're able to say thank you.
Jet...
...Stamp!
1, 2, 3!
Maybe getting frozen makes people nicer.
Straw Hat bro!
They're gone, again!
Let's get the party started.
Are you gonna go get me the candy?
What?
No, I can't! If Chopper says "No," I can't!
Hmm... What is that?
What do they keep in this warehouse?
Fool. We know these mountains
like our own backyard.
He is our doctor. Trust him!
Oh! Those are...
...Brownbeard-san's subordino-centaurs
that we robbed.
There are so many places
that we can hide ourselves!
Why?
--Stay with me! Keep running!
--Get away from the lake!
THE BURNING LANDS
A monster appeared on the other side!
What's that?
It must be around here.
So cool!
We have to tell the Master!
The place that the Master mentioned.
Where has it been hiding
on the island until now?!
I can't see. It's too dark.
Just keep running! It's gonna come after us!
It's a huge building.
Huh, a monster? You guys are monsters.
Is it a warehouse?
It's kind of eerie.
This door is the one, right?
Okay, let me open it.
They're the pirates who robbed us earlier!
Dammit! That's my coat!
What're we gonna do?!
Forget about them! Just run! To the lab!
Where are they?!
What happened?
They got our Boss!
You'll pay for that!
Why?!
Ow, ow, ow...
Oh, I fell asleep.
It's tight! Guys, give me a hand!
What's going on?
Something's going on outside.
I don't know. What was it?
What happened to you, Synd?!
Somebody's come to rescue me, maybe?
I'm scared!
Hey, Brook. They were coming from the
lake that we saw earlier, weren't they?
Law? The Master?
You said you're gonna go get it for me!
No, we're on a snow-capped
mountain so it must be them!
What?! Yes! You got it right!
I'm impressed, Zoro-san! And what about it?
Hey, brown guy! You know
something, don't you?!
You said you're gonna get it!
Well, if in fact that is the lake,
Who is it?! You better say
it or you'll get this!
You said you're gonna go get it for me!!
I don't think there was a mountain
there before, was there?
Beam!
Beam! Beam!
A mountain?
I think I heard something.
Luffy!
Where is this strength coming from?!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
I didn't hear a thing.
Beam! Beam!
Hey, we've been told not to go
anywhere near here, haven't we?
You're not taking the beam seriously!
Synd, stop!
I've never seen Synd get so violent!
It's no use looking for them because
they'll never show themselves!
Is it really okay to open it?
The Master was the one who told us
that and he wants us to open it.
Are you mad?
We don't even know their faces.
You don't trust the Master?
What?
However,
they'll carry out an assassination at
any cost in exchange for their reward.
N-No, that's not what I meant!
Then stop complaining and lend a hand!
As you can tell from the assassins earlier,
All we know about them is their
Caesar-ya wants to get rid of you
guys and White Chase-ya's G-5
footprints are huge and they have low voices.
Oh yeah! There is one
more thing that we know.
What power!
and take back those children.
It's no wonder if he's a Giant!
They're furry, giant, beast-like men.
Until he gets what he wants,
he won't stop attacking.
That strong?!
Why can't I have the candy?!
The Snow Mountain Killers - stalking
out from deep in the snowstorm!
--Synd is not a Giant!
--What?!
He is a former Government scientist,
When we came to this island,
we were all normal-sized.
And we happened to know their
names - Rock and Scotch!
who became a criminal four years ago.
If the fact somebody is here on
this restricted island leaks out,
I thought we had a disease
which makes us grow too big.
People call them the Yeti Cool Brothers!
Smiley is the embodiment of a
chemical weapon explosion...
he will lose this perfect hiding place.
There's nothing wrong
with us other than that!
We really don't know much about them
...that occurred on Punk
Hazard, four years ago.
but they were from a snowy
region and their age is...
There isn't such a disease that'd
turn an ordinary person into a Giant!
That's why he'll try to
kill you all at any cost.
You know a lot!
But nobody knows what they really look like.
A 300 million berry bounty.
Big people are big from the beginning!
They're giant and tough!
A Logia-type Gas-Gas Fruit eater who owns
Those of us who've been here
longer have a bigger body!
And they came here to rescue me!
weapons of mass destruction.
Your names are on their kill list now!
That's who Caesar Clown is.
That means...
...they didn't always have a problem with
the oversecretion of pituitary hormones.
300 million?
Those of you who can't use
Haki, stay away from him.
The candy!
You're Brownbeard, aren't you?
He's not just a scientist.
The candy!
They move so fast even though they're so big.
Your name is also on our kill list.
Those who can use Haki among
us are me and Zoro and Sanji.
These children are...
Oh yeah!
Gum-Gum...
…test subjects!
And you.
It's a dead-end for you!
The candy!
I think that's enough.
What's with that guy?!
...Balloon!
I'm gonna go back to the lab now.
I invented the H2S poison gas bomb.
He's huge but I didn't notice he was here!
Don't lose your mind, Ally!
So what we're gonna do is
kidnap the Master, right?
I want the candy!
Huh? Are you Rock?
It worked so well
It's a waste to use this power only
--I'm Scotch.
--You just made a joke, I think.
defensively just letting the
bullets bounce randomly.
and killed everything on the
island in a matter of seconds!
Yes, that's it.
But why should we kidnap him?
Oh, I probably misheard it.
What does the Master guy want?
That's what Rayleigh said.
He said I should focus on redirecting
Gee, was I scared!
Money? I thought the
Master guy is their boss.
By manipulating such little
children with drugs?
every single one of them
back with twice the force!
The Master asked you to save me, right?
Who else can pay us a ransom?
Then just unchain me and let's
take care of the Straw Hats...
Gum-Gum...
The candy!
...Fire Salute!
Other kids are losing it, too!
We're not gonna do it for
money. Just to raise havoc.
You didn't mishear it.
I'm here to kill you by the Master's request.
--Havoc?
--What do you mean?
No way!
Rock!
He did it!
There's no point to tell you
Listen.
We can't do anything!
what lies ahead before we
even kidnap him successfully.
Oh yeah, and what was that guy's name?
Focus on capturing Caesar Clown for now.
It's his voice!
Nami!
Stop, Franky!
He has been captured by them.
That shit with a beard.
It's not gonna be easy.
Why are you struggling with him more?!
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
--Synd, don't!
--Hey, can I stop him?!
He was known for his stupidity.
Oh yes, Brownbeard!
I'll tell you all the details
of my plan after that. However,
No! Move out of my way, Luffy!
What? Master!
ONE YEAR LATER
Usopp, don't hurt them!
That's him?
when we kidnap Caesar successfully,
My body's hot.
He was easy to manipulate because
he was so dumb, but he's a pain now.
Dammit! I know!
Are they having a falling
out now? Screw them!
things will start moving
whether you like it or not.
Special Attack - Sleep Star!
I don't need him.
Do they believe I purified
the gas all over the island?
There will be no turning back.
Kill him.
Stop!
Just see if you don't!
No way! No one would do
such a wasteful thing!
Icy mountains are filled
with potential weapons.
This is the last chance
for you to reconsider.
I compressed it and turned it into a monster.
That's okay. We're with you.
And there he is!
Hey, I was right! There's smoke!
Then, I will go along with
what you guys want to do.
Smiley!
Watch out! The tip of an
icy mountain is gonna fall!
You need to convince the rest of your crew.
Nami! Chopper! Are you all right?!
Luffy! Franky! Look up!
Yeah, I got it!
This island was once covered with
dead soil where no one could live.
You can't get away from it!
CAESAR CLOWN'S LABORATORY - THE FRONT
Answer my question. You're
Brownbeard, aren't you?
The other one is right there, too!
All right! They are all sleeping now.
People tend to forget tragedies in no time
You bastard! Damn you creature!
Choke on this KYP gas canister that
will make you drunk in a second
but that one has lingered here all along.
and drop dead like your friends!
It was always in my hand!
"Rebar" Smoothie!
So they were all kidnapped as I thought.
Fen Bock of the Gourd!
Get us out of here!
VEGAPUNK'S FORMER THIRD LABORATORY
I want to see my father and my mother!
He did something useful!
"Rope-Tugging" Chappe!
I'm glad that you got here.
Smoker-san! They are former
prisoners as we thought!
You'll be alright. Don't worry.
Luffy.
Just looking a little different.
These kids are going through
such a horrible ordeal...
THE REMAINS OF VEGAPUNK'S
FORMER FIRST AND SECOND LABORATORY
...without knowing anything
and it breaks my heart!
All right! That was great, Franky!
What's going on here?
They said they want to go
home and see their parents!
You are...
Then why did they say none of the
prisoners survived four years ago?!
Be quiet.
We've got to help them!
Hey, enough already!
Luffy! I wanna help them, too!
I'll never let him take these children again.
Third Gear!
I can't believe he was using them as
his test subjects and drugged them.
Alright, let's take them
all to their parents.
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
Fool! It's not that easy! We
have a mountain of problems.
I can't forgive the Master guy!
These are...
Smo-san, what are those people?!
Your new legs.
Okay, then let's just go
and kidnap the Master!
How should I know?!
He's right. Plus, it's just speculation now.
In any case, just hold them back!
He used one of his most daring attack there?!
Yeah, if we're too late,
we can't work with them.
Nothing can be solved until
we see the ringleader.
No!
We're not gonna be late. I have an idea!
Luffy!
We have to put the ship to sea...
The Master guy, huh?
No...
...to make a report!
But Zoro, Sanji, and Brook went
out looking for the samurai so...
Oh no!
What is it?
Sorry, Franky and Chopper!
It's a very good idea!
Shoot! Shoot!
I'll ask Chopper to treat you later!
How is it going?
Wait!
Well, that's okay!
Master! It's all clear around
here today like any other day!
We got their ship!
All right!
I told you. We know these
mountains like our own backyard.
Let's go to the laboratory to see the Master!
Stop the ship!
Good.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Brownbeard, you're such
a great security officer.
You can't catch up with me!
Hurry up! Let's finish them off!
--I'll stay here.
--What?
Help me!
Master, the Transponder Snail is ringing.
I really can't stomach what
the Master guy is doing
S-Smoker-san, how can I turn back?!
You're flattering me!
You don't have to take it.
You're in my way! Stay still, Tashigi!
They probably want to report
they opened the door.
and I wanna kick his ass!
No...
"And something came out."
But I can't leave these kids
here. I have to look after them.
No...
"It attacked our comrades. Help us."
Y-Yeah, h-he's right!
Then, I'll stay here, too!
The door is not open yet?!
They'll just go on like that. Quite annoying.
No!
Hey, Nami! That's not
fair! You're just scared!
Master!!
We don't often have this many visitors here.
The enemy is in the lab!
But it'll be crazy if they go wild again.
We can't just stay out here!
You can stop gathering test subjects now.
It's no good! The door is as
steady as a rock, Smo-san!
Nami!
How annoying! You should
drop dead in a cooler way!
What?
You just won't give up!
But I can reach way farther than you!
I feel miserable!
Let's leave the big ones like this.
If I were in my body, I could easily
force myself into the place!
I feel a little bad about this.
Whoa! He's like a monkey.
We have no choice. They go wild
like heavyweight fighters.
Alright!
And we don't know when they're gonna wake up.
Hello?! Master?! Hello?!
Hey, Scotch!
What should we do about the
body shuffle situation?
There's another one!
Please come in!
Don't shoot too wildly. You
don't wanna hit those brats.
I assume we can't go back to
normal unless the four of us
We're in the Burning Lands! We
opened the door as you said!
Oops. That's not cool.
see Trafalgar together.
Damn! Since it's a huge mountain
range, it'd be a pain if I lose them!
Why bother? Just leave it like it is.
Brownbeard!
No good! The Master is not picking up!
How terrible! They're on the same side!
No way! You gotta make it right!
Look at that. Their captain is back.
It's coming! What is that?!
It came out of the building!
The Master is a warm-hearted savior.
Room.
Let's start with them.
It killed all of our comrades! Just run!
He's...
Oh, you're the free-loader---
Trafalgar Law, aren't you?
I trust you, Master!
Huh? They're pretty big.
--Wh-Which way?!
--Th-This way!
I'm glad to see you here.
--Are they Giants?
--No, they're slightly different.
I was chased by Straw Hat Luffy and...
Your power is very useful!
Was it teleportation?!
Hey! Samurai-san!
You guys, you didn't harm
my friends, did you?!
Room.
Shut up and stay inside the bag.
Where are you?!
What?
We've almost reached the backdoor of the lab.
If only we could find traces
of his wooden clogs.
Caesar will probably be in the
main room with that woman.
So heavy!
My breasts are heavy when I run!
I'll try to draw them out of the room.
I thought you wanted to save that samurai!
I want you to find out about
the drug while we're gone.
Oh? Where did he go?!
Oh no!
How romantic!
But if you can reach the Master that easily
No, fool!
and you're so strong, why don't
you capture the Master yourself?
I don't care if you fall down!
You jerk! Treat Nami-san's
body more carefully!
Then we can take time to
find out about the drug.
Hey, you two! Take a look at this!
Because of a problem I have,
There is a footprint!
I can't do that and that's why
I need help from you guys.
What is that thing?! It's
bigger than a mountain!
A trace of his wooden clogs?
It's nothing like that!
Luffy!
In any case, I just want
you guys to kidnap Caesar.
Then, it must be some centaur's footprint.
You alright?
You bastard! What are you doing?!
I'm sorry! They took Nami with them!
No!
I'll do the rest.
Th-This is...
What?!
Hey, look at that!
He said he wants this one alive.
Wh-What's that?!
The Navy G-5 Vice Admiral Smoker's heart!
--Something's flying toward us!
--It's a big bomb!
A robot with Vegapunk's laser weapon, huh?
Counter Shock.
And kill all the rest.
What a nice gift, Law.
No, it's not!
Okay, let's enjoy every minute of this hunt.
The fight is over.
It's coming! Help me!
In a cool way!
Master!
Cien Fleurs!
Wing!
Since they lost their warship,
they will come to steal our
ship here to make a report.
Wham!
I assume the detachment team must
have stolen the ship by now.
Of course, that's already been taken care of.
What?! He said "Wham"?! Is it a human?!
Thank you!
Let me tell you about my pet.
No! Hey you, give me back my body!
What is that sound?
What about Straw Hat-ya's group?
It's a very rare slime-type creature.
Nami!
THE LABORATORY - THE FRONT AREA
Don't worry about them, either.
Luffy!
We will get rid of them soon
and take back those kids.
Oh, Tra-guy!
Did you save Nami?
We've been ambushed!
Master...
I mean, I know those brats will have an
I've been thinking.
No one...
Hot damn!
urge to come back here even
if we don't do anything.
It's not gonna be that easy, huh?
...can leave this island!
And I came here to talk to you
about something, Straw Hat-ya.
Let's go!
But since Monet told me to be
careful with the Straw Hats,
That was a nice shortcut!
I think you arrived on
this island by accident.
THE LABORATORY - THE BACKDOOR
I sent those two just to make sure.
Master, show yourself!
But there is an important key
lying somewhere on this island
We will kick your ass and kidnap you!
They never miss their target!
How does it feel to be loose after so long,
that can wreak havoc in the New World.
Luffy, that was supposed to be a secret.
The Snow Mountain Killers!
--Oh?
--Law-san, where are you going?
Smiley?!
There are only two ways to
survive in the New World.
Straw Hat!
It's the Straw Hats!
Yeti...
We just ran into the Navy.
...Cool Brothers!
Go, Luffy!
Either by living under the Four Emperors
That fool! Who said anything
about confronting everyone?!
Room.
or going against them.
There are six more.
And I guess you're not a kind of person
who wants to work under someone.
I thought they would be stronger than that.
Let's just finish them all off.
Yeah, I want to stay as a captain.
Then, we have to form an alliance!
Like we took down those three...
What?
We'll do it in a cool way!
An alliance?
If you and I join forces, maybe we can do it.
I don't give a damn.
I'm free to go...
Where are you, Master?!
...wherever I want.
Show yourself!
I have a plan...
...to bring down one of the Four Emperors!
Law declares to defeat the Four Emperors.
In order to get Nami back,
Luffy and crew hurry to the
laboratory to see the Master.
The ultimate weapon that Caesar created...
A battle unfolds between Smoker's G-5 Navy men and Luffy's crew.
Luffy and crew go after the assassins.
Nami and the others can't help but be hesitant by the frightening details...
While its identity is slowly coming to light,
In their absence, Nami and Chopper
stay behind to watch the children,
However, the ingenious trap
set within the snowy mountain,
After the violent clash, just when it seems like the research lab will be breached...
But Luffy's answer surprises not only his crew,
the Straw Hats make their move to capture Caesar.
and the relentless attacks from the Cool Brothers
when suddenly, invisible assassins attack!
but Law, as well.
...Caesar's deadly weapon, Smiley, rains down upon person after person...
However, Luffy's actions cause the
situation to go in an unexpected direction.
By the time Luffy realizes what's going on,
Meanwhile, Caesar was also setting
send Luffy into a dilemma. But then
the two are facing a life-or-death situation.
Law appears and makes an unbelievable move.
...throwing everyone into fear and chaos.
a terrible plan in motion.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Capture M!
The Pirate Alliance's Operation Launches!"
"To Annihilate the Straw Hats!
Legendary Assassins Descend!"
"Save Nami! Luffy's Fight on
the Snow-Capped Mountains!"
"Formed! Luffy and Law's Pirate Alliance!"
"On the Verge of Annihilation!
A Deadly Monster Comes Flying In!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!