All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New
World, the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
They landed on Punk Hazard; an island with
two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After forming an alliance with Trafalgar Law,
Luffy finally encountered Caesar
Clown who rules the island
After surviving a fierce battle,
but was beaten by his mysterious power.
the Straw Hats finally entered the New
World, the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
the Straw Hats finally entered the New
World, the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
My strong soldiers!
After landing on Punk Hazard; an island with
two parts, one burning, the other frozen,
After forming an alliance--
with Trafalgar Law,
Tie these five up!
Luffy finally encountered Caesar Clown
they learned about the hideous experiments
performed by Caesar Clown, the Master,
the Straw Hats learned about the hideous
experiments performed by Caesar Clown, the Master,
Use Sea Prism Stone chains
for the Devil Fruit eaters!
aka the Master who rules
the island. However...
When did you come here?
and headed off to investigate
but as things got going,
they came to form an alliance with the
Heart Pirates led by Trafalgar Law.
Vergo!
they came to form an alliance with the
Heart Pirates led by Trafalgar Law.
Luffy came to form an alliance with
the Heart Pirates led by Trafalgar Law
Just arrived. Luckily, I was at Dressrosa.
You shouldn't underestimate me.
And Luffy finally encountered Caesar!
Do as we discussed.
and is now headed to see
the Master Caesar Clown.
I got a ride in an SAD tanker
that was about to leave.
Yeah. While you're taking Caesar
and that woman somewhere else,
You're a Warlord-sama now, aren't you?
You've done so well.
I'm gonna find out about the drug.
When did you come here?
"Shocking! The True Identity
of the Mystery Man Vergo!"
You shouldn't underestimate me.
And Luffy is now headed to
see the Master Caesar Clown.
I'll never let him take these children again.
Vergo!
I can't believe he was using them as
his test subjects and drugged them.
It's inevitable. This is
Joker's important territory.
You will all experience it!
Who is there?!
THE ICE LANDS--THE LABORATORY
I can't just let those who learn
about his identity walk away.
I can't forgive the Master guy!
The chemical weapon explosion that
happened four years ago on Punk Hazard!
Hey, Tra-guy, who's Joker?
Hey, look at that!
Why are you...
A world of death in which no one can survive!
...here?!
He is a member of the Seven Warlords
authorized by the World Government.
Wh-What's that?!
And you will learn!
--Something's flying toward us!
--It's a big bomb!
Just how powerful my weapon is,
that it can destroy an island!
He is Don Quixote Doflamingo.
You have no mercy.
No, it's not!
It's been years.
And the greatness of the world's best
scientist who created the weapon!
If I had mercy, it wouldn't
make good punishment.
You've grown up.
Vergo... The Navy soldiers of the
G-5 are here on the island now.
"Save the Children! The
Master's Evil Hands Close in!"
Law.
Cien Fleurs!
It's me--Master Caesar Clown!
Since you're their base commander,
Wing!
I think you're gonna be in
trouble if you run into them.
Wham!
"A Samurai Who Can Cut
Fire! Foxfire Kin'emon!"
I got you!
Master, show yourself!
We will kick your ass and kidnap you!
Don't try to give me your advice.
You should know your place.
"An Intense Battle!
Caesar Exercises His True Power!"
Luffy, that was supposed to be a secret.
Also, don't make me repeat myself.
Straw Hat!
PUNK HAZARD ISLAND--THE
MIDDLE LAKE ZORO'S GROUP
Doflamingo...
Go, Luffy!
You have to address me with "san."
That fool! Who said anything
about confronting everyone?!
Is that a Slime?
Who is that?
Do you really think that he had no idea?
Didn't you see him at the Navy Headquarters?
Oh, scary!
A Slime?
At the Navy Headquarters?
Yes. I was once reading a
book that had a monster...
THE NEW WORLD--AN ISLAND
We don't trust Caesar, either.
...that looks exactly like
this one called a "Slime."
Oh yeah!
"On the Verge of Annihilation!
A Deadly Monster Comes Flying In!"
That's why he was being careful
and sent an undercover agent.
Hey, look! Soldiers of the G-5.
I couldn't stop reading it.
Hey, you, gator guy!
Getting drunk and partying in the
daytime? They're so obnoxious!
The Slime liked to attack women
You turned me down and now, you
wanna team up with Whitebeard?
Monet is that agent.
CAESAR'S LABORATORY - THE FRONT DOOR
and its body fluids would only
melt what the women were wearing!
You're a Warlord-sama now, aren't you?
SLIMY, SLIMY
It makes me jealous.
Do you have a problem?!
It was such a dirty monster!
You've done so well.
This island is safe from pirates
who are worth over 100 million
That bird guy!
NO!!
You better not take him lightly.
What?! That's too convenient!
When did you come here?
That bastard! Did he just say he will
kick our Master's ass and kidnap him?!
because we obnoxious soldiers are
Vergo!
He's right.
C-Can I borrow that book sometime?!
going around like this for you
people, don't you think so?!
And they say that Doflamingo
Screw it! Take the Straw Hats down!
Me, too!
Just arrived. Luckily, I was at Dressrosa.
Fools! Look carefully.
Huh?!
We deserve to take a little break, don't we?
attacked Moria after the War of the Best!
Pinky promise! Huh?
I don't know if it melts your clothes
but you might not wanna touch it.
I got a ride in an SAD tanker
that was about to leave.
He attacked Moria?
W-Well...
Strong...
...Right!
It was the right move.
The fish are dying from the fluid
that it dropped into the lake.
THE REMAINS OF THE FIRST AND SECOND
LABORATORY NAMI AND USOPP'S GROUP
The right move?!
THE NAVY "G-5" UNIT 06
COMMODORE YARISUGI
It's good! Too good!
Did I cause any harm to you guys?!
It's like it's made of toxins.
Owner, give me a thousand of these!
No but if you did, you'd be dead by now.
If nothing is done, the poison
will spread all over the lake.
W-We don't have that many in stock!
What?! Why?! It's too good!
Poison?
Then, samurai-san's torso will...
You can't fool grown-ups, Law.
Smoker-san, what should we do?
Navy people!
Master!
Please! Search for our children!
Obviously, we have to capture the Straw Hats.
In that case, I should just finish you!
What are you talking about?
Master!
Catch the Straw Hats!
Did you forget?!
Our children went missing three years ago!
Oh, I forgot to mention.
D-Don't tell me you're going in, Sanji-san?!
Cien Fleurs!
Do I have a choice? It's my personal mission!
You've got to say it properly.
Please! Just one more time!
They were just playing in
the neighborhood and then,
So...
Clutch!
I'm Sanji, I'm a man! I've got to do it!
...you're the one who
kidnapped these children?!
they got involved in an accident at sea?!
It doesn't make any sense!
Why is he here?
Sanji-san!
I'm begging you! For one last time!
Luffy and the others couldn't meet him?
Do something about the Slimes behind you.
Please search for them!
CAESAR'S LABORATORY - THE BACKDOOR
What? Behind me?
Can we talk to the officer
named Captain Tashigi?!
It's Vergo-san to you.
How could you do such a horrible thing?
Copies of the Slime?!
When did they get here?!
What should we do?
I heard she listens
empathetically to the people!
Just let it be.
Let's go inside.
Horrible?
Sorry, Nami-san.
Why did you take them away?
The children are suffering!
Do you have a key?
--I'm begging you! Let us talk to Captain Tashigi!
--Please! One more time!
IN FRONT OF THE LABORATORY LUFFY'S GROUP
I'm better at swimming than anyone else.
Oh, you can use teleportation, huh?
I'll try to get out of the water before
it causes damage to your beautiful body!
What?!
Hey, no! Don't, Nami!
Room.
You're making them suffer!
Cut it out!
Please be careful!
Whoa-whoa,
Law said he's a Logia-type Devil Fruit
eater with a 300 million berry bounty!
He's risking his life for me
How insulting! We're Navy
soldiers of the G-5, too!
Do as we discussed.
and going into the poisonous lake!
What just happened?
Yeah. While you're taking Caesar
and that woman somewhere else,
What did you give to such small children?!
First of all, you fools
doubt the Navy's report,
I have no idea.
Th-The water is ice-cold!
What should we do?
They said they want to go home!
I'm gonna find out about the drug.
and also complain about us who
are in charge of this area?!
I'm sure their parents are looking for them!
Where is his torso?
Tashigi-chan!
Too much complaining, don't you think?!
We will get them out of here at any cost!
The Slimes are coming toward us!
It's Vice Admiral Smoker!
I-It's not like that!
Weapons Left!
What should we do about them?
It's no use! Too useless!
You have to accept it
already! Too much evidence!
Yeah, what should we do?
Where are the children who wanna go home?
I can't believe I saw him
get taken down twice a day.
Your children died in an accident!
Master!
Three of the Straw Hats got beaten, too!
We made it here but where's the Master?
Hey!
Commodore, that's a bit yarisugi (too much).
Was it Conqueror's Haki?!
--Master!
--Hey, wait!
Just Monet in the room.
I don't think he's out here.
No way! There can't be that much
difference in their strength!
I asked Vice Admiral Vergo,
the head of the G-5,
Then where is he?
Then what was it?! He beat all of
them without even touching them!
This is the chance.
about this too many times--a thousand times!
Probably in the lab.
The Master is not here.
And we investigated ten thousand times!
Okay, that big door must be the entrance.
Don't go! Do you wanna go back to the lab?!
Yeah? Where did he go?
I don't know.
But...
Being such a hideous person, he's
probably watching the fight outside.
Let's go.
If you're gonna carry on about this,
I will kill you fools for interfering with us
That serves you right, Navy!
That was what our savior
- Master is capable of!
and burn down your town!
Straw Hat Luffy!
I've seen pretty much everything
what I wanted to see on the island.
Oh, Smokey!
Master! Master! Master! Master!
Commodore, that's yarisugi (too much)!
Get out of my way!
I'm thinking about leaving here soon.
Usopp!
Master! Master! Master!
You wanna talk to Tashigi-chan?
Oh, we'll miss you.
Don't push your luck too much!
There is something I could
use your help with though.
I mean, it'd be nice if she were
working under me! Too nice!
My strong soldiers!
Candy...
What?
Tie these five up!
THE REMAINS OF THE FIRST
AND SECOND LABORATORY
Master, give me the candy!
Could you come with me?
Use Sea Prism Stone chains
for the Devil Fruit eaters!
Imagining too much!
Are you asking me out? How sweet!
But unfortunately,
Leave the Navy soldiers here
and get inside the laboratory.
she works for Unit 01 as Vice
Admiral Smoker's right-hand girl.
Unchain me!
You're such an unfriendly person. What is it?
It's dangerous out here.
Too right-handy!
Big brothers, unchain me!
You'll see.
That's it. Come back to me, children.
Withdrawal symptoms again!
What should we do?!
Alright. I was bored anyway.
Something strange is raining
down but don't worry.
Wait, you all!
We should just let them sleep
it off! I'll use it again!
She's too busy to deal with you fools
You shouldn't go back to him!
Is that the bird woman that
Usopp was talking about?
I'll protect this place where you belong!
who are obsessed with an
incident from three years ago!
Special Attack - Sleep Star!
Don't you wanna go home?!
Yes, Master!
Too busy!
Don't touch me!
Looks like the Cool Brothers blew it.
What?!
Shitheads!
Cockroach!
That's too much!
CAESAR'S LABORATORY--THE FRONT DOOR
LUFFY'S GROUP
S-Straw Hat caught the Master!
But it can't be helped.
They're not gonna listen to us!
Way to go, Luffy!
Fighting against Straw Hat and Law
must've been too much for them.
Dammit! That bastard!
Let me go!!
I wonder if it's true that Vice
Admiral Vergo knows about this.
Straw Hat!
Go away, cockroach!
Let go of me, you fool!
No way! Sleep Star didn't work?!
He saved this island from pirates once.
No!
THE MIDDLE LAKE - ZORO'S GROUP
That's what Haki can do? I can't
believe Luffy can do that.
What?! What should we do now?!
I couldn't believe that he was
part of that rough group, the G-5,
He's grabbing a Logia eater!
Nami!
--You alright?!
--Y-Yeah.
because he was such a gentleman!
Straw Hat! Stay away from the Master!
You brat, don't push your luck!
He thinks that it was an accident, too?!
No, Usopp!
Let's save the Master!
Oh no!
Let go of me!
I won't let you guys do that!
We have no choice but to stop them by force!
He must be hallucinating!
He called you a "cockroach"!
Clutch!
They are still alive!
Outta my way!
But...
Since Luffy became so strong, I
bet he can easily beat that guy!
They're victims!
Gross!
Our children are still alive.
We don't know that yet.
Alright, Brook. Convince them.
It's not their fault!
What?
They fell asleep at last.
Unchain me!
That's impossible!
With Armament Haki,
Somewhere in this world!
it's possible to strike Logia eaters
who you can't even touch normally.
What kind of negotiation skill is
going to work for these monsters?!
But it didn't work as well as before.
PUNK HAZARD ISLAND
It's painful!
Yeah, we're gonna have a problem
next time they wake up.
THE REMAINS OF THE FIRST AND SECOND
LABORATORY NAMI AND USOPP'S GROUP
However, unlike the sea or Sea Prism Stone,
They're merging into one another!
But we have to do something
before they beat us!
it doesn't drain their powers.
Boy, they're merging into one
another and getting bigger.
My head is gonna explode!
We don't really know the extent
of the Gas-Gas Fruit's power.
Usopp, make them fall asleep already!
Straw Hat Luffy! What are
you up to on this island?!
Focus that anger at...
I'm doing it but it's not
gonna work that many times!
I-I-It got bigger!
...that jerk!
Smokey! I'm glad that you're okay!
Unchain me, brothers!
Take these off!
I was worried because they
were beating you up before!
Unchain me!
I guess the withdrawal
symptoms are way too painful!
Don't monkey around with me!
Then, what should we do?!
Do I have a choice? It's my personal mission!
What? You have a stomachache?
Is it constipation?
I'm Sanji, I'm a man! I've got to do it!
Just do everything we can!
I'm counting on you, Sanji!
I did it!
Sanji-san!
I'm Nami!
Do something about the Slimes behind you.
Oh, that's right!
Don't get carried away!
Damn, you look so dependable on the outside!
Please be careful!
What happened, Smokey? You got weaker.
I'm sorry!
Armament Hardening!
Brothers!
N-No, I'm...
--No way!
--They broke the chains?!
Candy... Give me the candy!
Gum-Gum...
...Bell!
Candy! Candy!
On top of that, you sound strange today.
Gas Robe!
My head hurts!
What a pain in the ass! That worthless chef!
Amazing!
Hey hey, please.
You became so powerful!
I can't stand it!
Don't get your ass kicked by him...
The smoke!
Oh, it's coming!
The candy will stop this pain!
That bastard!
Damn! Gas Robe!
...when you're in my body!
Don't... Don't... Don't attack me!
Candy!
Candy...
It's big, it's big!
What is this?
Oh no, you better not do that!
I can't shake it off!
Candy! Candy! Candy!
Master...
Whoa, don't! Help me!
Luffy, hold your breath!
The guy who got it is...
Candy...
Oh, that weapon!
--Master...
--Give me...
You're back out at sea, huh? Straw Hat!
I'm begging you!
Shit! It's poison gas!
That gas bastard! I'll show him!
But I won't let you do whatever you want!
Why can't you give it to me?!
Give me the candy!
This should work against gas!
Fool! It's no use doing that!
They're coming!
Special Attack!
Can I... Can I attack them
now?! They're like monsters!
Once you get wrapped up in the Gas Robe,
You did it!
Fire Bird Star!
you can't get away from
it no matter what you do!
I knew you could do it, Zoro-san!
No! Don't be ridiculous, they're just kids!
Kids, move aside!
It's gas! Run!
I've had enough!
How much longer can you hold your breath?!
But we can't just run around like this!
Just breathe deeply
I-I-It's poison gas!
I got hit.
and drop dead!
My eyes, my eyes!
--Luffy!
--Dammit!
Oh, I don't have eyes.
It's tipped with Sea Prism Stone.
What?!
After countless experiments,
I finally discovered the deadliest gas!
The girl with the glasses
became this strong, huh?
Hey, what's your problem?!
Her name was...
Did you think I would catch fire and explode?
You jelly-ish body entity!
Now, suffer and die!
You knew my powers are gas-based, didn't you?
Poison gas, again!
But it's too bad. I put the fire
out before it even touched me.
What should we do, Zoro-san?!
It's poison gas!
I'm Smoker!
Master!
What?!
I have front row seats!
I did the same thing before!
Are you okay, children?
Poison gas is not the only
kind of gas, you see.
Learn from observation, skeleton!
Luffy, I think Law did it to them, too.
I thought you were just unlucky.
Let's go back to the laboratory!
What? Ah, the "shuffle" thing. I see.
The air all around us is gas, too!
It's dangerous here.
We're surrounded.
Which means I can manipulate
the air within a certain area.
Is he going crazy?!
That's why that one was weak.
It's the candy!
He's sucking the Master's
poison gas up voluntarily!
This is not good.
Master!
So this one is...
--He can manipulate...
--...The air?
Master! Master! Master!
--He inhaled it all!
--He'll be dead soon!
You're...
I've never seen an idiot like that!
...Smokey?!
If I remove the oxygen, fire can't burn.
Master?
And you people can't even breathe!
What's so funny?!
Go to hell!
It's cold!
Where is the samurai's torso?
Master?
Fight me, Straw Hat.
Alright. Let's use it!
THE MIDDLE LAKE
Second Gear!
What?!
Observation Haki!
That makes it more exciting!
The Slime got mad!
Like this!
Poisons don't work so well
against me now, I guess.
Why, all of a sudden?
We have nowhere to go now!
Probably because those
small Slimes were blown up.
Thanks to Magellan.
Strong...
Oh yeah, they're jellies!
...Right!
Magellan?! The venomous
fool from Impel Down?!
Why don't you eat and digest them?
They were like a parent and its children?
No way!
But I had no choice.
Usopp!
Could you stop talking to me like a bully?!
I'm not like that pathetic Paramecia eater!
It'll take forever to beat all of them up.
Black Ball!
I'm like 70 years older than you!
Gum-Gum...
I'm sorry, grandpa!
Let's break the door and
get into the lab at once!
...Jet Mace!
Storm Cloud...
He's transforming!
Who did you call "grandpa"?!
I'm still a lively skeleton...
Here we go! Franky...
What's the matter?!
Master!
What is that?!
Samurai-san?! T-T-Take it easy!
Master...
Yeah!
Too fast!
So cold!
How could he do that to our Master?!
Sorry, Nami-san.
I'll kill him!
C-Candy...
Attack Straw Hat!
Candy...
Yeah!
Let's finish this some other time!
Could this be the Slime's toxin?!
Hurry...
What?!
What? Is it a frog?
It's not worth fighting when you
can't use all of your strength!
Stay out of it, weaklings!
Whoa-whoa, I hope his torso
is not engulfed by it!
Looks like a lizard to me.
W-Weaklings?
Don't get...
...saucy with me!
Were you wondering if
Straw Hat didn't meet me?
Bye, Smokey!
...Radical Beam!
I've been using Observation
Haki for quite a while
Well, he did.
Did he call us "weaklings"?
Straw Hat and two others.
but maybe the torso's getting weaker.
Or did we hear him wrong?
I can't distinguish its life
force from that of the fish!
I made them suffocate!
Run!
A shark?
He made a hole on the door!
How strong are they?!
That fool!
Was it a laser beam?
Hey!
I'll show him my Gas-Gas Fruit power!
Luffy, Robin, I broke the door!
Candy!
No way!
--Master! Candy!
--Candy... Candy... Candy...
Charge!
--Candy! Candy!
--Hurry!
Armament Hardening!
He can make as many copies
of himself as he wants?!
You did it already, Franky?!
--Master!
--Candy!
Gum-Gum...
No, it looks like the one on
the other side is shrinking.
Come on!
...Gatling!
Smo-yan!
A-Are you alright?
It means that one will disappear in the end?
Give me it! Give me it!
Gastanet!
Hey, what's the matter?! What's going on?!
Something strange is flying toward us!
There!
Maybe he's flinging pieces of
himself over to cross the lake!
What is it?
Children.
What?
Wait, you shithead! Don't mess with me!
I'm only giving it to the good
children who go back to the lab!
Good children only?
We don't want that monster
to run wild on this side!
That's right!
You're right! If we cut it, it spews
gas. If we burn it, it explodes.
That's...
What?
Yes, yes! I'll be good!
Stop chewing on it, shark!
And it's way bigger than
the ones from before!
Then just wait a little bit longer, can you?
I-I-It doesn't hurt at all! It itches!
Luffy!
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
The lab could be in danger, too!
Let's go back! Master!
That's our Master!
What's wrong with him?!
What? Then, we'd better hurry!
Now, I'm gonna finish you off!
Okay, okay! Well, before we do...
Is he bluffing?
Momonosuke!
Smilies, wake up!
What are you guys gonna
do?! I'm going to the lab!
That hurts... Not really!
Kill these devils who took you away
Smilies?
Then we gotta go, too! Idiot!
Maybe something happened to Sanji-san?!
and tried to worsen your pain!
Who're you calling "idiot"?!
You fool, let it go!
You're such a pain!
If you get separated from
Kin'emon and wander off,
Kill them...
What?! All of a sudden, they're moving...
we have to look for you all over the island!
Smilies, cling onto Straw Hat!
You can't fight now, Zoro-san, Sanji-san!
Now!
Jump!
Crush their skulls with that giant pipe!
Joue Shoot!
I want to see his swordplay, too!
Why are they listening to the Master?!
Let's go to the lab!
Uh-huh...
Luffy, watch out! They'll explode!
Alright, I got the last piece safely!
Don't...
I can't think clearly...
The samurai puzzle will be complete!
You awake?
I gotta go back now!
Luffy!
What are you doing here?
Go away!
I was gonna ask you the same thing.
The ship!
It's gonna close up!
Gastanet!
What is that?
It looks like we're all captured.
Luffy! Franky! Wait!
Oh, we're in a cell?!
Dammit!
When did that happen?
Oh, you're here, too, Smokey!
What is it?! It's moving!
Let me handle it!
Luffy!
It's no use. That's Sea Prism Stone chain.
You're giving me the creeps!
The poison got this far!
Shit! It's all around me now!
You're awake, huh?
What is she?
Can I do it with Nami-san's strength?
It's gonna put a strain on her body again...
You all look better than I thought.
Wh-What is this?!
What?! You're...
It's poison gas! Back off!
This is not good!
You're the head of the G-5!
Why the hell are you here?!
The whole lake is turning
to the color of the poison!
When it got cut and shot,
it spewed out poison gas!
Sanji-san, hurry up!
Put on your gas mask!
Vergo!
Run!
Blue Walk!
Caesar!
Don't close up! Don't
close up! Don't close up!
Huh?! What the hell is that?!
Don't close up!
Is it some kind of living thing?
I have no idea. What is that?
Sanji-san!
Give us back Smo-yan, Caesar!
Oh, he got it!
Say it! What is that?
CAESAR'S LABORATORY - THE FRONT
I-I don't know! I've never seen such a thing!
Give us back Tashigi-chan!
He really did it!
It fell from the sky, didn't it?
--Browncolor?!
--No, Brownbeard!
Straw Hat's gone!
Straw Hats!
Yeah, but it's moving!
I came to my senses!
That was a huge explosion! I don't
think there is even a hair left!
It's disgusting!
All clear!
He wasn't strong enough to fight against
our Master, the savior, in the first place!
Alright, close the shutters!
Don't let the Navy soldiers in at any cost!
I don't remember this one.
Is it alive?
No... Luffy!
Oh, look!
Oh yes! You're my dutiful
lackey - Brownbeard!
As soon as everybody gets
in, activate it immediately!
What can I say?!
They merge into one another...
You've got to be kidding!
...And get bigger!
You bastard! Did you even forget who I was?!
I have never felt so happy
to just have my own body!
I'm the greatest scientist in the
world, eater of the Gas-Gas Fruit!
What?!
You shouldn't have made me mad!
Of course not!
What?!
What happened to you?
I can just kill it by
pushing it into the river!
Wh-What is it?!
Master! Master!
Your whole body is charred
and you look terrible.
THE SAMURAI FROM THE WANO
KINGDOM FOXFIRE KIN'EMON
Hey, don't do it!
Master! Master! Master...
Oh, I didn't know you were so tall!
That's because you ordered them to kill me!
You're as tall as I am.
Wh-What the hell is that?!
Oh yes! Excuse me for not
introducing myself sooner!
They're closing the entrance!
You didn't know who you were messing with!
--Poison gas again!
--Pull him out!
My name is Kin'emon!
I was born in Kuri, Wano Kingdom!
1, 2, 3!
Oh, that was close!
--Hey...
--I-It's...
Just do it already! I'm
gonna freeze to death!
I remember now!
What?!
Dammit! It was too late!
You're Brownbeard, aren't you?
Ow! Ow! It touched my skin!
Wipe it off! Somebody!
Yes! I'm sorry!
Open it! Assholes!
Your name is also on our kill list.
Poof!
Let me handle this!
Hey, get me a piece of cloth!
We shouldn't touch it as I thought!
He was easy to manipulate because
he was so dumb but he's a pain now.
What?!
It's still cold.
--What should we do?
--I don't know!
The coat will disappear once
he takes it off, right?
I don't need him.--
Back off, you guys!
Funny-eyebrow man, what is
your honorable name, sir?
Kill him.
Gum-Gum...
The shutter is too thick!
It's as solid as rock!
The Cool Brothers, huh?
It doesn't look like it's resistant to fire!
...Jet Stamp!
Even a bazooka doesn't work?!
I'm Sanji!
What about the back entrance?!
Cut the "sir" crap!
Let's just burn it!
That's how you got charred.
It's all closed! The shutters
were down everywhere!
Now you have your whole body back
so you've changed your attitude!
Take this!
Damn, that gas bastard!
I trusted you.
But you were insulting me so much earlier
M-Master!
Hey, looks like we've been trapped, huh?
There is no living thing
that isn't afraid of fire!
hiding behind the fact you were disabled!
Don't be so angry.
That was a big explosion.
You're smart!
I hope you're not forgetting what you said!
Don't be ridiculous!
You're still alive after getting
attacked by the Cool Brothers.
Burn it up!
That fool! Did he avoid the
explosion? How fast can he move?!
Because, although those creepy
jellies stopped falling suddenly,
You people are pirates?!
You're very lucky!
See, it's weak against fire!
That serves you right!
What a relief.
No wonder you people are barbaric!
Shut up!
if you take a good look, they're merging
into one another and getting bigger!
--S-Straw Hat?!
--Is he invincible?
I don't like pirates! You make me sick!
--Clearly, it's suffering!
--It's starting to burn!
Caesar!
All right!
How dare you do that to our Master?!
Don't irritate me!
Move out of my way!
We can't steal another ship! All
the paths have been cut off!
Why don't you just ask me to find your body?!
Take it! Take it! Take it! Take it! Take it!
Hey, children, it's dangerous here!
They took our Transponder Snails
away so we can't make a call!
I don't wanna owe anything to pirates!
Okay, I really got you this time!
Get on board the Flying Gas Balloon outside.
What should we do?!
I wouldn't ask you even if it kills me!
Now, I'm not even capable of
fighting back if someone hits me
Master!
Let's get away from here!
Robin! Franky! Is there anything
that I can put him in?
Yeah!
so you can carry me if you want to.
All the shutters are closed!
Wait, everybody! Don't go!
He's a Logia eater so
tying him up won't do it.
Okay.
Clank.
Take it! Take it!
Isn't there a barrel or something?
Sounds like they're moving
ahead with preparations.
Caesar!
Whoa-whoa, hold on, Straw Hat!
Poor Navy soldiers.
We, the Navy G-5, are taking him into
custody and putting you guys under arrest!
I don't care that you fooled me.
What is Caesar up to?
I will never forget!
Well, I don't know exactly
Fools, be ready for it!
Ever!
I don't care about myself anymore.
but he woke his pet Smiley up so...
Smoker-san, Straw Hat and
his crew caught Caesar!
I will never forget your kindness
for the rest of my life!
But I want my crew back!
Dammit, those fools!
...I think he's planning
to do a big experiment.
I appreciate everything!
I'm not gonna let them go
through hell like I did!
Smoker-san!
And please forgive me for
having doubts about you all...
Let's go, guys!
Looks like it's going to
be a very dangerous one.
Follow Smo-yan and Captain-chan!
Yeah!
By the way, Vergo,
...until I got my torso back!
You can't escape, Straw Hat!
What?!
You guys!
did you eat a hamburger this morning?
I'm begging you! I'm begging you!
Idiot! You don't have a crew anymore!
I'm begging you!
How did you know? It's my favorite.
I'm begging you...
There is a piece of it still
stuck beside your mouth.
Stop it, fool! Lift your head up!
You and all of your crew
became my subordinates!
Men shouldn't kneel on
the ground that easily!
Hey, what just happened?
I would like to see the
experiment before I go.
Stop acting like a captain!
But if you, sir, weren't there, I probably...
I don't know! I've never
seen something like that!
You're just a shitty pirate who
got beaten in the New World!
When we touch it, it spews poison
and when we burn it, it explodes!
Everyone outside will die?
Hey, Nami! Let's go after the kids!
Probably. But you will be safe in here.
Um, I'm sorry to interrupt
you but, Sanji-san...
We don't even know if it's alive
or not in the first place.
Okay!
They will keep following me
thinking I'm their savior!
Hey, Vergo!
Who cares. It's gone now.
Looks like we're in big trouble.
Straw Hat?
They're all Navy soldiers of the G-5 outside!
Oh yeah, you're right.
They're too dumb to notice.
That's not all.
Your subordinates!
Look. You see?
They don't know that I kept them
alive because they're my guinea pigs!
It killed those Navy soldiers who
stole the ship and sailed out as well!
Are you gonna leave them to die?!
Luffy?
Yeah, I think so.
You bastard!
For us, that was...
What did he just say?!
What?
Anyway,
I can't believe there are
such big names in one cell.
THE THIRD LABORATORY
I like the view.
It brings back memories.
It's here!
Gastanet!
To see you two in the same cell.
Oh yeah, Smokey and I got caught
by you and the others at Alabasta!
It fell from the sky again!
--That's like the one from before.
--How many are there?
--Brownbeard!
--What happened?!
Shut up, you fools!
You people can never read the atmosphere!
Smoker-san, I don't know what to
do with this feeling right now!
You shouldn't underestimate me.
Is it some kind of living thing?
I don't know. I've never seen such a thing.
Gastanet!
You were right and this is
the worst-case scenario.
Me, too.
I'm so stunned - my eyes
popped out of my head.
Those news articles were false...
The drug...
PUNK HAZARD - THE MIDDLE LAKE
If only I could find out
how he made the drug...
...meaning somebody in the G-5 covered
up those child abduction cases.
But I don't have eyes in the first place.
They're so persistent!
How far is the lab?
So Caesar abducted those kids and...
Quite a strange thing...
Is that...
...Vergo covered it up as accidents at sea.
...Doing quite strange things.
Luffy!
The one that was on the other side
made it completely to this side now!
Oh no!
Of all others, the head of
the base was a double agent.
Wow! It's really flying up high!
Which means this one is the
last piece of him, doesn't it?
Great! It's a book about drugs!
That's characteristic of G-5 in a
way but it's a dishonor to the Navy!
Robin! I'll draw their attention to me!
Now I gotta look for sedatives.
Isn't it coming toward us?
You go and save Luffy!
It merged with a smaller one?
How dare you?!
Be careful! That guy's really tough!
What? Is he a bad person?
What did you do to Luffy?!
It seems like he is.
It's getting bigger and bigger!
No wonder you didn't notice it.
Get out of my way!
Just keep running to the lab!
Strong...
It's not like Vergo was selling the Navy out.
What is this?!
Right!
Wait for me!
Disgusting!
Momonosuke!
You're next!
Franky Radical...
He was a pirate originally.
Master, the airship is ready.
--Open it!
--Give us back Captain-chan!
...Beam!
Wing!
A pirate... You were?!
Okay.
Give us back Smo-yan!
That's right.
CAESAR CLOWN'S LABORATORY - THE FRONT
Before he made his name, he
joined the Navy by Joker's order
Then let's go pick them up.
Luffy!
It's starting to move!
It's about time for them to have these.
and spent fifteen years climbing
up the ranks from the very bottom.
Put Straw Hat and the others in a
cage and carry it to my chambers.
It's raining down!
Robin!
There is no Navy soldier who is more
reliable and convenient for Joker than him.
She passed out all of a sudden!
Yes, Master!
What happened to her?!
They're all heading in the same direction.
Run! Don't ever touch it!
Vergo had been working for
Joker from the very start!
Everyone, get out of here now!
Where are they going?
We have nowhere to run now!
Smoker-san, it's too dangerous here!
No way!
CAESAR'S RESEARCH ROOM
Joker is a name of an underworld
broker if I'm correct.
Let's take cover!
Tashigi!
Yeah.
Hey, guys! Didn't I tell you
to do something about them?!
I feel so pathetic! I can't believe I
didn't smell this rat so close to me!
I found out the formula of the
drug and I found sedatives.
It can't be helped because
we couldn't do anything.
Don't be so negative.
Captain-chan!
That's right.
Good boy! I'm sorry that I
locked you up for three years!
Why don't you just praise the rat for
eluding the eyes of the great "White Chase,"
Now I have to find a way to
rescue-- Luffy and the others.
Don't be such children, you idiots!
Robin, are you alright?!
I can't cause any damage to Nami-san's body!
Easy...--
Robin, stay with me!
Smoker-kun.
Master!
Easy...--
From the day that you transferred from the
headquarters, I was on the highest alert.
This body...
Luffy!
Why are you here?! It's dangerous out here!
Th-This body, I have to...
You bastard!
You're not gonna return it, are you?
I'm so happy that now I can
free myself from that stress.
Strong...
Wh-Who was that?
Of course not!
Ri...
Why don't we burn them down?
Anyway, you blabbed out so much, Law.
I knew it. So you're Caesar
Clown, aren't you?!
Can I have the candy?
What?
People call me Foxfire Kin'emon.
Didn't I punish you enough?
Where did the Master go?
You are...
...the Master?!
Master...
I can burn and slice an enemy with my sword.
But that's okay.
Hey, Master!
Damn! What's going on here?!
Let me burn them down and
clear the way to escape!
Yes, indeed!
You said that I'd be in trouble in
case I ran into the G-5 soldiers
Where are you?
Everyone from the Straw Hat
Pirates and the Navy G-5!
You can burn and slice an enemy?
This is Caesar. Are you there, Monet?
but that's not true.
Behold! The greatest scientist in the world!
It sounds like magic!
Yes.
I have been taming them for a long time
- I don't think they would suspect me.
I retrieved the children safely.
Is Smiley's food ready?
Master Caesar Clown!
Even if they find out about
my background like this,
Everything you ordered me
to do is prepared, Master.
I know what to do.
The Navy soldiers are in
front of the closed shutters.
You know what I mean, don't you?
Just wait a few moments.
And we can transfer the Straw Hats anytime.
I have them all now!
Since he's weak to water,
Vice Admiral Smoker, Captain Tashigi.
The Video Transponder Snails
are on standby outside.
he's flinging pieces of himself
over little by little...
So, when Smiley gets there,
...in order to cross the lake!
You two will die here
we can start broadcasting the fun experiment?
so you can keep your mouths shut forever.
Yes.
From the Burning Lands...
And I'll let Caesar handle
those soldiers outside.
Great. Connect me to all the receivers.
...to the Ice Lands!
When all of his pieces reach this side,
It's inevitable. This is
Joker's important territory.
Okay.
I can't just let those who learn
about his identity walk away.
you will all experience it!
He cut the fire!
Don't worry. I will process it
as an accident like I always did.
The chemical weapon explosion that
happened four years ago on Punk Hazard!
To all unlawful "brokers" wherever you are.
Now I cleared the way.
CAESAR'S LABORATORY LAW'S GROUP
I'm sorry to contact you on such short notice
I'm coming for you, Momonosuke!
Vergo!
Law?
Huh?! I'm still alive!
but you all are very lucky to see this!
A world of death in which no one can survive!
Hey, Tra-guy, who's Joker?
Who is it?
I thought we were engulfed by
the fire from the explosion!
What's wrong?
What you're about to witness is the
deployment of a poison gas weapon.
Oh no. You look like you're in pain.
I added a new feature to the
one from four years ago.
K-K-Kin'emon-san? What just happened?
I was working for him, too, once.
It's something those scum from the
Government-- can only dream of creating.
And you will learn!
Huh?
I just cut the explosion.
Just how powerful my weapon is,
that it can destroy an island!
That's why I knew Vergo.
The explosion?!
Today, we have uninvited
guests here on our island.
Joker is just his alias
as an underground broker.
And the greatness of the world's best
scientist who created the weapon!
My Foxfire Style
allows me to cut something
with fire and then cut flames.
Who is there?!
His true identity?  He's a
man that you know very well.
That's why I decided to
perform the experiment.
There is no flame that I can't cut!
It's me - Master Caesar Clown!
What do you mean?
One of the seven most notorious pirates.
Invasion, war, domination.--
It's me.
Now I'm going to go to the
laboratory to save Momonosuke!
He is a member of the Seven Warlords
authorized by the World Government.
It has various uses.
Why are you...
If it appeals to you,
If you'll excuse me!
let's talk business.
...here?!
Give us back Captain-chan!
Wait!
He is Don Quixote Doflamingo.
Are you interested in a
weapon of mass destruction?
I'm intrigued by a samurai's fight.
It's been years.
No.
I'll go with you to rescue your son!
I got you!
You've grown up.
But...
What?!
...I'd lose nothing by
learning about it, right?
Law.
A mysterious man suddenly appears
and hurts Law with his immense power.
Luffy and Caesar Clown have an intense battle
Sanji manages to make it out
of the poisonous lake safely,
An agreement has been made between Law and Caesar.
The revelation of the name, Doflamingo,
one of the Seven Warlords, causes quite the stir.
but there's little time to rejoice.
As that secret comes to light...
where neither side is willing to yield.
They end up surrounded by Smileys,
His identity causes quite the shock,
With the children in tow, Nami and
the others are already at a disadvantage,
At the end of the fierce battle,
...Zoro and gang, fleeing from Smiley, come upon a large object.
and are unable to escape from this crisis.
Luffy believes that he has Caesar, but then
and the identity of the powerful
enemy that stands behind
and are put in an even bigger life-or-death situation
It's in this hopeless situation,
where the samurai reveals his true power.
It is nothing less than an indication of the beginning of Caesar's fearsome plan!
the fearsome power of the
Gas Gas Fruit is revealed.
due to the Gas Gas Fruit's fearsome power.
Caesar and the mysterious
man finally comes to light!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An Intense Battle!
Caesar Exercises His True Power!"
"A Samurai Who Can Cut Fire!
Foxfire Kin'emon!"
"Shaking Up the New World!
Caesar's Horrendous Experiment!"
"Save the Children!
The Master's Evil Hands Close in!"
"Shocking! The True Identity
of the Mystery Man Vergo!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!