All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New
World, the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
After landing on Punk Hazard; an island with
two parts, one burning, the other frozen,
they learned about the hideous experiments
performed by Caesar Clown, the Master,
and headed off to investigate
but as things got going,
they came to form an alliance with the
Heart Pirates led by Trafalgar Law.
And Luffy finally encountered Caesar!
You shouldn't underestimate me.
Who is there?!
Why are you...
...here?!
It's been years.
You've grown up.
Law.
"A Samurai Who Can Cut
Fire! Foxfire Kin'emon!"
Do you really think that he had no idea?
We don't trust Caesar, either.
That's why he was being careful
and sent an undercover agent.
Monet is that agent.
You're a Warlord-sama now, aren't you?
You've done so well.
When did you come here?
Vergo!
Just arrived. Luckily, I was at Dressrosa.
I got a ride in an SAD tanker
that was about to leave.
It was the right move.
The right move?!
Did I cause any harm to you guys?!
No but if you did, you'd be dead by now.
You can't fool grown-ups, Law.
In that case, I should just finish you!
Oh, I forgot to mention.
You've got to say it properly.
It's Vergo-san to you.
IN FRONT OF THE LABORATORY LUFFY'S GROUP
What just happened?
I have no idea.
What should we do?
Tashigi-chan!
It's Vice Admiral Smoker!
I can't believe I saw him
get taken down twice a day.
Three of the Straw Hats got beaten, too!
Was it Conqueror's Haki?!
No way! There can't be that much
difference in their strength!
Then what was it?! He beat all of
them without even touching them!
That serves you right, Navy!
That was what our savior
- Master is capable of!
Master! Master! Master! Master!
Master! Master! Master!
My strong soldiers!
Tie these five up!
Use Sea Prism Stone chains
for the Devil Fruit eaters!
Leave the Navy soldiers here
and get inside the laboratory.
It's dangerous out here.
Something strange is raining
down but don't worry.
I'll protect this place where you belong!
Yes, Master!
Looks like the Cool Brothers blew it.
But it can't be helped.
Fighting against Straw Hat and Law
must've been too much for them.
THE MIDDLE LAKE - ZORO'S GROUP
Gross!
Alright, Brook. Convince them.
That's impossible!
What kind of negotiation skill is
going to work for these monsters?!
They're merging into one another!
Boy, they're merging into one
another and getting bigger.
I-I-It got bigger!
Do I have a choice? It's my personal mission!
I'm Sanji, I'm a man! I've got to do it!
Sanji-san!
Do something about the Slimes behind you.
Please be careful!
What a pain in the ass! That worthless chef!
Oh, it's coming!
Don't... Don't... Don't attack me!
It's big, it's big!
Oh no, you better not do that!
Whoa, don't! Help me!
You did it!
I knew you could do it, Zoro-san!
It's gas! Run!
I've had enough!
I-I-It's poison gas!
My eyes, my eyes!
Oh, I don't have eyes.
Hey, what's your problem?!
You jelly-ish body entity!
Poison gas, again!
What should we do, Zoro-san?!
It's poison gas!
I did the same thing before!
Learn from observation, skeleton!
I thought you were just unlucky.
We're surrounded.
This is not good.
It's cold!
Where is the samurai's torso?
Alright. Let's use it!
Observation Haki!
We have nowhere to go now!
Oh yeah, they're jellies!
Why don't you eat and digest them?
No way!
Could you stop talking to me like a bully?!
I'm like 70 years older than you!
I'm sorry, grandpa!
Who did you call "grandpa"?!
I'm still a lively skeleton...
What's the matter?!
Samurai-san?! T-T-Take it easy!
So cold!
Sorry, Nami-san.
Could this be the Slime's toxin?!
Whoa-whoa, I hope his torso
is not engulfed by it!
I've been using Observation
Haki for quite a while
but maybe the torso's getting weaker.
I can't distinguish its life
force from that of the fish!
A shark?
No way!
A-Are you alright?
Hey, what's the matter?! What's going on?!
Wait, you shithead! Don't mess with me!
Stop chewing on it, shark!
I-I-It doesn't hurt at all! It itches!
What's wrong with him?!
Is he bluffing?
That hurts... Not really!
Maybe something happened to Sanji-san?!
You fool, let it go!
Now!
Joue Shoot!
Alright, I got the last piece safely!
The samurai puzzle will be complete!
I gotta go back now!
It's gonna close up!
Dammit!
The poison got this far!
Shit! It's all around me now!
Can I do it with Nami-san's strength?
It's gonna put a strain on her body again...
This is not good!
The whole lake is turning
to the color of the poison!
Sanji-san, hurry up!
Blue Walk!
Don't close up! Don't
close up! Don't close up!
Don't close up!
Sanji-san!
Oh, he got it!
He really did it!
What can I say?!
I have never felt so happy
to just have my own body!
THE SAMURAI FROM THE WANO
KINGDOM FOXFIRE KIN'EMON
Oh, I didn't know you were so tall!
You're as tall as I am.
Oh yes! Excuse me for not
introducing myself sooner!
My name is Kin'emon!
I was born in Kuri, Wano Kingdom!
Just do it already! I'm
gonna freeze to death!
Yes! I'm sorry!
Poof!
It's still cold.
The coat will disappear once
he takes it off, right?
Funny-eyebrow man, what is
your honorable name, sir?
I'm Sanji!
Cut the "sir" crap!
Now you have your whole body back
so you've changed your attitude!
But you were insulting me so much earlier
hiding behind the fact you were disabled!
I hope you're not forgetting what you said!
You people are pirates?!
No wonder you people are barbaric!
I don't like pirates! You make me sick!
Don't irritate me!
Why don't you just ask me to find your body?!
I don't wanna owe anything to pirates!
I wouldn't ask you even if it kills me!
Now, I'm not even capable of
fighting back if someone hits me
so you can carry me if you want to.
I will never forget!
Ever!
I will never forget your kindness
for the rest of my life!
I appreciate everything!
And please forgive me for
having doubts about you all...
...until I got my torso back!
I'm begging you! I'm begging you!
I'm begging you!
I'm begging you...
Stop it, fool! Lift your head up!
Men shouldn't kneel on
the ground that easily!
But if you, sir, weren't there, I probably...
Um, I'm sorry to interrupt
you but, Sanji-san...
Looks like we're in big trouble.
Look. You see?
THE THIRD LABORATORY
The drug...
If only I could find out
how he made the drug...
Is that...
Great! It's a book about drugs!
Now I gotta look for sedatives.
Master, the airship is ready.
Okay.
Then let's go pick them up.
It's about time for them to have these.
Put Straw Hat and the others in a
cage and carry it to my chambers.
Yes, Master!
We have nowhere to run now!
Hey, guys! Didn't I tell you
to do something about them?!
It can't be helped because
we couldn't do anything.
That's right.
Don't be such children, you idiots!
I can't cause any damage to Nami-san's body!
This body...
Th-This body, I have to...
You're not gonna return it, are you?
Of course not!
Why don't we burn them down?
What?
People call me Foxfire Kin'emon.
I can burn and slice an enemy with my sword.
Let me burn them down and
clear the way to escape!
You can burn and slice an enemy?
It sounds like magic!
He cut the fire!
Now I cleared the way.
I'm coming for you, Momonosuke!
Huh?! I'm still alive!
I thought we were engulfed by
the fire from the explosion!
K-K-Kin'emon-san? What just happened?
I just cut the explosion.
The explosion?!
My Foxfire Style
allows me to cut something
with fire and then cut flames.
There is no flame that I can't cut!
Now I'm going to go to the
laboratory to save Momonosuke!
If you'll excuse me!
Wait!
I'm intrigued by a samurai's fight.
I'll go with you to rescue your son!
A mysterious man suddenly appears
and hurts Law with his immense power.
His identity causes quite the shock,
and the identity of the powerful
enemy that stands behind
Caesar and the mysterious
man finally comes to light!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Shocking! The True Identity
of the Mystery Man Vergo!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!