Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Alright! Light it flashily!
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
Zoro!
Stabbing him from behind is unfair,
Big Nose!
Hey, Zoro. You're hurt, you know...
Just shut up and stay in there!
I'm gonna do things my way!
Who is this guy?!
Luffy... Who's she?
Oh, she's our navigator!
Get serious! Who are you guys?!
Move...
You're in the way!
"Desperate Situation!
Beast Tamer Mohji vs. Luffy!"
Why would you go that far?
You're a pirate!
Those three think they
can mock me! Screw that!
Looks like I can consider this
a declaration of war against me!
Mohji! There you are!
Would you mind if I take
Roronoa Zoro's head?
Be my guest!
What's with this dog?
Dog!
Hey, Zoro! It's not moving at all!
Hell if I care!
It can do whatever it wants!
I wonder if it's dead?!
Oww! Oww! Oww!
Oww! What're you doing, stupid dog?!
Do you know the situation
we're in right now?!
Damn dog!
Not enough blood...
Heya, Navigator!
I guess you can have this,
since you did save me!
Oh! The key to the cage!
You went and got it for me?!
Don't get the wrong idea!
I just didn't want to wind up owing you!
I'm saved!
Stupid dog! Stupid dog!
That's not food! Gimme that key back!
Give it back! Give it back!
Stop that!
Quit bullying Chouchou, you young'uns!
Chouchou?
Who're you, old man?
I'm this town's mayor! Who are you?!
Huh?
My, what a terrible injury!
I take it Buggy went after you folks, too?
We need to get you to a doctor!
How's Zoro?!
He needs to see a doctor,
but he said he'd sleep
it off and went to bed.
So this dog's name is Chouchou?
What's it just sitting here for?
It's guarding the shop.
--Guarding?
--Yes...
Oh! This is a pet food shop!
Yes. This shop's owner
is a good friend of mine...
There you go.
So I'm here to feed his dog in his place.
--In his place?
--Yes.
He died three months ago, from an illness.
Don't tell me he's been waiting for
his master to return all this time?
That's what everyone says...
...but I don't think that's it.
Chouchou is a smart dog.
He's probably long known
that his master is dead.
Then why is he guarding the shop?
I think it's because this shop is
a treasure in Chouchou's eyes.
I think he continues to protect it
because it's a memento
of his dog-loving master.
I've tried to make him
evacuate on many occasions,
but he won't take as much
as a step away from here.
What's that war cry?!
It's him! Beast Tamer Mohji!
What do you mean by "Beast Tamer"?!
W-Wait! Hold on!
C'mon, something's here!
Give me the key back!
Oh, I see your friends have deserted you.
Just after you managed to escape, too...
Who're you?
I am Beast Tamer Mohji,
a member of the Buggy Pirates.
That sure is a weird
animal suit you got on!
How rude! This is my hair!
That's even weirder!
Do you think you can rest easy
because you're inside that cage?
You must not know my terrifying skill!
There is no animal in this world...
...that Beast Tamer Mohji can't tame!
Shake!
You're nothing but a
nameless sneak thief.
I have no interest in taking your life.
Tell me where Roronoa Zoro is!
No!
Sic him, Richie!
Yes! The cage is open!
An instant death.
Good Richie.
Now let's find Zoro,
so I can defeat him
and increase my name!
What is it?
Ah, a pet food store.
Alright, make your meal quick!
Huh? Don't tell me this is this
pathetic little shop's guard dog?
Whew, what a shock!
But now I'm out of that cage!
Alright! Now it's time
to beat all of them up...
...and have Nami the thief
be our navigator!
How are you alive?!
You're alive!
Is it wrong to be alive?
Being just fine after flying
through houses isn't normal!
It's not?
What is your purpose
for coming to this town?
Why are you involved
with those pirates?
I just decided our purpose!
To get a Grand Line map and a navigator!
I think that guy in the animal suit
said he was looking for Zoro!
I'll go check on him!
Chouchou. This shop
belongs to the two of us!
This bag is too big for you, Chouchou!
You don't want to get hurt, Chouchou!
Just leave it to me!
Bad Chouchou! I told you
not to eat the merchandise!
Now let's chow down!
Oh? You still come at us...
Chouchou. I'm getting up in age now.
I gotta check into the hospital.
But I will get better!
Guard the shop well until I come back!
Hold down the fort!
That tickles, Chouchou!
I think it's because this shop
is a treasure in Chouchou's eyes.
I think he continues to protect it...
...because it's a memento
of his dog-loving master.
Damn it! That dog even bit me!
Wait! I just killed you!
I won't die that easily!
Crunch his head for sure this time!
I won't lose to some lion!
Gum-Gum...
...Hammer!
Richie!
What are you?!
I ate the Gum-Gum Fruit!
You mean you have Devil Fruit powers,
just like Captain Buggy?!
A-all right! I peacefully
apologize to you!
You don't need to apologize now.
'Cause that dog's treasure
is never coming back.
That's why I'm gonna kick your ass!
Pirates are all the same, every last one!
They take what people hold dear
without a second thought!
Oh, you're alive, pirate!
I figured the lion ate you for sure!
As a pirate, you'll do the same thing!
Maybe I should kill you right here
before you can gather a crew...
...and attack people too!
Come! Stop that, girl!
As if you could ever kill me.
--Maybe I'll try and see, then!
--I said stop! What's with you people?!
This is all I could take back.
Bastard ate all the rest.
He... fought with that lion.
For that dog's sake...
You fought good!
I didn't see your fight, but I can tell!
Yeah! Good luck to you, too!
You were beaten?!
I- I'm very sorry, Captain Buggy!
Mohji! I can't believe
you'd lose to Zoro!
No, it wasn't Zoro!
It was that Straw Hat!
What?! That straw hat kid beat you?!
He's eaten the--
Now I'm pissed!
Prepare all the Special
Buggy Balls we have!
I'm gonna blow this entire
town to smithereens!
--Sorry about earlier!
--Huh?
I didn't mean to yell at you...
It's okay! You've been through a lot!
I don't feel like hearing
about it though.
I'm so pathetic!
Chouchou and this
young'un will fight so hard,
yet why must I, the mayor, sit by
and watch our town be obliterated?!
Calm down, Mayor!
40 years ago, this place
was nothing but barren land.
We all worked together to
clear the land, make fields,
open stores, and build our town.
This town is a treasure
to me and all the citizens!
I cannot let them
domineer over it any more!
Fire a Special Buggy Ball!
Blow the town away!
Even my own house...
Zoro's sleeping in there!
The young'un is dead now...
Hey! Zoro! Are you alive?!
That's one hell of a way
to wake a guy up...
Not enough sleep...
How are you still alive?!
Thank goodness! You're alive!
I refuse to let them get away with this!
I can stand this no more!
Some random scum has no right
to suddenly destroy our 40 years!
I am this town's mayor!
I will protect this town!
Stop! Stop, Mayor!
There are fights a man cannot run from!
Isn't that right, young'un?!
That's right, old man!
Don't urge him on!
What can he possibly do by
going to see them?! It's reckless!
I'm fully aware it's reckless!
I'm coming for you, Buggy the Clown!
The mayor was crying...
He was? I didn't see it.
Looks like the party's
gettin' more exciting!
Sure does!
This is no time to be laughing!
It's okay! I like that old guy!
I absolutely won't let him die!
In that case...
You're gonna go, too?!
With that wound?!
The injury to my name is much
worse than the injury to my gut!
Our destination is the Grand Line.
So we're gonna steal
that map back now!
Join our crew, Nami!
I'll never be a pirate.
How about we team up
for our common goal?
The second shot is ready, sir!
Alright! Fire!
Come out, Buggy the Clown!
I am Mayor Boodle!
This town is our treasure!
I've come to protect it! Fight me!
What are you, stupid?!
Treasure is gold, silver, and jewels!
This town, a treasure?! Cut the crap!
You'd never understand how I feel--
I'm soon going to conquer
the Grand Line and flashily obtain...
...all of the world's riches!
The world's riches are mine!
No one else in this world
needs treasure but me!
If this town's that important to you,
shall I destroy you with it?!
Quit prattling and fight me!
Don't get cocky now!
I won't let you destroy this town!
Even if it costs me my life!
Fire!
The straw hat guy!
I'm here to kick your ass,
just like I promised!
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Huh? Now there's some
swordsman or whatever guy!
--I'll clash swords with him!
--You sure? You're injured...
I'll show you our difference in level!
Ooh! Cool!
My ambition is to be the
world's greatest swordsman!
I can't afford to lose to anyone
who calls himself a swordfighter!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Epic Showdown!
Swordsman Zoro vs. Acrobat Cabaji!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!