All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,--
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,--
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard; an island with
two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
They landed on Punk Hazard; an island with two parts, one burning, the other frozen
They landed on Punk Hazard; an island with
two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen
and were held captive by Caesar Clown...
After forming an alliance with Trafalgar Law,
and were held captive, confined in a cage,
...to be used as guinea pigs for Shinokuni,
Luffy finally encountered Caesar Clown
by Caesar Clown who rules the island
a weapon of mass destruction.
aka the Master who rules the island
But the counter attack has begun with their ally - a Warlord - Trafalgar Law!
and were exposed to Shinokuni,
a weapon of mass destruction.
but was beaten by his mysterious power.
Meanwhile, Law, too, got taken down by
the Navy G-5 base commander - Vergo.
But they broke out of
the cage thanks to their ally ---
Meanwhile, Law, too, got taken down by
the Navy G-5 base commander - Vergo.
a Warlord - Trafalgar Law's tactful maneuvers
Franky...
and were reunited with their crew.
So what I'm going to do is give Smiley,
R...
...Fireball!
Run!!
Why did you take them away?
The children are suffering!
Now, outside of this laboratory
is filled with the poison gas
the weapon from four
years ago, a big "boost."
Straw Hat-ya...
It will add a new effect to the poison gas
but there is one passage
What?!
We can't miss a beat here.
Special Attack!
that could lead you directly to
the sea bypassing the air outside!
The ship is on fire!
Fire Bird Star!
and the weapon of mass destruction
will reach completion.
Put out the fire!
There is a big door marked
"R-66" that is an entrance
Let's fight back.
The new weapon that will make
its debut today is called...
Now that we are not being picked up on Caesar's Video Transponder Snail.
to the passage to the sea.
"Launching the Counter Attack!
Luffy and Law's Great Escape!"
You bastard!
I'd rather not have to create a massacre
but I can only give you two hours.
...Shinokuni!
Gastanet!
Hey, guys! I see a ball!
White Chase-ya, I have no obligation to save you
Those of you who stay longer than that,
--Brownbeard!
--What happened?!
A member of the Seven
Warlords - Trafalgar Law.
Let's go!
but if letting you go back to the base safely makes Vergo lose his footing,
I can't guarantee your safety.
Gastanet!
it work out well for me.
There are children who were kidnapped
two years ago in this laboratory!
A pirate who was on the news recently
for making a stunning comeback -
However,
Smiley! I missed you!
you need to forget everything that you heard about me and Joker.
Straw Hat Luffy.
Retrieve them and head for the "R-66" door!
"Shaking Up the New World!
Caesar's Horrendous Experiment!"
It's been three years!
And his comrade--the
Devil Child - Nico Robin.
I'm not asking you a favor.
Wait for me, Momonosuke!
I'll save you at any cost!
It's a condition.
For sparing your life.
Oh yes, Smiley?
The Wild Dog of the Navy--"White
Chase" - Smoker.
Hey, Luffy!
This brings back memories!
Get a grip!
Hey, Kin'emon!
IN FRONT OF CAESAR'S LABORATORY
How did these big-timers end up
Can you cut iron?
I have something good for you!
This is just the beginning of the New World!
VARIOUS PLACES IN THE NEW WORLD
being captured by Caesar?
That's not so hard to cut!
Yeah, sorry! I won't drop my guard again!
What?!
Brownbeard, keep charging like this!
Open up!
It's them! So that's where they are!
With Luffy in the lead, they start to move
Dammit! It's as solid as rock!
I'm gonna charge!
What should we do?
Hey! Open the shutter!
That's a big candy!
to rescue the children and kidnap Caesar!
Give us back Smo-yan and Tashigi-chan!
Let's see how things go for a while-bon.
Gum-Gum...
Those creepy creatures...
"Get to Building R! The Pirate Alliance's Great Advance!"
What is that?
They went that way but...
Hey, they are...
Good boy, Smiley.
Forget about them! Focus on saving
Smo-yan and Tashigi-chan now!
He finally got off his ass! Straw Hat!
EUSTASS "CAPTAIN" KID
Open it, Caesar!
Nobody can stop him now!
...UFO!
THE CAPTAIN OF THE KID PIRATES BOUNTY:
470 MILLION BERRIES
It's no use watching it.
What's that?
An airship?!
And you're not the kind of guy...
...who wants to play an arms trader, are you?
KILLER
Killer.
A CREW MEMBER OF THE KID PIRATES BOUNTY:
200 MILLION BERRIES
You're right.
"The Deadliest Weapon of Mass
Destruction in History! Shinokuni!"
But I can't believe those
three are there together.
Yeah, that asshole - Trafalgar!
"Tashigi's Tears! G-5's
Desperate Breakthrough Plan!"
I thought he had lost his mind when
he became the Government's dog
What have you done?!
but to nobody's surprise,
he was up to something.
--What is that creature?!
--Doesn't it look like those creepy jellies?!
Is he gonna start something?
Now, get off, children!
What is going on?!
We don't wanna fall behind! Let's move!
This is your home!
Don't ever go out on your own!
Kid, I beg you. Settle it peacefully.
Master, thank you!
I know! So shut up, already!
He ate it!
He ate the candy!
Sheep-san, give me the candy.
You ate it!
Master! I want the candy now!
Why?!
Smiley!
My head hurts! Master, give me the candy now!
SCRATCHMEN APOO
Hey, Captain Kid!
Oh no!
It's good that we made it in but the poison gas will come in, too!
Of course, you can have it soon.
BASIL HAWKINS
Why are they inside of the building?!
You look annoying as always!
Be reborn!
Everyone, go straight
back to the Biscuit Room.
The brokers are watching this!
Damn! What humiliation!
Scratchmen! What are you doing?!
I've left plenty of candy in there for you.
What can he be reborn as?
You made a big mess out of our lair!
I have to go back to my research room now.
The Straw Hats and the
group of Navy soldiers are...
The perfect weapon of mass destruction.
Sorry, Captain! We couldn't stop him!
Screw you guys! Are you trying to get us all killed?!
That's such a big frog!
...running toward the passage to escape!
Relax and enjoy the candies in the room!
I was making sure that
Everyone, try to plug up the hole!
you didn't have any snipers.
They are very, very delicious!
THE CAPTAIN OF THE ON AIR PIRATES BOUNTY:
350 MILLION BERRIES
Or we're all gonna die!
Anyone would do so
Yeah!
when he gets summoned by his enemy.
Let's go to the room! Show
me the way, Mr. Sheep!
See, Killer?!
Now...
This is why I told you not to call him!
...be reborn!
It's this way, kids.
Smiley!
Calm down. He's a powerful man.
--The Biscuit Room!
--I want the candy now!
What should I do? What should I do?
THE CAPTAIN OF THE HAWKINS PIRATES BOUNTY:
320 MILLION BERRIES
How thoughtless of you to
What should I do?!
keep a guest you invited waiting.
You know what to do, don't you?
Once they're all inside,
You assholes...
lock them up securely and
don't ever let them get out.
I'm gonna kill you both now!
Yes, sir.
Oh, I knew that's what you wanted!
The Master! He's like a devil!
I'm ready for it!
Bring it on! Check it out!
But looks like everybody's okay! I'm so glad!
This is so stupid. I'm leaving.
DON'T DO ANYTHING
It's scary here!
Wait, Hawkins! Not so soon!
Look out! Something's going on!
Hey!
I don't know who gave me this paper.
What's the matter, brat...
What is "something"?!
I mean, princess?
Did he or she mean Luffy and the
others can escape on their own?!
How do I know?! But I'm
sure it's something bad!
Everyone! Enough already!
Just do as the Master
says and run to the lab!
We wanted to discuss...
How did they break out of that cage?
...forming an alliance
with both of your groups!
Damn! I can't believe the
sled broke! Why now?!
What's wrong?
Who gave me this?
Master!
Why don't you go back to
the room like everyone else
Don't you guys even know how to talk?!
Who cares about those things now?
He's acting strange since he ate the candy!
and have that sweet candy?
I'm a doctor!
I wonder if the candy was that good!
I have to save those children!
Fighting back?
Let's just run!
I found out the formula of the
drug and I got the sedatives!
Yeah, it's no use wasting our time here.
Huh? What?!
Even soldiers from this island
are running desperately!
Let's get it over with.
I have a bad feeling about this!
Wait for me, kids!
Couldn't agree more!
Can anybody here burn things?
I will heal you at any cost!
Don't go! Do you wanna go back to the lab?!
If nobody can, that's fine, too.
Franky can set fires.
Get out of my way!
He can even shoot a laser beam!
Oh yeah!
Why don't you burn this chain with the beam?
Usopp!
Master, give me the candy!
I need to use both hands
to shoot the Radical Beam.
That's it. Come back to me, children.
The only thing I can shoot is...
Wait, you all!
...Coup de Boo from my ass!
You shouldn't go back to him!
But come to think of it,
which way should I go?!
Don't you wanna go home?!
Whatever.
Can you set fire to the Navy
ship down there on the right?
What are my soldiers doing?
Troops have mobilized
against them in A Building!
1, 2, 3!
Huh? That one?
The main unit is preparing to make a
stand at the post in the back of B Building!
No! I wanna get out!
That's as easy as pie, young man!
You can count on me!
What are you talking about?
Franky...
It's cold outside and don't you
realize what floor you're on?
I'm sure what they want is
to escape from the island.
I guess we're safe now.
Now, go back to the room.
No! Help me, Sis!
...Fireball!
Then, they must be heading for...
Mocha?
...the path going directly
to R Building - Gate 66!
Let's go get the candy already!
--The ship is on fire!
--Run!
Good girl! Go back to the room!
Put out the fire!
The candy is in that room!
What is he doing? Is he just desperate?
Why are you people so scary?
That Pacifista-esque guy!
I'm scared! I'm scared!
I won't let them do that!
Sis and the others were very nice to me!
Good work, Smiley!
It's no use.
Block off the passage
between Building A and B!
After the experiment,
See you again!
I'll chop up their bodies
and put them to good use.
Is it because I'm not a good child?!
Close the gate there and isolate Building A!
Oh yeah!
I'm sorry I didn't listen to you! Bro! Sis!
--I can't see the cage because of the smoke!
--Captain-chan, you okay?!
--Smo-yan, is it smoky there?!
--Fool! He's a smoke man in the first place!
Help me!
And then, destroy Building A
Hey, get away from the door!
Damn! What a pain in the butt!
and let Shinokuni flow in!
Help me! Sis!
What?! But if you do such a thing,
it will also kill our guards...
Sis!!
Just do it!
Don't forget to place a
Surveillance Transponder Snail!
Hey, Trafalgar! It's getting so smoky here!
What?! M-Master...
Now, come to life!
Let's restart this open
experiment for the brokers.
The weapon of mass destruction - Shinokuni!
You're the one who did it.
THE REMAINS OF THE FIRST
AND SECOND LABORATORY
You made me do it!
I haven't fully shown them
my scientific mastery yet!
What is that?!
Change the face of the island completely!
What are you doing?
Well then...
Just go already!
What?!
Y-Yes, sir!
Humph! How useless!
Ow, ow, ow...
Now that we are not being picked up
on Caesar's Video Transponder Snail.
I'm alive!
There are a whole bunch of cuts
and bruises on Sanji-kun's body
Hey, don't tell me...
They're not gonna find out for a while.
but it's so strong!
And what will you do, Vergo?
I'm alive thanks to his body!
You're unbelievable!
How did you free yourself
from Sea Prism Stone chain?
Only idiots will fall for such a trap.
Where are the children?!
Well, mine was just an ordinary
chain from the beginning.
You're not the only one who
will lose face if we let
Run!
What?
Usopp!
So I untied myself easily with my power.
Wait for me!
Law and Smoker get away, Caesar.
It's the end!
I can't trust you to handle this.
Room!
There is nowhere on Punk Hazard that is habitable!
I will cut everything up!
Stay with me, Usopp!
Do you know how many months I've been here?
Oh? That's strange.
You came to save me, Sanji?
Just in case of an emergency,
I can't find my sword.
I put a number of regular chains
everywhere in the laboratory.
You're not a swordsman.
I'm Nami!
Hey, don't be so disappointed!
Oh yeah, I'm not a swordsman.
So I could avoid Sea Prism Stone
Now, get up!
Alright, I'll go strike down those squirts.
It's still pretty dense.
even if I got caught by accident.
We have to save the children!
One foot out the door and it will kill you.
Oh! Hey, wait!
Hey, Usopp!
Oh, my legs!
Where are you, Caesar?!
LABORATORY BUILDING A
What happened?!
How was it, Brook?
Yes, it was like a land of dead.
I'm free!
Do you want milk?
Help me...
When I think of what would've happened if we couldn't plug the hole,
Quit cheering, fool.
No, just sugar is fine.
Yeah, yeah, I'm free!
I won't let you pass through here, Straw Hat!
--Yeah, yeah, I'm free!
--Now...
You don't have to take care of me.
it terrifies me.
You terrify us, too!
...what should I do with you two?
I'm a gatekeeper of B Building
and a former pirate!
--What's happening?!
--I don't know! Just run!
You've learned a little too much.
Okay!
People call me "Machete" Run!
It's not okay!
We all could've died because of you!
I have your destiny in my hands.
In the name of Master Caesar,
the scientist of love!
Anyway,
We plugged the hole, too!
You know what you wanna
do with it, don't you?
what's taking Caesar so long?
You don't have animal legs!
My body...
Just do it already!
I'm not a fan!
You guys are way more annoying than I expected!
I can't move it!
Just in time.
What kind of centaur you are?!
Give it up, Straw Hats! You too, Brownbeard!
Smoker-san?!
Spider...
Sorry to keep you waiting, Vergo!
Now we're cornered?! We have nowhere to run!
...desu.
Run! Just run!
We're back to ourselves!
No problem. I was having coffee and cookies.
Master!!
That's odd. The cookies are gone.
We don't need to run.
Outta my way!
Yes! It worked!
Don't scream like a woman, young girl!
I didn't serve you any cookies.
Well, this is so predictable.
Nobody can get away this time!
Oh yeah, I wasn't having cookies.
J-Just untie us!
This is it!
When does the experiment start, Caesar?
I'd do anything you say!
The problem with the last experiment
was there were survivors.
They shouldn't do that.
THE PASSAGE BETWEEN BUILDING A AND B
Stop it, Tashigi!
Soon. Monet, turn the video on.
Wouldn't you rather die than
grovel before a pirate?!
Right away.
They could still move even after being
poisoned so they were able to escape.
Th-They knew my name!
Right now, we have to beg for our lives,
Oh, it's starting down there!
By the way, I wish you had your man
Which means...
throwing ourselves at his
feet if that's what it takes!
It's a huge tunnel!
...I should've petrified them!
under better control, Vergo!
Because if we die here,
You two, don't stand in my way - or in his people's, understood?
The gas clings to people's bodies like ash.
we can't save our people
and Vice Admiral Vergo...
When I saw Smoker here,
I broke into a cold sweat.
Yeah.
It enters through their skin and
paralyzes their whole body at once!
Yeah, well - he was like a wild
dog. He was beyond my control.
I mean, Vergo will act as
he pleases in the Navy.
Oh, Tra-guy! Hey you!
Now is the chance! Hurry up!
And the children...
Now, the perfect weapon of
mass destruction, Shinokuni!
We can't die here!
Switch us back!
Law! What's this buzzer?
But that'll all change after today.
You don't have to!
Give us a good glimpse of hell!
It warns people that a gate
in this building will close.
Hey, what are you saying, Sanji-kun?!
She's a little smarter than you.
--Oh, it's nothing!
--No, we have to switch back!
Look at yourself!
And that's the only passage to Building B.
White Chase-ya, I have
no obligation to save you
Law!
Room.
--I want my body back! I want it back!
--It's not necessary...
What?!
I guess he's trying to keep us out.
I bet you were quite helpless
against Vergo! Hmm?
but if letting you go back to the base safely
Shambles.
makes Vergo lose his footing,
it works out well for me.
You better tell your men to move faster.
Oh, damn! The dream is over!
The deal I had with you worked in my favor!
However, you need to forget everything
that you heard about me and Joker.
What the hell is going on?!
I'm back!
People are...
In exchange for letting you stay here,
But, oh?
you're going to give my people legs?
I'm not asking you a favor. It's a condition.
Help me...
That would be nice, of course.
For sparing your life.
But since you're stronger than me
...solidifying!
Sanji-kun?
and I'm the boss of this island,
Why am I wearing a different coat?!
if you want to stay here, I
need a little bit of insurance.
You took my clothes off, didn't you?!
I can explain...
Master!
I wasn't planning on hurting you.
What do you want me to do?
How about this, Trafalgar Law?
Sanji, are you okay?!
Hey, what is that?
I want to entrust my dear
secretary Monet's heart to you!
Oh? My body...
This is something out of a horror movie!
But it's not just because of that punch.
Those who just died looked
like Caesar's men...
I can't see anything!
Nami was beaten badly in that body by Caesar.
Is that okay, Monet?
What was that purple smoke?
What's going on out there?
Yes. No problem.
What?
By the way, where are they filming this?
Yeah, I finally got out!
In return,
I don't know what Trafalgar Law meant
H-Hey, what's the matter?!
let me keep your heart!
when he said he can only give us two hours
--Aha!
--What are you...
If you don't know yet, you
better not turn around!
I'm so glad that it was my body that got hurt!
Yeehaw!
And that's a deal!
Hey, wait!
but we won't let you guys
get away, Straw Hats!
How dare he do whatever the pleases!
You're so noble!
As long as we have each other by the balls,
You have nowhere to run!
Don't tell me that was...
It's not like the cage is
made of Sea Prism Stone.
you can't do anything bad.
Everybody here, listen!
Our captain does that sort of thing
as soon as your back is turned.
And I feel safe.
What is this buzzer?
Law!
I knew I shouldn't trust anybody.
No! That was happening on this island?!
Don't do it!
Now, outside of this laboratory is filled with the poison gas
That fool!
It's your own fault!
Master!
but there is one passage that
I bet you learned it the
hard way already but...
could lead you directly to the sea bypassing the air outside!
Hey, Tra-guy!
...Vergo has your heart.
Oh no! We have to run! Or
we'll end up like them...
Aha!
How should I get in?!
It's impossible!
This laboratory consists of multiple buildings.
There's nowhere to run on
the island from such gas!
Don't stand in our way!
Hey, young man.
Oh, I see! That's why
they sealed off the lab!
I'd rather take care of the Sunny.
We're in Building A now.
Ouch!
They didn't want the gas to enter!
Hey!
Do as you like.
It's hot!
If you go through the gate at the back of this building
I know it was impossible even for
a man such as yourself to notice
Alright then, see you later!
and pass through Building B, the central part,
It's cold!
Open up, Caesar!
Coup de...
Damn! I don't wanna die here!
...Boo!
but Monet tactfully transformed
herself and followed you.
you'll find Building R.
So dependable!
You three swordsmen!
Damn! Damn! This is not joke! Open up!
I'm coming for you, Sunny!
There is a big door marked "R-66"
Alright, let's go!
I'm counting on you, Franky!
Th-They're coming!
Oh, it stinks!
that is an entrance to the passage to the sea.
Hey, are you alright?! Tra-guy!
I'd rather not have to create a massacre but I can only give you two hours.
I know what you guys are up to.
I think we can make it to the
children pretty easily like this.
Why are you looking at me like that?
What a shame, Law.
Those of you who stay longer than that,
Hey! What are you waiting for, Tra-guy?!
I thought we became good friends.
Thank you for carrying us, Brownbeard.
I can't guarantee your safety.
What?!
Don't mention it. But, guys,
Hey, what do you mean by that?!
You've been saved by your
diligent secretary, huh?
why did you bring the dragon with you?
--Hey!
--Screw you!
Well...
I should've been more careful about Monet.
Is something gonna happen to the lab?
We thought that we could get away
from the gas by flying on him
Hey! I found him!
Seeing as how the "Master" was
so dumb, I didn't care much.
Depends on how things go.
Brownbeard, you okay?!
I just have to do what I have to do now.
but he didn't fly at all.
He's still breathing but...
Hmm, I see.
He doesn't fly now because
he got injected with sedatives.
Watch your mouth, young man!
Robin, could you do me a favor?
Hey, Smo-yan!
He's badly wounded...
I can't believe it! He took your
heart and you're still alive?!
Captain-chan! Are you okay?!
But it wasn't a great idea
to let him in the laboratory.
What is it?
We're okay thanks to you...
G-5!
What should we do?!
How stupid can you be, letting him
take advantage of your own ability?!
Smo-yan!
Caesar!
Is he dangerous?
Hey, look. It's already...
There are children who were kidnapped two years ago in this laboratory!
He's kind of cute...
Where is mine?
Gastanet!
The poison gas will get here any minute!
Retrieve them and head for the "R-66" door!
Brownbeard...
This is a rare opportunity for us!
It's here!
Take them down!
Smo...
If he is right, you'll find a harbor there.
I'll take the credit!
Master.
Didn't I say "Don't do it"?!
Anyway, let's pull him out from
under this iron pipe, Sanji!
If nothing is done, just like
people in that video, we...
The video is ready.
Steal a ship and let's escape from Punk Hazard!
Oh yeah?
I am Nami!
You're a lucky man!
Alright!
I wanna leave this shitty island already!
I-It's no good! We need to
get inside the building now!
Hey! Don't be so disappointed again!
Children...
Everyone, let's split up and look for the children and take them to the passage!
Well, it's just...
--Open the shutter!
--Damn it! Open up!
Alright, put it on.
It's gonna be pretty heavy physical work!
It's "R-66"!
Okay!
Zoro! You can't go alone!
We have no choice!
Run!
Uh-huh!
Wait for me, Momonosuke!
It's a huge ball!
I'll save you at any cost!
What is he up to?
We can run faster like this
but it's catching up to us!
Damn! It won't budge an inch!
Okay. I got it.
Come on!
The dragon is so far ahead!
Thanks. Well then...
Let's catch it and fly already!
C-Captain-chan?!
Wait for me, Caesar!
We'll pull you out soon!
Hang in there, Brownbeard!
--I can't...
--Sanji-san, stay with us!
I'm not gonna get suffocated this time!
Wow, you became a Captain, Copy-cat?
He's right! You can do it!
I can't run anymore!
Nami-san's cardiopulmonary
functions can't take it anymore!
Finally!
I'll beat you up and kidnap you!
But you have no fighting spirit.
You two...
The chest feels tight!
Her chest... Breasts...
That's right. Just go ahead.
Oh, yes, yes!
Breasts!
Thank you so much!
Don't die, Brownbeard!
I caught it!
Wait!
What kind of stupid power was that?!
I'm not gonna...
G-5! This is no time for fight!
Something is on the screen!
…kick the bucket yet!
What is that? Where is it? That looks like...
Go to the passage at the back now!
What?!
...a candy! It's a huge candy!
The only gate in this
building is now closing.
--The smoke is closing in!
--That creepy color...
When did they place that
Video Transponder Snail?
That asshole - Caesar is...
It must be very poisonous!
Caesar is trying to fence us in.
...unforgivable!
Sorry, Brownbeard-chi!
Brownbeard...
If we can't make it to the
other side of the gate,
You're badly wounded but
you have to carry us!
But I have to save my crew first!
VARIOUS PLACES IN THE NEW
WORLD UNDERWORLD BROKERS
we can't escape from Punk Hazard!
Thank you for waiting, brokers.
No problem. It's just like carrying dwarves.
Just go!
It's going to start soon. The Smilies...
Otherwise, I can't die in peace!
What?!
You see? This is a great open experiment!
I have to save my men anyway!
Oh no!
...that made their way
We have to save those kids!
Hurry up, you guys!
from the Burning Lands separately...
Hey, you...
The Straw Hats, Trafalgar Law, the Navy G-5...
Do as Tashigi-chan says!
I hope they haven't eaten those candies!
...will all arrive at this
Carry the injured!
Hey, look! What is that?!
central part of the Ice Lands very soon.
I gotta get to the lab where my
crew are as soon as possible!
They all sacrificed themselves for me
Hurry up!
There! Somebody's running from the gas!
Go straight to the gate!
When they merge into one another
to prove how powerful Shinokuni is!
But you're hurt all over...
and become one big "Smiley" again,
So we all wanna go to the same place!
A dragon?
Don't tell me that's...
We have to save those
kids from that jerk, too!
the experiment will begin.
Can't you run more quietly?!
So why don't you join forces with
us and beat that gas bastard...
I mean, why doesn't it fly?!
What's that smoke?
I don't need a dragon's help!
Cut it out, guys!
We caught it thanks to Nami-san's sexy body!
How awful!
Huh? What's that? It's
a huge amount of smoke!
Just by thinking about it, I...
Robin, where were you?
That doesn't look like just smoke to me.
Robin-chan!
What happened?
This is no time for a nosebleed, you pervert!
It could be poison gas.
Luffy asked me to do something.
What's going on?
What? Poison gas?!
The poison gas is catching up to us!
Anyway, did you hear what the Navy girl said?
Why I don't see any G-5 soldier at the main entrance?
You see - Smiley is...
My arm muscles can't take it...
Come on, Brownbeard-cchi!
...the H2S poison gas bomb itself...
Why I don't see any solidified bodies?
It's coming this way!
Oh, I don't have muscles!
Go faster!
Hey hey hey! What should do?!
That's impossible.
...the same one that killed
everything on the island...
Don't ask me!
I can't prove the power of Shinokuni without them.
This is the fastest I can run.
Do something about it!
Oh no no! What do you want
me to do about that smoke?!
Brook!
...four years ago!
I'm sick of running!
The Straw Hats, Law, and Smoker... Did they die for sure?!
--Let's just go to the...
--You two, get on my back!
H2S gas?
No!
What?
--Brook!
--That was close!
I'm not a samurai so I'll just say it!
What do you think, Vergo?
Last time,
R...
--Usopp!
--N-Nami-san?!
Enough already!
Run!!
One thing is clear.
Let's keep running!
Hey, why is Brownbeard with those pirates?!
They are not in that cage anymore.
Why are you here?!
It's gonna reach us soon!
That bastard!
despite the fact they were
growing weaker by the minute,
We have tons of questions,
too, but they can wait!
Is he betraying the Master?!
What? What do you mean by that?!
those afflicted with the gas
were able to take cover.
The Master is our great savior!
Guys, run at full speed!
Let's get to the lab!
G-5 is a group of rough meatheads.
Let's just run for now!
If anybody gets caught,
we'll have to leave you!
We're in danger, too!
Yeah!
That was a problem.
I don't think they are smart enough to
Hey, he's getting tired!
get away from the gas on their own.
The gas will get us if nothing is done!
Zoro-san, it's gonna catch
us if we don't do something!
Come on, G-5!
You all have to jump on my back!
Which means?
I guess the Straw Hat and the others
The gate is right there!
Thank you!
Hurry up!
broke out of the cage and helped the G-5 soldiers escape.
It's really gonna close soon!
Come on, come on!
Ouch!
What?!
We're dead! It's catching up to us!
Experiment cannon, stand by!
Oh, this is good!
So what I'm going to do is give Smiley,
Run faster than the wind!
Good! Just go like that!
Let's go!
--That's nice!
--We're counting on you, Brownbeard!
the weapon from four
years ago, a big "boost."
You people are horrible!
It will add a new effect to the poison gas
Tashigi, I want you to lead the G-5 soldiers.
OUTSIDE THE LABORATORY
and the weapon of mass destruction
will reach completion.
Where are you going, Smoker-san?
Take aim at the outer wall of
Building A of the Third Laboratory!
Did we outrun it even a little bit?!
The new weapon that will make
its debut today is called...
Don't tell me you're going after Vergo!
Don't turn around! Just focus
on running at full speed!
I can't forgive him!
--Hey! Hurry up!
--We're gonna die!
...Shinokuni!
The law can't settle these matters, Tashigi!
We can't run like this for very long!
THE ICE LANDS - THE CENTRAL PART
Damn! Damn! Damn! Shit! Shit! Shit!
Just open!
I have to do it myself! He was messing around with the Navy!
I see a mysterious animal up ahead!
They're coming!
Th-The poison gas is...
What is that?!
That's...
Can we even outrun such monsters?!
...coming over the mountain!
Fire!
Take me with you, then!
--A dragon!
--A dragon?!
Oh, it's coming!
A dragon?!
He... Vergo is so strong!
No way! A dragon is a mythical creature!
The wall's been broken!
It finally coalesced into
one blob on this side!
They exist on this island!
If something happens...
But that one is way smaller
than the one I saw!
First of all, what is that?!
H-Hey, don't tell me...
Who's gonna protect our men?
Dammit!
Oh yeah! If we can catch
it, we can fly on it!
This is it... We're gonna die...
What difference does it make now?! Just run!
Help those fools escape. The children, too.
That's a great idea!
Alright! I can't run like this any longer!
The poison gas will reach here soon!
You've got to be kidding!
Hey, guys! I see a ball!
Let's catch it!
Wait, dragon!
Smo-yan and Captain-chan can't even escape!
What's that?!
It looks like... a candy?!
We're all gonna die!!
Smoker-san...
Somebody's there underneath it!
Oh, that's Zoro and the others!
VEGAPUNK'S DRAGON - SMALL SIZE
They're being chased by the smoke!
Run! Run!
Is it true? Luffy got beaten by Caesar before?!
Dragon!--
Master, I see a big, gel-like creature.
What are they doing there?
Yeah, we got caught off guard and suffocated, too.
I mean, why are they running like that?
I think that's Smiley.
Samurai-san got his whole body back.
Now we are going to project Master's
video on the fog as planned.
He can manipulate gas! He's such a pain in the ass!
Oh yeah! He's not gonna let
me have those legs, then.
No!
He can remove the oxygen out of the air!
What is it?
Yes.
Then you all have to get out
of there. It's too dangerous.
Hey, Robin! That's not important now!
Shut up!
Brownbeard-cchi! Faster, faster!
The shutter's opening!
Hey, guys! That smoke is
deadly! You have to run...
We had been put to sleep by the yetis, too.
Hurry up with the dragon sled...
--We have a problem!
--The shutter's opening!
What?
This is...
Who touched the lever?!
We have a problem! The sled is melting!
Oh no... I can't even raise my voice.
That's no good.
Damn it! G-5 soldiers are
entering one after another!
It's useless now!
Damn Sea Prism Stone!
Help those fools escape.
--What's going on?!
--Hey, look!
That's really no good!
The children, too.
Are they your friends, "Straw Hat Luffy"?
How did it happen? Is it some
kind of chemical reaction?
Don't look back and keep running!
That's just what I'd expect from
your friends - they're tough!
I'll handle it!
We can't use it!
Tashigi-chan!
N-No way!
The dragon escaped!
But soon they're going to be running
out of breath and poisoned by the gas.
We spent those two years for what?
What's going on?! One thing after another!
The Navy G-5 Vice Admiral Smoker!
Wh-What?!
Whoa, whoa, we're both still alive so...
This is terrible!
The Warlord - Trafalgar Law!
And eventually, there'll be only an
uninhabitable "Land of Death (Shinokuni)"!
Oh, help...
Screw that!
That's a bit overdramatic.
The pirate - Straw Hat Luffy!
Come on!
Being caught off guard could cost us our lives from now on!
You all, just run!
No one outside of this
laboratory will survive.
The protective suit won't help!
I thought they were held
captive by the Master!
Take it off and run to the lab now!
H-Hey!
Don't let them pass through!
Good! Everyone's inside!
What? O-Okay!
Take the suit off?!
Now, what should I do with my heart?
Neither will any of you!
The Master is always right!
Luffy!
Get inside the gate!
I'm sure he has a plan! Do as he says!
If you can't make it, you're gonna die!
Get out of our way already.
I'm getting excited!
What's happening?!
Why am I doing this with these guys...
Faster! Faster! Faster!
Luffy!
What is the Moss Head doing?
Smo-yan! Captain-chan! You're alive!
Now, nobody's left outside!
Hang on tight!
Let's go!
Now prove it to the world!
Before this weapon of mass
destruction - Shinokuni,
Hope this works right!
We're safe from the poison gas!
a pirate with a 400 million berry bounty,
Hey, Luffy!
a Navy vice admiral,
Yes, we made it!
Oh?!
Zoro?
Somebody's image is being
projected in the air this time!
We did!
What's that?
and even a Warlord...
Barely!
Forget about all that crap! Just run!
Get a grip!
...are totally helpless...
Ouch!
Hey, where's Tashigi-chan?!
...against the tide of death!
This is just the beginning of the New World!
Tashigi-chan told us to go head!
We arrived at the lab!
Smiley! I missed you!
What?!
Don't stop and go straight through the gate!
It's been three years!
Come on! Hurry!
Hurry!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Wait, wait!
Oh no! Oh no!
Oh yes, Smiley?
He's gonna do something
to Luffy and the others!
Don't close the shutter!
What should I do?!
What're you doing?!
This brings back memories!
Hurry up!
I want to help but I'd be easily
caught with these wounds!
Damn! We're so close!
Get me down!
Tashigi-chan! That's enough!
I have something good for you!
Open it! Let us get inside!
He's so tough on himself.
And then the formula for
the drug that I found
You have to survive!
Oh no! They're cutting us off!
We're gonna be killed by the gas!
Wait! Wait, Smiley!
Goodbye!
Yeah, sorry! I won't drop my guard again!
You have to wait!
and the sedatives I got will be wasted!
Oh no! What should I do?!
We can't make it. We're
going to kingdom come.
You must obey me! Just as I taught you.
What?! Captain-chan flew in!
What's going on?!
I'm glad!
Wait! I said "Wait"!
Hey, Kin'emon!
Ouch! Oh!
But why were you flying...
Can you cut iron?
Move out of my way!
We have a great deal to talk about!
There are still many Navy soldiers outside!
That's not so hard to cut!
Do you remember?
Boy! That was close!
No! It's filled with gas out there!
Brownbeard, keep charging like this!
That was just...
Huh? A paper?
It's Straw Hat!
Move!
I don't know what he's up to but take him down!
I said "No"!
The gate is gonna...
...four years ago!
That's ridiculous!
Let go of me! There are still...
I'm gonna crash into the wall!
"Don't do anything"?
There are...
Then do you wanna be
killed by the poison gas?
Who wrote this?!
--But the gate is already...
--There are... Let go of me!
No way!
Smoker-san told me...
A-All right.
...to help them!
What's that?! A cage?!
Yeah, all right! You can eat now! Oh yes!
So, move out of my way!
Gum-Gum...
Who cares!
--No, Captain-chan, it's too late!
--There's... There's no time!
Could it be...
He's not listening to you.
I'm gonna charge!
--Smo-yan!
--Tashigi-chan!
We don't have any other option now, do we?
Don't be ridiculous!
What a relief! They're fine!
Your colleagues
are still outside of the gate!
Yeah, it's hit-or-miss!
Oh no!
--But they're still held captive!
--Damn! So we're all gonna die!
Outta my way!
Let's take a chance!
...UFO!
No means no! Captain Tashigi!
Are you ready?
Smo-yan! Tashigi-chan!
Of course!
Everybody!
I'm just gonna go!
Well done, guys!
Take it more seriously...
We certainly got our beloved
Captain-chan in our hands!
Enough!
It's acting funny.
Master!
What's wrong?
With the pirate - Straw Hat Luffy in the lead,
all of the enemies have entered into the lobby of Building A
By the way,
and they are advancing!
that laboratory is really well-built!
What?!
What is that?
They got inside?!
It's Zoro and the others!
Yes, it is.
How did they open that solid shutter?!
That's a bizarre entrance!
You can easily carry big
equipment with this thing.
How did they break out of the cage?!
That's a big candy!
H-How can you two be so relaxed?!
We don't know yet!
What?!
Hmmm... Okay, what should we do?
In any case, it's not good to have Law loose.
I have to kill him myself depending on what his purpose is.
It was unexpected to see Vergo
here but Straw Hat-ya...
They cut the shutter!
Good boy, Smiley.
Hey! Everybody's here, huh?
Luffy!
We can't miss a beat here.
Luffy-san!
Those scum!
Nobody can stop him now!
Outta my way!
Luffy!
I can't believe that many of them survived.
The plan is still on.
Don't mess it up this time.
But I won't let anyone...
We're all back together!
Let's fight back.
...get away!
Alright! Let's let loose!
Let's go!
Okay!
Despite successfully getting through the gate,
The Straw Hats manage to escape the clutches of Shinokuni and reunite.
Used in the past to convert Punk
Hazard into a land of death,
Inside the sealed-off lab...
As it garners attention all across the New World...
...Luffy and the others frantically run
from the encroaching Shinokuni.
the Navy G-5 are attacked by Vergo.
...the Straw Hats finally come face to face with Shinokuni.
Caesar's ultimate poison is unleashed.
However, their only remaining escape route is through the door to Building R.
When Tashigi is in tears as she
witnesses her trusted superior
Facing instant death if unable to make it through the gate in their path...
It swallows person after person as it spreads...
Just when the crew's annihilation is all but guaranteed...
take down her comrades one after another,
Facing extreme circumstances...
...and closes in on the Straw Hats as the island is transformed into a hellish landscape.
...G-5 displays the Navy's pride!
a certain man from the Straw Hats appears!
...they finally signal the counterattack!
Law's life-or-death plan is set in motion!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Get to Building R!
The Pirate Alliance's Great Advance!"
"Tashigi's Tears! G-5's Desperate Breakthrough Plan!"
"The Treacherous Vice Admiral!
Demon Bamboo Vergo!"
"The Deadliest Weapon of Mass
Destruction in History! Shinokuni!"
"Launching the Counter Attack!
Luffy and Law's Great Escape!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!