All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
After surviving a fierce battle,--
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled
by the Four Emperors.
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts,
one burning, the other frozen.
one burning, the other frozen
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen.
an island with two parts,
one burning, the other frozen
and were held captive by Caesar Clown
who rules the island
and were held captive by
Caesar Clown who rules the island
After learning about
the ruler of the island -
After learning about Caesar's motive,
and were held captive,
by Caesar Clown who rules the island
Caesar clown, aka the Master's motive,
they are on the move to save the children,
and were exposed to Shinokuni,
a weapon of mass destruction.
kidnap Caesar, and escape from the island--
and all while trying to escape Shinokuni, the weapon of mass destruction,
But they broke out thanks to their ally -
But they broke out thanks to their ally
But they were reunited with
their crew thanks to their ally -
a Warlord - Trafalgar Law's tactful maneuvers
all while trying to escape Shinokuni.
along with their pirate ally -
a Warlord - Trafalgar Law's
tactful maneuvers
a Warlord - Trafalgar Law's tactful maneuvers
the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
and were reunited with their crew
I have treated him
as my young brother
and now they are heading
for R Building - gate 66.
they are on the move to kidnap Caesar,
and began heading towards the "R-66" door,
and now they are heading for R Building - gate 66,
and watched closely
over him as he grew up.
However, Caesar has let
Shinokuni flow into the laboratory.
the only door to the path of escape.
save the children, and escape from the island.
while Luffy finally got to
Caesar's research room
Meanwhile, Vice Admiral Vergo,
the base commander of the G-5,
What a shame.
and launched an intense battle to catch him.
Jet Spear!
appeared in front of Tashigi
and the others and...
I understand.
You've got to be kidding!
I know it's hard for you, Vergo,
Captain Tashigi,
you're gonna love this!
You can't tell me...
The floor!
but I need you to take care of Law there.
Run! Run!
...what to do!
Reinforcements have arrived!
I wanna make him wish
that he was never born.
Do you still wanna get hurt,
rubber bastard?!
What're you doing?!
The Vice Admiral came to help!
What tremendous hidden strength he has.
Hurry up!
Get me down!
Karakuni!
Tashigi-chan!
But falling through here
So kill him in a horrific way.
That's enough!
will land him in the slide to the
garbage dump deep underground.
You have to survive!
I can't breathe again!
"Luffy Dies from Exposure?!
The Spine-chilling Snow Woman Monet!"
Goodbye!
He'll never be able to come
back up unless he can fly.
Gum-Gum...
Vergo!
I won't let you do it!
I didn't expect him to
sabotage himself like that.
Smoker-san told me...
...Jet Pistol!
Goodbye!
...to help them!
--No, Captain-chan, it's too late!
--There's... There's no time!
It didn't work!
Th-That was fast!
I was pretty sure that I could
take my heart back from Caesar.
Vice Admiral Smo-yan
Blue Sword!
Don't be ridiculous!
and Vice Admiral Vergo!
Your colleagues are still
outside of the gate!
We have both key figures
of the G-5 here!
But I didn't expect you here.
Outta my way!
We're invincible now!
No means no!
Vergo!
Captain Tashigi!
No...
It's Vergo-san to you!
Yeah! Now we're safe!
Well done, guys!
Gum-Gum...
We certainly got our beloved
Captain-chan in our hands!
Run,
...Jet Gatling!
everybody...
Run!
D BUILDING - THE "SAD" MANUFACTURING ROOM
What's this?! A wall?!
Kamakura.
I'm impressed.
I'm in the middle of something.
Only you could break this wall!
Does it have to be now?
"The Treacherous Vice Admiral!
Demon Bamboo Vergo!"
Vice Admiral Smoker.
V-Vice Admiral Vergo,
did they do something wrong?!
Are you a Devil Fruit eater?
Even if they needed to be punished,
Dammit! You rubber bastard!
your Finger Pistol could kill them...
"Fists Collide!
A Battle of the Two Vice Admirals!"
THE PASSAGE BETWEEN BUILDING A AND B
What are you doing?!
Everybody, back away!
Are you gonna run?!
He is not the man
that you used to know!
Goodbye, Straw Hat!
Be as wild as you want!
I can't believe he broke
the wall of the lab
I feel like my hand has been bitten
I already have an idea of how to make
you people test subjects without fail!
For a long time, he has been...
and let the gas in.
by my own dog.
That Caesar guy does
such bizarre things.
B BUILDING 3RD FLOOR - BISCUIT ROOM
Law.
Look forward to it!
Captain-chan!
We got away for now
Wait!
but it's not safe yet.
I won't let you go after him.
You're right.
We have to find the children
Mocha, those sweet candies
are for everybody, aren't they?
If anything happens to the Master,
This is too much -
and head to R Building--gate 66 in hurry!
You're unforgivable,
you impostor!
even for a mischievous child.
Joker will kill me.
And then from this annoying lab,
Stop fighting.
You were too smart
for your own good.
Share and eat them together as usual.
we can escape.
No!
"A Mastermind Underground!
Doflamingo Makes His Move!"
People like you...
We shouldn't eat them anymore!
Hey, go faster!
Please stop!
You people!
...tend to die young.
When did all of you get on?!
You're a difficult girl.
Help us,
THE "SAD" MANUFACTURING ROOM
Hey, what have you done?!
Smoker-san!
Now it's too heavy even for me.
It'd be easiest for me to kill
you by crushing your heart
Yeah, we don't have any time for you!
I'm so sorry.
A lady is...
But you have to hang on.
We have no choice.
Who is it?!
...in need!
but I'm not gonna do that.
How could you say such a thing?
What?
Is there a compelling reason?
I know about you people so well.
I'll torment you slowly as I please
Yeah, we are...
The infamous Straw Hats.
and warp your smart-ass face...
...too tired and we don't want to run!
I'm happy to see you.
I heard the sound of...
...with fear.
That's the worst reason!
...a woman's tears falling.
Get off of me!
Who the hell are you?!
Your name...
I'm Monet, a Snow-Snow Fruit eater.
Like that time!
is Brownbeard, isn't it?
I'm sorry
Ready?
but I want to rescue
my son Momonosuke
No!
Wait a second!
You...
This thing
as soon as possible!
I've been running so fast that
the friction has burned the floor!
will shake up the New World.
R-Rescue your son?!
However,
Usopp! Brook!
since I ran a lot already
I'm catching my breath now.
I'll try to restrain the children here!
I just don't want to run anymore!
Get off, you fools!
THE PASSAGE BETWEEN BUILDING A AND B
You two, go find some
Sea Prism Stone handcuffs!
Hey, I didn't say "Okay"!
I'm pretty hot with my coat on.
Sea Prism Stone handcuffs?!
Stand up, Law.
Listen,
This is D Building!
Why?
Vergo is my enemy!
This is an emergency broadcast
You can hang it here.
Luffy asked me to find them!
It's too soon to die.
to all buildings of the Third Laboratory!
Great.
I know!
My enemy is Caesar!
The traitor - Trafalgar Law has...
I don't know why but...
I'm gonna take mine off, too.
Keep your hands off of him!
...just entered into the SAD manufacturing room!
C BUILDING 4TH FLOOR - CAESAR'S RESEARCH ROOM
Stay with me!
You can count on me to find things!
Don't get comfortable on my back!
I'll come with you!
I repeat.
If you're not hurt,
why don't you run yourselves?!
Damn! What does she want?!
The traitor - Trafalgar Law has...
I have to find Momonosuke!
Oh, it's my enemy!
All right! Let's go!
Wait, wait, don't close it yet!
I'm hungry.
Hey, bird woman!
Come on out!
I'm a samurai -
I don't get hungry.
The Vergo impostor  and
"Black Foot" are still in there!
I won't let you get away this time!
I won't let you go after the Master.
Brownbeard-san,
Caesar!
do you have anything I can eat?
It's closed!
It's too late!
Shut up!
This thing again! But it's nothing!
The other side of the gate
is filled with the deadly gas!
When we get to a soldiers' post,
D BUILDING - THE "SAD" MANUFACTURING ROOM
Gum-Gum...
Black Foot!
I will buck you all off!
...Jet Pistol!
"A Fierce Battle Gets Heated!
Luffy vs. Caesar!"
Young man!
Black Foot guy!
THE PASSAGE BETWEEN BUILDING A AND B
Hey!
Another wall?!
Are you okay?!
What's going on?
The Navy's...
Gum-Gum...
That's...
...cutie-san!
...Jet Gatling!
Oh, Black Foot!
Black Foot guy!
I'm glad that you're alive!
Thank you!
Captain-chan!
White Chase-ya.
What are those?
Shut up, you shitheads!
Captain-chan, are you listening?
This room's really disturbing.
Listen!
You need to keep your
hands off of Caesar.
I only accept accolades from girls!
Let's go ahead!
So he was making such a
deadly weapon on Punk Hazard
That's none of your business.
I'll be at a disadvantage
once we take advantage
while the island was
believed to be closed.
Hey, Black Foot!
of possessing each other's hearts.
Did you get hurt?
If nothing is done, the damage
will spread around the world!
Until I get my heart back from Vergo,
Hey, why are you looking away?
Shut up!
I only accept concern from girls!
you can't do whatever you like.
I haven't given up yet.
Let's get out of here
That was close!
I want you to follow my orders
What?!
and make a report to Navy HQ!
If I kept fighting with him...
What are these walls?!
while you're on the island.
Hey, bird woman!
What's the matter, Captain-chan?!
What are you doing?!
Understood?
If we can't escape from here alive,
Ten-layer Kamakura!
In any case,
what's wrong with that guy?
I'll take care of you later.
what did those guys who
saved your life died for?!
There are ten layers to this Kamakura.
I took the shortest way...
He's your superior, isn't he?
Why don't you just shut up
and grovel on the ground?
No way!
It's not easy to break the snow walls
That can't be Vice Admiral Vergo!
…as quickly as I could, I thought!
if they're layered one after another.
That was an impostor!
Where is he?!
Right, Captain-chan?!
What? Are you trying to buy time?!
Vergo!
I'm sorry.
Vergo.
I can break them all quickly...
Let's go!
I don't want the soldiers
to know the truth about you.
I bet so.
Soon, you'll see that they're very loyal.
Yeah!
I think you can break this Kamakura.
Damn! You're so annoying!
They admire you like a father.
Wait a minute!
I got ya!
If you think so, stop wasting my time!
What's that noise?
There is something on the ceiling!
Of course it's not him!
It's a serious breach of trust.
No, you didn't!
Don't get so hot!
Vice Admiral Vergo
I can't believe
is like a father to you all!
Flammable Type!
you're Joker's dog.
He wouldn't do such a thing!
I don't think I'm gonna lose you at all!
It's too late.
Yes, Vice Admiral Vergo is a kind
man who cares so much about us!
I'm not surprised.
I just saw them a few minutes ago.
What?!
What is that creature?!
I don't think I will win
if I fight you.
Miok Gas!
What did you do to them?!
I think that thing came here
along with the Straw Hats!
I don't remember.
Vergo!
However,
Hmm... Well,
You're heating up, Smoker-kun.
Straw Hat!
I don't know if that
was an impostor or not
the strongest isn't always
the winner in a fight.
Is it a lizard or something?
Don't tell me
but he turned pale
and went somewhere.
Why are you attacking me?!
I heard that there was a
dragon on Punk Hazard!
you're worrying about
those Navy misfits.
We have to get going, too.
I don't know yet!
But I've been told something fun would begin
We have to save the children
and escape from here!
if I kidnap you!
I'm a base commander.
Yeah!
I can do whatever I want
to my good-for-nothing subordinates.
You formed an alliance
with Law, didn't you?
We'll follow you, Captain-chan!
Did he tell you to do that?
It's a mythical animal
INSIDE OF B BUILDING
It's cold.
You can't trust him!
that Dr. Vegapunk created
for the security of the island.
She's like a block of ice.
I'm sure he'll betray you!
Plus, you're gonna have to die anyway
Don't do it!
Let go of me!
You can't tell me...
It didn't look so scary before.
since you know
who I really am now.
Law's going after SAD?!
You can't push me away.
...what to do!
Yes,
It's coming!
Do you still wanna get hurt,
rubber bastard?!
now there is no doubt
that Law is betraying us.
You're now in my embrace
and your power is diminished.
Karakuni!
He dodged them!
I see.
You will lose all of
your physical strength
to my cold body in no time.
I can't breathe again!
H-He's chewing on steel!
And eventually,
Yes! That's because
I removed the oxygen!
your heart will freeze
If you get bitten by such strong jaws...
and you will
Everybody!
Run to B Building!
die in your sleep.
You can't get me with
such a desperate attack!
THE NEW WORLD "DRESSROSA"
That's what I thought.
He flies, breathes fire,
and chews up steel!
I have treated him as my young brother
THE WARLORD - DON QUIXOTE DOFLAMINGO
(THE UNDERGROUND BROKER - JOKER)
What a creature!
and watched closely over him as he grew up.
Even if you've known them for a long time
What a shame.
So this is the distance I need.
I understand.
and even if you're a base commander
He's at the SAD manufacturing room, huh?
That's right!
which I don't acknowledge now,
It's only in a certain range
that you can't breathe!
What happened?
He's flying away.
once we're out of the base,
But are you sure
you can keep that distance?
Is he trying to escape?
Look.
an unit commander is
responsible for the troops' life.
He looked upset.
It's snowing heavily around you.
Did he get intimidated
by Captain Tashigi?
That's all I needed to know!
Don't lay a hand
Here is what I would do
if I were him.
He was very scared.
You feel very tired, don't you?
on my men!
Second Gear!
First,
That's it.
I'd destroy that room.
B BUILDING - THE G-5 AND SANJI
It's okay.
Just let it be.
Captain Tashigi,
you're gonna love this!
Gum-Gum...
I won't let you do it!
Reinforcements have arrived!
It feels good, doesn't it?
What's going on here?
...Jet Pistol!
The Vice Admiral came to help!
And kidnap Caesar?
Ouch! Ow! Ow!
There is no place to step!
Th-That was fast!
No, I would just kill him.
What happened here?!
Close your eyes slowly.
Hurry up!
Carry the injured and let's go!
How could you do that
to my boyfriend?!
Ouch, you bastard!
We gotta protect Tashigi-chan!
Now, relax.
Vergo!
Because Caesar is...
But...
...if you come closer,
you can't breathe!
Stop it!
...the only person in the world...
Don't be so friendly!
Again!
He's our enemy!
Good night.
Is it painful?!
That's just how people would
define our relationship!
Look! Here is the oxygen!
...who knows how to produce SAD.
But pirates are free!
Vice Admiral Smo-yan
When you gave the Vergo
impostor a blow, brother,
and Vice Admiral Vergo!
But if he does such things,
Blue Sword!
Get a grip!
We have both key figures of the G-5 here!
you looked so cool -
even I could fall in love!
I'll be in trouble, Vergo.
This is just the beginning
of the New World!
We're invincible now!
Yeah, you looked so hot, brother!
Shut up!
No...
Yeah! Now we're safe!
I said I don't need support from guys!
If Caesar gets killed,
no one else can produce that gas.
Stop calling a pirate "brother"!
I can manipulate gases.
Run, everybody...
Then it will ruin my business.
Jet Spear!
Even if you're immune to poison gas,
Run!
Chill out-in, Baby 5.
there are still tons of ways to attack you!
The tank exploded!
The floor!
You can't do that to the Young Master-in.
It caught fire!
Hey,
I'm not gonna forgive him this time!
How annoying!
that's not good!
There is a crack on the outer wall!
That technique makes me
unable to breathe.
I'm gonna kill
that asshole!
And what would happen next,
if I got into such trouble?
Again!
Another explosion!
Now, prepare to be burned and sliced!
What the hell!
V-Vice Admiral Vergo,
Hey-in!
Run, guys!
did they do something wrong?!
And after that?
Huh? What's wrong?
Gum-Gum...
Even if they needed to be punished,
You look pale.
your Finger Pistol could kill them...
Misfortunes never come singly.
What tremendous hidden strength he has.
Gastanet!
The gas is flowing in from the outside!
But falling through here
What are you going to
do with that cute boy -
The deadly gas from earlier!
will land him in the slide to the
garbage dump deep underground.
Law-chan,
What?!
Welcome.
Young Master?
That was close!
Run if you don't wanna die!
You know what he's gonna do.
Again!
He'll never be able to come
back up unless he can fly.
Go to hell, Straw Hat!
I've heard about you,
Law is rebelling against us.
Commodore Smoker.
I didn't expect him to
sabotage himself like that.
Right, Young Master?
Nice to meet you.
No!
I know it's hard for you, Vergo,
The soldiers of the G-5 are
rough and not very smart
What happened?
Goodbye!
THE PASSAGE BETWEEN BUILDING A AND B
but I need you to take
care of Law there.
Hurry up!
but once you get to know them,
The gate is closing!
I wanna make him wish
that he was never born.
This B Building is very big
Run!
they're not as bad as people say.
but it'll be filled up
with the gas in no time!
You're a pirate.
So kill him in a horrific way.
Why are you doing this?
Soon, you'll see
that they're very loyal.
I have to teach an asshole like you
Understood.
Stand up already!
I'll shoot a picture of his
dead body and show you,
who would hurt a lady,
proper "table manners."
Doffy.
That's my style.
Tashigi-chan, you have to lead them!
I'm too busy to be
bothered with your crap.
If you lose your way, you'll die!
With the camera I bought at Dressrosa.
Don't go the wrong way!
Where is Vice Admiral Vergo?
You didn't buy a camera.
He's not here.
Black Foot!
Come on, guys!
Where did he go?
B BUILDING 3RD FLOOR - NEAR THE BISCUIT ROOM
You're gonna die
if you're too slow!
Don't worry.
You're right.
Vice Admiral Vergo has to go home
suddenly sometimes.
I didn't buy a camera.
The candy!
Everybody! This way!
Give us the candy!
His younger sister's sick.
R BUILDING 2ND FLOOR - THE SECRET ROOM
You must never
eat that candy again.
He's "Black Foot"
of the Straw Hats!
Vice Admiral!
Why did he help us?
Stop it!
Shut up! Get out of our way!
Don't you wanna go home?
They're so dumb!
"Black Foot."
Then I'll cut his ear off.
I know it's hard
but you have to endure it.
They let Shinokuni in themselves!
I'm looking forward to see it.
But...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
I won't let you pass through here.
That's not what
Navy soldiers would say!
...letting them die there won't help
You can't go to the Biscuit Room!
bring my experiment show to completion!
Caesar. Monet.
Can you hear me?
Flanchet...
I don't think your house collapsed
because of our bombardment...
Move!
Hey, close the gates to Building C and D!
You're in our way!
Yes, Joker.
...Strike!
What do you mean by that?!
Joker?
Yes, sir. What about the one to R?
You bastard!
Keep that one open.
He's strong!
Oh, Joker!
I'm sorry.
The candy!
I want to lure them into
the first floor of R Building.
I'm responsible for their actions.
Wait.
You have to be careful with Law,
of course, but also with Straw Hat.
Let go of me!
Oh yeah?
Give me the candy!
The candy!
Then I want you
to take full responsibility!
That brat uses Conqueror's Haki.
They're trying to get to R Building -
gate 66 anyway.
No!
INSIDE OF B BUILDING THE
BROWNBEARD EXPRESS AND ITS RIDERS
Ouch! You're hurting me!
You...
Oh, sorry!
He could be of a higher caliber than Law.
Don't get carried away!
I don't want them to take
an unnecessary side trip
I didn't mean to hurt you...
I understand.
Don't get in our way,
you monster!
so let's just guide them!
Hey hey, that dragon
is out of control!
We will do anything
It's our candy!
Oh, are you really?
He's dangerous!
to make you satisfied.
He does look violent.
He uses
Brownbeard-cchi, run faster!
Vice Admiral Vergo.
C BUILDING - A GARBAGE DUMP
Conqueror's Haki?!
Damn!
This is the fastest I can run!
I can't stop them without hurting them!
Run yourself if you don't like it!
Now is our chance!
Let's go to the Biscuit Room!
We happen to have a
hot-blooded woman here.
Vice Admiral Vergo.
No!
He's coming!
About the report on the kidnapped
child from the other day...
Don't go that way!
I'm gonna send Baby 5
and Buffalo there.
The fire he breathes looks hot.
That was awful.
Don't say it so coolly!
Oh no!
Oh...
The effect of the Rumble Ball
is about to wear off!
When it's done,
I told some soldiers to look into it
Brook, do something!
you all need to come to Dressrosa once.
but it was an accident at sea,
as I suspected.
What?
We can eat the candy soon!
Yeah! We're counting on you!
Where am I?
Yes.
So it was a false report.
All right.
What?!
Wh-Wh-Why me?!
A false report?
I'm scared of the dragon, too!
It's hard for any parent to
accept his or her child's death.
C BUILDING 4TH FLOOR  -
CAESAR'S RESEARCH ROOM
Just do it now!
It's broken.
You're the oldest!
The candy!
So is this a garbage dump?
That's right! You should
respect your elders!
So they try to keep thinking
Clank.
Run! To the Biscuit Room!
that their child was kidnapped
to keep their hope alive.
I don't know what
the bird guy was saying
I guess I fell all the way down
to the deep underground.
We can eat the candy!
What?!
but I'm gonna catch Caesar!
Hey, kids, wait!
You will see
when you become
a mother someday.
What's this?!
Oh no!
D BUILDING - IN FRONT OF THE
"SAD" MANUFACTURING ROOM
I can't move!
Snow?!
Damn!
Is that how it is?
I'm hungry!
Kids, no!
Yes, that's how it is.
Come to think of it,
I had been running for so long!
If you take more of the drug,
Hey, we have a problem!
I won't let you do that!
What is it?
The Navy soldiers and the
Straw Hats entered B Building!
it will ruin your body!
Isn't there something to eat?
Please, everybody!
Then they'll get to D Building soon?
Everybody, back away!
Damn!
Stop!
Don't worry!
It's all garbage!
He is not the man
that you used to know!
Please stop!
Why is it snowing inside?!
Nobody can get to D Building...
Don't eat the candy!
I'm a snow woman
who ate the Snow-Snow Fruit.
Damn! Dammit!
For a long time, he has been...
Damn! Damn!
I can control snow at will.
Captain-chan!
I can't save them
because I have no power!
Be careful, you insolent fellow!
Captain-chan!
Who is it?
How do you like my power?
Chopper!
He's an impostor!
What's going on here?!
Vergo-san wouldn't do such
a thing to Captain-chan!
It's nothing!
It's just snow!
Nami!
Y-You're...
Everybody!
He's right!
But what about something like this?
Are you in disguise
or a Devil Fruit eater?
Are you all right, Chopper-san?!
Trafalgar Law!
What's wrong with those kids?!
Stop mocking Vice Admiral Vergo!
They've gotten more violent!
What's going on?!
Why is he here?!
Momonosuke! Where are you?!
Vice Admiral Vergo...
...always defends us
misfit Navy soldiers!
I'm glad that you're all here!
Tell us what's going on, Chopper!
Who cares!
He's a man of humanity and justice!
He's a traitor anyway!
Caesar is trying to turn them into giants
Stop mocking him!
in order to make them demonic
soldiers, just as we thought.
Gum-Gum...
Room.
I'll kick your ass,
you impostor!
I really don't like this room!
...Pistol!
Go to hell!
I can't handle them alone anymore!
What?!
The "secret room" on the
second floor of R Building.
You guys have to stop them
as soon as possible!
What's this?!
What happened?!
I didn't wanna come
to this shitty room.
What the hell?!
What did you do?! Hey!
The Biscuit Room is to the left!
You're unforgivable,
you impostor!
But I can't let the Straw Hats
do whatever they like.
The candies are there!
Mocha is the only child in her
right mind and she's helping me.
They pushed it a little too far.
I've got Joker on my back.
We were trying to stop the other children
Once they come this far,
I'll kill them all perfectly!
but we couldn't!
She is protecting the candies
in the room all alone!
Master!
We have been ready
to fight since yesterday!
So why did you summon us here
I've lost my voice!
We're here at the Biscuit Room!
Gum-Gum...
to the former office of
that despicable Vegapunk?
The candy!
...Pistol!
Please stop!
Mocha is in danger!
Vegapunk is also an enemy to us
Mil Fleurs
Help us, Smoker-san!
Gigantesco Mano!
since he caused the
accident four years ago!
Isn't there anything we can do?!
You can't run, Straw Hat!
Go forward while I hold them here.
Yeah, thanks!
Shouldn't we fight them?!
Get out of our way!
No, you shouldn't.
I can't breathe!
It didn't work, huh?
You people are the best soldiers I have!
He's so persistent!
They're not gonna be
stopped so easily!
I'm sorry
They'll stop at nothing
when they're in that state!
A lady is...
but you need to stay here for a while.
Who is it?!
I don't want you to shed
your blood for nothing!
Now I can breathe!
Mocha is...
Gum-Gum...
Kamakura!
M-Master...
...in need!
Mocha!
Give us the candy!
All right. Let me
explain about the plan.
I'll steal your breath!
When we close the gates
to C and D as I said before,
You can't breathe, can you?!
This thing again.
the only open paths left
You're slowing down, Straw Hat!
are the ones connected
There! There! There!
to the first floor of R Building
which is below this room.
Second Gear!
Gum-Gum...
The Straw Hats, the G-5, or the children.
...Jet Gatling!
Doesn't matter if they're our enemies or not,
There! There! There!
the only place those survivors can get to
is going to be the room below.
No, everybody!
I can't give it to you!
The candy!
There! There!
There are some air vents on
the first floor of R Building.
It's evil candy!
Die already,
Straw Hat!
The candy!
Is that...
So we can let the air from outside -
that is to say, Shinokuni - flow in.
Pull yourself together!
Where did she go?
Hey you!
O-One of the Straw Hats?
We asked Chopper-chan and
the others to help us!
Why is a pirate helping us?
Stay away from me!
And then there is no turning back.
Give it to me!
Who can survive that?!
No!
If we don't listen to them,
we can't go home!
When we close all the gates,
It's no use! Just run!
it will become a big gas chamber!
Run, Mocha!
We're gonna broadcast
what's going on in that room
I heard the sound of...
Hey, wait! That's no fair!
How annoying!
for all the underground
brokers in the New World!
...a woman's tears falling.
You Haki user!
Chase her!
B BUILDING 3RD FLOOR -
NEAR THE BISCUIT ROOM
So they will see
what I'm capable of!
Wait!
Open the door!
Are you gonna eat it all yourself?!
I'm not gonna let them have it!
INSIDE OF B BUILDING
I wanna go home with everybody!
Uh-huh!
I see!
I have to catch him soon.
Then I won't let anybody
eat the candy!
Sanji has taken off somewhere
making a serious face!
I wanna go home with everybody!
Before I get choked to death!
What's this?!
I felt a mysterious presence back there.
P-Pardon me for asking this,
Master Caesar.
Great!
Open the door, Mocha!
Oh yeah, Straw Hat.
Forget about him.
It's cold! I'm freezing!
You want to catch me, don't you?
Did you create that deadly poison gas?
Something is coming!
I'm afraid it's impossible!
No matter how strong you are,
The exit is sealed!
Is that...
What should I do?!
That's the dragon-san from earlier!
Yes, I did.
once I remove the oxygen,
They're gonna break
the door in any minute!
you won't be able to breathe
and will quickly die!
He looks a little different.
You don't have to
worry about anything.
Mocha, you better go!
Different? How?
Uh-huh.  But what are you
gonna do, Chopper-chan?
So,
I'm gonna try to hold the children here!
It's like Vegapunk's poison gas
The look in his eyes.
catch me if you can!
The sedatives have
worn off as I thought.
that spread all over the island
after the accident four years ago.
It's Monet-san!
You go and throw out all the
candies in the Biscuit Room!
Who is that woman?
Sedatives?
Oh, it's her!
Yeah, he's violent by nature.
So it freaks us out, to be honest.
She is the bird woman
that I told you about!
Okay!
It's horrible.
It's hard to handle him
without sedatives.
Monet-san, please help me!
"Black Foot" of the Straw Hats
Mocha, it's not nice
to keep it all to yourself.
I'll be counting on you, Mocha!
Plus, he's one of the smaller ones
that are newer and more advanced.
is fighting against the Vergo impostor!
Uh-huh!
You have to share
the candies with everyone.
We got to back him up!
They're faster and
much more resilient!
What are you guys doing?!
What?!
You better run already!
They're trying to block your way
and let the poison gas flow in again!
Let's just run for now!
What?!
Run faster!
INSIDE OF B BUILDING THE
BROWNBEARD EXPRESS AND ITS RIDERS
See? I told you!
Oh, she uses sorcery!
Master?
She's a Logia-type?!
The deadly gas is flowing in!
So she's our enemy, huh?!
This is...
Run!
A STAIRCASE IN THE MIDDLE OF B BUILDING
This dragon is more annoying
than that big one.
...an avenging battle of science!
Monet-san, why?
My people!
I see. So...
He's quicker.
Why are you lying around?!
...he's made out of iron or something.
Damn!
That day,
Stop that dragon!
I don't wanna fall behind!
I tried to stop...
B BUILDING 2ND FLOOR - AN EXAMINATION ROOM
Straw Hat,
...the mad scientist -
Stay out of this.
where are you heading?
Vegapunk!
B Building is sea of flame.
Oh yeah, where did the boy go?
I'm gonna catch Caesar!
"No! If such a weapon explodes,
It's our problem.
What about you?!
If we don't stop him and
You're the type of guy that
our captain hates the most.
I'm gonna sort things out with Vergo.
The boy?
what's gonna happen to
the people on the island?!"
one of these tanks
catches fire and explodes...
Uh-huh.
Is he with Caesar?
The outer walls will break and
the deadly gas will flow in!
"Stop it, Vegapunk!"
I think so.
He entered into the "secret room"
where no one is allowed
Don't get in my way!
Wait, you bastard!
If we let that happen,
and transformed into a small dragon.
no one can survive!
But the accident happened.
He's...
The boy named Momonosuke.
We've got to do something
or we're dead!
The brat who transformed into a dragon?
B BUILDING - THE GAS BALLOON LANDING PAD
I mean, "the boy"!
On top of that, he still lords over us
Wait, you all!
How did you know
about that, young lady?
as the head of the science
department of the Navy!
...quite strong!
I can't hold my own
Help!
I was watching it secretly.
when it comes to dragons!
Hey, "Black Foot"!
I'm scared!
It happened in the "secret room"
And he's considered the
world's greatest scientist!
Get me out of here!
so I didn't tell anyone.
The gate is gonna close!
I have a grudge against them!
I can't tolerate it!
Help me!
Come to this side already!
But I got here on the same ship
with him so I've been worrying.
I will definitely take care of him...
The poison gas is right behind you!
He's the cruel man who hurt you all!
Hey, stay away from the door.
No no!
I can't forgive that dragon, either!
Hurry up!
Let's go back with everybody!
Oh I see.
Do you think it's right that people
still call him the No.1 scientist?!
But he's doing okay.
You can have a sweet candy
with your friends.
What are you so mad?!
This laboratory is big and...
So let's go back to the Biscuit Room!
...there are various treatment rooms
Because...
and he's just in a different room.
Didn't you see his attitude
toward me earlier?!
Master!
Hmm.
That's why I want to prove them wrong!
Is he eating something?
What?!
Brothers!
Why doesn't he eat anything?
Sisters!
I didn't want to make a
weapon of mass destruction
Help me!
Why don't you give up
already, Straw Hat?!
No no, he's eating.
In any case, I have to
get out of here first
but I want to show them
that there is a greater scientist here!
Don't worry.
to go rescue the children!
He's fine.
You have two options.
Let me out!
That I am the greatest
scientist in the world!
Listen.
Don't tell anyone about him
Either you leave this room with
your tail between your legs...
Oh?
and the "secret room." Okay?
What is a child doing here?
He charged up to me
to eat me and...
...or face complete immolation.
Let me out!
Huh? Excuse me!
When the Navy acknowledges it
Uh-huh.
Be quiet!
What?!
and when I become the top
of the science department,
If you don't stop,
I'll shoot you!
He showed his disappointment
before my eyes! What an insult!
I want to show the brokers
Shinokuni's power in this experiment!
Weight Boost!
my dream will come true.
Stop it!
I can't stand it!
I can't believe one of the
children knows about it.
I can use my scientific knowledge
to bring peace to the world!
I really can't stand it!
Who is it?!
That's because you have no flesh.
I'll shoot you!
Don't move!
We have to let the Master know.
Bones are nutritious, too!
Killing you by fire is less than ideal!
Master!
Alright. I'll keep that in mind.
I'm sorry, Master! We should
be ashamed for suspecting you!
Kin'emon-san, let me do it!
Are you okay?!
Karakuni!
You're the savior after all!
What are you talking about?!
I never thought
Just stay back!
I'd come to this secret room myself.
No, I'll do it!
I'll do it!
I can't breathe again!
No, me (watashi)!
Master!
Me (sessha)!
A monster!
Me (watasha)!
Straw Hat, I'll let you go for now!
Oops?
Help!
Master!
It must be withdrawal symptoms.
So just...
Come on! Come on!
Calm down!
No!
Master!
Nin, nin, nin!
Oh yeah!
What are you doing?
Master!
The sedatives!
I will catch you!
Pretending to be a samurai.
Thank you! Thank you all!
But that's what ninjas do!
This will ease your pain.
But this is the only place I can pull it off.
You want to die, don't you?
Here he comes!
I'm gonna help you now.
If I can't breathe,
Thunder Trap!
Help!
It's all their fault!
I'll kick your ass in one breath!
Stop it, Caesar!
No, my (watasha) opponent!
You have to abort the experiment now!
Huh?
Wh-What?!
Good girl!
Breast-band girl!
What are you talking about?
It could've been a great show -
everything perfect and lovely,
I didn't know you used
ninja arts skills!
Armament Hardening!
It's done!
Stop calling me that!
and more befitting of the
world's greatest scientist!
Smell the stinkiest flower in the world!
If such a weapon explodes,
It's no use!
It's gonna work soon.
I'll give you the death
you've chosen for yourself!
Special Attack - Green Star!
what's gonna happen to
the people on the island?!
Rafflesia!
But they screwed it up!
Go to hell, Straw Hat!
Shut up, you boneheads!
What was I doing?
Straw Hat Luffy!
Where do you think you are?
And his crew!
You were pounding on the door.
This is the Navy's research facility!
The Navy G-5!
So, the long-nosed goblin
monster uses sorcery!
Trafalgar Law!
The Navy wants to kill as
many pirates as they can
Oh yeah,
I'll make them regret ruining my plan
"Monster"?!
I was trying to get out of here.
and what they need is a
weapon that will do it for them!
Cuarenta Fleurs!
Hey, we took you out of here earlier -
even after they go to hell!
Gum-Gum...
Cuatro Mano!
That's not true!
...Jet Gatling!
why are you back here?
Bow down to my scientific prowess!
They don't want a weapon
that would also kill civilians!
We came back here in
the Flying Gas Balloon
Hold!
Even the courtesan
uses ninja arts skills!
What's this?!
You're so dumb!
that the Master picked us up with.
A wall?!
Kamakura.
It's called collateral damage!
But...
He's falling!
I'm impressed.
…big brother and sister
told us not to go back.
Those who get themselves
involved must be stupid!
Only you could break this wall!
I'll finish him off!
No, let me do it!
If we blow away everything,
we can bring peace to the world.
Of course!
What about the other kids?
You're so...
Are you guys frustrated because your
scheme is coming crashing down?
Everybody's going to the Biscuit Room
You want to say I'm cruel?
Are you a Devil Fruit eater?
because they have the candies there.
Here he comes!
What?!
You've got to be kidding me!
No!
It is that important to you guys, isn't it?
Dammit! You rubber bastard!
You shouldn't eat the candy!
Follow my lead!
You're using the damn prisoners
What?
This thing?!
This is bad!
Corpse-dono!
as your guinea pigs
as if they're real trash!
Master, you must go.
This fight is meaningless.
Hey, could you take me
to the Biscuit Room?!
Foxfire Style!
What's the difference?
The incumbent fleet admiral,
Sengoku, is too soft.
You're right.
Flame Split!
Okay! I know a shortcut
to the Biscuit Room!
We're in the middle of
the important demonstration!
But Admiral Akainu would
want a weapon that I make.
Watch your mouth, you squirt!
Follow me!
What are you doing?!
Are you gonna run?!
Goodbye, Straw Hat!
If you finally get it, then go away!
He cut flames again!
Be as wild as you want!
Good job!
You're disturbing me.
Room!
CAESAR'S LABORATORY
Thanks!
I already have an idea of how to make
you people test subjects without fail!
Vegapunk must be jealous of me
because I'm such a genius!
Come back to me, my heart!
What the hell is Vergo doing?!
Look forward to it!
I heard he failed to turn
people into giants again.
The G-5 are my test subjects!
Wait!
Gavotte Bon en Avant!
It'll be a total waste if I don't kill
them with Shinokuni!
I won't let you go after him.
You can't make people bigger in a
short period of time unless you use magic.
Flaming Flash!
That fool!
If anything happens to the Master,
I have no choice.
So I kept telling him:
Block off the passage ahead of them
Joker will kill me.
He should just go kidnap some kids
and let the gas flow in
from the gate behind them!
That's the bird guy that
I saw in the war, isn't it?!
who are still developing
and try every drug he can think of!
Who is he?!
But Vergo is still there.
Did you call me "Corpse"?!
I don't care if that idiot lives or dies!
Caesar...
Oh, I am a corpse.
Just do it!
B BUILDING 3RD FLOOR - NEAR THE BISCUIT ROOM
Yeah!
That's it! That's it!
We did it!
It's a total victory!
Hey! Say "Bones are delicious"!
The Biscuit Room is down this way!
How annoying!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Let's go!
Hey, what's going on here?!
You puny dragon!
Don't fight!
The Biscuit Room is this way!
Do you think you can
talk to me like that?!
Trafalgar?!
Can I have the candy?!
Counter Shock!
Damn you! Damn you!
This is bad!
I'm almost finished making a weapon
Do an emergency broadcast to all buildings!
Oh no! Those are the children?!
Damn you! Damn you!
Hurry!
that you guys have only dreamed of!
Okay!
Damn you! Damn you!
Vegapunk!
What's going on here?!
I have a good reason to
hate him but, Kin'emon-san,
This is D Building! This is D Building!
We can't let them go beyond this door!
You're dismissed from the
science department, Caesar.
This is an emergency broadcast
why are you kicking the dragon
as if he killed your parents?
to all buildings of the Third Laboratory!
Mocha!
If you wanna save your friends,
What's this?!
Your eccentric behavior is intolerable
and I can't protect you anymore.
you have to help me!
This is D Building!
Okay!
This is an emergency broadcast--
Mocha, hold the door!
It was no worse than
having my parents killed!
to all buildings of the Third Laboratory!
Screw you!
The member of the Seven Warlords -
Don't do it, Caesar!
Trafalgar Law has...
What are you doing, Mocha?!
I have a message from Joker.
...just entered into the
Open up!
I wanna go to the Biscuit Room!
SAD manufacturing room!
Whoa! Th-That's...
He said "What a shame."
Both of you, get back on already!
It didn't work!
Listen!
Don't let them get to the Biscuit Room!
Or we'll leave you here!
I was pretty sure that I could
take my heart back from Caesar.
What?!
Uh-huh!
Please wait!
Open it!
Is that fool out of his mind?!
Hey!
But I didn't expect you here.
Once he opens that box,
Why shouldn't we...
there'll be irreversible
consequences even he can't avoid!
Oh? Hey, look at that!
Vergo!
...eat the candy?
Fools!
It's Vergo-san to you!
Vegapunk, the Navy, Straw Hat,
and these guys right here,
Because...
Is he...
That must be...
Now it all makes sense.
they're way less intelligent than me -
they're all dumb as a brick!
Wh-What the...
Now, let's do it!
Chopper has transformed
into a monster!
Ready?
There's another problem!
No!
Take this!
Wait a second!
The gate between C and B is closed!
You...
I've been running so fast that
the friction has burned the floor!
What is he doing?
He wants to kidnap the
Master and wants SAD to be...
The gate between D and B is closed!
B BUILDING 2ND FLOOR - AN EXAMINATION ROOM
Now I know what you guys are going for.
But that was...
No one can enter Building C and D
from B Building now!
...not fair!
You were gliding on smoke!
Okay, ready?
Run like hell!
Vergo!
Wait!
I told you to wait!
Here.
I'll say "Okay" when I'm ready!
Hmm...
I don't see any problem.
Law...
I'm in the middle of something.
I'm catching my breath now.
He formed an alliance
with Straw Hat for defense.
You can go back to the Biscuit Room now.
Does it have to be now?
Really?!
Hey, I didn't say "Okay"!
He joined the Warlords
to get to that room.
Yes.
Vice Admiral Smoker.
The candy is there, too.
Yes!
Listen,
Vergo is my enemy!
I know!
That brat!
My enemy is Caesar!
I was going to silence
you anyway, though.
He has a worst scenario in mind!
Oh yeah, where did the boy go?
Did you just say something?
Keep your hands off of him!
Who the hell are you?!
The boy?
Wh...
Uh-huh.
Is he trying to...
You better make your move.
Wh...
Oh, it's my enemy!
It's not so pleasant to watch...
...ruin the New World?!
He entered into the "secret
room" where no one is allowed
I won't let you get away this time!
...a scumbag like you!
and transformed into a small dragon.
Who...
Caesar!
The pirate -
...are you?!
The boy named Momonosuke.
Vergo!
Law breaks into the SAD manufacturing room.
The one who wields the powers
of the Snow-Snow Fruit: Monet.
The showdown with Caesar begins!
Deep within the depths of Building C,
which is said to be inescapable,
Smoker's rage explodes at the fact
that Vergo's betrayed his men,
He finally commences his plan that will shake up the entire New World.
Luffy is at the mercy of those powers,
As Caesar uses his Gas Gas Fruit abilities that previously defeated the Straw Hats...
Luffy finds himself in a desperate situation
and is then greeted by a small dragon.
and Vergo closes in on him
with overwhelming Haki!
trapped within a wall of snow,
But just then...
...Luffy launches a mighty offensive of his own!
The fierce battle between Smoker and Vergo intensifies,
and his strength is greatly drained.
The dragon calls himself a warrior
and has overcome a strange fate.
...the vile member of the Seven Warlords...
as Smoker puts his spirit and
pride as a Marine on the line.
The battle...
Meanwhile,
...who has been manipulating Punk Hazard from the shadows...
...grows more intense than ever!
Law is faced with danger, as well.
Because of their chance meeting,
Luffy decides to take action.
...finally breaks his Silence!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Fierce Battle Gets Heated!
Luffy vs. Caesar!"
"Luffy Dies from Exposure?!
The Spine-chilling Snow Woman Monet!"
"Fists Collide!
A Battle of the Two Vice Admirals!"
"A Small Dragon!
Momonosuke Appears!"
"A Mastermind Underground!
Doflamingo Makes His Move!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!