All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts,
one burning, the other frozen
and were held captive by
Caesar Clown who rules the island
and were exposed to Shinokuni,
a weapon of mass destruction.
But they were reunited with
their crew thanks to their ally -
a Warlord - Trafalgar Law's tactful maneuvers
and now they are heading for R Building - gate 66,
the only door to the path of escape.
Meanwhile, Vice Admiral Vergo,
the base commander of the G-5,
appeared in front of Tashigi
and the others and...
Captain Tashigi,
you're gonna love this!
Reinforcements have arrived!
The Vice Admiral came to help!
Vergo!
Vice Admiral Smo-yan
and Vice Admiral Vergo!
We have both key figures
of the G-5 here!
We're invincible now!
No...
Yeah! Now we're safe!
Run,
everybody...
Run!
V-Vice Admiral Vergo,
did they do something wrong?!
Even if they needed to be punished,
your Finger Pistol could kill them...
Everybody, back away!
He is not the man
that you used to know!
For a long time, he has been...
Captain-chan!
You're unforgivable,
you impostor!
Please stop!
Help us,
Smoker-san!
A lady is...
Who is it?!
...in need!
I heard the sound of...
...a woman's tears falling.
Ready?
No!
Wait a second!
You...
I've been running so fast that
the friction has burned the floor!
I'm catching my breath now.
Hey, I didn't say "Okay"!
Listen,
Vergo is my enemy!
I know!
My enemy is Caesar!
Keep your hands off of him!
Oh, it's my enemy!
I won't let you get away this time!
Caesar!
"A Fierce Battle Gets Heated!
Luffy vs. Caesar!"
White Chase-ya.
You need to keep your
hands off of Caesar.
I'll be at a disadvantage
once we take advantage
of possessing each other's hearts.
Until I get my heart back from Vergo,
you can't do whatever you like.
I want you to follow my orders
while you're on the island.
Understood?
I took the shortest way...
…as quickly as I could, I thought!
Where is he?!
Vergo!
Damn! You're so annoying!
I got ya!
No, you didn't!
Flammable Type!
What?!
Miok Gas!
Straw Hat!
Why are you attacking me?!
I don't know yet!
But I've been told something fun would begin
if I kidnap you!
You formed an alliance
with Law, didn't you?
Did he tell you to do that?
You can't trust him!
I'm sure he'll betray you!
Don't do it!
You can't tell me...
...what to do!
Do you still wanna get hurt,
rubber bastard?!
Karakuni!
I can't breathe again!
Yes! That's because
I removed the oxygen!
You can't get me with
such a desperate attack!
So this is the distance I need.
That's right!
It's only in a certain range
that you can't breathe!
But are you sure
you can keep that distance?
That's all I needed to know!
Second Gear!
Gum-Gum...
I won't let you do it!
...Jet Pistol!
Th-That was fast!
Ouch, you bastard!
But...
...if you come closer,
you can't breathe!
Again!
Is it painful?!
Look! Here is the oxygen!
Blue Sword!
I can manipulate gases.
Even if you're immune to poison gas,
there are still tons of ways to attack you!
How annoying!
That technique makes me
unable to breathe.
Again!
Now, prepare to be burned and sliced!
Gum-Gum...
Gastanet!
That was close!
Again!
Go to hell, Straw Hat!
What happened?
THE PASSAGE BETWEEN BUILDING A AND B
Hurry up!
The gate is closing!
Run!
You're a pirate.
Why are you doing this?
I have to teach an asshole like you
who would hurt a lady,
proper "table manners."
That's my style.
I'm too busy to be
bothered with your crap.
He's "Black Foot"
of the Straw Hats!
Why did he help us?
"Black Foot."
Flanchet...
...Strike!
He's strong!
INSIDE OF B BUILDING THE
BROWNBEARD EXPRESS AND ITS RIDERS
Hey hey, that dragon
is out of control!
He's dangerous!
He does look violent.
Brownbeard-cchi, run faster!
This is the fastest I can run!
Run yourself if you don't like it!
He's coming!
The fire he breathes looks hot.
Don't say it so coolly!
Brook, do something!
What?
Yeah! We're counting on you!
What?!
Wh-Wh-Why me?!
I'm scared of the dragon, too!
Just do it now!
You're the oldest!
That's right! You should
respect your elders!
What?!
D BUILDING - IN FRONT OF THE
"SAD" MANUFACTURING ROOM
Hey, we have a problem!
What is it?
The Navy soldiers and the
Straw Hats entered B Building!
Then they'll get to D Building soon?
Don't worry!
Nobody can get to D Building...
Who is it?
Y-You're...
Trafalgar Law!
What's going on?!
Why is he here?!
Who cares!
He's a traitor anyway!
Room.
What?!
What's this?!
What happened?!
What the hell?!
What did you do?! Hey!
You can't run, Straw Hat!
I can't breathe!
He's so persistent!
Now I can breathe!
I'll steal your breath!
You can't breathe, can you?!
You're slowing down, Straw Hat!
There! There! There!
There! There!
Die already,
Straw Hat!
Hey you!
Stay away from me!
How annoying!
You Haki user!
I have to catch him soon.
Before I get choked to death!
Oh yeah, Straw Hat.
You want to catch me, don't you?
I'm afraid it's impossible!
No matter how strong you are,
once I remove the oxygen,
you won't be able to breathe
and will quickly die!
So,
catch me if you can!
"Black Foot" of the Straw Hats
is fighting against the Vergo impostor!
We got to back him up!
What are you guys doing?!
You better run already!
They're trying to block your way
and let the poison gas flow in again!
What?!
See? I told you!
The deadly gas is flowing in!
Run!
I see. So...
...he's made out of iron or something.
Stay out of this.
It's our problem.
You're the type of guy that
our captain hates the most.
He's...
...quite strong!
Hey, "Black Foot"!
The gate is gonna close!
Come to this side already!
The poison gas is right behind you!
Hurry up!
Why don't you give up
already, Straw Hat?!
You have two options.
Either you leave this room with
your tail between your legs...
...or face complete immolation.
I want to show the brokers
Shinokuni's power in this experiment!
Killing you by fire is less than ideal!
Karakuni!
I can't breathe again!
Straw Hat, I'll let you go for now!
So just...
I will catch you!
You want to die, don't you?
If I can't breathe,
I'll kick your ass in one breath!
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Armament Hardening!
It's no use!
I'll give you the death
you've chosen for yourself!
Go to hell, Straw Hat!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
What's this?!
A wall?!
Kamakura.
I'm impressed.
Only you could break this wall!
Are you a Devil Fruit eater?
Dammit! You rubber bastard!
Master, you must go.
This fight is meaningless.
You're right.
We're in the middle of
the important demonstration!
What are you doing?!
Are you gonna run?!
Goodbye, Straw Hat!
Be as wild as you want!
I already have an idea of how to make
you people test subjects without fail!
Look forward to it!
Wait!
I won't let you go after him.
If anything happens to the Master,
Joker will kill me.
That's the bird guy that
I saw in the war, isn't it?!
Who is he?!
Hey, what's going on here?!
Trafalgar?!
This is bad!
Do an emergency broadcast to all buildings!
Hurry!
Okay!
This is D Building! This is D Building!
This is an emergency broadcast
to all buildings of the Third Laboratory!
What's this?!
This is D Building!
This is an emergency broadcast--
to all buildings of the Third Laboratory!
The member of the Seven Warlords -
Trafalgar Law has...
...just entered into the
SAD manufacturing room!
What?!
Is that fool out of his mind?!
Once he opens that box,
there'll be irreversible
consequences even he can't avoid!
Is he...
Now it all makes sense.
Wh-What the...
There's another problem!
He wants to kidnap the
Master and wants SAD to be...
Now I know what you guys are going for.
Vergo!
Law...
He formed an alliance
with Straw Hat for defense.
He joined the Warlords
to get to that room.
That brat!
He has a worst scenario in mind!
Is he trying to...
...ruin the New World?!
Law breaks into the SAD manufacturing room.
He finally commences his plan that will shake up the entire New World.
But just then...
...the vile member of the Seven Warlords...
...who has been manipulating Punk Hazard from the shadows...
...finally breaks his Silence!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Mastermind Underground!
Doflamingo Makes His Move!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!