All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,--
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts,
one burning, the other frozen
and were held captive by Caesar Clown
who rules the island
and were exposed to Shinokuni,
a weapon of mass destruction.
But they broke out thanks to their ally -
a Warlord - Trafalgar Law's tactful maneuvers
and were reunited with their crew
and began heading towards the "R-66" door,
while Luffy finally got to
Caesar's research room
and launched an intense battle to catch him.
You can't tell me...
...what to do!
Do you still wanna get hurt,
rubber bastard?!
Karakuni!
I can't breathe again!
Gum-Gum...
I won't let you do it!
...Jet Pistol!
Th-That was fast!
Blue Sword!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
What's this?! A wall?!
Kamakura.
I'm impressed.
Only you could break this wall!
Are you a Devil Fruit eater?
Dammit! You rubber bastard!
What are you doing?!
Are you gonna run?!
Goodbye, Straw Hat!
Be as wild as you want!
I already have an idea of how to make
you people test subjects without fail!
Look forward to it!
Wait!
I won't let you go after him.
If anything happens to the Master,
Joker will kill me.
"A Mastermind Underground!
Doflamingo Makes His Move!"
THE "SAD" MANUFACTURING ROOM
This thing
will shake up the New World.
THE PASSAGE BETWEEN BUILDING A AND B
This is D Building!
This is an emergency broadcast
to all buildings of the Third Laboratory!
The traitor - Trafalgar Law has...
...just entered into the SAD manufacturing room!
Stay with me!
I repeat.
The traitor - Trafalgar Law has...
Wait, wait, don't close it yet!
The Vergo impostor  and
"Black Foot" are still in there!
It's closed!
It's too late!
The other side of the gate
is filled with the deadly gas!
Black Foot!
Young man!
Black Foot guy!
Hey!
Are you okay?!
The Navy's...
That's...
...cutie-san!
Oh, Black Foot!
Black Foot guy!
I'm glad that you're alive!
Thank you!
Shut up, you shitheads!
Listen!
I only accept accolades from girls!
Hey, Black Foot!
Did you get hurt?
Shut up!
I only accept concern from girls!
That was close!
If I kept fighting with him...
In any case,
what's wrong with that guy?
He's your superior, isn't he?
No way!
That can't be Vice Admiral Vergo!
That was an impostor!
Right, Captain-chan?!
Soon, you'll see that they're very loyal.
Of course it's not him!
Vice Admiral Vergo
is like a father to you all!
He wouldn't do such a thing!
Yes, Vice Admiral Vergo is a kind
man who cares so much about us!
Hmm... Well,
I don't know if that
was an impostor or not
but he turned pale
and went somewhere.
We have to get going, too.
We have to save the children
and escape from here!
Yeah!
We'll follow you, Captain-chan!
INSIDE OF B BUILDING
Law's going after SAD?!
Yes,
now there is no doubt
that Law is betraying us.
I see.
THE NEW WORLD "DRESSROSA"
That's what I thought.
I have treated him as my young brother
THE WARLORD - DON QUIXOTE DOFLAMINGO
(THE UNDERGROUND BROKER - JOKER)
and watched closely over him as he grew up.
What a shame.
I understand.
He's at the SAD manufacturing room, huh?
Here is what I would do
if I were him.
First,
I'd destroy that room.
And kidnap Caesar?
No, I would just kill him.
How could you do that
to my boyfriend?!
Because Caesar is...
...the only person in the world...
...who knows how to produce SAD.
But if he does such things,
I'll be in trouble, Vergo.
If Caesar gets killed,
no one else can produce that gas.
Then it will ruin my business.
Chill out-in, Baby 5.
You can't do that to the Young Master-in.
I'm not gonna forgive him this time!
I'm gonna kill
that asshole!
And what would happen next,
if I got into such trouble?
Hey-in!
And after that?
Misfortunes never come singly.
What are you going to
do with that cute boy -
Law-chan,
Young Master?
You know what he's gonna do.
Law is rebelling against us.
Right, Young Master?
I know it's hard for you, Vergo,
but I need you to take
care of Law there.
I wanna make him wish
that he was never born.
So kill him in a horrific way.
Understood.
I'll shoot a picture of his
dead body and show you,
Doffy.
With the camera I bought at Dressrosa.
You didn't buy a camera.
You're right.
I didn't buy a camera.
Then I'll cut his ear off.
I'm looking forward to see it.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Caesar. Monet.
Can you hear me?
Yes, Joker.
Joker?
Oh, Joker!
You have to be careful with Law,
of course, but also with Straw Hat.
That brat uses Conqueror's Haki.
He could be of a higher caliber than Law.
Oh, are you really?
He uses
Conqueror's Haki?!
We happen to have a
hot-blooded woman here.
I'm gonna send Baby 5
and Buffalo there.
When it's done,
you all need to come to Dressrosa once.
Yes.
All right.
C BUILDING 4TH FLOOR  -
CAESAR'S RESEARCH ROOM
Clank.
I don't know what
the bird guy was saying
but I'm gonna catch Caesar!
What's this?!
Snow?!
Damn!
I won't let you do that!
Why is it snowing inside?!
I'm a snow woman
who ate the Snow-Snow Fruit.
I can control snow at will.
How do you like my power?
It's nothing!
It's just snow!
But what about something like this?
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
It didn't work, huh?
I'm sorry
but you need to stay here for a while.
Gum-Gum...
Kamakura!
This thing again.
Second Gear!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
Where did she go?
B BUILDING 3RD FLOOR -
NEAR THE BISCUIT ROOM
Open the door!
Uh-huh!
I see!
Then I won't let anybody
eat the candy!
I wanna go home with everybody!
Great!
Open the door, Mocha!
They're gonna break
the door in any minute!
Mocha, you better go!
Uh-huh.  But what are you
gonna do, Chopper-chan?
I'm gonna try to hold the children here!
You go and throw out all the
candies in the Biscuit Room!
Okay!
I'll be counting on you, Mocha!
Uh-huh!
INSIDE OF B BUILDING THE
BROWNBEARD EXPRESS AND ITS RIDERS
This dragon is more annoying
than that big one.
He's quicker.
Why are you lying around?!
Stop that dragon!
B Building is sea of flame.
If we don't stop him and
one of these tanks
catches fire and explodes...
The outer walls will break and
the deadly gas will flow in!
If we let that happen,
no one can survive!
We've got to do something
or we're dead!
Wait, you all!
I can't hold my own
when it comes to dragons!
I have a grudge against them!
I will definitely take care of him...
No no!
I can't forgive that dragon, either!
What are you so mad?!
Because...
Didn't you see his attitude
toward me earlier?!
What?!
He charged up to me
to eat me and...
Huh? Excuse me!
What?!
He showed his disappointment
before my eyes! What an insult!
I can't stand it!
I really can't stand it!
That's because you have no flesh.
Bones are nutritious, too!
Alright. I'll keep that in mind.
Kin'emon-san, let me do it!
What are you talking about?!
Just stay back!
No, I'll do it!
I'll do it!
No, me (watashi)!
Me (sessha)!
Me (watasha)!
Oops?
Come on! Come on!
Nin, nin, nin!
What are you doing?
Pretending to be a samurai.
But that's what ninjas do!
Here he comes!
Thunder Trap!
No, my (watasha) opponent!
Wh-What?!
Breast-band girl!
I didn't know you used
ninja arts skills!
Stop calling me that!
Smell the stinkiest flower in the world!
Special Attack - Green Star!
Rafflesia!
So, the long-nosed goblin
monster uses sorcery!
"Monster"?!
Cuarenta Fleurs!
Cuatro Mano!
Hold!
Even the courtesan
uses ninja arts skills!
He's falling!
I'll finish him off!
No, let me do it!
Here he comes!
Follow my lead!
Corpse-dono!
Foxfire Style!
Flame Split!
He cut flames again!
Good job!
Thanks!
Gavotte Bon en Avant!
Flaming Flash!
Did you call me "Corpse"?!
Oh, I am a corpse.
Yeah!
We did it!
It's a total victory!
Hey! Say "Bones are delicious"!
How annoying!
You puny dragon!
Damn you! Damn you!
I have a good reason to
hate him but, Kin'emon-san,
why are you kicking the dragon
as if he killed your parents?
It was no worse than
having my parents killed!
Whoa! Th-That's...
Both of you, get back on already!
Or we'll leave you here!
Please wait!
Oh? Hey, look at that!
That must be...
Chopper has transformed
into a monster!
Take this!
What is he doing?
B BUILDING 2ND FLOOR - AN EXAMINATION ROOM
Here.
Hmm...
I don't see any problem.
You can go back to the Biscuit Room now.
Really?!
Yes.
The candy is there, too.
Yes!
Oh yeah, where did the boy go?
The boy?
Uh-huh.
He entered into the "secret
room" where no one is allowed
and transformed into a small dragon.
The boy named Momonosuke.
The one who wields the powers
of the Snow-Snow Fruit: Monet.
Luffy is at the mercy of those powers,
trapped within a wall of snow,
and his strength is greatly drained.
Meanwhile,
Law is faced with danger, as well.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy Dies from Exposure?!
The Spine-chilling Snow Woman Monet!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!