Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Hey! I see the mystery mountain!
--A dragon graveyard?
--No! It's not!
Laboon isn't an ordinary whale.
He's a whale with a human heart.
Grandpa Ryu said going back to
his nest would make him better!
What?!
I can't see the top because of the clouds!
This can't be a graveyard!
"A Town That Welcomes Pirates?
Setting Foot On Whisky Peak"
Welcome to the Grand Line!
So this is the Red Line!
"A Promise Between Men!
Luffy and the Whale Vow to Meet Again"
Welcome to our town!
Apis...
To the welcoming town, Whisky Peak!
Grandpa Ryu was a lost Millennial Dragon...
Why does Laboon continue
to hit the Red Line?
Luffy?
Pirates! Welcome to our town!
He was all alone, for a thousand years.
This can't be for real!
Why does he continue to
howl at Reverse Mountain?
But he made friends with you, Apis.
The damn ocean really is
flowing up the mountain!
He said out of the
1,000 years he was alive,
this last year with you was his happiest.
What in the world is with this snow?
Gum-Gum Balloon!
It was warm just a little while ago.
I'll tell you... Laboon's story...
This is delicious!
Luffy... You understand
the dragons' language?
All right! Done!
Huh?
You're hopeless!
I just somehow know.
This is the man that fell
from the sky, Mr. Snow Barrel!
Geez, talk about half-baked...
But there's no doubt about it!
We made it!
You liar...
What fun!
That's such a crude snowman...
You're such a liar, Grandpa Ryu!
Yahoo!
What?!
If this is the dragons' nest...
Look at my soulful artwork,
the Snow Queen!
If you've made it back to the dragons' nest,
then open your eyes again!
Looks like there're about
100 bounty hunters here.
Whoa! That's incredible!
Talk to me!
Okay then! Snow Barrel Punch!
Get better!
One day, while I was on duty
as the lighthouse keeper as usual,
We're above the clouds now!
Grandpa Ryu wasn't lying at all!
I'll fight you all...
some good-natured pirates
We've made it to the top!
He said that Millennial Dragons
return to the nest every 1,000 years
came down Reverse Mountain
and entered the Grand Line.
What the hell are you doing?!
...Baroque Works!
Ahh! Mr. Snow Barrel!
and are reborn again.
Yahoo!
Humph...! Was it a secret?
How dare you...?!
And a small whale came in as well,
as if following them.
Damn you! Damn you!
Grandpa Ryu said that?
How is this?!
If you know our secrets,
There!
You bastard! Hold it, Luffy!
That was Laboon.
then we have no other
choice but to kill you.
All we gotta do now is go down!
The Island Whale lives
only in the West Blue,
How come they're so energetic
when it's this cold?
So this is the
greatest sea in the world!
and it's the world's largest whale.
Another gravestone...
The Grand Line!
The pirates had been traveling
with Laboon all that time,
...will be added to the Cactus Rocks...
Nami-san! How much snow shoveling
of love would you like me to do?!
but they left him in the West Blue since
the Grand Line is extremely dangerous.
A baby Millennial Dragon?!
Please continue until
it stops snowing, Sanji-kun!
"The First Line of Defense?
The Giant Whale Laboon Appears"
Kill him!
Yaay! Nami-san!
Hey, you. Doesn't this ship have a heater?
Although they thought they did,
he followed them.
I'm cold.
Island Whales usually
travel together as a group,
H... He disappeared...!
Shut up! You guys aren't guests!
Go help shovel snow or something!
Out of my way!
but I suspect Laboon felt that
he was a member of that pirate group.
"Explosion! The Three-Sword Style!
Zoro vs. Baroque Works!"
Lightning?!
What on earth is going on
with the weather around here?!
Whoa!! This is great!!
Since their ship had broken down,
they stayed at the cape for several months.
"An Angry Showdown!
Cross the Red Line!"
So we became quite good friends.
It was sunny up until recently.
H-He's gone!
The next moment, it started snowing,
and now lightning...
Wh-Where the heck did he disappear to?!
Because of that,
on the day of their departure...
Man, you're stubborn!
The seasons, as well as the weather,
go around randomly.
Yeah. I very nearly drowned to death.
I have a favor to ask, since I trust you.
Did you just hear something?
It's just like what Crocus-san said.
Could you take care of him for 2-3 years?
Huh? What'd you say?
That's how it is in the Grand Line.
Just look at this beautiful radiance!
Don't you hear a strange sound?
We'll go around the world
and definitely come back here.
It seems that you guys're
clueless about the Grand Line.
Isn't it the wind?
Isn't it marvelous?!
You haven't been steering for
a while now. Is that really okay?
There must be lots of unusual landforms!
--Ahh!
--What?!
Listen up, Laboon.
We'll now go into the Grand Line
and travel around the world.
I just checked the direction.
But you wait for us here.
Ahhhh!
All right then.
What's that?
Wh... What?
Nami-san! I see a mountain up ahead!
It's a dangerous place.
Shall we?
This is all Dragonite,
the legendary elixir of immortality!
What's the matter?
We can't take you with us.
How dare you mock us?!
A mountain?! That can't be!
What's wrong, Nami-san?!
Fire!
But it's really there!
Don't worry. Three years
will pass by like a flash.
Ahhh... No way!
But breaking these
fossilized Millennial Dragons
Who cares?! Go!!
Turn the ship around 180 degrees! Hurry!
Don't forget... that we're
buddies even if we're far apart.
won't produce anything usable!
After passing the Twin Capes up ahead,
there should be nothing but ocean!
180 degrees?! Why're we going back?!
Yes, so I hear.
Did you forget something?
But there is more than enough
live Dragonite here!
The ship has turned around and
is going in the opposite direction!
Hm?
Well then, we're setting off now...
When I looked away from
the log pose for a second...!
What do you say? A pointless
fight would only be tiring.
Oh, crap!!
Idiots! They shot each other!
The waves were calm earlier...
How about we make a deal
to split this treasure?
Guys! We're setting sail! Hoist the anchor!
H-He disappeared again!
It's not a mountain!!
Are you really a navigator?
It's a black wall!!
No.
Yeah!
Darn! Kill him already!
It's just a single swordsman!
No, it's not!!
--Do you not want eternal life?!
--Not interested.
In this sea, you can't trust the winds,
sky, waves, clouds... anything...
Then, what is it?!
I-I-I-It's a whale!!
You lie! There's no one
who's not afraid of dying!
Laboon!
The only thing that doesn't change is
the direction that the log pose points.
Laboon! Wait for us!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What're we gonna do?!
Both of us may have Devil Fruit powers,
Shall we fight?
We'll come back here for sure...!
Idiot! There's no way we can fight that!
Do you understand that?
but a pirate's life is always
only inches from death!
For sure!!
B-B-B-B-But, our path is blocked!
Stop bossing me around in those
cozy blankets and go help already!
There's no way you can't be afraid of dying!
What're we gonna do?!
Let me ask you a question.
I dunno. He's the kind of guy who'd
die smiling doing what he does.
Hold on a sec!
Brace the yard!
Are you sure that you need
to add only one gravestone?
Receive the wind from the starboard!
Turn the ship 180 degrees to the left!
If it looks like a wall from this close,
then where are its eyes?!
--Usopp! Take care of the lateen sail!
--Got it!
That's right! It's possible
that he may not have noticed us!
--Sanji-kun! Take the helm!
--Leave it to me, Nami-san!
There he is!
Oh...
Fine, then!
That was 50 long years ago...
You guys! I'm counting on you!
I-Idiots! Don't!
Are you gonna shoot me, too?!
You can sit there and watch
as I take my Dragonite and leave!
But unless we do something,
we'll run into it!
She's such a slave driver.
Stop! Igarappa!
50 years...!
Hey! We can get through on the left!
Hey, wait! The wind has changed.
Laboon has been waiting
for those guys for 50 years?
Port! Hard to port!
No way!
No!
Is that why he continues to howl
at the wall, hitting himself on it?
Stop right there, girl!
But the rudder is broken!
Do something!
Apis!
It's the first spring gale!
Yeah...
I'll help, too!
U-Usopp!
Why?!
Oh, yeah! I've got an idea!
D-Don't be reckless, Apis!
Don't just sleep there while
the snow accumulates on you!
Where did that man disappear to?
Even if it's reckless,
I have to protect them!
Luffy...? Hey, what're you doing?!
This is a very important place
for the Millennial Dragons!
Hey! I saw a dolphin jump
over there! Let's go there.
Phew.
This is an amazing canal.
You keep quiet!
I'm going to protect this
place forever and ever!
So that's a shotgun?
That thing sure is dangerous.
I'm surprised that he's still alive,
having a hole like this inside his body.
It doesn't work! The ship doesn't turn!
Is this also your playful mind?
It seems he's good enough
that even we must be cautious.
The waves are getting high!
--A doctor's playful mind.
--Doctor?
Dammit!
I see an iceberg in the
10 o'clock direction!
Don't give up!
I may not look one, but I'm a doctor.
So you insist on defying me, huh?
Nami-san! It's getting foggy!
I also ran a clinic on
the cape a long time ago.
What the hell's with this sea?!
W-W... We're gonna crash!!
In that case, you can all die!
It was just for a few years,
but I was also a ship's doctor.
Sickle-Sickle...
Really?
...Whirlwind!
Is this it...?!
Then be our ship's doctor!
Does he seriously think that
he can fight all of us by himself?
Don't be ridiculous.
I no longer have the energy to do
reckless things like you guys do.
It's hard to believe
that he challenged us
Luffy!
A doctor, huh? That's why the inside
of the whale's body is like this...
Cannon?!
even after knowing
we're with Baroque Works.
All right! Did it stop?
Then these are from the treatment...
That's right.
Hey! Water's leaking
at the bottom of the ship!
When the whale is this big,
it's impossible to treat it from outside.
I'll deal with him.
We have to patch it right away!
Got it!
--But, Luffy!
--I promised him!
Ah... We're screwed...
You're fine staying here?!
What kind of wimpiness is that?!
I'm gonna open the doors.
The clouds are moving fast!
This might be it...
You still haven't accomplished your goal!
What happened to going to your nest?!
My special seat...!
Don't give up by saying
you're staying here!
W-Wind's coming!
It's strong!
Of course I will! Don't worry about Apis!
It's coming!
There it is!! The real sky!!
Unfurl the sails!
That wind is too strong!
Ladies, please come closer...
If we take it directly, we'll overturn!
I don't think so!
Sickle-Sickle...
Everyone! Eat this!
Let's gather our strength!
Gum-Gum...
I'm gonna sing Usopp Cheer #721!
--...Whirlwind!
--...Pistol!
You're eating too much!
Hm? Miss Wednesday, what on earth...
So the welcoming town, Whisky Peak,
is the bounty hunters' nest, huh?
Shhh...
But 50 years....?
Oh, crap! The sail is gonna be torn!
Let's get out of here before it's too late!!
You can't hit me, rubber man!
Forget about things up here.
Go fix the bottom of the ship!
Those pirates sure are
making him wait a long time...
I thought it might be something like that.
What the heck is going on?!
There's another part of the
bottom of the ship damaged!
Idiot! This is the Grand Line.
Did he not notice the cannon
attack because his body's too big?!
Dammit!
Where did he go?! Find him!
Or is he just slow?!
They're dead.
Well? Are my wind slashes
sharp enough for you?
Who knows?! Anyway,
let's get out of here now!
No matter how long he waits,
they won't come back.
Run or hide wherever you want,
there's no escape!
The new recruits that I got in Loguetown,
Yubashiri and Kitetsu III...
Yeah, it's true that 50 years ago
Ahhhhh! My ears hurt!
Now, how will you dodge this?
the Grand Line was an uncharted sea
more terrible and chaotic than it is now.
Paddle! Just paddle!!
This guy's pretty tough...
This is a good chance to
try you guys out in earnest.
We have to get away from him!
Is Luffy in trouble?!
Why are you talking so hopeless?!
Luffy...
I'm going to go all-out!
You don't know that for sure yet!
Sickle-Sickle...
There you are!
Luffy...?
They might come back!
Die!
You...! What the hell did
you do to my special seat?!
...Wind Slash!
It's a very touching story!
Tsk! Dammit!
Rapid Fire!
A whale continues to believe
in the promise his friends made...
Ahhh, that felt good.
Right, pops?!
Dumbass!!
Yeah... But reality is cruel.
I'm not gonna run or hide!
I confirmed it using reliable information.
Fool! Go ahead and get chopped up!
First, I'll try Yubashiri.
They ran away... from the Grand Line.
Hey, no matter how nice the weather is,
you guys shouldn't be so lazy.
How was that?! Bring it on, you bastard!
Can't be... Don't tell me...
they left without him?!
It's light! This is a good sword!
We'd better be on the right track.
Shut up already, you idiot!
You...
Gum-Gum...
Ran away from the Grand Line...
Hm?
Why're you guys on this ship?
Does that mean they went
through the Calm Belt alive?
There he is! This way!
You're slow!
W-What?!
Hold it!
Even if they are alive,
We're heading to their town right now.
It's called Whisky Peak.
Looks like they found me!
Wh-What?
they'll probably never come back here.
...Bell!
He went up!
Seasons. Weather. Current. Wind direction.
You mean we're taking them back?
We don't owe them anything.
Welcome!
Whoa! That thing's dangerous!
They are all random.
Right, we don't.
This is it for you.
Common sense is useless in the Grand Line.
And...
Well, not like it matters to me...
...Bazooka!
The terror of the Grand Line
takes over weak minds in an instant.
Yeah, your faces say that
you're thinking bad thoughts.
Miss Monday!
What were your names again?
Ahh... That was an expensive drink.
So having weak minds,
they ran away from this sea
I-I'm Mr. 9.
--Luffy!
What a waste!
I win!
without keeping their promise
in order to save their asses...
I'm Miss Wednesday.
Right... Something has been bothering
me ever since I first heard your names...
You did it!
What was that feeling
in my hand just now?!
I'm not gonna die!!
They abandoned this whale?!
When he's been waiting for 50 years...?!
How sharp this Kitetsu III is!
I feel like I've heard them
somewhere before, or maybe not...
That's cruel!
A legendary sword cuts only
when its master wishes it,
If you know that,
why haven't you told him?
Well, either way...
but this one is a problem child.
So this is what a cursed sword is like.
--What is this?!
--Creatures like this really exist?!
That whale can understand
what people say, right?
How dare you sleep
comfortably all this time...?
I-It wasn't just a legend?!
I did tell him... everything.
You kept sleeping no matter how
many times we tried to wake you up...
Huh?
Lord have mercy!
Laboon! Listen up!
Do you suppose this place'll
sink again after a little while?
What?!
I heard that they left the Grand Line.
I beg you for mercy.
When it does, will the Millennial
Dragons leave the island, too?
Lord have mercy! Please save us!
You were certainly friends,
Don't let your guard down, everyone!
We don't know what else might happen.
and the promise they made
with you was certainly for real.
Merciful Lord Blinding Powder!
And I guess that baby Millennial
Dragon will fly off somewhere too?
I was finally able to realize
the danger of this sea just now.
You should use such a cheap trick
on someone with a pure heart.
I was able to understand the
reason why it's called the Grand Line.
What do you say, everyone?
Won't you have some of my
special pork buns before you go?
But they'll never come back here...
What am I gonna do?
I used the back of the blade,
so forgive me.
There's no doubt about it, since my
navigation skills don't work at all.
Oh! Thank you! But that's okay!
They've all been eaten...
We gotta get back to our
journey right away! Right?!
He went further up!
Hey you! Spit them out!
Give everyone back to me!
How blunt... Are we gonna be okay?
Corner him!
We do? I wanna eat some pork--
He's over there!
Cut him off!
Spit them out!
I'm saying give them back!
Oww!
Go around to the back!
We'll be fine! Things will
still work out for sure.
Okay!
We'll just take the recipe.
You...! You...! You jerk!
I see. That's too bad.
In fact...
Look! Our first journey is over.
It'd only take three days
to prepare them, too.
You're diving into the water,
aren't you?! Stop it!
Hey! I'm telling you to stop! Hey!
Did someone step on me?
I could tell you about the royal
family of Lost Island in the mean--
Please wait! Give my friends back!
We've already heard about it!
Mademoiselle, would you
care to dance with me?
Hey! I said stop it!
Listen to me, Laboon! They're not gonna...
We're gonna go on adventures together!
They're precious to me!
Alright! Set sail for the Grand Line!
Give them back!!
It's an island!
Apis. Want to come with us?
So this is Whisky Peak...
Huh?
I've made friends with you all,
and I would like to go with you...
I understand you don't wanna accept it.
But it's really a funny looking island.
Darn... Is this all the treasure they have?
Those cacti are huge!
...but I'm going to stay on this island.
But somehow you have to accept it...
Some bounty hunters' nest this is!
Laboon!
I'm gonna learn all sorts of
customs from Grandpa Bokuden
Hm?
Well then, we'll be leaving now.
Whisky Peak sure is a crappy town.
and protect the dragons' nest just
like my ancestors did before me!
Thanks for taking us home, honeys.
Laboon!
If we're linked by fate, we'll meet again!
There's nowhere to escape up there!
Bye bye, baby!
What do you think...?
I'm going to wait for the baby dragons
to come back here someday!
What do I think...?
Huh?
How should I think...?
H-H-H-H-How...
But those baby dragons won't
be back for another... uhh...
It's since then that he started
howling at Reverse Mountain
I was sure that we were
swallowed by the whale...
They're gone...
S-Stop it!
Who on earth were they?
A-Another thousand years!
Help me! Help me!
Who cares? We're landing!
and that he started slamming
his body against the Red Line...
Is this a dream?
Hey, now! Don't be so cynical!
There's a river at the front.
Looks like we can go inland by ship.
Yeah, it's probably a dream.
No, it's okay!
It's as if he's insisting that
I won't get to see the
dragons all grown up,
they'll come back from the other
side of that wall any time now...
The ladder's falling!
I-Isn't it possible that there're
monsters or things like that?
but I'm sure my kids' kids will get to!
Then, what're the island
and house doing there?
What a whale...
It's definitely possible.
This is the Grand Line.
When there's no point in waiting...
Ahh! He's jumping over here!
So I'm going to keep protecting
this dragon nest forever and ever!
They must be illusions.
He refuses my words
because if he accepts them,
If we come across monsters,
we can just leave the island.
Shoot him!
That's crazy talk!
it means that there
is no point in waiting.
Two-Sword Style!
Then this is...
He's afraid of that more than anything.
Hold on a sec.
You guys kept doing
crazy stuff too, you know!
Don't forget that we have to stay
on this island for a certain period of time.
...a Great King Squid!!
We did?
Hawk Wave!
He's from the West Blue.
There's no way of going back there now.
Why?
That's why those pirates he came here
with are his only buddies and hope.
Unless we store the magnetism
of this island in the log pose,
See ya, Apis!
we can't go to the next island.
Apis! Never forget about Usopp-sama,
the brave warrior of the sea!
Since each island requires a different
amount of time to store the log,
Watch out. That place is unstable.
But you know, it's true
that he is a poor whale,
What?
some islands require only several
hours while others require days.
Bye-bye!
but in a way you were
also betrayed, right?
Bye-bye! Take care, everyone!
Th-Then even if this is a monster island
that we want to escape from right away,
That was close! It grazed me!
Haven't you done
enough for him already?
it's possible that we have to stay
here for days until the log is stored?
--See ya, Apis!
--Bye! So long!
Look at the scars on his forehead!
Looks like there's at least someone there.
That's right.
I hope it's really a person...
If he continues to hit his head hard
like that, he'll die without doubt.
Bye-bye!
Don't try our patience.
Well, we can think about that
when it happens. Let's go already!
I've had enough. I wanna go home.
There's no man who can best my strength.
Luffy went somewhere, too.
What's gonna happen to us?
It's a strange relationship, but
I've been with him for 50 long years.
Luffy's right. Let's go.
It's not worth thinking about it.
This is the end of you.
Is Apis really gonna be
okay all by herself?
Come to think of it, where's Luffy?!
I can't just stand by
and watch him die now.
No matter what happens,
I'll protect Nami-san.
Hmph!
I'm sure Apis will keep the nest safe!
What the heck is this?
Huh?
She may be little,
Why is there a door and
a passageway in a whale?
What's that idiot doing?
H-Hey, wait. Listen, everyone.
My chronic illness is suddenly...
but she's got twice the energy
and motivation of a normal person!
When we looked away for a second...
Is he pretending he's mountain
climbing or something?
My "do not go to the island" disease is...
She'll be fine!
Superhuman...
You're right, Nami-san.
Then we're going in.
A ship...
Gum-Gum...
--Listen. Make sure you're
prepared to run as well as fight.
--No...
She'll be okay!
Sh-Sh-Sh-Shall we fire
the cannon at that island?!
Brass Knuckles!
Yeah!
...Flower Arrangement!
Ah, well... like I said,
my chronic illness is...
Because she's our friend!
Isn't that a mast?
No, hold on a sec...
She sure is.
Yep. It's from our ship.
Someone's coming out...
Well, I guess you're not listening...
It's the main mast...
Hey! Don't break the ship!
We've wast...
I wonder what'll appear...
Ma-ma...
We've wasted time,
but we finally settled it. The End!
P-Please...
Are you sure you didn't
want to go with them, Apis?
What?!
What the hell are you doing?!
M... Miss Monday!
I'd only get in the way if I went with them.
Besides, now I have
something I want to do!
What's the matter, muscle woman?
Hey, it's a pirate ship.
Didn't you want to have
a contest of strength?
I'm pretty reckless too,
but until I met Luffy and the others,
Well?!
Pirates are here!
Wha...?! Hey, kid!
Don't worry. He doesn't
die even when he's crushed!
I don't think I would've felt like
I could protect this island.
I thought Lost Island was just
a story and that it didn't exist,
Ha! Dummy!
--Ah?! It's a flower!
--A flower?
but Luffy and the others took
Grandpa Ryu on a search for it
Shall we continue, Baroque Works?
without even doubting its
existence in the slightest!
Fighting isn't a joke.
Oh, never mind. It's a person.
What does he think he's doing?!
What is he?
That old man killed a
Great King Squid with a single hit...
I get the feeling that they taught me
Was he just fishing...
or did he do it to save us...?
Luffy! What the hell
are you trying to do?!
that if you never give up on
your dreams and try your hardest,
your wishes just may come true!
Huh? Something's moving.
It's a draw!
Humans? Humans are there!
Everyone worked so hard and
risked their lives for their friends,
Everyone, be careful.
I'm strong, aren't I?
who all had a heart-to-heart connection!
Ahhh, dammit! Since it's come
to this, I've prepared myself.
And I'm one of their friends, too!
You wanna defeat me, don't you?!
Our fight isn't over yet!
So we have to fight again.
Monsters or whatever you are,
come on out!
So I'm going to try my hardest, too!
Your buddies're dead,
but I'm your rival forever.
He's asleep!
We definitely have to fight again
in order to decide who is stronger.
Say? Will you help me with my dream?
After going around the Grand Line,
we'll come back to see you again.
Say something, you jerk!
Thanks! Let's try our best!
Welcome to the Grand Line!
When I come back, let's fight again!
Oh, right! If you're going
to protect Lost Island,
Welcome to our town!
I-If you wanna fight,
we'll fight, you bastard!
To the welcoming town, Whisky Peak!
you'll need to know about your ancestors!
We've got cannons!
F... Far from monsters,
we're being welcomed!
First, there was the first king...
I-I've already had enough of that!
What's going on?
Hold on, Apis! Get back here!
Pirates! Welcome to our town!
M-Miss Monday was overpowered...!
Stop!
Hurray for the heroes on the sea!
You need to know about these things!
You'd better not, or someone will die.
I-Impossible! This can't be true...!
--No!
--Apis!
I-I got it! The Navy made a
mistake on that wanted poster.
Oh? Just who're you saying will die?
Whoa! There're lots of cute girls!
I see. It makes sense if this guy has
a 30 million-Berry bounty on his head.
--Me.
--You?!
Ahh! Look this way! They're handsome!
--Why, you...
--Well, calm down.
He's mocking us. That bastard...
He is the real captain.
Maybe pirates are
people's heroes after all.
Hmmm. This is good.
Hey, old man. Tell us where
we are and who you are.
Right. I thought it was strange
that such a namby-pamby guy
This is the symbol of
our promise to fight again.
Heeeey!
was worth 30 million Berries.
Until we come back,
don't remove that mark by
hitting your head. Got that?!
But, even so, how disgraceful...
Welco...
If we lose against one pirate swordsman,
Ma-ma-ma...
we'll be held responsible since
the boss put us in charge of this town.
Nami-san! I have a report of love!
All right!
Welcome.
When asking someone a question,
I see big rain clouds up ahead!
isn't it proper manner
to give your name first?
Hm? Where're those guys?
It seems that it's finally our turn to fight.
Those guys? Oh, those two weird people?
My name is Igarappoi.
I'm the mayor of Whisky Peak.
There's a storm under 'em!
Hm? Yeah, good point. Sorry.
Looks like we're back
on our original course...
You may know this,
but with members of Baroque Works,
Maybe they ran away?
I wonder who they were after all...
Okay. I'm Luffy. Nice to meet you.
We should be seeing the
Red Line at any time now...
--My name is Roronoa...
--My name is Crocus.
the smaller his number, the higher
his level and destructive power are.
Pops, you went overboard
on curling your hair.
I'm the lighthouse keeper
of the Twin Capes.
Whisky Peak is a town that thrives
on making liquor and music.
Miss Wednesday. What do we do now?
The three of us, Mr. 9,
Mr. 8 and Miss Wednesday
I'm 71 years old and a Gemini.
The Grand Line, at last!
Hospitality is the pride of our town.
Hmmm.
--Can I cut him?!
--My blood type is AB.
--Now, calm down.
In any case, we have to go back once
and at least report to the boss...
As for our proud liquor,
it's as bountiful as the seawater.
You're asking where we are?
Hey, Sanji! We're finally going!
We're finally going!
are agents with a single digit number,
Would you allow us
to throw a party for you
How dare you run your mouth when
you barged into my private resort?
Our estimated mission
completion time has long passed.
which means we're powerful people
That hurts!
so that we may hear your tales of...
Right. That's not good.
They'll make us out to be traitors.
who are beyond comparison
to those you just beat.
Sowwy!
Zoro!
Ma-ma-ma...
But is it really like how it's drawn here?
Humph. Aren't titles useless
when it comes to fighting?
Yes. Since we don't have
our weapons any more,
Does it look like we're in a rat's belly?
...your tales of adventure?
we'll go back to our
office and start over.
The stronger one wins. That's all.
We'll be glad to!
Stop that!
S-So we were eaten by a whale after all...
It can't be helped.
Well then, we... will...
All right!
But is this really inside
a whale's stomach?
Hm? Well...? What?!
Three idiots...
Say, by the way,
Wait a sec! What's gonna happen to us?!
What's the matter?
how long will it take for the log
of this island to be stored?
Look at this!
--It's gone...
--What?
I don't wanna be digested!
I'd heard the rumors about it,
and it's drawn on this map, too!
Log? Forget such boring stuff.
Huh?
Igarappa!
Hmmm? What the heck is this?
If it really is true, then the entrance
to the Grand Line is a mountain!
Please just rest after such a long journey.
Let's go, Miss Wednesday!
You dropped the log pose?!
Now, everyone! Prepare for the party!
Sing to entertain the adventurers!
Okay, Mr. 9!
I'm really sorry, Miss Wednesday!
A mountain?
We can't even go back
to our town without it.
--We gotta crash into a mountain?
--You can't be serious.
Come, Karoo!
Would you cut that out?!
Party time!!
I didn't believe it myself,
Haven't you guys heard of
the "repeating gag"?
As it stands...
but the map has canals
that lead to the mountain.
Ah!
That was a gag?!
I didn't say "give me your hand"!
Come over here!
The exit is over there.
C... Could that be...?!
That might mean we have to go up it!
We can get out?!
What?!
Now, show him your quick speed
that leaves leopards in the dust!
Hold on a sec! Why's there
an exit in a whale's belly?!
Neat!
That's...
What're you talking about?!
O-Oh, no...
Even if there are canals or whatever,
a ship can't climb up a mountain!
Why's the door in the sky?!
Who said "sit"?!
Wait... Look at it carefully...
--The Unluckies!!
--Darn it! Is it too late now, then?!
But that's what the map says!
--Mr. 13!
--Miss Friday!
This sky... Those seagulls...
What the hell is that?
Yeah! Nami-san would never
say anything that's wrong!
Can you afford to let your guard down?
Please wait! We can explain!
Follow my acrobatics, if you can!!
You stole that map from Buggy, right?
Can we really trust it?
They're all painted! It's all a painting
inside of the whale's stomach!
We'll report to the boss immediately!
Hot-blooded...
Huh?!
H-Hey! Someone help with the rudder!
Call it a doctor's playful mind.
...Bat of Guts!
You bastard! What the hell
are you doing here?!
--Sanji-kun! Give Usopp a hand!
--It won't budge!
That's enough. Leave him alone.
--I can't think with all his shouting!
--It won't move! Someone help!
Then I said with utter coolness,
"Sea Kings, don't you touch my friends."
These're metallic bats. Be careful
not to chip your blades on them.
Agreed.
Nami! There's an exit, so
let's get out of here already.
Yes, Nami-san!
Okay!
Yeah.
D-Doesn't this current
seem a bit strong?!
What's the matter? Are you
so frightened you can't move?
--Wow...
--Captain Usopp!
--You're so amazing!
Okay then! I'm finally drawing up the
plans for the Grand Line journey now.
Eh?! Usopp! What did you just say?
Well, regarding the Calm Belt,
even I trembled a bit, though.
What's going on?!
"D-Doesn't this current
seem a bit strong?!"
It's started...
Current...
--A tremble of excitement, that is.
--Whoa!
--That's it!
--That's what?
Look!
What happened to your proud acrobatics?
--Amazing!
--Cheers to Usopp-san!
All right! I'm finally cooking
the Elephant Bluefin Tuna!
That's not an island! It's a ship.
On top of that, it's made of iron!
They really do go up the mountain!
Now, please don't hold back, drink up.
If you wanna see it that bad,
watch carefully!
Are you still saying that stuff?!
Damn...! How dare Luffy
break the ship?! Geez...
Of course! It's because
this sea is gastric acid!
Ahh...
No, thank you.
I'd rather not drink alcohol.
Look here!
See? The guiding light was
definitely pointing to here
I guess that means that wooden ships
would melt if they stayed here long.
Don't worr...
on the Red Line... Reverse Mountain!
Hey, Zoro! Help me out here!
I'm not a shipwright!
Ma-ma-ma...
Hey! What's started?! Tell us!
Hey! Little help over here!
Don't they have anyone better?
Don't worry.
It's a special drink made of prime grapes
that are used to make prime wine.
See these canals here?
This whale has...
Anyone better? That would be me!
If major currents from the four oceans
all flow toward this mountain...
Be prepared... Mr. Bushido!
Laboon has started hitting
his head against the Red Line.
What's going on? Quiet down.
Its flavor is wine itself,
but it doesn't contain alcohol.
What's the matter, Nami-san?!
Now, take in my allure
to your heart's content!!
If it's food you're
worried about, it's ready!
Then the four currents would go up
these canals, collide at the top,
I see...
Oh? Meal time?
Th-The compass is broken!
You're right! This is delicious!
and then flow into the Grand Line!
We had a good grape
harvest again this year.
It doesn't point in any direction...!
Charming Perfume Dance!
Reverse Mountain is a "winter island,"
Ahh, you're right.
Now, to celebrate the harvest,
we'll have our usual toast competition!
It's spinning.
What?!
So any currents that
collide into the Red Line
Come to think of it, this whale
had terrible scars on his forehead.
Whoa! That's cool!
will plummet from the
surface into the depths.
That is, you continue to toast and
the last one standing is the winner.
Looks like you guys came
here with no knowledge.
He was also howling at the sky...
If we screw up and miss
the entrance to the canal...
What does that mean?
For heaven's sake!
Did you come here to die?
Please join in on our competition.
...the Going Merry will run smack
into the Red Line's rock face...
He's suffering!
No thanks. I can't drink that much.
--What?
--Meal?
Feed, in your case!
The prize money for the winner
is 100,000 Berries!
...and get wrecked!
I thought I told you...
...that common sense
is useless in this sea.
And then we'd be at the bottom
of the ocean. Understand?
I see! So that's what that
geezer's trying to do!
Another cup, please!
Good boy...
Oh! Interesting!
It's not that that compass is broken.
Zoro! You participate, too!
You don't have money, do you?
So, basically, it's a mystery mountain!
Likely... He's probably trying to
kill the whale from inside his body!
What?!
Hm? Then, could it be that
the magnetic fields are...
Cheers!
Now...
Well, maybe you don't get it...
What a vicious way to kill it...!
That's right. The islands in the Grand Line
contain lots of magnetic minerals.
I'll finish you off with...
Peacock Slasher!
Now that the mystery is solved,
it's time to hurry up and get out.
Anyways, now that we're on this current,
Whoa! Amazing! He finished his 10th cup!
If we take our time here,
we'll be digested.
Go, Karoo!
As long as we don't
mess up with the rudder,
This is it. I can't drink any more.
Because of that, they are causing
abnormality throughout the Grand Line.
we should be able to go straight
to the summit of Reverse Mountain!
We have nothing to say
about his whale hunting
Furthermore, the current and
the winds don't have constancy.
This girl's downing her 12th cup!
nor are we under obligation
to save the whale.
Nami-san! You're so amazing!
You went too far!
If you're a navigator, you
should know how scary that is.
Let's get out of here.
I've never heard of ships
going over mountains before.
Take that!
More food!
It's true that if we don't have a way
of knowing our direction, it's hopeless.
I've heard some stuff before!
Whoa! The captain finished
a meal for 20 people!
Stories about the mystery mountain?
Fighting these guys is
starting to get embarrassing...
No.
The cook is down!
Yummy!
I heard that half of everyone
who heads to the Grand Line
I-I didn't know! Oh, well...
Please, I can't go on...
Hey! That's bad! Are we gonna be okay?!
dies before entering it...
Whoa! This young man is trying
to hit on 20 girls at the same time!
This isn't bad. It's yummy!
Ahhh! Dammit! With the
waves surging like this,
I knew getting in wouldn't be easy.
Hey, you guys! Please just be quiet!
He escaped below using that hole.
What's with this gang?!
I don't know if we can
even reach the doors...
The nose of the Elephant
Bluefin Tuna tastes good!
It's really a fu...
We have no other choice but
to paddle! Take the oars!
That's useless...
--Sanji-kun! Could you get the sail?
--Yes, Nami-san!
You need a log pose to
travel around the Grand Line.
Let's leave quickly!
I'm worried about Luffy.
Ma-ma-ma...
--Luffy! Help out!
--Eh?!
Get a good taste of how
frightening I really am!
...a fun night!
He's outside!
I saw him fly out of the mouth!
I'm glad that you all
seem to be having fun.
Log pose? I've never heard of it.
That shotgun of his is a pain...
How should I close the distance?
It's a special compass
that can record magnetism.
That old man jumped in!
Is it a strange-looking compass?
Huh? What's he gonna do?
He's gonna be digested.
Ka-boom!
Yeah, its shape is unusual.
Yes, indeed, I'm very glad...
Is it something like this?
Yeah, that's it.
How dare you beat me like that earlier?!
Hey! I see the mystery mountain!
For that reason, we failed
our mission of securing food...
Without the log pose,
it's impossible to travel in the Grand Line.
You won't get away with it!
W-What?!
You fell on your own!
T-That's insanely huge!
Home Run Sneaky Bat!
I see... But hold on a sec.
However, we'd like to
report that we succeeded
The entrance to the Grand Line...
What?! What's going on?! Huh? Why?!
--Luffy?
--Hm?
Dizzy... Dizzy... I'm dizzy...!
in leading the gang
to Cactus Island. Baby.
How come you have one?!
I tied up one of your arms!
So that's the Red Line, huh?!
It's an iron chain...
I-I-I can't see the top
because of the clouds!
This is something that those
two weirdoes dropped on the ship.
All right! If we submit this, we somehow
should be able to clear our names.
You caught him.
They did?
Mr. 8, do it now!
Right. I'll drop it in the
Unluckies Box immediately.
Why did you hit me?
Just going with the flow.
I won't let you escape!
Oh, the flow, huh?
That's right. Don't move.
So this is the log pose.
There's no dial face.
If you make a stupid move,
What is it this time?
The sea? A river? A channel?
I'll have to take your
precious friend's life as well.
It's known that the magnetism of islands
in the Grand Line follow a certain rule.
They'll deliver it for us...
...to the boss...
That is, by recording the magnetism
of two islands pulling against each other,
This is it. I quit. I'm gonna sleep.
Good job, Miss Wednesday.
You can't escape or attack now.
Whoa! The young man is finally
down after his 13th cup.
you can find the route to the next island.
We're getting sucked in!
Since you can't even figure out
its location in this sea,
What?! You're hopeless, Zoro!
--Hold the rudder good!
--We're on it!
Okay. We've succeeded
in infiltrating this far.
That idiot! At least wake up
when you're being held hostage!
the magnetism record of the log pose
is the only thing you can depend on.
There're only two left.
Listen, Miss Wednesday.
They're at the 15th cup.
She's competing against the sister.
Prepare to open fire!
Behind those doors is the stomach
and that geezer is likely to be there.
At first, you can pick one out of the seven
magnetisms produced by Reverse Mountain.
You should quit soon,
too, for your own sake.
Preparations completed!
N-Nami! Where's the entrance?!
Don't be silly! I definitely won't
quit until I get the prize money.
We must eliminate him.
What?!
We're gonna crash into the rocks
if we keep going this way!
But no matter which island you start with,
Igarappappa!
Everything is for the whale.
those magnetisms will eventually
pull against each other
Is he a toy?!
Yes, Mr. 9. This whale is a
precious sweet honey to our town.
Ahhh! Thanks for the food.
I can't eat any more.
and link themselves to one route.
The crack in that cliff...
And the name of the island
at the end of the route is... Raftel.
Three cooks are also down!
Nami! What do we do?!
Glad you enjoyed it.
It's the last point on the Grand Line.
--Keep going straight ahead!
--A-Are you serious?!
Hey! The geezer came out!
I can't drink any more.
Forget about him.
The only one in history who confirmed
that island is the King of the Pirates.
Just do it!
More importantly,
how do we open these doors?
I won!!
Nami! Is that the canal entrance?
It's a legendary island.
Most likely!
Okay, Miss Wednesday?
Ahh, what fun!
This can't be for real!
Raftel...
We'll open the doors with
"Three, two, one, baby!"
She's finally down.
Igarappappa! Igarappappa!
Then, the One Piece is there?!
The damn ocean really is
flowing up the mountain!
Don't let down your guard.
Who knows? That's the
most prominent theory,
What a nice town...
Roger, Mr. 9. I'm ready any time.
Luffy! Let me use your belly!
but no one has been able to reach there.
This is a paradise.
What?!
We'll know once we get there.
We gotta make our way through
those water gates just right!
I can't stop!!
What is this voice, Mr. 9?
I don't know, Miss Wednesday.
Otherwise the ship'll
be busted into pieces!
Now that I'm done eating,
shall we get ready?
Did you eat this all by yourself?!
So they wore themselves out
partying and fell asleep...
Okay! Done!
Whoa! Even the bones're gone.
W-We're getting off course!
More to the right! Right! Right!
Log pose, huh? We have
to take good care of this.
The right?! Go starboard!
This is the key to our journey.
Sweet dreams...
Those guys're...
Ahh!
You damn rubber man!
It's finally become a quiet, nice night.
Huh?
C-Come on, now!
...adventurers...
I wanted Nami-san...
I wanted Nami-san to...
This isn't good, Miss Wednesday!
It's a sea of gastric acid below us!
Huh? Why am I outside?
...eat more!!
Again tonight the
Cactus Rocks look beautiful,
Oh, well. I'm sleepy. I'm gonna sleep.
dancing under the moonlight.
--Luffy?
--Hey! So everyone's okay?
The rudder!
I never thought that four agents
with numbers under 12 would lose!
Gum-Gum...
In any case, help me!
You're such a poet, Igarappoi-- no, Mr. 8.
...Balloon!
But where are you
planning to escape to?!
Oh, it's you guys...
Aside from Luffy...
there're two weirdoes...
In any case, we'll hide somewhere
until they leave this island and...
What happened to them?
Ouch! What're you doing?
Hey! That old man disappeared!
They've fallen...
--That'll show you, you damn rubber man.
--Sanji-kun...
Don't bother! For now, let's save Luffy!
Luffy!
Yes, Nami-san!
Ahh! The Unluckies!!
Grab on!
...to hell...
Both of you, go cool your heads off!!
H-Hold on a sec!
Geez... Since they were so stubborn,
I added a little alcohol in their drinks.
We're not running away!
It's not that...
Please! Don't report to the boss!
Hey, hold on a sec...
Wasn't that something really important?!
Otherwise they might still be
up and having a good time.
But was it really necessary
to put on an elaborate act...
We made it!
Our precious log pose was...
Stop it, Laboon.
Don't panic. I'll give you mine.
Hold it!
Don't hurt yourself any more.
I wanna thank you guys for Laboon, too.
There's only a little sedative left.
I have to make some more...
This town is quite lively
despite how late it is.
...for just five weak-looking brats?
Now it's just a straight shot to the summit!
We should've beat them at the harbor.
This town is already short of food.
Ha! What a boring job he gave us...
Hey! I wanna see! I wanna see!
That wall divides the world's oceans.
Ahhh... I thought I'd die. Hm?
...sending us all the way
to the front lines...
I'm unstuck!
Also, we didn't have our hopes up
for the whale meat anyway.
Even if you hit it until you die,
it won't break, Laboon.
Hey! Let me see, too!
You didn't have to say it like that!
We did try our best!
Here, take my hand, honey.
--Oh, thank you.
--Nice day, isn't it?
Calm down. Look at this.
I've checked them out beforehand.
A-Awesome!
Hey!
We have a favor to ask.
It's calmed down.
The whale is quiet now.
Th-Thirty million Berries?!
Seems like it. Now...
Them?!
Hm?
Whisky Peak? That's a weird name.
It's foolish to judge a pirate's ability
based on their looks, Miss Mon...
What's that?
We did save you guys for the
time being, but who are you?
Curse you all!
That's where we live... uhm, sir.
I can't fall in a place like this.
I've got an important mission...
--Huh?
--It's the Sicko Fruit guy...
What happened to your own ship?
--You!
--You're still alive?!
Mr. 9, they're pirates.
Ma-ma-ma...
It's busted.
--What tiny eyes!
--Shut up!
Miss Monday.
I-I know, Miss Wednesday.
How pitiful...
Curse the whole lot of you!
Isn't that asking too much, Mr. 9,
after trying to kill the whale?
S-Sorry.
...losing against just one swordsman...
B-But if we talk to them,
they should understand... perhaps...
Thanks to you, my dream of
Dragonite has been crushed!
But we've already settled.
Hm?!
So what are you guys?
I can't just leave things as they are now!
Mr. 5! Miss Valentine!
Looks like we can send
a good report to the boss.
You thugs're still around?!
I'm a king.
Confiscate all the money and other
valuables on the ship immediately.
At the very least, I'll have
your 30 million-Berry head!
Are you guys kidding around? Huh?
--Huh?
--Don't make me say this yet again!
Liar.
So what about them?
Just surrender to your fate
like a good little boy!
We can't say!
I won't let you lay a finger
on Laboon as long as I'm alive!
What do we do?
But we want to go back to the town.
After all, this is the difference
between our rank and yours, isn't it?
If we kill them, the bounty drops by 30%.
Now what?!
We don't want to be
secretive, either, but...
If he uses his wind slashes here,
there's no telling what he'll rip apart!
The Government wants
to hold public executions.
Did you come to laugh at us?
The motto of our company
is "mystery," after all...
He's back.
That, too, but...
Who's that pops?
We just can't tell you anything about us.
We can't act carelessly...
Huh?
Go! Capture them alive!
Placing confidence in your character,
we're begging you.
Of course, we're here under our mission.
Even if you say so, we can't leave.
Hey... Sorry, but...
Taking down this whale is our mission.
We will definitely return the favor.
Thank goodness. If you help us,
that man is no match for us!
How do you like that?!
You can't lay a finger on me now!
Don't do it.
We won't let you interfere with
our whale hunting this time!
...do you mind letting them sleep?
No matter what they say,
they're dishonest people.
That's right. Please beat
that swordsman right away.
We'll open an air vent in
his stomach! Let's go, baby!
Oh! Dragonite!
They're all exhausted from
the journey this afternoon.
By the way, we don't have a
log pose because we broke it.
Roger!
Huh? Enough with the bad jokes.
Do you still wanna ride with us?
What?! You broke it?!
That's mine, you know!
Us help you?
Mr. 8! Miss Monday!
Ah! Bastards!
Did you really think that
we'd come all the way
How dare you act stuck up
just because we're being humble?!
The guy with the bellyband escaped
from the room when we weren't looking!
You guys can't go anywhere, either!
to the end of the Grand Line for that?
He's over there.
Bye-bye!
Oh, but actually, we have
one that Crocus-san gave us.
You bastard...! I thought
you were completely asleep!
Oh! Good thinking!
That pops jumped
straight into the bullets...!
What? Then what mission
did you come here for?
Could it be...
that he protected the whale?!
He can't swim either, so I don't
think he'll be following us any more!
Swordsmen never make the mistake
of letting their guard down that much.
We beg you people of such character...
You really have no idea?
Dammit! This bitch tricked us!
There're criminals here that
are big enough for the boss
Given this current, being able
to swim wouldn't matter anyways!
Stop this pointless resistance!
So, let's see if I've got this right.
This is a nest of bounty hunters.
You can ride with us.
If you want to protect the
whale that badly, go right ahead.
to send us here to deal with.
Way to go, Nami-san!
What?!
Did you say Whisky Peak? Let's go there.
We'll turn it into food for our town!
These're the boss' words:
"They've found out my secrets."
You dupe pirates who are in high spirits
after having just entered the Grand Line.
What?
We're in the clouds!
Hey, are you serious?
We're troubling ourselves
to take these shadowy people?
Of course, I don't even know what
kind of secrets they are, but...
What's the problem?
Don't worry about small things.
Looks like there're about
100 bounty hunters here.
...our company's motto is "mystery."
What's going on?
But you can only choose the
route here, the starting point.
No matter whose identity it is,
the rule is that you never nose around.
I'll fight you all... Baroque Works!
Huh?
If someone finds out the boss' secrets,
If we don't like it, then we
can go around one more time.
You bastard! How is it that
you know our company's name?!
Awesome!
Luffy...?
that's, of course, a sin worthy of death.
I see...
When I used to be in a similar line of work,
I was recruited by your company once.
We're above the clouds now!
I just... felt like hitting them.
Now, shall we get going?
So, when we very carefully
investigated who learned his secrets...
Now I've made a promise with the whale.
Let's get ready to set sail.
Naturally, I rejected it.
Employees don't know each other's
identity and are called by code names.
Who on earth are you?
Me? I'm...
Oh boy, we found out that a VIP
Of course, the boss' whereabouts and his
identity are also a mystery, even to them.
...the man who'll be King of the Pirates.
Look! The summit! It's the summit!
from a certain kingdom
sneaked into Baroque Works.
I thank you for saving me... but why?
Baroque Works is a criminal group that
just faithfully carries out their orders.
I wasn't trying to save you.
I just didn't like them for some reason.
A certain kingdom? W-Wait a sec!
What a stupid pirate...
Humph...! Was it a secret?
Although I'm wearing a crown,
I'm not a king or anything!
Huh?
--Say, who are these guys?
--Hey, Luffy! What're you doing?
It should be okay by now.
The log must've been stored.
It's just my hobby!
This is surprising...
--What're you doing inside this whale?
--Hey, Luffy! What're you doing?
We're not talking about you!
--What're you doing inside this whale?
--Stop it! Hey, Luffy! Stop it!
The sinners are those who're missing
from Alabasta Kingdom right now...
Is it pointing at the
same direction as the map?
If you know our secrets,
Yahoo!
--They're thugs from a nearby town.
--Stop it! Hey, Luffy! Stop it!
Yep. It's pointing at Whisky Peak.
then we have no other
choice but to kill you.
--They're after whale meat.
--What're you trying to do?
It belongs to someone else.
They know! It's all over!
See ya, flower pops!
Thanks for the log pose!
If they capture Laboon,
Another gravestone...
it can feed the townspeople
for at least 2-3 years, so...
Die! Igarappappa!
Yeah. Have a safe trip!
...will be added to the Cactus Rocks...
See ya, whale! I'm leaving now!
I won't let you lay
a finger on our princess!
Laboon?
It's the name of this whale.
On my name as Squad Captain
of Alabasta Kingdom Security!
It's the world's largest whale,
called the Island Whale,
Igaram!!
To Whisky Peak...
...full speed ahead!!
Igaram, the Squad Captain
of Alabasta Kingdom Security.
which live only in the West Blue.
To do what Mihawk said...
Yeah!!
I won't let them have him as food.
To find the All Blue there...
And its princess, Nefertari Vivi.
To draw my perfect sea charts...
There's a reason he keeps
hitting himself on the Red Line
In the name of the Baroque Works'
boss, we'll eliminate you two.
To prove I'm a brave warrior of the sea...
and howling towards Reverse Mountain.
A reason?
Yeah. He's a whale with a human heart.
This isn't good...
I see it!
Kill him!
This is the greatest sea
in the world! The Grand Line!
I left Luffy down there...
I wonder if they're the pirates that
we've been waiting for all this time...
And he's been devotedly
waiting for a certain pirate group...
H... He disappeared...!
The One Piece is up ahead, somewhere!
That man has such
an uncanny air about him...
Go!
...for 50 long years...
Don't you think, Roger?
You've got me!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
Ah, gentle song
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
Make it there for us
I'll set off by myself,
After a wave washed away
that little sand castle
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
You looked up at the passing
clouds with a sad smile
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
If you find the world is full of enemies,
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I've got your back
Don't lose faith
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
You've got me!
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
Ah, my love
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
I'll hold you in my arms forever
With you, I can run there
You've got me!
Whoa!! What a feast!
The welcoming town is
a nest of bounty hunters.
Why do I have to help
Nami make money?!
Nami-san! I see a mountain up ahead!
There's a reason he keeps
hitting the Red Line?
Are you sure that you need
to add only one gravestone?
Receiving this kind of treatment
as soon as we arrive?
Who cares?! Go!
--Zoro!!
--What's the matter, Luffy? Oh, you too?!
What a strange whale...
No one's eating that meat?
I wanna eat it.
I'm glad I'm a pirate!
That can't be! It should be
nothing but ocean up ahead!
--So he's a whale with a human heart...
--Okay!
I'll beat up an ungrateful jerk like you!
Hey, don't you guys think it's weird?
It's a good chance to try out
the Kitetsu III and Yubashiri
When he says "Okay!" nothing
good usually comes of it.
Huh? A black wall?
There're many cute girls, too!
What're you talking about?!
Crap! We gotta do
something before we crash!
I got in Loguetown.
Shut up! I won't forgive you! Fight me!
The entire town is welcoming us...
What do you think, Nami?
Ladies, please come closer.
H-Hey, look!
--No! This is...!
--A whale!
What's he thinking?
When it comes to a drinking game,
I won't lose! Bring it on!
Are you really serious?!
I'm Captain Usopp!
A whale?!
Now how is this?
What're you doing?!
I'm going to go all-out!
On the next episode of One Piece!
You too?!
"All-Out Battle! Luffy vs. Zoro,
Mysterious Grand Duel!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Promise Between Men!
Luffy and the Whale Vow to Meet Again"
"The First Line of Defense?
The Giant Whale Laboon Appears"
"A Town That Welcomes Pirates?
Setting Foot on Whisky Peak"
"Explosion! The Three-Sword Style!
Zoro vs. Baroque Works!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!