All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled
by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts,
one burning, the other frozen.
After learning about
the ruler of the island -
Caesar clown, aka the Master's motive,
and all while trying to escape Shinokuni, the weapon of mass destruction,
along with their pirate ally -
the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
they are on the move to kidnap Caesar,
save the children, and escape from the island.
Jet Spear!
The floor!
What tremendous hidden strength he has.
But falling through here
will land him in the slide to the
garbage dump deep underground.
He'll never be able to come
back up unless he can fly.
I didn't expect him to
sabotage himself like that.
Goodbye!
It didn't work!
I was pretty sure that I could
take my heart back from Caesar.
But I didn't expect you here.
Vergo!
It's Vergo-san to you!
I'm in the middle of something.
Does it have to be now?
Vice Admiral Smoker.
"Fists Collide!
A Battle of the Two Vice Admirals!"
B BUILDING 3RD FLOOR - BISCUIT ROOM
Mocha, those sweet candies
are for everybody, aren't they?
Stop fighting.
Share and eat them together as usual.
No!
We shouldn't eat them anymore!
You're a difficult girl.
Hey, what have you done?!
Yeah, we don't have any time for you!
How could you say such a thing?
I know about you people so well.
The infamous Straw Hats.
I'm happy to see you.
Who the hell are you?!
I'm Monet, a Snow-Snow Fruit eater.
Usopp! Brook!
I'll try to restrain the children here!
You two, go find some
Sea Prism Stone handcuffs!
Sea Prism Stone handcuffs?!
Why?
Luffy asked me to find them!
I don't know why but...
You can count on me to find things!
I'll come with you!
I have to find Momonosuke!
All right! Let's go!
D BUILDING - THE "SAD" MANUFACTURING ROOM
What are those?
This room's really disturbing.
That's none of your business.
Hey, why are you looking away?
I haven't given up yet.
I'll take care of you later.
Why don't you just shut up
and grovel on the ground?
Vergo.
I don't want the soldiers
to know the truth about you.
They admire you like a father.
It's a serious breach of trust.
I can't believe
you're Joker's dog.
It's too late.
I just saw them a few minutes ago.
What did you do to them?!
I don't remember.
Vergo!
You're heating up, Smoker-kun.
Don't tell me
you're worrying about
those Navy misfits.
I'm a base commander.
I can do whatever I want
to my good-for-nothing subordinates.
Plus, you're gonna have to die anyway
since you know
who I really am now.
Even if you've known them for a long time
and even if you're a base commander
which I don't acknowledge now,
once we're out of the base,
an unit commander is
responsible for the troops' life.
Don't lay a hand
on my men!
B BUILDING - THE G-5 AND SANJI
What's going on here?
Ouch! Ow! Ow!
There is no place to step!
What happened here?!
Hurry up!
Carry the injured and let's go!
We gotta protect Tashigi-chan!
Stop it!
Don't be so friendly!
He's our enemy!
That's just how people would
define our relationship!
But pirates are free!
When you gave the Vergo
impostor a blow, brother,
you looked so cool -
even I could fall in love!
Yeah, you looked so hot, brother!
Shut up!
I said I don't need support from guys!
Stop calling a pirate "brother"!
The tank exploded!
It caught fire!
Hey,
that's not good!
There is a crack on the outer wall!
Another explosion!
What the hell!
Run, guys!
Huh? What's wrong?
You look pale.
The gas is flowing in from the outside!
The deadly gas from earlier!
What?!
Run if you don't wanna die!
No!
This B Building is very big
but it'll be filled up
with the gas in no time!
Stand up already!
Tashigi-chan, you have to lead them!
If you lose your way, you'll die!
Don't go the wrong way!
Black Foot!
Come on, guys!
You're gonna die
if you're too slow!
Everybody! This way!
R BUILDING 2ND FLOOR - THE SECRET ROOM
They're so dumb!
They let Shinokuni in themselves!
But...
...letting them die there won't help
bring my experiment show to completion!
Hey, close the gates to Building C and D!
Yes, sir. What about the one to R?
Keep that one open.
I want to lure them into
the first floor of R Building.
They're trying to get to R Building -
gate 66 anyway.
I don't want them to take
an unnecessary side trip
so let's just guide them!
C BUILDING - A GARBAGE DUMP
That was awful.
Where am I?
It's broken.
So is this a garbage dump?
I guess I fell all the way down
to the deep underground.
I'm hungry!
Come to think of it,
I had been running for so long!
Isn't there something to eat?
Damn!
It's all garbage!
Be careful, you insolent fellow!
I really don't like this room!
The "secret room" on the
second floor of R Building.
I didn't wanna come
to this shitty room.
But I can't let the Straw Hats
do whatever they like.
They pushed it a little too far.
I've got Joker on my back.
Once they come this far,
I'll kill them all perfectly!
Master!
We have been ready
to fight since yesterday!
So why did you summon us here
to the former office of
that despicable Vegapunk?
Vegapunk is also an enemy to us
since he caused the
accident four years ago!
Isn't there anything we can do?!
Shouldn't we fight them?!
No, you shouldn't.
You people are the best soldiers I have!
I don't want you to shed
your blood for nothing!
M-Master...
All right. Let me
explain about the plan.
When we close the gates
to C and D as I said before,
the only open paths left
are the ones connected
to the first floor of R Building
which is below this room.
The Straw Hats, the G-5, or the children.
Doesn't matter if they're our enemies or not,
the only place those survivors can get to
is going to be the room below.
There are some air vents on
the first floor of R Building.
So we can let the air from outside -
that is to say, Shinokuni - flow in.
And then there is no turning back.
Who can survive that?!
When we close all the gates,
it will become a big gas chamber!
We're gonna broadcast
what's going on in that room
for all the underground
brokers in the New World!
So they will see
what I'm capable of!
P-Pardon me for asking this,
Master Caesar.
Did you create that deadly poison gas?
Yes, I did.
It's like Vegapunk's poison gas
that spread all over the island
after the accident four years ago.
So it freaks us out, to be honest.
It's horrible.
Master?
This is...
...an avenging battle of science!
My people!
That day,
I tried to stop...
...the mad scientist -
Vegapunk!
"No! If such a weapon explodes,
what's gonna happen to
the people on the island?!"
"Stop it, Vegapunk!"
But the accident happened.
On top of that, he still lords over us
as the head of the science
department of the Navy!
And he's considered the
world's greatest scientist!
I can't tolerate it!
He's the cruel man who hurt you all!
Do you think it's right that people
still call him the No.1 scientist?!
Master!
That's why I want to prove them wrong!
I didn't want to make a
weapon of mass destruction
but I want to show them
that there is a greater scientist here!
That I am the greatest
scientist in the world!
When the Navy acknowledges it
and when I become the top
of the science department,
my dream will come true.
I can use my scientific knowledge
to bring peace to the world!
Master!
I'm sorry, Master! We should
be ashamed for suspecting you!
You're the savior after all!
Master!
Thank you! Thank you all!
Stop it, Caesar!
You have to abort the experiment now!
If such a weapon explodes,
what's gonna happen to
the people on the island?!
Shut up, you boneheads!
Where do you think you are?
This is the Navy's research facility!
The Navy wants to kill as
many pirates as they can
and what they need is a
weapon that will do it for them!
That's not true!
They don't want a weapon
that would also kill civilians!
You're so dumb!
It's called collateral damage!
Those who get themselves
involved must be stupid!
If we blow away everything,
we can bring peace to the world.
You're so...
You want to say I'm cruel?
You've got to be kidding me!
You're using the damn prisoners
as your guinea pigs
as if they're real trash!
What's the difference?
The incumbent fleet admiral,
Sengoku, is too soft.
But Admiral Akainu would
want a weapon that I make.
If you finally get it, then go away!
You're disturbing me.
Vegapunk must be jealous of me
because I'm such a genius!
I heard he failed to turn
people into giants again.
You can't make people bigger in a
short period of time unless you use magic.
So I kept telling him:
He should just go kidnap some kids
who are still developing
and try every drug he can think of!
Caesar...
That's it! That's it!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Don't fight!
Do you think you can
talk to me like that?!
I'm almost finished making a weapon
that you guys have only dreamed of!
Vegapunk!
What's going on here?!
You're dismissed from the
science department, Caesar.
Your eccentric behavior is intolerable
and I can't protect you anymore.
Screw you!
Don't do it, Caesar!
Fools!
Vegapunk, the Navy, Straw Hat,
and these guys right here,
they're way less intelligent than me -
they're all dumb as a brick!
Now, let's do it!
The gate between C and B is closed!
The gate between D and B is closed!
No one can enter Building C and D
from B Building now!
Run like hell!
Did you just say something?
Who the hell are you?!
Wh...
Who...
...are you?!
Deep within the depths of Building C,
which is said to be inescapable,
Luffy finds himself in a desperate situation
and is then greeted by a small dragon.
The dragon calls himself a warrior
and has overcome a strange fate.
Because of their chance meeting,
Luffy decides to take action.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Small Dragon!
Momonosuke Appears!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!