All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled
by the Four Emperors.
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
the harshest sea ruled
by the Four Emperors.
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts,
one burning, the other frozen.
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen
an island with two parts,
one burning, the other frozen.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen.
burning, the other frozen
and learned about the ruler of the
island - Caesar Clown's motive.
After learning about the ruler of
the island - Caesar Clown's motive,
After learning about the ruler of the island -
Caesar Clown, aka the Master's motive,
After learning about the ruler of
the island - Caesar Clown's motive,
and learned about the ruler of the
island - Caesar Clown's motive.
and all while trying to escape Shinokuni,
All while trying to escape Shinokuni,
along with their pirate ally -
and all while trying to escape Shinokuni,
Now, get off, children!
along with their pirate ally -
along with their pirate ally
- the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
This is your home!
along with their pirate ally
- the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
they are on the move to kidnap Caesar,
Luffy and the others are on
the move to kidnap Caesar,
Don't ever go out on your own!
save the children,
they are on the move to kidnap
Caesar, save the children,
save the children,
My head hurts!
and escape from the island.
-- save the children, and
escape from the island.
and escape from the island.
Master, give me the candy now!
After falling into a garbage dump,
Did you just say something?
Give us the candy!
and escape from the island.
Of course, you can have it soon.
Luffy met a dragon named Momonosuke -
Who the hell are you?!
--No!
--Give it to us!
Relax and enjoy the candies in the room!
who has the same name as the boy that
the samurai Kin'emon was looking for.
No, you can't have it!
Shut up!
What a shame.
Who are you?!
They are very, very delicious!
Why are you trying to attack the weak ones?
Just give us the candy already!
Wh-What?!
All while trying to escape Shinokuni,
Hey, wait!
What is she thinking?!
"A Small Dragon!
Momonosuke Appears!"
No, spit them all out!
Mocha, can you hear me?!
along with their pirate ally
- the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
We're... flying!
Mocha!!
Wait, Mocha!
Luffy and the others are on
the move to kidnap Caesar,
I told you what kind of drug they are!
How did the gas flow in?!
Don't do that.
-- save the children, and
escape from the island.
Robin!
I thought the door was closed!
Is it leaking from somewhere?
What?!
Really?!
If so, this building is no longer safe!
Momonosuke?
THE BASEMENT OF C BUILDING -
A GARBAGE DUMP LUFFY'S GROUP
Oh!
That is my name.
We have no time!
Straw Hat Luffy! Why are you here?!
Let's split up to look for the
Sea Prism Stone Handcuffs!
You're Pirate Hunter Zoro
I heard that name before somewhere.
Shoot! Shoot!
with a 120 million berry bounty!
Where was it?
How do I know?
You've been only defending yourself
She's a Logia-type.
It must be somebody else.
More importantly, you...
I'll take care of her!
Where's Caesar?
without even trying to attack. Why is it?
I don't know! I-I don't know anything...
"To Save Her Friends! Mocha
Runs at the Risk of Her Life!"
"A Deadly Fight in a Blizzard!
The Straw Hats vs. the Snow Woman!"
...stop drooling!
Could it be what I think it is?
Where's Caesar?!
You can't eat me!
Mocha!
To be honest, I didn't think
I could beat you but...
Give us the candy!
"Brownbeard in Grief! Luffy
Lands a Furious Blow!"
If you try to eat me,
I'll eat you first!
Behave yourself!
B BUILDING 3RD FLOOR - THE BISCUIT ROOM
...maybe I can.
MOMONOSUKE (DRAGON)
--Sis!
--Hurry up!
I'm gonna stay here!
Uh-huh!
Shinokuni, the deadly gas, is
flowing into the Third Laboratory
What?!
Get off of me! What are you doing?!
Oh?
Maybe "Momonosuke" is
stuck on a dragon's body
and starting to fill up B
Building where the Straw Hats,
Calm down! It's a sedative.
the Navy G-5, and the children are.
and he's talking with his farts...
Hey, where are you?!
What are you doing?!
Huh? Where am I?
It's not this way! Go back, go back!
What are you thinking?
Here we go!
It's nothing!
I think you need my help here!
Oh no! Go after the children!
Alright!
What?
He's torn in half! I'm sorry!
Give us the candy!
It's only gas - how is it outpacing me?!
Robin! Are you okay?
Yes,
Because you went the wrong way!
Oh, I'm finally separated from it-bu!
Wait!
it's just a scratch.
"Showing Off His Techniques! Zoro's
Formidable One-Sword Style!"
Milky Ball!
We must stop the children quickly.
I'm not talking with my farts!
Yeah.
Keep still, you brats!
Again!
How rude!
This is getting nowhere!
What are you talking about?!
Sedate them already, G-5!
Alright! Let's go, G-5!
How far does Mocha have to run?!
Nami, please hurry!
Come to think of it, that dragon
Let's go save the children
like Captain-chan said!
A few more to go, brother!
Candy!
The kids are gonna
leave the room soon!
was bigger
--Don't resist, children!
--Calm down!
Wait, Mocha!
Yeah!
and we already ate it.
Sis!
I promised her that I will hold them
Who are you then?
I can't believe there is another
Logia eater besides Caesar!
Candy...
What?!
but I couldn't
Candy!
An eel is talking to me?!
That cute harpy-chan was
a Devil Fruit eater?!
and I put Mocha in danger!
Hey, hurry up, racoon! We don't have time...
Stop drooling!
Dont give up, Mocha!
How awful!
Stop!
Are you alright, Mocha?!
We can't handle her!
I'm not an eel!
Give us the candy!
Chopper-chan!
You can make it!
Black Foot brother!
Go ahead while we hold them!
Why didn't you help us when
she was attacking us?!
Mo... Momonosuke!
You can't have it!
Uh-huh!
You're starving, aren't you?
Wait, Mocha!
W-W-Wait, Kin'emon-san!
Don't be such a baby! I don't kick women!
Chopper-chan told me
what these candies do to us!
If you go that way, you'll run into the gas!
Don't be ridiculous.
Let's hold the kids here!
We won't let them go after Mocha!
Samurai warriors don't get hungry
Then what would you do in
a life-or-death battle?!
It's not fair!
after just ten days of fasting.
Wait, Mocha! Give us the candy!
Please, Mocha! Hang on, somehow!
I'd choose death!
Ten days?!
You shouldn't eat these candies!
That's ridiculous!
They're all so different even though
they're in the same pirate group!
Come to your senses, everybody!
Who are you and
why are you here?
That Pirate Hunter guy looked like
THE BISCUIT ROOM
I'm Luffy.
I don't even see any soldiers,
let alone my people!
he'd chop up anybody without mercy.
I'm gonna become
the King of the Pirates!
P-P-P-P...
Yeah, yeah.
P...
What was that creepy room?!
Surprisingly, he has a soft side
too but he will find a way out!
Mocha, we have no choice.
You must be joking.
Wh-Where am I?
You can count on him.
We are sick.
Pirates are big, heavyweight men.
Don't worry about Tashigi-chan, either!
Mommy!
What's this door?
Wh-Wh-Wh-What're you... what're you doing?!
What we have got to do
They are more violent and strong-looking.
Daddy!
is save those damn children to impress
Nami-san, Robin-chan, and Tashigi-chan!
This is embarrassing! No! Put me down!
I hear something...
Anyway, eel, how can I get out of...
They said we couldn't
see our parents now.
...or not.
Shut up! This is no time
for that kind of crap!
If adults get infected with the
disease we have, they'll die.
Yeah!
It's Momonosuke!
Look!
All for the ladies!
Master! Look!
The deadly gas is flowing
into the Biscuit Room?!
So you're from somewhere
else, too, aren't you?
That's Brownbeard!
You don't want your mother
and father die, do you?
I thought he was captured by Straw Hat.
NEAR THE EXIT OF THE BISCUIT ROOM
Why don't you go with them?
Oh no! It'll fill up B Building in no time!
I'm free to do whatever I want!
--He looks okay.
--Good, good.
All I know is there are
so many sick children here.
I don't need you here!
You're free to think whatever you like!
Now you know. So shut up!
Well then,
You're causing me a lot of trouble!
I don't even know what kind of island
this is and what happened to me.
What do you want?!
am I free to take care
The exit is not that way!
of you first since I'm a
pirate, Navy soldier girl?!
What?! You should've told me sooner!
Let's get good treatment
for a year and get better!
Put me down before we
catch up with my people!
It all began when I happened
to stow away on a ship.
Why do you have so much pride?!
You can't do that.
I can just throw you away if you want!
What?!
Uh-huh!
You're not gonna cut me...
What now?!
I tried not to be so friendly
Is this the legendary sword - Shusui?!
or that woman!
Don't touch it! Shut up and
just hold on, you sword geek!
but those children were kind to me.
The Video Transponder Snail is running.
I'm glad that you made it!
You don't know that!
That means...
Soldiers of Punk Hazard! Listen!
Good to see you!
That's what I was just thinking.
My name is Caesar Clown.
They're giving out food.
Aren't you hungry?
I know you're watching me somewhere!
Call me "Master."
I was right.
Shut up!
You're all being fooled!
I don't want any!
You two are a part of my
first-generation of patients.
Caesar is telling you nothing but lies!
I am a samurai!
I'm looking forward
to working with you.
You're all gonna die if you stay here!
I don't accept alms!
I bet you were scared and worried
What is he talking about?
Well then... I'm in a hurry, so...
Has he gone crazy after being
captured by the Straw Hats?
when you heard
that you're sick out of the blue.
They were very nice to me
but I was on edge so...
Brownbeard is on the floor
below - R Building 1st floor.
But everything is okay now.
Where should I go?
I don't know which way I should go anymore!
I got you some food.
You don't have to worry about anything.
Why aren't you finishing me off?!
But the Straw Hats and Navy
soldiers will arrive there
I said I don't want any!
I will treat you at any cost!
You better eat something.
soon according to your plan.
Candy!
Is it because I'm a woman?!
We're all separated from parents
so we must stick together...
Should we tell Brownbeard to come up here?
No!
Nobody can understand how I feel!
It's humiliating that you won't
fight seriously in a game played
I'll tell you the truth about Caesar!
To tell you the truth,
Mocha?!
Give us the candy!
I lost my only son to this disease.
in earnest just because men're
physically stronger than women!
No, I'll go down.
No!
We're coming with you then.
Candy! Candy!
I'm sure you don't understand the feeling
I never wanna see another
child suffering from it!
Konbu! Biyo! Stop! Please listen to me!
THE BISCUIT ROOM
that I wish I was born a boy!
Candy!
Give me the candy!
I don't carry a sword for pleasure!
I am "Master" Caesar!
Also, I don't wanna see another parent
Come on in!
I don't like your very being!
--Mocha!
--Oh no!
Some children took a detour!
This is your playground from today!
lose their child and have to grieve like me!
Caesar!
Listen! Your face!
Oh, my dear underling - Brownbeard!
Everybody, stop!
Oh no! If they get the candies,
we have to start all over again!
It looks exactly like my close
friend's who died long ago!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
There are many giant children!
Are they sick, too?
How embarrassing.
I shouldn't cry in front of you.
I'm glad that you got away from Straw Hat!
On top of that, you started saying
the same thing she used to say!
We have to separate Mocha from the kids!
You can count on me!
Are you okay, Master-san?
--Mil Fleurs...
--Outta my way!
Are you alright?
Don't imitate, you copycat woman!
I'll treat you all at any cost!
Thank you. You're very kind.
Let's go!
You look awful!
Milky Ball!
Oh yes! I must introduce you to them!
Hi!
What?! Stop talking like a child!
Don't touch me!
Gigantesco Mano!
We're all friends from today!
Oh? Why are you in such a bad mood?
They're from other islands
but have the same disease.
Thank you!
Hey, what about you?
Give us the candy!
What's your name?
Mocha!
What's wrong?
--No!
--Give it to us!
I don't have
Wait!
No, you can't have it!
a name.
I want my people back!
It's not fair! You can't have it all!
I'm Uzu. Nice to meet you!
We got robbed at the center of
the island but they didn't die!
If you eat it, you can't go home!
Here.
Candy!
Don't you wanna see your father and mother?!
Have some snacks.
I'm sure they're back already!
You view women as inferior!
I'm Doran.
Whoa-whoa, he's messing with the Master.
Shut up!
You don't really try to fight us!
I don't want any!
Wait! Mocha!
Just give us the candy already!
Candy?
You won't kill us!
Huh? Your people?
I don't want any!
Maybe you're not gonna lose but
you're not gonna win either!
I want to go home!!
I'm Konbu.
Oh yeah...
That's why I had to stay here!
Give me the candy!
I want to go home with
everybody! Safe and healthy!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
If I let this Logia eater go after
my people, there will be carnage!
A FEW DAYS LATER
Clank!
M-M-Master!
Hey, is it true that one of the kids escaped?
Master!
Are you looking down on me?!
What's going on?
Yes but everybody on the
boarding list was accounted for.
Oh, you must be one of Brownbeard's.
Yes, I am.
We have some new friends here!
Master! There are Navy soldiers at
the main entrance and it's closed!
That's strange.
Oh!
In any case,
let's split up and search.
Teach them about this place, okay?
Okay!
We can't get inside! Please guide us!
Do as you like.
Oh no! That's serious!
Let's play over there!
My duty is to keep her from
going after my friends, too.
Let me see what I can do! Wait there!
Let's play!
Th-Thank you very much, Master!
I just wanna keep her away from that path.
Go ahead!
Master...
How can I get out of here?
How can you take it so easy?
Uh-huh!
Master, how are you going to let them in?
Don't you know that we're out of time?!
You better run, too!
Everybody! Be nice to each other!
Let me know if you need any help!
Don't drop your guard.
She's willing to kill you.
Okay, Monet-san!
Forget about it.
Shinokuni will be inescapable
out there soon enough.
He's right! Thank you for
sharing his weak point!
Monet-san was kind
but she was lying!
Even though you can use Haki,
it's not so hard for me to gnaw you to death!
I wonder what happened to them.
It was all lies!
They don't even call me anymore.
This is a reward for
enduring with the treatment.
If they're not here, they must be...
It's a candy from the Master.
She ate them all!
Mocha!
What is she thinking?!
How annoying!
--Give them back to us!
--Screw you!
But even if Haki allows you to sense
a Devil Fruit eater's true form,
Are you worried? I think you are.
How dare you eat them all, you jerk!
Let's escape from here together!
If they were out there, they're
definitely dead because of Shinokuni!
you can't catch me unless
you can keep up with me!
Please!
Come to your senses now!
What'd you say?!
Isn't that right?!
Screw you!
Hey, what're you doing, Brownbeard?!
We gotta catch up with the children!
Mocha!!
Yeah!
I thought so.
You're a cold man.
Brownbeard?!
No, spit them all out!
Mocha, can you hear me?!
I can't trust your words anymore!
This? Coming from a snow woman?
Where did she go?!
Mocha!!
--What happened to him?!
--What is he doing to the Master?!
Pay attention!
Hey you!
I told you what kind of drug they are!
Do you like snowball fights?
I'll tell you guys this
What are you doing?!
because we spent the last two
years together on this island.
Hey!
Snow Rabbit!
What?! Wait a sec!
Leave the island now!
Why shouldn't we eat the candy?
Hey, you!
Do you wanna know what he
called you behind your back?!
Why is he coming this way?!
Shave!
You were on the same ship with me.
Wait, Nami! No!
You can't use me as a shield!
Do you remember me?
This was his special name for you!
Because...
Oh, so your name is Momonosuke-kun.
...that candy is a deadly poison!
You're Smoker's right-hand girl.
Guinoa pags.
Maybe I have underestimated you a little bit.
This is a "secret room"
where no one is allowed.
Guinoo pah!
What a shame.
What?!
Why are you trying
to attack the weak ones?
You're so annoying.
I wonder how he is now.
Guinoa poh...
Chopper-chan.
Don't get involved with me.
It's strategic to finish off
easier foes first.
I know he's pretty strong
but Vergo is more...
Guinoh... Guinah...
They're all...
Why?
Because...
You don't have to worry about Smoker-san!
There is no reason!
...my friends!
You people can't beat him!
Not in a million years!
I'm just looking for an exit.
What're you trying to say, Brownbeard?!
--Speak clearly!
--Is it some kind of spell?!
I'm gonna get out of here.
Zoro, move out of my way!
I know that better than anybody!
There is something I need to do.
I know it's hard but every child here
is going through the same thing.
How scary.
Heat Egg!
It's a promise!
He's a funny guy!
Snowstorm.
--I promise!
Guinoh...
I promise!
I don't know what you're saying!
--I promise!
Everybody wants to see his or her
father and mother as soon as possible.
I promise!
They will keep following me
thinking I'm their savior!
The heat worked, just as I thought!
Don't do it!
Whoa-whoa!
I promise!
All of us came here from
different islands to be treated
They don't know that I kept them
alive because they're my guinea pigs!
but everybody feels the same way.
Don't come after us!
I said "Guinea pigs"!
Stay away!
There are so many things I wanna do
if I could just get back home!
Why is it chasing me?!
When we grow up,
B BUILDING - USOPP
Why?! I got tongue-tied!
Everybody is friendly at the
Biscuit Room and it's fun there.
Don't follow me!
Cat Burglar -
let's set out to the sea!
You did something, didn't you, Caesar?!
You can forget the pain.
a 16 million berry bounty.
Alright. It's not gonna be safe here
To the sea?!
So why don't you eat
something, Momonosuke-kun?!
To fish?
and I gotta find the Sea Prism
Stone handcuffs already!
No, fool! To go on an adventure!
She hid herself in the snow again!
Well, but...
Don't you wanna fight me,
snow woman?!
We'll look for an island made
of gold and that sort of thing.
Hm?
Sounds like fun!
What's wrong?
Oh no, somebody's coming!
When we get well and go home,
we'll all be separated, right?
Let's go, Momonosuke-kun!
The exit is...
But if we all set out to
That was close...
Oh no!
the sea when we grow up, we
can see each other again!
The door to the secret room is open!
What is this place?
Oh, that'll be great! We've
become such good friends now!
Oh, what is it this time?!
It's dark and I can't see anything!
Come on!
Snow Fence!
Are you putting on an act?!
Don't worry about me!
And it's cold!
Just go!
Oh, are you okay? Huh?
Perpetual Snow!
When do we set out to the sea?
Nami?!
The handcuffs... Where are the handcuffs?
It's a muscle relaxant.
The snow is...
You're losing strength around your mouth
Well...
I hope there are no monsters in here!
and your whole body, aren't you?
It's cold! I can't move!
When we turn 20 years old!
Nami!
That'll take forever.
Oh! Oops!
That makes it more exciting to wait for!
Oh yeah, I remember now, Brownbeard.
You're right!
Anybody there?!
Okay, let's make a promise!
About your former subordinates...
She did it again!
Excuse me, Kin'emon-san!
Watch out, Chopper!
I let them die!
Wh-What is it?!
Where are you hurrying off to?
I promise!
Who is it?!
Corpse-dono! I heard children's
voices - they were close!
Cuatro Mano!
Spank!
What?! But that doesn't
mean you can leave me here!
You asshole!
So, the Master is a bad person?!
The poison gas is coming this way, too!
Nami!
How dare you!
Yes, he's a very bad person.
How dare you kill my people!
Momonosuke!
I was scared!
A d-dragon?!
But he's always very nice to us!
--Oh, children!
--Who are you?!
Robin! Thank you!
And he gives us the sweet candy everyday!
Do you kids know Momonosuke?
He is my son!
That's his trick.
What's going on?
What?! No way! But...
I don't know.
--I'm scared!
--What?
Wait! Just wait!
You children are his test subjects!
M-Momonosuke-kun...
Oh, there is another thing
that I'd like to tell you.
What?
T-Test subjects?!
There are so many of them!
Open up, Mocha!
Oh please.
Momonosuke! Is Momonosuke here?!
We're gonna go to the Biscuit Room!
Look!
Answer me if you're here!
Candy!
The chemical weapon explosion
that nearly killed all
If I remember correctly,
Those children are the Master's
precious test subjects.
there was a man-made Devil
Fruit that Vegapunk created here.
You kids were never sick from the beginning.
these soldiers four years ago?
And I'm responsible for protecting
Caesar and his experiment.
I heard it was a failure.
Th-That can't be...
There were still this many kids?!
Yeah, I heard so, too.
Your giant body is proof.
Who planted this rebellious
spirit in Mocha's mind?
Alright!
I've heard turning people
into giants has been
It's dangerous here! Everybody,
get to R Building!
I was the one who caused it!
What?!
a project underway for hundreds
of years all over the world.
Those kids asked for help on their own!
A skeleton!
Move out of my way!
How could you say that?
But I'm glad they're fine!
That pain in my chest I felt suddenly -
Which means they've kept
failing at it for hundreds
I thought my heart was gonna explode!
Go to R Building now!
of years and no one has succeeded yet.
Hey, are you looking for Momonosuke-kun?
I had trouble running before.
You may not want to hear this but...
What happened...
Mocha!
It wasn't Vegapunk?!
Give us the candy!
B BUILDING 3RD FLOOR - A PATH IN THE BACK
This experiment...
Stop! You can't have it all!
This bastard did harm to everybody
and pretended that he saved them?!
You go ahead!
is doomed to failure, too!
Konbu! Doran! Everybody!
We'd better hurry!
Uh-huh!
I know it's hard but you can't have it!
Mocha, please hang on!
Caesar knows that.
I suppose he's just collecting
data for his next experiment.
There she is! Mocha!
Robin! Hold the children!
Then, what's gonna happen to us?
You people are so uncool.
Cien Fleurs!
Hey, stop! Stop it!
Every single day, we treat them nicely
Help me! Brownbeard is going crazy!
What?! The hands again?!
You're all gonna die.
I'm sorry! I had to do this.
None of you will make it home.
and allow them to live in great comfort.
That sweet candy is a deadly poison.
This will ease your pain a bit.
Run, everybody!
What you people are trying to do is
Everything that's been going on this
island is all staged by Caesar!
It'll destroy your body before you know it.
So I am originally a human.
take away these "treasures"
from us "foster parents."
But as soon as you eat one,
you'll crave another one.
Run, guys! He's a devil disguised as a human!
Sis!
The more you eat, the harder it is
for you to get away from Caesar!
You people are like pirates.
You ate a Devil Fruit, huh?
Mocha!
Hey, Brownbeard!
So you have no problem with it, right?
How could you do that to
a person who saved you?!
You see how scary it is
when you look at those kids
And it made you an eel man, maybe?
Mocha! Don't let them have those candies!
I said it's uncool.
Eels don't have horns.
on the other side of the door, don't you?
Stop interfering with my duty!
Oh no! He's really dangerous!
Then why don't you turn
yourself back into a human.
Sword Snow!
It's too late!
What?!
I guess Straw Hat did something to him!
Skin Sword!
Keep running!
I-I can turn myself back to myself?!
Uh-huh!
I sedated you already.
Chopper-chan, I'm not gonna give up!
Brownbeard!
How?!
But, from side-effects of the
candy and the experiment,
I don't know.
Shoot! Shoot him! He's gonna attack you guys!
I won't give up - for everyone's sake!
I'm not a Zoan-type.
I'm not gonna let anybody have it!
before you can even become an adult,
By the way, I wonder
how high this ceiling is.
Shoot!
you'll probably die.
I can't even see the hole
that I fell through.
I want to get out of here, too,
and tell those children the truth!
Mocha!!
I happened to hear something!
That Caesar guy was talking...
THE BASEMENT OF C BUILDING - A GARBAGE DUMP
Great! We can get out of here like this!
We have another group
of good obedient kids.
We can't even become adults?
The other kids are growing
bigger without problem.
We can't see our fathers and mothers again?
Hey, are you alright?!
Wh-What?!
What's the matter?!
But, after all, this is an experiment
to see the limitations of drug dosing.
I don't think they can take it that long.
Now, let me finish him off.
I'll take it from here, Momo!
No, if you kids don't escape now.
I assume they'll all be dead in five years.
Gastane...
Wait for me, Caesar!
We never even thought about that.
I'm not hungry at all...
So we need to find more kids.
We asked you to help us
because we wanted to go home!
I'm not...
Well, experiments come with failures.
We were afraid to be told to stay here
It's a necessary sacrifice.
for another year without knowing
what kind of disease we have!
Those stupid kids can help
the world's greatest scientist -
Master Caesar Clown
I'll say hi to your people for you
and do good for the world!
and tell them "She died a tragic death."
But...
Even if it's a short life,
they have to be happy with it!
Don't you think?!
I thought he was a doctor
But...
Sword Snow - Skin Sword!
but he is actually a bad man
We never thought that we were gonna die.
who is going to let the children die!
What is Monet doing?
Oh?
And the kids have no idea.
Did we make it out of that hole?
The children are getting away!
We thought we could grow up!
Here.
Yeah.
Have some snacks.
That's not what we've been told!
But who cares?
You climbed that wall to the top, huh?
We can always restock
guinea pigs through kidnapping.
I know it's hard but every child here
is going through the same thing.
Shoot!
We ate the candy because they gave it to us!
We never thought we were gonna die from it!
Our priority now is providing
a showcase for Shinokuni
Everybody wants to see his or her
father and mother as soon as possible.
Wh-What happened to my shoulder?!
I know! It's not your fault at all!
and getting rid of the Straw Hats.
That's why we can't forgive Caesar!
Because the gas is
flowing into the building,
I feel sorry for them.
We're not gonna forgive him!
the situation is favorable for us.
If I don't do anything,
I should be ashamed of
myself as a samurai warrior!
I was on my way to tell the
children but I fell down here
I'm sorry!
when I tried to hide in a trash can.
Now, let me finish him off.
Momo, stay back!
What are you doing?! Let go of me!
Gastane...
B Building will be
Caesar!
filled up with gas soon.
That we didn't find you sooner!
They have no choice
but to head to R Building.
Alright, Momo,
I'm gonna climb up there.
If I let go of her, she's
gonna bite off my shoulder!
They're gonna be killed
by the gas anyway though.
Chopper-chan?
I'll take you with me!
What?!
How are you gonna climb that high?!
Master!
Oh, that was close!
I'm gonna climb the wall.
Chopper-chan, we...
It grazed my body!
I can just shred it to pieces if you prefer!
Hold onto me!
What?!
Oh no! Oh no! Oh no! Oh no! Oh no...
...don't wanna die!
Dammit! Who is it?!
Don't worry about the children.
You're not gonna die!
We're gonna save you all!
Oh no! Oh no!
Oh no! Oh no! Oh no! Oh no! Oh no!
My friends are on their way to help them.
It's coming again!
Really?!
Caesar is actually a powerful,
horrible, evil man.
They always keep their word!
How did the gas flow in?!
So don't worry!
But... But...
I thought the door was closed!
Okay!
Our captain is stronger than him!
Is it leaking from somewhere?
Really?!
What I thought was right!
He's gonna become the
king of the sea someday!
You are not an ordinary...
If so, this building is no longer safe!
...pirate.
We have no time!
Luffy will kick Caesar's butt for sure!
Let's split up to look for the
Sea Prism Stone Handcuffs!
You talked so big but took so much time.
What's the matter?
Again?!
It's Straw Hat...
...Luffy!
But I guess we have no choice.
Time's up.
What happened?
Brook, you go with Kin'emon!
Are you too hungry?!
Hey, stay with me!
So listen carefully.
Stay with me! Stay with me!
We can't leave him alone -
he's too clumsy!
Your name is Mocha, isn't it?
Alright!
Hey, stay with me!
I have to go now.
We can't let other children
have any more candy!
Corpse-dono, thank you!
Stay with me! Stay with me! Hey!
See you at R Building!
Uh-huh!
Okay!
Stay with me!
I'll try my best to sedate them all here!
Stay with me! Stay with me!
Uh-huh!
So, Mocha, can you guard the
candies in the Biscuit Room?
I thought he wouldn't cut women.
Stay with me!!
But he just tried to cut me!
You've been only defending yourself
Uh-huh!
Wh-What?!
I see! Then I won't let
anybody eat the candy!
without even trying to attack. Why is it?
You've underestimated me, snow woman.
I wanna go home with everybody!
What's going on?
Great!
When you thought you couldn't beat me,
Could it be what I think it is?
you should have run.
His kindness saved my life
as it did to the others.
To be honest, I didn't think
I could beat you but...
Of course, there are things
that I don't wanna cut.
Mocha!
Hey, what's the matter?!
...maybe I can.
The Master was our warm-hearted savior!
But...
H-Hey!
Mocha spewed up blood!
...let me ask you something.
There's another room!
Why? Those were just the sweet candies.
Hey, wait!
Have you ever seen a fierce animal
you were sure would never bite?
Find the children and
take them out of here!
Return to 2nd floor, everyone!
Hey, isn't it a little cold here?
The Straw Hats and the
Navy will be here soon!
The Navy?
We're...
Let's go through the door!
flying!
--Get ready for the experiment!
--Yes, sir!
Yeah!
Broadcast it for the brokers!
What happened to Mocha?
Because I haven't.
--Let's go!
--Hustle!
Hey, she doesn't look well.
Everybody's trying to take
the children away from us!
AT THE BACK OF 2ND FLOOR OF B BUILDING
A PATH AT AN EXAMINATION ROOM
Wh-What?!
--I can't believe it...
--The children have stopped!
I assume they'll all be dead in five years.
I won't allow it!
I can't move!
One-Sword!
That's what happens when you're greedy.
He's gonna cut me!
Let's go!
So we need to find more kids.
Charge!
I wonder if Nami and the others
are doing okay without me!
Mocha!
Luffy! It was him!
Why are you leading them?!
Well, at least Zoro is with them!
He was the one who were talking about...
Brother! I don't see any children
I'll save you at any cost
Mocha! Stay with me!
...harming those kindhearted children!
but there's Pirate Hunter Zoro!
so wait for me, Momonosuke!
I know.
He's such a pain.
Brook!
Why?
Let me know if you see the
This is what the candy really does to you!
Sea Prism Stone handcuffs
that Robin told us to find!
Alright, guys!
People on this island were tricked
into being here, weren't they?
Stick out your lower lip
and make fun of him!
Mocha tried to save you all by...
I'm sorry, corpse-dono!
I have to depend on your sorcery!
Great Dragon Shock!
What is this island?!
...sacrificing herself!
Count on me!
I hope they all slip on the snow,
hit their heads and die.
Chopper! If you wanna sedate
them, now is the chance!
I just need to look
for samurai-san's son
and some Sea Prism
Stone handcuffs, right?
But I have to treat her first!
Hey, Nami and Robin went ahead.
Let's check the other side of that wall.
We have no time!
All right.
Just go away already.
You don't know anything so let me
tell you the secret of this island.
Oh! What good information
even from a fool!
Was his name Momonosuke-kun?
The children are standing still!
I bet he is a boy
who dresses like samurai-san!
Alright, let's go, guys...
--There's no sound!
--Hurry up!
Go!
--Checking the video!
--Pull the elevator up!
Yeah!
Hey! Where are you?!
Are you two happy now?
Don't use violence, guys!
D BUILDING - THE "SAD" MANUFACTURING ROOM
This island is like gas or air.
But there's a cutie behind him!
Yeah!
Oh! She's so cute!
Fight numbers with numbers!
You people are so obnoxious!
An island that doesn't seem to exist.
He cut her!
Yeah!
Just go already!
My Armament Haki
surpasses your ability by far.
Do you get it?
Bring them under control!
Hey. But look!
Her appearance.
Alright!
She's not a human.
--Sanji-kun?!
--The Navy?!
A bird with a human face?
How insulting!
Listen, this island shouldn't even exist.
She's a harpy!
Sanji!
Brother! Is aiming for the
balls considered violence?
What?!
I think you're smart enough to know
That's why it's suitable to the
work of an underground community.
What?
B-But...
that it's useless to fight against me.
Is she still alive?!
...she's still cute!
--It's a close call, but yes, it is.
--Alright!
It's an epicenter of evil science.
Rather bewitchingly beautiful!
--Medical team, step forward!
--Yes, sir!
We can do unlawful experiments or get
test subjects illegally as we like!
Yeah, so sexy!
Chopper, use them! They know how
to give injections at least!
He didn't use Haki?
Smoker.
You're enjoying this, aren't you?!
Or are you trying to avenge
those dumb-asses' death?
Okay!
We have some powerful people backing us
Alright, let's calm the kids down!
Is this how he shows his mercy?
Hey, why is it snowing in here?
and they'll cover up everything.
Thank you, guys!
So no one out there would know a thing.
1, 2, 3!
Oh yeah.
Advance!
If I'm correct, there is an
examination room around here!
They're not gonna die that easily -
No matter how much you cry or scream,
Carry her there!
they're not that weak!
It's because of me.
no one will come to the rescue.
We have no time! Do you know that, racoon?!
Even though they're misfits,
they're still Navy soldiers!
You don't know a damn thing
about this island, Straw Hat!
Yes, I do!
Enough of the chitchat! Let's just go!
It's getting stormy
all of a sudden!
If you're getting involved without taking
it seriously, you'll end up dead!
No matter who you are,
Mocha.--
I guess she can't control her body.
I'm not gonna let anybody
Shave!
take the children!
Because she's frightened by
his overwhelming strength
Allying with Law is also not a good idea.
and the fact she could have
died if he had used Haki!
He wants to mess with SAD.
She's gone!
He is using you to kidnap me because I'm
I've never seen anyone
beat somebody like this!
Where did she go?!
the only person who can create SAD.
Damn! It's my fault!
When the Straw Hats disappeared
for two years,--
I wonder where they were
and what they were doing.
Let me tell you about SAD, Straw Hat.
Don't mess with the Navy!
The most dangerous Warlord - Don
Quixote Doflamingo owns this factory
Just how strong have they become?!
Chopper-chan...
Ro... ro... noa... Zoro!
Mocha, are you okay? Are you in pain?
and here, SAD is processed
into a fruit called "SMILE."
I didn't know you cared
so much about your men,
Chopper-chan, I...
Smoker-kun.
Hey! Are you alright?!
Do you know what SMILE is?
I won't let you get away!
We successfully recreated a Devil Fruit!
Wh-What happened to my shoulder?!
I didn't give them the candies.
B BUILDING - NEAR THE BISCUIT ROOM
Sword Autumn Rain!
Mocha! You...
SMILE is a Zoan type, man-made Devil Fruit.
You bastard!
Everybody, this way!
Get to the Biscuit Room
where the children are!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
You lose.
Anyone who wants to become
powerful yearns for it.
Uh-huh! You tried to save
your friends, didn't you?
You guys are too slow!
Thank you! Thank you!
The deadly gas is right behind you!
Doflamingo is selling SMILEs
to big-timers in the New World.
They can all go home thanks to you!
If you don't wanna die, run faster!
Hurry up!
Ouch!
Brother, don't kick me!
Sh-She's a Logia-type!
Uh-huh...
I heard one of the Four Emperors
is already on the move...
Ouch, brother!
I will save you at any cost, Mocha!
That bitch!
...to form an army of hundreds
of Devil Fruit eaters with SMILE.
Come on, everybody!
Hurry up!
What was that?!
Damn!
I will!
You didn't try to kill
her after all, did you?!
Don't kick me!
Doesn't it send a chill down your spine?
Ouch!
The Black Foot brother is gonna
kill us before the deadly gas does!
See, like I said, you're...
Do you understand what you're dealing with?
I didn't ask you to do that. So shut up.
You'll become an adult!
Don't be a baby!
By interfering with Doflamingo's business,
you'll piss so many big names off.
He's crazy!
If you didn't kill her, I did.
Uh-huh.
Hurry up!
If you wanna save the children,
Don't lie! It's not fair! I already cut her!
go to the Biscuit Room now!
When they start going into action,
it's gonna shake up the whole world.
B BUILDING 3RD FLOOR - THE BISCUIT ROOM
A swordsman using Haki?!
You didn't have to do that.
And that's what Law wants.
What?!
C BUILDING 1ST FLOOR - A DUMPSTER
But...
What fools!
They're out of your league!
It's cold! The whole
room is in a blizzard!
Good job, Captain Eyeglasses.
Why did the dumpster
explode all of a sudden?!
You stopped her from going after anybody.
I just took off my coat!
What is a Snow-Snow Fruit?!
Captain-chan!
Catch me if you can! But I'm protected!
Damn that snow woman!
You can take the credit.
Everybody, stop!
Doflamingo! The Four Emperors!
We sealed off the door to the room
to prevent the gas from flowing in.
You shouldn't eat the candy!
Why do you always talk like
you're greater than me?!
Wh-Who is it?!
Do you even have balls to
pick a fight with them?
Mocha, run!
Because I am.
Wait, Mocha!
But we don't know
Give us the candy!
where it might start leaking again.
I don't think so!
No! You all have to
come to your senses!
Straw Hat Luffy! Why are you here?!
If you wanna run, do it now!
There's not much time!
You can't have it all to yourself!
Everybody, do all you can
to save the children!
Get out of my face!
Shoot! Shoot!
Stop running!
What about you?
I'll try to hold them,
if even for a little while.
What's wrong?
I'm gonna stay here!
It's nothing. You can go ahead.
What?!
Don't do that.
A fight?
Robin!
Hey, hey!
Are you alright, Robin?!
Monet... Huh! How useless!
Where's Caesar?
Straw Hats! Make your way
to R Building already!
Huh?
What?!
That's where you'll meet your demise!
I don't know! I-I don't know anything...
I can't wait to see you suffer
What are you thinking?
from the gas and groan, as my test subjects!
Oh!
Where's Caesar?!
You're Pirate Hunter Zoro
Wow!
I-I-If you go straight down this path,
you'll get to R Building and he's there!
with a 120 million berry bounty!
You three, go stop those kids!
I see.
I've been...
She's a Logia-type.
I think you need my help here!
...picking fights all along!
I'll take care of her!
Thanks.
What?!
Even while he's at the mercy of Monet's ability to freely manipulate snow,
Brownbeard tries to save the soldiers
by revealing Caesar's true identity.
While holding the candy,
Mocha desperately tries to get away.
Undaunted by the powerful Gas Gas Fruit attacks...
Monet attacks, using the powerful
Snow-Snow Fruit powers,
But then the crazed children surround her.
...Luffy corners Caesar with his fists of rage.
and Tashigi desperately fights
back by using her Haki.
Zoro still tries to let Nami and the others
escape, despite the relentless attacks.
But Caesar manages to twist his words, and ingeniously conceals the truth.
But she is then caught by
Monet's monstrous fangs,
Just when the children almost
successfully take the candy,
But elsewhere, Smoker,
It's then that Monet transforms
into a terrifying monster
facing another powerful Haki user,
and just as her shoulder is
about to be torn to shreds,
Mocha makes a surprising move,
After seeing Caesar laughing triumphantly,
Luffy's rage reaches its limit
is fighting an overwhelmingly losing battle...
and the situation worsens.
making Chopper's heartbreaking scream resonate.
Zoro's beast-like instincts cause him into action.
The crew find themselves backed into a corner.
...and lies on the verge of death and defeat.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To Save Her Friends! Mocha
Runs at the Risk of Her Life!"
"A Surprising Outcome!
White Chase vs. Vergo!"
"Brownbeard in Grief! Luffy
Lands a Furious Blow!"
"Showing Off His Techniques!
Zoro's Formidable One-Sword Style!"
"A Deadly Fight in a Blizzard!
The Straw Hats vs. the Snow Woman!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!