All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled
by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts,
one burning, the other frozen.
After learning about the ruler of the island -
Caesar Clown, aka the Master's motive,
and all while trying to escape Shinokuni,
along with their pirate ally -
the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
they are on the move to kidnap Caesar,
save the children,
and escape from the island.
Did you just say something?
Who the hell are you?!
Who are you?!
"A Small Dragon!
Momonosuke Appears!"
Momonosuke?
THE BASEMENT OF C BUILDING -
A GARBAGE DUMP LUFFY'S GROUP
That is my name.
I heard that name before somewhere.
Where was it?
How do I know?
It must be somebody else.
More importantly, you...
...stop drooling!
You can't eat me!
If you try to eat me,
I'll eat you first!
Behave yourself!
MOMONOSUKE (DRAGON)
Oh?
Maybe "Momonosuke" is
stuck on a dragon's body
and he's talking with his farts...
Hey, where are you?!
What are you doing?!
Here we go!
He's torn in half! I'm sorry!
Oh, I'm finally separated from it-bu!
I'm not talking with my farts!
How rude!
What are you talking about?!
Come to think of it, that dragon
was bigger
and we already ate it.
Who are you then?
What?!
An eel is talking to me?!
Stop drooling!
I'm not an eel!
You're starving, aren't you?
Don't be ridiculous.
Samurai warriors don't get hungry
after just ten days of fasting.
Ten days?!
Who are you and
why are you here?
I'm Luffy.
I'm gonna become
the King of the Pirates!
P-P-P-P...
P...
You must be joking.
Pirates are big, heavyweight men.
They are more violent and strong-looking.
Anyway, eel, how can I get out of...
It's Momonosuke!
So you're from somewhere
else, too, aren't you?
All I know is there are
so many sick children here.
I don't even know what kind of island
this is and what happened to me.
It all began when I happened
to stow away on a ship.
I tried not to be so friendly
but those children were kind to me.
They're giving out food.
Aren't you hungry?
Shut up!
I don't want any!
I am a samurai!
I don't accept alms!
They were very nice to me
but I was on edge so...
I got you some food.
I said I don't want any!
You better eat something.
We're all separated from parents
so we must stick together...
Nobody can understand how I feel!
THE BISCUIT ROOM
I am "Master" Caesar!
Come on in!
This is your playground from today!
There are many giant children!
Are they sick, too?
You can count on me!
I'll treat you all at any cost!
Hi!
We're all friends from today!
Thank you!
Hey, what about you?
What's your name?
I don't have
a name.
Here.
Have some snacks.
I don't want any!
Candy?
A FEW DAYS LATER
Hey, is it true that one of the kids escaped?
Yes but everybody on the
boarding list was accounted for.
That's strange.
In any case,
let's split up and search.
How can I get out of here?
Hey, you!
You were on the same ship with me.
Do you remember me?
Oh, so your name is Momonosuke-kun.
This is a "secret room"
where no one is allowed.
You're so annoying.
Don't get involved with me.
Why?
Because...
There is no reason!
I'm just looking for an exit.
I'm gonna get out of here.
There is something I need to do.
I know it's hard but every child here
is going through the same thing.
Everybody wants to see his or her
father and mother as soon as possible.
All of us came here from
different islands to be treated
but everybody feels the same way.
There are so many things I wanna do
if I could just get back home!
Everybody is friendly at the
Biscuit Room and it's fun there.
You can forget the pain.
So why don't you eat
something, Momonosuke-kun?!
Well, but...
Hm?
What's wrong?
Oh no, somebody's coming!
Let's go, Momonosuke-kun!
The door to the secret room is open!
Come on!
Don't worry about me!
Just go!
Anybody there?!
Wh-What is it?!
Who is it?!
A d-dragon?!
What's going on?
I don't know.
M-Momonosuke-kun...
Look!
If I remember correctly,
there was a man-made Devil
Fruit that Vegapunk created here.
I heard it was a failure.
Yeah, I heard so, too.
That pain in my chest I felt suddenly -
I thought my heart was gonna explode!
I had trouble running before.
What happened...
So I am originally a human.
You ate a Devil Fruit, huh?
And it made you an eel man, maybe?
Eels don't have horns.
Then why don't you turn
yourself back into a human.
What?!
I-I can turn myself back to myself?!
How?!
I don't know.
I'm not a Zoan-type.
By the way, I wonder
how high this ceiling is.
I can't even see the hole
that I fell through.
I want to get out of here, too,
and tell those children the truth!
I happened to hear something!
That Caesar guy was talking...
We have another group
of good obedient kids.
The other kids are growing
bigger without problem.
But, after all, this is an experiment
to see the limitations of drug dosing.
I don't think they can take it that long.
I assume they'll all be dead in five years.
So we need to find more kids.
Well, experiments come with failures.
It's a necessary sacrifice.
Those stupid kids can help
the world's greatest scientist -
Master Caesar Clown
and do good for the world!
Even if it's a short life,
they have to be happy with it!
Don't you think?!
I thought he was a doctor
but he is actually a bad man
who is going to let the children die!
And the kids have no idea.
Here.
Have some snacks.
I know it's hard but every child here
is going through the same thing.
Everybody wants to see his or her
father and mother as soon as possible.
I feel sorry for them.
If I don't do anything,
I should be ashamed of
myself as a samurai warrior!
I was on my way to tell the
children but I fell down here
when I tried to hide in a trash can.
Caesar!
Alright, Momo,
I'm gonna climb up there.
I'll take you with me!
What?!
How are you gonna climb that high?!
I'm gonna climb the wall.
Hold onto me!
What?!
Don't worry about the children.
My friends are on their way to help them.
Really?!
They always keep their word!
So don't worry!
Okay!
What I thought was right!
You are not an ordinary...
...pirate.
What's the matter?
What happened?
Are you too hungry?!
Hey, stay with me!
Stay with me! Stay with me!
Stay with me! Stay with me! Hey!
Stay with me!
Stay with me! Stay with me!
Stay with me!!
Wh-What?!
What's going on?
Hey, what's the matter?!
H-Hey!
Hey, wait!
We're...
flying!
AT THE BACK OF 2ND FLOOR OF B BUILDING
A PATH AT AN EXAMINATION ROOM
I wonder if Nami and the others
are doing okay without me!
Well, at least Zoro is with them!
I'll save you at any cost
so wait for me, Momonosuke!
Brook!
Let me know if you see the
Sea Prism Stone handcuffs
that Robin told us to find!
I'm sorry, corpse-dono!
I have to depend on your sorcery!
Count on me!
I just need to look
for samurai-san's son
and some Sea Prism
Stone handcuffs, right?
Let's check the other side of that wall.
Was his name Momonosuke-kun?
I bet he is a boy
who dresses like samurai-san!
Hey! Where are you?!
D BUILDING - THE "SAD" MANUFACTURING ROOM
My Armament Haki
surpasses your ability by far.
I think you're smart enough to know
that it's useless to fight against me.
Smoker.
Or are you trying to avenge
those dumb-asses' death?
They're not gonna die that easily -
they're not that weak!
Even though they're misfits,
they're still Navy soldiers!
Shave!
Don't mess with the Navy!
I didn't know you cared
so much about your men,
Smoker-kun.
B BUILDING - NEAR THE BISCUIT ROOM
Everybody, this way!
Get to the Biscuit Room
where the children are!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
You guys are too slow!
The deadly gas is right behind you!
If you don't wanna die, run faster!
Hurry up!
Ouch!
Brother, don't kick me!
Ouch, brother!
Come on, everybody!
Hurry up!
Don't kick me!
Ouch!
The Black Foot brother is gonna
kill us before the deadly gas does!
Don't be a baby!
He's crazy!
Hurry up!
If you wanna save the children,
go to the Biscuit Room now!
B BUILDING 3RD FLOOR - THE BISCUIT ROOM
It's cold! The whole
room is in a blizzard!
I just took off my coat!
What is a Snow-Snow Fruit?!
Damn that snow woman!
Everybody, stop!
You shouldn't eat the candy!
Mocha, run!
Wait, Mocha!
Give us the candy!
No! You all have to
come to your senses!
You can't have it all to yourself!
Stop running!
I'll try to hold them,
if even for a little while.
Don't do that.
Robin!
Are you alright, Robin?!
Oh!
You're Pirate Hunter Zoro
with a 120 million berry bounty!
You three, go stop those kids!
She's a Logia-type.
I'll take care of her!
Even while he's at the mercy of Monet's ability to freely manipulate snow,
Zoro still tries to let Nami and the others
escape, despite the relentless attacks.
It's then that Monet transforms
into a terrifying monster
and the situation worsens.
The crew find themselves backed into a corner.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Deadly Fight in a Blizzard!
The Straw Hats vs. the Snow Woman!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!