All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen
and learned about the ruler of the
island - Caesar Clown's motive.
Now, get off, children!
This is your home!
Don't ever go out on your own!
My head hurts!
Master, give me the candy now!
Of course, you can have it soon.
Relax and enjoy the candies in the room!
They are very, very delicious!
All while trying to escape Shinokuni,
along with their pirate ally
- the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
Luffy and the others are on
the move to kidnap Caesar,
-- save the children, and
escape from the island.
"To Save Her Friends! Mocha
Runs at the Risk of Her Life!"
Mocha!
Give us the candy!
--Sis!
--Hurry up!
Uh-huh!
Get off of me! What are you doing?!
Calm down! It's a sedative.
Huh? Where am I?
It's nothing!
Oh no! Go after the children!
Alright!
Give us the candy!
Wait!
Milky Ball!
Again!
This is getting nowhere!
How far does Mocha have to run?!
Candy!
Sis!
Candy...
Candy!
Are you alright, Mocha?!
Chopper-chan!
Go ahead while we hold them!
Uh-huh!
Wait, Mocha!
Let's hold the kids here!
We won't let them go after Mocha!
Please, Mocha! Hang on, somehow!
THE BISCUIT ROOM
Wh-Where am I?
Wh-Wh-Wh-What're you... what're you doing?!
This is embarrassing! No! Put me down!
Shut up! This is no time
for that kind of crap!
Look!
The deadly gas is flowing
into the Biscuit Room?!
Oh no! It'll fill up B Building in no time!
Now you know. So shut up!
You're causing me a lot of trouble!
What do you want?!
The exit is not that way!
What?! You should've told me sooner!
Put me down before we
catch up with my people!
Why do you have so much pride?!
I can just throw you away if you want!
What now?!
Is this the legendary sword - Shusui?!
Don't touch it! Shut up and
just hold on, you sword geek!
Where should I go?
I don't know which way I should go anymore!
Candy!
No!
Mocha?!
Give us the candy!
No!
Candy! Candy!
Konbu! Biyo! Stop! Please listen to me!
Candy!
Give me the candy!
--Mocha!
--Oh no!
Some children took a detour!
Everybody, stop!
Oh no! If they get the candies,
we have to start all over again!
We have to separate Mocha from the kids!
--Mil Fleurs...
--Outta my way!
Let's go!
Milky Ball!
Gigantesco Mano!
Give us the candy!
--No!
--Give it to us!
No, you can't have it!
It's not fair! You can't have it all!
If you eat it, you can't go home!
Don't you wanna see your father and mother?!
Shut up!
Just give us the candy already!
I want to go home!!
I want to go home with
everybody! Safe and healthy!
She ate them all!
Mocha!
What is she thinking?!
--Give them back to us!
--Screw you!
How dare you eat them all, you jerk!
Mocha!!
No, spit them all out!
Mocha, can you hear me?!
Mocha!!
I told you what kind of drug they are!
Hey!
Why shouldn't we eat the candy?
Because...
...that candy is a deadly poison!
What?!
Chopper-chan.
They're all...
...my friends!
It's a promise!
--I promise!
I promise!
Don't do it!
When we grow up,
let's set out to the sea!
To the sea?!
To fish?
No, fool! To go on an adventure!
We'll look for an island made
of gold and that sort of thing.
Sounds like fun!
When we get well and go home,
we'll all be separated, right?
But if we all set out to
the sea when we grow up, we
can see each other again!
Oh, that'll be great! We've
become such good friends now!
When do we set out to the sea?
Well...
When we turn 20 years old!
That'll take forever.
That makes it more exciting to wait for!
You're right!
Okay, let's make a promise!
I promise!
So, the Master is a bad person?!
Yes, he's a very bad person.
But he's always very nice to us!
And he gives us the sweet candy everyday!
That's his trick.
What?! No way! But...
You children are his test subjects!
T-Test subjects?!
Open up, Mocha!
We're gonna go to the Biscuit Room!
Candy!
You kids were never sick from the beginning.
Th-That can't be...
Your giant body is proof.
I've heard turning people
into giants has been
a project underway for hundreds
of years all over the world.
Which means they've kept
failing at it for hundreds
of years and no one has succeeded yet.
You may not want to hear this but...
This experiment...
…is doomed to failure, too!
Caesar knows that.
I suppose he's just collecting
data for his next experiment.
Then, what's gonna happen to us?
You're all gonna die.
None of you will make it home.
That sweet candy is a deadly poison.
It'll destroy your body before you know it.
But as soon as you eat one,
you'll crave another one.
The more you eat, the harder it is
for you to get away from Caesar!
You see how scary it is
when you look at those kids
on the other side of the door, don't you?
I sedated you already.
But, from side-effects of the
candy and the experiment,
before you can even become an adult,
you'll probably die.
Mocha!!
We can't even become adults?
We can't see our fathers and mothers again?
No, if you kids don't escape now.
We never even thought about that.
We asked you to help us
because we wanted to go home!
We were afraid to be told to stay here
for another year without knowing
what kind of disease we have!
But...
We never thought that we were gonna die.
We thought we could grow up!
That's not what we've been told!
We ate the candy because they gave it to us!
We never thought we were gonna die from it!
I know! It's not your fault at all!
That's why we can't forgive Caesar!
We're not gonna forgive him!
I'm sorry!
That we didn't find you sooner!
Chopper-chan?
Chopper-chan, we...
...don't wanna die!
You're not gonna die!
We're gonna save you all!
Caesar is actually a powerful,
horrible, evil man.
But... But...
Our captain is stronger than him!
He's gonna become the
king of the sea someday!
Luffy will kick Caesar's butt for sure!
So listen carefully.
Your name is Mocha, isn't it?
We can't let other children
have any more candy!
Uh-huh!
I'll try my best to sedate them all here!
So, Mocha, can you guard the
candies in the Biscuit Room?
Uh-huh!
I see! Then I won't let
anybody eat the candy!
I wanna go home with everybody!
Great!
Mocha!
Mocha spewed up blood!
Why? Those were just the sweet candies.
What happened to Mocha?
Hey, she doesn't look well.
--I can't believe it...
--The children have stopped!
That's what happens when you're greedy.
Mocha!
Mocha! Stay with me!
Why?
This is what the candy really does to you!
Mocha tried to save you all by...
...sacrificing herself!
Chopper! If you wanna sedate
them, now is the chance!
But I have to treat her first!
We have no time!
The children are standing still!
Go!
Yeah!
Don't use violence, guys!
Fight numbers with numbers!
Yeah!
Bring them under control!
Alright!
--Sanji-kun?!
--The Navy?!
Sanji!
Brother! Is aiming for the
balls considered violence?
--It's a close call, but yes, it is.
--Alright!
--Medical team, step forward!
--Yes, sir!
Chopper, use them! They know how
to give injections at least!
Okay!
Alright, let's calm the kids down!
Thank you, guys!
1, 2, 3!
Advance!
If I'm correct, there is an
examination room around here!
Carry her there!
We have no time! Do you know that, racoon?!
Yes, I do!
Enough of the chitchat! Let's just go!
Mocha.--
Damn! It's my fault!
Chopper-chan...
Mocha, are you okay? Are you in pain?
Chopper-chan, I...
I didn't give them the candies.
Mocha! You...
Uh-huh! You tried to save
your friends, didn't you?
Thank you! Thank you!
They can all go home thanks to you!
Uh-huh...
I will save you at any cost, Mocha!
I will!
You'll become an adult!
Uh-huh.
What?!
C BUILDING 1ST FLOOR - A DUMPSTER
Why did the dumpster
explode all of a sudden?!
Wh-Who is it?!
Straw Hat Luffy! Why are you here?!
Shoot! Shoot!
Where's Caesar?
Huh?
What?!
I don't know! I-I don't know anything...
Where's Caesar?!
I-I-If you go straight down this path,
you'll get to R Building and he's there!
I see.
Thanks.
Brownbeard tries to save the soldiers
by revealing Caesar's true identity.
But Caesar manages to twist his words, and ingeniously conceals the truth.
After seeing Caesar laughing triumphantly,
Luffy's rage reaches its limit
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Brownbeard in Grief! Luffy
Lands a Furious Blow!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!