Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in
search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu
kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu
kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to
the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to
the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that's what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner :D
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece,
I'll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece,
I'll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It's important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won't left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that's our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I'm
aiming at hasn't changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I'm
aiming at hasn't changed
I can't stand still, I can't stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
we go!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
However, no one has
ever fully explored it
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
They learned about the ruler of
Punk Hazard - Caesar's motive
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
I'm gonna become the
King of the Pirates!
and all while trying to escape Shinokuni,
along with their pirate ally
- the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
they are on the move to kidnap Caesar,
The Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
After surviving a fierce battle,
The Straw Hats landed on Punk Hazard;
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen.
save the children, and
escape from the island.
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They learned about the ruler of the island
---Caesar Clown's motive
and landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
Catch me if you can! But I'm protected!
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen
and all while trying to escape Shinokuni,
They learned about the ruler
of the island and the puppeteer
Doflamingo! The Four Emperors!
and learned about the ruler of the
island - Caesar Clown's motive.
along with their pirate ally
- the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
of Shinokuni - Caesar Clown's motive
Do you even have balls to
pick a fight with them?
and along with their pirate ally -
the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
Luffy and the others are on
the move to kidnap Caesar,--
All while trying to escape Shinokuni,
they are caught in a climactic battle.
they are caught in a climactic
battle in order to
save the children, and
escape from the island.
they are heading to R Building with
the children that they rescued.
--I don't think so! If you wanna run, do it now!
--A fight?
And they finally defeated Caesar.
kidnap Caesar, save the children,
and escape from the island.
Get out of my face!
Finally, a climactic battle rages
on-- between Luffy and Caesar!
I have that crazy pirate backing me!
What's that?!
One of the Seven Warlords
- Don Quixote Doflamingo!
LAND OF DEATH
I said...
Smoker! The least I can do is...
...I don't care!
This is my scientific power!
...take you along to hell with me!
I've been...
...picking fights all along!
Caesar is...
Monet. I can't believe you're alive.
...the type of person that
Luffy hates the most!
Vergo's been beaten.
"A Surprising Outcome!
White Chase vs. Vergo!"
H-Help me, Master!
It's all because of my misjudgment.
Luffy won't forgive Caesar!
I broke... the gear!
I feel bad for you all.
M-Master!
Now,
Caesar!
But I want to make sure
to wipe out all those squirts now.
there is no turning back!
I don't ever wanna see your face again!
At the Third Laboratory, there
is another weapon that was
"Caesar's Defeat!-- The
Powerful Grizzly Magnum!"
"Running Wild!
Invincible General Franky!"
Go to hell!
responsible for destroying the
First and Second Laboratory
Gum-Gum...
...Grizzly Magnum!
and the rest of the
island four years ago.
The deadly gas - Shinokuni will fill
up the building-- in five minutes.
Ow, ow, ow... My nose!
With just the push of a button,
You broke my nose!
The survivors are all heading
toward R Building -
there will be only one survivor on the whole island.
How dare you! Dammit!
Ow, ow, ow...
the "R-66" door, the only
exit to escape. However...
No one else can take
that highly toxic gas.
Damn you! Were you even listening to me?!
Oh yeah, Straw Hat!
And that's Caesar!
You can't get away with this!
You can work under me if you want...
The button is at...
You don't have to say it, Joker.
I have that crazy pirate backing me!
B BUILDING - SANJI
I was gonna do that, anyway.
One of the Seven Warlords
- Don Quixote Doflamingo!
Thank you.
I need you to perish along
with everything else.
He is the behind-the-scenes
string-puller of the New World!
"Raid! An Assassin from Dressrosa!"
The ceiling lifted up just now!
Small arms, war weapons, drugs...
What just happened?!
Understood.
He's involved in every risky transaction!
The gas has started flowing
in from the cracks!
"A Critical Situation!
Punk Hazard Explodes!"
This is no good.
He's the mastermind of the underground!
General Left!
--Everybody! Get to R Building now!
--Run!
He's connected to all the notorious figures!
But I'm scared, Sis!
You're no match for him!
I can't run anymore!
He'll bring you under in a matter of minutes!
We have no time for wimping out, kids!
You and your friends!
Stand up and run!
Don't give up, everybody!
Stand up! Now!
You okay, Buffalo?!
What is that-dasuyan?!
B-But I can still spare your life.
How do I know?!
I-I-If you apologize now...
--Captain-chan!
--I'm glad that you're okay!
Can't believe it's just
shooting at us like that!
So you beat that bird woman, huh?!
Again?!
Think about how many monsters you will
But why are they coming from that direction?!
I thought they were behind
us to let us get away!
piss off if you do something to me!
The G-5 is coming this way?!
Okay?!
What is that?! A Pacifista?!
Hey, are you listening?! Hmmm?
I told you we were going the wrong way!
It's fast!
No, it can't be!
I'm talking about the Warlords
and the Four Emperors!
VARIOUS PLACES IN THE NEW WORLD
Caesar has no interest in human weapons!
That aside, p-put me down!
This is embarrassing!
They'll make you...
Buffalo!
That's a pain! Just stay where you are!
...drown at sea in the blink of an eye!
What is going on?
Hey, get off of him!
Hey! Who said you can carry
Tashigi-chan on your shoulder?!
Alright! I don't know what it is but...
I-If you apologize now, I'll
let you off the hook...
Is this some kind of joke?!
I won't!
This is what they call a "public experiment"?
Zoro! Head back!
He kicked Caesar's ass!
Hey, you're heavy! Get off!
Mama should know about this-bon!
Gastille!
Why is there a dragon here?!
...if it wants a fight,
that's what it'll get!
--Hurry up, everybody!
--This way!
Oh, I met him at a garbage dump.
Joker is going to take action.
You brought him with you?
That serves you right!
Let "Jack" know about this.
Yeah!
A gas burner attack that could melt iron!
It's no mistake!
You sure?! It's not gonna be pretty!
I think they formed an alliance.
Let the world know.
Did he get melted away? Or incinerated?!
This is not just a problem
in the underground anymore.
Father!
What's wrong with him?
Watch out! This place is gonna collapse!
Father!
I don't know what it
was but I destroyed it!
B BUILDING 2ND FLOOR
The eel is gonna attack me!
I-I-I-I know! It doesn't feel
like it's real, does it?!
"Broke the gear"?
"There's no turning back"?
Hurry up! Hurry up! Hurry up!
It's too much for a rookie who
just came to the New World!
Hey, Momo!
That's hysterical.
Mocha! You can make it!
But one of those monsters is here in the lab.
Who is this dragon? He said "Father."
THE THIRD LABORATORY- R BUILDING
It's Vergo!
No one can compete against his Armament Haki!
Mocha! You're gonna be alright!
Find out later.
Everybody, hurry up! Get on the truck!
Show some medical team guts, guys!
Smoker and Law are goners!
--Get on the front car, too!
--Watch your step!
I don't see any light.
The exit must be farther away.
So are all of your crew!
Hey, Chopper-yan! Are you
sure this is the right way?!
--Kids, come on!
--Hurry up!
I-I-I said you're all gonna die!
S-S-So why don't you listen to me...
The building will collapse soon!
How far did Caesar fly?!
I think so!
We gotta join the rest of our
crew as soon as possible!
I said...
--I can't climb!
--Come on, you can do it!
Realize your place!
Chopper, can you hear me?
They're not here yet.
...I don't care!
Law!
Is that Usopp?!
Yeah, that's not good.
Keep going straight and
go down the stairs.--
It's dangerous here. We have no time!
That's the fastest way to R Building!
B BUILDING 2ND FLOOR - THE EXAMINATION ROOM
The ceiling's gonna collapse!
Hey, where does this passage lead to?
Smoker...
Chopper-yan, it's not safe to stay here!
R BUILDING 2ND FLOOR - THE SECRET ROOM
I'm gonna shut the door to R building
If we go through, we'll reach a harbor
that has a tanker docked in it.
before the gas flows in!
Uh-huh! I've done all I could for now!
So hurry up!
A-Alright, thanks!
That deadly gas is covering the island!
Are we gonna be okay?!
Go to R Building now!
Vergo!
Alright, count on us! Let's go, guys!
Everybody, hurry up!
Okay!
Yes, we have to risk
exposure to the air outside
Yeah!
How dare you screw with the Navy!
in order to get on the tanker
Hurry up, Chopper!
but isn't it better than
being buried under some wreckage?
You're too weak. You can't beat me.
This is it for you!
Mocha! Stay with me! Let's get out of here!
Everybody, you're almost there! Keep running!
But the children...
Smoker!
We'll be fine, Sis!
We want to get out!
Nami, you're almost at R Building!
Get out and go home!
Damn.
She's right! We can make
it if we hold our breath!
How will I eat breakfast tomorrow?
We want to see our fathers and mothers!
What a horrible turn of events.
Please! Take us with you!
Why is this happening to us?
Please!
You guys are just a bunch of guinea pigs!
How dare you, Law.
No one would care if
hundreds of you die or not!
You never learn.
You're right. When it comes to this,
My basic fighting skill and
Haki are better than yours.
This is an upset.
You are the dregs of society!
we have no choice but
to leave it to fate!
You still don't get it?
I can't believe the Master
was such an awful person.
Kids! We'll make it
through this at any cost!
But I know you're going to regret it.
Who should we trust from now?!
You have to survive this and go home!
Keep that in mind.
The Straw Hats.
Yeah!
You don't know Joker's past.
Too slow!
Trafalgar Law.
This room is not gonna
last very long, either!
And that will cost you your life!
Now, let's go and
recover Caesar-dasuyan!
Hurry up, everybody!
I found the stairs!
Okay, I can't believe we
got sidetracked like this!
G-5.
We're almost there!
Upstarts like you who have
acquired just a touch of fame
A little more to go, Mocha! Stay with me!
can't hope to take over the world.
Poor children.
It's filled with those
who are much stronger.
Chopper-san!
Tell him, Smoker.
What? Brook?!
White Blow!
This is serious! Kin'emon-san got...
You all...
Kin'emon-san got harmed by the gas and...
...have to...
All you squirts got is energy.
...died!
But this world is much...
...die with me.
General I'm-Okay!
What?!
No damage at all?!
Don't worry about me.
No way!
Goodbye, Young Master.
Just worry about yourself.
Take this! Now's my chance!
What happened, Brook?!
I know you will become...
While we were helping the children
in the examination room evacuate
General...
...Shield!
...the King of the Pirates.
Too slow and too small!
and looking for Kin'emon-san's
son, we met a girl.
You keep on fighting because you're
Too slow? Too small?!
angry at me for betraying the Navy?
Are you saying...
This room will explode.
...that I'm too dull and
I have no tactical skills?!
And she said...
I just want to settle the matter!
Goodbye, Vergo the pirate!
What?! Momonosuke turned to a small dragon?!
I have to finish you off with my own hands!
No, I didn't.
Don't underestimate General
Franky, the pervert robot!
Pirate Vergo!
Uh-huh! I shouldn't tell
anybody but it's true.
Your Haki isn't good enough to beat me.
General Shield...
Could it be...
Corpse-dono! Maybe, the dragon
I sliced up earlier was...
R BUILDING 1ST FLOOR
Why can't you see that?
You're trying to make up your mind now?!
Oh, um, what should I do...
What was that?
Boomerang!
--He threw his shield!
--Is he desperate?!
Shinokuni is a lethal gas that petrifies
human bodies and kills them.
Momonosuke!
S-Something is falling down!
I've done a terrible thing!
And it is now flowing into the laboratory.
Kin'emon-san, you can't go back!
My "toy" wasn't enough for you, was it?
That area is filled up with the gas by now...
I know who could have done such a thing!
Hey, what are you doing?!
All right!
If you're not letting us recover Caesar,
you're our enemy!
The deadly gas is right in front of us!
If you were going straight,
It must be Law.
we should've been caught
up with the kids by now!
My spirit will carry me through anything!
Shut up! You're wounded - shut your mouth!
Hm? What is she doing?
Whether it's fire or gas!
I am going straight!
She gave up fighting?
What is Vergo doing?!
Momonosuke!
No! Not that way!
No, that's impossible! Kin'emon-san!
Master! What's going on?!
The real fight starts now.
No! You went too far!
--Some of us buried under the wreckage!
--Master!
How can you mess up something this simple?!
And he ended up like this.
Weapon-morphosis!
Shut up!
Dammit!
That's crazy!
What should I do?! What should I do?!
You assholes ruined my "paradise"!
Hurry up, kids! Keep running!
What the hell is that?
What should I do?! What should I do?!
I feel dizzy. It feels
like I've been dreaming.
Chopper! Brook!
I wonder if everybody is okay.
What are you doing?! Don't stop!
That's because of the sedatives.
They're harmless so don't worry!
Just go down the stairs right
there and get into R Building!
Guys! Keep your eyes on the kids!
The gas is really closing in!
Yes, sir! Brother!
Gotta take advantage of this confusion!
Yeah!
Espada Girl!
Why is the Transponder Snail
still receiving the signal?
We're almost at R Building! You can make it!
Roll!
Mocha! Stay with me!
Buffalo, ready?!
Alright. Now let's look for
the Sea Prism Stone handcuffs.
You're gonna be alright soon!
Come on! Get it all out!
We're almost there! Keep running!
Dasuyan!
You've got to be kidding!
Dasuyan! Dasuyan! Dasuyan!
The survivors are heading
toward R Building, 1st floor -
--The Straw Hat member's gone!
--Where did he go?!
Dasuyan! Dasuyan!
Dasuyan! Dasuyan! Dasuyan...
the location of the last exit
Find him!
R BUILDING 1ST FLOOR
and ground zero of the fight
between Luffy and Caesar!
R Building 2nd floor, can you hear me?
Luffy!
Interesting!
Meanwhile, Kin'emon is looking
for his son Momonosuke...
Oh, it's the Master!
General Shield Boomerang!
Oh, Nami!
If the Master is okay,
we're gonna be alright!
Great! You're here already!
What have I done?! Momonosuke!
That's nothing!
Oh, Brownbeard-cchi's on the ground!
I'm at full blast-dasuyan!
Secret room, come in!
Is he okay?!
Yeah, he's okay.
What?! Momonosuke turned to a small dragon?!
Yes, Master, what just happened?
Oh, I mean, he's not okay.
Are you okay?
Open the air vents now!
Not bad! Weapon Girl and Fan Man!
Uh-huh!
The children!
I shouldn't tell anybody but it's true.
Let Shinokuni flow into this room!
Seems like there was an explosion!
Are you trying to fight
against my weapon?!
See, Momo? I told you!
I think it was in D Building.
Maybe I...
I'm just trying to protect the Sunny!
Don't worry about the children.
B-But that will...
The SAD Manufacturing
Room where I was before.
...sliced up Momonosuke?!
I'm a gas man. I'm not gonna die.
My friends are on their way to help them.
General Left!
R-Roger!
Really?!
Momonosuke!
Then let's get our fellow soldiers
on the 1st floor upstairs first!
They always keep their word!
The Young Master said
"immediately"-dasuyan!
I've done a terrible thing!
I said "Now"!
I know! I'll finish him
off with a single blow!
So don't worry!
Kin'emon-san, you can't go back!
I said "Do it now"!
Monet.
That area is filled up with the gas by now...
Stop complaining and just do it already!
Missile Girl!
Hurry up! Get to where
Nami-san and the others are!
But there are over a hundred soldiers!
The deadly gas is right in front of us!
--You ready-dasuyan?!
--Go ahead!
--This way!
--Hurry up!
I don't care, you idiot!
Dasuyan!
My spirit will carry me through anything!
This way!
I see R Building!
You guys are just a bunch of guinea pigs!
Spin-Spin Projectile Cannon!
Whether it's fire or gas!
Chopper and the others are not there yet?
No one would care if
hundreds of you die or not!
We'll take Caesar with us!
Momonosuke!
What are you talking about?! Caesar?!
No, that's impossible! Kin'emon-san!
He was giving the girl first aid.
You are the dregs of society!
Can he make it?
General Left!
Goodbye, Smoker!
This is no good.
The Sea Prism Stone handcuffs...
Maybe, they're here.
No, they aren't!
I made it!
Now that was a dramatic finish.
Because I hear the "Usopp
alarm" ringing in my head now.
Are you guys okay?! Good to see you!
Yes, let's just pretend
that I checked this room.
He's not here.
What are you doing?! Can't you hear me?!
That's it!
Tell them "I looked all over but
the Sea Prism Handcuffs weren't..."
Smoker-san...
I can find replacements
for you fools so easily!
THE PATH BETWEEN BUILDING R AND D
What happened, Monet?
"...in that room!"
Do we really need this?
Yes, this is the truck that they
use to transport containers of SAD.
Young Master...
Shinokuni is my true power!
I'm gonna let everybody ride it.
This laboratory will collapse soon.
We have to escape as soon as possible.
He's an enemy!
Where am I?
Why is this always happening to me?!
That was close!
I can't move! Damn! Am I going to die?!
Straw Hat-ya!
Now they know who Caesar really is.
Tra-guy! Smokey! I didn't expect
you to come from that way!
Dammit! It's all because of them!
Zoro and the others!
Trafalgar Law!
Hey, Law.
They're really in danger!
Oh, Smo-yan!
What?! Smo-yan?!
Could I control the doors
from here, by any chance?
--It's Smo-yan!
--Smo-yan!
If we can get out of here,
we'll go separate ways.
It's really him!
Smoker-san!
But there is something
I want to ask you.
I'm glad that you're okay!
Smo-yan! I'm so glad! We
have so much to report!
What?
Hey! Why're you looking at me like that?
Stop screaming!
Huh? N-No, I...
I know.
White...
Oh, I get it!
...Blow!
The Navy G-5 Vice
Admiral Smoker's heart!
The Master is trying to fool the enemies!
Hey! Where did Caesar go?!
This is yours.
What?
What a nice gift, Law.
Oh yeah! You're right!
Oh, I kicked his ass and he got blown
away along with the door that way!
He must have a plan about
the deadly gas, too!
The fight is over.
How far did he go?
He's not gonna let his people die!
Hey! You... Our plan was to kidnap him!
Right, right!
Are you satisfied now, Smoker-kun?
The Master is a kind man. It would hurt him
I thought Caesar had my heart.
But I don't even wanna
catch that bastard anymore!
if he finds out we suspected him.
That was the plan if you like it or not!
What are you gonna do if he runs away?!
Smoker! The least I can do is...
How did it end up in your hands?
Master! I opened the air vents!
...take you along to hell with me!
Who cares about that jerk?!
He just got the wrong idea.
You think you can just
change a plan as you like.
Let me keep your heart!
It's a shame that I
can't watch him dying!
No! The deadly gas!
I shouldn't have trusted you!
And that's a deal!
It's flowing in!
Let's get him!
He'll open his eyes wide,
spew up blood and suffocate in no time!
Yes. You should've done
as I said from the start!
What?!
Dregs shouldn't think!
It'll cause fear and panic
in all those he's with!
To earn the trust of Caesar,
No matter how deeply you believe in justice,
The Straw Hats have foiled the plans
I let him keep my heart
I get excited just by imagining it...
Now, become my power! Shinokuni!
you can't do anything if you're weak!
of Master Caesar Clown, scientist
and ruler of Punk Hazard Island.
and took his secretary
Monet's heart in return.
The door's starting to close!
Who did that?!
Now it's a deal!
Hey, what is that?
However, A Building has filled up
with Shinokuni, the deadly gas.
And then I cut your heart
out when you got to the lab.
And now, B Building is almost filled as well.
The deadly gas!
Hurry up! Get on now!
What do you want?
On top of that, Caesar's laboratory
has started collapsing.
If I can take my heart back,
So I had two hearts in my possession.
LAND OF DEATH
Hey, what're you guys
doing, Straw Hats?!
Hurry up! Brook! Chopper!
I can kick your ass easily, Vergo!
Run! Run!
The only exit to escape from
the laboratory as well
Don't make me repeat myself, squirt!
All of you, get on now!
This is my scientific power!
as the island is the "R-66"
door in R Building.
If we let Caesar get away,
our plan will be ruined!
It's Vergo-san to you!
Hang on, Brownbeard-cchi,
for a little bit more.
What're you talking about?!
This is not "all of us"!
Chopper will take care of you soon!
Some of my crew are not here yet!
Mocha is not here, either!
Hey, Luffy.
The Navy G-5 Vice
Admiral Smoker's heart!
Do you think they are alright?
Some of our soldiers
are not here, either!
Of course.
What a nice gift, Law.
I'm sure they will get here!
Tashigi, I want you to lead the G-5 soldiers.
I gave his secretary Monet's heart
back to him out of kindness.
Where are you going, Smoker-san?
Don't tell me you're going after Vergo!
The law can't settle these matters, Tashigi!
I have to do it myself! He was
messing around with the Navy!
Stop it, Tashigi!
It's kicking in.
THE PATH BETWEEN BUILDING B AND R
Wouldn't you rather die than
grovel before a pirate?!
Meanwhile, before the showdown
between Luffy and Caesar...
Hurry up, Chopper! Brook!
Right now, we have to beg for our lives,
Okay, I'll hurry, Usopp!
Respond.
throwing ourselves at his
feet if that's what it takes!
We are the ones who are running!
Because if we die here,
we can't save our people!
Outrun the gas somehow!
Monet.
Hurry up! 50 meters to go!
R BUILDING 2ND FLOOR - THE SECRET ROOM
Look, Straw Hat Luffy!
This amazing appearance!
And the children...
In the sky near Punk Hazard...
The gate is closing! Slide in!
As they say, if you are kind to people,
This building is gonna collapse soon!
This is my scientific power!
I better go, too!
The end of mission is the end of love.
You're gonna die here, too, Law!
DON QUIXOTE PIRATES - A
SERVANT / AN ASSASSIN BABY 5
good things will happen to you.
Through this experiment,
Oh no! I completely forgot about
the Sea Prism Stone handcuffs!
I'll finish him off when I get back!
two countries have already expressed
interest in the weapon - Shinokuni.
Hey guys, I don't think you know where
Joker! What an asshole!
they are but I'm looking
for the Sea Prism Stone...
He killed my sweet fianc
by destroying the whole town!
They are both quite peaceful.
These, young man?!
How easy!
Yeah, there are a lot of them!
But when humans get serious
about defending themselves,
I don't need that many!
I won't forgive him!
But I'm glad that I asked!
And this is the eighth time!
they'll look for any way
possible to kill their enemies!
Are you gonna go downstairs?!
He killed eight men that I loved
and made a commitment to,
Smoker...
It's too mortifying to die here
because of that jerk!
Everybody needs me!
and destroyed eight towns!
Do you still wanna fight, Smoker-kun?
Why does he want to screw up my happiness?!
We'll come with you!
I'll spread weapons all over the world
You know you're no match for me.
Do as you like!
Chopper, Brook! Get clear safely!
and become the king of the
land of death (Shinokuni)!
Because the Young Master loves you-dasuyan!
The gate is gonna close!
DON QUIXOTE PIRATES - A COMBATANT BUFFALO
He loves you like his own sister
--Damn! We're dead!
--We can't make it!
so he doesn't begrudge destroying a town
Look!
It's only over when you give up!
or two-dasuyan!
What are you doing?
We'll survive at any cost!
Run!
You have to learn to say "No"!
--But the deadly gas is...
--It's the end!
You shouldn't turn to
smoke and spread yourself
What was wrong with him?! He needed me!
No...
thin when you're facing a better Haki user.
I fell in love with you at first sight!
--He killed our fellow soldiers!
--What is he doing?!
Will you marry me?
It just makes it easier for me to hit you!
What?!
Master!
Does he really think of us as guinea pigs?
How did you like it?
This Missile Girl's...
It's amazing if I do say so myself!
...flame of love?
Just ten days later, he
became the eighth victim.
Look how fast it works on their nerves!
Hey, Baby 5!
Why do you keep using
your Devil Fruit power?
Luffy!
That's almost an art!
Do you need this weapon?
Even though you're a weapon woman yourself.
I feel terrible!
Can't you even think straight?
He shouldn't have loved
me in the first place!
Wh-What... What was that?
It's not like you, Smoker-kun.
When someone asks you something,
you can't say "No."
Thank you for picking it up, Buffalo!
Those people are...
You have to do something about it!
It's them!
That's my good luck charm!
It's weird to subscribe to
50 different newspapers!
Hey, everybody!
Enough playing around!
Mocha!
You lend others too much money!
An owner of this weapon is
destined to become happy
What a relief!
You are forced to buy so much stuff!
Momo, look after Brownbeard.
and if you buy this,
you'd make me happy, too!
Hey!
How much debt do you have now?
Huh? Okay!
What?! He...
It's none of your business!
About 98 million berries!
We made it!
--Okay, we're all here!
--You had us worried!
...needs me!
Hey, where are you going, Straw Hat Luffy?!
It's my life!
I'm glad that you made it!
I'm absolutely sure that he fooled you!
Stay out of it!
Yeah, thanks to you, Usopp!
Demon Bamboo!
Did you chicken out all of a sudden?!
We were the ones who ran like hell!
Oh yeah! Can I borrow 2 million berries?
Behind you-dasuyan!
What a pathetic man!
We have no time! Hurry up!
What?!
But B Building beyond that path is
almost filled up with Shinokuni!
He needs me!
Get on, everybody!
This place is gonna collapse!
I don't know who you are but...
Um... When do you need it?
Hear that?! Get on the truck, you...
There is no place to run
on the island anymore!
I'm an invincible Iron Pirate!
Huh?! Where did they go?!
Let's go!
When I go back, I wanna hit a casino!
That's fast!
I know you wanna kill me
for messing with the Navy.
Hurry up!
That goes for all of you guinea pigs, too!
Th-Then, I'll get it ready for you
as soon as we complete our mission!
I don't fight for the peace of the sea!
Let's get out of here, guys!
Yeah!
But you have to be strong
enough to do so, Smoker.
--Iron Pirate!
--How persistent!
Hey, what should we do?!
What should we do about Kin'emon-san?!
If you're just reckless, you can't
make your people proud of you.
Weapon-morphosis!
What?! Kin'emon?!
Revolver Girl!
All of you,
What can we do? I mean, he's like...
die...
Oh! It doesn't work!
Ki... Kin'emon?!
...like trash!
I'll carry out this mission because he
asked me but I'll kill Joker at any cost!
It's over.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
It just made me itchy!
That's who the Master really is?!
This guy's pretty tough!
Ring, ring, ring... Clank!
Baby 5!
Catch it!
There it is!
Thanks, Buffalo!
Smoker, my heart...
Punk Hazard-dasuyan!
Master!
It's not over yet!
I trusted him so!
Joker... Can you hear me?
Thank you for winning it back!
The island is covered in Caesar's
gas and I can't see a thing.
Excuse me. I know you're broken-hearted
but could I sit in that control seat?
Now it makes sense! You bastard!
That's why you turned to smoke!
I wanna save my friends from the gas!
Will it go away if I fire this?
You bastard!
It's...
You were watching it, weren't you? Dammit!
Now we're even.
No, it won't!
Let me take care of it!
This is no good!
It's collapsing faster!
Stop! I know you all watched it, too.
...Monet.
Just finish him off already!
Could you hop off and wait for me, Baby 5?
Monet. I can't believe you're alive.
Yeah, you're right. We've
been terribly betrayed!
You don't wanna owe a pirate, huh?
Okay!
Look out!
Vergo's been beaten.
We're finished.
It's a dishonor to a Navy soldier.
Now we know that he was our enemy but...
Caesar, too.
I'm too ashamed to be seen by my people.
The passage is gonna collapse!
But Baby 5 and Buffalo
will probably recover him.
...we can't run from here!
But...
But so are you people!
...that was just the help I needed.
We're in a tunnel through a mountain.
If it collapses, we'll be buried alive.
Oh. That's good to hear.
Did you just see your
captain run from Caesar?!
Don't say it in a relaxed matter!
It's all because of my misjudgment.
It's over.
That serves you right!
He took off leaving you guys behind!
I feel bad for you all.
Behold! My typhoon-like power!
Vergo... -san.
You child!
Whoa-whoa, are you dissing our
captain right in front of me?
But I want to make sure
to wipe out all those squirts now.
Now you remember that I'm better than you?
Oh no! The wreckage blocked our way!
Gust - Matasaburo!
I just want you to keep thinking like that.
Where are the brakes?!
But you can't stay sitting
on that "throne" forever!
Yee-haw!
If he were the kind of
person who would betray us,
Keep going.
You two!
At the Third Laboratory,
What?!
there is another weapon
that was responsible for
it would've been easier for me.
I know you're listening, "Joker"!
destroying the First
and Second Laboratory
I would've just run away with
my tail between my legs!
and the rest of the
island four years ago.
Third Gear!
With just the push of a button,
there will be only one survivor on the whole island.
But he never ever stops...
Now let's wait there until Caesar,
Monet, and Vergo come out.
Vergo is a dead man, Joker.
No one else can take
that highly toxic gas.
...believing in us...
You're about to lose your right-hand man.
And that's Caesar!
...so we had no choice but to support him.
And Straw Hat-ya will take care of Caesar.
I wanna get back quick to play
roulette at a casino-dasuyan!
The button is at...
You don't have to say it, Joker.
That means you're also gonna lose SAD.
We pledged to live up to his
expectations as long as we breathe!
You couldn't see this coming
because you were overconfident.
I was gonna do that, anyway.
What's this noise?
Cool!
Can't believe it! He saved us!
So why don't you just keep
cackling like always
I'm right in front of
the triggering device.
Master, please don't...
I don't want him to be my enemy!
Although he already is!
It's from there!
and think about your next move.
But you won't be laughing for long because...
The explosion will ruin the tanker
that they're planning on escaping with.
You people are just crumbs. You
shouldn't stand against your master!
You're gonna lose one of your tankers -
is it okay?
...we're gonna do the unthinkable!
Just drop dead like a dog!
Thank you.
Don't get too comfortable yet.
I need you to perish along
with everything else.
What?!
The tanker exploded?!
No! Something hit it-dasuyan!
Nice try acting strong, squirt!
--What should we do?
--There's nothing we can do.
But are you sure you'll survive?
Understood.
We can't beat such a powerful man!
--Yes, you can!
--What?
Young Master.
Look at Vergo in front of you.
It's a human! There!
You guys should just believe in our captain!
Didn't you piss him off?
The deadly gas!
What?! Caesar Clown?!
You've got to be kidding!
No way!
Caesar is...
...the type of person that
Luffy hates the most!
Do you remember what happened last time?
It's that thing again.
DRESSROSA
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Is it flowing in through
cracks of walls?
How did it go?
Ring, ring... Clank!
You pissed Vergo off and then what happened?
It's gonna be more than
just being buried alive.
H-Help me, Master!
Joker! This is Buffalo from Punk Hazard!
Yes!
Stop saying such horrible things
in a cool manner!
What's up?
I am the Master!
It must've been traumatic.
You probably can't forget it.
Joker! We just arrived
at Punk Hazard-dasuyan!
I am your savior and I can make efficient
use of you good-for-nothings!
You must be afraid of Vergo.
We don't know what's going on
but we just saw Master Caesar...
Even with your incomparable swordplay,
There is going to be
gas around the exit.
...getting blown out of the
building, injured-dasuyan!--
his Haki will allow him to
block your every attack.
Can anybody here generate wind?
What?!
Luffy won't forgive Caesar!
Both in terms of status and power,
What?
It's not so easy to find a person
with such a special skill!
Armament Hardening!
you're no match for Vergo!
I can do that.
Recover Caesar immediately
and come back to Dressrosa!
How easy?!
Okay! We'll recover Caesar-dasuyan!
Here we go!
Caesar!
I see the exit!
What about Monet and Vergo?!
You're back, Straw Hat Luffy!
There must be a reason. Let's do as he says.
Alright, we're almost there!
I don't ever wanna see your face again!
Go faster!
Roger! Joker!
Clank!
Your death is going to be the
climax of this experiment show!
I'll make you realize my anger!
Go to hell, Smoker!
I'm sorry, partner.
I've known you the longest.
Go to hell!
Fools.
Hey, squirts! Luck is on my side!
Gum-Gum...
Thank you for all your work.
As long as I have Caesar in my
custody, he can create SAD for me!
...Grizzly Magnum!
Young Master!
Young Master?
Hey, you all! We got to go! Get on the truck!
Now, drop dead! Behold my scientific power!
It's been two years since
the War of the Best.
I can't find him.
Kneel before my power!
Young Master!
Did anyone actually accomplish anything?
All you did was stay calm.
The Young Master is nowhere to be found.
He must be in the room
on the fourth floor.
All Whitebeard did was end the era.
Shut up!
Uh-uh! He wasn't there.
I wonder what happened to him-dasuyan.
The Navy Headquarters rounded up new forces.
The window was open.
Oh, okay.
The big-timers didn't take any action!
Huh?! Do you see someone
on the deck of the tanker?!
Then I don't know where he is.
It was like everybody was
just preparing for something.
No, I think no one could survive that gas.
Goodbye, Young Master.
That war was only a beginning.
He went out by himself again.
What's that?!
I know you will become...
Oh yeah, Straw Hat!
You can work under me if you want...
It's me. Tell me what's
going on over there.
You always told me...
...the King of the Pirates.
W-We've actually been blocked by
some kind of iron guard!
...that the new era of the daring ones
is coming along with an unstoppable swell!
Is it still safe there?
Yes, it is!
Which means the island and those squirts
haven't been wiped out.
I broke... the gear!
A robot?!
You two.
Now,
Take care of that guard.
there is no turning back!
What is that strange bird?
I'm on my way!
In Building R, which is on
the verge of collapse...
Law's attack turns the tables in an instant.
Luffy has crushed Caesar.
...Luffy waits intently for his
crewmates to wrap things up.
The shocking news...
The Straw Hats scramble
and aim for a quick getaway.
...spreads across the New
World in the blink of an eye.
Meanwhile,
Meanwhile...
But Caesar, at the pinnacle of his rage...
with the help of some powerful Devil Fruit powers...
...an assassin sent by Doflamingo...
...Baby 5 and Buffalo attack.
...flies toward the island of Punk Hazard.
...unleashes a terrible attack on Luffy...
General Franky alone confronts them.
...that annihilates friend and foe alike.
The storm of a new battle rages!
On the next episode of One Piece!
Running Wild!
Invincible General Franky!
"Caesar's Defeat!-- The
Powerful Grizzly Magnum!"
"Raid! An Assassin from Dressrosa!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!