All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They learned about the ruler of
Punk Hazard - Caesar's motive
and all while trying to escape Shinokuni,
along with their pirate ally
- the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
they are on the move to kidnap Caesar,
save the children, and
escape from the island.
Catch me if you can! But I'm protected!
Doflamingo! The Four Emperors!
Do you even have balls to
pick a fight with them?
--I don't think so! If you wanna run, do it now!
--A fight?
Get out of my face!
I've been...
...picking fights all along!
"A Surprising Outcome!
White Chase vs. Vergo!"
M-Master!
Ow, ow, ow... My nose!
You broke my nose!
How dare you! Dammit!
Ow, ow, ow...
Damn you! Were you even listening to me?!
You can't get away with this!
I have that crazy pirate backing me!
One of the Seven Warlords
- Don Quixote Doflamingo!
He is the behind-the-scenes
string-puller of the New World!
Small arms, war weapons, drugs...
He's involved in every risky transaction!
He's the mastermind of the underground!
He's connected to all the notorious figures!
You're no match for him!
He'll bring you under in a matter of minutes!
You and your friends!
B-But I can still spare your life.
I-I-If you apologize now...
Think about how many monsters you will
piss off if you do something to me!
Okay?!
Hey, are you listening?! Hmmm?
I'm talking about the Warlords
and the Four Emperors!
They'll make you...
...drown at sea in the blink of an eye!
I-If you apologize now, I'll
let you off the hook...
Gastille!
That serves you right!
Yeah!
A gas burner attack that could melt iron!
Did he get melted away? Or incinerated?!
I-I-I-I know! It doesn't feel
like it's real, does it?!
It's too much for a rookie who
just came to the New World!
But one of those monsters is here in the lab.
It's Vergo!
No one can compete against his Armament Haki!
Smoker and Law are goners!
So are all of your crew!
I-I-I said you're all gonna die!
S-S-So why don't you listen to me...
I said...
...I don't care!
Smoker...
Vergo!
How dare you screw with the Navy!
You're too weak. You can't beat me.
You never learn.
My basic fighting skill and
Haki are better than yours.
You still don't get it?
Too slow!
White Blow!
You keep on fighting because you're
angry at me for betraying the Navy?
I just want to settle the matter!
I have to finish you off with my own hands!
Pirate Vergo!
Your Haki isn't good enough to beat me.
Why can't you see that?
Shinokuni is a lethal gas that petrifies
human bodies and kills them.
And it is now flowing into the laboratory.
Hey, what are you doing?!
If you were going straight,
we should've been caught
up with the kids by now!
Shut up! You're wounded - shut your mouth!
I am going straight!
No! Not that way!
No! You went too far!
How can you mess up something this simple?!
Shut up!
Hurry up, kids! Keep running!
I feel dizzy. It feels
like I've been dreaming.
That's because of the sedatives.
They're harmless so don't worry!
Guys! Keep your eyes on the kids!
Yes, sir! Brother!
Yeah!
Mocha! Stay with me!
You're gonna be alright soon!
Come on! Get it all out!
The survivors are heading
toward R Building, 1st floor -
the location of the last exit
and ground zero of the fight
between Luffy and Caesar!
Meanwhile, Kin'emon is looking
for his son Momonosuke...
What have I done?! Momonosuke!
What?! Momonosuke turned to a small dragon?!
Uh-huh!
I shouldn't tell anybody but it's true.
Maybe I...
...sliced up Momonosuke?!
Momonosuke!
I've done a terrible thing!
Kin'emon-san, you can't go back!
That area is filled up with the gas by now...
The deadly gas is right in front of us!
My spirit will carry me through anything!
Whether it's fire or gas!
Momonosuke!
No, that's impossible! Kin'emon-san!
The Sea Prism Stone handcuffs...
Maybe, they're here.
No, they aren't!
Because I hear the "Usopp
alarm" ringing in my head now.
Yes, let's just pretend
that I checked this room.
That's it!
Tell them "I looked all over but
the Sea Prism Handcuffs weren't..."
"...in that room!"
He's an enemy!
Why is this always happening to me?!
White...
...Blow!
Are you satisfied now, Smoker-kun?
No matter how deeply you believe in justice,
you can't do anything if you're weak!
What do you want?
If I can take my heart back,
I can kick your ass easily, Vergo!
Don't make me repeat myself, squirt!
It's Vergo-san to you!
Tashigi, I want you to lead the G-5 soldiers.
Where are you going, Smoker-san?
Don't tell me you're going after Vergo!
The law can't settle these matters, Tashigi!
I have to do it myself! He was
messing around with the Navy!
Stop it, Tashigi!
Wouldn't you rather die than
grovel before a pirate?!
Right now, we have to beg for our lives,
throwing ourselves at his
feet if that's what it takes!
Because if we die here,
we can't save our people!
And the children...
You're gonna die here, too, Law!
Smoker...
Do you still wanna fight, Smoker-kun?
You know you're no match for me.
What are you doing?
You shouldn't turn to
smoke and spread yourself
thin when you're facing a better Haki user.
It just makes it easier for me to hit you!
Why do you keep using
your Devil Fruit power?
Can't you even think straight?
It's not like you, Smoker-kun.
Enough playing around!
Demon Bamboo!
I know you wanna kill me
for messing with the Navy.
But you have to be strong
enough to do so, Smoker.
If you're just reckless, you can't
make your people proud of you.
It's over.
Smoker, my heart...
Thank you for winning it back!
Now it makes sense! You bastard!
That's why you turned to smoke!
Now we're even.
Just finish him off already!
You don't wanna owe a pirate, huh?
It's a dishonor to a Navy soldier.
I'm too ashamed to be seen by my people.
But...
...that was just the help I needed.
It's over.
Vergo... -san.
You child!
Now you remember that I'm better than you?
I just want you to keep thinking like that.
But you can't stay sitting
on that "throne" forever!
You two!
I know you're listening, "Joker"!
Vergo is a dead man, Joker.
You're about to lose your right-hand man.
And Straw Hat-ya will take care of Caesar.
That means you're also gonna lose SAD.
You couldn't see this coming
because you were overconfident.
So why don't you just keep
cackling like always
and think about your next move.
But you won't be laughing for long because...
...we're gonna do the unthinkable!
Nice try acting strong, squirt!
But are you sure you'll survive?
Look at Vergo in front of you.
Didn't you piss him off?
Do you remember what happened last time?
How did it go?
You pissed Vergo off and then what happened?
It must've been traumatic.
You probably can't forget it.
You must be afraid of Vergo.
Even with your incomparable swordplay,
his Haki will allow him to
block your every attack.
Both in terms of status and power,
you're no match for Vergo!
Here we go!
It's been two years since
the War of the Best.
Did anyone actually accomplish anything?
All you did was stay calm.
All Whitebeard did was end the era.
The Navy Headquarters rounded up new forces.
The big-timers didn't take any action!
It was like everybody was
just preparing for something.
That war was only a beginning.
You always told me...
...that the new era of the daring ones
is coming along with an unstoppable swell!
I broke... the gear!
Now,
there is no turning back!
Law's attack turns the tables in an instant.
The Straw Hats scramble
and aim for a quick getaway.
But Caesar, at the pinnacle of his rage...
...unleashes a terrible attack on Luffy...
...that annihilates friend and foe alike.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Caesar's Defeat!-- The
Powerful Grizzly Magnum!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!