All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
The Straw Hats landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen.
They learned about the ruler of the island
---Caesar Clown's motive
and all while trying to escape Shinokuni,
along with their pirate ally
- the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
Luffy and the others are on
the move to kidnap Caesar,--
save the children, and
escape from the island.
I have that crazy pirate backing me!
One of the Seven Warlords
- Don Quixote Doflamingo!
I said...
...I don't care!
I broke... the gear!
Now,
there is no turning back!
"Caesar's Defeat!-- The
Powerful Grizzly Magnum!"
The deadly gas - Shinokuni will fill
up the building-- in five minutes.
The survivors are all heading
toward R Building -
the "R-66" door, the only
exit to escape. However...
B BUILDING - SANJI
The ceiling lifted up just now!
What just happened?!
The gas has started flowing
in from the cracks!
This is no good.
--Everybody! Get to R Building now!
--Run!
But I'm scared, Sis!
I can't run anymore!
We have no time for wimping out, kids!
Stand up and run!
Don't give up, everybody!
Stand up! Now!
--Captain-chan!
--I'm glad that you're okay!
So you beat that bird woman, huh?!
But why are they coming from that direction?!
I thought they were behind
us to let us get away!
The G-5 is coming this way?!
I told you we were going the wrong way!
That aside, p-put me down!
This is embarrassing!
That's a pain! Just stay where you are!
Hey! Who said you can carry
Tashigi-chan on your shoulder?!
Zoro! Head back!
--Hurry up, everybody!
--This way!
"Broke the gear"?
"There's no turning back"?
That's hysterical.
Realize your place!
Law!
B BUILDING 2ND FLOOR - THE EXAMINATION ROOM
The ceiling's gonna collapse!
Chopper-yan, it's not safe to stay here!
Uh-huh! I've done all I could for now!
Go to R Building now!
Alright, count on us! Let's go, guys!
Yeah!
Mocha! Stay with me! Let's get out of here!
Damn.
How will I eat breakfast tomorrow?
What a horrible turn of events.
How dare you, Law.
This is an upset.
But I know you're going to regret it.
Keep that in mind.
You don't know Joker's past.
And that will cost you your life!
Upstarts like you who have
acquired just a touch of fame
can't hope to take over the world.
It's filled with those
who are much stronger.
Tell him, Smoker.
All you squirts got is energy.
But this world is much...
Don't worry about me.
Just worry about yourself.
This room will explode.
Goodbye, Vergo the pirate!
R BUILDING 1ST FLOOR
What was that?
S-Something is falling down!
I know who could have done such a thing!
It must be Law.
What is Vergo doing?!
Master! What's going on?!
--Some of us buried under the wreckage!
--Master!
Dammit!
You assholes ruined my "paradise"!
I wonder if everybody is okay.
Gotta take advantage of this confusion!
Roll!
Alright. Now let's look for
the Sea Prism Stone handcuffs.
You've got to be kidding!
--The Straw Hat member's gone!
--Where did he go?!
Find him!
R Building 2nd floor, can you hear me?
Oh, it's the Master!
If the Master is okay,
we're gonna be alright!
Secret room, come in!
Yes, Master, what just happened?
Open the air vents now!
Let Shinokuni flow into this room!
B-But that will...
I'm a gas man. I'm not gonna die.
R-Roger!
Then let's get our fellow soldiers
on the 1st floor upstairs first!
I said "Now"!
I said "Do it now"!
Stop complaining and just do it already!
But there are over a hundred soldiers!
I don't care, you idiot!
You guys are just a bunch of guinea pigs!
No one would care if
hundreds of you die or not!
You are the dregs of society!
What are you doing?! Can't you hear me?!
I can find replacements
for you fools so easily!
Shinokuni is my true power!
That was close!
Now they know who Caesar really is.
Zoro and the others!
They're really in danger!
Could I control the doors
from here, by any chance?
Hey! Why're you looking at me like that?
Huh? N-No, I...
Oh, I get it!
The Master is trying to fool the enemies!
What?
Oh yeah! You're right!
He must have a plan about
the deadly gas, too!
He's not gonna let his people die!
Right, right!
The Master is a kind man. It would hurt him
if he finds out we suspected him.
Master! I opened the air vents!
No! The deadly gas!
It's flowing in!
Yes. You should've done
as I said from the start!
Dregs shouldn't think!
Now, become my power! Shinokuni!
LAND OF DEATH
This is my scientific power!
It's kicking in.
Look, Straw Hat Luffy!
This amazing appearance!
This is my scientific power!
Through this experiment,
two countries have already expressed
interest in the weapon - Shinokuni.
They are both quite peaceful.
But when humans get serious
about defending themselves,
they'll look for any way
possible to kill their enemies!
Everybody needs me!
I'll spread weapons all over the world
and become the king of the
land of death (Shinokuni)!
Look!
Run!
No...
--He killed our fellow soldiers!
--What is he doing?!
Master!
Does he really think of us as guinea pigs?
It's amazing if I do say so myself!
Look how fast it works on their nerves!
That's almost an art!
Wh-What... What was that?
Those people are...
Momo, look after Brownbeard.
Huh? Okay!
Hey, where are you going, Straw Hat Luffy?!
Did you chicken out all of a sudden?!
What a pathetic man!
But B Building beyond that path is
almost filled up with Shinokuni!
There is no place to run
on the island anymore!
That goes for all of you guinea pigs, too!
All of you,
die...
...like trash!
That's who the Master really is?!
Master!
I trusted him so!
Excuse me. I know you're broken-hearted
but could I sit in that control seat?
I wanna save my friends from the gas!
You bastard!
You were watching it, weren't you? Dammit!
Stop! I know you all watched it, too.
Yeah, you're right. We've
been terribly betrayed!
We're finished.
Now we know that he was our enemy but...
...we can't run from here!
But so are you people!
Did you just see your
captain run from Caesar?!
That serves you right!
He took off leaving you guys behind!
Whoa-whoa, are you dissing our
captain right in front of me?
If he were the kind of
person who would betray us,
it would've been easier for me.
I would've just run away with
my tail between my legs!
Third Gear!
But he never ever stops...
...believing in us...
...so we had no choice but to support him.
We pledged to live up to his
expectations as long as we breathe!
Master, please don't...
You people are just crumbs. You
shouldn't stand against your master!
Just drop dead like a dog!
--What should we do?
--There's nothing we can do.
We can't beat such a powerful man!
--Yes, you can!
--What?
You guys should just believe in our captain!
Caesar is...
...the type of person that
Luffy hates the most!
H-Help me, Master!
Yes!
I am the Master!
I am your savior and I can make efficient
use of you good-for-nothings!
Luffy won't forgive Caesar!
Armament Hardening!
Caesar!
You're back, Straw Hat Luffy!
I don't ever wanna see your face again!
Your death is going to be the
climax of this experiment show!
Go to hell!
Gum-Gum...
...Grizzly Magnum!
Now, drop dead! Behold my scientific power!
Kneel before my power!
Shut up!
Oh yeah, Straw Hat!
You can work under me if you want...
Luffy has crushed Caesar.
The shocking news...
...spreads across the New
World in the blink of an eye.
Meanwhile...
...an assassin sent by Doflamingo...
...flies toward the island of Punk Hazard.
The storm of a new battle rages!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Raid! An Assassin from Dressrosa!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!