Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in
search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu
kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu
kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu
kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu
kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu
kara no janpusutaato
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to
the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to
the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to
the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to
the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that's what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner:D
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece,
I'll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece,
I'll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece,
I'll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece,
I'll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It's important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won't left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that's our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I'm
aiming at hasn't changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I'm
aiming at hasn't changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I'm
aiming at hasn't changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I'm
aiming at hasn't changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has
ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the
King of the Pirates!
The Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors
the harshest sea ruled
by the Four Emperors
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors
and landed on Punk Hazard;
and were drawn into a climactic
battle on Punk Hazard
and landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen.
which ended with Caesar's capture.
two parts, one burning,
the other frozen.
an island with two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
Then, they left the island
along with their pirate ally -
They learned about the ruler
of the island and the puppeteer
They learned about the puppet
They learned about the ruler of the island
and the puppet master
They learned about the ruler
of the island and the
master of Shinokuni -
Caesar Clown's motive
the Warlord - Law. However...
of Shinokuni - Caesar Clown's motive
and along with their pirate
ally - Trafalgar Law,
puppet master of Shinokuni
- Caesar Clown's motive
and along with their pirate ally
- the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
Law is different but Straw Hat
is just an ordinary pirate.
and along with their pirate
ally - the Warlord -
ally - the Warlord - Law,
were drawn into a climactic battle
Trafalgar Law, were drawn
into a climactic battle
were drawn into a climactic battle
which ended with Caesar's defeat.
Where did they go, you bastards?!
which ended with Caesar's
defeat and capture.
You haven't eaten anything until today,f
have you?
Finally, they beat
Doflamingo's subordinates
Come to think of it,
However...
you were talking on the
Transponder Snail earlier.
Pirate brothers and sisters!
Baby 5 and Buffalo.
That's my son!
Goodbye, Young Master.
Who were you talking to?
Thank you for helping us!
But it must've been hard!
That was Doflamingo.
His underground alias is Joker.
When we grow up, we will become...
I know you will become...
You don't have to worry
about anything anymore!
"A Touching Reunion!
Momonosuke and Kin'emon!"
And Joker's most important
business partner now is...
...Pirates!
...the King of the Pirates.
Don't!
Let's hope that everybody
else is okay, too!
...one of the Four Emperor -
Kaido, the King of the Beasts.
Goodbye, Smoker!
Now,
let's keep living, Momonosuke!
Our target.
Let's sail out!
Listen, you damn pirates!
Uh-huh.
There is no way to find
out who knows what.
The tanker is yours!
Let's negotiate.
And this is the line
between good and evil!
What happened, Monet?
Your most important business partner is
one of the Four Emperors.
That's why, Law, Straw
Hat, and you soldiers,
So don't think of crossing it!
Got that, Straw Hats?!
Guys!
Young Master...
Somebody's coming after us.
The big-time pirate - Kaido,
the King of the Beasts.
I'm gonna kill you all!
So...
No!
...you gotta hurry!
Who told you to do
such a childish thing?
What would happen if he finds out
you can't produce SMILE anymore?
It's a banquet!
What I said was
"Don't make friends with the pirates."
Whoa-whoa.
He'll destroy you.
Weapon-morphosis!
Then it's better to just shut them out,
Vice Admiral Smo!
Excuse me, young man.
Thus, they started the victory banquet.
What do you want in exchange for Caesar?
Revolver Girl!
But it doesn't apply to the medics!
Name your price.
I got a connection to the G-5 base.
Resign from the Seven Warlords.
Could you step aside?
Oh! It doesn't work!
We're gonna wait to be picked up here.
"It's Time to Say Goodbye!
Leaving Punk Hazard!"
Damn squirt!
Yes, sir!
He is my...
What?!
It just made me itchy!
Brownbeard, you're turning yourself in?!
...friend.
Alright, we're almost there!
Super!
We became friends after all.
Go faster!
"Intense!
Aokiji vs. Doflamingo!"
"The G-5 Wiped Out!
Doflamingo's Sudden Attack!"
Seems like he has
performed poisonous drug
Is it still safe there?
experiment on us, too, a little bit.
Law.
And they said they're gonna treat me
if I allow myself to be arrested.
Which means the island and those squirts
haven't been wiped out.
I know you don't really think that
I see.
Hey hey, Straw Hat!
I'll keep my promise with a pirate like you.
How were you doing, Sunny?
I just told you not to
come across the line!
You're not listening!
You two.
But if you really wanted to silence me,
I can't see the island anymore.
I don't care! You guys just made it up!
Take care of that guard.
there were several occasions
that you could've killed me.
The fire, the ice, and the deadly gas.
Well,
The centaurs, the G-5, and the Warlord.
it's better to go to prison than let
I'm on my way!
What are you up to,
taking advantage of Straw Hat?
Caesar do whatever he wants to us.
Is that the former admiral - Aokiji?!
I'm taking advantage of him?
Maybe he's taking advantage of me.
I thought he disappeared
after Akainu beat him!
"Capture Caesar!
General Cannon Blasts!"
It was like hell.
Well, we're in the New World.
Which of the Four Emperors
are you talking about?
And my people are all gone so...
I'm sure it's not gonna get any easier.
The Emperor's name is...
It felt so good when I
saw you knock Caesar out!
THE SEACOAST OF PUNK HAZARD
...Kaido, the King of the Beasts!
Ow, ow, ow... Easy!
Thank you!
Be quiet!
As long as Shanks is not
the first one to fight,
To be honest, I wanna kick your ass!
Here.
I have no problem.
Because...
By the way, what are we making?
Ouch!
...I plan to beat all
of the Four Emperors!
But I'm a doctor.
A stove.
"Beat all of the Four Emperors"?
So I won't!
It's so big.
Please don't hurt me!
We have so many people here.
We share a mutual interest
but you're underestimating them.
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow!
I have to use a big pot so I need a big stove.
They are the emperors of the sea
No, Brook! It's not a "little lamb"!
who have skirmished over territories
even against Whitebeard himself.
I see.
It's the Mini-Merry!
Oh, Kin'emon-san!
It's so painful to see you like that!
Now, with that much
ordinance, he must be...
MINI-MERRY
And above all, they say Kaido,
the King of the Beasts
I see.
You're the eighth person to ask me that.
What?!
I am an invincible Iron Pirate!
is the strongest creature in the world.
I can't turn my eyes towards him!
Even though I don't have eyes!
Huh? What? He's not even a human?!
1, 2, 3!
We'll ally with each other
until we kill Kaido.
Young Master!
Super!
Like I told the rest,
Okay, pull!
Young Master-sama!
And our chances of success are...
1, 2! 1, 2!
after I broke out the cage
parting ways with Luffy and the others...
Even a Pacifista would
take damage from that!
Well, I'll just say they're really low.
Honestly! If we were
gonna use this tanker,
What is that bastard?!
Why does he stand in our way?!
What?! We shouldn't go
along with this, Luffy!
you should've told me!
If I knew that I'd have to fix it,
I wouldn't have fought them here!
There you are, Sunny!
Because you guys are
trying to steal my cola!
I see.
Cola?! What is he talking about?!
So they hid you here, huh?
Okay, let's do it!
What?
Cola is my energy source!
Hand the children over to the Navy?
What?!
So what?!
Wait a minute!
What's wrong, Weapon Woman?
Aren't you gonna transform?
Yes!
Let's go, Sunny!
There is no particular reason
I liked those looks on you!
I got out to the sea through
a channel in the lab
that I didn't kill you, White Chase-ya.
They ended up
Then I'll show you!
like that because the
Navy was in charge!
By the way,
and retrieved the Mini-Merry...
...which had been docked
at the entrance to the island.
I'm thinking about going to Green Bit.
Th-Thank god-dasuyan!
And then, in order to join you guys,
Am I wrong?!
I wonder if I can handle the Straw Hats.
Weapon-morphosis!
He didn't get frozen to the bone!
Because you people were irresponsible,
I used the General Franky
which is impervious to toxic gas
Flying Disc Girl!
the children had to go through
such a terrible time.
Young Master-sama!
and went back to the lab.
Here we go-dasuyan!
It must've been very painful for them.
Smo-yan!
Super!
You're doing great!
He can barely lift the kid up!
That's nothing!
I promised them!
I see, I see.
Gum-Gum...
Let's help these children!
...Big-eater!
So that little lamb
was okay. That's good!
Weapon-morphosis!
You can't turn your back
on a child crying for help!
Brother Luffy, you're big!
Oh? What is it this time?
Can we have a cup of tea?
--Stretchy!
--Cool!
Fire Girl!
Mocha, are you alright?
I will save them!
Sure.
Aren't you cold?
Uh-huh, I'm fine!
I'm gonna finish you off
with this one-dasuyan!
So...
Here you go.
Oh! Ouch! Ow, ow... Ouch! Ow, ow, ow...
You guys are kind of nice!
All I can do is apologize.
Shut up! We are the fearsome Navy G-5!
Burn up-dasuyan!
It was very delicious!
But I'll take full responsibility.
I'm glad that you liked it.
As for their treatment,
I'll ask Vegapunk for assistance
By the way, why are
you two on this ship?
Oh yeah, I haven't thought about that
and look after them until
they're fully recovered.
but the kids had gone with the Navy.
And I'll take them to their
parents safely at any cost!
Law!
Fire Girl's "flame of love" burns any enemy -
it's the most...
We're in the midst of
our important trip.
So...
So we didn't want to get
Just kidding!
Please!
involved with the Navy
and waste our time.
Leave the children up to me!
I'm not interested in fighting you.
You can drop us off on
some island with a harbor.
It's all ready now!
General I'm-Okay!
But if I can't silence that guy,
I thought you guys were
gonna take the tanker.
What?!
Until then, please let us stay on board.
N-No way!
Well, no, because Nami
and Chopper claimed
I have to change my plan.
Please!
Okay, no problem!
Law said "Whatever you
do, don't look inside"
Come on, Fan Man and Weapon Woman!
Can I ask you something?
we're not going anywhere until
we see the children sailing out.
Yeah!
You can pay us later.
but I wonder if they are really okay?
What is your...
Are you gonna charge us?!
What is he gonna do to them?
It's a pain to wait
for other Navy people
...current status, Kuzan?!
Nami, where are we going next?
The tunnel is gonna collapse!
so take the tanker with the children.
Hold on.
What's wrong?!
The next destination is already set.
Get on board, kids!
We're gonna take you home!
What?!
Don't collapse before
we get to the exit!
Even if we can make it out,
there's the gas to deal with!
There is no need to hurry. One by one.
Hey girl, can you really generate wind?!
It's Dressrosa.
Are we gonna be okay?
The gas didn't work at all?!
Hey, hey!
Why is he screaming?
What's going on?
Take care!
This protective suit is made by Vegapunk
and in fact...
Those of you who don't
trust Nami-san, get off!
Your reputation is sullied.
No, I'm gonna kick you out!
...it's way beyond Caesar's ability.
Luffy!
Hey hey, Straw Hats!
You're scaring us, brother.
Y-You have to stop him!
Caesar knew that, so that's why he said
If the tanker is ours,
that to my colleagues who
were his test subjects.
What?
We'll be counting on you, Nami!
this is the line!
You're our only hope now!
Don't think of crossing it!
He's a murderer!
Hey, treat him already!
This is the line between good and evil!
What?! A murderer?!
You all, just run!
Y-Yes, sir!
Trust me!
Don't step on it! Stay away!
The protective suit won't help!
Again?! You were enjoying the banquet
a few minutes ago.
Take it off and run to the lab now!
No, no! No, idiot!
What is that iron soldier?!
Nothing works on him!
What? O-Okay!
About that, we really...
I am a murderer, too!
Master!
...Thank you for the meal!
Who is a murderer?
I can't let you have my cola!
But you guys are pirates!
A dishonor to the human race!
It's Law!
I said we're not
interested in your cola!
Tra-guy?
And that's how they all got petrified.
He's keeping us too long!
We got to take care of him already!
What's going on there?
--Let's get going!
--Yeah!
I-I murdered somebody, too!
There is a difference between
the look of an ordinary vagabond
Let's do it, Baby 5!
Looks like they're leaving.
I mean, Kin'emon-san
was already dead but...
No one's ever warded off
this attack of ours!
1, 2, 3!
I broke his body!
No matter what you try,
and that of a determined man.
super nothing will work!
Hm? What's that?
Big Sis Nami!
He's dead and now broken?!
We're gonna chop up your body!
Chopper-chan!
Dead and broken?!
Wh-Wh-What should I do?!
--Where is the robot?
--Oh? Where are the pirates?
What can you do?!
Weapon-morphosis!
I never thought that the World
Government was almighty.
He's broken - you can't do anything!
Those who got petrified are still alive!
Take that down! How annoying!
What if we stick them back together?!
Idiot! It's not gonna help!
If Caesar is telling the truth,
It's a barrier!
There are things I can do
without belonging to the Navy.
Even just looking at pirates hurts your eyes!
Momonosuke!
You guys are not so
different from us, G-5!
they're just in a state of apparent death
paralyzed in the shell.
There are things I can see now
because I'm not part of the Navy.
Why are you alive?!
But they got on board safely.
What are you doing, Sanji-san?!
Feast your eyes on this
weapon that I'm swinging...
Yeah, but the poison will damage
Hey!
I don't know!
--Brother!
--Sis!
You said he was dead
but he was alive!
Sickle Girl!
their body and kill
them in twelve hours!
I was dead for a moment.
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
But you didn't have to kick him!
We are the champions of justice!
We have to find them
and break the shell before that!
I did it on the spur of the moment.
What's wrong with that?
And we're gonna exterminate all pirates
who cause civilians grief!
It's all wrong.
Let's save them all at any cost!
Hey, look at him!
Maybe I was fated to come here.
The guy who they thought was
killed by the gas was alive!
Yeah!
What brought you here?
Thank you...
I came here to see you.
...for allowing us to enter the island.
How did you know that I'd be here?
I'm glad, Kin'emon-san!
Okay, I praise you...
I'll never forget your name.
I thought you were...
Pirates are the scum of the world!
...for your power - you made
it through this General body!
Don't tell me
Father!
And we're men of justice!
Don't let the kids see them!
you have something to do with
the underground community now.
I can save my people's lives!
But this is like a mantis
going up against a warship!
I promise I'll come
back to turn myself in!
--Sis!
--Robot!
No! You shouldn't see them!
Th-The former admiral has
something to do with...
This is the only exit anyway.
--Brother!
--Where are you?!
If you're done with the
treatment, go away!
Mo...
Just go!
You don't wanna see them!
The Thousand Sunny will
conquer the whole sea someday.
Okay!
Momonosuke!
--They lifted it up!
--Move it!
I can't see them!
You shouldn't see them, brats!
And I'm gonna give you a taste of
It's nice to see them well
and yelling like that.
Father!
its ultimate secret weapon although
you guys don't deserve to see it!
She said she'll ask Vegapunk for
assistance about their treatment.
This is a land-based
version of Gaon Cannon!
Oh yeah?! That's great!
What should we do with these?
Franky, I've been thinking.
Father!
Momonosuke!
I'm still me, Smoker.
What happened to the Mini-Merry
after we took it to get to the island?
Are they pirates?
I don't know. It's just creepy.
Oh, Robin! You're the fifth person
to ask that question.
I can't believe you're okay!
Then I have no qualms.
Something's flying toward us.
I call it...
Don't make eye-contact
with those trashy pirates!
Anyway, you guys should
keep an eye on Doflamingo.
It'll ruin your eyes!
What?!
What? Momonosuke?
Isn't that somebody's head?!
But we Navy won't let it happen!
Huh? Don't be ridiculous!
Oh yeah, he said he used to be a human.
He's a Warlord and the
king of Dressrosa.
We're men of justice!
So he was the Momonosuke-san
Run, guys!
He's an unusual pirate in many ways,
who Kin'emon-san had been looking for!
The deadly gas from earlier!
What?!
but not like the Snake Princess of the Kuja.
Y-You were right!
Run if you don't wanna die!
Uh-huh!
Heads are...
...Flying toward us!
Tell Sakazuki and get the
admirals into action.
You are naked!
General Cannon!
We're... men of justice!
In the worst-case scenario,
things could go very wrong, very quickly,
What?!
The spiral-eyebrowed brother!
Poof!
Who is he-dasuyan?!
The Navy's in our way!
and it would become the most
serious matter Sakazuki faced
Move!
Why is he preventing us
from recovering Caesar?!
A CHILD FROM THE WANO KINGDOM
(KIN'EMON'S SON) - MOMONOSUKE
since taking over Navy HQ.
That guy is...
That's how a kid from
the Wano Kingdom looks!
If you wanna say goodbye to
pirates, you're a bad kid!
I warned you.
You look good in a kimono!
If you say "Thank you" to them,
we'll drag you out of the
tanker and leave you here!
But, Father,
how did you know that I was... here...
Hey, guys!
Pops! Hold my hand! Hurry!
You have to keep it...
Listen! Pirates are bad
and the Navy is good!
Momonosuke! Are you alright?!
I mean, you know.
I'm...
Pirates have been causing
so much chaos in the world!
N-No way!
not hungry...
Y-You're...
What was it?
You should know that even
if you're just a kid!
Momonosuke?!
We'll never forgive pirates!
Because we should not!
I forgot. Who cares.
Yes, we'll keep it
secret that we saw you!
Law! Show yourself, Law!
Isn't that Caesar who's lying there?
D-Doflamingo!
Unforgivable! Unforgivable!
Pirates are unforgivable!
The Warlord?!
What did you do to the children?!
W-Why is he here?!
We don't want pirates!
Say "No" to pirates!
How did he get there?
If you hurt them in any way, I...
Doflamingo.
We don't want pirates!
Pirates are unforgivable!
That's why I told you
not to look inside.
Joker.
We don't want pirates!
Say "No" to pirates!
Those kids...
We don't want pirates!
We can't fail!
No matter who you're working for!
...I sliced them up.
But when we asked them to help us,
It's a drug.
They still have to go through
a long, painful treatment.
His underground alias is Joker.
Whoa-whoa, I can't believe it!
They are so tough.
they helped us!
And Joker's most important
business partner now is...
Oh, Racoon-chan!
They didn't even know
what was going on with us
Racoon-kun!
Don't think that we're
just ordinary underdogs.
Is everybody okay?!
...one of the Four Emperor -
Kaido, the King of the Beasts.
but they took us with them
without being bothered by our size!
The young man with a fur hat just...
In the name of Joker...
Our target.
...Cut out the bad
parts from our bodies!
...We're gonna recover Caesar
no matter what it takes!
I wanna go home!
What?! K-Kaido?!
Conqueror's Haki!
What?
We can go home soon! Hang tight!
So what you're trying to do is...
Why did you do that?!
Kaido?!
I was scared but I feel good now!
There was nothing on the island
and no one had come to help us!
recover Caesar over there, isn't it?
They're not here.
Our bodies' got all chopped
up and it was fun!
What's the matter?
But they came!
The ship is gone.
I'm hungry!
Never mind. Go on.
You're a Warlord!
Why are you attacking the Navy?!
I see.
I'm sorry!
Mocha hasn't woken up yet.
Go, truck!
That we didn't find you sooner!
She fought for us, didn't she?
We're almost there!
I know some pirates were
here a little while ago.
Alright, we can make it...
I had no idea that
the Master was such a bad person.
Pirates stink and they're disgusting!
Why is there a dragon here?!
Where did Momonosuke go?!
What?
I remember vaguely that
Where did they go?
But the Navy is...
That's him.
Look! The deadly gas is
everywhere at the exit!
Mocha spewed up blood
and passed out!
...always clean and beautiful!
How dare you do that to our colleagues!
Hey, Racoon-kun.
N-No!
Th-This dragon is Momonosuke?
Don't do it!
I'm a reindeer.
The gas is coming from
both front and back!
Is she gonna be okay?
Uh-huh.
We have no choice but go through that!
She can go home with
us, right, Racoon-kun?!
What?! What happened to you?!
Pirates are a bunch of cowards
and they're sloppy!
I can't move my fingers.
Of course!
What happened?!
Let's get out of this
nightmare and go home!
We don't want pirates!
The Navy is great!
Sis, save us! Please!
Kaido of the Four Emperors.
Where is the young
woman with orange hair?
If they don't let us say
"Thank you" to them,
Wh-What are you doing?!
Please!
In order to take him down,
we have to weaken his forces.
She said she's gonna take us home.
W-What about you?!
We want to say "Thank you" to her!
No, I can't... control my body!
the Navy is...
Kaido is buying a large amount
of fruit from Joker now.
Wait! I'm sorry!
Hi!
We don't want pirates!
The Navy is great!
Law is different
It's a Zoan-type, man-made
Devil Fruit - SMILE.
but Straw Hat is just an ordinary pirate.
We Navy are going to take
care of you all from here!
But, in contrast, the Navy is...
M-Man-made?!
Don't!
...very brave and righteous...
If such a thing exists,
Get us out of here!
Where did they go, you bastards?!
What?! No!
the number of Devil Fruit
eaters will keep multiplying!
Sis, please! Help us!
Stop it, you guys!
--What about the robot?!
--The bouncy guy?!
That's right.
Shame on you!
You can't turn your back
on a child crying for help!
Don't say it so casually!
The spiral-eyebrowed guy?!
Since it's man-made, however,
it seems like there are some risks involved.
Smells good! I wonder
what Sanji is making.
But, in fact, Kaido has
more than 500 Devil Fruit
Can't wait!
eaters in his pirate group.
I'll keep my word at any cost!
Okay! Now it's standing straight!
Who doesn't wanna do this?! I don't!
B...
Let's do a super quick fix!
Wh-What are you gonna do to me?!
Let's go!
But Tashigi-chan,
--I don't!
Nami?
Shut up.
unless we keep saying bad things about them,
Answer my question.
But Devil Fruit eaters
won't multiply anymore.
Ouch!
Which direction did those shitheads go?!
Sorcery Climate Baton!
Have you come to terms with the Navy?
Uh-huh.
Gust Sword!
we will start...
I'll leave them up to the Navy.
Really? Him?
I don't know what you're talking about!
Even if I commit myself to saving them,
we're pirates. It could cause them trouble.
liking these outlaws!
Let's get out!
Were you making a substance
for the man-made Devil Fruit?
Then go to hell.
How cool! SAD!
Keep the wind going, Nami!
The most we can do
I can't believe it.
is get wrongly accused
for kidnapping as always.
The gas will be everywhere outside, too!
Don't praise him!
Is it that hard to make the SAD thing?
They're in better hands!
I'll accomplish the mission
from Joker at any price!
You're right. And...
He just put Vegapunk's discovery
of "lineage factor" into practice.
E-Even though they're pirates!
Stop messing with my soldiers!
Although I'll kill him when I get back!
You iron soldier!
...I have this thing for the
eyes of female Navy soldiers.
We won't let you mess
with us anymore-dasuyan!
So Vegapunk is the smart one.
He's just a piece of shit.
Female soldiers?
Shut up, you bastards!
Can you fools even make it?!
Uh-huh.
They make me feel at ease.
Don't ever call us "fools"!
Oh yeah!
Your mother was a Navy
soldier, wasn't she?
We made it out!
Joker is finished.
It's always better to get help
We're gonna go onto the next move.
What?!
from a strong, warm-hearted female soldier!
They're odd Navy soldiers!
There is a factory manufacturing SMILEs
somewhere on Dressrosa.
That's true!
You have no right to say it!
We should just find it and destroy it?
That's right.
No, you said it!
Then, Kaido's forces won't strengthen.
However, he's a professional
businessman.
S-Smo-yan...
I'm sure he'll retaliate.
Dressrosa, huh?
Smoker.
Is that where you wanna go, Kin?
Tell me where those shitheads went.
Indeed!
New Kama Kempo Technique!
They're keeping one of
my comrades prisoner.
Pirate brothers and sisters!
99 Vital Recipes!
I'm thinking about going to Green Bit.
Thank you for helping us!
It'll boost up your cold, weary body!
When we grow up, we will become...
Well, I don't know,
Hormone soup with sea pork!
...Pirates!
Don't!
"Joker."
Since you guys haven't eaten for days,
Take care!
We could've caught them
but we let them get away.
Get good rest!
start with the soup and eat it slowly.
I don't know what to say
to our base commander - Vergo.
When you get home,
you deserve to be spoiled by
Yum-yum!
your father and mother!
He died, didn't he?!
Kids! You gotta eat something healthy!
I think you know too much.
Super!
Oh, something is falling.
Smoker!
You're starving, aren't you, Momo?
What are those clouds?
It's gonna start raining.
Sanji is the best cook!
It's not rain, it's hail (arare).
Alright, shall we go?
Oh (ara).
The weather is good considering
it's the New World.
This is...
I-I don't want it!
I'm not hungry at all!
But I know the sea will be rough.
Take this!
Hey, wait, you!
Nami!
Hey, is he coming with us?
What're you gonna do with the bowl?!
What's wrong?
Is there something to those clouds?
Even if you're a kid,
I can't stand anyone who wastes food!
Oh yeah! We haven't told
you about the alliance.
Yeah!
Luffy got us involved in trouble again.
Franky, prepare for Coup de Burst!
I said I don't want it!
Okay, I got it!
Straw Hat! Next time we see you,
we'll take you down!
Somebody, take the helm!
See? Your stomach is growling!
Oh? Why isn't the gas here?
I'll take it!
--You're our enemy next time!
--Be ready for it!
No, it's not! I'm not hungry and...
You've made it here finally!
I was getting tired of waiting!
We gotta furl the sails!
...I'm not gonna eat this!
See you!
Don't!
Wow! Look at that!
I wonder what those clouds are.
I'm going to eat!
We will catch you!
It's the General!
What?
It's no use!
Super!
What?
--It's a robot!
--The ultimate one!
H-Hey!
--Wow! Cool!
--That's what we boys love!
Hard aport! Coup de
Burst toward 9 o'clock!
Delicious!
Head for an area with no clouds!
Yeah, isn't it?!
What is this?! I feel
like my energy's back!
Alright!
Whenever you're ready, Luffy!
Let me try this!
It's no good!
He keeps suffering that guy's strange attacks!
And this!
Yeah!
Hey you, what's your name?!
Where are you?!
He has to defend himself!
Buffalo!
I can't believe how good this is!
Why doesn't he use his jitte
with the Sea Prism Stone tip?!
Are you Baby 5?!
Somebody please help me! I'm on...
It'll cancel out Devil Fruit powers!
Law! Are you really going
to stand against Joker?!
Father...
...Punk Hazard!
Let's accept their kindness!
You traitor!
No, don't! No, no, don't!
In fact, they saved my life!
Joker is still saving the
"heart seat" for you!
Coup de Burst!
Who are they? Are they your friends?
Demon Bamboo!
You can trust them!
Who are they?
No.
What?!
I can... trust them?
They're my enemies!
You haven't eaten anything until today,
have you?
You're no match for me.
That was close!
That's my son!
NHC10.
I detected it in their body.
But it must've been hard!
Although it was just a trace amount,
it's...
All of the Straw Hats and the Navy G-5!
Odds are against us!
Stop resisting and just
accept your death.
You don't have to worry
about anything anymore!
--Smo-yan!
--We'll fight, too!
...a drug!
W-We're flying!
Let's hope that everybody
else is okay, too!
Wh-What's going on, Baby 5?
Do you guys wanna die first?
Now,
In any case, we gotta take
Caesar to the Young Master!
let's keep living, Momonosuke!
They took Caesar and ran!
There are children who were
Alright, I got it!
We got away!
Stay away!
That was close!
It's a sniper's work to
take down a flying enemy!
kidnapped two years ago
in this laboratory!
Thanks, Nami-san!
Uh-huh.
Are you guys trying to kill me?!
Steal a ship and let's
escape from Punk Hazard!
--Those bastards!
--Whoa-whoa!
Wait for me, Caesar!
Usopp said he can handle it.
Oh, that was fun!
I'll beat you up and kidnap you!
Momo, did you like it?
Don't you think this ship is cool?!
Don't underestimate our sniper.
Smo-yan!
Even his nose is too long.
I-It is cool!
The last part isn't necessary!
No way! If we let them get away,
our plan is...
Oh, is it so delicious that
you can't help crying?!
Nothing is impossible
for the Thousand Sunny that I built!
Mocha!!
Idiot!
You allied with us, didn't you?
They must've gone through something serious.
It's super, isn't it?!
What happened to them?
You saw what I did earlier.
I need you to trust us a little bit.
Vice Admiral Smo!!
It is super!
Momo-chan, do you wanna
look around the ship?
Oh?
Allied? What are you talking about?
I'll give you a tour.
I've been running around
all this time so...
Catch me if you can! But I'm protected!
You jerks!
Really?! Alright, you may!
What happened to the line
between good and evil?!
Doflamingo! The Four Emperors!
When did you turn back to yourself?
...I feel like attacking now!
We call for a ceasefire, brother!
Dressrosa?!
Yes, there is something
we have to do there.
Do you even have balls to
pick a fight with them?
I'm not afraid of enemies
who are far away
Let's go!
Then why don't you guys go
get some sake from the tanker?
D-Dressrosa?!
A fight?
and have no intention to fight!
Gotcha!
Juice, too!
What? Do you know the place?
On top of that, they're wounded
and turning their backs on us!
Hey, Straw Hat-ya.
Th-That's exactly where we...
I mean, I want to go!
We have to leave in hurry.
I've been...
We don't have much time to eat here
...picking fights all along!
You need to go there, too?!
somebody's coming after us.
Uh-huh, I think so!
Really?
Tell your crew.
You have no idea what's
going on, do you?
Alright! Let's just do it!
All right.
Nope!
Now I give you some water.
Guys!
Caesar!
Okay, let's do it!
Somebody's coming after us.
The current is shifting?!
Grow Up!
Gum-Gum...
So...
Chomping Grass on Black Kabuto!
What's going on here?!
...you gotta hurry!
...Grizzly Magnum!
It's a banquet!
A slope?!
Now, eat up and get your fill!
Yee-ha!
It's fast! The ship's going fast!
Cheers!
Look out for rock reefs!
What's going on around here?!
It's a sea slope. It's not uncommon.
Be careful, Buffalo!
They're up to something!
It is uncommon!
We don't have to go against the current.
You have to watch my back, Baby 5!
Neither of you can fly so I have to!
The needle in the middle
No!
on your Log Pose must be
pointing toward Dressrosa.
Stop!
Let's complete the mission!
Momonosuke, what are you doing?
But don't try to go straight.
Take a detour.
What?!
Father.
Okay! You need me, don't you?
Warriors shouldn't cry
in front of people!
Why?
Because it'll work out better for us.
I'll defend you with my life!
Momo!
Let's sail out!
He's being such a know-it-all smart-ass.
What do you want, Luffy?
Go! Weather Egg!
Come to think of it,
Hey, it's a banquet!
Why are you crying?!
you were talking on the Transponder Snail earlier.
Something's flying this way!
Laugh! Laugh!
Who were you talking to?
Now, hatch! Thunder-chan!
That was Doflamingo.
Doflamingo?! The Warlord?!
I've heard he's the most evil one!
The plan is already in action.
Looks like those squirts
have the devil's luck.
What plan?
All right!
Cheers, brother!
Yeah, tell us about the plan!
Get together, everybody!
Yeah!
It's already late! No one has come!
I can't believe the
Sky Path ended there.
Look closely!
We formed an alliance
to kill one of the Four Emperors?!
1, 2, 3!
Thundercloud?!
Yes, sir! I didn't see anybody!
The Four Emperors, huh?
It's great!
Uh-huh. Good job!
No, it's not!
Buffalo! I have a bad feeling!
Here.
That's a super big deal!
Thank you, sir!
Thank you!
I can't go any faster than this!
Wait, wait! Let's calm down, everybody!
It's good!
Hey, do you think they
can still find us?
Luffy, tell them about the alliance.
No, you can't get away!
How many people are looking for us?!
Tens of thousands?
Okay! We and Tra-guy's pirate group
formed an alliance!
Get in the line if you wanna eat!
The Science of Weather!
I can't stop worrying
since I heard you blackmailed Doflamingo!
You can have more - there is a lot!
Let's be nice to each other!
Thunder Breed...
Does anybody wanna oppose this?!
--I do!
Me, neither, you fool!
Young Master!
I do!
Damn! That bastard Law
really betrayed us!
Does it make any difference?
Kin gave us armor and some helmets.
Just let it go!
No!
...Tempo!
Resign from the Warlords
or fight one of the Emperors.
Luffy's mind is already set, isn't it?
--It warms you up, doesn't it?
--Uh-huh!
I'm sorry-dasuyan!
I want to pay for it with death!
Thank you.
Nobody can choose between those options.
He'll just come to kill us.
You needed me but I couldn't please you!
But I have to warn you.
There may be a slight difference between
I'm scared!
how you define "alliance" and how Luffy defines it.
Baby 5! Damn, she got hit!
You bastard! Fight me squarely!
This is a life yacht
that was on our tanker.
Be careful.
I'm so ashamed-dasuyan!
After I hung up...
That's why Luffy kept saying "kidnap"
Stop!
which was so out of character for him.
I said it's a long story!
I see!
It's okay. You don't have to explain.
--Cut it out!
--Stop!
If he had just come to me
with that strange sheep
Then I won't let anybody eat the candy!
Here is a final blow!
Go, Chomping Grass!
and ask me to cook it, I
wouldn't know what to do.
You two were just following my orders.
Come on! It's dangerous
to fight on the ship!
I wanna go home with everybody!
Special Attack - Charging Shooting Star!
Oh, are you playing samurai?!
Fight, fight!
What a surprise.
Mocha!
I didn't expect the boss
himself to show up!
You should be ashamed of yourself!
The whole country was left heartbroken!
You bastards.
You're not gonna get away with this.
Go!
Is that Law?
The grave of the Wano Kingdom's hero,
left plundered by a thief!
I haven't seen you for a while.
H-Hey, Buffalo! You got to protect me.
Extraordinarily big names
will hunt you down!
That was you!
It's a shame that you're not here.
I can't move myself!
I said I didn't do it!
If you're looking for
Caesar, he's with me.
Idiots!
You must have! You have
legendary swordsman
O-Of course! Don't underestimate me.
Realize how stupid you are! Go to hell!
Ryuma's great sword Shusui on your belt!
J-Joker! Help me!
I'm a member of Don Quixote's family!
Mocha!
Come on, come on! Fight, fight!
Just cut him already!
I'll complete a mission at any cost!
Hey, Sanji! I was in the
middle of his treatment!
Where are Baby 5 and Buffalo's bodies?
Who wants to eat a midnight snack?
Wait until I finish it.
Oh! What is it?!
I don't know.
Really?!
Pizza.
Don't ask me about
such frivolous things.
Pida?
Let's negotiate.
I asked you guys to kidnap
Caesar at Punk Hazard.
I don't know what that is
but if he cooked it, it should be good.
Idiot! What a good-for-nothing!
You can't hit me, fool! I'm a gas man!
Momonosuke went to bed already?
Meanwhile, I destroyed
the machine which was
He's taking a bath with Robin.
manufacturing a substance called SAD.
What?!
I-I must make it to Dressrosa
with or without them!
The great pirates in the New World
often have their own territory.
Hey Law, come to your senses.
Law.
A squirt like you shouldn't
imitate what grown-ups do.
You haven't taken a bath
for days, have you?
You can't run! The last ammo is...
I'm sorry that I suspected you earlier.
They lead countless numbers of people
and reign like a syndicate.
Nope.
Where are you now?
Don't make me mad.
Wh-What is this?!
Did you get all warmed up?
He told me.
Sea Prism Stone handcuffs!
I got better because you treated me.
Uh-huh. Not bad.
Make you mad?
It's nothing like what
you've seen before.
Your most important business partner is
one of the Four Emperors.
Thank you!
Alright, I caught him!
One pirate group is never strong enough
even to see their captain's face.
The big-time pirate - Kaido,
the King of the Beasts.
That serves you right, Caesar!
Vice Admiral Smo-yan!
But since it's an underground community,
And I know you can't make
him mad at any cost.
You came at just the right time!
We're heading back to the island!
Kin'emon-san, he needs a kimono.
they have to do their businesses secretly
to avoid the Navy.
You can count on me
when an enemy turns his back...
What happened?
We made Caesar tell us about
the weakness of the deadly gas!
What are you doing, you dirty brat!
What would happen if he finds out
you can't produce SMILE anymore?
Alright!
Our colleagues are still alive!
We can save them!
And Doflamingo is the most trusted
and powerful man among them.
Why is Smoker still alive?
Since he's not the negotiating type,
there'll probably be a fierce battle.
It's not fair!
His underground alias is Joker.
You're taking full advantage
of being a child!
Let's go, guys!
All right. the initial
phase is accomplished.
Young Master, you're turning blue.
And Joker's most important
business partner now is...
Yeah!
Just cut off your top-knot!
And he'll destroy you.
See? They are strong, aren't they?
Hey, you carried the joke too far, Law.
...one of the Four Emperor -
Kaido, the King of the Beasts.
What do you want in exchange for Caesar?
Name your price.
Hey! Why did you gang up on a child?!
Our target.
Resign from the Seven Warlords.
Law.
No, it's not what you think, Nami-san!
I know you don't really
think that I'll keep
--Stop!
--Smo-yan's gonna die!
Men are all...
I can't believe this squirt-dasuyan!
my promise with a pirate like you.
I was scared, beautiful princess!
Then he can no longer stay in Dressrosa!
If you kill him,
But if you really wanted to silence me,
All I want is for you
to abandon everything
Beautiful princess?!
Don't be so honest!
there were several occasions
that you could've killed me.
who would lead misfits like us!?
that you spent a decade to attain
and go back to being
a common pirate again.
You're such a lovely boy!
In that case, however,
What are you up to,
taking advantage of Straw Hat?
Don't worry.
You sleep in our room, Momo-chan!
the Admirals from the Navy HQ
will hunt you down!
What?!
I'm taking advantage of him?
They'll let him in the girls'
room - the secret garden?!
Maybe he's taking advantage of me.
There is no way to find
out who knows what.
I'm expecting to see it in the newspaper
tomorrow morning.
If your resignation from the Warlords is
in the paper,
That's why, Law, Straw
Hat, and you soldiers,
What?!
You're the worst, you brat!
Wait for me!
Which of the Four Emperors
are you talking about?
I will call you.
I'm gonna kill you all!
Squirts!
If I don't see it, the
negotiation is off.
No!
Goodbye.
Whoa-whoa.
Clank.
Wait a minute! Law!
Excuse me, young man.
The Emperor's name is...
...Kaido, the King of the Beasts!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Could you step aside?
What?!
Ring, ring, ring...
Young Master!
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
As long as Shanks is not the first one to fight,
I have no problem.
I overslept.
Oh really? You found them?
He is my...
Because...
...I plan to beat all
of the Four Emperors!
Which way is Punk Hazard?
...friend.
Damn squirt!