Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
once attained everything this world has to offer.
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
drove people around the
world to the seas.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
My treasure? If you want
it, you can have it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in
search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
namikaze tateyou suriipu
kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu
kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu
kara no janpusutaato
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to
the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to
the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that's what it takes
Force it and go
go-in Go
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner:D
Wanted->means Winner:D
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece,
I'll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece,
I'll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
samenai koto ga daiji--
It's important not to wake up
We are the one! Go ahead!
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
We won't left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Keep going forward, that's our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
the future that I'm
aiming at hasn't changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I'm
aiming at hasn't changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I'm
aiming at hasn't changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
I can't stand still, I can't stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
WE GO!
we go!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are  after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
However, no one has
ever fully explored it
However, no one has  ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,  a boy whose body turned
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the
King of the Pirates!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
I'm gonna become the
King of the Pirates!
The Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
While the Straw Hats were
on their way to Dressrosa,
The Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
After leaving Punk Hazard,
the Straw Hats headed to Dressrosa.
After a fierce battle on Punk Hazard,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
a mysterious man named Breed, who
leads a pack of sea monsters,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors
the Straw Hats along with their pirate ally -
the Warlord - Law...
After capturing Caesar,
along with their pirate ally - Trafalgar Law,
But a mysterious man,
Breed, who leads a pack
and were drawn into a climactic
battle on Punk Hazard
made a raid on them
and kidnapped Caesar.
...finally captured Caesar and
of sea monsters made a raid on them
which ended with Caesar's capture.
they finally arrived at their
next destination - Dressrosa.
and kidnapped Caesar.
Luffy and two others snuck into the
enemy's ship to take back Caesar
Then, they headed out
for their next destination - Dressrosa
headed out for their next destination - Dressrosa.
To take back Caesar, Luffy, Law,
and were reunited with a Kung Fu
Dugong who they met in Alabasta
along with their pirate
ally - the Warlord - Law.
Let's negotiate.
and Chopper snuck into the enemy's ship.
"Explore!
A Kingdom of Love and Passion - Dressrosa!"
but like the Dugong and
the other monsters,
In the course of their
trip, they were attacked by
Resign from the Seven Warlords.
There, they happily reunited
with a Kung Fu Dugong
they've been taken control of by
Breed's Peto-Peto Fruit power.
the Breed Pirates who were
looking to get hold of Caesar
who had become Luffy's disciple in Alabasta.
I'm expecting to see it in the newspaper
tomorrow morning.
but they defeated them
after a great struggle.
Kill those two, Dugong!
Goodbye.
Pull your arm back all
the way - like this!
"Don Quixote Doflamingo..."
Clank.
Wait a minute! Law!
And use the lower half of your body!
"...Withdraws from..."
Damn squirt!
"...the Seven Warlords"!
However, Breed's Peto-Peto
Fruit power controlled
"A Major Turnaround! Luffy's
Angry Iron Fist Strikes!"
the Dugong and the others.
We made it! Dressrosa!
Breed gained control of Chopper, Luffy,
"Startling!
The Big News Shakes Up the New World!"
We found you!
I said you're too loud, Luffy!
We're in their territory now!
and even Law with his mysterious power.
Pet-peto!
Dammit!
"Caesar Goes Missing!
The Pirate Alliance Makes a Sortie!"
I can control any living thing
Boy...
and bring out all of its power!
"Withdraws from the Seven Warlords"?
What's going on?
This week, I'm...
...super!
You will see how deadly it is!
How do I know? Don't ask me!
I'm gonna find the factory right away
and ka-boom!
Dressrosa is finished!
I said you guys are being too loud!
All tall waves were originally...
That was quite a punch, Kung Fu Dugong!
"Luffy Dies at Sea?!
The Pirate Alliance Comes Apart!"
We should just go to the town, right?
...little waves, barely worthy of notice.
Yes.
How do you feel now?
Listen, don't let your guard down.
You sent some shitty humans
to hell with your own hands.
Damn! I can't take it off!
If we fail to destroy the factory,
it'll mess up our whole plan.
Hey! What's gonna happen to the arms deal
Luffy, look up!
Doflamingo! I know he's gonna make
Oh yeah!
between Don Quixote family and us?!
a raid in the darkness of the night!
I just had a good idea!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Just bring it on! I mean, don't!
Lie down!
Momo!
I can't control myself!
I've been trying to reach them
but nobody picks up!
I-I can't sleep!
Now I have to discipline you
because you disappointed me!
Damn!
What should we do?!
Alright, go Momo!
To the town without stopping!
Calm all the way to the horizon!
I-I can't believe this!
We will lose the war without arms!
Watch out!
Fly!
Wait!
Stop!
You're too heavy! Get off of me!
Hey, listen to this!
Chopper stopped!
Oh, Chappy!
I can't fly and I'm not
gonna enter the island!
Those reckless rookies from two years ago
formed an alliance!
What's wrong?!
My father told me not to!
You're just the bait.
You must forget about Straw Hat!
You can't fly?! What are you talking about?!
My main target was you
two from the beginning.
I'm sure they're up to something!
I saw you flying!
What did you say?!
You will live in a kingdom that I
Doflamingo resigned from the Warlords!
Wait!
I don't know what you're talking about!
I said I can't!
will create as my loyal pet
for the rest of your life!
Why did he do that?!
Isn't there anymore information?!
Go.
Oh? I can't move!
I really saw him flying!
Roo...
Wait!
--What's that?
--What?
Alright! Get more information!
But he doesn't have wings.
You guys are going
to be eating out of my hand forever.
See? I told you!
I don't remember flying!
How did they find out about our alliance?!
As long as I hold you two as my slaves,
What's going on?!
E-Even if I did fly...
there's nothing to be afraid of!
Who is this freelance writer named Absa?!
What do you think you're doing?
I'm a pirate!
What?! Who is it?!
He gets scoops very often these days!
What happened?!
Straw Hat! Trafalgar!
Sit!
I don't care about us.
I'm more concerned about the other news.
What's your name?
Pirates should be free!
Straw Hat and Trafalgar!
I-I'll never do such a dreadful thing again!
I'm not gonna become your
pet even if it means death!
Dammit!
I'm sure they're looking to take out
one of the Four Emperors like we are.
Shake hands!
Son of a bitch!
I'm not gonna fly in the sky!
Pirates are free.
Which one is their target?!
You bastard!
See what I'm capable of?!
This is the power of the Peto-Peto Fruit!
Huh? Are you scared of heights?
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Are you gonna betray me?!
Where did they come from?!
Whether you're a Warlord
or a rascal pirate
You bastard!
There are about thirty of them!
Watch out!
Ring, ring, ring...
with a 400 million bounty,
you're powerless before me!
Thirty?! Really?!
I can't see - it's too dark!
Ouch!
Betray you?! Luffy is my only captain!
Ring, ring... Clank.
Don't disrespect me!
We warriors don't get scared of anything!
It's me.
I resigned from the Warlords.
Are you stupid?!
They're quite strong!
If you were an animal, you
could've become my pet.
Straw Hat has been swallowed by
the sea along with Trafalgar!
Ow, ow, ow... You!
--He picked up!
--Picked up!
Who are they?!
But stinking humans like
you will become my slaves!
Stop it, you fool!
Finally!
You know what happens to
Devil Fruit eaters when
they fall into water...
Doflamingo?!
What? What did you just say?
What do you think you're doing?!
He'll never be defeated
by a guy like you!
Ow, ow, ow...
He will hear you!
You're unforgivable!
He's gonna become the
King of the Pirates!
Hey, you guys! Keep it down!
Hello? I'm Monkey D. Luffy!
What the hell are they doing?
The King of the Pirates?!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy-san, he's an eight-year old...
I told you to shut up!
Are you out of your mind?!
Cut the "warrior" crap!
What?
Hey, Mingo!
I'm gonna become the King
of the Pirates someday!
Are you stupid, old Caesar's boss?!
You are out of your mind!
How cute!
Idiot!
Huh? What was that? What's going on?
You say you're gonna create a
kingdom of submissive animals?!
He gave Brownbeard and the children hell!
I'm gonna become the shogun
of the Wano Kingdom someday!
I didn't realize because you
had a strange outfit on before!
Nice to meet you, ladies and gentlemen!
We will give you back Caesar as we promised
but if you do that again,
Your blue nose is so cute, Raccoon-kun!
There's not a chance for
you to create such a thing!
Who are you?!
Fool!
I've never had a pet like you before!
What did you say?! You eel!
You never try to understand
the people around you!
I will beat the hell out of you!
You're so arrogant! You monkey!
I'll dress you up right away!
Straw Hat Luffy.
Who did you call "monkey"?!
You're being rude to a monkey!
No one's gonna follow someone like you!
Don't!
Oh, good boy, good boy, good boy!
Enough, Momonosuke!
You went away for two years
after your brother died.
My name is Breed.
He saved us!
Hey, get your hands off of Chopper!
You never try to understand
the people around you!
Shut up! You two are
gonna get locked up!
I'm a Peto-Peto Fruit eater!
Where were you
and what were you doing?
Put Sea Prism Stone handcuffs on them!
I shouldn't tell anyone about it!
Peto-Peto (sticky)?!
No one's gonna follow someone like you!
What's that?! Are you
some kind of slimy man?
That's not Doflamingo?
I'm sorry, Luffy-dono. Please forgive him.
I wanted to see you.
I guess not.
Shut up!
What?
Even though he's a child,
he's a proud warrior of the Wano Kingdom.
It won't be long.
Oh no!
I have something
that you'll want very badly now.
It won't be long
before my dream kingdom becomes reality.
Caesar!
Having said that,
I can't believe you take an
eight-year old so seriously!
Fools! You can't keep me as a prisoner!
Something... that I'll want...
Don't underestimate Doflamingo!
I don't like cowards! Idiot!
So that guy's working
for Doflamingo, huh?
very badly?
I'll leave the rest up to you guys!
Hey, Peto-guy! Let us out!
Wait!
You...
Give us back Chopper! Dammit!
Luffy?!
I said "Enough"!
Ow, ow, ow...
You...
Dammit!
Your body is rubber, it can't hurt!
Hey, didn't you hear me?!
--Oh, Nami!
--Yes, yes! Momo-chan, come here!
Unless that thing can...
I'm losing my strength...
I guess the cage is...
H-Hey!
I mean "You all have
to finish them off"!
...Made of Sea Prism Stone.
That monkey is...
How delicious is that meat
you're talking about?!
...use Haki!
I know, I know.
You guys are so pathetic.
What? Maybe, the Peto-Peto Fruit is...
You bastard!
Straw Hat-ya!
Don't get drawn into his pace!
You...
...Damn...
...Brat!
I'll take Caesar! Goodbye!
Now,
One chunk of meat! Two chunks of meat!
Get off of her!
Caesar!
Hey, let us out!
do it!
Dammit!
What's their problem?
Luffy!
Shut up! Why does everybody
give me orders?!
Keep yourself together!
What now?!
Like father, like son!
I didn't know warriors were so sick!
This is a special attack called "His Pace"!
Did he take control over you?
One hundred chunks of meat!
Two hundred chunks of meat!
He's right! I wanna call you people "pervs"
instead of "warriors"!
Giant waves!
Yes, he did. A collar and a leash!
Stop! Don't get drawn into it!
H-How dare you say that!
I feel like a pet!
Joker! Cut the crap!
Is that a Rabbit Wave?!
But I'm a great scientist!
Oh no! The ship is bouncing up and down!
I can't control it!
Hey, Kin'emon! Let's go to the town already!
We'll hand Caesar over to you as we promised.
He said he's a Peto-Peto Fruit eater.
What's going on?!
Well, that's for your own good.
How should we pervert...
And with that power,
I mean, how should we change
our clothes for a disguise?
If you try to run away with him,
What's that?!
he can make people obey whatever order he gives.
Guys, look!
Oh yeah!
you know what will happen to you guys.
Dress shirts for men!
Caesar, is he one of
Doflamingo's associates?
Let-it-all-hang-out for women!
Now, can I hear my precious
business partner's voice?
This is how people dress in Dressrosa.
Are you stupid?
What the hell is that?!
If he were, why would I be held captive still?
An enormous island?
Let me change you all so you can fit in!
As far as I know,
Joker! I'm sorry!
A Jolly Roger?!
That means it's a ship?!
Doflamingo doesn't have
any subordinates like him.
You resigned from the Warlords for me!
That guy was a pirate?!
Dressrosa is the best!
Let's chase him!
We can't let Caesar get away!
Did you hear him?
What?!
That guy told me he wants to create
a dream kingdom or something.
Yeah!
Yeah, he sounded fine.
Luffy! Take the Shark Submerge!
Stop lying!
What kingdom?
Eight hours from now,
How do I know?! Dammit!
It only can carry three people
but it can travel underwater!
at the beach on the southeast
side of Green Bit,
Excuse us for a while, you guys.
N-Nami...
It's so humiliating...
the solitary island north of Dressrosa.
Okay!
Hey.
Luffy, I'll come with you!
...for me to take that whip fool's orders!
Screw him!
There's something that concerns me.
Luffy!
I want you to keep this.
We will leave Caesar there
at three in the afternoon.
Alright!
Hey, Luffy! What about us?!
I'm here to get Chopper back!
Look after the Sunny!
Caesar!
Go ahead and pick him up.
And this will all be finished.
And, to give you a good, solid punch!
Is this a Vivre Card?
Gotcha! Don't worry about the Sunny!
Lie down!
Why are you here?!
Yes. It'll point toward an island called Zou
that I talked about earlier.
You two got thrown into the sea!
Hey, Caesar!
Nose-ya, stay alert!
That's too bad.
I wish I could have a drink with you...
I said "Lie down"! Can't you hear me?!
Your little power won't
work against us anymore.
Doflamingo himself may come and attack!
After handing over Caesar
and destroying the SMILE factory,
Huh? What are you talking about?!
Just hang up!
Be careful!
Dammit! That asshole! I can't take it!
Clank.
I was gonna head for Zou.
Trafalgar! Straw Hat! Sit down!
Attack?
My crew is there.
Who did you call "Nose-ya"?!
You guys can't get away from me!
That was close.
But if anything happens
to us, go straight there!
You almost got drawn into his pace.
Hey! I said "Sit down"!
Did they leave already?!
Your eyes! Your eyes!
W-Wait a second!
Don't you hear me?!
Now,
Are they gonna be okay?
Hey, wait!
I thought so.
What?
What do you mean "Anything happens"?
Nothing will happen, right?
We didn't tell him how many men he can bring!
it's all ready!
If we can't hear your command, your
special power won't affect us.
What should I make them to do for me?
All three of them are Devil Fruit eaters
so if the unexpected happens...
"How many men"?
Who knows.
What's that?
That's right.
What are we gonna do
if he brings his entire crew?!
This is a map that my crewmember drew.
Am I right?
Peto-guy!
Give us back Chopper...
Wow! So terribly drawn!
You shitty humans never learn.
Damn!
I can't hear your orders like
this. I can shut out your voice.
We're here now, at the
west coast of Dressrosa.
Are they going to be alright?
Don't worry. Chappy's here.
It doesn't matter.
Doflamingo's palace is at
the center of Dressrosa.
The handover of Caesar is a part of our plan.
You have Transponder Snails
and loudspeakers everywhere
Chappy?
There they are!
The SMILE manufacturing factory must be
somewhere on the island.
It's just to lure them.
so you can give the animals
commands all at once, don't you?
You mean, destroying a
SMILE manufacturing factory
When did you figure it out?!
We don't have much time.
Alright, Chopper, go faster!
while it's unguarded is our main purpose?!
The Factory Destroying Team must move quickly.
Luffy, don't they look like Lapins?
Chappy!
It went through my mind at that time.
Yes. But we don't know where it is.
Lapins?!
I'm not Chappy!
Caesar!
The big rabbits you encountered
at the Drum Kingdom,
Chopper!
What's this smell?
Lie down!
You're joking.
Chappy!
where I come from.
We, the Caesar Handover Team, will...
I'm Chopper!
Hey, Caesar!
Don't worry!
I said "Lie down"! Can't you hear me?!
Factories are big. You can barely miss them.
...go across Dressrosa and
cross the very long bridge to north
Oh, you mean those big
bear-like rabbits!
Chopper, what are you wearing?!
Hey, Luffy! Stop laughing!
After I figured it out,
and get to Green Bit.
Once we get there, we'll super find it!
They look a little different
and Lapins can't swim but...
I pretended that I was
being controlled by you
Why do we have to go across Dressrosa?
Oh... I'm exhausted because
of the Rumble Ball...
I will destroy it with my laser beam!
and looked for a chance
to take Caesar back.
I think they are Sea Lapins.
We can just take the ship!
All of us together!
Are you shy because you're dressed up?!
What?
Oh, brother!
You know what they are?
Even the fight against Straw Hat, you...
I heard it's impossible to travel by water.
I saw them once when I was
sailing across the North Blue.
No...
Oh, that sounds interesting.
Yes, I was pretending that I
was being controlled by you.
I have intelligence on
everything but the factory.
Oh, somebody's in a bad mood!
P-Please get me there safely!
They don't live in the
New World normally.
He, however,
No wonder.
Stop!
CAESAR HANDOVER TEAM
Oh no. I have a Fear-of-Dressrosa-itis.
was really being puppeteered.
Was that why you came
with us, Raccoon-ya?
It's an important asset for them, isn't it?
Luffy!
Uh-huh.
Kanjuro... I hope he's still alive.
Maybe, there is a secret to it.
Did you say something?
I can't hear what you're
saying with these earplugs.
I mean, who are you
calling "Raccoon-ya"?!
Law-dono!
And you all, the Sunny's Security Team,
I'm not a raccoon, I'm a reindeer!
should watch out for the enemy's attack.
It wasn't too hard for me to break
You said you're gonna
go to Green Bit earlier!
Don't push your luck.
Keep it in mind, you fool!
our fall because I could
use my Devil Fruit power.
Don't let them take the ship!
Luffy, it's not funny!
You must be happy when I pet you.
--What?! What do you mean by that?!
Earlier!
I'm sorry!
Are they gonna attack us?!
That's not the only reason I
came with you. That animal...
We will dock this ship at Dressrosa.
Don't worry.
Submit to my demands!
What?! I thought guarding
the ship was the safest!
Guys, we're in the enemy's stronghold.
Are you okay, Chopper?!
Is that so? Thank you!
Yeah.
He said "I don't actually
want to do this."
I gotta get away while that jerk
is focusing on Straw Hat and Law.
Chappy, get on your knees!
Thank you!
But we're with Sanji so...
Tra-guy, have you been to that island?
THE SUNNY'S SECURITY TEAM
Lower to the ground!
Raccoon-ya,
can you understand what the animals are saying?
Now, it's time for discipline!
Is that Straw Hat's submersible?!
Dress-roba!
Huh?! Sanji's not here!
Yeah, I can understand what they...
Dress-roba (old woman)?
How lucky I am!
I mean, Luffy and the others are gone, too!
It's "rosa"!
I've never been there.
I said I'm not a raccoon!
They're the key to this plan!
Where did they go?!
Hey, stop!
It's that bastard's kingdom.
Oh, Caesar!
Hey! Who's gonna protect us?!
That Breed guy who is
leading those sea monsters.
Hey Luffy, stop laughing!
Hey, are you listening?!
We were lucky to catch
Caesar right away.
Then, let's figure everything out
once we get there!
I said "Stop"!
What are you doing to my friend?!
Is he really working for Doflamingo?
Hey, are you listening?!
I wasn't lucky at all! It
couldn't have been worse!
It's gonna be an adventure!
I hope we're not getting
ourselves into a mess.
Can't wait to see Dressrosa!
"Friend"...
Huh? What did you say?!
"Friend"?
Oh, they're going in there.
"Friend"!
If you wanna join the conversation,
take out your earplugs!
I wanna go to the Wano Kingdom soon, too!
"Friend"!
Visitors to this kingdom are fascinated
by a number of things.
Don't be ridiculous!
"Friend"!!
--What did you say?!
--I said "Take out your earplugs"!
You can't just show up without a plan...
Sanji, I'm hungry!
I said...
Cut the "friend" crap!
What do we have for breakfast?
Sandwiches.
First, by the fragrantly-scented flowers
I don't believe in friendship!
Yeah! I want a cotton-candy sandwich!
Pets are useless!
I'll just have a cup of tea.
It's not worth a damn!
Humans are worthless!
I'm gonna have cola!
Listen! All I need is...
Everyone is a piece of trash!
and the delicious smell of local food.
A glass of milk for me!
We're in the enemy's territory.
Be really careful...
I think the best breakfast in the world is
Sanji-kun's sandwiches!
...loyal followers - tools -
who just work for me!
Hey, it's brighter over here!
What is a sandwich?
I have no need for insubordinates!
Earplugs?! What a stupid gimmick!
Don't shout, you idiot! Listen to me!
Smells good!
I don't like bread!
He's right, Luffy! Listen to him!
Do you think you're outsmarting me?!
Everyone should just do as
I say without complaining!
Let me show you the true, formidable
power of the Peto-Peto Fruit!
I can't tell you why we were being chased.
Second,
Worthless humans always
stand against me!
the tireless, passionate
dancing of the local women.
Wow, how awesome!
But we set sail for the
place called Zou originally.
That's why I have no need
for their friendship!
What?
It's a big fish tank!
Now, "me"!
I don't need them!
Smells lovely!
Feels like we're in the sea.
Zou?
But animals... pets are different!
Kill all those...
Do you know it?
Look, Chopper!
It's another coincidence.
It's a fish tank all the way to the ceiling.
They just follow my orders
quietly and submissively!
And another thing...
...stinking humans!
Hey, Straw Hat-ya!
We're not here for fun.
After handing over Caesar
and destroying the SMILE factory,
Hey! Wait! Give it back!
Animals! Pets! They're the best!
Look, Chopper! A sparkling shrimp!
I was gonna head for Zou.
Huh?!
Wow, cool!
What is he doing? He put
a collar on himself!
Wait! Mario! Hey!
That aside...
Really?!
Give me back my arm!
Yes, my crew is already there.
He is...
No way!
Boy! You're a bad dog!
The cotton's gonna fall out!
That's why I need you.
I-If so, can we go along with you there?
Caesar.
What?!
That's right!
Okay, let's fight!
Wait!
Once you have been given an order
through the Peto-Peto power,
Yes, you can! Let's go there
and then the Wano Kingdom!
Room!
No!
To make...
I got a side stitch!
Although there's only cotton inside!
Hey!
...this!
S-Stuffed toys?!
it will bring forth all of your power
even that is normally impossible!
Thank you!
Is that... SMILE?!
Where did you get it?!
W-Well...
A shocking surprise for all
visitors to this kingdom.
Luffy-dono, thank you for everything!
I have a connection
with the underground.
I can have more arms than you!
Hello!
Everything!
I'm gonna use this Zoan type,
man-made Devil Fruit...
Don't mention it!
I am a soldier!
Right, Tra-guy?
Oh? Have we met before?
...to turn humans to animals forcibly!
Pardon me.
Your faces look familiar.
Three samurais including me, and Momonosuke -
Then there will be no more detectable,
pathetic humans in the world!
four of us headed for Zou
but our ship wrecked
Fall in, my damned pets!
Oh, yeah!
You were in the paper this morning...
and two of us samurais and Momonosuke
drifted to Dressrosa.
You bastard! What are you really up to?!
Ouch!
Oh no! The strings got tangled up! Help me!
But we had been chased by
Doflamingo and the others there
A kingdom.
What's this?! A toy?!
I will create an animal-only kingdom -
without a single stinking human!
Hey, Luffy! Look at that!
How did you like that?
and I ran into an unknown ship.
Wh-What's going on?!
It's almost morning. Let's move.
And I will conquer all the animals
using my Peto-Peto power!
There, I met the children
who were looking to get treated.
And unfortunately, the ship left the port
Everywhere you look,
I will turn them to loyal pets!
before I knew it and headed for that island.
blending in with the town
That's my dream kingdom!
--Father!
--Oh no! Momonosuke!
Now, guys,
What?!
and living side-by-side with humans.
Like we thought, he uses Haki.
those lousy humans are
not following my orders!
I was gonna go after the ship
and my fellow samurai Kanjuro tried
to cover me but got caught!
They are living toys.
Kill them!
Suit yourself!
Go after Momonosuke! Don't worry about me!
We have unfinished business.
But you can't make me follow anybody!
THE FACTORY DESTROYING & SUMURAI RESCUE TEAM
This is a kingdom of love
and passion and toys.
If you can use Haki, I'll
fight with the gloves off!
What are you talking about?!
Didn't you see what I'm capable
of with the Peto-Peto power?!
Stop!
He let me sail out to the sea!
The port town - Acacia.
Let's do this!
It means nothing to me!
I have to save him!
You silly human!
I have to go back!
A man has been stabbed!
What a man, Kanjuro!
Oh, again?
Worthless humans like you should just
shut your mouths and follow my orders!
What do you mean "Again"?
Kanjuro!
Is there a phantom slasher or something?
Alright! I'm gonna go save him with you!
No. Women in this country are passionate
Guys! Don't forget our purpose!
Stop resisting!
about love and most are the jealous type.
Kanjuro!
I'm a pirate!
So when a man cheats on a woman,
I'm not gonna follow anybody's order!
things can get pretty violent.
I win!
Pirates should be free!
How scary!
The more beautiful they are,
the more likely to stab a man!
How could you do that to your own crew?!
I win!
Toys are moving by themselves
but that's okay!
"Pirates"? "Free"?
Seal?
Let's eat!
I hate humans like you the most!
What do you want?!
"We are not your tools!"
Alright.
Wh-What? What?
That's what the Dugong said!
I was gonna spare your
life and enslave you.
"We might be your crew but
we won't be your tools!"
What's going on?
But all you damn humans
deserve death after all!
He's saying "Master, long time no see."
Young Master-sama,
Trbol-sama is not here yet.
Hey! Wait, wait!
Oh, don't tell me you're...
Okay.
"We are no longer your pets!"
You became Luffy's disciple in Alabasta!
The Kung Fu Dugong!
"We're not gonna give in
to your power! We're...
What is this place?
...pirates!"
Thank you for waiting.
Where are we?!
It's showtime!
You bastards!
I'll show you the terror
of my Peto-Peto power!
Hey, what's going on?!
What do you think you're doing?!
Alright, Trafalgar, here
is my order to you!
I'm the great scientist -
Master Caesar Clown-sama!
Kill Straw Hat!
Hey, somebody, let me out!
Is anybody listening?!
Seal!
Hey!
Let's knock him on his ass!
Tra-guy!
Straw Hat, I want you to kill Trafalgar!
Hello.
All right! We're in disguise!
NAVY
How are you?
I'm hungry!
Oh, good. Thank you!
Let's go this way!
Dammit!
Now, let me out.
Where is Doflamingo?
No!
This is outrageous!
Go ahead and kill each other!
You can't use your Devil Fruit power though!
Shut up, you worthless human!
Hey! Let's eat here!
THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
Punch each other to death
like idiots - just as you pathetic humans are!
There are only seven Warlords in the world!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Damn!
Don't tell me you're not
working under Doflamingo!
They are the pirates who
were chosen and given
Now, the bloody show begins!
Stop messing with me!
the carte blanche for robbery
by the World Government
Who do you think I am?!
How dare you all go against me?!
You're Caesar Clown - Joker's pet scientist.
Am I right?
in exchange for their overwhelming strength
and notorious prestige!
Fine! I'll destroy everything!
Did you say Joker?
Are you connected to the
underground community?
Them taking sides with
the Government has to be
Come on, Sea Lapins!
seen as a threat to all
other pirates in the world.
Now, you better wag your
tail for me - Breed-sama!
Use your scientific mastery
to create my dream kingdom!
The greatest swordsman in the world!
"Hawk-Eye" Dracule Mihawk!
Huh? No way. I'm a great scientist.
The king of Dressrosa
and a charismatic devil!
Why should I follow orders from some guy
that I don't even know?
"Heavenly Demon" Don Quixote Doflamingo!
I wonder how much longer
you'll be able to say such a thing.
He is now the Navy's human weapon!
Luffy! Law!
"Tyrant" Bartholomew Kuma!
How do you like my overwhelming power?!
I can't believe this!
What are you gonna do to me?! No!
Hey! You bastard!
I'll let you all be
swallowed by the sea!
The empress of Amazon Lily!
"Pirate Empress" Boa Hancock!
Oh, I remember you!
One of the Worst Generation
You're the Kung Fu Seal from Alabasta!
and the mastermind of the Rocky Port Incident!
"Surgeon of Death" Trafalgar Law!
"It's been a while, Master!"
Tra-guy, it's no good!
There's nothing you can do!
And this man has become powerful rapidly
in last two years.
That's what he said.
I can't control my body!
Let's do it, Seal!
It's nice to see you again!
How have you been?!
You two hit it off already?!
The leader of the Pirate Dispatch Organization
and a living legend.
Those of you who disobey
me are all worthless!
What is this all about?
Oh, he is a Kung Fu Dugong
who became friends
Excuse me.
All of you deserve death!
with Luffy in a kingdom called Alabasta.
"Star Clown" Buggy!
Straight to hell with you all...
Are you surprised that I'm a Warlord?
Kung Fu Dugongs like to fight
and will challenge anyone to a duel.
I heard there is a gambling
house around here.
What's wrong with you
guys?! Hey! Let go of me!
Do you know where it is?
You win.
You dummies!
But Luffy...
It's not like I wanted to become one.
Hey! Let go of me!
I win!
I'm sorry, old man.
This is my first visit to this town.
The World Government begged me in tears
...Defeated him.
Hey!
When they lose a fight, they have to
Gum-Gum...
so I accepted reluctantly!
Why don't you ask someone in that restaurant?
become a disciple to the one who beat them.
Dammit!
Oh, I see. Thank you for your kindness.
But this is only the beginning.
...Fore-fist...
That's what this is all about.
I see. And what are they doing now?
No one can stop me from advancing!
...Punch!
Yes! This is the greatest show ever!
Huh?
Like this, Seal!
One, two, one, two!
I'm gonna join the Four
Emperors in a few years!
And I'm gonna become the King of...
Pull your arm back all
the way - like this!
And the man I told you about earlier.
And use the lower half of your body!
They are the Seven Warlords.
Damn! I can't stop myself!
Put more power to it!
One, two, one, two!
But that all changed early this morning.
What're you doing?!
I don't have time to fool around like this!
They're getting along so well...
Doflamingo resigned out of the blue.
You really are the seal!
You got much stronger, didn't you?
And we might need to expel Law
I need to look for Kanjuro
as soon as possible!
I don't wanna fight you like this!
from the Warlords depending on his intention.
Dammit!
Whoa-whoa, relax.
Together, they're one of the
Three Great Powers along with the
Navy HQ and the Four Emperors.
Oh, what's that?
I know we need to hurry
but it's better to get some information
rather than just run everywhere.
Things shouldn't be so unstable...
"I saw the scar on your chest
in the newspaper and copied it."
Isn't it strange?
Did you hurt yourself?
Their king just abdicated from the throne
this morning.
"I painted it on!"
That's funny!
Yes, I know, Brandnew.
I thought there would be more confusion.
Now I know that you're
Straw Hat-ya's disciple
Maybe, they don't know yet.
Get away from me!
but why did you come to the New World
Fleet Admiral!
Destroy each other! You foul humans!
No way.
I'm not gonna let Law and Straw Hat
do whatever they want!
and kidnap our important hostage?
Hey!
Let's ask. Hey, pops!
I got an annoying call from
Smoker of the G-5 yesterday.
What's that?
Don't!
What's your problem?!
He said "I'm sorry for attacking the ship.
I didn't know it was your ship, Master."
What's wrong?
You were on the front page of
the newspaper this morning!
No, I mean, look.
The leash!
Hey!
Let's see how things go for today.
"I have a good reason for that."
Here's your order.
I sent Fujitora!
Keep fighting!
Luffy and Chopper and... a dugong and...
Thank you for waiting...
...or not!
"When I met you in
Alabasta, you said..."
Tiptoe, stealthy steps... Goodbye!
Your Majesty!
...rabbits?!
Here it comes!
I couldn't wait any longer!
Please don't quit!
Pirates are free.
What a fool.
Dress Shrimp Paella!
Doflamingo-sama!
He still doesn't understand
that nobody can get away from me.
The sea is vast
and there is so much fun out there!
Is it true what they say on the newspaper?!
Rose Squid Ink Pasta!
He said if we keep going straight,
we'll get to Dressrosa in no time.
Well, I'll let him go for now.
Please tell us it's not true!
And Fairy Pumpkin Gazpacho!
"Those words inspired me
so I sailed out to the sea all alone...
Thank you for carrying the Sunny!
Trbol-sama!
Everything looks yummy!
I'm enjoying this bloody show!
Let's eat!
Thank you!
Trbol-sama, where are you?!
...dreaming of becoming
a free pirate like you!"
Yum-yum!
"I came across some very
formidable enemies!"
Have you seen Trbol-sama?
What's "Fairy Pumpkin"?
What are you all gonna do now?
No.
"I made a lot of friends!"
Um, that's... In this country,
we still believe in a myth about fairies!
Okay.
Are you gonna go back to Alabasta?
I wonder what Young
Master-sama is going to do?!
If the Navy is gonna come to attack,
I want to fight-in!
"It's too early to go home," he said.
"We overcame so many difficulties
and formed a pirate
group of sea creatures."
Or not!
What kind of myth?
"Then, we finally
entered the New World!"
We will just follow the Young Master.
"We're Sea Monster Pirates!"
Well, people claim to see fairies! Or not!
"But that was when...
"We're gonna explore the New World,
chasing dreams and adventures!"
Trbol-sama, where are you?
Seeing fairies?
...we met that guy, Breed."
Sounds good!
Yes! Isn't it interesting?
Oh, Baby 5!
Hmmm. A pirate group of sea monsters?
How interesting!
For centuries!
Even though most of us haven't
seen them, they do exist.
All of you can join my crew!
What are you doing up there?!
Look! The whole kingdom is going crazy!
People call those fairies...
Seal, watch out!
I'm sure the whole world is getting upset!
"We're his slaves now."
..."guardian deities of Dressrosa"!
Hey you, stay out of it!
"We kidnapped Caesar on his orders."
"Everybody! Thank you for everything!"
Hey, hey!
Do you wanna get whipped?!
Or not!
By the way, did you get
your fianc killed again?
Ah, shut up!
Breed. So He is the mastermind.
Well, you travelers, please
take care of yourselves.
It seems like Doflamingo has
nothing to do with this.
Or not!
What?! Stop barking!
I don't get it.
Too close!
Why do you keep asking me that?
You're so annoying!
I know you're pretty strong.
Why do you have to listen to him?
Boy...
Take care, Seal!
Annoying but?
They are stranger than fairies.
"Because..."
--Too close!
Annoying but what? Hmmm?
Fall in, all of you!
He got it right again! 14 times in a row!
--What was that?
--That was...
What's going on?
It's a little noisy back there.
Annoying but you like me, maybe?
You fool!
What's wrong?
It's a roulette game.
Don't tell me you're
speaking against me!
That's enough!
Young Master-sama was calling you!
What?
Some blind man is on a winning streak.
"Get out of here now"?
Young Master-sama?
A blind man?
He wanted you to bring that thing!
What?
Damn you!
He said "All right,
everybody, time to go."
Stay away! You make me sick!
Hey, hey, hey!
You just keep getting your fianc killed! Baby 5!
Damn! Damn! Damn!
Place your bets!
Stop choosing guys that would
be killed by Doffy and marry me!
You idiot!
How are you doing, pathetic humans?
I've made up my mind.
Black, please.
Hey, you all are too slow.
Did you hear it? It's black!
See you!
--I bet on black!
--Me, too!
Listen, here's how pets should be;
First, loyal. Second, loyal.
Me, too, of course!
Hmm, just kidding!
Stop!
Take care!
Don't catch a cold!
No more bets!
Third and fourth, loyal.
And lastly, loyal!
See you again!
Dugong!
When I say "Fall in,"
you have three seconds!
Do you...
...need me?
Don't you get it?!
Cut it out!
Hey, Kung Fu Dugong.
The Colosseum is always packed.
You have to bring them together!
Why are you being so slow?!
The morning paper!
Do you want to help them so bad?
If you let me down, you're
a failure as a pet!
Thanks to you, Diamante.
It's black 29!
Oh, it's black!
You're no better than those shitty humans!
"Don Quixote Doflamingo..."
What are you saying?
Doffy, that's because
you're a charismatic king.
I can't believe it! That
was 15 times in a row!
You're Breed, aren't you?
Give us back Caesar!
"...Withdraws from..."
Alright, if you insist, I'll stop them.
Thank you! Really, thank you!
Huh?! Shut up, foul human!
"...the Seven Warlords"!
No.
We became very rich thanks to you!
"And abdicates the throne of
Dressrosa"?! What the hell?!
Straw Hat, Trafalgar, wait!
Oh yeah, it's you guys.
That's because you're strong.
Boy, what should I say?
Stop. You make it sound like
I'm the hero of the Colosseum.
I was just lucky.
"Throne" means he was a king?!
Yes, I am Breed!
It's not that much but
keep it. It's a present!
A king?!
You are the hero of the Colosseum.
I'm a pirate.
My body stopped.
Then it must be a birds' kingdom!
This is from me! Go for more!
A pirate?
Stop saying that.
When things go this well,
it's kind of scary.
--This is from me!
Okay, I stop.
I can't believe a Warlord like
Trafalgar Law is here along
Alright, I admit it if you insist!
It's good. He had no choice.
with Straw Hat Luffy, a pirate
with a 400 million bounty!
Yes, I am the hero of the Colosseum!
Thank you for chasing us all the way here,
you pain-in-the-ass, shitty humans!
Instead,
By the way, why are our
faces here as well?
you do it.
I brought it!
Doffy, it's that thing!
You're too close!
"The Warlord - Trafalgar Law..."
Too close but?
Since you like them so much,
it'll be far more interesting
You are quite a gambler, huh?
But I like it. Sit down.
You can't hit us with that.
"Forms an unusual alliance
with the Straw Hats"?
Let's play just me and you! What do you say?
I'm not so sure about that!
to see you beating them up!
"It is still unknown what the
Government will do to Law." It says!
What? Just you and me?
Pet-peto!
Kill those two, Dugong!
If Straw Hat Luffy finds out about this,
What the hell?!
That's right!
I wanna play a game against
such a very lucky guy!
There's something else!
What?
VARIOUS PLACES IN THE WORLD
I'm sure he will try to get hold of it.
There's so much going
on in today's paper!
Now, go!
Don't tell me you're gonna quit now.
Ouch!
An alliance can sometimes prove a hindrance.
What's this?!
That guy's terrible!
Doflamingo quits the Warlords and
Law and Straw Hat join forces!
No, I got chips from everybody as you see
I can't take it off!
How does this work?!
Diamante. I want to entrust this to you.
And these guys, too!
You okay, Chopper?!
so I'm going to play a lot more.
Wait a second, Doffy! I can't take it.
Captain Kid!
Trafalgar! Straw Hat!
Good! I like you, old man!
No, I want to entrust this to you.
Scratchmen Apoo!
You two are strong.
Stronger than me.
Basil Hawkins!
Stop. You make it sound like
I'm some kind of genius.
The Kid Pirates, the On Air Pirates,
So everybody else, please
go to the room in the back
I can only entrust this to a genius like you.
But is that enough to beat me?!
and the Hawkins Pirates have
formed a pirate alliance, too?!
to exchange your chips.
Stop saying that.
Now, you...
Okay, I stop.
They were the troublemakers
Now, place your bets.
Wh-What do you want?
that everyone kept an eye
on for last two years
Alright, I admit that I'm
a genius if you insist!
Seal, I'll be alright!
Tear Trafalgar and Straw Hat...
White, please.
and now they've joined
forces all at once!
Yes! I can take care of
that dumb-ass Straw Hat!
Oh, okay.
...limb to limb!
Is something about to
happen in the New World?!
Then, I bet on black.
I can't believe other pirates
were forming an alliance, too!
What? What's going on?
What's wrong, Chopper?
I'll be counting on you!
How does it go? What is it?
I can't control my body!
They formed an alliance, too, huh?
I know he will jump at it!
I wonder if they're thinking
the same thing as us.
What's this? What's going on here?!
Forget about them.
We're gonna go on with the plan.
I'm sorry! It's black!
Focus on Doflamingo for now.
You were off!
H-Hey...
Oh, did I? Then I'll get it right this time!
The source of his late brother's power.
The Flare-Flare Fruit.
Okay, white!
Now you know how important yesterday's
negotiation was for him.
That's amazing!
Let's see.
Chopper, what's happening to you?!
You've missed it again. It's black 20!
That was close!
I'm sure he wouldn't want
anybody else to have it!
All we did was kidnap Caesar.
It should be white this time!
Why are you attacking?!
In contrast, seemingly
overnight, he gave up
That bastard!
his throne which he's had for ten years
It's black again!
and the carte blanche given to him
as a privilege of being a Warlord.
White!
It's black!
Do you realize what happens
if you disobey me?!
Get away, you two!
Black!
He did it just to get this
guy back and that says a lot!
What's going on?!
White!
Now, throw them into the sea!
It seems as though he
hasn't lost his senses.
I'm sorry!
I can't control myself!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty! Why did you resign?!
It's black!
Please! Get away from me!
That's awful!
They're a disgrace to Don Quixote!
Please give us a reason, Your Majesty!
Seal!
I have no choice. Room!
I told you to use the lower half
What's the matter with them?
I see an island!
Don't do it! You can't hurt Chopper!
of your body and pull your
arm back all the way!
Okay, say goodbye to your bets!
You fool! I'm not gonna kill him!
We can make a lot of money
when Buffalo-san isn't here.
I just wanna control him!
Right.
I see it!
Dammit!
I guess I'm running out
of luck. This is no good.
But you sure got stronger!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
The Straw Hats see a shadow of an island.
What do you wanna do? Do you wanna quit?
I ate the Peto-Peto Fruit!
Your Majesty!
No.
Peto-Peto? Don't tell me it's...
One last time.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
That's right!
I can manipulate all living things as I want
with my Peto-Peto power!
I bet everything!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
What is that rocky island?!
Great!
Then I'm gonna bet everything
on whichever color you don't pick.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Which means I can make them my pet!
Let's play it like real men!
Pet? So "Peto-Peto" means "pet"?
Ring, ring, ring...
Everything? Really?
Yeah.
I can control any living thing
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Alright, let's do it.
and bring out all of its power!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
We made it! It's Dressrosa!
Place your bets!
You idiot! Don't shout!
Doflamingo will hear us!
You will see how deadly it is!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
No, he won't!
I've made up my mind.
We'll save you soon, Kanjuro!
Ring, ring, ring...
White, please!
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
This is a kingdom of love
and passion - Dressrosa.
It's me.
I can't wait!
I resigned...
...from the Warlords.