Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around the
world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want
it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in
search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can't stand still, I can't stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu
kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to
the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that's what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner:D
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece,
I'll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It's important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can't stand still, I can't stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won't left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that's our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I'm
aiming at hasn't changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can't stand still, I can't stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
we go!
All the pirates who are  after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has  ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,  a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the
King of the Pirates!
While the Straw Hats were
on their way to Dressrosa,
a mysterious man named Breed, who
leads a pack of sea monsters,
made a raid on them
and kidnapped Caesar.
Luffy and two others snuck into the
enemy's ship to take back Caesar
and were reunited with a Kung Fu
Dugong who they met in Alabasta
but like the Dugong and
the other monsters,
they've been taken control of by
Breed's Peto-Peto Fruit power.
Kill those two, Dugong!
"A Major Turnaround! Luffy's
Angry Iron Fist Strikes!"
That was quite a punch, Kung Fu Dugong!
How do you feel now?
You sent some shitty humans
to hell with your own hands.
Lie down!
Now I have to discipline you
because you disappointed me!
Stop!
Oh, Chappy!
What's wrong?!
You must forget about Straw Hat!
You will live in a kingdom that I
will create as my loyal pet
for the rest of your life!
What do you think you're doing?
I'm a pirate!
Pirates should be free!
I'm not gonna become your
pet even if it means death!
Pirates are free.
Are you gonna betray me?!
Betray you?! Luffy is my only captain!
Are you stupid?!
Straw Hat has been swallowed by
the sea along with Trafalgar!
You know what happens to
Devil Fruit eaters when
they fall into water...
He'll never be defeated
by a guy like you!
He's gonna become the
King of the Pirates!
The King of the Pirates?!
Are you out of your mind?!
You are out of your mind!
You say you're gonna create a
kingdom of submissive animals?!
There's not a chance for
you to create such a thing!
You never try to understand
the people around you!
No one's gonna follow someone like you!
You never try to understand
the people around you!
No one's gonna follow someone like you!
Shut up!
I'll leave the rest up to you guys!
Hey, didn't you hear me?!
I mean "You all have
to finish them off"!
What? Maybe, the Peto-Peto Fruit is...
Now,
do it!
What's going on?!
What?!
Excuse us for a while, you guys.
Luffy!
I'm here to get Chopper back!
And, to give you a good, solid punch!
Why are you here?!
You two got thrown into the sea!
Your little power won't
work against us anymore.
Huh? What are you talking about?!
Trafalgar! Straw Hat! Sit down!
Hey! I said "Sit down"!
Don't you hear me?!
I thought so.
If we can't hear your command, your
special power won't affect us.
Am I right?
I can't hear your orders like
this. I can shut out your voice.
You have Transponder Snails
and loudspeakers everywhere
so you can give the animals
commands all at once, don't you?
When did you figure it out?!
It went through my mind at that time.
Caesar!
Lie down!
Hey, Caesar!
I said "Lie down"! Can't you hear me?!
After I figured it out,
I pretended that I was
being controlled by you
and looked for a chance
to take Caesar back.
Even the fight against Straw Hat, you...
Yes, I was pretending that I
was being controlled by you.
He, however,
was really being puppeteered.
Did you say something?
I can't hear what you're
saying with these earplugs.
It wasn't too hard for me to break
our fall because I could
use my Devil Fruit power.
I gotta get away while that jerk
is focusing on Straw Hat and Law.
Is that Straw Hat's submersible?!
How lucky I am!
Oh, Caesar!
We were lucky to catch
Caesar right away.
I wasn't lucky at all! It
couldn't have been worse!
Huh? What did you say?!
If you wanna join the conversation,
take out your earplugs!
--What did you say?!
--I said "Take out your earplugs"!
I said...
Pets are useless!
Humans are worthless!
Everyone is a piece of trash!
Earplugs?! What a stupid gimmick!
Do you think you're outsmarting me?!
Let me show you the true, formidable
power of the Peto-Peto Fruit!
What?
Now, "me"!
Kill all those...
...stinking humans!
What is he doing? He put
a collar on himself!
He is...
No way!
That's right!
Once you have been given an order
through the Peto-Peto power,
it will bring forth all of your power
even that is normally impossible!
Fall in, my damned pets!
Wh-What's going on?!
Now, guys,
those lousy humans are
not following my orders!
Kill them!
Stop!
How could you do that to your own crew?!
Seal?
What do you want?!
"We are not your tools!"
That's what the Dugong said!
"We might be your crew but
we won't be your tools!"
"We are no longer your pets!"
"We're not gonna give in
to your power! We're...
...pirates!"
You bastards!
What do you think you're doing?!
Seal!
Let's knock him on his ass!
Damn!
How dare you all go against me?!
Fine! I'll destroy everything!
Come on, Sea Lapins!
How do you like my overwhelming power?!
I'll let you all be
swallowed by the sea!
There's nothing you can do!
Let's do it, Seal!
Those of you who disobey
me are all worthless!
All of you deserve death!
Straight to hell with you all...
What's wrong with you
guys?! Hey! Let go of me!
Hey! Let go of me!
Hey!
Gum-Gum...
...Fore-fist...
...Punch!
Hey!
What's that?
What's wrong?
No, I mean, look.
Hey!
Luffy and Chopper and... a dugong and...
...rabbits?!
He said if we keep going straight,
we'll get to Dressrosa in no time.
Thank you for carrying the Sunny!
Thank you!
What are you all gonna do now?
Are you gonna go back to Alabasta?
"It's too early to go home," he said.
"We're Sea Monster Pirates!"
"We're gonna explore the New World,
chasing dreams and adventures!"
Sounds good!
"Everybody! Thank you for everything!"
Take care, Seal!
He said "All right,
everybody, time to go."
See you!
Take care!
Don't catch a cold!
See you again!
The morning paper!
"Don Quixote Doflamingo..."
"...Withdraws from..."
"...the Seven Warlords"!
"And abdicates the throne of
Dressrosa"?! What the hell?!
"Throne" means he was a king?!
A king?!
Then it must be a birds' kingdom!
When things go this well,
it's kind of scary.
It's good. He had no choice.
By the way, why are our
faces here as well?
"The Warlord - Trafalgar Law..."
"Forms an unusual alliance
with the Straw Hats"?
"It is still unknown what the
Government will do to Law." It says!
What the hell?!
There's something else!
VARIOUS PLACES IN THE WORLD
There's so much going
on in today's paper!
Doflamingo quits the Warlords and
Law and Straw Hat join forces!
And these guys, too!
Captain Kid!
Scratchmen Apoo!
Basil Hawkins!
The Kid Pirates, the On Air Pirates,
and the Hawkins Pirates have
formed a pirate alliance, too?!
They were the troublemakers
that everyone kept an eye
on for last two years
and now they've joined
forces all at once!
Is something about to
happen in the New World?!
I can't believe other pirates
were forming an alliance, too!
They formed an alliance, too, huh?
I wonder if they're thinking
the same thing as us.
Forget about them.
We're gonna go on with the plan.
Focus on Doflamingo for now.
Now you know how important yesterday's
negotiation was for him.
All we did was kidnap Caesar.
In contrast, seemingly
overnight, he gave up
his throne which he's had for ten years
and the carte blanche given to him
as a privilege of being a Warlord.
He did it just to get this
guy back and that says a lot!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty! Why did you resign?!
Please give us a reason, Your Majesty!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Your Majesty!
Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
It's me.
I resigned...
...from the Warlords.