Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Laboon isn't an ordinary whale.
He's a whale with a human heart.
"A Promise Between Men!
Luffy and the Whale Vow to Meet Again"
Why does Laboon continue
to hit the Red Line?
Why does he continue to
howl at Reverse Mountain?
I'll tell you... Laboon's story...
Huh?
One day, while I was on duty
as the lighthouse keeper as usual,
some good-natured pirates
came down Reverse Mountain
and entered the Grand Line.
And a small whale came in as well,
as if following them.
That was Laboon.
The Island Whale lives
only in the West Blue,
and it's the world's largest whale.
The pirates had been traveling
with Laboon all that time,
but they left him in the West Blue since
the Grand Line is extremely dangerous.
Although they thought they did,
he followed them.
Island Whales usually
travel together as a group,
but I suspect Laboon felt that
he was a member of that pirate group.
Since their ship had broken down,
they stayed at the cape for several months.
So we became quite good friends.
Because of that,
on the day of their departure...
I have a favor to ask, since I trust you.
Could you take care of him for 2-3 years?
We'll go around the world
and definitely come back here.
Listen up, Laboon.
We'll now go into the Grand Line
and travel around the world.
But you wait for us here.
It's a dangerous place.
We can't take you with us.
Don't worry. Three years
will pass by like a flash.
Don't forget... that we're
buddies even if we're far apart.
Well then, we're setting off now...
Guys! We're setting sail! Hoist the anchor!
Yeah!
Laboon!
Laboon! Wait for us!
We'll come back here for sure...!
For sure!!
That was 50 long years ago...
50 years...!
Laboon has been waiting
for those guys for 50 years?
Is that why he continues to howl
at the wall, hitting himself on it?
Yeah...
This is an amazing canal.
I'm surprised that he's still alive,
having a hole like this inside his body.
Is this also your playful mind?
--A doctor's playful mind.
--Doctor?
I may not look one, but I'm a doctor.
I also ran a clinic on
the cape a long time ago.
It was just for a few years,
but I was also a ship's doctor.
Really?
Then be our ship's doctor!
Don't be ridiculous.
I no longer have the energy to do
reckless things like you guys do.
A doctor, huh? That's why the inside
of the whale's body is like this...
Then these are from the treatment...
That's right.
When the whale is this big,
it's impossible to treat it from outside.
I'm gonna open the doors.
There it is!! The real sky!!
Hm? Miss Wednesday, what on earth...
Shhh...
But 50 years....?
Those pirates sure are
making him wait a long time...
Idiot! This is the Grand Line.
They're dead.
No matter how long he waits,
they won't come back.
Yeah, it's true that 50 years ago
the Grand Line was an uncharted sea
more terrible and chaotic than it is now.
Why are you talking so hopeless?!
You don't know that for sure yet!
They might come back!
It's a very touching story!
A whale continues to believe
in the promise his friends made...
Right, pops?!
Yeah... But reality is cruel.
I confirmed it using reliable information.
They ran away... from the Grand Line.
Can't be... Don't tell me...
they left without him?!
Ran away from the Grand Line...
Does that mean they went
through the Calm Belt alive?
Even if they are alive,
they'll probably never come back here.
Seasons. Weather. Current. Wind direction.
They are all random.
Common sense is useless in the Grand Line.
The terror of the Grand Line
takes over weak minds in an instant.
So having weak minds,
they ran away from this sea
without keeping their promise
in order to save their asses...
They abandoned this whale?!
When he's been waiting for 50 years...?!
That's cruel!
If you know that,
why haven't you told him?
That whale can understand
what people say, right?
I did tell him... everything.
Laboon! Listen up!
I heard that they left the Grand Line.
You were certainly friends,
and the promise they made
with you was certainly for real.
But they'll never come back here...
Listen to me, Laboon! They're not gonna...
I understand you don't wanna accept it.
But somehow you have to accept it...
Laboon!
It's since then that he started
howling at Reverse Mountain
and that he started slamming
his body against the Red Line...
It's as if he's insisting that
they'll come back from the other
side of that wall any time now...
What a whale...
When there's no point in waiting...
He refuses my words
because if he accepts them,
it means that there
is no point in waiting.
He's afraid of that more than anything.
He's from the West Blue.
There's no way of going back there now.
That's why those pirates he came here
with are his only buddies and hope.
But you know, it's true
that he is a poor whale,
but in a way you were
also betrayed, right?
Haven't you done
enough for him already?
Look at the scars on his forehead!
If he continues to hit his head hard
like that, he'll die without doubt.
It's a strange relationship, but
I've been with him for 50 long years.
I can't just stand by
and watch him die now.
Hmph!
Huh?
What's that idiot doing?
When we looked away for a second...
Is he pretending he's mountain
climbing or something?
Gum-Gum...
...Flower Arrangement!
Isn't that a mast?
Yep. It's from our ship.
It's the main mast...
Hey! Don't break the ship!
What the hell are you doing?!
Wha...?! Hey, kid!
Don't worry. He doesn't
die even when he's crushed!
Ha! Dummy!
What does he think he's doing?!
Luffy! What the hell
are you trying to do?!
It's a draw!
I'm strong, aren't I?
You wanna defeat me, don't you?!
Our fight isn't over yet!
So we have to fight again.
Your buddies're dead,
but I'm your rival forever.
We definitely have to fight again
in order to decide who is stronger.
After going around the Grand Line,
we'll come back to see you again.
When I come back, let's fight again!
Hmmm. This is good.
This is the symbol of
our promise to fight again.
Until we come back,
don't remove that mark by
hitting your head. Got that?!
All right!
Hm? Where're those guys?
Those guys? Oh, those two weird people?
Maybe they ran away?
I wonder who they were after all...
Miss Wednesday. What do we do now?
Hmmm.
In any case, we have to go back once
and at least report to the boss...
Our estimated mission
completion time has long passed.
Right. That's not good.
They'll make us out to be traitors.
Yes. Since we don't have
our weapons any more,
we'll go back to our
office and start over.
It can't be helped.
Well then, we... will...
Hm? Well...? What?!
What's the matter?
--It's gone...
--What?
Huh?
Hmmm? What the heck is this?
You dropped the log pose?!
I'm really sorry, Miss Wednesday!
We can't even go back
to our town without it.
As it stands...
Ah!
C... Could that be...?!
What?!
That's...
O-Oh, no...
--The Unluckies!!
--Darn it! Is it too late now, then?!
--Mr. 13!
--Miss Friday!
Please wait! We can explain!
We'll report to the boss immediately!
Okay then! I'm finally drawing up the
plans for the Grand Line journey now.
All right! I'm finally cooking
the Elephant Bluefin Tuna!
Damn...! How dare Luffy
break the ship?! Geez...
Hey, Zoro! Help me out here!
I'm not a shipwright!
What's going on? Quiet down.
What's the matter, Nami-san?!
If it's food you're
worried about, it's ready!
Oh? Meal time?
Th-The compass is broken!
It doesn't point in any direction...!
Ahh, you're right.
It's spinning.
Whoa! That's cool!
Looks like you guys came
here with no knowledge.
For heaven's sake!
Did you come here to die?
--What?
--Meal?
Feed, in your case!
I thought I told you...
...that common sense
is useless in this sea.
It's not that that compass is broken.
Hm? Then, could it be that
the magnetic fields are...
That's right. The islands in the Grand Line
contain lots of magnetic minerals.
Because of that, they are causing
abnormality throughout the Grand Line.
Furthermore, the current and
the winds don't have constancy.
If you're a navigator, you
should know how scary that is.
It's true that if we don't have a way
of knowing our direction, it's hopeless.
Yummy!
I-I didn't know! Oh, well...
Hey! That's bad! Are we gonna be okay?!
This isn't bad. It's yummy!
Hey, you guys! Please just be quiet!
The nose of the Elephant
Bluefin Tuna tastes good!
You need a log pose to
travel around the Grand Line.
Log pose? I've never heard of it.
It's a special compass
that can record magnetism.
Is it a strange-looking compass?
Yeah, its shape is unusual.
Is it something like this?
Yeah, that's it.
Without the log pose,
it's impossible to travel in the Grand Line.
I see... But hold on a sec.
--Luffy?
--Hm?
How come you have one?!
This is something that those
two weirdoes dropped on the ship.
They did?
Why did you hit me?
Just going with the flow.
Oh, the flow, huh?
So this is the log pose.
There's no dial face.
It's known that the magnetism of islands
in the Grand Line follow a certain rule.
That is, by recording the magnetism
of two islands pulling against each other,
you can find the route to the next island.
Since you can't even figure out
its location in this sea,
the magnetism record of the log pose
is the only thing you can depend on.
At first, you can pick one out of the seven
magnetisms produced by Reverse Mountain.
But no matter which island you start with,
those magnetisms will eventually
pull against each other
and link themselves to one route.
And the name of the island
at the end of the route is... Raftel.
It's the last point on the Grand Line.
The only one in history who confirmed
that island is the King of the Pirates.
It's a legendary island.
Raftel...
Then, the One Piece is there?!
Who knows? That's the
most prominent theory,
but no one has been able to reach there.
We'll know once we get there.
Now that I'm done eating,
shall we get ready?
Did you eat this all by yourself?!
Whoa! Even the bones're gone.
Log pose, huh? We have
to take good care of this.
This is the key to our journey.
You damn rubber man!
I wanted Nami-san...
I wanted Nami-san to...
...eat more!!
Ouch! What're you doing?
--That'll show you, you damn rubber man.
--Sanji-kun...
Yes, Nami-san!
Both of you, go cool your heads off!!
Hey, hold on a sec...
Wasn't that something really important?!
Our precious log pose was...
Don't panic. I'll give you mine.
I wanna thank you guys for Laboon, too.
Ahhh... I thought I'd die. Hm?
Here, take my hand, honey.
--Oh, thank you.
--Nice day, isn't it?
Hey!
We have a favor to ask.
Whisky Peak? That's a weird name.
What's that?
That's where we live... uhm, sir.
What happened to your own ship?
It's busted.
Isn't that asking too much, Mr. 9,
after trying to kill the whale?
So what are you guys?
I'm a king.
Liar.
We can't say!
But we want to go back to the town.
We don't want to be
secretive, either, but...
The motto of our company
is "mystery," after all...
We just can't tell you anything about us.
Placing confidence in your character,
we're begging you.
We will definitely return the favor.
Don't do it.
No matter what they say,
they're dishonest people.
By the way, we don't have a
log pose because we broke it.
Do you still wanna ride with us?
What?! You broke it?!
That's mine, you know!
How dare you act stuck up
just because we're being humble?!
You guys can't go anywhere, either!
Oh, but actually, we have
one that Crocus-san gave us.
We beg you people of such character...
Dammit! This bitch tricked us!
You can ride with us.
What?!
Did you say Whisky Peak? Let's go there.
What?
Hey, are you serious?
We're troubling ourselves
to take these shadowy people?
What's the problem?
Don't worry about small things.
But you can only choose the
route here, the starting point.
If we don't like it, then we
can go around one more time.
I see...
Now, shall we get going?
Now I've made a promise with the whale.
Let's get ready to set sail.
Who on earth are you?
Me? I'm...
...the man who'll be King of the Pirates.
What a stupid pirate...
It should be okay by now.
The log must've been stored.
Is it pointing at the
same direction as the map?
Yep. It's pointing at Whisky Peak.
See ya, flower pops!
Thanks for the log pose!
Yeah. Have a safe trip!
See ya, whale! I'm leaving now!
To Whisky Peak...
...full speed ahead!!
Yeah!!
I wonder if they're the pirates that
we've been waiting for all this time...
That man has such
an uncanny air about him...
Don't you think, Roger?
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Whoa!! What a feast!
Receiving this kind of treatment
as soon as we arrive?
I'm glad I'm a pirate!
Hey, don't you guys think it's weird?
There're many cute girls, too!
The entire town is welcoming us...
What do you think, Nami?
When it comes to a drinking game,
I won't lose! Bring it on!
You too?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Town That Welcomes Pirates?
Setting Foot on Whisky Peak"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!