Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
koukishin ni makasete
Go along with your curiosity
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
kokoro no chizu hirogete
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
The Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law.
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed
a pirate alliance with Law
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law.
and were drawn into a climactic
battle on Punk Hazard
Planning to hand over Caesar,
who they caught in Punk Hazard,
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
Now, they have come to Dressrosa
which ended with Caesar's capture.
and to destroy the factory
producing the deadly weapon - SMILE,
Then, they headed out for
their next destination
Their plan was to destroy the
SMILE manufacturing factory
When Luffy found out that the prize for a
along with their pirate ally
- the Warlord - Trafalgar Law.
they came to Dressrosa -
the kingdom that Doflamingo rules.
Their plan was to destroy the SMILE
and rescue a samurai
fighting event was the Flare-Flare
Fruit, he decided to enter.
manufacturing factory and rescue a samurai
but after Zoro's sword was stolen,
they got separated.
Are you interested in that guy?
but after Zoro's sword was stolen,
they got separated.
Ace's...
When Luffy found out that the
prize for a fighting event
Who are you?
...Flare-Flare Fruit?!
I'm Rebecca. A gladiator.
We made it! Dressrosa!
Please! Hold me!
at the Corrida Colosseum
was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
"A Dangerous Love!
The Dancer Girl - Violet!"
Luffy and the others arrived at Dressrosa -
a kingdom ruled by Doflamingo,
he decided to enter.
This man was a legend.
The other competitors, however,
and divided into three teams.
were the heavy hitters
from all over the world!
A legend? This old man?
The first team will head for
Green Bit to hand over Caesar.
He was the strongest
gladiator in the history
Hey you, right there.
of the Corrida Colosseum, named Kyros.
Or I will... fall for you.
The second team will stay at
the Sunny to guard the ship.
That's no good.
The winner of the Block
A battle group emerged:
BANG!!
There is a weight limit for gear.
The third team will...
Burgess from the Blackbeard Pirates.
Huh? Is that so?
...destroy the SMILE factory
and rescue a samurai.
My name is Violet.
Whatever you do,
there is no chance for you.
Now, the battle of Block B is about to start.
Could you escort me to the next town
if you don't mind?
Luffy and the others entered
a port town - Acacia
I will win the Flare-Flare Fruit.
The champion will get a Devil Fruit?!
Meanwhile...
where they came across living toys.
The next town?
Yes! That beautiful power belongs only to me.
And...
On top of that, it's none other than "Fire-Fist" Ace's
Flare-Flare Fruit?!
Then, they walked into a bar to eat something.
However...
Let's go this way!
...I want you to kill someone!
What?
Hey.
"A Pirate Noble!
Cavendish!"
I'm not blind.
The champion will get a Devil Fruit?!
Today, here in this Colosseum,
No matter how you disguise yourself,
On top of that, it's none
other than "Fire-Fist" Ace's
My name is Cavendish.
I can't help recognizing the face of the guy...
we have tough fighters from the New World
who were summoned by our king
How does it go? What is it?
Flare-Flare Fruit?!
CAVENDISH OF THE WHITE HORSE
Oh, here, here! I want to enter!
I didn't have to tell you my name because...
Enter! Enter! Enter! Enter!
and brave participants from the public
who are confident of their ability.
...who put a blot on my record!
THE CAPTAIN OF THE BEAUTIFUL PIRATES
BOUNTY: 280 MILLION BERRIES
...everybody knows who I am.
I'm sorry! It's black!
What?
You!
What?!
No, you don't! You're too old!
They will be divided into separate blocks
How beautiful!
You were off!
"The Fateful Reunion!
Bellamy the Hyena!"
The "Pirate Noble" of the
white horse - Cavendish-sama!
and the winners of each block
will get to go to the next round.
Okay, white!
Oh, I didn't expect to see you here!
Let's see.
However, they can't have this valuable prize
so easily!
You've missed it again. It's black 20!
"A Formidable, Unknown Warrior!
Here Comes Lucy!"
How sinful it is to be this beautiful!
SCENE-1
THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
It should be white this time!
It's theirs for the taking - if they can!
It's black!
Perfect as this rose. That is what I am.
The gladiators that they're gonna fight
are not the ordinary bunch!
White!
The ones who are gonna fight
the winners of each block are...
I'm sorry!
Grandpa, I'm currently accepting
I've been blessed with
everything all my life.
It's black!
entries for the competition
in the Corrida Colosseum.
I guess I'm running out
of luck. This is no good.
I know! I'm entering!
From the Don Quixote Family...
Because I've made it this far without
Huh? Does that old man want to enter?
You...
eating a Devil Fruit or even really trying.
What do you wanna do? Do you wanna quit?
...gave the diamond-head pops hell.
Is he nuts?
Does he have any idea about
the other competitors?!
Just with my natural gifts!
No.
I'll be back by morning!
I don't think so.
Because, in addition to
all those powerful people
One last time.
Señor Pink!
from the New World, looking
to win the Flare-Flare Fruit,
You're overweight.
A city of gold? A sky island?!
I bet everything!
What?!
I told you earlier! Come here!
there are some formidable fighters
from the Don Quixote Family!
Great!
The era of dreams is over,
you pathetic excuses for pirates!
Tsk! I look awesome this way!
Then I'm gonna bet everything
on whichever color you don't pick.
Dellinger!
Hey Luffy, listen. Promise me just one thing.
That's why everybody's half-naked.
Let's play it like real men!
You can fight as you like
Lao G.!
but don't ever let them know who you are.
Everything? Really?
Your name was...
Okay!
Yeah.
Everybody's excited!
Sign your name.
...Maro.
-Bellamy!
Machvise!
Luf...
Alright, let's do it.
Oh yeah, Bellamy!
You idiot!
Do you know what makes them so excited?
Why are you here?!
Place your bets!
And the hero of the Colosseum...
No particular reason.
THE FORMER CAPTAIN OF THE BELLAMY PIRATES
I'm not a resident of Jaya.
It's blood.
BELLAMY THE HYENA
BOUNTY: 195 MILLION BERRIES
I've made up my mind.
I can be wherever I want.
Gladiators are just part of a show for them.
White, please!
On top of that,
People get excited seeing a loser's blood.
Beyond this point, competitors only.
Doflamingo has been my pirate hero
since I was a kid.
At the Colosseum, people
really show their true color.
Follow me.
Mr. Diamante!
"Full of Enthusiasm!
The Corrida Colosseum!"
I've no interest in the Flare-Flare Fruit
Just go ahead and beat them all up.
but I have my own reason to win this thing!
They're bottling up frustration,
fear, and anger everyday
--Diamante-sama!
--Diamante!
But keep a low profile.
Well, then I'll have to just fight you again!
Count on me!
and hiding their bestiality
deep inside of them.
If you pick white, I bet on black, of course!
I'll be back with the Flare-Flare Fruit!
But I'm not the man I used to be.
Just start already!
But they want to let it all out.
We wanna see a fight!
Straw Hat.
Okay.
Who wants to see a prolonged match
between heavily armored competitors?
I visited the Sky Island.
Can't wait any longer!
Just start a match already!
For them, this competition is just a show.
You mean Skypiea?!
I lost my crew but it turned my
view of the world upside down.
Come on, white! White!
It's gonna be black! Black!
Should I take off this cape, too?
But it looks so good!
You didn't do anything to
the people there, did you?!
Hey you.
As I thought, she entered. Rebecca...
I was watching you take
down that big guy earlier.
Maybe. Maybe not.
How did Ace's Flare-Flare Fruit get here?!
Who are you?
Anyway, I'm not holding a grudge
against you anymore.
I'm Luffy!
Huh?!
--What?!
--Lu...
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
I heard there are no two
I'm gonna get on board Doflamingo's
ship to ride through
Devil Fruits of the same
power existing at once.
Lu...
the "wild wave" that will come soon or later.
Your name is Lucy!
Oh yeah, it's Lucy.
However,
Which is it?!
when a Devil Fruit eater dies,
Ouch.
Don't confuse us!
I'm done picking on you.
a Devil Fruit with the power that
the deceased possessed will pop
up again somewhere in the world.
Oh, you're Lucy!
I thought Straw Hat Luffy was here!
And when somebody eats it,
he'll become the new holder of that power.
No way!
I heard the real one is
an eight-meter-tall giant!
Hey.
This is nice!
After "Fire-Fist" Ace died,
Huh?! Wh-What do you want?!
You're not saying anything. That means...
the Flare-Flare Fruit was,
without anyone knowing, reproduced
If you were really...
Were you born in this country?
...it's white, isn't it?!
...Straw Hat Luffy, I would have...
and the Young Master-sama got hold of it!
Of course! I was born and raised here!
I'm a pure Dressrosan!
Hey.
I'm sorry, old man!
...killed you here and now.
What?
That bastard!
What?! That means it's...
I see.
Why?
I can't believe the Young Master-sama
I entered the New World three years ago.
made the Logia type Devil Fruit
a prize for the competition!
Yes!
AT A CAFE IN THE NORTHEAST
--It's bl...
--White!
If I can possess such incredible power,
my life will change!
The whole world was talking
about this beautiful rookie
Can I ask you something?
SCENE-2
CAESAR HANDOVER TEAM
Do you know if the big guns of
the Don Quixote Family
who was worth over 200 million.
Green Bit?
are here today?
I'm not gonna let you eat it!
Newspapers covered me everyday.
Don Quixote?!
I don't recommend you to go there.
Ah?! Who the hell are you?!
Now I remember. Ace was your...
Keep it down!
Girls went nuts over my wanted posters.
Are you people researchers or explorers?
Do you know or not?
I want it! The Flare-Flare Fruit!
Why do you wanna know such a thing?!
They stole all of the
posters throughout a town.
Yes, something like that.
You better not go
unless you have a purpose
I can't tell you why.
Alright, then do you know something
about the factory?
that's worth risking your life.
Everybody was going crazy about me.
Th-The factory?!
That bridge looks very strong though...
"Hey, big star!"
Look carefully! It's black, idiot!
I said "Keep it down"!
"Who? Me?"
Yes, it's made of iron.
"Of course!"
It's white.
Oh yeah! Why don't you eat it, Franky?
Old man, you win!
"Cavendish-sama, look at me!"
But, look at the entrance.
Nobody's crossing it nowadays as you see.
What?!
You bastard! Stay out of it!
I don't wanna lose my ability to swim.
"Don't worry! I'm always looking at you all!"
That's right!
Do you wanna get your ass kicked?!
I ate the Gum-Gum Fruit so
I can't eat another one.
A school of Fighting Fish inhabit
the area around Green Bit.
Thank you!
Huh?
But I don't want some stranger
to possess Ace's power.
The food was really amazing!
Before they came,
people used to come and go freely
Who is he?
But...
Doesn't he have any idea who they are?!
...a year later,
but that was 200 years ago.
He got himself involved, as usual!
Whitebeard's War of the Best
drew their attention away!
Now I know.
How annoying!
He looks so calm and composed!
Mister, what's a Fighting Fish?
I've been improving my
skill in cooking but...
Straw Hat Luffy came into the public spotlight
along with Whitebeard!
D-Do I really win?!
It's a savage fish with horns.
It's like a memento of him to you, isn't it?
Yeah, you win.
...it was all for Violet-chan!
It's possible that it's a trap
considering the way
I don't know who you are
but thank you for your kindness!
If you approach them by a ship,
they'll capsize you.
On top of that,
Doflamingo dangled it in front of you.
new rookies kept coming up one after another
That's so...
That's why they reinforced the bridge with iron
but it's no use.
I have something that you'll
want very badly now.
and became popular as the Worst Generation
Don't mention it. I just said what I saw.
Thank you!
and wreaked havoc like crazy!
No use?! What do you mean?!
I'm happy for you.
Reporters don't pay attention to me anymore!
Can they even tear down an iron bridge?!
But, old man, you look so strong...
But one thing is for sure!
Somebody's coming again!
What you're doing is so senseless, you brat!
That's why I'm gonna kill them!
Those annoying newcomers!
Well, I don't know
the current condition of the bridge.
This way!
You shouldn't let the chance slip by!
When we say "It's black," it's black!
All of them!
Only people who crossed it know
but I don't know anyone who came back.
What you're saying is absurd.
He can't see anyway so it doesn't matter!
You don't wanna regret it afterward.
Say whatever you like!
Yes! I will follow you
to the end of the world!
We have to go to the Colosseum anyway.
What?!
You're so annoying!
To recapture everybody's heart,
Hey, Tra-guy!
Go away!
Let's just go there!
You have to change the handing-over spot now!
I would kill as many newcomers as it takes!
Uh-huh!
He's right!
Oh no, did I trip a big boar or something?
Think what it's like to be handed
over at such a place, fool!
Oh! We're like runaway lovers!
To do so, I'm gonna win the
Flare-Flare Fruit today!
You fool!
Idiots!
I'm not gonna change.
The more they chase us, the closer we get!
If you think you can have it just because
If so, I'm sorry.
Your weight is okay now.
you want it, no one would
be risking their life.
We're already here. Stop making a fuss.
Great!
Y-You fool!
Hey, you can't ignore me like that!
Don't underestimate the
level of the competitors.
More importantly,
The more we turn the world against us,
I'm worried about the situation of this country.
Dammit! I'm gonna win the
Flare-Flare Fruit at any cost!
the more the flame of our love burns!
THE GROUP THAT WENT AFTER
THE MYSTERIOUS FAIRY
I wish this happiness would last forever!
Their king quit all of a sudden.
How come they are so calm?
We're in unexpected circumstances already.
This is no good.
They can easily spot us if we keep running.
Let's walk.
That's what worries me!
Young man, could you step aside a little bit?
Okay! Oh?
What are you doing, Robin?
It was a short-lived dream.
Are you a competitor?
I'm going to send those people to hell.
You don't look strong but you're cute!
They call it a fairy?!
It's just a dirty thief!
Kill him!
What's going on?
Damn, she's not very friendly.
Where did it go?
CP-0.
Don't mess with her too much.
What?! "CP"?
Why?
Don't you know?
This way!
I said "Wait"!
Just give up a sword or two!
What?
The strongest intelligence
organization in the world.
No way, idiot!
Th-Th-This is...
Cipher Pol Aigis Zero!
Damn!
Let's go.
D-Don't tell me they're related to CP9!
I won't let it get away!
Stop striking off on your own!
We don't have that much time!
They're the greatest of
all of those organizations!
CP9 was fairly strong!
They are more formidable?!
Oh, that's...
Did you find the fairy?!
When they're on the move,
nothing good happens.
A fairy...
Hmmm... How interesting.
No, she must be a goddess.
What?!
Indeed.
I ended up looking like this old man.
Are you interested in that guy?
SCENE-3
THE FAIRY AND ZORO
This is the dressing room
for the competitors.
Who are you?
You're free until we call you.
I'm Rebecca. A gladiator.
Wow! It's filled with excitement!
REBECCA
A GLADIATOR OF THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
Thank you for what you did earlier.
I won't let you get away, you thief-fairy!
I didn't like Spartan.
The Flare-Flare Fruit is mine!
Ah, don't mention it.
No, it's mine, idiot!
This man was a legend.
Move! You're in my way!
A legend? This old man?
What did you say?!
He was the strongest
gladiator in the history
of the Corrida Colosseum, named Kyros.
He won 3000 out of 3000 matches.
Where did it go?
What?!
The only wound he ever
got was a single slash.
Is that it?!
Wow! He was that strong?!
He used to fight here until 20 years ago.
There it is!
This is it!
But no one in this country knows about him.
I caught you!
Huh? What do you mean?
Hey, who is that little guy?
It's heavy! So heavy...
None of elders or gladiators in this country
has ever seen him.
Give me back my sword!
I-I'm going to get crushed!
It's the strangest statue in Dressrosa.
What?
We don't know if Kyros the
Gladiator actually existed
I see.
or somebody made up the story.
Can we use any weapons we like?
And when and why they built this statue here.
Oh no!
Ow, ow, ow... This is no good!
All we know is
what's written on this plate right here.
Hey, who is he?
I'm so dumb! This human will see me!
A DANCER - VIOLET
Oh, he's the last person to enter.
Although nobody knows about him,
I have to run! Otherwise, the human will...
nobody wants to remove it.
What is that little guy here for?
What?! What's wrong with him?!
That's strange, too.
What did he do?!
--How fascinating!
--How intense!
Hmmm... It's so mysterious but...
SCENE-4
STRAY KIN'EMON
This is the kind of joke I hate the most!
SPARTAN - A GLADIATOR AT THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
(WON A MONTHLY TOURNAMENT 51 TIMES)
Wow! It left a hole!
...I like this statue! It's so manly!
You're the best dancer in the world!
It's not too bad to be blind.
I like it, too.
Where are you, Kanjuro?!
I know there are many hideous things
that are better unseen.
Hey, great warrior - Rebecca-chan!
An undefeated girl!
We know you'll do it today, too!
I'm sure you were happy earlier!
Huh?
To see Spartan who bullied you for
a long time got his ass kicked.
Who are you people?
Stop it, idiot! Let's go!
Hey, fake-bearded brat!
This is a fighting arena!
I'm just an old man passing by!
Everybody's looking forward
to see you get beat!
S...
Don't, Spartan!
She's beautiful!
Don't lie! Isn't that a
topknot under your hat?
It's no fun seeing a weakling get pummeled!
You heard that women in this country stab men,
didn't you?
Okay, excuse me.
What's wrong with them?
A guy like you will get stabbed.
The spectators only get excited
when the strong go head-to-head!
Don't pay attention to them.
N...
No, it's a topknot-shaped hat!
Who is he?
This is not a place for you! Go home!
Then, take it off for us!
I don't mind getting stabbed!
Go home now!
I can't do it - for a good reason.
You're a samurai - Foxfire Kin'emon,
aren't you?!
Oh no! I lost him!
Is he a Devil Fruit eater?
I...
I am not!
What kind of Devil Fruit is that?
That stray Moss Head!
You must confuse me with someone else!
Excuse me, mister.
We saw you in the video from Punk Hazard.
You can send a bill for the repairs here.
I'm gonna fight for the last time today.
Aha!
And we figured a samurai like
you will come back here.
This is a good chance.
Let's leave him on this island!
O-Okay...
I'm gonna win the Flare-Flare Fruit and...
Wh-What?! Don't tell me you're...
I tried as best as I could to catch him.
I made a sincere effort!
That's what samurai do, right?
...kill Doflamingo!
Goodbye.
If so, what are you gonna do?
Old man, you're so strong! Who are you?
What?! Mingo?!
Let me tell you something.
If you point your gun at a samurai,
What block are you in?
you better prepare yourself for the worst!
C.
Great. I'm in D.
Whoa, easy!
I should not tell you that
for the sake of both of us.
I hope we both survive the first round.
If you don't want Kanjuro
who you're obviously looking for, to die.
There are so many couples around here!
I'm jealous!
What?! Did you just say Kanjuro?!
Lucy.
Keep your hand away from
the sword, samurai-san.
Hey, are you blind?!
I wish Nami-san and Robin-chan suddenly
became attracted to me!
You know where Kanjuro is, don't you?!
I-I'm sorry. Did you get hurt?
Excuse me!
Of course, I do.
But if you don't listen to me,
We caught each other's eye earlier,
didn't we?
"For the sake of both of us"?
Is he extraordinarily infamous or something?
I will kill both you and Kanjuro.
Please! Hold me!
Whoever he is, he is not an ordinary man.
What?!
--Oh, my bag is gone!
--So is my watch!
That guy is so strong!
Now, the competitors of
I can't find my wallet!
Happy Store!
Block B are entering the ring
one after another!
Oh no! My jacket got stolen, too!
He's overwhelmingly strong!
The man with a paper bag mask!
In broad daylight,
while there was dust everywhere...
Mr. Store!
That old man was a thief?
I wonder if anyone can defeat him!
I gotta hurry! It's gonna start soon!
There are only two!
Hey, there is an extraordinary
guy in Block A!
What's the matter?
One of my swords is missing!
Huh? What? Who?
Oh, I have a good view from here!
My Shusui that was here a minute ago!
I'm not gonna lose here!
What?! The national treasure
of the Wano Kingdom?!
Where did she go?!
I don't think he can't get away now!
She must've slipped out the back door
to this Lover's Alley!
I don't think she went that far yet!
--We can't let her leave the town!
--Yes, sir!
Damn! My Shusui...
How could you do such a
dirty thing, Navy-san?
Thank you! They're gone now.
Nice to meet ya!
Happy Store!
Where did it go?!
What are you gonna do?!
Excuse me. You can let go of me now.
They stole from everybody.
You people sent in a rat to this competition
It was fairies who took your stuff.
to arrest all the wanted pirates, didn't you?
What are you talking about?!
Well... It's really my pleasure!
Is that the name of a group of thieves?!
What are you talking about?
Fairies are fairies.
All you can do is laugh it off and let it go.
You're good at playing dumb!
I'm sorry! Did you hit
your head or something?
The winner of Block A is the masked man!
Hey, what's wrong with that little guy?!
But I can't just let you go
after getting my dear subordinate beaten.
How can I laugh it off?!
No, it's just meeting you
comes as a shock to me!
He took down Spartan!
Those invisible fairies are
the guardian deities of
Mr. Store!
Dressrosa from ancient times.
I guess I'd better silence you, Bartolomeo.
But you're bleeding a lot!
No way!
We have to turn a blind
eye to whatever they do.
He's one of the star gladiators
of this Colosseum!
It was so fast!
No, it's nothing...
Maybe, he just tripped over himself.
It must hurt.
Well, if fairies did it...
We got the new hero in the Colosseum!
I can't believe how famous I became!
That wouldn't lodge someone in the ground!
We should just forget about it!
No! I can't help falling in love!
I can't just let it go!
Now, where should I sit?
He's right!
The sword is the national
treasure of the Wano Kingdom!
What?! No, you shouldn't
look at me like that!
Did you just start that fight?!
That's my sword!
It's not yours!
Oh? Is he going to take his mask off?!
For real?!
You'll have to leave now!
You're disqualified!
I have already given up on love!
I told you! Somebody gave it to me!
What?!
We don't need hooligans like you
causing scuffles before a match...
All the men who have gotten
involved with me are…
I'll have to challenge you
to a duel at some point
He took it off!
Yes!
and win the Shusui back for the Wano Kingdom!
They were all happy!
What?!
Whoa-whoa!
He's...
They were looking for you! Who were they?!
Yeah, I'll accept it and defeat you!
SCENE-5
SANJI IN LOVE
Hold it right there, you fool!
Tell me if there's something
I can do to help!
I can't believe this! We all know him!
That big one started it!
If you wanna throw someone
out, it's got to be him!
You got too greedy, fairy!
They were the police.
You can't get away!
What an interesting beginning!
And an unexpected competitor!
He passed out though.
There was this man and I...
Hey, Zoro! Where are you going?!
Oh! It's Sai and Boo from the Kano Kingdom!
The battle royal of Block
A - the winner is...
Wait, wait!
Even Don Chinjao is here!
We don't have time to let you wander!
...stabbed him after things went sour.
He's a legend!
Oh, he's...
SAI OF THE CHINJAO FAMILY -
A GANG FROM THE KANO KINGDOM
Sounds like fun!
What?!
Wait, Luffy!
So it's true that women in this
Violet-chan!
Did you find the thief?!
Yes?
country are so passionate about
love that they'd stab a man for it!
BOO OF THE CHINJAO FAMILY -
A GANG FROM THE KANO KINGDOM
No, I just wanted to call your name!
I'm not gonna let anybody
have the national treasure!
Oh my!
--Okay!
--Okay?! Really?!
Hey, let go of me! We should go, too!
DON CHINJAO - A LEADER IN THE CHINJAO FAMILY -
A GANG FROM THE KANO KINGDOM
I have an idea.
What's wrong now?!
An idea?
Is it true?
Sanji-san.
Yes?
Yeah, it is. Spartan started it.
No! Don't be so nice to a bad woman like me!
The winner of Block A is...
I just wanted to call your name!
I see.
...the captain of the first ship of
the fearful Emperor Blackbeard's group -
What?
Then Spartan has to go.
Lucy, you can stay.
Or I will... fall for you.
I understand now.
Jesus Burgess!
Okay!
When there are only these guys around,
I have to take charge.
BANG!!
You saved me! Thank you!
Don't mention it, fool!
Boy, they're all out to get attention?!
I got my sights on the target.
Boy, you don't have to mention it...
He's...
You don't have to say "Thank you"...
Leave everything up to this big brother.
The champion I met that time!
My name is Violet.
I don't like to hear the words "Thank you."
Could you escort me to the next town
if you don't mind?
I'm the Fighting Champion.
Take back your "Thank you," you bastard!
You don't have to refuse
his thanks that much, brother!
The next town?
The Blackbeard Pirates?!
And...
Don't ever say those words to me, idiot!
Why is such a guy fighting here?!
Violet-chan!
Sorry. He's easily excitable.
I can't believe it was Burgess!
"Dear Nami-san and Robin-chan."
No wonder he was so formidable!
There are all kinds of people in the world.
Hey! Stop ganging up with other powerhouses
in your block, Dagama!
There it is! Wait, you fool!
...I want you to kill someone!
"How is the weather there?"
This is exciting! Go, Burgess!
What?
Yee-ha!
You wait, you idiot!
Huh? What the hell are you
talking about, Kelly Funk?
Burgess! Burgess! Burgess! Burgess!
Give me back the national treasure of
the Wano Kingdom!
I can't believe it! You're very strong!
I don't care if it's a
national treasure or not!
Hey hey, look at them.
I can't allow myself to lose the Shusui!
Yeah, there are a whole bunch
The Blackbeard Pirates, huh?
No no! Anybody can detect a sniper
at 16 meters above the ground!
of big names from each and every country!
I was expecting
Luffy will win this thing pretty easily
Wait!
FUNK BROTHERS
ASSASSINS FROM A NEIGHBORING COUNTRY
Boy! First, we saw toys living side-by-side
with humans
It's like a war for the Devil Fruit between nations!
It was nothing!
How dependable!
You wait!
but maybe it's gonna be tough.
"I'm getting hit by a hurricane called love!"
and now, a thieving fairy?!
Give me back the national treasure of
the Wano Kingdom!
KELLY FUNK
(THE OLDER OF THE TWO BROTHERS)
I hope no one finds out who he is.
Ganging up and paying people off?
Damn! What an annoying island!
"I'm...
Now, I've got work to do.
Hey, you make me sick!
It was fairies who took your stuff.
BOBBY FUNK
(THE YOUNGER OF THE TWO BROTHERS)
It's an individual fight.
...in love!"
Hey! Wait a minute!
What are you talking about?!
I'll come with you!
Even if you cheat like that, only one winner per block
We have to turn a blind
eye to whatever they do.
I'm here for you!
What?! Go away!
Look! He has a strange hairstyle!
Can we talk a little bit?
SCENE-6
THE SUNNY'S SECURITY TEAM
What did you say?! How rude!
can go to the next round.
I don't have time to waste!
If it was a fairy or not,
I'm gonna catch it and...
DAGAMA
A TACTICIAN OF THE PRODENCE KINGDOM
Cut that crap!
Well, I'm gonna chop it up
to get the sword back!
I know you two are here on your country's order, too!
Wait!
I didn't know my topknot was exposed!
You fool! That's enough!
Possessing the Flare-Flare Fruit,
I don't need a guy who doesn't
know where the factory is!
which is more powerful than any weapon,
ELIZABELLO II - "THE FIGHTING KING"
THE KING OF THE PRODENCE KINGDOM
Wait! You thief-fairy!
I'm gonna beat the hell out of
would give any country an
some high-ranked guy in the Doflamingo Family...
advantage in diplomatic relations.
No, you shouldn't drink it all up!
--...and make him cough up where it is...
--Whoa-whoa! Wait! Be quiet!
Look around you. See those faces?
What?!
Listen! A poison tester's job is
Peeking, peeking... Peeking, peeking...
There! He is a class-A war criminal
to try the food for a shogunjust a little to see
who was involved in the Sea Battle of Dias
- Suleiman the beheader!
"Dear Nami-san and Robin-chan."
if there isn't any poison in it!
They're former bounty hunters
"I hope you will forgive this sinful man."
Let's go some place else!
who bombed a government
institution - Abdullah and Jeet.
Understood?!
You shouldn't say such a radical thing here!
Yes, sir!
Do it again!
"I finally... finally...
Who the hell are you?
He's a fake adventurer -
"The Surmounter" Orlumbus.
Oh no! I'm not a child but...
Get me a cup of tea, Choppa'emon.
...met the love of my life!"
Medical team! Give aid to
the injured of Block A.
Yes, sir!
A VASSAL: CHOPPA'EMON
...I'm lost!
I'll bring it to you right away, sir!
He's sponsored by the Don Quixote Family -
a sadistic pirate who's worth over 100 million -
Bellamy the Hyena.
"Pirate Mercenary" Hajrudin! Cavendish!
Sir, how are you feeling now?
A MAID: O-NAMI
And "The Missionary" Gambia?!
And "Pirate Noble" Cavendish is here...
Let's go!
Ah, it's so comfortable.
Hey hey, you don't have to rush like that.
I'm your bodyguard.
...as well as the crazy rookie Bartolomeo
I'm feeling great.
Yeah, there are a bunch of bad eggs.
Yes. I was born to protect you!
who became notorious a year ago.
Yeah? That's good.
It's gonna be big trouble if one of
these guys wins the Flare-Flare Fruit!
Now, do you really think all
of these ill-famed people
You're working under Doflamingo, aren't you?
Yeah. So what?
I was surprised about Burgess, too.
are not plotting anything?!
I'm feeling great, too!
I love this romantic island - Dressrosa!
I'll talk to Issho-san right away.
Super that's what we thought!
It's crazy if they don't have a plan!
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey hey!
I'm sure you guys have something! Don't you?
Do you guys think
you can mess with the Young Master-sama
Young man, are you talking to yourself?!
I will get the national treasure of the Wano Kingdom
back for sure!
Hey, aren't you gonna serve food?
Y-You hurt me, Nami-san!
in Dressrosa and get away with it?
No.
The first round is a battle royal.
But first, I have to rescue Kanjuro
who is held captive by Doflamingo's clan!
Huh? I thought it was a
sleeping-in-your-lap party!
You were talking to somebody
A STAFF OFFICER OF A PIRATE GROUP
- THE BARTO CLUB - BOUNTY: 67 MILLION BERRIES
Only one winner per block
will go to the next round.
What kind of party is that?!
out there, weren't you?
Yeah!
Kanjuro!
Brook.
You're fishy!
"THE MISSIONARY" GAMBIA
Block A's match will start soon!
He's playing shogun.
Why are you rushing?!
That's not gonna work for us.
And then, B, C, and D will follow.
Playing shogun?
Wh-What was that?!
Old buddy, why don't you spit it all out -
everything we just asked you...
Am I right? Am I right?
There are 550 competitors here.
Whenever we leave Momo alone,
he looks very serious and depressed.
She was trying to show her
affection for me apparently!
What's that note?!
You were whispering those cool guys' names!
And only four of us may win the first round!
I-I told you!
How aggressive! But...
I remember going after a couple of samurai
"The Missionary" Gambia. That's... me!
Maybe, he's thinking about dirty things.
It's not that easy to win.
Come stop by for a while!
but I don't know how one got captured
and where he is now.
I-I shouldn't allow myself!
No, he's not!
He's not gonna share it with us
What are you up to?
So I guess...
Yielding to a young lady's temptation is...
And I don't know what SMILE is.
...you brothers are in
the same block because
You can't say?!
but maybe he has had some kind
of trauma even at that young age.
...a dishonor to a warrior!
of paying somebody off, am I right?
What?!
Where are you?! Kanjuro!
You don't even know a bit about SMILE?
I see. I didn't notice that.
It's just a coincidence.
Don't tell me you're a Navy soldier...
Yeah, and I don't know the
factory you're talking about.
It's a coincidence.
But he tries to act cheerfully like that
because he doesn't want us to worry.
Which block am I in?
Who are you people?!
Are you all right, sir? Please respond.
I'm sure the receptionist told you already.
I'm coming in!
Your number is 556 so you're in Block C.
I can't believe this.
Even his man doesn't know about it.
How touching.
Everything's fine.
Mister, you can't just come in.
I know everybody has a different purpose
I'll call you back in ten minutes.
Hey, Bone-kichi!
Yes?
We're closed now!
Roger that.
Do something to warm the place up.
but the world could fall
into chaos depending on
Then tell us where people of higher rank are.
Clank.
They have some stuff to cook.
No way. I only take orders from Luffy-san...
who gets the Flare-Flare Fruit.
This guy is too low in rank maybe.
But the knives and frying
pans are not well maintained.
Let's cut the crap and
do our best, everybody!
You don't wanna put your nose in any further.
Do it!
Everyone's too busy today -
I don't know where they are.
All right!
They haven't even washed their dishes.
(I won't!)
I'm gonna sing a song.
These are the guys. No wonder.
"The Missionary" Gambia.
I've been summoned to the Colosseum, too.
Ah, great!
Who do you think you are?!
Soul King!
Go away.
Look!
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for waiting!
Don't like it
I don't like it
I'm gonna cook for
the most wonderful lady in the world.
That bastard!
Let me explain about today's competition!
Get out of this kitchen!
Don't like it
I don't like it
All the people in this kingdom
are heading to the Colosseum today.
I'm scared! Th-That beast is gonna kill me!
Don't mess with us cooks!
Doesn't matter how many times we bury him
Come to yourself! It's over!
You're okay now!
What Colosseum?
It's the Corrida Colosseum.
Wh-Who is he?
The Colosseum is still excited
from the battle of Block A!
He's gonna come back
For the first round, competitors
are divided into four blocks
If you wanna see high-ranked
officials, go there!
I wonder how it's going to be for Block B!
and it's gonna be a battle royal!
You shouldn't mess with a cook.
Why are they going there?
Yeah!
The Vitality Corpse
There will be a very big event today.
A battle royal is a match in which
all competitors fight at once
All the executives of our
family should be there.
Let me use this kitchen for a while.
so everybody is your enemy except yourself!
Come on!
Shall we go?
The very big event that you're talking about is
that super event?
And the last one standing without being
There are so many familiar
names, aren't there?
I'm sorry to keep you waiting, Violet-chan!
eliminated
or getting killed will be the winner!
I think dancing requires stamina.
Thank you, everybody!
For whatever reason, Young Master-sama
offered an unbelievable prize!
A competitor will be
eliminated if he gets thrown
--Huh?
--What?
Enjoy this tasty and nutritious special dish!
out of the ring or if he
gets killed in the ring!
What should we do now?
Oh, it was so surprising!
I don't like it...
Meanwhile, in the water outside of the ring,
Oh, your coat.
Are you...
What?!
Wait!
the Colosseum's unique attraction -
Everyone wants it!
a school of Little Fighting Fish are
waiting to attack whoever falls!
You thief-fairy!
D-Don't tell me it's...
...that delicious meat
that Mingo was talking about!
What's going on?
Moss Head?!
I thought there are only
four of us on the ship.
Huh?
Where are you?!
Doesn't matter if you're
in or out of the ring!
Kanjuro!
So did I... Then what's that noise?!
It's Hell! That's the Corrida Colosseum!
He said he has something that you will want.
We're about to get started!
Kin'emon!
Creepy!
Then what is the prize?
I'm scared!
Is there something wrong?
Here. Are you okay?
O-Nami!
Oh no. Not at all.
Prepare yourself for the shock...
I don't like it... Honestly...
Uh-huh!
The prize is...
Thank you, mister!
All right!
I-I-It's from the men's dormitory.
It's the first round of the special
event in the Corrida Colosseum!
You're welcome!
I wasn't planning to go off on my own.
THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
Oh, I don't like it!
A battle royal of the
Block A - 137 competitors!
Forgive me, Luffy.
Issho-san, here is your coat.
Because it's destiny!
Ouch!
There is somebody in there!
Let the battle begin!
Here he comes! The Lightning Soldier!
Oh, thank you.
THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
Who is it?
You hurt me!
Is this...
What the hell?!
We want to see it, too!
It's a huge Colosseum!
Let us in!
What kind of competition is it gonna be?!
Shall we?
It is not for kids to watch!
What, what's going on?!
People will kill each other! Go home!
Chopper!
The people are going nuts!
That makes me wanna enter the competition!
Take this!
Bone-kichi!
Go look!
What?!
They're going crazy!
That's the wanted toy soldier!
He's making it harder for us!
He just won't give up!
I think we don't have a choice.
Just give up already!
We need, maybe, three Navy ships.
Uh-huh.
You infamous wanted toy soldier!
You can't shoot me!
Jet Walk!
And in the meantime, let's head for... um...
AN ADMIRAL OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
Jet Walk!
Ladies and gentlemen and toys!
What was the name?
It's Green Bit.
FUJITORA (ISSHO)
What you will see today is...
Yes, let's go there.
Armor! Helmets!
And um...
We need as many medics as possible.
This is awesome!
Can we use anything here?!
...one hell of an event!
Just in case, we have casualties.
You can use anything
except projectile weapons.
Yes, sir.
The king entrusted us
with an extraordinary prize...
I also want to know how many spectators
there are in the Colosseum
A half-naked statue of an old warrior man!
...for today's event!
and the population of this town.
You guys are too slow! Look!
Wh-What's going on in here?!
Cool!
I have my foot in the Colosseum!
Okay... Instead of the enemy numbers?
THE ONE-LEGGED SOLDIER
AKA THE ANGRY LIGHTNING SOLDIER
Can I have it?!
You know the law, don't you?!
Is it necessary?
No.
What we have to consider first is
not the number of enemies...
The police and the Navy are not allowed
in the Colosseum!
There was a man who died
in the War of the Best
Even if a criminal is in the Colosseum,
it's not your jurisdiction!
in Marineford two years ago.
...but the number of people we have to protect -
don't you think so?
I can't believe this.
What?! He means...
I will wear this armor!
The only rule of law in here
is that of the Don Quixote Family!
You're too weak and this
is like a joke, Navy-san!
And a helmet that's cooler
than that old man's!
He was a 2nd division commander of
the legendary Whitebeard Pirates
Oh! This is good, too!
Yes, sir!
If you pull that trigger,
you will become a criminal yourself!
I'm gonna use this big sword!
All Navy soldiers in Dressrosa!
and a son of the King of the Pirates -
his name was Ace!
We're gonna head for Green Bit now!
This is nice! I look awesome!
--What?!
--Ace?!
Go away!
Meet us in front of the Colosseum!
Competitors of Block B! Is Capman here?!
Damn!
So cool!
Under command of the Admiral,
we put our plan...
I wish Usopp and the others
were here to see me!
This island is so strange.
They put a toy on the wanted list?!
...into action!
And Bartolomeo?!
Flame Commandment!
And he's very arrogant for a toy!
Fire Pillar!
Hey, what's wrong?!
This is Maynard.
Th-The nobleman is so...
They say he could smash through a warship
with his Fire Fist
Excuse me for hanging up earlier.
You're Bartolomeo, aren't you?
Oh, elderly people!
Do you want me to carry your bag or something?
Nobleman?!
All of the female staff are fainting.
Everything is okay here.
and could burn down a town,
turning it into hell!
Block B's match will start soon!
What?!
Oh, and earlier, I mentioned a name -
"The Missionary" Gambia...
Huh? He became polite all of a sudden.
Okay.
And did you see a competitor named Capman?
No, I can't take it anymore!
That tremendous power is now
reproduced as a Devil Fruit!
...who works under Bartolomeo.
No. 0429 - CAPMAN
What a funny toy soldier!
But you can cross it out.
Oh?
Am I funny?
It wasn't him that I saw after all.
--R-Reproduced?!
--For real?!
I don't think so.
What about this? Or this?
D-Damn! That Navy soldier...
Look!
Look, that's Cavendish!
Hey buddy, get out of our way.
The Pirate Noble?! Is he alive?!
The winner will get this forbidden fruit!
A VICE ADMIRAL OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
"MAYNARD THE PURSUER"
I'll keep going on with the plan here, too.
Oh, I was in your way. I'm sorry!
I can't believe how beautiful he is!
Can I watch it with you, Lucy?
It's Logia, the most powerful
type of Devil Fruit!
You're blushing so much!
Of course, you can!
You're a serious guy, aren't you?
This is the dressing room, huh?
Now, the next competitor to enter is...
N-No way!
--No way!
--That's...
Hey you, right there.
a latecomer!
He's in Block B, too!
Toys have to make people smile!
There is no such a thing as a serious toy!
It's the Flare-Flare Fruit!
That's no good.
It only took him a year to become infamous
and enter the New World!
There is a weight limit for gear.
LUCY - A GLADIATOR
The medical room is that way!
--Wow!
--I can't believe it!
He took it personally!
We don't have enough stretchers.
Walk by yourself if you can!
We're closing entries from the public
for today's competition!
Huh? Is that so?
An incomparably brutal and crazy rookie!
They got beaten badly by the champion.
But it's so cool...
He roasted some pirates on a skewer
and shared the video!
Well, whatever you do,
there is no chance for you.
I don't think anyone from the public wants to enter.
They're all cowards!
And he also bombed some innocent civilians!
Hey Luffy!
I guess we have to go in separately.
I will win the Flare-Flare Fruit.
He ranked No.1 in the "most annoying pirate
who should just go away" competition!
Hey.
Okay.
Oh, here, here! I want to enter!
I'm not blind.
Is it a real one?
A pirate -
Enter! Enter! Enter! Enter!
Young Master-sama won't lie about this!
No matter how you disguise yourself,
Bartolomeo!
Yes! That beautiful power belongs only to me.
I can't help recognizing the face of the guy...
What?
What?!
No, you don't! You're too old!
All of you!
Ace's...
Go to hell!
...who put a blot on my record!
...Flare-Flare Fruit?!
You!