Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
koukishin ni makasete
Go along with your curiosity
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
kokoro no chizu hirogete
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law.
Planning to hand over Caesar,
who they caught in Punk Hazard,
and to destroy the factory
producing the deadly weapon - SMILE,
they came to Dressrosa -
the kingdom that Doflamingo rules.
Ace's...
...Flare-Flare Fruit?!
"A Dangerous Love!
The Dancer Girl - Violet!"
The champion will get a Devil Fruit?!
On top of that, it's none other than "Fire-Fist" Ace's
Flare-Flare Fruit?!
Today, here in this Colosseum,
we have tough fighters from the New World
who were summoned by our king
and brave participants from the public
who are confident of their ability.
They will be divided into separate blocks
and the winners of each block
will get to go to the next round.
However, they can't have this valuable prize
so easily!
It's theirs for the taking - if they can!
The gladiators that they're gonna fight
are not the ordinary bunch!
The ones who are gonna fight
the winners of each block are...
From the Don Quixote Family...
Señor Pink!
Dellinger!
Lao G.!
Machvise!
And the hero of the Colosseum...
Mr. Diamante!
--Diamante-sama!
--Diamante!
Just start already!
We wanna see a fight!
Can't wait any longer!
Just start a match already!
How did Ace's Flare-Flare Fruit get here?!
Huh?!
I heard there are no two
Devil Fruits of the same
power existing at once.
However,
when a Devil Fruit eater dies,
a Devil Fruit with the power that
the deceased possessed will pop
up again somewhere in the world.
And when somebody eats it,
he'll become the new holder of that power.
After "Fire-Fist" Ace died,
the Flare-Flare Fruit was,
without anyone knowing, reproduced
and the Young Master-sama got hold of it!
That bastard!
I can't believe the Young Master-sama
made the Logia type Devil Fruit
a prize for the competition!
If I can possess such incredible power,
my life will change!
I'm not gonna let you eat it!
Now I remember. Ace was your...
I want it! The Flare-Flare Fruit!
Oh yeah! Why don't you eat it, Franky?
I don't wanna lose my ability to swim.
I ate the Gum-Gum Fruit so
I can't eat another one.
But I don't want some stranger
to possess Ace's power.
It's like a memento of him to you, isn't it?
It's possible that it's a trap
considering the way
Doflamingo dangled it in front of you.
I have something that you'll
want very badly now.
But one thing is for sure!
You shouldn't let the chance slip by!
You don't wanna regret it afterward.
We have to go to the Colosseum anyway.
Let's just go there!
Uh-huh!
Idiots!
If you think you can have it just because
you want it, no one would
be risking their life.
Don't underestimate the
level of the competitors.
THE GROUP THAT WENT AFTER
THE MYSTERIOUS FAIRY
They call it a fairy?!
It's just a dirty thief!
Where did it go?
This way!
I said "Wait"!
Just give up a sword or two!
No way, idiot!
Damn!
I won't let it get away!
Stop striking off on your own!
We don't have that much time!
Oh, that's...
Did you find the fairy?!
A fairy...
No, she must be a goddess.
What?!
A DANCER - VIOLET
--How fascinating!
--How intense!
You're the best dancer in the world!
Huh?
S...
She's beautiful!
You heard that women in this country stab men,
didn't you?
A guy like you will get stabbed.
I don't mind getting stabbed!
Oh no! I lost him!
That stray Moss Head!
Aha!
This is a good chance.
Let's leave him on this island!
I tried as best as I could to catch him.
I made a sincere effort!
There are so many couples around here!
I'm jealous!
I wish Nami-san and Robin-chan suddenly
became attracted to me!
Excuse me!
We caught each other's eye earlier,
didn't we?
Please! Hold me!
What?!
Where did she go?!
She must've slipped out the back door
to this Lover's Alley!
I don't think she went that far yet!
--We can't let her leave the town!
--Yes, sir!
Thank you! They're gone now.
Excuse me. You can let go of me now.
Well... It's really my pleasure!
I'm sorry! Did you hit
your head or something?
No, it's just meeting you
comes as a shock to me!
But you're bleeding a lot!
No, it's nothing...
It must hurt.
No! I can't help falling in love!
What?! No, you shouldn't
look at me like that!
I have already given up on love!
All the men who have gotten
involved with me are…
Yes!
They were all happy!
They were looking for you! Who were they?!
Tell me if there's something
I can do to help!
They were the police.
There was this man and I...
...stabbed him after things went sour.
What?!
So it's true that women in this
country are so passionate about
love that they'd stab a man for it!
--Okay!
--Okay?! Really?!
What's wrong now?!
No! Don't be so nice to a bad woman like me!
What?
Or I will... fall for you.
BANG!!
My name is Violet.
Could you escort me to the next town
if you don't mind?
The next town?
And...
...I want you to kill someone!
What?
I don't care if it's a
national treasure or not!
I can't allow myself to lose the Shusui!
Boy! First, we saw toys living side-by-side
with humans
and now, a thieving fairy?!
Damn! What an annoying island!
It was fairies who took your stuff.
What are you talking about?!
We have to turn a blind
eye to whatever they do.
If it was a fairy or not,
I'm gonna catch it and...
Well, I'm gonna chop it up
to get the sword back!
Wait! You thief-fairy!
"Dear Nami-san and Robin-chan."
"I hope you will forgive this sinful man."
"I finally... finally...
...met the love of my life!"
I'm your bodyguard.
Yes. I was born to protect you!
I love this romantic island - Dressrosa!
I will get the national treasure of the Wano Kingdom
back for sure!
But first, I have to rescue Kanjuro
who is held captive by Doflamingo's clan!
Kanjuro!
Why are you rushing?!
Wh-What was that?!
She was trying to show her
affection for me apparently!
How aggressive! But...
Come stop by for a while!
I-I shouldn't allow myself!
Yielding to a young lady's temptation is...
...a dishonor to a warrior!
Where are you?! Kanjuro!
I'm coming in!
Mister, you can't just come in.
We're closed now!
They have some stuff to cook.
But the knives and frying
pans are not well maintained.
They haven't even washed their dishes.
These are the guys. No wonder.
Who do you think you are?!
I'm gonna cook for
the most wonderful lady in the world.
Get out of this kitchen!
Don't mess with us cooks!
Wh-Who is he?
You shouldn't mess with a cook.
Let me use this kitchen for a while.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting, Violet-chan!
I think dancing requires stamina.
Enjoy this tasty and nutritious special dish!
Are you...
Wait!
You thief-fairy!
Moss Head?!
Where are you?!
Kanjuro!
Kin'emon!
Is there something wrong?
Oh no. Not at all.
I wasn't planning to go off on my own.
Forgive me, Luffy.
Because it's destiny!
THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
Is this...
It's a huge Colosseum!
What kind of competition is it gonna be?!
The people are going nuts!
That makes me wanna enter the competition!
They're going crazy!
He's making it harder for us!
Just give up already!
You infamous wanted toy soldier!
You can't shoot me!
Jet Walk!
You guys are too slow! Look!
I have my foot in the Colosseum!
THE ONE-LEGGED SOLDIER
AKA THE ANGRY LIGHTNING SOLDIER
You know the law, don't you?!
The police and the Navy are not allowed
in the Colosseum!
Even if a criminal is in the Colosseum,
it's not your jurisdiction!
The only rule of law in here
is that of the Don Quixote Family!
If you pull that trigger,
you will become a criminal yourself!
Go away!
Damn!
This island is so strange.
They put a toy on the wanted list?!
And he's very arrogant for a toy!
Oh, elderly people!
Do you want me to carry your bag or something?
Huh? He became polite all of a sudden.
What a funny toy soldier!
Oh?
Am I funny?
What about this? Or this?
Hey buddy, get out of our way.
Oh, I was in your way. I'm sorry!
You're blushing so much!
You're a serious guy, aren't you?
N-No way!
Toys have to make people smile!
There is no such a thing as a serious toy!
He took it personally!
We're closing entries from the public
for today's competition!
I don't think anyone from the public wants to enter.
They're all cowards!
Hey Luffy!
I guess we have to go in separately.
Okay.
Oh, here, here! I want to enter!
Enter! Enter! Enter! Enter!
What?
What?!
No, you don't! You're too old!