Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the
prize for a fighting event
When Luffy found out that
the prize for a fighting
was the Flare-Flare Fruit, he decided to enter.
event was the Flare-Flare
Fruit, he decided to enter.
was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
he decided to enter.
event was the Flare-Flare
Fruit, he decided to enter.
The first round is a battle royal
where only one can win.
Burgess from the Blackbeard Pirates won
the match of Block A.
Meanwhile, after falling in
love with Violet, Sanji made a
The first round is a battle royal
where only one can win.
Burgess from the Blackbeard Pirates won
the match of Block A.
raid on an unknown villain's hide-out
Now, the battle of Block B has begun.
Burgess from the Blackbeard Pirates won
the match of Block A.
to grant her wish. However...
Now, the battle of Block B has begun.
Can I ask you a favor?
Meanwhile, Law and the others are...
Now, the battle of Block B is about to start.
Now, the battle of Block B has begun.
Let the battle...
Hey, Tra-guy!
Huh?
Straw Hat.
Competitors led by Dagama, the tactician,
are protecting Elizabello II,
Then will you...
You have to change the handing-over spot now!
I visited the Sky Island.
I'm not gonna change.
...begin!
...die for me, "Black Foot" Sanji?
the king of Prodence Kingdom!
We're already here. Stop making a fuss.
I lost my crew but it turned my
view of the world upside down.
When is he going to throw
the devastating King Punch?!
More importantly,
What? V-Violet-chan?
What are you talking about?
I'm worried about the situation of this country.
You didn't do anything to the people there,
did you?!
Their king quit all of a sudden.
Oh shit! I'm gonna fall!
What an idiot.
How come they are so calm?
A school of Little Fighting Fish!
Bellamy!
At the same time, Usopp and the others are
"Atrocious"! "Evil"!
Maybe. Maybe not.
We're in unexpected circumstances already.
heading to Green Bit to hand Caesar over.
Anyway, I'm not holding a grudge
against you anymore.
Those are the words only fitting to this man!
That's what worries me!
King...
Is he the top contender
to beat Elizabello II after all?!
I'm gonna get on board Doflamingo's ship
It stopped.
...Punch!
--We caught it!
--Alright, let's pull it in!
to ride through the "wild wave"
that will come soon or later.
In the meantime,
the Jiaokungdo martial artist - Blue Gilly
A very wild forest?!
I'm done picking on you.
Barrier!
I'm a barrier human who ate
the Barrier-Barrier Fruit!
and the mysterious gladiator - Ricky,
Oh, is this the place to watch the battle?
Can I watch it with you, Lucy?
the two strong men are fighting each other!
Barrier Crash!
Of course, you can!
You're...
4000 Brick...
"Explore!
Fairies' Island - Green Bit!"
How is Garp-san doing?
Now, the next competitor to enter is...
The winner of Block B is...
Straw Hat Luffy-kun!
...a latecomer!
He's in Block B, too!
...Fist!
You know my grandpa?
Dammit!
Th-This is...
...Bartolomeo!
What?!
It only took him a year to become infamous
...Green Bit?!
I almost got killed by Garp-san once.
What are those giant plants?!
and enter the New World!
Just kidding!
"The Fighting Fish Strike!
Across the Deadly Iron Bridge!"
An incomparably brutal and crazy rookie!
And I've made up my mind to carry the grudge
even against his children and grandchildren.
He roasted some pirates on a skewer
and shared the video!
What did he do?!
Hack is the one who collapsed!
And he also bombed some innocent civilians!
What was that?
Wh-What kind of monster are you?!
He ranked No.1 in the "most
annoying pirate who should
I can't believe it!
Bartolomeo!
just go away" competition!
Hey, Joker, it's me! Pick me up!
Now it's clear, the battle of
A pirate -
"Big Names Duke It Out!
The Heated Block B Battle!"
Bartolomeo!
Block B ended with Bartolomeo as its winner!
Don't be in such a rush.
"A Deadly Blow!
The Astonishing King Punch!"
That is the beach on
the southeast side of the island.
Garp was like a real demon
for us pirates back then.
"A Super Rookie!
Bartolomeo the Cannibal!"
We will leave you there
at three in the afternoon.
It's been decades now
but my wound hasn't healed.
That strange guy won after all.
He will come soon.
Now...
Look at the beach on the other side!
Isn't that a Navy ship?!
The giant old pops and Cabbage are gone.
Hey, is it true?!
Hack got defeated!
It got stuck on the island!
It's not just beached!
No, no, no... I just misheard it! I'm Lucy!
I better run now!
He couldn't even reach Bartolomeo!
You don't mishear your own name!
How is it possible?!
All of you!
What did Bartolomeo do to him?!
Go to hell!
I need you to pay for
what your grandfather did to me.
Damn! I was rooting for Hack!
That chicken head!
Those cuts on the plants look fresh.
--Move!
--You're in our way!
What my grandpa did is none of my business!
What?
What did you say, you asshole?!
Gyats-san, you have to be fair!
I estimate that ship arrived recently.
So you are Garp's grandson!
Relax!
Go home!
No, I'm not!
You go to hell!
We can't see a clear winner yet!
If you're the real Straw Hat Luffy,
Its body is not as damaged as I thought.
Bellamy?
B Block - 24 competitors remain.
Don't throw stuff!
Please don't throw stuff!
Did they make it through
the water filled with the Fighting Fish?!
I'm gonna chop you up now!
It's gonna be over soon, huh?
If I had found out about the existence of
Garp's son Dragon sooner,
He looks like something.
It's only a matter of time
before the Navy soldiers get here.
You...
Hm? What?
Bellamy.
Everybody's got a wound or two now!
What?!
Do they know about the trade-off?!
Why did you cheer me on?
It's about time!
you would have never been born.
I didn't know that!
Oh? Why is everyone so angry?
You stupid scientist, you're too loud!
Shh! Shh!
That was so embarrassing!
Because of him.
I haven't changed a bit.
THE CAPTAIN OF A PIRATE
GROUP - THE BARTO CLUB
Hey, I'm a wanted person!
He's the captain of a pirate
group called Barto Club -
You've changed, Bellamy.
BARTOLOMEO THE CANNIBAL
BOUNTY: 150 MILLION BERRIES
Bartolomeo the Cannibal!
Since my boss - Joker resigned
from the Warlords,
Hey, what happened?!
Don Chinjao is going crazy!
Go away!
there isn't any law that protects me!
Powerful competitors are getting eliminated
one after another!
That's not good!
If you leave me with handcuffs on
on the island where the Navy
soldiers are wandering, I'll...
Following Hack's defeat,
the unknown gladiator,
No, you have changed.
Hey, wait a minute, old pops!
Ricky, also got taken down!
You now use Haki that's far greater
than anyone can imagine.
I said "Shh! Be quiet!"
Blue Gilly is strong!
Take that beard off!
Wait a minute! Joker is
just a pirate now, too!
That pisses me off!
Stop! No! Let go of me! Let go!
--Blue Gilly-sama!
--So cool!
My pride has been broken to pieces!
Either way, I'm doomed!
What are you doing, you bastard?!
What do you think you can cut
You've got to be kidding!
Is he gonna attack again?!
with such a blunt sword, old man?
This is hell!
Straw Hat!
Enough, you idiot!
We're all screwed if the Navy finds us!
I don't know how much weaker he's become
but his bounty was more than 500 million berries
at his peak!
What is that?
I guess I can't fight aging.
Why is the Navy here?
S... S... S... S...
I'm Lu...
What?
Don't tell me it's...
You look like you're hiding something.
I can't stand all this cheering.
S...
It's just a coincidence.
It's a bomb!
Damn you Don Chinjao! Back off!
I can't stand you, Doflamingo!
How could I control the Navy?
Straw Hat?!
He's my enemy!
By the way,
It's packed and I can't get out!
I'm thinking about going to Green Bit.
Move aside, old man! You're too slow!
Cavendish drew his sword!
45 MINUTES BEFORE THE HANDOVER
I wonder if I can handle the Straw Hats.
You're in my way, too!
Is that it?!
You have to let ladies go first!
Let me out!
One of the greatest swords
in the world - Durandal!
CAESAR HANDOVER TEAM
Forget the others, just help me!
I'll give you my money!
There aren't that many men left
thanks to Dagama's tactics!
Yeah.
It's not fair to hand me over here!
Abort this mission!
Wow... It's a very solid-looking bridge.
Here it goes! Head-Arms!
Most of the competitors are gone
except for us.
Beautiful Sword!
The Navy is my enemy, too,
It's landing!
Can't believe I'm still here.
I'm glad that I allied with them!
Blue Bird!
We'll be okay if that Fighting Fish thing
since I'm allied with the Straw Hats.
Me, too!
attacks us on this, won't we?
When Dagama gives us the cue,
we'll disband.
Don't tell me you set me up!
It's piercing his skull...
I hope so.
No, it isn't!
Then we'll fight amongst ourselves
until one of us wins.
We still have 15 minutes before they come.
Let's take down as many
enemies as possible for now!
Everyone, cover me with
sniping and surveillance.
It's coming.
They're pushing against each other!
--Huh?!
--What's coming?
I know!
They may be hiding.
Go check the forest.
I can't stab him with Durandal!
A skull impervious to a sword!
The power to push back a giant!
Hey hey, don't tell me
you're talking about...
If you find something,
let me know as soon as possible.
Okay, I got it.
They're both beyond human power!
Blue Gilly!
Wait a minute!
We didn't expect the Navy to be here so...
Here he comes!
A ball...
Guys! Take care of Blue Gilly
while we're fighting together!
Gross.
Okay!
Oh? What is that noise?!
Gross!
Hey, look!
It...
Gross!
It's here!
I can't take him down without going all out!
R-Robin!
Dagama?!
You bastard!
They hate you so much, brat.
This forest is dangerous! Wait!
You did a fine job, you stupid dogs!
It...
I don't even want those shitheads to like me.
It showed itself!
I said "Stop"!
Let's not get separated!
Why?
Hey, you haven't given us the cue!
Thank you for being so manly, Usopp.
He's smiling. That guy's so weird.
Don't tell me he... Hey, Dagama!
You're too loud!
He's not just a menace
but he also has an insolent manner.
He knocked down Chinjao!
Oh no!
Who is that little bearded guy?!
I thought a Fighting Fish would be a fish.
Please don't leave me!
Unlike me, he has a bad reputation.
You two!
It is a fish.
Sorry! I've been told to hunt you dogs!
You can't call that a fish!
It's no different from a sea monster!
Can you walk a little more slowly?
Damn Bartolomeo,
how dare he make fools of us!
Were you plotting together?
It's a beast!
Ouch! Don't stop suddenly, Robin...
To get rid of us from the beginning?
But there is another competitor for Block B!
Oh my...
Who is it?! The Straw Hats?!
It's coming again!
Wow! It didn't work against him!
He's the last one!
There is more than one!
He's nothing like that Crazy-lomeo!
They found us!
I will pay you later!
Your job is done now!
Shh.
Maybe the legend about him is true!
There are a bunch of them!
They say he broke up the Ice Continent
with a head-butt!
The guy said they reinforced the bridge
Dagama!
with iron to protect it from them!
He admires our king - Doflamingo
Where?! Where are they?!
The Ice Continent?!
I-It's going to be alright, isn't it?!
Just surrender without resistance!
It didn't work at all.
I thought I used enough strength.
Warriors who can't use their brains
and declared his loyalty to him
We know you're here on the island!
just end up as someone's
puppets on a battlefield!
by bringing him a giant gold
pillar from a distant country!
Damn! Come on out, Straw Hats!
I'll be counting on you, Longfeet man!
The bridge is a piece of crap!
Now you turned your back to me,
you're dead, too.
That's not my name! I'm Leo!
Oh, don't tell me it's...
Oh my...
Blue Gilly.
Who is it?! Where is he?!
Since then, he's been
destroying various towns
It seems like you two are quite strong!
We of the Prodence Kingdom
Can we make it to Green Bit like this?!
It's the Navy soldiers.
Who are they talking to?
will win the Flare-Flare Fruit
at any cost!
in many countries where they insulted us...
We're gonna be okay.
But you guys need more training!
Looks like they knew
we were coming to this island.
...by calling us a barbaric kingdom of pirates,
and bringing them to terms!
They can take care of them.
You handle it, Warlord!
What?!
Seeing how strong you are...
I'm now sure you're Straw Hat.
Are you good people or bad people?!
He is the "Bullet of Dressrosa"!
I can't fight now.
He has been given a chance
by the royal finally!
You betrayed me, Blue Gilly!
We're Navy soldiers! We protect citizens.
What do you want from me?
Leave me alone!
Here it comes!
Being born as a grandson of the demon
We're definitely good people!
Dagama the tactician got eliminated!
Special Attack - Green Star...
and stealing other people's popularity -
Then, hand over your weapons!
you really incur everybody's hatred.
Here comes a leading competitor of Block B.
Neither of those things are my fault!
Another one from the opposite side!
You can't have our weapons!
We have work to do!
--Way to go, Longfeet guy!
--Blue Gilly-sama!
They're gonna crush us!
I'm Lucy, by the way.
Mil Fleurs!
--Hey, who are you?!
--Show yourself!
If he wins this competition,
Gigantesco Mano!
If you keep standing in my way,
I'm gonna kill you, too, young knight!
I can't believe people would trust a
Spank!
dubious guy like him
in the first place.
his tenacity will bear fruit
and it has been decided that
he will get promoted to
Skull Bombgrass!
So that is your answer.
Where are you?!
an executive position in
the Don Quixote Family!
Hey, where is your cape?!
Wait, wait, old man! That's enough!
He is a real contender for
winning this competition!
Oh? On the other hand...
My gun!
If you cause trouble here,
they'll eliminate you!
A pirate!
Oh?!
You're doing great!
--Go, Bellamy!
--Kick his ass!
What was that?!
Bellamy the Hyena!
No, we're not!
Can't you see how many there are?!
It's Sai and Boo from the Kano Kingdom!
Our man - Bellamy is beginning to attack!
My hat!
It's a school!
Oh no!
Let's just run!
It'll take forever to fight them all!
Let go of me, my dear grandsons!
--Bellamy!
His target is the "most annoying pirate
who should just go away"!
No! I don't know what's going on
but you got to stop!
Bellamy!
Skull Bombgrass!
Huh?! What's going on?!
I finally found my sworn
enemy - Garp's grandson!
Bartolomeo!
I can't see. It's too fast.
Nose-ya, uncuff Caesar!
I want him to fight, too!
If we get eliminated here,
Huh? Me?
we can't fulfill the real purpose
that we entered for, grandpa!
Just go away already!
--What is this forest?!
--Dammit!
What are you saying?!
He's gonna fly away then!
We got stripped of all we have!
Hey, you guys!
What's going on over there?!
That will teach you!
You villainous Big Humans!
He wouldn't dare make a move like that.
We'll have to ask you to leave
if you're fighting outside of the ring!
Yeah!
Now, all 138 competitors are in the ring!
What?
Don't tell me it's...
The guards are coming.
My heart!
Mil Fleurs! Campo de Flores!
I don't care if I get eliminated here or not!
I'm going to...
What?!
He can't be that popular
even if this is his home.
You won't die a peaceful death...
Where did he go?!
Bellamy who went in for the attack
is down on the floor?!
I caught one!
Huh?! What did you catch?!
...after pushing around a
great scientist like me!
There are so many!
Old man, the guy with the fake beard
I think it's a little person!
What did Bartolomeo do?!
They're gonna fight at once, aren't they?
What?!
is in Block C so are we!
Gastille!
Help me!
Where should I look?
Kabu-san!
It sure is a battle royal
but this is just a preliminary round.
We have a problem!
Bellamy delivered an attack
and got hurt like Hack!
If you wanna kill him, do it in the match!
Oh, that's so powerful!
Let go of me!
I'm not gonna let you get away, Straw Hat!
There is no chance for the weak to win.
Only a criminal with a 300 million
berry bounty could do that!
What did he do to him?
Gastille!
I'm gonna kill you before the match!
I thought so!
I got caught!
You can just focus on the big names.
What did he just do?
DRESSROSA - THE PORT TOWN "ACACIA"
Run!
Do you want me to tell you
who I think has a chance?
What a mess. What was that all about?
Like I said, why aren't you fighting?!
Yeah, don't just make me fight all of them!
Ah, please!
Damn it all!
I heard someone said "Straw Hat."
It reminds me of the
pirate - Straw Hat Luffy.
The king of the Prodence Kingdom.
I shouldn't be...
It takes so much energy to use my ability.
Turn right! I said "Right"!
"The Fighting King" - Elizabello II!
Do you think he entered this competition?
...struggling like this right here!
No way!
And I have to be at my best on our way back!
Why did you turn left?!
Boy...
Do you understand?!
I promised Franky that
I wouldn't let anybody know who I am!
Shut up! Be quiet! You're distracting me!
And his tactician.
I want to keep my strength up
as much as possible!
Because our enemy is Doflamingo!
Dagama!
What the...
Mom, he's talking to himself...
There are about 70 competitors
left in the ring now!
A Jiaokungdo martial artist
from the Longfeet Tribe.
Law... Is he really going
to fight against Joker?!
Don't look him in the eye!
Already half of the competitors are gone!
Blue Gilly!
Go, Bellamy!
I'm in hurry!
We are coming to the moment of truth!
The Military Captain of
Dressrosa's Self-Defense Army.
Spring...
Not as much as I am!
Oh no! What should we do?!
...Death Knock!
If I can't make it, it's your fault!
Tank Lepant!
The bridge is collapsed.
A criminal - Abdullah!
Get to the Flower Field already!
On top of that, I can't see the other
side clearly because of the fog!
All right! Just shut up!
Another criminal - Jeet!
A master of the Fish-Man Karate
A Fighting Fish is coming towards us!
Hack, the master of the Fish-Man Karate,
and a martial artist of the Fish-Man Jiu-Jitsu.
Damn! I can't let it destroy
anymore of the bridge!
Give me back my sword!
has taken down his 17th opponent!
Hack!
Lastly, the pirates - Bellamy and...
What?
Roo...
Hey you stupid Fish-Man!
...Bartolomeo.
Why are you participating in
a human competition, freak?!
One of them will win this match, I suppose.
Oh no!
Hmmm...
Can you repeat that?
Ow, ow, ow... This is no good!
Say something! Hey, fish!
I-I can't believe it!
It stopped.
What the hell?
Our man - Bellamy is worn out!
Alright, the battle royal of Block B
is about to begin!
I'm so dumb! This human will see me!
Poor man.
Huh?!
I can't hear you!
I have to run! Otherwise, the human will...
What kind of Devil Fruit did he eat?!
You're like a puppet
who can't speak in words of its own.
Let's "communicate" with our fists at least!
--We caught it!
--Alright, let's pull it in!
Bellamy! You can do it!
That's a good idea!
We had a decisive battle today!
A competitor will be eliminated
if he gets killed in the ring!
Let's eat Fighting Fish stew
to boost up our energy!
I'm gonna smash your annoying fists!
Bellamy...
Or if he gets thrown out of the ring!
Yeah!
I've no interest in the Flare-Flare Fruit
Excuse me.
Who's voice is that?
but I have my own reason to win this thing!
There will be only one winner!
Who are you?!
Residents of the island?
I'm gonna get on board Doflamingo's
ship to ride through the
I thought it was a deserted island.
Oh? It got stuck!
"wild wave" that will come sooner or later.
I'm so dumb!
Hey! Who is over there on the other side?!
So dumb and stupid and blockheaded!
Let the battle...
I always knew I'd fail like this!
I'm done picking on you.
We want to cross the bridge!
Is this what they call a fairy?
Oh no! It's a human!
Is it a toy?
4000 Brick Fist!
Hurry up! Run!
WICKA - A MEMBER OF THE SCOUTING UNIT OF
THE TONTATTA (A TRIBE OF LITTLE PEOPLE)
I'm not a toy!
...begin!
Hey, Bellamy! Don't give up!
I'm Wicka from the Tontatta Tribe!
Please don't tell anybody that you saw me!
Now what are you gonna do, Elizabello?
I beg you!
I don't know what's going on here.
Nothing is more helpless than a king
without his court.
That was awesome, Hack!
He beat his 18th opponent!
Now, who should I start with?
I don't have time for this!
Bellamy!
What was that all about?
Like my friend and our
species' hope, Jimbei, does,
Anyway, let's keep moving!
Five men at once, already?
we can establish friendly relations
with our fists!
Huh?
Guys! Enough already!
I wasn't gonna eat you or anything.
Hence, I'm gonna keep fighting!
Tell me what's going on.
Spring Hopper!
I-I can't do that!
Caesar!
Cool! Was that the famous Fish-Man Karate?!
What?
I can't share any information
with you Big Humans!
Fly us to the island.
Everybody was dying to kill you.
And this man is runner-up!
I'm sorry! I gotta go!
Law, you bastard!
I'll get even with you, I mean it!
An unknown gladiator who burst
into prominence - Ricky!
All the people who had been guarding you
Wow, what a view! What a lovely view!
have turned against you.
What now?!
He may be the one everyone should
keep an eye on in Block B!
I can't walk!
I think I twisted my ankle earlier!
We should have flown ourselves
like this from the beginning.
He did it! He cut down his 16th man!
Oh, you're right!
I'm so dumb, dumb, dumb, dumb, dumb, dumb...
H-How strong?
Cut that crap!
He's so great!
How much gas energy do you think
you need to fly three people?!
--Hey!
--Huh?
You're pretty strong!
You're smashing the ground.
There is a gladiator who
I've never seen before.
I'm an important hostage for you!
What are you saying?!
We're in the middle of a fight!
Please!
Take me to my commander!
Look! That's the guy!
He's quite strong. Do you know him?
When you come right down to it,
it's kind of your fault.
THE DESERTED ISLAND NORTH OF DRESSROSA
You stole my sword!
I've been fighting here as
a gladiator for a long time
"Stole"? What are you talking about?
but I've never seen him before!
We manage the greenery of this land!
What's the matter?
Gladiators of this Colosseum
You can't do anything
without Dagama, can you?
The drag marks from the fish end there.
The Big Humans of this kingdom call us "fairies"
and give us things!
are trained to fight
with a sword and a shield!
But he just uses a sword!
Like a samurai from the Wano Kingdom!
Nobody is here yet.
"Give"? No, you're stealing them!
Let's test his skill!\
Okay!
What was that about?
I said too much again!
Shipwrecks from Fighting Fish attacks
I have to go!
I'm a member of a scouting unit!
are filling up the water around here.
Dagama did a great job.
I have to report the Don Quixote Family's
I'm all set now.
Too slow!
whereabouts to my commander!
All I need to do is throw it!
What's that?!
Bellamy!
Now is our chance!
I saw the Don Quixote Family on their way
You guys are the ones who were protected
Now, Ricky beat the same
number of men as Hack!
while we were in that battle formation.
to attack the Straw Hats' ship!
Did you just see what the gladiator
with a skull on his cape did?
Because nothing is more dangerous
than an exposed blade.
What?!
Yeah.
He's that strong but I don't
remember seeing him here before.
Don't you think so, you punk?
Well, I was gonna say...
I think I've seen him before.
Hey, I just thought of something.
What?
A man who fought like that without a shield.
There was a report about
the king of Prodence.
What was his name?
They said he destroyed an
I have to go!
I'm a member of a scouting unit!
enemy country's fort
with a single punch.
I have to report the Don Quixote Family's
No way! He must've used some kind of weapon.
whereabouts to my commander!
No, they say it could take down
even the Four Emperors!
Now is our chance!
What is this place?!
I saw the Don Quixote Family on their way
What the hell? It's like an army!
What?
If it's true, he's gonna throw a punch that
That's not fair! They're teaming up!
to attack the Straw Hats' ship!
What?!
That's not a battle royal!
will destroy this part of the Colosseum!
I'm so dumb! I told him everything!
What?!
No way! That can't be true!
GREEN BIT
You can call us cowards
as you like after you die!
Hey, is that true?!
I'm a member of the Straw Hats!
A very wild forest?!
I've heard the same thing!
No! He can't throw such a destructive punch
at a place like this!
Abdullah!
There will be only one winner!
All we need is to win!
Dumb! So dumb!
Take this!
Dumb! I'm so dumb! Dumb!
I'm a blockhead!
Looks like we have some competitors
who are fighting together!
Whoa-whoa!
There is a restlessness in the air!
The king who kept quiet
Stop wrecking the town!
Is that allowed?
in the battle formation is
now on the move!
Calm down, fairy!
It's not sportsmanlike
but it's not against the rules, I think.
Is it true that the
Don Quixote Family is going to
attack the Sunny?!
The man behind such a trick must be...
Jeet!
We of the Prodence Kingdom will win
the Flare-Flare Fruit!
It's a secret! But I saw it!
...Dagama, a tactician
of the Prodence Kingdom.
Oh, I did it again!
Now, the battle of Block C!
I don't have a Transponder Snail.
We the Prodence Kingdom will take home
the Flare-Flare Fruit.
The battle will commence shortly
after they finish fixing the ring!
You're showing your back to me!
There's no way to tell them about it.
Of all the others,
All competitors of Block C,
please go to the entrance gate!
I can't believe they're attacking those four.
Our king - Elizabello II was born to be
a weapon of destruction!
Oh, it's about time, huh?
You cowards!
Alright, I'm gonna head back to the Sunny!
I repeat! All competitors of Block C,
please go to the entrance gate!
I can't believe it!
Wait!
Jeet and Abdullah, a pair of evils,
beat 10 strong men at once!
Take me to the Flower Field first!
A punch that is thrown
from his naturally gifted
Hey!
physique is terribly powerful...
I'll guide you to the sea right after that!
Alright! I'm ready to go!
Hey, are you listening?
What do you wanna talk about?
No, I'm gonna head to the sea now!
Now let me introduce
Like I said, in order to
destroy the SMILE factory,
the competitors who everyone
should keep an eye on!
But...
"Cowards"?
I gotta beat up someone in the Doflamingo...
He is the two-time champion of
the New World Central Fighting Tournament!
...you're running in the opposite direction!
I like the sound of that!
Halt.
Let's kick that guy's ass next!
You don't know which way to go, do you?!
"Destruction Cannon" Ideo!
Alright!
What?
He went over to Elizabello's
side, huh? Great!
So...
I'm busy! I've got work to do!
...Don Quixote's people were
following our movements.
They are savage assassins
who are able to kill pirates
with more than a 100 million bounty!
I'm sorry but I have no time for this.
Yes. And we were keeping an eye on them.
The Funk Brothers!
Now, Blue Gilly is attacking
Elizabello II's clan!
If you have nothing to talk about, I'm gonna go now!
Bye!
You guys have some kind of
a conflict with him, too?!
He is from the famous
Giants' country - Elbaf!
He blew a hole
Yes! Oops!
in an enemy country's fort
with a single blow, shocking the world!
That was a secret.
Damn! It's not only the ship that's in danger
The most formidable "Pirate Mercenary"!
You...
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow... Damn that bastard!
However, his power has one drawback.
but all of us!
Hey, are we there yet? The Flower Field?!
You keep talking about this radical plan
Hajrudin!
It takes an hour to increase
What the hell are you doing?!
He's just an unarmed, spindly man!
Go up the stairs there!
concentration and warm up to throw one punch.
There are a lot more!
but why do you want to do such a thing?
I said "Go up"!
Known for his violence
I-It doesn't matter
whether he's unarmed or spindly!
which he uses in order to drive
his target into the corner!
He can only use it once per battle!
You seem like you know things
that ordinary people don't!
Are you a b-blockhead?
Jean the Bandit!
Shut up!
They say it could take
down even the Four Emperors
if it hits them. The "King Punch"!
What is your true purpose?
Who can stop this bull?!
His legs are like iron whips!
The Colosseum's Grim Reaper!
His victory depends on his timing!
My true purpose?
Brutal Bull!
Hey guys, come closer!
King-sama, how is the preparation going?
It's too boring when you're standing back like that!
Today's likely winner!
It's gonna take a while. Guard me.
The gang from the Kano Kingdom!
What's going on?
He's just a guy from the Longfeet Tribe!
As you wish!
Sai!
Why don't you try to attack his legs, then?!
Boo!
I need you guys to earn your salt!
And the legendary former
pirate - Don Chinjao!
Protect the king and
It's impossible!
We can't approach him!
Where did he hide? That coward!
Damn!
cut down the number of the
competitors in the ring!
Yeah!
Hey, that's Don Chinjao!
Straw Hat!
The king's punch that broke down a fort...
That movement!
You got to be kidding.
I can't figure out where his
kick is gonna come from!
There are also a lot more tough contenders!
I heard about it.
I want to hear the sound of the gong
They're trying to buy themselves some time
that signals the start of the match!
It's going to be an exciting match!
to throw the punch, aren't they?
Hey, I think we better run!
The punch! No way!
Damn! I don't care anymore!
The battle of Block C will
be a very fierce one!
Garp's grandson!
I'm gonna kick his ass before he throws it!
Get ready for it!
That sound signals your death!
Oh shit! I'm gonna fall!
Hey, we better run!
That's a hell of a kick!
A little while ago...
Three competitors got eliminated
by being thrown out of the ring!
This doesn't look good!
Prepare yourself!
Blue Gilly kicked some guys' ass again!
You've got to be kidding!
Whoa-whoa, we better go!
In the "next town" over in Dressrosa...
Run!
And of course,
in the water outside of the ring...
I think you can't protect your king
with such weak soldiers.
Control yourself, old man!
The Colosseum's unique attraction!
They'll eliminate you
if you fight outside of the ring again!
Maybe, he really did destroy the fort!
Don't forget what we are here for, grandpa!
Get them!
Let's go!
A school of Little Fighting Fish!
Looks like he has spirit.
I know.
Oh, in the meantime,
Abdullah and Tank are facing each other!
You're so persistent!
What's this?! Get it off of me!
Oh, that was scary.
No way! Don't underestimate
the power of my spring!
Doesn't matter if you're in
or out of the ring! It's Hell!
What's the matter?
This was a bad idea! Why don't you go back?!
No one can survive uninjured!
That old guy is such a pain in the butt.
Sanji-san, I must've been out of my mind!
That's the Corrida Colosseum!
How horrible I was to ask you such a thing!
King...
Is it okay, Lepant?
To ask you to kill that man!
I'm gonna kill Elizabello!
For the captain of Dressrosa's army to help
Outta my way!
How could I ask you such a thing?!
What the...
Shooting...
Everybody's naked before my eyes.
a tactician from another country?
Even though you're quite a strong man!
...Punch!
I've seen everything that's been
in your mind since we first met.
Bellamy, money controls this world!
I tried to use you.
They bought you off, huh?
Please! Just walk away!
Should I fight him, Dagama?
I-I can't believe it!
They're taking down Tank!
Yes, let's get rid of those
pains in the ass first
Don't get involved with me anymore!
before we lose too many people on our side.
I don't want you to die because of me!
The military captain of
Dressrosa's Self-Defense Army -
I heard you have a soft spot for women
Tank Lepant got eliminated!
Be ready for it, Bellamy!
but I didn't expect it to be that soft.
He fell a prey to the pair of evils -
Abdullah and Jeet!
I'd rather make easy money
than chase a big dream!
How pathetic!
Your collar is wrinkled up
and your tie is crooked.
You said the man is in that storage room,
didn't you, Violet-chan?
They keep using dirty tricks!
That makes my ears burn.
Your shirt is stained with blood.
Captain Tank!
I'm going in.
Over a 100 competitors have been eliminated
What?
You can't hit me like that!
You look terrible.
and there are only 30 some
men left in the ring!
Aren't you gonna ask me why?!
You're a good-for-nothing,
Spring...
"Black Foot" Sanji!
A little more to go.
Ask you why?
VIOLET - AN ASSASSIN OF
THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY (THE TREBOL ARMY)
Did you really think that
It doesn't matter how tough
the remaining one will be
a guy like you could win my heart?
What's going on in the Colosseum?
as long as we have the King Punch...
...Death Knock!
I mean, the reason I want you to kill him!
Competitors led by Dagama, the tactician,
How funny.
I don't need to hear that.
are protecting Elizabello II,
the king of Prodence Kingdom!
I can't believe you were
attracted by Sis' beauty,
Seeing your tears is good enough for me.
When is he going to throw
the devastating King Punch?!
you stupid jerk!
Sanji-san!
Didn't you know it was a trap?! You idiot!
How...
Wait for me!
Who's next?!
How powerful was that?!
Bellamy! Go for it!
You're lying, Violet-chan...
Those who wish to bleed, come fight us!
I'll take care of everything and be back!
I don't think anyone in the
ring could survive that!
Bellamy!
I'm your bodyguard!
The pair of evils - Abdullah and Jeet
Elizabello II wiped out all of his enemies...
Hey, quit dreaming already!
Sis was just acting!
It's not easy to beat him as I thought.
who took down the strong man - Lepant,
are trying to provoke their next victim!
...with a single punch!
I-I know you have a beautiful heart...
What a man!
He got so much stronger!
What the...
Who is it?!
What?!
How could you still say such a thing
after getting hurt so badly?
It's so exciting to see
so many different people!
Hey, stand up!
Why don't you have your last cigarette?
You must have been coaxed
into this by some bad guys.
I'll give you a few minutes to do that.
You don't even want to be here.
He's pretty strong, too!
That was a hell of a punch!
Bellamy!
Huh? Who the hell are you?
I've never seen something like that before!
Violet-chan...
Indeed.
Bellamy-sama!
Why don't you quit being so romantic?!
Bellamy! Blue Gilly!
Are you the asshole
who makes Violet-chan cry?
"Atrocious"! "Evil"!
And all other potential
winners have been eliminated!
Those are the words only fitting to this man!
What? So that woman asked you to do this?
The battle royal of Block B - 138
competitors - the winner is from
Is he the top contender to
beat Elizabello II after all?!
Poor Violet-chan...
the Prodence Kingdom...
She shouldn't be fooled by a crumb like him.
The gladiator - Ricky...
His background is a total mystery.
Hey, look! Somebody's there!
What?! Screw you!
You see? Right over there!
Guys!
Who do you think is gonna win?!
So stupid!
In the meantime,
the Jiaokungdo martial artist - Blue Gilly
The audience in that direction
didn't get blown away
How do I know?! It just got started!
--That's terrible! But she's beautiful!
Kill that son of a bitch!
because of his defense!
--That was a hell of a kick, Sis!
and the mysterious gladiator - Ricky,
--Look at him!
--What?!
You're trying to hold back
your anger against me
the two strong men are fighting each other!
What are you doing?!
Do you wanna get killed?!
Go away, small fry.
and looking for a way to run.
--What did you say?!
--Kill him!
Why isn't anybody attacking him?!
That Fish-Man is so tough!
Bartolomeo!
If you're not gonna fight, go home!
Do you think you can persuade me
with your lies?
He's been knocking out all of his
opponents with a single blow!
Oeil!
Flanchet!
I wish somebody would kick your ass already!
That's so cool!
Joue!
Barrier!
Poitrine!
I'm so excited!
Party Table Kick Course!
I don't fall for lies.
People can create barriers
by crossing their fingers.
I ate the Glare-Glare Fruit and became
quite an insightful woman.
It's common knowledge!
Even kids know it!
It seems like one of these competitors
is likely to win Block B!
I can see through anything.
Men are all liars.
He's fooling around again.
That guy is one of those annoying newcomers,
I'm a barrier human who ate
the Barrier-Barrier Fruit!
I told you.
Let me see inside of your head.
It must be filled with lies.
just like Straw Hat Luffy.
Go away, small fry.
Stop him!
I need to take care of him,
too, in this competition.
Barrier Crash!
Unbelievable!
Why did Trafalgar Law
and Straw Hat become allies?
How much more does Bartolomeo
want to offend other people?!
Violet-chan!
What are you doing, Cabbage?!
Sanji-san!
What brought you to Dressrosa
besides the business at Green Bit?
I'm checking the wanted posters of
the Worst Generation.
Dammit! You bastard!
Why is nobody kicking his ass?!
Get your filthy hands off of her!
But I have to get new ones.
What's your plan and what are you up to?!
In front of this huge audience,
Shut up!
I can barely see their pictures
with these knife cuts.
If you don't want me to kill her,
you better not move...
he pulled it out and started peeing!
You don't have to tell me.
Why don't you just let it go already?
All the answers are inside of your head.
No one has ever done such a thing
in this Colosseum!
No way!
"The Fighting King" - Elizabello
II got knocked out!
Damn!
Where... Where did he go?!
We will catch all of your crewmates.
I'll kill them!
Hey!
There is a big prize for this competition.
She's gonna strike the pose!
It feels so good!
The winner of Block B is...
That's her true power!
I was hoping Apoo or Kid or at
Somebody, stop him!
Dammit!
I won't forgive a man like you
who makes a woman cry!
least one of them
would enter but...
...Bartolomeo!
...I don't know yet
if any of them are here or not.
Diable Jambe!
Peeping Mind!
All of you, go to hell!
They can hide their face
like Burgess did earlier.
Here comes that somebody!
Amour Shot!
Some of us are taking this
thing seriously, brat!
--Go away!
--Screw you!
If any of them are here,
What?
You'll have to excuse me
for attacking you from behind!
should I wait for them to move
on to the next round or...
Nobody can stop...
Hey, wait! I'm not even
ready to fight back! Hey...
What? That strange guy won.
Wh-Wh-What's the matter?!
...our love!
The hero who came in to punish him is
the Fish-Man warrior - Hack!
Sanji-san, I was scared!
Sis!
H-How perverted!
You're not hurt, are you, Violet-chan?
I will dedicate the Flare-Flare Fruit
to that person!
Perverted?!
4000 Brick...
No! Thank you!
Oh, is this the place to watch the battle?
I've never seen anyone
who's whole mind is
Do it! Kick his ass, Hack!
That's good.
as pink-colored as his!
What?!
Sanji-san,
You're...
Then, you, too?!
What is your plan?!
What is your true purpose?!
...Fist!
Shh! Shh!
can I ask you a favor?
You're too loud!
What are you thinking
under these circumstances?!
We have a good view of the match from here.
You're plotting to destroy the factory, too?!
What is it?
He did it!
I would do anything for you, Violet-chan!
I'm thinking about you.
Indeed! My friends and I have been
carrying out preparations for it!
T-T-Too tight!
Oh, excuse me.
The way you looked at me
at that moment...
Yeah?
Who are you, old pops?
Tell me where it is!
I'll destroy it right away!
By the way,
I want you to kill someone!
Huh?
You can't do that!
how is Garp-san doing?
Just kidding!
Then will you...
Why?!
Because we want to save the
workers in the factory!
I knew you were telling the truth!
Straw Hat Luffy-kun!
What?
...die for me, "Black Foot" Sanji?
You know my grandpa?
It doesn't matter
if a million people accuse you, I...
The workers in the factory?
What?!
Yes!
What? V-Violet-chan?
I almost got killed by Garp-san once.
Our plan could lead to
the fall of this country!
I believe in women's tears!
What are you talking about?
What did he do?!
Hack is the one who collapsed!
It's a big project!
If you have the nerve and are
determined to go against Doflamingo,
And I've made up my mind to carry the
What an idiot.
What's going on?!
grudge even against his
children and grandchildren.
What was that?
I'm going to tell you everything
about this tragic kingdom - Dressrosa!
Wh-What kind of monster are you?!
Bartolomeo!