iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
go-in Go
Force it and go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the
prize for a fighting event
was the Flare-Flare Fruit, he decided to enter.
Meanwhile, after falling in
love with Violet, Sanji made a
raid on an unknown villain's hide-out
to grant her wish. However...
Can I ask you a favor?
Huh?
Then will you...
...die for me, "Black Foot" Sanji?
What? V-Violet-chan?
What are you talking about?
What an idiot.
At the same time, Usopp and the others are
heading to Green Bit to hand Caesar over.
It stopped.
--We caught it!
--Alright, let's pull it in!
A very wild forest?!
"Explore!
Fairies' Island - Green Bit!"
Th-This is...
...Green Bit?!
What are those giant plants?!
Hey, Joker, it's me! Pick me up!
Don't be in such a rush.
That is the beach on
the southeast side of the island.
We will leave you there
at three in the afternoon.
He will come soon.
Look at the beach on the other side!
Isn't that a Navy ship?!
It got stuck on the island!
It's not just beached!
How is it possible?!
Those cuts on the plants look fresh.
What?
I estimate that ship arrived recently.
Its body is not as damaged as I thought.
Did they make it through
the water filled with the Fighting Fish?!
It's only a matter of time
before the Navy soldiers get here.
What?!
Do they know about the trade-off?!
I didn't know that!
You stupid scientist, you're too loud!
Shh! Shh!
Hey, I'm a wanted person!
Since my boss - Joker resigned
from the Warlords,
there isn't any law that protects me!
If you leave me with handcuffs on
on the island where the Navy
soldiers are wandering, I'll...
I said "Shh! Be quiet!"
Wait a minute! Joker is
just a pirate now, too!
Either way, I'm doomed!
This is hell!
Enough, you idiot!
We're all screwed if the Navy finds us!
Why is the Navy here?
You look like you're hiding something.
It's just a coincidence.
How could I control the Navy?
By the way,
I'm thinking about going to Green Bit.
I wonder if I can handle the Straw Hats.
It's not fair to hand me over here!
Abort this mission!
The Navy is my enemy, too,
since I'm allied with the Straw Hats.
Don't tell me you set me up!
We still have 15 minutes before they come.
Everyone, cover me with
sniping and surveillance.
They may be hiding.
Go check the forest.
If you find something,
let me know as soon as possible.
Okay, I got it.
Wait a minute!
We didn't expect the Navy to be here so...
R-Robin!
This forest is dangerous! Wait!
Let's not get separated!
Thank you for being so manly, Usopp.
You're too loud!
Oh no!
Please don't leave me!
Can you walk a little more slowly?
Ouch! Don't stop suddenly, Robin...
Who is it?! The Straw Hats?!
They found us!
Shh.
Where?! Where are they?!
Just surrender without resistance!
We know you're here on the island!
Damn! Come on out, Straw Hats!
That's not my name! I'm Leo!
Who is it?! Where is he?!
It's the Navy soldiers.
Who are they talking to?
Looks like they knew
we were coming to this island.
Are you good people or bad people?!
We're Navy soldiers! We protect citizens.
We're definitely good people!
Then, hand over your weapons!
You can't have our weapons!
We have work to do!
--Hey, who are you?!
--Show yourself!
So that is your answer.
Where are you?!
Hey, where is your cape?!
My gun!
Oh?!
What was that?!
My hat!
Oh no!
Huh?! What's going on?!
I can't see. It's too fast.
--What is this forest?!
--Dammit!
We got stripped of all we have!
That will teach you!
You villainous Big Humans!
Yeah!
What?
Mil Fleurs! Campo de Flores!
I caught one!
Huh?! What did you catch?!
I think it's a little person!
What?!
Help me!
Kabu-san!
We have a problem!
Let go of me!
I thought so!
I got caught!
DRESSROSA - THE PORT TOWN "ACACIA"
Turn right! I said "Right"!
Why did you turn left?!
Shut up! Be quiet! You're distracting me!
What the...
Mom, he's talking to himself...
Don't look him in the eye!
I'm in hurry!
Not as much as I am!
If I can't make it, it's your fault!
Get to the Flower Field already!
All right! Just shut up!
Give me back my sword!
What?
Oh no!
Ow, ow, ow... This is no good!
I'm so dumb! This human will see me!
I have to run! Otherwise, the human will...
Excuse me.
Who are you?!
I'm so dumb!
So dumb and stupid and blockheaded!
I always knew I'd fail like this!
Is this what they call a fairy?
Is it a toy?
WICKA - A MEMBER OF THE SCOUTING UNIT OF
THE TONTATTA (A TRIBE OF LITTLE PEOPLE)
I'm not a toy!
I'm Wicka from the Tontatta Tribe!
Please don't tell anybody that you saw me!
I beg you!
I don't know what's going on here.
I don't have time for this!
Huh?
I wasn't gonna eat you or anything.
Tell me what's going on.
I-I can't do that!
I can't share any information
with you Big Humans!
I'm sorry! I gotta go!
What now?!
I can't walk!
I think I twisted my ankle earlier!
I'm so dumb, dumb, dumb, dumb, dumb, dumb...
You're pretty strong!
You're smashing the ground.
Please!
Take me to my commander!
When you come right down to it,
it's kind of your fault.
You stole my sword!
"Stole"? What are you talking about?
We manage the greenery of this land!
The Big Humans of this kingdom call us "fairies"
and give us things!
"Give"? No, you're stealing them!
I said too much again!
I have to go!
I'm a member of a scouting unit!
I have to report the Don Quixote Family's
whereabouts to my commander!
Now is our chance!
I saw the Don Quixote Family on their way
to attack the Straw Hats' ship!
What?!
I have to go!
I'm a member of a scouting unit!
I have to report the Don Quixote Family's
whereabouts to my commander!
Now is our chance!
I saw the Don Quixote Family on their way
to attack the Straw Hats' ship!
What?!
I'm so dumb! I told him everything!
Hey, is that true?!
I'm a member of the Straw Hats!
Dumb! So dumb!
Dumb! I'm so dumb! Dumb!
I'm a blockhead!
Whoa-whoa!
Stop wrecking the town!
Calm down, fairy!
Is it true that the
Don Quixote Family is going to
attack the Sunny?!
It's a secret! But I saw it!
Oh, I did it again!
I don't have a Transponder Snail.
There's no way to tell them about it.
Of all the others,
I can't believe they're attacking those four.
Alright, I'm gonna head back to the Sunny!
Wait!
Take me to the Flower Field first!
I'll guide you to the sea right after that!
No, I'm gonna head to the sea now!
But...
...you're running in the opposite direction!
You don't know which way to go, do you?!
So...
...Don Quixote's people were
following our movements.
Yes. And we were keeping an eye on them.
You guys have some kind of
a conflict with him, too?!
Yes! Oops!
That was a secret.
Damn! It's not only the ship that's in danger
but all of us!
Hey, are we there yet? The Flower Field?!
Go up the stairs there!
I said "Go up"!
Are you a b-blockhead?
Shut up!
Where did he hide? That coward!
Hey, that's Don Chinjao!
You got to be kidding.
I want to hear the sound of the gong
that signals the start of the match!
Hey, I think we better run!
Garp's grandson!
That sound signals your death!
Hey, we better run!
Prepare yourself!
Control yourself, old man!
They'll eliminate you
if you fight outside of the ring again!
Don't forget what we are here for, grandpa!
Let's go!
I know.
Oh, that was scary.
That old guy is such a pain in the butt.
Everybody's naked before my eyes.
I've seen everything that's been
in your mind since we first met.
I heard you have a soft spot for women
but I didn't expect it to be that soft.
How pathetic!
Your collar is wrinkled up
and your tie is crooked.
Your shirt is stained with blood.
You look terrible.
You're a good-for-nothing,
"Black Foot" Sanji!
VIOLET - AN ASSASSIN OF
THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY (THE TREBOL ARMY)
Did you really think that
a guy like you could win my heart?
How funny.
I can't believe you were
attracted by Sis' beauty,
you stupid jerk!
Didn't you know it was a trap?! You idiot!
You're lying, Violet-chan...
Hey, quit dreaming already!
Sis was just acting!
I-I know you have a beautiful heart...
How could you still say such a thing
after getting hurt so badly?
Hey, stand up!
You must have been coaxed
into this by some bad guys.
You don't even want to be here.
Violet-chan...
Why don't you quit being so romantic?!
So stupid!
--That's terrible! But she's beautiful!
--That was a hell of a kick, Sis!
You're trying to hold back
your anger against me
and looking for a way to run.
Do you think you can persuade me
with your lies?
I don't fall for lies.
I ate the Glare-Glare Fruit and became
quite an insightful woman.
I can see through anything.
Men are all liars.
Let me see inside of your head.
It must be filled with lies.
Why did Trafalgar Law
and Straw Hat become allies?
What brought you to Dressrosa
besides the business at Green Bit?
What's your plan and what are you up to?!
You don't have to tell me.
All the answers are inside of your head.
We will catch all of your crewmates.
She's gonna strike the pose!
That's her true power!
Peeping Mind!
Wh-Wh-What's the matter?!
Sis!
H-How perverted!
Perverted?!
I've never seen anyone
who's whole mind is
as pink-colored as his!
What?!
What is your plan?!
What is your true purpose?!
What are you thinking
under these circumstances?!
I'm thinking about you.
The way you looked at me
at that moment...
I want you to kill someone!
I knew you were telling the truth!
It doesn't matter
if a million people accuse you, I...
I believe in women's tears!