iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
koukishin ni makasete
Go along with your curiosity
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
kokoro no chizu hirogete
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the
prize for a fighting event
When Luffy found out that the prize for a
fighting event was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
When Luffy found out that the prize
When Luffy found out that the
prize for a fighting event
When Luffy found out that the prize for a
was the Flare-Flare Fruit, he decided to enter.
for a fighting event was the Flare-Flare
Fruit, he decided to enter.
was the Flare-Flare Fruit, he decided to enter.
fighting event was the Flare-Flare
Fruit, he decided to enter.
he decided to enter.
Meanwhile, Sanji found out that
Caesar's hand-over was Doflamingo's trap and...
Finally, the match for Block C
which Luffy registered for, started!
He's worth 77 million berries!
Meanwhile, Robin and Usopp arrived at Green Bit
to hand Caesar over
Finally, the match for Block C
which Luffy registered for, started!
A member of the Straw
Hats! "Black Foot" Sanji!
and came across little people in the forest.
Listen carefully!
Do you wanna fight me?
Let's cut his head off!
Oh, crap! Run, Ucy!
Let's do this together!
We've been totally deceived!
Mil Fleurs! Campo de Flores!
Ucy!
Sanji was saved by Violet who
was working for Doflamingo,
I have only one purpose, Law.
Meanwhile, Nami and the others who stayed
on the Thousand Sunny, encounter...
What a disappointment!
and has found out some shocking news!
I caught one!
I just wanted to kill you!
Huh?! What did you catch?!
From the moment
you all arrived here with Caesar,
I think it's a little person!
At the same time,
to grant the girl
you were walking into that man's trap!
Wh-What's going on in here?!
that he met on the street, Violet's, wish,
"Shaking Heaven and Earth!
Admiral Fujitora's Power!"
Sanji made a raid on an
unknown villain's hide-out
and got caught in a trap.
You're a good-for-nothing,
"Black Foot" Sanji!
"A Blow of Anger!
A Giant vs. Lucy!"
The Giant's been knocked down!
What you see is Dressrosa this morning.
Did you really think that
a guy like you could win my heart?
What does this mean?
OFF THE COAST OF DRESSROSA
How funny.
"Destruction Cannon Blasts!
Lucy in trouble!"
You're lying, Violet-chan...
THE THOUSAND SUNNY
Alright! It's time finally!
Rebecca.
I'm thinking about you.
I saw the list in the Colosseum.
You entered the competition as I thought.
GREEN BIT - THE BEACH ON THE SOUTHEAST SIDE
I told you not to!
The way you looked at me
at that moment...
Wh-What is this?
I...
I knew you were telling the truth!
Joker! Kick this guy's ass already...
I'll do it! I'll win it!
It doesn't matter
if a million people accuse you, I...
Soldier-san!
I'm not gonna hand him over to you!
So...
So... Hey, can we live together?!
You didn't do anything that I asked you to!
I believe in women's tears!
Doflamingo! This deal is off!
A warrior who cries easily can't win
a competition!
No! Wh-What're you talking about, you fool?!
We got this far!
What's going on in here?
It's so creepy.
Anesthetic flowers!
Franky-san will be pissed if he sees this!
Is that how you talk to your boss
after 10 years of silence?
"The Unknown World!
The Tontatta Kingdom!"
What's this smoke?
Leave him, Law.
Caesar is one of my precious subordinates.
Meanwhile, after passing out
in the forest of Green Bit,
Jo...
"Believe in women's tears"? How absurd!
Robin woke up in the Tontatta Kingdom -
the country of the Little People.
Issho-san, it's Caesar Clown who is with Law.
He must've gone crazy in fear of death!
I see. He is the scientist from
the poison gas incident...
Joker!
The Big Human is waking up!
Face reality!
That was awesome, Lucy!
You were completely fooled by Sis' act!
Don't try to run! Stay calm!
But if he is that Warlord's subordinate,
he is not going to get charged.
Can't help getting more excited as we go on!
My body is pinned to the ground!
What?!
What a shithead!
They'll grant him amnesty.
It's no use trying to move!
Sis, if this pervert is useless to us now,
It's you!
He came in and stirred things up in Block C!
You're a villainous Big Human, aren't you?
You are Fujitora, appointed as a Navy admiral
through the World Military Draft.
So this is you Little People's kingdom.
let's just kill him already!
Th-The door got deformed, too!
Lucy did it again!
I hear a lot about you.
Is she a Devil Fruit eater?!
It's two fifty-seven.
But what kind?!
We don't have time!
They say you're a monster who has
unquestionable power as well as Ryokugyu.
"BAD TASTE" Fruit?
We got her permission!
Oh, why thank you.
"The Stratagem of the Century!
Doflamingo Makes His Move!"
He's worth 77 million berries!
Thank you for fighting together with me.
A member of the Straw Hats! "Black Foot" Sanji!
Don't play dumb.
Oh boy, oh boy!
Let me carry you to the
side of the ring, Ucy.
I'm still new to the Navy so
it's hard for me to
Let's cut his head off!
Hierro Lágrima!
understand what you're doing.
I believe this guy still
has a lot more to show!
I don't like people who
have no artistic sense!
I don't have enough evidence yet
Whoa! Sis, what're you doing?!
GREEN BIT - THE BEACH ON THE SOUTHEAST SIDE
Eye Whale!
but I have some information about
W-Who are you?!
Be quiet!
you doing things that go against
the rules of the Seven Warlords.
Help!
The appointed time
for Caesar's hand-over is...
The man right there was calling you "Joker" -
is that your nickname?
Did you just call me a mermaid?
...in two minutes.
What else is new?
We didn't say that!
Violet-chan?
I can't believe it!
I didn't expect he'd be that strong!
Whoa-whoa, who do you
think you're talking to?!
Eye Whale!
If you want to investigate me,
you have to be really determined
and collect enough evidence.
Lucy!
This is Giolla-sama of
the Don Quixote Family!
GIOLLA
THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY
(THE TRÉBOL ARMY)
Now, what's the Navy's decision
about Law's punishment?
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Hey, Giant man! You're still in the ring.
Clank!
The Don Quixote Family?!
Hey, Law! This is Sanji!
Oh boy!
Black Foot-ya! Did you find the factory?
My soul is swinging!
If you wanna take a nap, you better get out!
Violet-chan, you were working for
That's not important now!
Doflamingo against your will, weren't you?!
I see an image! My mind is gonna erupt!
There he is! "Black Foot" Sanji!
Regarding the news about you and
the wanted pirates, the Straw Hats,
Don't let the traitor
Violet get away, either!
Run, Black Foot.
--Kill them!
--This is it!
You're in my way!
Violet-chan, what about you?!
if you're allying with them as they say in the news,
you're guilty!
It's gonna explode!
An image of liberty and beauty!
Forget about me!
Why?!
If they have become your subordinates,
Law-san, you're...
We know
This way!
what you people have
been doing all along.
...not guilty!
Our mission depends on your response.
What?
Hajrudin's enormous body's been
blown up by an explosion?!
I was your enemy
but you kept believing in me!
We may have to arrest you and the Straw Hats.
What just happened?!
You sure are a good-for-nothing!
H-Hey, what kind of decision is that?!
He can just get away by lying!
Thank you for what you've said.
My original plan failed completely.
The Navy is targeting us now.
You assholes!
It made me happy!
Wh-What the...
I don't know why but
Black Foot!
Even if I lie now and try to
take this matter to Dressrosa,
you don't wanna work for Doflamingo, do you?!
Oh my face!
You even fought your own men!
It got all flattened and smooth!
How dare you!
it only makes it worse.
Do you know what you're in for
if you hit Violet-chan?!
Let's escape from this island together on our ship!
I have to buy some time.
No!
The Straw Hats are not working under me!
We're allies as you read in the paper!
No, it wasn't an explosion!
Hey you! What do you think you're doing?!
Hajrudin got eliminated
but there are still many tough ones in Block C!
It's art. A work of art.
Listen carefully!
You're such a clumsy man!
You've got to get out of there!
I know you ordinary people
can't understand art.
Look at me, Black Foot!
Then, we have to strip you of your title.
What are you talking about?
That was an explosive punch
powered by some odd-shaped shoulders!
From the moment
you all arrived here with Caesar,
I have to hand Caesar over soon!
It'd be nice if the story ended there but...
Doflamingo didn't resign
from the Seven Warlords!
Cut the art crap! Turn us back!
you were walking into that man's trap!
Ideo!
Yeah, turn us back!
Trap?
Yes. Look inside my head.
The one who blew away the
No no, I can't do that.
Giant's huge body was...
"DESTRUCTION CANNON" IDEO
AN XXX RANK BOXER
Even if you hand Caesar over to him,
there is no trade whatsoever!
...the two-time champion of...
How can I do that?
All right, I can turn you back if you want.
...the New World Central Fighting Tournament!
But in exchange, you need to hand Momonosuke
"Destruction Cannon" Ideo!
That doesn't make sense.
over to us without any trouble!
What do you mean?
What you see is Dressrosa this morning.
Don't worry, Momo-chan!
We won't let them take you!
--Ideo's strong!
--Yeah, amazing!
Cut the "two-time champion" crap!
I heard you!
What does this mean?
We've been...
The past record from
other competitions doesn't matter!
Oh, my soul is swinging!
...totally deceived!
What?
I'm gonna make you more beautiful!
You're right.
No way!
Here it comes again!
What matters is...
If we get distorted anymore,
what will we look like?!
What the...
...how strong you are!
THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
Is it a meteorite?!
-D-Don't be ridiculous!
So the winner of Block A was Burgess!
You've got to be kidding!
The winner of Block B was Bartolomeo!
And I'm stronger than you.
Run!
And the match of Block C is about to start!
A meteorite is coming toward us!
They're gone!
I'm gonna win this thing!
--There is a hatch!
--Should we go after them?
Who is going to win this one?!
I'm gonna be the champion!
Oh boy, oh boy! What a pain!
--Your Majesty!
--Please don't quit!
All competitors seem eager to start!
Room!
--Doflamingo-sama!
--We need your explanation!
Alright! It's time finally!
Why did you abdicate from the throne?!
What is it?
How noisy. Aren't they here yet?
A bull?!
Are you gonna fight, too?!
How funny! You're all fired up!
Meanwhile, elsewhere in Dressrosa...
Here they come.
Hey, who's forcing his way in?!
Stop pushing, idiot!
It's not me, shithead!
What?!
--There they are!
--When did they get out there?!
Whoa!
A warship is arriving into the harbor!
I'm so surprised!
What?!
You're unbelievably terrible with directions!
Isn't it starting yet?!
Hey! What do you think you're doing?!
Get back here!
Shut up! It was just a slight mistake!
I've seen that logo before!
Hey, an old geezer like you should stay back!
Or I'll make you look more like art pieces!
"Slight"?!  That wasn't "slight"!
Screw you!
Cipher Pol Aigis Zero!
What did you say?
You can't reach us with your
bizarre power ever again!
Say it again!
You've gone in the opposite direction
from where I told you 27 times!
I said "Your grandpa is an old geezer"!
That's right!
Just try it!
Whoa-whoa, brother, relax.
You ran down stairs that
you just climbed up 31 times!
Oh boy, oh boy!
That's enough, squirt.
They're the Government officials
who work directly under the World Nobles!
She's getting mad, just as we planned.
We will show you
Why are they here?
Uh-huh.
It was not "slight" at all!
Boy, if she keeps using that weird power,
Calm down, people of Dressrosa.
what we are capable of in the match!
We're moving away from the Flower Field
rather than getting closer!
the Sunny will get all messed up!
What did you say?!
Don't mess with us Funk Brothers!
I know Franky-san will be furious
About the report on
Pull yourself together!
but aside from that, can
we even turn it back?
Shut up! It's your fault
because you suck at leading the way!
Doflamingo's abdication from the throne
Thank you for waiting!
The room that used to be
the men's dormitory...
and the Seven Warlords that
spread all over the world...
I don't know.
The time has come!
The competitors of Block C are...
I-I can't believe it.
No...
But all we can do now is
try to keep it from getting
Where's Issho-san?
It's your fault!!
any more screwed up!
It was a mistake. Just a false report.
I hope she focuses out this way!
Away from the ship!
--What the...
He jumped up and fell down himself.
Huh?
That means...
She's going to the other side!
Ouch!
What do you think you're doing?!
...entering!
Doflamingo-sama is not quitting!
What's going on?
How annoying! Oh boy, oh boy!
What happened to him all of a sudden?
Who is he yelling at?
So creepy. Let's go.
That's great!
Hey, guys!
Now, we will let the world know about it
I have to tell my people where the
Yes, ma'am!
through an extra edition
of the newspaper at three today.
members of the Don Quixote Family
are, as soon as possible!
What?! What happened in that moment?!
So pull yourself together!
The competitors are coming
in one after another!
It's going to be a secret until then.
Don't you get it?!
You mustn't tell anybody about it.
Just like Block B,
I-Is that...
Block C has many formidable contenders!
You're gonna break my bones!
All nations, keep living peacefully
as if nothing has happened.
Doflamingo's submarine?!
You're too strong to lose control like that!
Ah, so that's how they got here!
The battle will start soon!
I have friends that I care about, too!
They came hiding in the fog, didn't they?!
Who is going to win...
This is no good.
Stop complaining or
go ask some damn cat to carry you!
I didn't realize there were so many of them!
...Portgas D. Ace's Flare-Flare Fruit?!
Only those three spots that they're standing
have no damage!
That wasn't a dream, wasn't it?
What are you guys doing?!
They're going to get away!
It all happened for real
right before you people
Just go and take Momonosuke away
from them already!
Issho-san...
came to this island.
Hey!
How did the Fleet Admiral train you?!
You damn stray dog!
I can't believe it! I'm so confused!
Yes, Giolla-sama!
It doesn't matter if he can see or not.
The World Government?!
My soul is swinging! I see an image!
It's beyond a Warlord's control, isn't it?!
Oh, thank you.
I just wanted to test your skills.
My mind is gonna erupt!
Yes, you're right.
Now, I'm going to arrest you.
Until the day you are filled with happiness,
Oh, she's gonna do it again!
I'm
Is it okay, Law-san?
scared of Doflamingo so I can't go
Hello?! We're here!
I will always be by your side!
Don't tell me you're thinking
you can get away from me.
You have to aim at us!
but maybe you people can get away in time!
Don't bother with the ship! We're here!
Oh, it's gonna explode!
An image of liberty and beauty!
DRESSROSA - FRANKY AND THE OTHERS
Was it a dream?
Did you get that?!
The Flower Field?!
Are you gonna go on a picnic?!
No!
Leave the island now!
What about you?!
Where have you been, Sanji?!
The world should be free!
This place looks familiar... Or not...
I've been...
Shouldn't it?!
...in love!
Is this...
Oh, that's nice to hear.
By the way, I think I can find the factory.
Where am I?
You already got lost?
Really?!
But unfortunately,
we can't just destroy it and get away.
A-Are you some kind of idiot?!
The news about Doflamingo was a mistake?
Who are you calling an idiot?!
It's gonna be a much bigger task
than we expected.
What do you mean by that, Saka-san?
Damn!
Hey, wait! We don't allow credit!
Please! Take me to my people!
She did it! We're in big trouble!
Are you saying the Navy Headquarters
were fooled by a false report?
Wait! Monkey-san!
Somebody, catch that toy!
All right.
He ran away without paying!
Yes, it's so aggravating!
I'm going to go talk to
the Five Elders at Marie Jois.
You're going the wrong way!
I got you!
Wait!
Let's go!
I'm sorry but that's what happened.
We don't have time!
Doflamingo was...
Okay!
I need you to keep going ahead to
Yeah, I just read the extra edition.
He sure fooled us!
Trafalgar Law and Doflamingo's
rendezvous point.
If he gets Caesar back,
our entire plan ends in failure!
Roger that.
Again! What kind of place
is the Flower Field?!
Clank.
This is what beauty is!
Be quiet and keep running.
I'll tell you later.
Let's destroy the factory and
put his nose out of joint!
All units! Go to the beach
on the southeast side!
And at Green Bit...
What do you think?
Isn't it beautiful?
Anyway, you have to come meet us
at the Flower Field!
Hurry up!
Watch out for the police!
You fool. It's too late.
Oh no! You can't call it a ship anymore!
Aren't you a soldier?!
Don't be scared of the police!
I'm busy, too! I'm gonna hang up now!
Why is the name of that
place so fairytale-ish?!
Clank!
Oh boy, oh boy!
Soldier-san!
By the way, I can't reach Nami-san!
There they are! Go after them!
I'm not gonna fall for your trick!
Soldier-san!
You still see her as weak?
She's gonna be fine!
What the hell? Do you know her?
Young Master-sama ordered
me to kidnap Momonosuke
Brook and Monster Chopper are with her!
and hijack your ship!
Rebecca.
What should I do?!
Room!
--What is that?
--Huh? What's wrong?
Wow! What the...
Now, there is no way for you Straw Hats
to escape from Dressrosa!
Nico Robin's upper half came out of the sand!
I saw the list in the Colosseum.
Violet-chan, what is that?
Nico-ya!
This is just a clone.
You entered the competition as I thought.
That's a broadcast from the Colosseum.
I told you not to!
An unknown gladiator, Lucy, is pretty strong!
I was listening to the conversation.
It was Sanji, wasn't it?
I...
Our plan failed!
--He's quite a fighter!
--Small but tough!
Hey, where are your actual body and Nose-ya?
I'll do it! I'll win it!
Soldier-san!
If what Black Foot-ya
Only a Warlord could do that.
So...
was talking about is true,
the deal with Doflamingo is off.
Franky, you won't believe
this but, Luffy is...
Damn you, Fujitora. He's mine to kill.
So... Hey, can we live together?!
Just give up and surrender yourselves!
Off?!
Yeah, he's fighting in a competition now.
Then, what's gonna happen to my hand-over?!
Bullet String!
It's not gonna happen!
A warrior who cries easily can't win
a competition!
Why did you let him?!
You should've kept an eye on him!
No!
Nico-ya! Summon Nose-ya!
You're in no place to judge me!
You lost Zoro, didn't you?!
Let's get off of the island now!
Hey, let's go!
The thing is, we're
underground Green Bit now!
Is it okay?
Yes.
You wanna play tag, Law?
Just go!
Underground?!
Black Foot, I have to go!
We had some trouble...
My men are coming after me!
But both Usopp and I are safe.
You want to go to the
secret factory, don't you?
I don't need any medical attention!
We can't help you but
I'm leaving!
Here is a map.
if you're gonna escape,
go without us.
Mr. Ricky! We can't just let you go!
It's disguised as "Toy House."
Let's chase them.
We'll go to the harbor
where we agreed to meet up.
Is it really okay?! That girl was crying!
Our job is to take care of all competitors
including treatment of injuries,
Yes, sir!
But that's the factory.
Okay, I got it...
I can't take this!
If you help me more, you're gonna...
especially you guests.
Treatment?
You let people kill each other
in front of an audience!
You're a funny man.
It doesn't make any difference.
Th-The Navy!
That's why we got to hurry!
It seems like the executives
already know that I betrayed them.
Cut the treatment crap!
You're bleeding from the head!
You are Trafalgar Law-san, aren't you?
Take off your mask and let us take a look!
Don't touch my mask!
You're the new admiral,
Violet-chan...
I know what you're doing, Law.
The western harbor! Meet me there!
I'm just a toy but I have something
that I want to protect!
Fujitora, aren't you?
You're trying to buy some time, aren't you?
A-Are you alright, Mr. Ricky?
Hide yourself there and
wait until I get there!
Here he comes.
That's our rendezvous point!
I don't need treatment.
Good luck!
Good luck to you guys, too!
That's...
But I can't even shed
tears from these tin eyes.
Open the exit!
No, we're not allowed to do that.
I will help you get away
from here at any price!
Everybody, hold him down.
He's badly wounded!
I'm not gonna let you have it your way.
You really are a good-for-nothing.
THE FOREST OF GREEN BIT
Joker!
Hey, Robin, what's going on?!
You said there was a little person!
Sorry to interrupt, you good-for-nothing!
Yes, I have him here.
Huh? That's not even funny!
You fool! Where did you come from?!
Oh, Violet-chan?!
Nobody's out there, right? It's all safe?
This is serious.
You have to beat them all up first.
You have to get treated.
There he is!
Did you rob those Navy soldiers?
Hey, Law!
What are they doing on the street like this?!
Well done!
Lucy and Ideo's one-on-one fight!
I didn't expect to see a Navy admiral here!
This should be an interesting match-up!
This is no good!
We have to do something!
Here.
Since I'm no longer a Warlord,
I'm scared as hell!
There is no little person...
Wow, there is one!
Move! I can walk by myself!
So strong!
I think his friends are still around here.
Why didn't you do it yourself?
Go straight and take the
stairs to the basement.
Liar!
I couldn't do anything because they're
holding Kanjuro as a hostage.
What?!
I heard someone talking.
Take this!
Rebecca... I'm sorry.
You have to come with me, Sanji-dono!
To the place called Toy House!
Anesthetic flowers!
What the... Your punch is like a bomb.
That's where they are keeping
my fellow samurai - Kanjuro!
What's this smoke?
I don't know where it is, though!
I'm not satisfied with my power yet.
Count on me.
I want to get to the top of the ladder!
Hey, are you alright? Robi... n...
Entering from the general public,
no one really cared about him
So I want to be stronger!
Tired...
but Lucy's doing really well!
Usopp...
By eating the prize of this competition -
the Flare-Flare Fruit!
Now, all competitors of
Block C are out there finally!
She's gonna fall asleep soon.
I'm not gonna let you have Ace's fruit.
139 warriors!
A WAITING ROOM FOR THE DON
QUIXOTE FAMILY IN THE COLOSSEUM
What should we do with these people?
I will win it!
Now, who's next?!
It's a battle royal!
Since they saw us,
No, I'm gonna be the champion!
Who's gonna win this?!
we must get rid of them!
Straw Hat is fighting in
the match now, Diamante.
Oh, there is a strong
contender left! Who is it?
After the match is fine.
This is hot!
Finally!
Now, the battle is...
What a breathtakingly heated battle!
The bull from earlier?!
But that's not the only fight
you want to keep an eye on!
I can't believe you're already
in the ring, Straw Hat!
Now, take a look!
Joker wants me to kill Straw Hat?
Those three gangs from the
Kano Kingdom in the far east
Doffy's too indulgent.
You're in Block D, aren't you, Cavendish?!
are very unique, too!
He's giving the man who couldn't
win the match one more chance.
Are you trying to break in?!
Let go of me!
Cut it out! Or you'll get eliminated!
Aren't you happy, Bellamy?
Assassination is an easy task.
Finish it up before the competition's over.
It's no use!
Hey, Bellamy! Don't give up!
What's in her bag?
A book, a notebook, and clothes.
Let's do it!
Alright! Do you wanna fight me?!
--A candy.
--A Transponder Snail.
Then, you'll get promoted
to be an executive of the Family.
There you go!
You can't protect yourself from it!
Make sure to take all weapons.
SAI - THE 13TH LEADER OF THE HAPPO NAVY -
A GANG FROM THE KANO KINGDOM
The Eight-Impact Fist that allows
There must be something on her!
Oh, now Brutal Bull is facing
the unstoppable Lucy!
them to manipulate an impact!
Shields and armor are useless against them!
We are searching her clothes!
Brutal Bull fought death row prisoners
in this Colosseum the other day!
Yeah!
--Nothing around Point C.
--Roger.
Kick his ass!
--Nothing around Point A.
--Roger.
They will free the one of us who kills it
from death row.
She's not hiding anything
around Point B, either.
This is a chance that doesn't come twice!
With centuries of history,
I heard you're trying
to kill Lucy, Cavendish.
I killed so many tough
guys before I got caught!
Yes!
the Happo Navy is...
BOO - THE VICE LEADER OF THE HAPPO NAVY -
A GANG FROM THE KANO KINGDOM
I'm gonna drop every single
one of you into the water!
...just unbeatable!
I'm gonna kill this one!
You're Bartolomeo, aren't you?
Congrats on making it to final.
No, I am!
About Lucy, it's none of your business.
The Big Human is waking up!
No, that man is...
Great!
If we can kill you,
Go on the alert!
...not yours to kill!
Prepare to get crushed!
it's almost as big a prize as
winning this competition, Chinjao!
Okay!
W-Wait a minute! Ouch!
Boy...
Don't try to run! Stay calm!
I see. You want to kill him, too.
My body is pinned to the ground!
Because he's in the limelight!
It's no use trying to move!
Go home and train yourselves more
before coming back, punks!
But I'm the one who will kill him.
I won't let anybody else to do it.
I sewed your body onto the ground
Of course, you're no exception!
with my magical Stitch-Stitch power!
He killed more than half of
the prisoners in the fight!
Huh?! Where did he go?!
If you get in my way, you'll get hurt.
Stitch-Stitch power?
That's a big hammer!
Yes! I sewed you up with this needle!
He's certainly a killer bull!
You scare me!
When did you get there?!
The Colosseum's Grim Reaper!
My connection with him is much deeper.
Gum-Gum...
FORMERLY THE 12TH LEADER
OF THE HAPPO NAVY (RETIRED)
- A GANG FROM THE KANO KINGDOM
Because of his behavior, people call him Brutal Bull!
You're a villainous Big Human, aren't you?
...Pistol!
Many people are eliminated already!
I'm sorry but I think there
is a misunderstanding.
That guy's arm stretched like rubber!
DON CHINJAO
The battle for Block C is heating up!
Are you a Devil Fruit eater?
A Devil Fruit eater?!
He's charging at Lucy!
A guy with the "Gum" power -
must be Straw Hat...
I'm a Tontatta Tribe warrior - Leo!
A WARRIOR - LEO
THE TONTATTA TRIBE
(A TRIBE OF LITTLE PEOPLE)
It's so fierce both
offensively and defensively!
That was Conqueror's Haki!
Oops.
But Lucy is just standing still!
I'm gonna fight you next!
No wonder!
Leo-san. Where am I?
But even though they're all tough fighters,
He used to be a pirate
worth 500 million! He's the legend!
Um...
Did he get paralyzed with fear?!
There is only one man that I want to fight!
Where is Usopp?
there is one giant warrior who is
literally sticking out!
I mean, the other human - he's not here?
This is just a normal punch!
Brutal Bull stabbed him with his horns...
Don't get in my way!
Is he okay?
Thank you, Chinjao!
We also captured that long-nosed Big Human
There are so many nice weapons to pick up!
That was close.
in accordance with our kingdom's rules.
Whoa!
Did you just see it?
He's not Lucy! He's Straw Hat...
That man didn't get beaten
by Don Chinjao's Haki
So this is you Little People's kingdom.
Hey. I'm here!
Stop it!
and he's now picking up weapons in the ring!
Indeed, you're in the Tontatta Kingdom
L-Lucy fended it off!
JEAN ANGO AKA JEAN THE BANDIT
A BOUNTY HUNTER
How annoying!
He is a dark horse in this competition -
Gum-Gum...
underneath the great forest that we created.
Jean the Bandit!
--Huh?!
--He did it again!
I'm over here! Come on!
A bounty hunter that all big-time pirates
Oh, never mind.
The forest? You mean Green Bit?
What the hell?!
in the New World
hold a grudge against!
Did you people grow all those giant plants?!
Here's a normal kick!
Wait, you shithead!
Yes! There is no plant that we can't grow!
Now that I found you, your number is up!
Watch out, everybody!
He is a warrior of the new generation
from the famous Giants' country - Elbaf!
I won't forgive you
for sending my partner to prison!
Kabu-san!
What a pain in the butt.
This Big Human can sprout flower-like hands
on the ground!
Hey, that guy with a helmet is interesting!
The most formidable "Pirate Mercenary"!
These weapons that
I picked up will make nice bullets.
Oh yeah?!
Flower-like hands?!
I've never seen him before.
His name is...
We've never grown such things!
Who is it?
I'm a sniper after all!
...Hajrudin!!
Like I said, he's Straw Hat...
Yes, it must be a magic!
The strangest thing I've ever seen!
He's gigantic!
Go back to the bleachers!
If that partner guy was so important to you,
Whoa! What are you doing?! Straw Hat!
There was no time to run
before she caught me!
you should've shown your
mettle by raiding the prison!
That little one is quite strong.
Like the idiot who actually did it
a couple years ago.
That's right!
I got hypnotized by something
and they must've carried me here!
Let's take care of him first.
You're too big, you bastard!
That's not fair!
Hey! That guy has already passed out!
B-Brutal Bull... s-stopped?!
How much more is he gonna punch him?!
I can maybe get away from here with my power
Have you ever seen a Giant
who ate a Logia fruit?
What did Lucy do? What happened?!
Oh, they're coming all at once!
but it can create a stir.
Hey, stop, brother!
He's already knocked out!
I like you!
That's enough!
You Big Human! What are you up to?!
Go away!
Let's do this together!
I restrained the wrong person.
Are you here to destroy the Tontatta Kingdom?!
That's what I'll become once
I win the Flare-Flare Fruit!
I-I can't believe it!
No! I'm sorry!
I just caught him out of curiosity!
He's riding on the Colosseum's Grim Reaper!
I'm gonna become the king of...
What a man! Lucy!
You can't get away this time!
...all Giants!
Whatever the reason is,
This bastard! He called me shorty!
With just a single blow!
It was like lightning!
we can't let anybody who
saw us Tontatta Tribe go alive.
THE FUNK BROTHERS
ASSASSINS FROM THE MOGARO KINGDOM
Hey, Bobby, am I a shorty?! Huh?!
Who can stop him?!
BACK IN GREEN BIT
Why?! I wasn't going to hurt any
of you people in the first place
No, you're not! You're a big man!
Whoa, on the other hand,
there is a fighting bull
running out of control
and I'll never tell anyone that I saw you!
UNDER THE FOREST
Say something, you dickhead!
showing no fear for all those tough contenders!
Brother! That's enough!
THE TONTATTA KINGDOM
Don't lie!
I don't wanna hear your excuses!
He's a killer bull who slayed
21 death row prisoners
I mean it!
I restrained the wrong person.
What?
during a fight in this very Colosseum!
Then, I'll let you go!
Why is it shaking?
KELLY FUNK
THE OLDER OF THE TWO BROTHERS
If I ever hear you say it again,
I got him!
I'll gouge your eyes out!
That won't work.
What?!
It must be Law and the others.
The Colosseum's Grim Reaper!
--Oh, what a relief!
--
Don't keep trying to stop me, Bobby!
Boom!
Because of his behavior, people call him Brutal Bull!
BOBBY FUNK
THE YOUNGER OF THE TWO BROTHERS
I thought she was a bad person.
Great!
But this is a competition, brother.
Damn! I don't wanna die here!
And somehow, someone knows how to tame
and ride this Grim Reaper!
The Funk Brothers are so brutal!
They believed me!
--What?!
--The hero is getting upset!
They're assassins well known
in the underground community!
Bursting into prominence,
with his cool strength,
Why are they so credulous?
he instantly became a crowd favorite!
You're free now!
I heard they're very powerful fighters and
Lucy!
Here are your glasses.
J-Just kidding.
The truth is the shake was...
Go Usy (bull)!
they even killed some pirates
worth over a 100 million!
Because...
Thank you.
...caused by my Haki!
I don't care if it's a competition
or not! I'm not short!
Hey, Leo!
How annoying.
I like that guy, too!
Haki?! Isn't that the technique that
Tonta-chief-sama!
...I'm a rubber man.
What are you doing?
you used to kick 50 thousand villains'
asses on the Fish-Man Island?!
He's just an untrained amateur boxer.
Gyats-san, you should be impartial!
That was awesome!
Tonta-chief-sama, she is a good person!
That's our hero!
Let's see what you got!
No way!
He's quite a fighter!
Your energy can shake up this kingdom!
But she said so herself.
Hey, shrimp!
What?!
Please, please eat this!
Alright!
Okay, then.
What did you just say?!
Bring it on!
It's a Fighting Fish.
It's big and a close relative of the goldfish.
Again?!
Everybody here is so credulous?!
Hmmm, we don't often have a chance to
stare at a Big Human like this.
Brother!
--A Fighting Fish?!
--Yes!
Good boy! Go, go!
Take them all down!
On this day,
What?!
How weak!
the story spread by the News Coos
It's good!
I didn't expect it to taste this good!
Who are you?
My name is Gancho.
I mean, maybe the Happo
Navy people are too strong!
takes the whole world by surprise again.
I'm the Tonta-chief, the king
It tastes like the sea monster
that I killed easily.
GANCHO
THE TONTA-CHIEF (THE KING)
OF THE TONTATTA KINGDOM
of the Tontatta Kingdom.
What a disappointment!
He became popular even under
a fake name! Straw Hat!
You can stay as long as you like.
An extra edition?!
You're not a powerful fighter
at all, you idiot! You fool!
It seems like a correction about something.
As I thought,
Hey! Hello!
What?!
they're the ones who
caught the Fighting Fish.
Gyats-san!
What a funny guy.
Do you want to eat some simmered pumpkins?
How could they do that?
These Little People are that strong?
That was easy!
Ah!
Go Ucy!
What the hell?!
Thank you! But I don't have time.
You're next, younger brother!
It's pretty big so it's several-months' worth of food
for everyone in this kingdom.
Here, here!
Wait! I won't fight.
A CANDIDATE FOR WARLORD
Captain, look at this!
Our tree sap cookies are delicious!
Oh?
What is it?
Usoland, you're a Big Human
so I guess you can eat a lot.
The big news about Doflamingo was...
Why don't you have tea with us?
I've never got into a
fight in my entire life!
I'm sorry. I have to go.
A mistake?!
Go to hell!
Do you want some grilled mushrooms?
--That's insane!
--How could this happen?
Luffyland who belongs to my
fighting force - the Usolanders,
Oh no, they're challenging Hajrudin!
Where is my Transponder Snail?
can eat the whole fish with one bite!
He turned his back?!
These brothers are the worst!
Do you wanna fight me?
Oh, crap! Run, Ucy!
Oh!
What's an Usoland?
I released it into the wild!
Ucy!
Look. Doesn't that look familiar?
The ax is broken!
This was not just some ax!
It was infused with Armament Haki!
Oh no! There is not much time until three!
Bull!
He's from the picture book
that we read in Jaya.
His body is strong!
I have to call Law!
Where can I get out?
NOLAND THE LIAR
Brother.
I must go!
Wait! Are you leaving?
Th-That bastard called me shrimp.
Is that a statue of Mont Blanc Noland?!
I thought that you were a good person!
If you're a good person, give us your weapon!
Just put it on already, Bobby!
Yes, it is!
That's the rule!
But I...
You know him, too, of course, don't you?
Answer me, Doflamingo!
What?
If you don't give it to us,
we're gonna strip you of all you have!
Okay.
You used the authority of the
He was a Big Human botanist who came
visit this kingdom 400 years ago.
But I don't have any weapon!
Bull!
World Government
to fool the whole world...
Lucy!
Then we have no choice.
What a disappointment!
At that time, our ancestors
were having a hard time
...just to deceive 10 or so of us?!
Oh, damn!
because the villainous Big Humans
were messing up this island.
Often, the more spectacular the magic,
the simpler the trick.
Wait!
We're gonna strip you of all you have!
And he fought with our ancestors
and led them to victory
What's going on?!
It was obviously a mismatch!
Take everything she has!
so he became the legendary hero of
the Tontatta Kingdom!
Boo!
Law.
The rookie from Elbaf...
When Usoland said his name
and told us that he's one of his descendants,
My sunglasses!
They're gone!
"That's ridiculous."
Boo from the Kano Kingdom
is taking quite a beating!
...crushed the Colosseum's Grim Reaper
and the unknown gladiator - Lucy.
Go!
I was speechless!
People usually have a stereotypical idea
L-Look at my head!
He's already passed out!
No! Wait a minute!
Gyats-san!
or an assumption like that
and that's what creates a blind spot.
This chestnut-like head is the proof!
Who's punching him?!
Is that the wimpy younger brother - Bobby?!
They couldn't do anything...
What's the matter?
--Oh yeah!
--The chestnut-like head!
Nobody can really do such a thing,
Or the weak older brother - Kelly?!
I didn't have any idea! I'm so sorry!
even if he hatched some scheme.
That Big Human is...
I guess that's the older one!
You're a horrible person.
...the hero's partner!
He got bigger and looks like a different man!
You were saved by it, too!
You're a pirate!
What?!
Even if you're a Warlord and a king,
Th-The hero?!
Let's eat and get some gifts and go!
Who did you call shrimp?
If I ever hear you say it again,
Usopp?
Who is the hero that you're talking about?
But this must be destiny.
you don't have the power to spread a lie
I will chew a hole in your throat!
I'm talking about the other Big Human
that we captured earlier.
To see them today.
all over the world!
Indeed!
He came to save us!
Wow! Lucy's helmet got knocked off!
Today is the day we vowed to fight
Doflamingo and after 400 years,
He's the legendary... legendary...
Hey, give it back!
I heard this strange story, Lucy.
The only people in this world
He's the legendary hero!
and a legendary hero came along again!
who have the power to do such
a ridiculous thing are...
I heard a pirate who's worth 400 million
named Straw Hat Luffy is...
Usoland! After you finish eating,
let's go to the Flower Field via underground passage!
That's good!
--Awesome!
--I wanna see him!
...the Celestial Dragons!
...secretly fighting in this competition.
Usopp... What did he tell them?
Let's go!
Yeah!
You don't know Joker's past.
At Dressrosa where we're gonna fight,
Straw Hat Luffy!
It's two fifty-seven.
And that will cost you your life!
the commander and our fellow soldiers of
the King Riku Army are expecting us!
We don't have time!
Yeah!
Don't tell me...
Please stand at the forefront and lead us!
The appointed time for Caesar's hand-over
from Law to Doflamingo is...
Don Chinjao is charging at something!
...you're...
Let's destroy the Don Quixote Family!
Garp, watch me!
...in...
Yeah!
I'm gonna kill your grandson!
With Usoland, we're unbreakable!
...two minutes.
It's bit more complicated.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Yeah!
Block C! There are approximately
40 contenders remaining!
Our hero!
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring,
ring, ring... Clank!
Hey, Law! This is Sanji!
It's narrowing down to the strongest!
Black Foot-ya! Did you find the factory?
I have only one purpose, Law.
Usoland?!
That's not important now!
What's wrong?
Listen carefully!
You've got to get out of there!
The Giant's been knocked down!
I just...
...wanted to kill you!
Who's gonna win this?!