Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the prize
for a fighting event was the Flare-Flare
Fruit, he decided to enter.
He's worth 77 million berries!
A member of the Straw
Hats! "Black Foot" Sanji!
Let's cut his head off!
Sanji was saved by Violet who
was working for Doflamingo,
and has found out some shocking news!
From the moment
you all arrived here with Caesar,
you were walking into that man's trap!
What you see is Dressrosa this morning.
What does this mean?
Alright! It's time finally!
Rebecca.
I saw the list in the Colosseum.
You entered the competition as I thought.
I told you not to!
I...
I'll do it! I'll win it!
Soldier-san!
So...
So... Hey, can we live together?!
A warrior who cries easily can't win
a competition!
Anesthetic flowers!
What's this smoke?
Meanwhile, after passing out
in the forest of Green Bit,
Robin woke up in the Tontatta Kingdom -
the country of the Little People.
The Big Human is waking up!
Don't try to run! Stay calm!
My body is pinned to the ground!
It's no use trying to move!
You're a villainous Big Human, aren't you?
So this is you Little People's kingdom.
It's two fifty-seven.
We don't have time!
"The Stratagem of the Century!
Doflamingo Makes His Move!"
GREEN BIT - THE BEACH ON THE SOUTHEAST SIDE
The appointed time
for Caesar's hand-over is...
...in two minutes.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank!
Hey, Law! This is Sanji!
Black Foot-ya! Did you find the factory?
That's not important now!
There he is! "Black Foot" Sanji!
Don't let the traitor
Violet get away, either!
--Kill them!
--This is it!
This way!
You assholes!
Black Foot!
Do you know what you're in for
if you hit Violet-chan?!
Listen carefully!
You've got to get out of there!
What are you talking about?
I have to hand Caesar over soon!
Doflamingo didn't resign
from the Seven Warlords!
Even if you hand Caesar over to him,
there is no trade whatsoever!
That doesn't make sense.
What do you mean?
We've been...
...totally deceived!
--Your Majesty!
--Please don't quit!
--Doflamingo-sama!
--We need your explanation!
Why did you abdicate from the throne?!
How noisy. Aren't they here yet?
Here they come.
What?!
A warship is arriving into the harbor!
I've seen that logo before!
Cipher Pol Aigis Zero!
They're the Government officials
who work directly under the World Nobles!
Why are they here?
Calm down, people of Dressrosa.
About the report on
Doflamingo's abdication from the throne
and the Seven Warlords that
spread all over the world...
It was a mistake. Just a false report.
That means...
Doflamingo-sama is not quitting!
That's great!
Now, we will let the world know about it
through an extra edition
of the newspaper at three today.
It's going to be a secret until then.
You mustn't tell anybody about it.
All nations, keep living peacefully
as if nothing has happened.
That wasn't a dream, wasn't it?
It all happened for real
right before you people
came to this island.
I can't believe it! I'm so confused!
The World Government?!
It's beyond a Warlord's control, isn't it?!
Yes, you're right.
I'm
scared of Doflamingo so I can't go
but maybe you people can get away in time!
Did you get that?!
Leave the island now!
The news about Doflamingo was a mistake?
What do you mean by that, Saka-san?
Are you saying the Navy Headquarters
were fooled by a false report?
Yes, it's so aggravating!
I'm going to go talk to
the Five Elders at Marie Jois.
I'm sorry but that's what happened.
I need you to keep going ahead to
Trafalgar Law and Doflamingo's
rendezvous point.
Roger that.
Clank.
All units! Go to the beach
on the southeast side!
Hurry up!
You fool. It's too late.
I'm busy, too! I'm gonna hang up now!
Clank!
There they are! Go after them!
What should I do?!
Wow! What the...
Nico Robin's upper half came out of the sand!
Nico-ya!
This is just a clone.
I was listening to the conversation.
It was Sanji, wasn't it?
Hey, where are your actual body and Nose-ya?
If what Black Foot-ya
was talking about is true,
the deal with Doflamingo is off.
Off?!
Then, what's gonna happen to my hand-over?!
It's not gonna happen!
No!
Nico-ya! Summon Nose-ya!
Let's get off of the island now!
The thing is, we're
underground Green Bit now!
Underground?!
We had some trouble...
But both Usopp and I are safe.
We can't help you but
if you're gonna escape,
go without us.
We'll go to the harbor
where we agreed to meet up.
Okay, I got it...
Th-The Navy!
You are Trafalgar Law-san, aren't you?
You're the new admiral,
Fujitora, aren't you?
Here he comes.
Good luck!
Good luck to you guys, too!
That's...
Joker!
Hey, Law!
Well done!
I didn't expect to see a Navy admiral here!
Since I'm no longer a Warlord,
I'm scared as hell!
Liar!
Now, all competitors of
Block C are out there finally!
139 warriors!
It's a battle royal!
Who's gonna win this?!
Finally!
Now, the battle is...
I can't believe you're already
in the ring, Straw Hat!
You're in Block D, aren't you, Cavendish?!
Are you trying to break in?!
Let go of me!
Cut it out! Or you'll get eliminated!
Let's do it!
Yeah!
Kick his ass!
Yes!
I'm gonna drop every single
one of you into the water!
Great!
Prepare to get crushed!
Huh?! Where did he go?!
That's a big hammer!
When did you get there?!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
That guy's arm stretched like rubber!
A Devil Fruit eater?!
A guy with the "Gum" power -
must be Straw Hat...
Oops.
I'm gonna fight you next!
Um...
This is just a normal punch!
That was close.
Did you just see it?
He's not Lucy! He's Straw Hat...
Stop it!
How annoying!
Gum-Gum...
--Huh?!
--He did it again!
Oh, never mind.
What the hell?!
Here's a normal kick!
What a pain in the butt.
Hey, that guy with a helmet is interesting!
Oh yeah?!
I've never seen him before.
Who is it?
Like I said, he's Straw Hat...
Go back to the bleachers!
Whoa! What are you doing?! Straw Hat!
That little one is quite strong.
Let's take care of him first.
Oh, they're coming all at once!
Go away!
You can't get away this time!
I got him!
That won't work.
Boom!
Because...
...I'm a rubber man.
That was awesome!
He's quite a fighter!
Alright!
Bring it on!
On this day,
the story spread by the News Coos
takes the whole world by surprise again.
An extra edition?!
It seems like a correction about something.
What?!
What the hell?!
A CANDIDATE FOR WARLORD
Captain, look at this!
What is it?
The big news about Doflamingo was...
A mistake?!
--That's insane!
--How could this happen?
Answer me, Doflamingo!
You used the authority of the
World Government
to fool the whole world...
...just to deceive 10 or so of us?!
Often, the more spectacular the magic,
the simpler the trick.
Law.
"That's ridiculous."
People usually have a stereotypical idea
or an assumption like that
and that's what creates a blind spot.
Nobody can really do such a thing,
even if he hatched some scheme.
You're a pirate!
Even if you're a Warlord and a king,
you don't have the power to spread a lie
all over the world!
The only people in this world
who have the power to do such
a ridiculous thing are...
...the Celestial Dragons!
You don't know Joker's past.
And that will cost you your life!
Don't tell me...
...you're...
It's bit more complicated.
I have only one purpose, Law.
I just...
...wanted to kill you!