iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the
prize for a fighting event
was the Flare-Flare Fruit, he decided to enter.
Meanwhile, Sanji found out that
Caesar's hand-over was Doflamingo's trap and...
Listen carefully!
We've been totally deceived!
I have only one purpose, Law.
I just wanted to kill you!
"Shaking Heaven and Earth!
Admiral Fujitora's Power!"
GREEN BIT - THE BEACH ON THE SOUTHEAST SIDE
Joker! Kick this guy's ass already...
I'm not gonna hand him over to you!
You didn't do anything that I asked you to!
Doflamingo! This deal is off!
No! Wh-What're you talking about, you fool?!
We got this far!
Is that how you talk to your boss
after 10 years of silence?
Leave him, Law.
Caesar is one of my precious subordinates.
Jo...
Issho-san, it's Caesar Clown who is with Law.
I see. He is the scientist from
the poison gas incident...
Joker!
But if he is that Warlord's subordinate,
he is not going to get charged.
They'll grant him amnesty.
It's you!
You are Fujitora, appointed as a Navy admiral
through the World Military Draft.
I hear a lot about you.
They say you're a monster who has
unquestionable power as well as Ryokugyu.
Oh, why thank you.
Don't play dumb.
I'm still new to the Navy so
it's hard for me to
understand what you're doing.
I don't have enough evidence yet
but I have some information about
you doing things that go against
the rules of the Seven Warlords.
The man right there was calling you "Joker" -
is that your nickname?
If you want to investigate me,
you have to be really determined
and collect enough evidence.
Now, what's the Navy's decision
about Law's punishment?
Regarding the news about you and
the wanted pirates, the Straw Hats,
if you're allying with them as they say in the news,
you're guilty!
If they have become your subordinates,
Law-san, you're...
...not guilty!
Our mission depends on your response.
We may have to arrest you and the Straw Hats.
H-Hey, what kind of decision is that?!
He can just get away by lying!
My original plan failed completely.
The Navy is targeting us now.
Even if I lie now and try to
take this matter to Dressrosa,
it only makes it worse.
I have to buy some time.
The Straw Hats are not working under me!
We're allies as you read in the paper!
You're such a clumsy man!
Then, we have to strip you of your title.
It'd be nice if the story ended there but...
No way!
Is it a meteorite?!
-D-Don't be ridiculous!
You've got to be kidding!
Run!
A meteorite is coming toward us!
Room!
I-I can't believe it.
Where's Issho-san?
What?! What happened in that moment?!
Only those three spots that they're standing
have no damage!
Issho-san...
How did the Fleet Admiral train you?!
You damn stray dog!
It doesn't matter if he can see or not.
Oh, thank you.
I just wanted to test your skills.
Now, I'm going to arrest you.
Is it okay, Law-san?
Don't tell me you're thinking
you can get away from me.
DRESSROSA - FRANKY AND THE OTHERS
The Flower Field?!
Are you gonna go on a picnic?!
What about you?!
Where have you been, Sanji?!
I've been...
...in love!
Oh, that's nice to hear.
By the way, I think I can find the factory.
Really?!
But unfortunately,
we can't just destroy it and get away.
It's gonna be a much bigger task
than we expected.
Hey, wait! We don't allow credit!
Somebody, catch that toy!
He ran away without paying!
Wait!
We don't have time!
Doflamingo was...
Yeah, I just read the extra edition.
He sure fooled us!
If he gets Caesar back,
our entire plan ends in failure!
Let's destroy the factory and
put his nose out of joint!
Anyway, you have to come meet us
at the Flower Field!
Why is the name of that
place so fairytale-ish?!
By the way, I can't reach Nami-san!
You still see her as weak?
She's gonna be fine!
Brook and Monster Chopper are with her!
--What is that?
--Huh? What's wrong?
Violet-chan, what is that?
That's a broadcast from the Colosseum.
An unknown gladiator, Lucy, is pretty strong!
--He's quite a fighter!
--Small but tough!
Franky, you won't believe
this but, Luffy is...
Yeah, he's fighting in a competition now.
Why did you let him?!
You should've kept an eye on him!
You're in no place to judge me!
You lost Zoro, didn't you?!
Black Foot, I have to go!
My men are coming after me!
You want to go to the
secret factory, don't you?
Here is a map.
It's disguised as "Toy House."
But that's the factory.
I can't take this!
If you help me more, you're gonna...
You're a funny man.
It doesn't make any difference.
It seems like the executives
already know that I betrayed them.
Violet-chan...
The western harbor! Meet me there!
Hide yourself there and
wait until I get there!
That's our rendezvous point!
I will help you get away
from here at any price!
You really are a good-for-nothing.
Sorry to interrupt, you good-for-nothing!
You fool! Where did you come from?!
Oh, Violet-chan?!
You have to beat them all up first.
There he is!
What are they doing on the street like this?!
So strong!
Why didn't you do it yourself?
I couldn't do anything because they're
holding Kanjuro as a hostage.
You have to come with me, Sanji-dono!
To the place called Toy House!
That's where they are keeping
my fellow samurai - Kanjuro!
I don't know where it is, though!
Count on me.
Entering from the general public,
no one really cared about him
but Lucy's doing really well!
Now, who's next?!
Oh, there is a strong
contender left! Who is it?
The bull from earlier?!
Alright! Do you wanna fight me?!
Oh, now Brutal Bull is facing
the unstoppable Lucy!
Brutal Bull fought death row prisoners
in this Colosseum the other day!
They will free the one of us who kills it
from death row.
This is a chance that doesn't come twice!
I killed so many tough
guys before I got caught!
I'm gonna kill this one!
No, I am!
He killed more than half of
the prisoners in the fight!
He's certainly a killer bull!
The Colosseum's Grim Reaper!
Because of his behavior, people call him Brutal Bull!
He's charging at Lucy!
But Lucy is just standing still!
Did he get paralyzed with fear?!
Brutal Bull stabbed him with his horns...
Hey. I'm here!
L-Lucy fended it off!
I'm over here! Come on!
B-Brutal Bull... s-stopped?!
What did Lucy do? What happened?!
I like you!
Let's do this together!
I-I can't believe it!
He's riding on the Colosseum's Grim Reaper!
What a man! Lucy!
BACK IN GREEN BIT
UNDER THE FOREST
THE TONTATTA KINGDOM
Why is it shaking?
It must be Law and the others.
Damn! I don't wanna die here!
--What?!
--The hero is getting upset!
J-Just kidding.
The truth is the shake was...
...caused by my Haki!
Haki?! Isn't that the technique that
you used to kick 50 thousand villains'
asses on the Fish-Man Island?!
That's our hero!
Your energy can shake up this kingdom!
Please, please eat this!
It's a Fighting Fish.
It's big and a close relative of the goldfish.
--A Fighting Fish?!
--Yes!
It's good!
I didn't expect it to taste this good!
It tastes like the sea monster
that I killed easily.
As I thought,
they're the ones who
caught the Fighting Fish.
How could they do that?
These Little People are that strong?
It's pretty big so it's several-months' worth of food
for everyone in this kingdom.
Usoland, you're a Big Human
so I guess you can eat a lot.
Luffyland who belongs to my
fighting force - the Usolanders,
can eat the whole fish with one bite!
What's an Usoland?
Look. Doesn't that look familiar?
He's from the picture book
that we read in Jaya.
NOLAND THE LIAR
Is that a statue of Mont Blanc Noland?!
Yes, it is!
You know him, too, of course, don't you?
He was a Big Human botanist who came
visit this kingdom 400 years ago.
At that time, our ancestors
were having a hard time
because the villainous Big Humans
were messing up this island.
And he fought with our ancestors
and led them to victory
so he became the legendary hero of
the Tontatta Kingdom!
When Usoland said his name
and told us that he's one of his descendants,
I was speechless!
L-Look at my head!
This chestnut-like head is the proof!
--Oh yeah!
--The chestnut-like head!
I didn't have any idea! I'm so sorry!
You're a horrible person.
You were saved by it, too!
Let's eat and get some gifts and go!
But this must be destiny.
To see them today.
Indeed!
Today is the day we vowed to fight
Doflamingo and after 400 years,
and a legendary hero came along again!
Usoland! After you finish eating,
let's go to the Flower Field via underground passage!
Let's go!
Yeah!
At Dressrosa where we're gonna fight,
the commander and our fellow soldiers of
the King Riku Army are expecting us!
Yeah!
Please stand at the forefront and lead us!
Let's destroy the Don Quixote Family!
Yeah!
With Usoland, we're unbreakable!
Our hero!
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
Usoland?!