Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the prize for a
fighting event was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
he decided to enter.
Finally, the match for Block C
which Luffy registered for, started!
Do you wanna fight me?
Oh, crap! Run, Ucy!
Ucy!
What a disappointment!
The Giant's been knocked down!
"Destruction Cannon Blasts!
Lucy in trouble!"
That was awesome, Lucy!
Can't help getting more excited as we go on!
He came in and stirred things up in Block C!
Lucy did it again!
Thank you for fighting together with me.
Let me carry you to the
side of the ring, Ucy.
I believe this guy still
has a lot more to show!
What else is new?
I can't believe it!
I didn't expect he'd be that strong!
Lucy!
Hey, Giant man! You're still in the ring.
If you wanna take a nap, you better get out!
You're in my way!
Hajrudin's enormous body's been
blown up by an explosion?!
What just happened?!
No, it wasn't an explosion!
Hajrudin got eliminated
but there are still many tough ones in Block C!
That was an explosive punch
powered by some odd-shaped shoulders!
Ideo!
The one who blew away the
Giant's huge body was...
"DESTRUCTION CANNON" IDEO
AN XXX RANK BOXER
...the two-time champion of...
...the New World Central Fighting Tournament!
"Destruction Cannon" Ideo!
--Ideo's strong!
--Yeah, amazing!
Cut the "two-time champion" crap!
The past record from
other competitions doesn't matter!
You're right.
What matters is...
...how strong you are!
And I'm stronger than you.
I'm gonna win this thing!
I'm gonna be the champion!
Meanwhile, elsewhere in Dressrosa...
I'm so surprised!
You're unbelievably terrible with directions!
Shut up! It was just a slight mistake!
"Slight"?!  That wasn't "slight"!
You've gone in the opposite direction
from where I told you 27 times!
You ran down stairs that
you just climbed up 31 times!
It was not "slight" at all!
We're moving away from the Flower Field
rather than getting closer!
Pull yourself together!
Shut up! It's your fault
because you suck at leading the way!
No...
It's your fault!!
--What the...
He jumped up and fell down himself.
Ouch!
What do you think you're doing?!
What happened to him all of a sudden?
Who is he yelling at?
So creepy. Let's go.
I have to tell my people where the
members of the Don Quixote Family
are, as soon as possible!
So pull yourself together!
Don't you get it?!
You're gonna break my bones!
You're too strong to lose control like that!
I have friends that I care about, too!
Stop complaining or
go ask some damn cat to carry you!
Hey!
This place looks familiar... Or not...
Is this...
Where am I?
You already got lost?
A-Are you some kind of idiot?!
Who are you calling an idiot?!
Please! Take me to my people!
All right.
You're going the wrong way!
Let's go!
Okay!
And at Green Bit...
Room!
Only a Warlord could do that.
Damn you, Fujitora. He's mine to kill.
Bullet String!
You wanna play tag, Law?
Let's chase them.
Yes, sir!
I know what you're doing, Law.
You're trying to buy some time, aren't you?
I'm not gonna let you have it your way.
Lucy and Ideo's one-on-one fight!
This should be an interesting match-up!
Take this!
What the... Your punch is like a bomb.
I'm not satisfied with my power yet.
I want to get to the top of the ladder!
So I want to be stronger!
By eating the prize of this competition -
the Flare-Flare Fruit!
I'm not gonna let you have Ace's fruit.
I will win it!
No, I'm gonna be the champion!
This is hot!
What a breathtakingly heated battle!
But that's not the only fight
you want to keep an eye on!
Now, take a look!
Those three gangs from the
Kano Kingdom in the far east
are very unique, too!
It's no use!
There you go!
You can't protect yourself from it!
SAI - THE 13TH LEADER OF THE HAPPO NAVY -
A GANG FROM THE KANO KINGDOM
The Eight-Impact Fist that allows
them to manipulate an impact!
Shields and armor are useless against them!
With centuries of history,
the Happo Navy is...
BOO - THE VICE LEADER OF THE HAPPO NAVY -
A GANG FROM THE KANO KINGDOM
...just unbeatable!
If we can kill you,
it's almost as big a prize as
winning this competition, Chinjao!
Boy...
Go home and train yourselves more
before coming back, punks!
FORMERLY THE 12TH LEADER
OF THE HAPPO NAVY (RETIRED)
- A GANG FROM THE KANO KINGDOM
DON CHINJAO
That was Conqueror's Haki!
No wonder!
He used to be a pirate
worth 500 million! He's the legend!
There is only one man that I want to fight!
Don't get in my way!
Thank you, Chinjao!
There are so many nice weapons to pick up!
Whoa!
That man didn't get beaten
by Don Chinjao's Haki
and he's now picking up weapons in the ring!
JEAN ANGO AKA JEAN THE BANDIT
A BOUNTY HUNTER
He is a dark horse in this competition -
Jean the Bandit!
A bounty hunter that all big-time pirates
in the New World
hold a grudge against!
Wait, you shithead!
Now that I found you, your number is up!
I won't forgive you
for sending my partner to prison!
These weapons that
I picked up will make nice bullets.
I'm a sniper after all!
If that partner guy was so important to you,
you should've shown your
mettle by raiding the prison!
Like the idiot who actually did it
a couple years ago.
Hey! That guy has already passed out!
How much more is he gonna punch him?!
Hey, stop, brother!
He's already knocked out!
That's enough!
I restrained the wrong person.
This bastard! He called me shorty!
THE FUNK BROTHERS
ASSASSINS FROM THE MOGARO KINGDOM
Hey, Bobby, am I a shorty?! Huh?!
No, you're not! You're a big man!
Say something, you dickhead!
Brother! That's enough!
I restrained the wrong person.
KELLY FUNK
THE OLDER OF THE TWO BROTHERS
If I ever hear you say it again,
I'll gouge your eyes out!
Don't keep trying to stop me, Bobby!
BOBBY FUNK
THE YOUNGER OF THE TWO BROTHERS
But this is a competition, brother.
The Funk Brothers are so brutal!
They're assassins well known
in the underground community!
I heard they're very powerful fighters and
they even killed some pirates
worth over a 100 million!
I don't care if it's a competition
or not! I'm not short!
How annoying.
He's just an untrained amateur boxer.
Let's see what you got!
Hey, shrimp!
What did you just say?!
Brother!
What?!
How weak!
I mean, maybe the Happo
Navy people are too strong!
What a disappointment!
You're not a powerful fighter
at all, you idiot! You fool!
Gyats-san!
That was easy!
You're next, younger brother!
Wait! I won't fight.
I've never got into a
fight in my entire life!
Go to hell!
He turned his back?!
These brothers are the worst!
The ax is broken!
This was not just some ax!
It was infused with Armament Haki!
His body is strong!
Brother.
Th-That bastard called me shrimp.
Just put it on already, Bobby!
What?
Okay.
Oh, damn!
Wait!
What's going on?!
Boo!
Boo from the Kano Kingdom
is taking quite a beating!
He's already passed out!
Who's punching him?!
Is that the wimpy younger brother - Bobby?!
Or the weak older brother - Kelly?!
I guess that's the older one!
He got bigger and looks like a different man!
Who did you call shrimp?
If I ever hear you say it again,
I will chew a hole in your throat!
Wow! Lucy's helmet got knocked off!
Hey, give it back!
I heard this strange story, Lucy.
I heard a pirate who's worth 400 million
named Straw Hat Luffy is...
...secretly fighting in this competition.
Straw Hat Luffy!
Don Chinjao is charging at something!
Garp, watch me!
I'm gonna kill your grandson!
Block C! There are approximately
40 contenders remaining!
It's narrowing down to the strongest!
Who's gonna win this?!