Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the prize for
When Luffy found out that the prize for a
fighting event was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
When Luffy found out that the
prize for a fighting event
a fighting event was the Flare-Flare
Fruit, he decided to enter.
When Luffy found out that the
prize for a fighting event
he decided to enter.
was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
Finally, the match for Block C
which Luffy registered for, started!
he decided to enter and fight
fierce battles against other tough
was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
he decided to enter and fight
fierce battles against other
he decided to enter and fight fierce battles
contenders from the New World.
Brother.
"Light and Shadow!
Darkness behind Dressrosa!"
Meanwhile, at the Tontatta
Kingdom in Green Bit,
tough contenders from the New World.
among other tough contenders from the New World.
Th-That bastard called me shrimp.
where the Little People reside...
Stop whining over one punch!
"Chinjao the Drill."
That's what they used to
call me but not anymore.
Alright, everybody! Let's get going!
I can't count how many times
I got punched by him!
Just put it on already, Bobby!
With our hero Usoland!
It seems like those famous tough warriors
have been knocked out by...
I'm going to smash you
to the marrow of your bones!
I heard this strange story, Lucy.
Answer me!
To take back the 500 friends
who are held captive!
Do you know what Garp has done to me?!
Eight-Impact Fist Technique!
I heard a pirate who's worth 400 million
named Straw Hat Luffy is...
...the impact from the epic
clash of those two men
Don Quixote Doflamingo has
been causing us Tontatta Tribe
I told you - I don't know!
and have been taken out of the fight!
Gum-Gum...
a lot of pain recently.
Since you're that bastard Garp's grandson,
But what did we actually see?!
...secretly fighting in this competition.
...Thor...
But our connection with him
goes way back before last decade, actually.
I can't just let you walk away
because you have no idea!
Non-Drill Dragon...
...Elephant Gun!
I didn't know you could use Conqueror's Haki!
"The Legendary Pirate!
Don Chinjao!"
...Non-Nail!
For 30 years,
It goes back about 900 years ago.
What kind of king are you dreaming to become?!
I've been holding a grudge!
The King of the Pirates!
Shut up!
Meanwhile, at the King Riku
Army Headquarters where
Now, the battle for Block C
is reaching its final phase!
There are so many in the New World
who can use that power!
anti-Doflamingo protesters are assembling...
Who's gonna win it?!
Take a look at the hot contenders!
Hey, don't let him attack you, Luffy!
Whaaat?!
Damn, that bastard!
And only battling it out amongst you all
will determine the winner!
Say it, Straw Hat!
What has Garp done to me?!
The assassin from Mogaro - Kelly Funk!
If there is an event like this, why didn't he tell me?!
The strongest among a legion of "Conquerors"!
He is unstoppable now!
I wanna fight with my swords!
Boo has been knocked out completely
after Kelly battered him!
Give me back Caesar's heart already.
That's who the King of the Pirates is!
What did he take away from me?!
What a man!
Sai is approaching Boo.
Will the "Eight-Impact
Fist" be defeated here?!
He beat the legend and
won the fierce battle for Block C!
It's so meaningless for you
to keep hanging on here.
Hey soldier, what's your point?
What's going on here?
Meanwhile, Ideo is blowing through and
Who taught you how to use the Haki?
beating tough contenders one after another!
Lucy the Gladiator!
Your partner - Straw Hat has already
walked into the trap that I set up.
What I wanted to show you is...
Can't anybody stop this man?!
Rayleigh!
Yeah!
...this country is filled with both
Is he still alive?!
the forgotten and those who forgot them!
And Don Chinjao keeps charging
ahead in a fit of anger!
He will never come out
alive from the Colosseum.
How annoying!
All of us toys were once humans!
And, and, and,
"Luffy and the Gladiator of Fate - Rebecca!"
I don't even want to think about
what happened in the past!
this guy is stirring things up in this competition!
It's the end of your alliance.
What?!
Lucy is the center of everybody's attention!
Law!
A Devil Fruit eater who Doflamingo
brought 10 years ago,
He landed a powerful kick against Lucy!
He is now desperately
chasing Jean the Bandit!
Just give up!
THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
Even though he's already retired,
The battle royal at the Corrida Colosseum!
turned us to toys!
Wait!
the strength of the 12th leader
of the Happo Navy remains!
You! Cactus! Give me back my helmet!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Now, three contenders have
"The Fierce Battle Coming to the End!
Lucy vs. Chinjao!"
gotten the chance to challenge
the Don Quixote Family!
What?
Damn that bastard!
What is she doing?! Pick up already!
Whaaat?!
Wait, you brat!
Garp's grandson!
Whoa! He's coming after me!
The winner of Block A is
the "champion" of the Blackbeard Pirates,
Your grandpa is Garp? So you're really him!
Tell me, Straw Hat.
Jesus Burgess!
I want to forget but it's always
right there in front of me!
Get out of my way!
Oh? Where is he?
You have no mercy!
But it's out of my reach! My treasure!
Where did he go?! Garp's grandson!
I'm all thumbs so...
Can you imagine anything harder than that?!
From Block B,
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Give me back my helmet!
the captain of a pirate group, Barto Club,
Bartolomeo the Cannibal!
Why is she not picking up?! Nami-ya!
They call me Jean the Bandit!
I'd never give back what I stole!
I know I'm not calling the wrong number!
What's going on?! The legendary pirate is...
Gum-Gum...
Eight-Impact Fist!
...Jet Pistol!
And from Block C,
...crying!
Oh no! My beard!
It's Usoland's Haki!
everybody's favorite gladiator - Lucy!
Gum-Gum...
So powerful!
...Jet Gatling!
Why are you panicking?
Grandpa...
Look, my body trembles with excitement
so the ground is shaking!
That was close!
I thought the plan was to
let Sai move into the final!
Why are you hiding your face?
Only one more contender can advance
to the championship.
B-Because...
I'm still not strong enough.
You can't say it?
How awesome!
Nobody can stop him once he's at it!
There is only one reason
why you can't say it.
However, due to the extensive
damage to the ring,
He's unbelievable!
the start of the battle for Block D
will be delayed by 15 minutes.
That's because you are...
...Straw Hat Luffy!
By the way, Leo,
you people keep saying "fight" but...
Yeah!
Just fix it up already!
"Chinjao the Drill."
No, I'm not! I'm Lucy!
Don't you have a backup ring?!
That's what they used to
call me but not anymore.
Please wait for a while,
for the Block D match.
...why do you wanna fight Doflamingo?
Charitable Donation!
What?
The hero's very funny!
Answer me!
We want to rescue the 500 friends who are
Do you know what Garp has done to me?!
Oh? Where did he go? Where's my helmet?
forced to work
at the shady factory, of course!
I told you - I don't know!
Hey! Where are you, Cactus?!
Since you're that bastard Garp's
grandson, I can't just let you
Straw Hat!
The battle will take place in Dressrosa!
walk away because you have no idea!
You can't run this time!
I can't believe that
Straw Hat really entered this event.
Underneath the Colosseum!
At the shady factory!
Cabbage!
Gum-Gum...
Let's go, everybody!
For 30 years,
Durandal!
But I have a chance to win.
...Jet Stamp Gatling!
Yeah!
I've been holding a grudge!
Because there are so many
weapons I can steal.
Don't try to get away!
You fool!
I know I can beat him with my shooting skill.
"Making a Sortie!
The Legendary Hero Usoland!"
Cavendish is going at it again!
I'm gonna collect as many
weapons as I can and...
He's showing his fighting spirit again!
THE TONTATTA KINGDOM - UNDERNEATH GREEN BIT
Go Lucy!
Don Chinjao!
...I will defeat Straw Hat Luffy!
That bastard!
Say it, Straw Hat!
What has Garp done to me?!
Kick his ass, Chinjao!
What's going on?
Cactus... Where did he go?
Usoland! Usoland!
He's yelling "Straw Hat" again!
They're exchanging fierce punches and kicks!
Straw Hat is the pirate who couldn't even
Usoland! Usoland!
What a fight!
What?! What? What? What's going on?!
save his brother's life in the
War of the Best, isn't he?
What did he take away from me?!
How strong!
Usoland! Usoland!
The contenders are getting blown
away like sheets of paper!
Anyone could do what
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!...
He's crying again!
It's Kelly Funk who is punching them!
he did if he doesn't have
to save anybody's life!
This old man is such a pain in the ass.
Rah-Rah-Rah Rampage!
Where did Bobby go?
I can't tell if he wants to cry or be mad.
Wh-What are you doing?!
Cut it out, you fool!
Kelly got bigger and surprisingly stronger!
It's too fast and I can't even
see what's going on anymore!
I'm a noble of the Kingdom of Biggschots!
I don't know what is going on anymore!
Going underground?
I saw it! I sure did!
What was that all about?!
Stop it!
That's right.
My body's gonna be crushed!
Go Lucy! Now's the chance!
But I can feel their fighting spirit!
There is an underground passage
between Green Bit and Dressrosa.
What was that joke you just made,
so lightheartedly?
He... The one that's fighting right now...
I'm sure what we're seeing now is...
Luffy-dono!
Is he Kelly or Bobby?!
I don't have time for this!
So we're gonna go through the passage
and meet up with your friends?
Sanji-dono, I want to get to the
Bobby and Kelly... The two became one!
That is correct!
Toy House to rescue Kanjuro already!
...one of the greatest fights ever
in this Colosseum!
Listen!
Are they really gonna fight Doflamingo?!
Jacket-Jacket Two-in-a-Coat!
The Straw Hat Luffy-senpai
I wanna help you with that
but you have to wait.
will eventually be
the standard-bearer of this era!
Here we are! At the airport!
We have a situation here.
He's gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Look how many Navy soldiers
there are around the Colosseum.
You're quite a fighter.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Why are there so many?
It was more than two years ago...
It seems like pirates and criminals are
freely entering this competition.
You're strong, too, as I thought.
Wh-What the hell are they doing?!
Put me on already!
An army of bugs!
The Navy is here to catch them
as they come out.
At Loguetown in the East Blue,
What did you say?!
Huh?
How cute!
Uh-huh.
What's going on with them?!
on the legendary scaffold where the
King of the pirates, Roger, died,
Well, criminals should be caught.
What did you just say?!
Yellow Cub 43 through 48
are prepared for takeoff.
I'm strong?!
Brother, like I said before,
I don't want to fight.
Don't forget that you
were on the pirate ship!
he shouted it out in that
desperate situation!
Are you trying to insult me?!
Idiot! Just stop thinking like always
Keep standing by.
Oh yeah!
I'm the man who'll be King of the Pirates!!
What?! I just said "You're strong"!
Pink Bee 21, 22, 25, 26, proceed to Runway B.
We have to tell Luffy about this situation
and put me on!
As far as I'm concerned, that's an insult!
but the entrance for the competitors is
completely closed off.
Bobby was born with such a strong body,
I'm no better than a wolf
without its fangs now.
but it was wasted on him - he's such a wimp!
This is Yellow Cub 43. Ready to takeoff!
What's going on here-dara?
I mean, a skin-headed man without his drill!
43, cleared for takeoff.
However, when he puts me on as his "skin,"
At that moment, straight from heaven...
I can take over his personality
A brat like you can't understand
how miserable I feel living my life like this!
No one has come out
from the Colosseum yet-dara?
and show my fighting skills and
Pink Bee Squad, ready to go!
brutality at full
with his body!
Pink Bee, roger that.
No, sir. Not yet.
All bugs, stand by and wait
for further instruction.
There must be hundreds of losers
from Block A and B-dara!
I'm frustrated, disappointed, and sad!
Oh, Usoland, watch your step!
Why hasn't even a single one of them
come out-dara?
Sorry!
But you can never understand!
Cub-san! Bian!
...came a bolt of thunder
which saved his life!
It's strange.
Leo, you're late!
Vice Admiral Maynard went undercover as a competitor
How can I understand?!
CUB - A LEADER OF YELLOW CUB SQUAD
(BUG-BUG FRUIT, MODEL RHINOCEROS BEETLE)
"SHARK SLICER" BASTILLE
- A NAVY VICE ADMIRAL
You just keep messing with me
without explaining anything!
The guy from earlier?!
but we haven't had any contact with him for a while.
I'm a jacket human
who ate the Jacket-Jacket Fruit!
Why did he do that on his own?
We're ready to go!
Do you really want to know
why I've become like this?!
BIAN - A LEADER OF PINK BEE SQUAD
(BUG-BUG FRUIT, MODEL HORNET)
We're gonna fly at high speed!
That punk!
Whether it's an animal or a monster,
Is something going on...
once someone puts me on,
I get control over all of him!
I'll be counting on you two!
No, I'm not that interested.
...in the Colosseum-dara?
Bobby is wearing me
so we're one in body and mind now!
I'm still alive after all. I got lucky.
Leave it to us!
Well then, I'm gonna tell you before you die
since you insist.
Squad members have been
training so hard for today!
What I saw was a miracle.
We're the Funk Brothers!
It was 30 years ago.
To save our friends and Princess Mancherie,
So you're saying you can't fight on your own!
Here in Dressrosa, there are two laws...
we had no other choice!
Yeah!
...that people have obeyed strictly
I've been following
Uh-huh!
news stories on the Straw Hats
from that day on.
I've never seen this kind.
since Doflamingo came to the throne 10 years ago.
What did you say to me earlier?
Alabasta, Enies Lobby,
I wanna show it to Luffy!
--Two laws?
--Yes.
Huh? I'll say it as many times as you want!
Usoland! Robiland!
Impel Down!
First, lights should be out by midnight.
You two are big so take the 20 passenger bus.
You can't fight on your own!
And the fateful event...
Not that! You called me shrimp!
Citizens must not go out after that.
...at Marineford! It was all fascinating!
What?! Even adults?!
Come on, Linear Foxes!
What the hell is wrong with this ice?!
Rah-Rah-Rah Rampage!
Humans have to go back to their homes
We can't break it with fire or an ax!
and toys have to go back to their toy houses.
LINEAR FOXES - TWENTY-MAN BUS
(KON EXPRESS)
No one's allowed to go out after midnight.
Rah-Rah-Rah Rampage!
Boss! What should we do with
the soldiers that we defeated.
You can't even go for a drink!
But look at all that unbelievable pirate treasure
under the ice!
Dump them into water or something.
Everything is closed anyway.
This is nice! It's like a couch for a king!
I was just some leader of a
Second,
gangland who took control
of 150 towns back home
toys must not enter human's houses
They're fast when they run.
and humans must not enter toy's houses!
Such beautiful hair!
but I've been inspired by Luffy-senpai and...
How's that?
What?!
Do you realize how strong I am?!
You can't make a scratch
with what you have there,
It looks like they're
friendly with each other
...sailed out to the sea!
even if you keep trying for 100 years!
It was over before I knew it!
but that's prohibited?!
This continent is made of what
they call "Crystal Ice Sheet"
Alright, everybody! Let's get going!
But if that's the sad boundary between
With our hero Usoland!
and to break it,
artifacts and living things, it can't be helped.
you have to put tremendous
pressure on one spot!
Well, come to think of it,
I'm kind of getting used to it already but...
Now, why don't you say it again?
Drill Dragon Nail!
They're all weak!
...what kind of toys are you guys?
Hey!
You shut your eyes to your crappiness
Oh, you're the older of the brothers
from the Kano Kingdom!
To take back the 500 friends
who are held captive!
You have free will and you can talk.
and said something about Luffy-senpai
like you're better than him!
Whoever made you all should
be a genius like Vegapunk.
Open Chinjao!
Yeah!
I beat your brother in a second!
Is this the tongue you used to say it?
Who was it?
We brothers are working together
and killing people for living!
Somebody, call the police!
You think you're capable of doing anything?!
What's going on?!
You worthless shit!
--Please! Let go of me!
--Esta, it's me!
You're so pathetic!
It's really fast!
Bartolomeo is at it, too!
The toy's broken! It's got "human disorder"!
You can't even save your own brother!
I think I have to tell you two...
Listen to me! It's not that!
He lost because he trained himself poorly.
Don't you remember, Esta?!
Don't be so hard on him.
...why we want to do this.
It's me!
Get away from me! You're freaking me out!
Where're you coming out from?!
You're gonna get beaten just like he was!
Let it go!
What happened all of a sudden?!
Gancho-san!
I won't!
Boobie-morning! I'm the Tonta-chief - Gancho!
You've been friendly with her until now!
Please! Try to remember!
Rah-Rah-Rah Rampage!
Thank you for doing this!
Do you like it there, you thieves?
Get away from her!
Get your hands off of my sword already!
Isn't the martial art of
the Kano Kingdom strong?!
Why should I fight you in the first place?!
I want you to know since you're gonna risk
Come with us!
Huh?!
I'm tired!
your life fighting for us.
Damn!
Esta! I'm your boyfriend!
You can't even talk because you're
moaning about your brother?!
No, I'm not gonna risk my life...
Don Quixote Doflamingo has
been causing us Tontatta Tribe
From the moment I became a disciple
in order to learn the Eight-Impact Fist,
Don't hook up with that bastard!
a lot of pain recently.
Guys, tie those treasure thieves up
and dump them into the sea!
I have had no emotional
attachment to my brother!
You know who I am! Remember me!
But our connection with him
goes way back before last decade, actually.
Okay, Boss!
--Let go of me! Dammit!
--Calm down!
But,
Don't!
Hey, stop them!
Lots of happiness!
No! Don't!
We can't approach them!
It's too dangerous!
CHINJAO THE DRILL
THE 12TH LEADER OF A PIRATE GROUP - THE HAPPO NAVY
(30 YEARS AGO)
This room of ice contains everything.
It goes back about 900 years ago.
H-He's right! I can't approach him.
When it comes to it, I can't do it.
as the 13th leader of the Happo Navy,
Joys and sorrows from the past.
Hopes for the future.
No! Let go of me, you bastards!
I'm too nervous to go anywhere near him.
What?!
Several decades worth of
my family's treasures!
I will avenge my subordinate!
The scar under his left eye... It's real!
I'm a human!
My drill head is the only key to the room.
Here in Dressrosa, there
is a vast sunflower field.
He's really cool!
Oh? My eyes are blind with tears.
Somewhere in that field
of blooming sunflowers,
That stupid cabbage shit!
at a place no one knows,
Nobody can invade this place!
Not even the Navy!
I wanna beat him to death
and save Luffy-senpai!
there is a secret entrance.
Hey you, Cav... Cavendi...
Descend the stairs there,
That was scary!
I can't! I can't even speak!
Boy...
Hey, Chinjao!
In order to break your head today,
I can't believe that toy thinks he's a human.
and you will hear energetic voices.
I know.
Hey, Straw Hat!
I've trained myself by destroying
about eight mountains
What was it all about?
S...
Where's this connecting to?
Let me ride you, Onepoko!
S...
Listen!
You'll see soon.
like they were my punching bags!
Our old man wants to say something to you!
No-wan! You're too heavy now-wan!
S...
It's no use!
Strong!
Onepoko!
Let me introduce!
There is not a thing in the world
harder than my head!
Grandpa, are you okay?!
I'm not heavy!
Onepoko!
Commander!
What?! Leave me alone! I won!
Prepare for it, Chinjao!
We've been waiting for you, Commander!
The Eight-Impact Fist!
Let me go talk to him.
He showed off what it takes to be the leader!
I'm gonna break that fist of yours
that you're so proud of, Garp!
Thanks, you all!
Nobody could stop the monster, Kelly,
No!
but he took him down with a single kick!
AN ANTI-DOFLAMINGO COALITION -
"THE KING RIKU ARMY" HEADQUARTERS
Until we accomplish our true purpose,
I can't lose.
He looks like a strong toy man!
What kind of Big Human was he?!
Dammit! Where did he go?
Don't worry. He's a toy, too.
I don't even hold a grudge
against Garp anymore.
It's good to have him on
the day of the battle!
Well, yeah, a half of me is.
I want to express my deepest
appreciation to you.
Hmmm, Onepoko's got it!
We're gonna fight with them!
Let me say thank you...
They're Little People from the Tontatta Kingdom!
Who are you?
I have no doubt.
You're the strongest in this block.
Little People?
They're as strong as you are.
Wait, Garp's grandson!
They move so fast that
people can barely see them.
You should not praise your enemy!
I'm that boy's father.
And that woman is my wife.
Wait, Straw Hat!
So they call them "fairies" in the town.
Well, I wanted to face a
strong opponent like you.
My name is Milo, not Onepoko.
He just passed by me!
So the one who stole Zoro's sword was...
Excuse me... Wait!
Hey, you can't run from a fight!
What?!
Hey boy, don't you have a daddy?
I will defeat you, the strongest here,
Let's go!
Wh-Wh-What should I do?!
What should I do?!
Huh? No, I don't!
I thought that you wanted
to go back to your ship!
Boss!
and advance to the top!
I wanna talk to him but how can I?!
Do you have a husband?
He did it!
Hey, don't let him attack you, Luffy!
No, I don't. I'm not married.
Shut the fuck up!
Please wait!
Young man, I can't see!
In appreciation for restoring my head,
It's not so unusual, is it?
--Let's leave!
--All ships, set sail!
Zoro!
It was such a pain just to get here!
Stop!
I want you to put my grandson's Happo Navy
under you command.
Bye bye!
Let's get going!
Hold on tight, Momo-chan!
Let's go to your ship!
You're some kind of idiot
like I said, aren't you?!
Wait!
Straw Hats! Just give up!
Hey soldier, what's your point?
What's going on here?
Damn, that bastard!
What's wrong with them?!
It's not beautiful to keep fighting a losing battle!
If there is an event like
this, why didn't he tell me?!
So persistent!
--Wait!
With my Art-Art Fruit power,
Please wait!
I wanna fight with my swords!
I turned your ship to an art
piece like this, so now,
What I wanted to show you is...
Oh, Commander!
Oh, Franky!
Boss!
you can't get away from Dressrosa!
Can't you see it?!
Boss! I'm glad that you're okay!
...this country is filled
with both the forgotten
What are you doing here?
and those who forgot them!
Commander, we already sorted out the intelligence
from the scouting unit!
Hand Momonosuke over to us already!
Boy... There's no place that
I can feel comfortable.
All of us toys were once humans!
It's no use trying to get away
leaving your ship behind!
We know what the enemies and Sugar are doing.
"Get away"?
This way, Lucy!
And, no big surprise, with
the battle close at hand...
Hey, where did the others go?!
What?!
Where's the skeleton and the raccoon?
Oh, you're...
A Devil Fruit eater
who Doflamingo brought 10 years ago,
It's Rebecca.
That's right!
Some legendary heroes have appeared at Tontatta!
You have so many enemies!
Follow me!
Wh-What is it?!
turned us to toys!
Oh, thanks!
We're here!
The drill...
Their names are Usoland and Robiland!
Where is my drill?!
Hey! That means you were...
Hello!
They say they're on their way here!
When did you get there?!
Okay, bye!
On top of that, they have
some friends with them
There!
By that logic, Shiryu is no different!
Oh? Where did the brat
from the Wano Kingdom go?!
I see the Flower Field!
I'll tell you everything there!
and their names are...
The woman's gone, too!
...Luffyland, Zoroland, Namiland, Sanland...
What?!
What the hell is this?
Where did my drill go?!
...Chopperland, Fraland, and Boneland!
I didn't notice those at all!
What are they?!
Must be Usopp!
Why did he tell such a lie?
Um, I think I'm Zoroland.
Open Chinjao!
Thunder clouds?!
I'm Fraland! Nice to meet you!
Thunderbreed Tempo!
Drill Dragon Nail!
What?! Great!
Open Chinjao!
Hey! You people are so annoying!
They're so naive.
But I can't trust Aokiji!
Drill Dragon Nail!
Oh, I don't have time for this!
Open! Drill Dragon Nail!
My submarine! My people!
I gotta get back to the Sunny!
Nami and the others are in danger!
Open! Drill Dragon Nail!
I kept telling you so, didn't I?!
Oh, hold on a sec, Captain.
No matter how tough the situation is,
we're not gonna get away
leaving the Sunny behind!
--Boss!
--Please stop, Boss!
The Sunny?!
Straw Hat is here.
Although he's already retired,
Now, let's get it back!
You're gonna die!
his Eight-Impact Fist is still
as sharp as it used to be!
Yeah!
Open! Open! Open! Open! Open!
Nami-san, you're great! So cool!
Lucy fended off this one easily, too!
He is full of fight spirit! Don Chinjao!
Go, Chopper, Brook!
Are you there?
The champion hopefuls -
Sai, the 13th leader of the Happo Navy,
What?!
You're making us fight after all?!
Straw Hat.
and "Destruction Cannon" Ideo
have surprisingly been eliminated!
He's been fighting so hard
but his Haki hasn't weakened at all!
I don't think I can fight
with a body like this!
Will the legendary gangster
- Don Chinjao win?!
Help!
Luffy-san!
How tenacious you are, Grandpa!
You're...
Or Lucy, the unknown powerhouse
who keeps going strong?!
What?!
It won't open.
Whaaat?!!
You're...
I'm gonna avenge my head with my head!
What should I do?! Those are my treasures!
You annoying grandson of Garp!
...Blackbeard?!
Avenge your head?
What are you talking about?
I can see them right there!
They're my everything!
Eight-Impact Fist!
Long time no see, Straw Hat!
Take this as payment for what he did to me!
Head-Arms Spin!
I was surprised, too,
Here it goes! Head-Arms!
My fortune!
Wh-What the hell are you carrying?!
when I heard that you were
the brother of my commander!
That technique again?
Gum-Gum Balloon!
Th-That's a lot!
What?!
Are you sure you want to be here?
You're gonna miss it!
He collected as many weapons
as he can in the Colosseum!
Damn Garp! I won't forgive you!
This is why we call him Jean the Bandit!
Your brother's public execution!
Chinjao's been deflected off of Lucy!
Damn you!
Jean Ango is now facing Lucy!
Gum-Gum...
I will carry this anger even towards
your children and grandchildren, Garp!
Oh, that was close!
Take this and fly away!
Fight me, Lucy!
I mean...
But it didn't work for him!
I will keep...
...Jet Cannon!
...Blackbeard, aren't you?
...holding a grudge against you, you bastard!
Dammit! If I were still "Chinjao the Drill"
like people used to call me,
...Straw Hat Luffy!
Yes, it's me! It's been a while.
I'm sure I could have taken
him down with that one!
A short time later, I retired from pirating.
I heard you're fighting
in the competition, Lucy!
I lost my power and my heart was broken.
Not just my treasure and fortune
But my man, Burgess,
is gonna win the Flare-Flare Fruit!
I became a lifeless shell,
just idling my time away.
but Garp also took my strength away!
I'm gonna get back at him after 30 years!
I can't wait because it'll be like having Ace
in my group!
But...
Hmmm... If he already knows who I am,
there's nothing I can do.
...I didn't expect to see
Garp's grandson like this!
He turned me down in the past!
Then, just give me back my helmet!
Charitable Donation!
This must be destiny!
Gum-Gum...
I have to take you down
right here at any cost
I said...
You guys are the last people I want,
to have Ace's power!
Take this and fly away!
I made so much money last
two years thanks to you!
..."Talk to...
and make you pay for what your grandpa did!
...Jet Cannon!
Huh? Thanks to me?
I captured dozens of prisoners
What?!
who you set free from the
great prison - Impel Down!
...my grandpa"!
What just happened?!
I'm looking to catch
every single one of you escapees!
I can't wait to fight you!
Jet Whip!
"Star Clown" Buggy!
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei!
This must be destiny!
Sir Crocodile!
I have to take you down
right here at any cost
Did it work this time?!
The Queen of the Queers - Ivankov!
Let's go!
Did he knock him out?!
Shiryu of the Rain!
and make you pay for what your grandpa did!
DRESSROSA - SANJI AND KIN'EMON
Go! Luffy-dono!
I'll hunt you all down
and make a name for myself!
Chinjao isn't moving a bit!
What are you talking about?!
Grandpa and I are different people!
Lucy!
Why're you cheering with the others?!
Yeah.
I wonder how Jimbei and Ivan-chan are doing.
But, Sanji-dono, when a man fights,
he has to win!
Not so different to me!
Not just you guys!
Do you know that pirate?
There are also brutal
escapees from level 6...
Isn't your friend captured at the Toy House?!
Are you gonna forget about him?!
I can't get beaten by you here!
A little bit. I can't let him win!
...which they didn't announce to the public.
I've got things to do!
I'm gonna win Ace's fruit at any price
and become the King of the Pirates!
From level 6?
That's right!
N-No, it didn't work this time either!
I know where they are now!
Hey lady, there're no more samples?
I didn't know there were other escapees.
That's a joke! You have no chance!
Damn! Why can't I get him?!
You, Straw Hat!
You're gonna just keep eating
and not gonna buy anything, are you?!
They lionized you squirts by calling you all
"the Worst Generation"
Wh...
Hey!
and it looks like it emboldened you.
What the hell?!
Burgess!
I'm sorry, ma'am!
Which one do you want, Lucy?
I heard that it's getting interesting!
But you guys aren't strong enough to
go across the sea that we fought on.
What?! Are you gonna buy it for me?!
Wow! Chinjao, is he gonna attack like that?!
After Whitebeard's death,
not much can be expected.
Who is that little guy?!
Oh, Rebecca, is he your friend?
What kind of technique is it?!
GREEN BIT
Oh?
The only guy who looks
good is Blackbeard Teach!
Thank you!
Blackbeard?
If I had to pick one, it's him.
But anyway,
Eight-Impact Fist! Head-Arms Spin!
if you're only good enough
to compete against me
Yum-yum! I'm gonna eat!
in my present condition, you have no chance!
Sorry that I don't have that much money.
Just give up being a pirate!
Oops...
Go, grandpa!
No, thank you for the lunch, Rebecca!
Head-Arms Spin!
Old man, beat him up!
In the name of Eight-Impact Fist!
Give it back.
You bastard!
Where are we?
I'm gonna make you pay! Stop me if you can!
That hurt.
This is a quarter
for us gladiators of the Colosseum.
Wild Dance!
I don't know why you're mad at my grandpa
O-Out of the ring!
Some people call it a prison.
What are you gonna do?!
Jean the Bandit has been eliminated!
but I have to win this thing!
Here I go!
Knocked out at a single blow!
Gum-Gum...
There's nowhere to run!
...Gatling!
The legendary pirate -
Don Chinjao head-butted him!
Guest competitors wouldn't come in here
Now it's the one-on-one fight between
Hey, Joker!
He's still got it after all these years!
so you can stay here until your next match.
the remaining two - Lucy and Don Chinjao!
Before you kill him,
Which one is going to...
I need you to take something back for me!
Yeah? Thanks!
Meanwhile, there is a breathtaking fight
...win the Block C match!
It's my heart! Law took my heart!
going on, between two
equally matched contenders!
I don't know what he's gonna do with it!
REBECCA: A GLADIATOR ATTACHED
TO THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
That battle was amazing!
Room!
I was surprised at your strength!
Shambles!
GREEN BIT
Gum-Gum...
They're really a good match-up!
...Hawk Rifle!
Is it good?
Yeah, this Colosseum lunch box is so good!
That bastard!
Lucy's going for it!
Why are you trying to buy time, Law?
I'm sure he's up to something again.
Aren't you hungry?
This life-and-death struggle
seems as if they're trying to
It's no use!
Mother-sama, I'm hungry.
Nobody can stop art!
figure out which one of them
is the strongest in this event!
I know.
They're both overwhelmingly strong!
We haven't eaten anything for two days.
Blow Kung-Fu...
No one else can compete!
They both take pride in their skills!
...Art!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
This is a battle royal!
Rebecca, do you think you can
stay here alone for a while?
This is just smoke!
--Yeah!
--Fight, fight!
Here I go! Weather Egg!
What is she doing?! Pick up already!
The excitement is reaching its peak!
Come on out, Snow Clouds!
I don't get hungry.
Go!
It's not over yet!
This is great!
Ideo!
Sai!
You're not too bad but if
a guy like Rayleigh chose
Huh? Sounds like you're
a samurai or something.
The whole Colosseum is keeping an eye
a brat of this level...
Ewww! Disgusting!
on the fight between those two!
...as the flag-bearer for the new generation,
It's really getting exciting!
I got you!
You turned my Clima Takt into a toy!
he's not as smart as he used to be!
Rebecca, just do it!
You can't get away now!
The Navy showed some good insight
What an insult!
What?!
Who did you call a super model?!
You brought him to do it, didn't you?!
when they squelched the most evil of the lot,
You have no mercy!
Garp's grandson!
I didn't say that!
I mean Ace, of course,
in the war two years ago.
Hey, what's going on here, Rebecca?!
"Turned it into a toy"?
Don't confuse it with a toy!
I'm all thumbs so...
Pay for what he did to me, Straw Hat Luffy!
That fool had the demon's blood in his veins!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
You have no taste!
You think you can beat the Navy admirals
Hurry up!
Your obnoxious grandpa took
all of my fortune away!
Yes, we have a Devil Fruit eater
and the Four Emperors and surpass Roger?!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Hey, my lunch is gonna spill out!
who can turn people into toys in our family.
That's impossible!
He also took away my power
Why is she not picking up?! Nami-ya!
--Do it!
--What's wrong?!
But I'm an art human who
ate the Art-Art Fruit!
and the sweet memories of my younger days!
I know I'm not calling the wrong number!
If you don't do it,
you can't carry out your purpose!
Gum-Gum...
You people have been turned into art!
Like I said before, I don't
know what you're talking about!
...Rocket!
Her purpose?
Talk to my grandpa!
Lucy is flying?!
"Art"?!
It's too easy for Garp
if I punish him by death!
It's Usoland's Haki!
That's an incredibly high jump!
Damn! Nami got defeated, too!
So powerful!
I will make him feel how painful
it is to live with loss!
But my antlers and hooves are useless!
Come on! I'm gonna teach you a lesson!
Just give up!
With 30 year worth of my anger toward Garp,
Hey, Bone-kichi, she's trying to kidnap me!
We need tension rods for the shelf -
it's gonna fall over.
Why didn't they put me in Block C?!
I'm gonna give you an all-out blow,
Straw Hat Luffy!
I know! I'm not gonna let her do it!
Leo, are you ready to go? Do you need lunch?
I should be the one who kills him -
Straw Hat Luffy!
But look at this.
What's that?!
Grandma, I'm sure there is something
to eat at the headquarters.
Am I just hallucinating or...
My Soul Solid looks like this!
Yeah?
Lucy's arm looks very big!
Why are you moaning like you're a victim?!
Watch what I'm gonna do, Garp!
Grandma!
You should be happy that I made you artistic!
I'm going to kill your precious grandson!
Oh yeah, I'm gonna sew up everything
that might fall over!
More importantly,
look what you did to my submarine!
Pay for it!
Your old man's punch took everything
away from me!
I have no choice.
And to my men!
Stop whining over one punch!
To avenge them,
Okay, now it's safe!
I can't count how many times
I got punched by him!
I can't believe how powerful the hero is!
Let's do it.
what kind of artistic death
should I bring to you?!
He can shake up the whole kingdom
with the thing called Haki!
I'm going to smash you
to the marrow of your bones!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Eight-Impact Fist Technique!
Rebecca got caught!
That's right!
--Ring, ring... Clank.
Because Usoland is the legendary hero!
--Hello? It's me! Who is this?!
I can't believe he can move faster than her!
We're in big trouble right now! Help us!
Gum-Gum...
By the way, Leo, I won't fall
over even though I look weak.
Second Gear!
...Thor...
Who said you can pick that up?!
Chopper-san, way to go!
Non-Drill Dragon...
Is this Tony-ya?!
Do whatever you like to me.
...Elephant Gun!
I don't care what's going on over there!
Listen carefully!
So this is the Tontatta Kingdom.
What?! Is this Tra-guy?!
...Non-Nail!
What kind of relationship do they
have with the Warlord Doflamingo?
I'll pay the price.
Is it Law?
I'm not gonna do anything
to somebody who bought me food.
Whatever it is,
they're serious about fighting him.
What are you doing, Tra-guy?!
Come to the ship now!
I tried to kill you!
Oh, Usoland and Robiland,
have you eaten enough?
That's okay. I'm not dead.
We got turned into art! Help us!
And I think you weren't gonna kill me.
Even if this weren't a personal matter,
Yeah, I'm totally pigged out...
I-I'm just fine!
Ow, ow, ow.
I can't win this thing without beating him.
Being forgiven that easily
makes it more obvious
I mean, I had enough and I'm ready to go!
Listen, I need you to...
that it was really unevenly matched, Rebecca.
....sail the ship to Green Bit now!
I won't let anybody have
the Flare-Flare Fruit!
I wanna leave Caesar with you guys!
Look, my body trembles with excitement
so the ground is shaking!
I'm gonna finish you off
right here, right now!
I've got no time to fill you in!
Come to Green Bit now!
If we could beat one Devil Fruit eater here,
--How awesome!
--He's unbelievable!
--Clank.
--What?!
Whaaat?!
there was still a slight hope.
Whaaat?! He asked us the
impossible and hung up!
Whaaat?!
Huh?! Mummies?!
By the way, Leo,
you people keep saying "fight" but...
No, we're not!
I thought he already handed Caesar-san over!
We are convict gladiators!
What's wrong with him?!
Whaaat?!
He just talked
without hearing what we had to say!
...why do you wanna fight Doflamingo?
So is Rebecca.
Is he Luffy?!
I... h-h-have no problem!
What?
We will keep fighting
Outta my way!
and get killed someday
in the ring, as part of a show!
I have nothing but a bad feeling!
Move!
What's going on out there?!
Just because we protested against the
Doflamingo Family, even moderately.
The hero's very funny!
I can't take it anymore!
We want to rescue the 500
friends who are forced
The king says we will be released
if we can win a thousand times.
to work at the shady factory, of course!
What?! A factory?!
Whaaat?!
But no matter how tough you are,
you'll die when you fight to
the death a hundred times!
Is that the one that Luffy and
the others went to destroy?!
Everybody who tried to escape from here
got shot and killed.
Is that the one that's manufacturing SMILEs?
Bullet String!
I don't know what they are making there
There is nowhere to run for us.
--Old man!
--Grandpa!
but they also have the Tontatta Tribe's...
Before Doflamingo became king a decade ago,
...obnoxious, selfish, mean, moody,
short-tempered Princess Mancherie, too.
Oh, he went out of the ring!
gladiatorial matches were not to the death.
Chinjao is eliminated
by being thrown out of the ring!
It's no use, Law!
So we have to get going!
In this kingdom that he governs,
Sounds like she's a horrible person!
Yes but...
there are very bright side and very dark side.
Who did you just call for help?
...she's one of us, too!
Noland would save everybody
who's in trouble, wouldn't he?
What a man!
Give me back Caesar's heart already.
What?!
He beat the legend and
won the fierce battle for Block C!
Y-Yeah, he would! That's
what a true hero does!
I'm...
...going to win today's competition
no matter what it takes...
It's so meaningless for you
to keep hanging on here.
Since I'm his descendant,
I'd do the same, of course!
Lucy the Gladiator!
That's our legendary hero!
and kill Doflamingo
with the Flare-Flare Fruit power!
Yeah!
Your partner - Straw Hat has already
walked into the trap that I set up.
Lucy! Lucy! Lucy!
Leo!
Flapper!
What's wrong?
Lucy! Lucy! Lucy!...
Leo, I just heard the Don Quixote
Family at the palace is on the move!
Today, an army led by Soldier-san
will come to let us out...
He's now fighting in the gladiatorial contest
at the Colosseum.
They're probably heading to
the basement of the Colosseum!
I didn't expect him to go this far!
Kabu-san's Yellow Cub
and Bian's Pink Bee
It's really a surprising ending!
are ready to take off anytime!
...by provoking a battle against Doflamingo!
Okay!
Tough contenders from all over
the world come to fight in
That's what it takes to be a king.
Cut the "Lucy" crap!
Those cheers are irritating!
He is willing to sacrifice his life
that outlaws-only, deadly competition.
Let's go! Usoland! Robiland!
It's a clash of two Conqueror's Haki users.
He got into the limelight
even under a fake name!
to destroy this kingdom!
When someone loses,
it's a one-way ticket to hell.
Is everybody ready now?!
Just come back here already!
It's gonna be alright!
I'm not gonna let you get
away this time, Straw Hat!
Yeah!
He will never come out
alive from the Colosseum.
The legendary hero - Usoland is here with us!
Didn't you hear what I said before?
I'm a brave soldier and
I will always be by your side!
I'm not gonna let you kill him.
He's the strongest ally that we can expect!
Cavendish!
If you get in my way,
I'm gonna kill you, too, Bartolomeo!
This is not a miracle! This must be destiny!
Let's win today's battle
and rescue our friends!
Try it!
I'm gonna do it before he does!
I'm gonna kill Straw Hat!
Straw Hat?
How much farther can he carry the momentum?!
I don't want to be just protected anymore!
And who is going to win the championship
and the Flare-Flare Fruit?!
It's the end of your alliance.
B-Block C!
The battle will take place in Dressrosa!
Underneath the Colosseum!
Law!
At the shady factory!
I want to protect Soldier-san this time!
There are only...
Let's go, everybody!
Just give up!
...two men left!
Yeah!
How exciting!
I get it now!