Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the prize for a
fighting event was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
he decided to enter.
Finally, the match for Block C
which Luffy registered for, started!
Brother.
Th-That bastard called me shrimp.
Just put it on already, Bobby!
I heard this strange story, Lucy.
I heard a pirate who's worth 400 million
named Straw Hat Luffy is...
...secretly fighting in this competition.
"The Legendary Pirate!
Don Chinjao!"
Now, the battle for Block C
is reaching its final phase!
Who's gonna win it?!
Take a look at the hot contenders!
The assassin from Mogaro - Kelly Funk!
He is unstoppable now!
Boo has been knocked out completely
after Kelly battered him!
Sai is approaching Boo.
Will the "Eight-Impact
Fist" be defeated here?!
Meanwhile, Ideo is blowing through and
beating tough contenders one after another!
Can't anybody stop this man?!
And Don Chinjao keeps charging
ahead in a fit of anger!
And, and, and,
this guy is stirring things up in this competition!
Lucy is the center of everybody's attention!
He is now desperately
chasing Jean the Bandit!
Wait!
You! Cactus! Give me back my helmet!
Damn that bastard!
Wait, you brat!
Garp's grandson!
Whoa! He's coming after me!
Your grandpa is Garp? So you're really him!
Get out of my way!
Oh? Where is he?
Where did he go?! Garp's grandson!
Give me back my helmet!
They call me Jean the Bandit!
I'd never give back what I stole!
Oh no! My beard!
Why are you panicking?
That was close!
Why are you hiding your face?
B-Because...
You can't say it?
There is only one reason
why you can't say it.
That's because you are...
...Straw Hat Luffy!
Yeah!
No, I'm not! I'm Lucy!
Charitable Donation!
Oh? Where did he go? Where's my helmet?
Hey! Where are you, Cactus?!
I can't believe that
Straw Hat really entered this event.
But I have a chance to win.
Because there are so many
weapons I can steal.
I know I can beat him with my shooting skill.
I'm gonna collect as many
weapons as I can and...
...I will defeat Straw Hat Luffy!
Cactus... Where did he go?
What?! What? What? What's going on?!
How strong!
The contenders are getting blown
away like sheets of paper!
It's Kelly Funk who is punching them!
Rah-Rah-Rah Rampage!
Where did Bobby go?
Kelly got bigger and surprisingly stronger!
I don't know what is going on anymore!
I saw it! I sure did!
What was that all about?!
He... The one that's fighting right now...
Is he Kelly or Bobby?!
Bobby and Kelly... The two became one!
Jacket-Jacket Two-in-a-Coat!
Wh-What the hell are they doing?!
Put me on already!
Uh-huh.
What's going on with them?!
Brother, like I said before,
I don't want to fight.
Idiot! Just stop thinking like always
and put me on!
Bobby was born with such a strong body,
but it was wasted on him - he's such a wimp!
However, when he puts me on as his "skin,"
I can take over his personality
and show my fighting skills and
brutality at full
with his body!
The guy from earlier?!
I'm a jacket human
who ate the Jacket-Jacket Fruit!
Whether it's an animal or a monster,
once someone puts me on,
I get control over all of him!
Bobby is wearing me
so we're one in body and mind now!
We're the Funk Brothers!
So you're saying you can't fight on your own!
What did you say to me earlier?
Huh? I'll say it as many times as you want!
You can't fight on your own!
Not that! You called me shrimp!
Rah-Rah-Rah Rampage!
How's that?
Do you realize how strong I am?!
It was over before I knew it!
They're all weak!
Hey!
Oh, you're the older of the brothers
from the Kano Kingdom!
I beat your brother in a second!
We brothers are working together
and killing people for living!
You're so pathetic!
You can't even save your own brother!
He lost because he trained himself poorly.
Don't be so hard on him.
You're gonna get beaten just like he was!
Rah-Rah-Rah Rampage!
Isn't the martial art of
the Kano Kingdom strong?!
Huh?!
You can't even talk because you're
moaning about your brother?!
From the moment I became a disciple
in order to learn the Eight-Impact Fist,
I have had no emotional
attachment to my brother!
But,
as the 13th leader of the Happo Navy,
I will avenge my subordinate!
S...
Strong!
The Eight-Impact Fist!
He showed off what it takes to be the leader!
Nobody could stop the monster, Kelly,
but he took him down with a single kick!
Until we accomplish our true purpose,
I can't lose.
Dammit! Where did he go?
I have no doubt.
You're the strongest in this block.
You should not praise your enemy!
Well, I wanted to face a
strong opponent like you.
What?!
I will defeat you, the strongest here,
and advance to the top!
Shut the fuck up!
Stop!
Hold on tight, Momo-chan!
Straw Hats! Just give up!
It's not beautiful to keep fighting a losing battle!
With my Art-Art Fruit power,
I turned your ship to an art
piece like this, so now,
you can't get away from Dressrosa!
Can't you see it?!
Hand Momonosuke over to us already!
It's no use trying to get away
leaving your ship behind!
"Get away"?
Hey, where did the others go?!
Where's the skeleton and the raccoon?
Wh-What is it?!
We're here!
Hello!
When did you get there?!
Okay, bye!
Oh? Where did the brat
from the Wano Kingdom go?!
The woman's gone, too!
What?!
What the hell is this?
I didn't notice those at all!
What are they?!
Thunder clouds?!
Thunderbreed Tempo!
Hey! You people are so annoying!
My submarine! My people!
No matter how tough the situation is,
we're not gonna get away
leaving the Sunny behind!
Now, let's get it back!
Yeah!
Nami-san, you're great! So cool!
Go, Chopper, Brook!
What?!
You're making us fight after all?!
I don't think I can fight
with a body like this!
Help!
Luffy-san!
What?!
Whaaat?!!
Wh-What the hell are you carrying?!
Th-That's a lot!
He collected as many weapons
as he can in the Colosseum!
This is why we call him Jean the Bandit!
Jean Ango is now facing Lucy!
Fight me, Lucy!
I mean...
...Straw Hat Luffy!
Hmmm... If he already knows who I am,
there's nothing I can do.
Then, just give me back my helmet!
Charitable Donation!
I made so much money last
two years thanks to you!
Huh? Thanks to me?
I captured dozens of prisoners
who you set free from the
great prison - Impel Down!
I'm looking to catch
every single one of you escapees!
"Star Clown" Buggy!
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei!
Sir Crocodile!
The Queen of the Queers - Ivankov!
Shiryu of the Rain!
I'll hunt you all down
and make a name for myself!
I wonder how Jimbei and Ivan-chan are doing.
Not just you guys!
There are also brutal
escapees from level 6...
...which they didn't announce to the public.
From level 6?
I know where they are now!
I didn't know there were other escapees.
Damn! Why can't I get him?!
Oh?
Oops...
Give it back.
You bastard!
That hurt.
O-Out of the ring!
Jean the Bandit has been eliminated!
Knocked out at a single blow!
The legendary pirate -
Don Chinjao head-butted him!
He's still got it after all these years!
Meanwhile, there is a breathtaking fight
going on, between two
equally matched contenders!
They're really a good match-up!
This life-and-death struggle
seems as if they're trying to
figure out which one of them
is the strongest in this event!
They're both overwhelmingly strong!
No one else can compete!
They both take pride in their skills!
This is a battle royal!
--Yeah!
--Fight, fight!
The excitement is reaching its peak!
Go!
This is great!
Ideo!
Sai!
The whole Colosseum is keeping an eye
on the fight between those two!
It's really getting exciting!
You can't get away now!
Garp's grandson!
Pay for what he did to me, Straw Hat Luffy!
Your obnoxious grandpa took
all of my fortune away!
He also took away my power
and the sweet memories of my younger days!
Like I said before, I don't
know what you're talking about!
Talk to my grandpa!
It's too easy for Garp
if I punish him by death!
I will make him feel how painful
it is to live with loss!
Just give up!
Why didn't they put me in Block C?!
I should be the one who kills him -
Straw Hat Luffy!
I have no choice.
Let's do it.
Second Gear!
Even if this weren't a personal matter,
I can't win this thing without beating him.
I won't let anybody have
the Flare-Flare Fruit!
I'm gonna finish you off
right here, right now!
Outta my way!
Move!
That's what it takes to be a king.
It's a clash of two Conqueror's Haki users.
B-Block C!
There are only...
...two men left!