iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
koukishin ni makasete
Go along with your curiosity
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
kokoro no chizu hirogete
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the prize for
a fighting event was the Flare-Flare
Fruit, he decided to enter.
"Light and Shadow!
Darkness behind Dressrosa!"
It seems like those famous tough warriors
have been knocked out by...
...the impact from the epic
clash of those two men
and have been taken out of the fight!
But what did we actually see?!
I didn't know you could use Conqueror's Haki!
What kind of king are you dreaming to become?!
The King of the Pirates!
Shut up!
There are so many in the New World
who can use that power!
And only battling it out amongst you all
will determine the winner!
The strongest among a legion of "Conquerors"!
That's who the King of the Pirates is!
Who taught you how to use the Haki?
Rayleigh!
Is he still alive?!
How annoying!
I don't even want to think about
what happened in the past!
He landed a powerful kick against Lucy!
Even though he's already retired,
the strength of the 12th leader
of the Happo Navy remains!
What?
Whaaat?!
Tell me, Straw Hat.
I want to forget but it's always
right there in front of me!
But it's out of my reach! My treasure!
Can you imagine anything harder than that?!
What's going on?! The legendary pirate is...
...crying!
Grandpa...
I thought the plan was to
let Sai move into the final!
I'm still not strong enough.
Nobody can stop him once he's at it!
"Chinjao the Drill."
That's what they used to
call me but not anymore.
Answer me!
Do you know what Garp has done to me?!
I told you - I don't know!
Since you're that bastard Garp's
grandson, I can't just let you
walk away because you have no idea!
For 30 years,
I've been holding a grudge!
He's showing his fighting spirit again!
Don Chinjao!
Say it, Straw Hat!
What has Garp done to me?!
What did he take away from me?!
He's crying again!
This old man is such a pain in the ass.
I can't tell if he wants to cry or be mad.
Go Lucy! Now's the chance!
Luffy-dono!
I don't have time for this!
Sanji-dono, I want to get to the
Toy House to rescue Kanjuro already!
I wanna help you with that
but you have to wait.
We have a situation here.
Look how many Navy soldiers
there are around the Colosseum.
Why are there so many?
It seems like pirates and criminals are
freely entering this competition.
The Navy is here to catch them
as they come out.
Well, criminals should be caught.
Don't forget that you
were on the pirate ship!
Oh yeah!
We have to tell Luffy about this situation
but the entrance for the competitors is
completely closed off.
What's going on here-dara?
No one has come out
from the Colosseum yet-dara?
No, sir. Not yet.
There must be hundreds of losers
from Block A and B-dara!
Why hasn't even a single one of them
come out-dara?
It's strange.
Vice Admiral Maynard went undercover as a competitor
"SHARK SLICER" BASTILLE
- A NAVY VICE ADMIRAL
but we haven't had any contact with him for a while.
Why did he do that on his own?
That punk!
Is something going on...
...in the Colosseum-dara?
Here in Dressrosa, there are two laws...
...that people have obeyed strictly
since Doflamingo came to the throne 10 years ago.
--Two laws?
--Yes.
First, lights should be out by midnight.
Citizens must not go out after that.
What?! Even adults?!
Humans have to go back to their homes
and toys have to go back to their toy houses.
No one's allowed to go out after midnight.
You can't even go for a drink!
Everything is closed anyway.
Second,
toys must not enter human's houses
and humans must not enter toy's houses!
What?!
It looks like they're
friendly with each other
but that's prohibited?!
But if that's the sad boundary between
artifacts and living things, it can't be helped.
Well, come to think of it,
I'm kind of getting used to it already but...
...what kind of toys are you guys?
You have free will and you can talk.
Whoever made you all should
be a genius like Vegapunk.
Who was it?
Somebody, call the police!
What's going on?!
--Please! Let go of me!
--Esta, it's me!
The toy's broken! It's got "human disorder"!
Listen to me! It's not that!
Don't you remember, Esta?!
It's me!
Get away from me! You're freaking me out!
What happened all of a sudden?!
You've been friendly with her until now!
Please! Try to remember!
Get away from her!
Come with us!
Damn!
Esta! I'm your boyfriend!
Don't hook up with that bastard!
You know who I am! Remember me!
--Let go of me! Dammit!
--Calm down!
Don't!
No! Don't!
No! Let go of me, you bastards!
I'm a human!
That was scary!
Boy...
I can't believe that toy thinks he's a human.
I know.
What was it all about?
Let me ride you, Onepoko!
No-wan! You're too heavy now-wan!
Onepoko!
I'm not heavy!
Let me go talk to him.
Don't worry. He's a toy, too.
Well, yeah, a half of me is.
Hmmm, Onepoko's got it!
Who are you?
I'm that boy's father.
And that woman is my wife.
My name is Milo, not Onepoko.
Hey boy, don't you have a daddy?
Huh? No, I don't!
Do you have a husband?
No, I don't. I'm not married.
It's not so unusual, is it?
Bye bye!
Hey soldier, what's your point?
What's going on here?
What I wanted to show you is...
...this country is filled
with both the forgotten
and those who forgot them!
All of us toys were once humans!
What?!
A Devil Fruit eater
who Doflamingo brought 10 years ago,
turned us to toys!
Hey! That means you were...
There!
I see the Flower Field!
I'll tell you everything there!
Although he's already retired,
his Eight-Impact Fist is still
as sharp as it used to be!
He is full of fight spirit! Don Chinjao!
He's been fighting so hard
but his Haki hasn't weakened at all!
How tenacious you are, Grandpa!
I'm gonna avenge my head with my head!
Avenge your head?
What are you talking about?
Take this as payment for what he did to me!
Here it goes! Head-Arms!
Gum-Gum Balloon!
What?!
Chinjao's been deflected off of Lucy!
Oh, that was close!
But it didn't work for him!
Dammit! If I were still "Chinjao the Drill"
like people used to call me,
I'm sure I could have taken
him down with that one!
Not just my treasure and fortune
but Garp also took my strength away!
I'm gonna get back at him after 30 years!
I said...
..."Talk to...
...my grandpa"!
Did it work this time?!
Did he knock him out?!
Chinjao isn't moving a bit!
N-No, it didn't work this time either!
You, Straw Hat!
Wh...
What the hell?!
Wow! Chinjao, is he gonna attack like that?!
What kind of technique is it?!
Eight-Impact Fist! Head-Arms Spin!
Go, grandpa!
Old man, beat him up!
In the name of Eight-Impact Fist!
I'm gonna make you pay! Stop me if you can!
I don't know why you're mad at my grandpa
but I have to win this thing!
Here I go!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Now it's the one-on-one fight between
the remaining two - Lucy and Don Chinjao!
Which one is going to...
...win the Block C match!
GREEN BIT
Why are you trying to buy time, Law?
I'm sure he's up to something again.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
What is she doing?! Pick up already!
You have no mercy!
I'm all thumbs so...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Why is she not picking up?! Nami-ya!
I know I'm not calling the wrong number!
It's Usoland's Haki!
So powerful!
We need tension rods for the shelf -
it's gonna fall over.
Leo, are you ready to go? Do you need lunch?
Grandma, I'm sure there is something
to eat at the headquarters.
Yeah?
Grandma!
Oh yeah, I'm gonna sew up everything
that might fall over!
Okay, now it's safe!
I can't believe how powerful the hero is!
He can shake up the whole kingdom
with the thing called Haki!
That's right!
Because Usoland is the legendary hero!
By the way, Leo, I won't fall
over even though I look weak.
So this is the Tontatta Kingdom.
What kind of relationship do they
have with the Warlord Doflamingo?
Whatever it is,
they're serious about fighting him.
Oh, Usoland and Robiland,
have you eaten enough?
Yeah, I'm totally pigged out...
I mean, I had enough and I'm ready to go!
Look, my body trembles with excitement
so the ground is shaking!
--How awesome!
--He's unbelievable!
By the way, Leo,
you people keep saying "fight" but...
...why do you wanna fight Doflamingo?
What?
The hero's very funny!
We want to rescue the 500
friends who are forced
to work at the shady factory, of course!
What?! A factory?!
Is that the one that Luffy and
the others went to destroy?!
Is that the one that's manufacturing SMILEs?
I don't know what they are making there
but they also have the Tontatta Tribe's...
...obnoxious, selfish, mean, moody,
short-tempered Princess Mancherie, too.
So we have to get going!
Sounds like she's a horrible person!
Yes but...
...she's one of us, too!
Noland would save everybody
who's in trouble, wouldn't he?
What?!
Y-Yeah, he would! That's
what a true hero does!
Since I'm his descendant,
I'd do the same, of course!
That's our legendary hero!
Leo!
Flapper!
What's wrong?
Leo, I just heard the Don Quixote
Family at the palace is on the move!
They're probably heading to
the basement of the Colosseum!
Kabu-san's Yellow Cub
and Bian's Pink Bee
are ready to take off anytime!
Okay!
Let's go! Usoland! Robiland!
Is everybody ready now?!
Yeah!
The legendary hero - Usoland is here with us!
He's the strongest ally that we can expect!
This is not a miracle! This must be destiny!
Let's win today's battle
and rescue our friends!
The battle will take place in Dressrosa!
Underneath the Colosseum!
At the shady factory!
Let's go, everybody!
Yeah!