Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the
prize for a fighting event
was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
he decided to enter and fight
fierce battles against other tough
contenders from the New World.
Meanwhile, at the Tontatta
Kingdom in Green Bit,
where the Little People reside...
Alright, everybody! Let's get going!
With our hero Usoland!
To take back the 500 friends
who are held captive!
Don Quixote Doflamingo has
been causing us Tontatta Tribe
a lot of pain recently.
But our connection with him
goes way back before last decade, actually.
It goes back about 900 years ago.
Meanwhile, at the King Riku
Army Headquarters where
anti-Doflamingo protesters are assembling...
Hey, don't let him attack you, Luffy!
Damn, that bastard!
If there is an event like this, why didn't he tell me?!
I wanna fight with my swords!
Give me back Caesar's heart already.
It's so meaningless for you
to keep hanging on here.
Your partner - Straw Hat has already
walked into the trap that I set up.
He will never come out
alive from the Colosseum.
It's the end of your alliance.
Law!
Just give up!
"The Fierce Battle Coming to the End!
Lucy vs. Chinjao!"
Gum-Gum...
Eight-Impact Fist!
...Jet Pistol!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
...Jet Stamp Gatling!
You fool!
Go Lucy!
Kick his ass, Chinjao!
They're exchanging fierce punches and kicks!
What a fight!
It's too fast and I can't even
see what's going on anymore!
But I can feel their fighting spirit!
I'm sure what we're seeing now is...
...one of the greatest fights ever
in this Colosseum!
You're quite a fighter.
You're strong, too, as I thought.
What did you say?!
Huh?
What did you just say?!
I'm strong?!
Are you trying to insult me?!
What?! I just said "You're strong"!
As far as I'm concerned, that's an insult!
I'm no better than a wolf
without its fangs now.
I mean, a skin-headed man without his drill!
A brat like you can't understand
how miserable I feel living my life like this!
I'm frustrated, disappointed, and sad!
But you can never understand!
How can I understand?!
You just keep messing with me
without explaining anything!
Do you really want to know
why I've become like this?!
No, I'm not that interested.
Well then, I'm gonna tell you before you die
since you insist.
It was 30 years ago.
What the hell is wrong with this ice?!
We can't break it with fire or an ax!
But look at all that unbelievable pirate treasure
under the ice!
You can't make a scratch
with what you have there,
even if you keep trying for 100 years!
This continent is made of what
they call "Crystal Ice Sheet"
and to break it,
you have to put tremendous
pressure on one spot!
Drill Dragon Nail!
Open Chinjao!
Do you like it there, you thieves?
Guys, tie those treasure thieves up
and dump them into the sea!
Okay, Boss!
Lots of happiness!
CHINJAO THE DRILL
THE 12TH LEADER OF A PIRATE GROUP - THE HAPPO NAVY
(30 YEARS AGO)
This room of ice contains everything.
Joys and sorrows from the past.
Hopes for the future.
Several decades worth of
my family's treasures!
My drill head is the only key to the room.
Nobody can invade this place!
Not even the Navy!
Hey, Chinjao!
In order to break your head today,
I've trained myself by destroying
about eight mountains
like they were my punching bags!
It's no use!
There is not a thing in the world
harder than my head!
Prepare for it, Chinjao!
I'm gonna break that fist of yours
that you're so proud of, Garp!
Boss!
He did it!
--Let's leave!
--All ships, set sail!
Boss!
Boss! I'm glad that you're okay!
The drill...
Where is my drill?!
Where did my drill go?!
Open Chinjao!
Drill Dragon Nail!
Open! Drill Dragon Nail!
--Boss!
--Please stop, Boss!
You're gonna die!
Open! Open! Open! Open! Open!
It won't open.
What should I do?! Those are my treasures!
I can see them right there!
They're my everything!
My fortune!
Damn Garp! I won't forgive you!
I will carry this anger even towards
your children and grandchildren, Garp!
I will keep...
...holding a grudge against you, you bastard!
A short time later, I retired from pirating.
I lost my power and my heart was broken.
I became a lifeless shell,
just idling my time away.
But...
...I didn't expect to see
Garp's grandson like this!
This must be destiny!
I have to take you down
right here at any cost
and make you pay for what your grandpa did!
This must be destiny!
I have to take you down
right here at any cost
and make you pay for what your grandpa did!
What are you talking about?!
Grandpa and I are different people!
Not so different to me!
I can't get beaten by you here!
I've got things to do!
I'm gonna win Ace's fruit at any price
and become the King of the Pirates!
That's a joke! You have no chance!
They lionized you squirts by calling you all
"the Worst Generation"
and it looks like it emboldened you.
But you guys aren't strong enough to
go across the sea that we fought on.
After Whitebeard's death,
not much can be expected.
The only guy who looks
good is Blackbeard Teach!
Blackbeard?
If I had to pick one, it's him.
But anyway,
if you're only good enough
to compete against me
in my present condition, you have no chance!
Just give up being a pirate!
Head-Arms Spin!
Wild Dance!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Rifle!
Lucy's going for it!
It's not over yet!
You're not too bad but if
a guy like Rayleigh chose
a brat of this level...
...as the flag-bearer for the new generation,
he's not as smart as he used to be!
The Navy showed some good insight
when they squelched the most evil of the lot,
I mean Ace, of course,
in the war two years ago.
That fool had the demon's blood in his veins!
You think you can beat the Navy admirals
and the Four Emperors and surpass Roger?!
That's impossible!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Lucy is flying?!
That's an incredibly high jump!
Come on! I'm gonna teach you a lesson!
With 30 year worth of my anger toward Garp,
I'm gonna give you an all-out blow,
Straw Hat Luffy!
What's that?!
Am I just hallucinating or...
Lucy's arm looks very big!
Watch what I'm gonna do, Garp!
I'm going to kill your precious grandson!
Pay for it!
Your old man's punch took everything
away from me!
Stop whining over one punch!
I can't count how many times
I got punched by him!
I'm going to smash you
to the marrow of your bones!
Eight-Impact Fist Technique!
Gum-Gum...
...Thor...
Non-Drill Dragon...
...Elephant Gun!
...Non-Nail!
Whaaat?!
--Old man!
--Grandpa!
Oh, he went out of the ring!
Chinjao is eliminated
by being thrown out of the ring!
What a man!
He beat the legend and
won the fierce battle for Block C!
Lucy the Gladiator!
Yeah!
Lucy! Lucy! Lucy!
Lucy! Lucy! Lucy!...
I didn't expect him to go this far!
It's really a surprising ending!
Cut the "Lucy" crap!
Those cheers are irritating!
He got into the limelight
even under a fake name!
Just come back here already!
I'm not gonna let you get
away this time, Straw Hat!
Didn't you hear what I said before?
I'm not gonna let you kill him.
Cavendish!
If you get in my way,
I'm gonna kill you, too, Bartolomeo!
Try it!
I'm gonna kill Straw Hat!
Straw Hat?
How much farther can he carry the momentum?!
And who is going to win the championship
and the Flare-Flare Fruit?!
How exciting!
I get it now!