iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the prize for a
fighting event was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
When Luffy found out that the prize for
When Luffy found out that the
prize for a fighting event
a fighting event
was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
he decided to enter and face
the fierce competition!
he decided to enter and fight fierce battles!
was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
he decided to enter and fight fierce
battles against other tough
he decided to enter and fight
fierce battles against other tough
Please don't die, Soldier-san!
I don't want to be just protected anymore!
he decided to enter and fight
fierce battles against other tough
I won't...
contenders from the New World.
Come after me, Doflamingo!
I want to protect Soldier-san this time!
Alright! Here we go!
...give up, either!
What? Is he gonna go across the bridge?
The Gaon Cannon! Fire!
"The Last - and Bloodiest - Block!
Block D Battle Begins!"
What is that?
"Protect You to the End!
Rebecca and the Toy Soldier!"
Yes!
Soldier-san's gonna die.
No! Idiots!
Head blow!
Fujitora?
Excuse me.
Soldier?
Why did you help him?
He's a one-legged toy soldier.
I get it.
A long time ago...
It goes back 800 years, Law.
I have to stop you right there,
Heavenly Demon.
A toy?
Oh, elderly people!
I'm here to...
Do you want me to carry
your bag or something?
Wait, Doflamingo!
They have nothing to do with this!
20 kings from 20 countries came together
at the center of the world
Oh?
...arrest him, not to kill him.
It's over, Law!
Am I funny?
--Doflamingo is flying towards us!
--What?!
I met a guy like that
in front of the Colosseum.
and formed one giant organization.
By the way,
you seem quite curious about
that "complication" that I mentioned.
Young Master-sama!
Yeah, I guess that's him.
That's what we call
the World Government now.
What is this?! A nightmare?!
Are we gonna get killed?!
We're not allowed out of the Colosseum.
Do you wanna hear about it?
No!
We can't do anything if there's
something going on out there.
The kings who created it...
Drop dead, Rebecca!
...decided to move to the Holyland of
Watch this, Law!
You're worrying that a toy is gonna die?
Marie Jois and live there
with their families.
You foul-blooded wench!
I'll viciously slay your allies
right before your eyes!
A living toy seems really odd to me.
Go to hell, Rebecca!
The Nefeltari Family of Alabasta refused,
"A Decisive Battle!
Giolla vs. the Straw Hats!"
Today's your execution day!
Don't!
You're not from here
so maybe it's hard to understand.
so there were 19 families to be exact.
Tra-guy, help...
The descendents of those
creators who still live there
Hey!
My friends are crying in fear!
They're the same as humans.
The shame of Dressrosa!
and reign over the world are the Celestial Dragons.
Leave them alone!
They are friends for the friendless.
Set her on fire!
That'll make her pyromaniac
grandfather happy!
They are siblings for those who have none.
Sanji!
In those countries, they elected
new kings out of necessity
The battle royal in the
Corrida Colosseum - Block D!
They are lovers for the loveless.
and new royal families rose.
I don't understand why they
aren't allowed to live with us.
Here comes quite a tough one.
In the case of my country - Dressrosa,
As the "Phantom Princess" Rebecca enters,
the crowd is really heating up!
Since the day I lost my mother
who was my only family,
the new royalty was the Riku Family.
"A Big Clash!
Sanji vs. Doflamingo!"
Soldier-san raised me.
A long time ago...
And the old royalty who
moved to the Holyland
It goes back 800 years, Law.
of Marie Jois
as the creators of the world were...
He's like a father to me.
Even if she's the former king's granddaughter,
it had nothing to do with her!
...the Don Quixote Family!
I see. So that toy is...
20 kings from 20 countries came together
Whatever her grandfather did!
at the center of the world
Thank you for waiting!
The ring has been fully prepared!
"Beautiful Sword!
Cavendish of the White Horse!"
and formed one giant organization.
Yeah, you're right.
You're the "Black Foot" of
the Straw Hats, aren't you?
Rebecca, the match is gonna start.
Uh-huh.
I wouldn't expect that to come from you.
Diable Jambe...
That's what we call
the World Government now.
Hey, what are you doing, Lucy?
Even if her grandfather is the former king
who the whole country despises,
OFF THE COAST OF DRESSROSA
...Premiere Hachis Hash!
When we struggled earlier,
the two lunch boxes fell on the floor.
The kings who created it...
...decided to move to the
Holy land of Marie Jois
Sorry! You emptied your
wallet to buy me these.
Rebecca is our hope!
and live there with their families.
But they still taste good!
Pentachromatic Strings!
The Nefeltari Family of Alabasta refused,
Your hope?
Yes, Rebecca and all of
us have been fighting
--Sanji-san!
--What did Doflamingo do?!
so there were 19 families to be exact.
You don't look like a prisoner to me.
Now, what should we do with this?
desperately to claw our way
up from this dark abyss…
The descendents of those
creators who still live there
Bone-kichi, I gave her a single blow, too!
Buy me lunch again sometime!
...with no way out.
Save your friends if you can.
and reign over the world
are the Celestial Dragons.
I know. You have a great suji (aptitude).
We were not strong enough
so we ended up like this
Y-Yeah? Do I?
It means, however, that those
I don't have any suji (muscle), though.
--Doflamingo is coming this way!
--You've got to be kidding!
but Rebecca isn't hurt.
19 countries lost their royal
families 800 years ago.
Because I'm a skeleton.
I mean, hurt or not,
only Rebecca can keep our hope alive.
Young Master-sama!
See you at the finals.
--Stay away from us!
--Go away!
Are you following?
It'd be too cruel to dump her into the sea.
Yeah!
Good luck!
Yeah, she's a Devil Fruit eater.
In those countries, they elected
new kings out of necessity
No!
If she can win this thing
and get the Flare-Flare Fruit,
We're gonna start the match!
Competitors of Block D, enter the ring!
I don't even wanna see her panties.
and new royal families rose.
Wh-Who did you call Miss Universe?
things may get a little better here.
Alright! I'm gonna win the Flare-Flare Fruit!
In the case of my country - Dressrosa,
Nobody said such a thing! No!
Say whatever you want now!
Should I hit her one more time?
the new royalty was the Riku Family.
Diable Jambe...
Just leave her alone.
...Poele a Frire...
We gotta hurry and meet Tra-guy.
And the old royalty who moved to the
...Spectre!
But why does he wanna leave Caesar with us?
Holyland of Marie Jois as the
creators of the world wereÂ
Mother-sama!
Listen, I need you to...
Go to hell!
Mother-sama, I picked so many flowers!
....sail the ship to Green Bit now!
...the Don Quixote Family!
You're hated by the whole
country, Rebecca-chan!
It's powerful! He's quite strong!
I wanna leave Caesar with you guys!
Wow, Rebecca!
That means you're...
Despite that pretty face,
Would you like to have one?
Yeah, it is strange.
All right, Sanji!
Thank you. I would like to.
people think you're a bigger villain
than Bartolomeo from Block B!
Go!
Doflamingo resigned from the
Seven Warlords by our request
And this is from your mother to you!
That's right!
Okay, let's go.
so we have to return Caesar to him.
Uh-huh!
--Screw you, Rebecca!
--The corrupted King Riku's family!
Y-You idiots don't know anything, don't you?
1, 2! 1, 2!
It's so fun!
The great music and the art of the sea, yeah!
Young Master-sama doesn't take negotiation
We sold all the flowers today!
You sure know art, don't you?!
with brats like you seriously.
Yes, we did.
Stop the ship!
Maybe people bought them
because you're so cute!
He didn't resign from the Seven Warlords.
Don't tell me you're going to Green Bit!
That's enough!
Wh-What happened? I can't move!
What?
Law would be stunned!
Hey, what do you mean by that?!
Let's eat!
If I come to pick up Caesar,
not you guys!
What do you mean?!
Oh! The man that's coming into the ring is...
Go ahead. Dig in.
Oh? Sanji-san got frozen in mid air!
Ouch!
That hurt, you damn brat!
Brook is acting strange!
Are you gonna turn around on us?!
You must be tired
from walking all over the town.
What an ill-behaved crowd! I can't stand it!
Yeah, I'm so hungry!
My stomach was growling!
O-Nami!
He's been grappled
by the Young Master's power!
Bone-kichi!
You call yourself a swordsman
but betray your friends?!
Shame on you!
You guys have been fooled!
Oh no!
Doflamingo's power?!
--It's yummy!
--Yeah!
I just realized something!
Violet must've unearthed
all of your plans by now
Here comes the captain of the Beautiful Pirates -
Cavendish of the White Horse!
I'm an artist after all!
I'm living to create!
Black Foot is like a bug caught
in a spider's web now!
and all of your friends
are probably captured!
All he can do is wait for death!
What?!
I'm dead though!
Boy!
CAVENDISH OF THE WHITE HORSE
These ordinary people can't
understand, Soul King!
What?!
The King Riku Army is setting
the village on fire!
Look!
Please stop!
More than anything, we
want to express ourselves!
Why is the king doing this?!
They don't understand that kind of passion!
Cavendish-sama!
--What is it?!
--A whip?!
This is an art of life! Dying Art!
Oh, how beautiful!
Don't do anything! Just run!
Use Coup de Burst to get out of here!
That's amazing, Giolla-san!
Get ahold of yourself!
We can't do that!
Some women in the audience are collapsing!
The palace is on fire!
No!
Overheat!
All right! This stormy battle
royal is finally coming
Help!
Sanji!
I'm fine...
Get away, Sanji-kun!
He still has the look that everybody
was talking about three years ago!
to the final match - Block D!
What's going on in this country?
I couldn't be more excited!
I represented the tragedy of
Dressrosa quite exquisitely!
Shambles!
All the competitors are
fighting for survival!
Cavendish-sama!
Kick that little tramp's ass!
In 10 minutes or so,
these annoying kids will
Room!
This battle is also going to
be bloody since there're so
Go! Don't let them get away!
Law, eh?
become part of the art completely
many tough contenders.
Teach Rebecca a lesson!
DRESSROSA
First, I have to draw
your attention to this man!
Run, Lady Scarlet!
and choke to death!
--What?!
--Brook!
He is a notorious class-A war criminal
from the Sea Battle of Dias!
Shut up, you bastards!
Bone-kichi!
I can't tell you how impressed I am!
Run!
I don't know why you hate her so much,
Let me play a song to celebrate!
but she's a young girl who stands in the ring,
putting her life on the line!
Would you mind doing so, Soul King?!
It's Tra-guy! He saved Sanji!
Yes, I'd love to!
So could you turn my violin
and bow back, Giolla-san?
You guys are not risking your lives
so you have no right to jeer at her!
Sorry. I made a mistake!
Let's get on the ship!
Alright! Take it away, brother!
--Who are you, shorty!
--Outta our way!
SULEIMAN THE BEHEADER
A CLASS-A WAR CRIMINAL FROM THE SEA BATTLE OF DIAS
If you really want to kill her,
Suleiman the Beheader!
Run!
Wow, thank you!
As far as you can!
take a weapon and come
down to the ring yourself!
Tra-guy-san!
And...
No!
I'm not... suffering...
Sanji!
I'm almost unconscious...
I don't wanna die!
Damn! I'm on the ship again!
An admiral of the Yonta Maria Grand Fleet!
Take a look at this, Giolla-san,
this bow is actually a cane sword.
Caesar!
"The Surmounter" Orlumbus!
Oh, Giolla! Help me!
"THE SURMOUNTER" ORLUMBUS - AN ADVENTURER/
AN ADMIRAL OF THE YONTA MARIA GRAND FLEET
Mother-sama, I'm hungry.
Uh-huh, uh-huh, play nice music for me!
The voices of people who have no guts
are nothing but irritating noise!
I'm being held captive, too!
A military captain of a southern country -
the Majiatsuka Kingdom!
I know.
We haven't eaten anything
for two days.
I have my reasons for entering this event,
but even so I can't stomach it!
Okay! I cut you already.
Cut me?!
Rolling Logan!
Painting Song Bamboo Flute Slice!
I dropped my guard.
The lives and deaths of
warriors are not a show!
ROLLING LOGAN - A MILITARY CAPTAIN OF
A SOUTHERN COUNTRY - THE MAJIATSUKA KINGDOM
Rebecca,
PAINTING SONG BAMBOO FLUTE SLICE
do you think you can stay
here alone for a while?
Sanji-kun!
Nami-san!
And there are more!
Promise me to stay here, no matter what.
JOINT
I'm sorry but I don't understand
art after all because...
I'm gonna go buy something to eat.
No! Doflamingo's coming again!
Uh-huh!
...my eyes
KNOTHOLE
A FIGHTING LION - AGYO
A fighting lion - Agyo!
are like knotholes!
Thank you, Farul.
Damn!
Brook!
Black Foot-ya!
What are the horse and the bullhorn for?
Bone-kichi!
How's the plan to destroy
the factory going?
Oh, Cabbage spoke up and
said the right thing.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
We found out where it is
I'm impressed.
but Franky said it's gonna
be harder than we thought.
AN ARSONIST - DAMASK
An arsonist - Damask!
I still don't like him though.
How's my father?! And Kanjuro?!
San-goro!
--Cavendish-sama!
--What a great man!
How are they doing?!
A sorcerer - Mummy!
I started to worry
about Nami-san before you did!
Momonosuke.
And I know she wants me
to come instead of you!
I don't care about Rebecca anymore!
Mother-sama!
So I'm going!
The samurai is heading to the factory.
I'm gonna support you!
Alright! Go!
A SORCERER - MUMMY
He'll be alright once everything is over.
Cavendish!
Kin'emon, this is a map to the
Toy House where your friend is.
I can't believe it! He's so charismatic!
So we need more time.
Oh, thank you!
I... I couldn't protect her!
A GLADIATOR - AGILIA
A gladiator - Agilia!
When you get to see Luffy,
contact the Sunny with this.
He turned the tumultuous booing
to a shower of applause!
Any one of them can win this battle!
Let's check to see what everybody is doing.
I'm sorry!
Hey, you!
Is that my heart?!
I couldn't protect your mother!
I'll stay on the Sunny.
The match has just begun but
Were you keeping it in the cabin?!
the one that stands out the most so far is...
Now, how can we reach Luffy?
This is mine.
Hey, I understand how you feel.
This is not what you wanted, right?
...the man that we were expecting!
I had your heart with me.
She told me to give you these.
If I knew how,
we wouldn't be standing here.
She said that you're waiting here hungry.
I think it bothers you
how easily they change their mind
Cavendish of the White Horse!
The place is all closed up
Mother-sama, I'm hungry.
but people are often like that.
They don't listen to you...
and I don't see anybody to ask.
They love me so much! I'm so happy!
Damn!
I'm gonna go buy something to eat.
We should not make a bold move.
I almost got caught earlier.
Y-You had it in your body the whole time!
--You like it?!
--It's been three years...
Who are you?
Then should I just chop up the wall?
That's what I call a bold move!
Everyone!
Excuse me.
Gardoa, the beautiful bounty hunter!
I want you to take him
and head for Zou!
I can slice it gently instead?
Thank you for standing up for me earlier.
That's not the point! Boy!
Zou?
Don't mention it.
It's true that it aggravated me.
I gave you the Vivre Card
that leads you to the island.
Gardoa-sama! You're so handsome!
Mother-sama?
--We have to be careful!
--How do you want me to cut it then?!
It must be hard for you.
Mother-sama...
Is this a Vivre Card?
What's with that spear?
Mother-sama!
But forget it.
We have to fight each other.
Yes. It'll point toward an island called Zou
that I talked about earlier.
Mother-sama!!
This is like a medal to me.
Right.
I use bounties I get from catching pirates
That's "Pirate Hunter" Zoro-senpai!
Here it is.
Head for the island?!
By the way, there must be one
or two news reporters here.
to get shinier and shinier spears.
They say he chopped up 100 men
in Whisky Peak
What about Luffy-san and the others?!
and rampaged through Enies Lobby!
The only thing left to do on this island is
destroy the factory.
There are so many people with a
high prize in this competition.
What should I do
if this gets in the newspaper?
I saw a trail of blood on the staircase!
The Three-Sword Style swordsman!
They must be hiding somewhere!
Let's search!
It's nice to make money.
After the match, they'd interview me and go,
"Hey there, big star!"
We'll catch up with you guys soon.
He's always supporting the Straw Hats
as Luffy-senpai's right-hand man
If I can get hold of the prize on you -
280 million berries,
No! We'll wait!
And I'd go, "What did you call me?"
We can't set sail without our captain!
and is considered vice captain!
I'm sorry.
I can even make a diamond spear!
Maybe!
We're the Straw Hats!
He's so cool!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!!
Oh? Why am I crying? Why?
What?!
While all of that was going on,
we have all the competitors in the ring!
Zoro-senpai!!
With one abstention,
there are 137 contenders for Block D!
You have to eat.
Do you know that man?
I-If you don't want it, I'm gonna eat it.
Who the hell is he?
Okay?
I'm really gonna eat it!
A tough warriors' battle royal!
Now, let's start...
Smells good!
Yeah! Go, Rebecca!
Damn!
How would you like this, then?!
You did it! Way to go!
She made another guy drop!
...the match!
Your mother was high-born.
Where is he?!
I'm here!
Go, go! Whew! Awesome!
He's getting really excited.
The Navy ship is flying towards us!
A diamond spear?
Do you know we have a new king now?
You've got to be kidding!
Alright!
Go, Rebecca!
How is that possible?!
Cavendish-sama!
It must be Fujitora.
The new king wants to capture
all the former nobility.
Doflamingo is coming from that way!
He even wants to capture
you because you have
I'm so glad to be back to myself!
The Navy ship is getting closer!
Decapitate somebody, Suleiman!
your mother's blood in your veins.
Thanks, Brook!
No!
Kick their asses, Orlumbus!
You did great, Bone-kichi.
You made me happy.
What?!
People like you who try to best me,
Although I couldn't protect your mother,
You can wait here if you want
but don't let them take Caesar!
Yeah, I thought I was
gonna die at that moment.
I'm gonna protect you to the end,
with my life!
I'll never forgive them!
Go to hell, Rebecca!
Fire!
You saved us, Brook.
Until the day you are filled with happiness,
Well, it's not that big a deal...
Watch me, Soldier-san!
I will always be by your side!
I mean, it is a very big deal! Yes!
GREEN BIT
We were wrong!
Cavendish-sama, you're so cool!
Let's have a sleep-in-your-lap party!
He's really strong!
What kind of party is that?!
I want my mother!
That hurts, Nami-san.
Now,
I don't like you, Soldier-san,
Something's falling from the sky!
Yes!
handcuff her, Brook.
because you couldn't protect my mother!
You hear that, Straw Hat Luffy?!
People cheer for me!
What?! Me?!
Meteorites?!
H-How do you like this?
I'm more popular than you!
I don't wanna touch those.
They drain my energy.
Room!
Or this?
Tra-guy-kun, we "Spiral Hats" are
gonna leave now!
Move, Cabbage!
I have no interest in your past but...
Stop complaining and just do it!
Or this?
I can't see Rebecca because of you!
I agree!
You're the only one who hasn't
eaten a Devil Fruit here
...only people who can use the World
Government just to deceive us are...
Where are you going, Rebecca?!
Just go!
so why don't you...
I'm going home!
Hey, Law!
--He's right!
--We don't wanna see you!
I said "Do it"!
You can't!
I realize we have
to carry Caesar as far as possible.
...the Celestial Dragons!
The new king's friends
Just go away!
are all over the town
and at your house looking for you!
Oh boy, oh boy!
It's clear we have to leave here now.
Doflamingo-sama!
So what?
Rebecca!
But I thought Dressrosa was just a waypoint.
Soul King! How dare you!
Doflamingo! Doflamingo!
Our main purpose was killing Kaido
of the Four Emperors, wasn't it?
I'm gonna take her down!
I got fooled completely!
The Riku family has been running
this poor country for centuries!
I thought we were connected
to each other because we're
Just as we expected,
both artists and I dropped my guard!
Aren't you getting too hung up
on Doflamingo?
contenders who are looking to gain fame are
In the end, they became shameless and robbed
You guys are such imprudent people!
money and goods from citizens for themselves!
I'm gonna imprint my
ultimate art on your mind
targeting the despised Rebecca!
It may be just a matter of time
before she gets defeated!
Meteorites! Meteorites!
I'm gonna make this country wealthy, instead!
and send you off to heaven!
Takt!
G-Giolla-san... R-Relax...
Rebecca, behind you!
Take this!
Issho-san, they hit the bottom of our ship!
Oops, I hadn't thought about that.
Law-san is there, isn't he?
You can't buy any more time, Law.
Heaven's Door Art!
Why don't you stop eating?!
I didn't know toys are capable to work.
You said "It's more complicated" earlier.
What did you mean by that?
I need money!
Kill her!
If you wanna chat with me,
hand Caesar over first.
--What the hell?!
--What happened?
And his heart.
Rebecca!
What's the matter?
Caesar is...
I mean, those SMILEs are
that important to you?!
Let's get back to Dressrosa now.
What?!
Chop her up and let her fall into the water!
The tide of the war...
I guess they are.
...will turn, it seems.
Without the SMILEs, Kaido's gonna
kill you and it's all over for you.
Tell them to turn around!
Yes, sir!
Room!
Shambles!
Idiot!
Look! I'm unbreakable!
I'm unbreakable and strong - a super toy!
Everybody, ready?!
I'm ready!
I'm ready, Nami-san!
You damn pip-squeak!
Soldier-san is a brave man
This is the pinnacle of artistry -
Heaven's Door Art!
I won't let you get away!
He will always be by your side
GREEN BIT
The whip, again!
Joker! Help me!
Fujitora?
She must be feeling cold.
Excuse me.
With this tin body, I don't feel anything.
Excess Whip String!
Why did you help him?
Oh, how beautiful this world of art is!
I have to stop you right there,
Heavenly Demon.
You guys should be happy!
Because you can die
seeing the most
Isn't this warmer?
I'm here to...
Yes, it's much warmer!
beautiful thing in the world!
Nami-ya! Listen.
...arrest him, not to kill him.
So you're the Celestial Dragon.
You have to sail where there are no clouds!
What?! Why?!
Soldier-san is a brave man
Doflamingo!
Doflamingo is a String-String Fruit eater!
He will always be by your side
He moves through the air
by attaching strings to clouds!
I was, to be exact.
He can't follow you if there are no clouds!
Alright.
Strings? I see!
Just go now!
But not anymore.
But I need Caesar's heart back, Law.
Get ready for Coup de Burst!
DRESSROSA - THE PALACE
What is "bloodline"? What is "destiny"?
I don't think there are that
many people who've led such
Gladius, why don't you cool down
a little bit?
Doflamingo, look!
a checkered life as mine.
Baby 5.
Law, what do you think you're doing?!
Can't you see how badly
By the way, you seem quite curious about
that "complication" that I mentioned.
that woman's betrayal
upsets our plan?
Explain it to me so I can understand!
Young Master-sama, don't worry about me!
The plan was simple: that woman, Violet,
captures "Black Foot" Sanji
Do you wanna hear about it?
I'm sorry, Law.
and looks into his mind
to see all of their strategies.
I wish I could tell the story of my life
before I met you, over drinks.
With that, we could foil all of their plans
and kill them all one by one.
But I don't have time for that.
I've got to do something about
the Straw Hats in Dressrosa.
But what did she do instead?!
Hey you!
I want to ask you something!
She beat up her own men and ran!
I know there are quite a few people
who underestimated them and got hurt.
No, calm down!
DRESSROSA - THE FLOWER FIELD
Hey, you on the second floor!
You're not gonna explode here, are you?!
How much is the rent here?
It's abandoned so you can just use it.
I'm talking to you! Say something!
Since the King Riku Army ransacked this area,
I despise and wish death
upon people who aren't
Hey, can't you hear me?!
so many residents have moved away.
punctual and who can't follow a plan!
You, right there!
It's warm in the house!
What's the matter, Fujitora?
Close the window.
No.
Hey!
Well...
There are other toys.
I heard a clap of thunder
from the direction of the sea.
I just met my hero - Luffy-senpai today
Other children as well.
Go out and play with them.
How does the sky look?
I guess you're gonna be safe here.
but now, Zoro-senpai is talking to me!
Thunder?
Since there are other people in the village,
I may be blind,
GLADIUS
THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY (THE PICA ARMY)
we have to follow the law.
I can't stop crying from happiness!
but I always thought I could tell the weather.
AN ANTI-DOFLAMINGO COALITION -
"THE KING RIKU ARMY" HEADQUARTERS
After you fall asleep at night,
I'll go back to my toy house.
Maybe I'm getting too old.
He's acting strange.
But I'll be back before you wake up.
Hey!
I believe Nami-ya can manipulate the weather.
I wonder who he is.
We brought the legendary heroes -
Usoland and Robiland!
To let you know I'm here all the time,
What's worse, she betrayed us - I mean,
Hey, I don't know who you are
The ship is here!
Hey, Joker!
I'll drop a new flower
petal through the crack
the Young Master. I'm not gonna
let her get away with that!
but can you tell us how to enter the Colosseum?
If you got it back, give it to me already!
in the window every morning.
Usopp! Robin!
All the doors are closed!
Violet was acting strange from last night.
My heart! My heart! Hey!
Give it to me now!
Z-Zoro-senpai is asking me a question!
Think about it.
With her Clairvoyance, she could've found
the Straw Hat's ship yesterday.
I never said that was Caesar's heart!
I'm so glad that I sailed out to the sea!
What?! You've been lording that
over me all along!
Good morning, Soldier-san!
Yellow Cub and Pink Bee Squad!
NORTHEAST DRESSROSA
IN THE DIRECTION OF GREEN BIT
Yeah, good morning!
What is he talking about?
Arrived from Green Bit!
In fact, my heart is missing from my body!
Seems like he got very excited.
Thank you, Leo!
You little monkey!
Hey, calm down and listen. We're...
Hey, you're not supposed
to be here, Violet-chan!
Yeah, I can't hear my heartbeat!
The time has come, Commander!
There are so many clothes that would fit you!
I wish you were there to see it, Zoro-senpai!
I told you to wait at the harbor!
This battle is to restore
the honor of King Riku
Cute!
Luffy-senpai was awesome as hell!
The Navy soldiers are
everywhere at the harbor.
who was dethroned in
disappointment ten years ago
Cool!
You and your friends may want to
change your rendezvous point.
I just heard him say Luffy-dono
and Zoro-dono's names now!
Joker! What are you doing?!
You're killing me! I'm gonna die!
and to take back our freedom!
W-We're not here shopping for me.
Go ahead and pick out what you want.
I see. The Navy...
Yes!
There are four Navy ships.
That day, Doflamingo came to this country
and took away everything with violence!
Why does he know who you two are?
At least three thousand Navy soldiers
are here now.
I'll never forget that!
I don't know.
You found out all of that alone
in that short amount of time?
I didn't feel anything.
Ta-dah!
It's one of my abilities.
What?!
Hey, what's wrong?! Stay with me! Hey!
Clairvoyance.
With this power, I can see
things within a 4000km
You're small but you really go at it!
We spent one whole year...
Now, the battle royal here
in the Corrida Colosseum!
...preparing our plan!
I need money.
diameter as from a bird's point of view.
What?! Was it a Navy soldier's?!
Then, where's mine?!
Only one winner from Block D can
move to the finals!
Even though they're the Warlord's pirate group,
we have a chance to win!
I heard my man screaming!
H-Hey!
What are you doing, Heavenly Demon?!
I need money!
They are all fighting intensely
to get that one spot!
Room!
Happy Birthday, Rebecca!
I should listen to their plan carefully
and look for the best timing to get away!
Keep pinning me down with gravity, Fujitora.
Or I'll run!
DRESSROSA - ACACIA
It's yummy!
Shambles!
Zoroland, we're gonna turn left soon.
The way she moves...
I can see everything that's
going in this country from here.
I don't think she's just another gladiator.
Left is the side that you
don't have your swords.
What? What?!
--You don't even trust me with "right" and "left"?
--Not at all!
So you don't have to worry about me.
But why?
Why doesn't she make an
attack even passing up
They can't catch me.
Here!
Joker! Help me!
some critical chances?
Then, are you gonna stay in this country?
The one who's attacking your ship is...
Rebecca! Try to catch this!
No. Don't worry.
...one of the executives of the Don Quixote Family -
Giolla!
You still have that much energy, Law?
Ouch!
What I'm gonna do is...
She can disarm her opponent
in an artistic way!
How did you like it?!
Violet-chan?
He just doesn't know when to give up.
She's quite strong!
It's odd.
Hey!
You know that much?!
I can't find your ship anywhere!
I memorized the names and
faces and abilities of those
What?!
You bastard! Let go of me, Law!
Where's my heart?!
at the executive rank and
up as much as I could!
What is she doing?!
She's at the edge of the ring!
What do you want?
Um...
Especially those three top executives...
Read this!
You'd better worry about yourself
before you worry about someone else!
Hey!
Don't give me trouble, you squirt!
...who destroyed the entire Dressrosa army
ten years ago.
W-Why?
Rebecca will be fine.
Trébol!
What should we do?! Hey!
What should we do?!
Here!
You know there's no place to run!
Diamante!
Pica! I'll never forget those three faces!
What can we do?!
Here!
Bye-bye!
Go get them!
We've no choice but to fight!
Ten years ago? How old are you?
Hey, stop backing up!
I'm 27!
You're at the edge now!
Y-You're 27?!
All right! Stay at it!
Weather Egg!
It's not all right!
You see Tra-guy?
He's...
She must be an orphan.
Well, you'll see.
This way!
Come hatch, thunder-chan!
I can't see clearly because of the fog.
I see a weird forest.
She has no family who cares about her.
Zoro-dono! Zoro-dono!
We're here! Hey!
Take it!
Rebecca!
Don't shout, you fool!
What the hell is this?
Who are they?!
They're fooling around with each other.
Prepare for death, you little tramp!
Spiral-eyebrows-land and Topknot-land.
I don't wanna believe
what that old bat said but...
Rebecca!
What?!
Where are you?!
Rebecca!
...what if, what if Tra-guy's
plan didn't work out well
Your technique is not very beautiful.
What?! Are you gonna go save Nami-san?!
Rebecca!!
Go to hell, Rebecca!
Just finish her off!
So she was in trouble!
That's why she didn't pick up the Snail!
and if we take Caesar with us,
what's gonna happen, then?
For these kinds of things, I would do this...
She's cute. We probably can
sell her for a high price.
Drop dead!
Okay, I'm coming with you!
Doflamingo will come after us.
...and this...
Wait, Sanji-dono!
Rebecca!
--What?!
--Huh?
.We're here to tell
Luffy-dono what's going on!
Rebecca!
I'm scared!
...and this, to accentuate its beauty!
Hey, that strange toy is chasing us.
Black Foot!
Ow, ow, ow...
My sweet Violet-chan!
What? What? What just happened?!
Rebecca!
Soldier-san!
I wish that dumb passion
would kill you already.
My colleague, Giolla, hijacked your ship!
Who cares.
He's not gonna catch up with us.
Brook!
What?
Wh-What's going on?
And they're on their way to Green Bit!
Will you excuse me
for cutting you, Giolla-san?!
There is something in the water!
Alright!
You bastard!
Who's going to win the battle royal for Block D?!
I-I-It's a school of the Fighting Fish!
You're just a toy!
Don't stand against humans!
See?
I'm gonna destroy you!
That's my girl, Rebecca!
I can't get eliminated here!
This Heaven's Door Art is imbued with my soul
You got too close to the island!
No matter what it takes, I'll win this
What?
for pursuing ultimate beauty!
Soldier-san!
The Fighting Fish?
and get the Flare-Flare Fruit
What did she just do?
What are they?
so I can take down Doflamingo!
The greatest beauty is the strongest!
Rebecca!
They're killer fish that can sink a warship!
--What?!
--O-Nami!
Let's start with Rebecca!
Cola barrels have been set!
Good idea!
Nice, Chopper!
I'm sorry.
Yeah, we barely outran
the Navy and Doflamingo.
They put me on the wanted list.
And I will protect Soldier-san this time!
What is this?
I'm on it, too! Let's find a new place!
It's the Sunny's source of power.
We're gonna head for Zou.
Huh? No, wait, Sanji!
Are you gonna leave us?!
With that, we can fire the Gaon Cannon!
The Gaon Cannon?!
Sorry.
Get through somehow and meet us there.
I want to live with you one day,
in the same house.
Everybody hates you, Rebecca-chan!
What?!
If I remember correctly,
I put a target in the circle with this.
I'm ready to get away
as soon as I have a chance!
If I defeat you, I'm gonna
become the hero of the country!
Come after me, Doflamingo!
If he goes for the ship,
it's all over for us!
You can't do that to me!
I wish Usopp were here
but the target is big so I can do it!
Sorry.
Let me teach you how to fight.
Sanji, we'll be alright!
I'm gonna draw him to the bridge
It's not fair!
There's no need since I have you.
You can go to Zou (elephant)
or Giraffe or wherever!
and get Caesar on board the ship
Those five men are going for Rebecca at once!
Brook! It's ready!
Get out of the way!
If something happens to
me, what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna destroy the factory for sure!
You're right. But it's always like that
when Rebecca enters a competition.
I got it!
and fight Doflamingo on the bridge
Come on!
My mother said I shouldn't hurt anyone!
What are Luffy and Law doing?
so I can buy enough time
for the ship to get away!
I'm gonna teach you how to not get hurt!
Zoro and Kin'emon went
to tell Luffy what's going on.
Most of the time, Rebecca is the only woman
competing among tough guys!
Come on!
What?
Law is...
In addition, everybody in the Colosseum
wants to see Rebecca beaten!
Is he gonna go across the bridge?
I don't get it.
Why does he want to get to Dressrosa?
Okay!
Alright! Here we go!
It's more favorable for me.
I don't wanna do it anymore!
So it's only natural that
they're going for Rebecca first!
The Gaon Cannon!
Take up your sword!
Alright, here we go!
Fire!
Listen. We're not playing here!
Go get them, Rebecca! Don't lose!
What is that?
Go go, Rebecca!
Let's have fun, Rebecca-chan!
Faster!
Use the lower half of your body!
No! Idiots!
We're gonna do this everyday!
You do realize you can attack, too, right?
I get it.
What?!
You think you're better than me?!
Wait, Doflamingo!
They have nothing to do with this!
It's over, Law!
What?!
The ship is gonna break up!
--Screw you!
--Dammit!
He has always been by my side
--You bitch!
--Go to hell!
Stop! Or I'm gonna grill you!
and he saved me so many times.
Yes!
Damn!
What's the point in letting half
of the Straw Hats get away?
You're such a coward, Rebecca!
Show us blood!
Kill each other!
Here she comes!
Where did those Fighting Fish go?
The other half is in Dressrosa.
Are you all ready?!
Bone-kichi, where did they go?
How dare you!
I'm not gonna let you get away with it!
If I take them as hostages,
they'll come back
She's the most beautiful
gladiator in the Colosseum!
The Fighting Fish... The Fighting Fish...
The Fighting Fish...
right away to return Caesar to me.
The "Phantom Princess"!
--Just how tough is she?!
--She just won't go away!
Let me teach you how to fight.
What?!
No one else can make
the place heat up like she does!
I thought that you knew
there are quite a few people...
My mother said I shouldn't hurt anyone!
What is it this time?!
I'm gonna go all out now!
You pissed me off!
--Doflamingo is flying towards us!
--What?!
...who underestimated them like that
and got burned.
Please don't die, Soldier-san!
You...
Young Master-sama!
Alright, who wants to die first?!
I won't...
What is this?! A nightmare?!
Are we gonna get killed?!
All you can do is deflect attacks?!
I'm afraid that I have to break up my alliance
with the Straw Hats now.
--Screw you, Rebecca!
--Cut her to pieces!
No!
Head blow!
Take this!
Watch this, Law!
King Riku's line - burn in hell!
I'm gonna teach you how to not get hurt!
I'll viciously slay your allies
right before your eyes!
When I joined forces with them,
You damn brat!
A corrupted family!
my only purpose was to use them
to stop the manufacture of SMILEs.
Drop dead!
Momo-chan, move aside!
...give up, either!
Don't!
What?!
Even if I can't kill you right now,
Tra-guy, help...
Stand up, Rebecca!
--What's wrong?
--It's bad.
You have to become stronger!
Hey!
Kaido will kill you sooner or later
once you lose all the SMILEs.
Your ship emerged out of nowhere
and it's been hit by lightning!
You bitch! Stop moving around!
My friends are crying in fear!
What?!
Lightning?!
Why does everyone hate her so much?!
Leave them alone!
Screw you!
Oh, lightning...
She's a very nice person! Screw them!
I see.
Sanji!
So you're gonna sacrifice
yourself to kill me.
She bought me lunch...
I know!
Wh-Who did you call Ms. Mermaid...
I want to see how the world
falls into a mess after you die,
But Rebecca's grandfather is...
Way to go, Rebecca!
...despised by the whole country!
He's the former king!
but more importantly, I want to make
you pay for what you did 13 years ago.
--You did it, Momonosuke!
--Yes, I did!
Stay at it!
I won't give up!
No problem!
Here comes quite a tough one.
Joker!