Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the
prize for a fighting event
was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
he decided to enter and fight
fierce battles against other tough
contenders from the New World.
Fujitora?
Excuse me.
Why did you help him?
I have to stop you right there,
Heavenly Demon.
I'm here to...
...arrest him, not to kill him.
By the way,
you seem quite curious about
that "complication" that I mentioned.
Do you wanna hear about it?
"A Decisive Battle!
Giolla vs. the Straw Hats!"
A long time ago...
It goes back 800 years, Law.
20 kings from 20 countries came together
at the center of the world
and formed one giant organization.
That's what we call
the World Government now.
The kings who created it...
...decided to move to the
Holy land of Marie Jois
and live there with their families.
The Nefeltari Family of Alabasta refused,
so there were 19 families to be exact.
The descendents of those
creators who still live there
and reign over the world
are the Celestial Dragons.
It means, however, that those
19 countries lost their royal
families 800 years ago.
Are you following?
In those countries, they elected
new kings out of necessity
and new royal families rose.
In the case of my country - Dressrosa,
the new royalty was the Riku Family.
And the old royalty who moved to the
Holyland of Marie Jois as the
creators of the world were
...the Don Quixote Family!
That means you're...
It's so fun!
The great music and the art of the sea, yeah!
You sure know art, don't you?!
Stop the ship!
Don't tell me you're going to Green Bit!
Law would be stunned!
If I come to pick up Caesar,
not you guys!
Brook is acting strange!
Are you gonna turn around on us?!
Bone-kichi!
You call yourself a swordsman
but betray your friends?!
I just realized something!
I'm an artist after all!
I'm living to create!
I'm dead though!
Boy!
These ordinary people can't
understand, Soul King!
More than anything, we
want to express ourselves!
They don't understand that kind of passion!
This is an art of life! Dying Art!
That's amazing, Giolla-san!
No!
Help!
I'm fine...
I couldn't be more excited!
I represented the tragedy of
Dressrosa quite exquisitely!
In 10 minutes or so,
these annoying kids will
become part of the art completely
and choke to death!
--What?!
--Brook!
Bone-kichi!
I can't tell you how impressed I am!
Let me play a song to celebrate!
Would you mind doing so, Soul King?!
Yes, I'd love to!
So could you turn my violin
and bow back, Giolla-san?
Alright! Take it away, brother!
Wow, thank you!
No!
I'm not... suffering...
I'm almost unconscious...
I don't wanna die!
Take a look at this, Giolla-san,
this bow is actually a cane sword.
Uh-huh, uh-huh, play nice music for me!
Okay! I cut you already.
Cut me?!
Painting Song Bamboo Flute Slice!
PAINTING SONG BAMBOO FLUTE SLICE
JOINT
I'm sorry but I don't understand
art after all because...
...my eyes
KNOTHOLE
are like knotholes!
Brook!
Bone-kichi!
I started to worry
about Nami-san before you did!
And I know she wants me
to come instead of you!
So I'm going!
Alright! Go!
Kin'emon, this is a map to the
Toy House where your friend is.
Oh, thank you!
When you get to see Luffy,
contact the Sunny with this.
Let's check to see what everybody is doing.
I'll stay on the Sunny.
Now, how can we reach Luffy?
If I knew how,
we wouldn't be standing here.
The place is all closed up
and I don't see anybody to ask.
We should not make a bold move.
I almost got caught earlier.
Then should I just chop up the wall?
That's what I call a bold move!
I can slice it gently instead?
That's not the point! Boy!
--We have to be careful!
--How do you want me to cut it then?!
That's "Pirate Hunter" Zoro-senpai!
They say he chopped up 100 men
in Whisky Peak
and rampaged through Enies Lobby!
The Three-Sword Style swordsman!
He's always supporting the Straw Hats
as Luffy-senpai's right-hand man
and is considered vice captain!
He's so cool!
Oh? Why am I crying? Why?
Zoro-senpai!!
Do you know that man?
Who the hell is he?
Yeah! Go, Rebecca!
You did it! Way to go!
She made another guy drop!
Go, go! Whew! Awesome!
He's getting really excited.
Go, Rebecca!
I'm so glad to be back to myself!
Thanks, Brook!
You did great, Bone-kichi.
You made me happy.
Yeah, I thought I was
gonna die at that moment.
You saved us, Brook.
Well, it's not that big a deal...
I mean, it is a very big deal! Yes!
Let's have a sleep-in-your-lap party!
What kind of party is that?!
That hurts, Nami-san.
Now,
handcuff her, Brook.
What?! Me?!
I don't wanna touch those.
They drain my energy.
Stop complaining and just do it!
You're the only one who hasn't
eaten a Devil Fruit here
so why don't you...
I said "Do it"!
Oh boy, oh boy!
Soul King! How dare you!
I got fooled completely!
I thought we were connected
to each other because we're
both artists and I dropped my guard!
You guys are such imprudent people!
I'm gonna imprint my
ultimate art on your mind
and send you off to heaven!
G-Giolla-san... R-Relax...
Heaven's Door Art!
--What the hell?!
--What happened?
What?!
This is the pinnacle of artistry -
Heaven's Door Art!
Oh, how beautiful this world of art is!
You guys should be happy!
Because you can die
seeing the most
beautiful thing in the world!
DRESSROSA - THE PALACE
Gladius, why don't you cool down
a little bit?
Baby 5.
Can't you see how badly
that woman's betrayal
upsets our plan?
The plan was simple: that woman, Violet,
captures "Black Foot" Sanji
and looks into his mind
to see all of their strategies.
With that, we could foil all of their plans
and kill them all one by one.
But what did she do instead?!
She beat up her own men and ran!
No, calm down!
You're not gonna explode here, are you?!
I despise and wish death
upon people who aren't
punctual and who can't follow a plan!
GLADIUS
THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY (THE PICA ARMY)
What's worse, she betrayed us - I mean,
the Young Master. I'm not gonna
let her get away with that!
Violet was acting strange from last night.
Think about it.
With her Clairvoyance, she could've found
the Straw Hat's ship yesterday.
NORTHEAST DRESSROSA
IN THE DIRECTION OF GREEN BIT
Hey, you're not supposed
to be here, Violet-chan!
I told you to wait at the harbor!
The Navy soldiers are
everywhere at the harbor.
You and your friends may want to
change your rendezvous point.
I see. The Navy...
There are four Navy ships.
At least three thousand Navy soldiers
are here now.
You found out all of that alone
in that short amount of time?
It's one of my abilities.
Clairvoyance.
With this power, I can see
things within a 4000km
diameter as from a bird's point of view.
I can see everything that's
going in this country from here.
So you don't have to worry about me.
They can't catch me.
Then, are you gonna stay in this country?
No. Don't worry.
What I'm gonna do is...
Violet-chan?
It's odd.
I can't find your ship anywhere!
What?!
What should we do?! Hey!
What should we do?!
What can we do?!
We've no choice but to fight!
Weather Egg!
Come hatch, thunder-chan!
Take it!
What the hell is this?
What?!
Your technique is not very beautiful.
For these kinds of things, I would do this...
...and this...
...and this, to accentuate its beauty!
Brook!
Will you excuse me
for cutting you, Giolla-san?!
This Heaven's Door Art is imbued with my soul
for pursuing ultimate beauty!
The greatest beauty is the strongest!
Cola barrels have been set!
Nice, Chopper!
What is this?
It's the Sunny's source of power.
With that, we can fire the Gaon Cannon!
The Gaon Cannon?!
If I remember correctly,
I put a target in the circle with this.
I wish Usopp were here
but the target is big so I can do it!
Brook! It's ready!
Get out of the way!
I got it!
Okay!
Alright! Here we go!
The Gaon Cannon!
Fire!
What is that?
Yes!
How dare you!
I'm not gonna let you get away with it!
--Just how tough is she?!
--She just won't go away!
I'm gonna go all out now!
You pissed me off!
Alright, who wants to die first?!
Head blow!
You damn brat!
Momo-chan, move aside!
--What's wrong?
--It's bad.
Your ship emerged out of nowhere
and it's been hit by lightning!
Lightning?!
Oh, lightning...
Wh-Who did you call Ms. Mermaid...
--You did it, Momonosuke!
--Yes, I did!
No problem!