Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass, We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass, We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed everyday, Go east, Go west!
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed everyday, Go east, Go west!
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we want to do and doing them all
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we want to do and doing them all
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the morning (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the morning (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
sore nara isso taiyou sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
sore nara isso taiyou sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel something - that's the treasure
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel something - that's the treasure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of burning, intense excitement!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of burning, intense excitement!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
omoi no mama mezasu basho e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to go - that's the adventure
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
omoi no mama mezasu basho e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to go - that's the adventure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power will seize the "end of the dream"
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
a boy whose body turned
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
and have come to Dressrosa.
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
Now, the detail of the
Luffy entered a fighting competition - in which a winner will
get the Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize - and won the first round.
Luffy entered a fighting competition - in which a winner will get
Luffy entered a fighting competition
- in which a winner will
nightmare that Dressrosa faced
10 years ago is revealed.
When Luffy found out that the prize for a fighting event
was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
the Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize - and won the first round.
get the Flare-Flare Fruit as the
prize - and won the first round.
And while the last match of the first round is on,
the losers are...
I am the rightful king of this country!
And now, I'm...
And Rebecca, the gladiator girl Luffy supports,
And Rebecca, the gladiator
girl Luffy supports,
is now fighting the last match of the first round.
he decided to enter and fight fierce battles
against other tough contenders from the New World.
...back!
is fighting hard in the last match of the first round.
You're...
I didn't know she used the Observation Haki!
I'm going to sell you this country
for 10 billion berries.
I mean, you, sir, are...
Haki?
Premier Hachis Hash!
She has also never been
wounded by anybody
Please let me borrow all of your money!
...King Riku-sama, aren't you?
and she won it all by letting opponents fall out of the ring!
"A Big Surprise!
A True Identity of the Toy Soldier!"
She has never been defeated!
Since I'm deep underground now,
Pentachromatic Strings!
I no longer need to disguise myself.
Stop! Don't make me do this!
Overheat!
Let's see what happens
if I break your bones!
--King Riku-sama, please stop!
--What are you doing?!
Ill Weed-chan!
"A Horrible Past!
The Secret of Dressrosa!"
Room!
L-L-L-L....
Law, eh?
If I bring Luffy-senpai here,
can I have your autograph?
Everyone!
Luffy-senpai!
Boy... What kind of king he is!
I want you to take him
and head for Zou!
THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
You can do that for me?
I'll be counting on you!
L-L-Luffy-senpai!
Well, the night has just begun, soldiers.
Luffy-senpai!
The Navy ship is flying towards us!
Hey! You must be Bartolomeo-kun.
I'm gonna bring him at the risk of my life!
You should dance, too!
Doflamingo is coming from that way!
Oh?! You must be...
You were pretty impressive in the Block B match!
Oh, wait! No! My name is Lucy!
Yes, I am, Luffy-senpai!
I've got to do this right!
That's not important now...
Meteorites?!
Y-Y-You know my name?!
Parasite String!
Room!
Oh, I can't!
I'm too nervous to even speak.
Wh-What the hell? What's going on?!
Hey, Law!
Of course, I do!
M-My arm is moving on its own!
"The Most Violent Fighter!
Logan vs. Rebecca!"
I realize we have
to carry Caesar as far as possible.
Let's wish each other good luck in the finals!
Why does it move on its own?!
If you've got nothing to say, I'm gonna go now.
I wanna go support Rebecca.
It's clear we have to leave here now.
I have no chance!
Is it what's happening to King-sama?!
I'm just a guy who set out to the sea
wanting to be like you!
But I thought Dressrosa was just a waypoint.
Don't go!
There's no way to justify myself!
I was asked by Z-Z-Zoro-senpai!
This country is finished!
Our main purpose was killing Kaido of the Four Emperors,
wasn't it?
What?! By Zoro?!
Doflamingo set us up!
Yes!
He asked me to bring Luffy-senpai to him!
Let's see...
I have to be careful
not to bump into Luffy-senpai.
Aren't you getting too hung up
on Doflamingo?
Which way was it to the
place to watch the fight?
Oh, that way!
Because his awesomeness might blind my eyes and make my heart explode.
I see! Where is he?
Hey, hey!
Can we do it already, Doffy?
Luffy-senpai!
H-He's outside of the Colosseum.
Get ready for Coup de Burst!
I-I'm gonna show you! This way!
I need to look for him with caution.
Idiot. Don't rush.
I'm afraid that I have to break up my alliance
with the Straw Hats now.
Come to think of it, since the captain
and the vice captain are here,
Okay!
I'm counting on you, Crest Head!
I have to make the people tremble
with fear more
other members must be here
on the island, too.
and get them hate King Riku
with all their heart!
"Counting on you, Crest Head"?!
Luffy-senpai's counting on me and...
When I joined forces with them,
my only purpose was to use them
to stop the manufacture of SMILEs.
And then, the heroes will appear!
Sniperking-senpai and...
I'm counting on you, Crest Head!
..."Black Foot" Sanji-senpai!
...he gave me a nickname!
That means...
Whoa-whoa, people keep
falling one after another.
Even if I can't kill you right now,
Sis Nami!
I'm counting on you, Crest Head!
The great doctor - Chopper-senpai and...
...I'm Luffy-senpai's friend now?!
...Big Sis Nico Robin!
Kaido will kill you sooner or later
once you lose all the SMILEs.
The great shipwright - Franky-senpai!
Hey, what's wrong?
"A Nightmare!
The Tragic Night of Dressrosa!"
I see.
The great musician - Soul King - Brook-senpai!
So you're gonna sacrifice
yourself to kill me.
Oh, grandpa!
I can see them, too!
I want to see how the world falls into a mess
after you die,
Brother!
I'm getting really nervous!
I can't help getting excited!
It stinks!
Hi, Boo.
but more importantly,
I want to make you pay for what you did 13 years ago.
Heated fights are going on
in the battle royal of Block D!
By the way,
I know I didn't miss a thing
Where are we?
A stack of toys and trash?
but why isn't there anyone here,
besides Luffy-senpai?
Joker!
What is this place, brother?
How do we know?
There were a whole bunch
of people here earlier.
"Rebecca's Special Attack!
Back-to-the-Water Dance!"
The next one will fall there.
Get out of his way!
Is that...
--What happened to King-sama?!
--The whole country is in chaos!
...a staircase?
I haven't been downstairs.
I can't believe there is such a huge
junkyard underneath the kingdom.
He didn't look right
when he left the palace earlier
She's so persistent! Very tenacious!
The contender - Rebecca!
It's really creepy down here.
but I didn't expect this!
I don't think Luffy-senpai is here
in such a gloomy place.
It's more than we can handle within
the country so I called the Navy!
Sorry if I'm wrong.
You want to make me pay?
For what I did 13 years ago?
Captain Vergo said
he's gonna take care of it!
What is it? I hear voices.
Watching her not-unbeautiful fighting style
makes me...
But I have the slight suspicion that...
Oh, that's good!
You know what I'm talking about.
Hurry up! Out of our way!
...you're...
...wanna not unsupport her!
Father-sama!
Get out of our way!
What are you gonna do with Giolla?
I mean, you, sir, are...
You know what kind of family we are.
What is this place?
I'm Rebecca's real father!
A WAITING ROOM FOR MEDICAL TREATMENT
IN THE BASEMENT OF THE COLOSSEUM
He's right, Law!
I don't mind sacrificing myself for the Young Master!
...King Riku-sama, aren't you?
Next! Come in!
There are so many people here.
You better run as far as you can.
Well, let's go look.
--King Riku?!
--No way!
I'm not gonna leave
the Young Master and run!
Father-sama...
They're all injured.
Is Luffy-senpai here?
THE KING RIKU ARMY HEADQUARTERS
Why?
I don't need you.
Hey, look!
I don't need you here. Just go.
Why are you doing that?!
Why is he here?! This is bad!
He's gonna agitate everybody here!
Y-Yes, sir!
He's King Riku?! That's absurd!
Mr. Bartolomeo!
Wh-Why are you here?
I thought he was dead.
I'm looking for someone. Excuse me.
I heard the former king of Dressrosa...
Y-You shouldn't be here!
I saw Black Foot earlier.
This is where we treat the losers!
...resorted to unbelievable
violence and got killed!
Which means our plan is not going so well.
A-Are you?!
If they see you...
Treat the losers?
Drop dead already, Rebecca!
Snow?
--You kin of King Riku!
--Part of that evil family!
I see! They're losers!
You lost your trump card, Caesar.
Granddaughter of the pyromaniac!
Go to hell!
Damn you! Did you come here to make fun of us, Bartolomeo?!
If you're her father...
You will lose the SMILE factory
while you're fighting me here.
Since I'm deep underground now,
If you're telling the truth,
since she's King Riku's granddaughter...
You won the match with your pathetic power!
Monet! What are you doing there?!
I no longer need to disguise myself.
I'll kick your ass right here!
When you were a human,
don't tell me you were...
You're a maid!
S-See, I told you!
Why are you opening the gate of the palace?!
Please don't cause any trouble in here!
This will be your end.
Everything started that night.
All right. I think he has no business here.
Princess Viola.
Hey, answer my question!
It is unreasonable for you to hold a grudge against me,
Law!
If you use your Clairvoyance,
you can see clearly...
Were you King Riku's...
Sorry to bother you all!
No, it might
have started long before.
Get yourselves looked at!
...what is happening in this country!
You're right.
It's not a grudge.
But don't call me "King" anymore,
Captain Tank!
Since the day a woman named Monet
started to work at the palace...
What did he come here for?
I'm waiting to welcome
the new royal family.
What?
I've been living my life until today...
Monet?!
Next! Mr. Sai from the Kano Kingdom!
...to attain that man's
long-cherished ambition!
THE FORMER KING OF DRESSROSA
Next?!
He's King Riku!
The bird woman that we encountered
in Punk Hazard?
Our old man that you carried in
hasn't come out yet!
RIKU DOLDO III
(REBECCA'S GRANDFATHER)
I can't believe he's alive!
This country has changed
in a big way last decade.
Oh, Mr. Chin Jao.
Is he dead?! Huh?!
Both the scenery and the people!
King Riku-sama!
I'm so happy to see you again!
DRESSROSA - 10 YEARS AGO
Ah? What's going on?
I'm just another old man now.
Shut up, you martial arts fool!
He's quite tough but he is really old now!
Just a sinful old man who can't
even save his own granddaughter.
Hey, what happened?
Some pirates did this.
If he's dead, don't hide it!
It's been a while!
But the King Riku Army fought for us
so we got away with this little damage.
He's so loud.
I am now...
Wh-What are you...
You're overreacting.
Oh, the King Riku Army!
...Doflamingo's...
Mr. Chin Jao hasn't come out here
because...
Don't say it!
Now, shall we?
I know.
...there is an exit at the back of the room
Viola-sama.
I have a message from King Riku-sama.
and those who are treated are not coming back here.
You're watching over Viola.
OFF THE COAST OF DRESSROSA
What? From King-sama?!
Oh, is that so? I'm sorry.
How could I disbelieve
a dutiful man like you?
"I'm sorry that I couldn't protect
my dear citizen's house from the pirates."
--The east tower has been bombed!
--Some pirates have breached the palace!
Do you understand?
Then, please come in.
It must've been hard for you.
They took Viola-sama!
"The King Riku Army will handle
the repair of your house."
The palace is not too bad.
It's kind of nice.
It's nothing compared with
what you've gone through.
I'm sorry for getting it wrong!
We barely got away
from Doflamingo but...
--That's more than we deserve!
--Don't worry. Guys, get to work!
Really, I'm sorry!
How can I even make it up to you?
Yeah, I love it-dasuyan!
...will Tra-guy be okay?
I can't believe it! You are King Riku!
It's perfect for Young Master-sama-in!
Alright! Let's help them!
Hey, guys!
Are you keeping a lookout?
I'm on my knees! Please forgive me!
Yeah! We help each another when someone's in trouble.
Oh! You're the king of Prodence!
--Stop, you fools!
--Are you Doflamingo's clan?
This is Brook here! It looks all serene
from a 45-degree angle!
That's what King Riku-sama always says!
Don't worry!
He gets emotional easily.
Monet! Let go of Viola-sama!
Long time no see!
Okay! Let's do it together!
Did you guys do something to King Riku-sama?!
You saved my kingdom when we
were in trouble many times!
Oh, I see...
You gotta look in all directions!
This way, sir. Please come in.
All right, ma'am!
A 360-degree spin!
Now, we have a lot to do!
I'm glad that you're alive!
Whoa-whoa!
We have to "clean up" the whole palace!
Since you've been gone,
Mr. Sai from the Kano Kingdom, am I correct?
the countries around here lost balance
and there's been war after war!
Yeah.
Lie down on the bed here.
Father-sama!
It's been two weeks without rain.
I see some clouds now.
Like this?
I'm sick and tired of it.
Yes. And close your eyes.
Yeah but even during this drought,
the flowers don't die.
I can't believe that guy can move through the air
by attaching strings to clouds!
Wait a minute, Elizabello!
All right. We're going to start.
Why is that?
Maybe you're tired of it but
each time somebody cries,
It's thanks to the fairies.
Brook!
Don't miss even a slight movement.
They are protecting the flowers.
somebody else laughs!
What the...
Oh, I don't know
since my eyes are like...
Next! Come in!
I wanna eat more!
Someone is agitating the countries to fight
and making millions!
--If you have energy to shout, you're fine.
--What?
...knotholes!
Although we're very poor,
we don't have to fight in a war in this country.
By selling tons of weapons
to those countries at war!
Why are you doing such a thing?!
King Riku Army!
If he comes flying towards us again,
I'll generate strong wind and blow the clouds away!
That's the best thing. Don't you think so?
Please stop!
Ow, ow, ow...
Then he can't chase us.
What is this? A toy?
Is this a stack of toys?
Boy... That broker is named Joker.
Uh-huh!
That's a good idea.
Only Nami-san could've come up with it.
For 800 years
under the reign of the Riku Family,
And that's Doflamingo's alias.
Toys and fighters.
But I wonder if it's really okay for us to head to Zou
like Law told us.
this country had never been involved
in a war.
Who is it?
But we don't know where they manufacture
those weapons or keep them.
That's amazing.
Yeah.
It's miraculous for a country.
We were under attack by the Navy and Doflamingo
at that moment so we needed to get away but...
Please stop!
Hajrudin!
Our country, the Kano Kingdom,
is at war now
Even though the country was poor,
the people and fairies all helped each other
You guys?
and we're in trouble because the
enemy keeps getting weapons.
Why are you all here?
In any case, you guys gotta protect Robin-chan
even if it costs your life! Okay?
and were rich in spirit.
Old man! You're alive!
That's great!
Dressrosa was a very peaceful country.
However...
We entered the competition in the Colosseum
just to search for the weapons!
Clank.
What's so great, you fool?!
How were they?
My precious Robin-chan is
with Franky and Usopp.
I guess they dropped all the losers of
the competition in here.
We Happo Navy's true purpose is
to break down the smuggling ring of weapons...
A "nightmare" came flying to the palace
out of the blue!
Then, if Zoro and Kin'emon can meet Luffy,
everything's okay, right?
What?!
What do you mean by that?!
How can I get out of here?!
...by the request of the king
of the Kano Kingdom!
Yeah, but Zoro is bad at directions.
I don't know if he can make it to the Colosseum.
King Riku! Because you did such a foolish thing
and Doflamingo became king,
There's no way out!
We must've got set up by Doflamingo!
the neighboring countries are in trouble!
Well, Kin'emon's with him so he'll be fine.
This means war, Elizabello-sama!
Who are you?
I wonder if Tra-guy is okay.
I can't believe it but, even with my King Punch,
I can't break this wall.
He's right, Elizabello-sama!
His plan was not to kill Doflamingo
but let Kaido of the Four Emperors take care of him.
Yes, we were deeply indebted to
Dressrosa in the past
Whoa-whoa, we're underground.
That means the wall is the ground itself.
Don't try to scream or call for help.
If there's no preventing me
hurting the citizens...
but there's no need to keep affection for
that man anymore!
Y-You are...
As long as he focuses on getting away,
he'll be fine.
No matter how strong your punch is,
it's impossible to break it.
The name "King Riku" is now...
Uh-huh.
My name is Don Quixote Doflamingo.
Shut up, Dagama!
What are they gonna do
collecting us here?
I'd rather be dead!
I guess you know what my name suggests,
don't you?
What's the matter, Momo?
You turned into a dragon, again.
You don't know what really
happened 10 years ago -
Somebody, please...
I don't think they're gonna treat us here.
...kill me!
the tragedy of that day!
I-I thought back and I can't stop shaking.
So don't talk shit
about the king's personality!
I've been troubled by hearing
about a pirate named Don Quixote these days.
That man who flies...
Tank! It's okay!
It's too late to say anything!
If this turns out badly, Doflamingo,
You mean Doflamingo.
Yes, you were right to be troubled.
King Riku-sama, I, too, was...
I'll carry this anger
even towards your grandchildren!
I saw him
the last time I came to Dressrosa.
Why is it, King Riku-sama?
...a soldier of the army!
I'm a descendent of the Don Quixote Family
that once governed this country.
What?
Did we do something wrong?
Me, too!
Me, too, King Riku-sama!
Listen to this rousing cheer!
Young Master, you're gonna kill him!
Now, the potential winner of Block D...
I am the rightful king of this country!
And now, I'm...
What's your problem?
You were always just.
...Rolling Logan sets his sights on Rebecca!
...back!
What the...
You were...
The toys are starting to move!
Who are you?
You're a gladiator, aren't you?
...the king we were proud of.
But you robbed a transport ship
of the Heavenly Tribute
I thought they were all broken!
Let's see!
Which bone should I break?
of money for the Celestial Dragons
from various countries
You told us that you needed our money.
and became a Warlord by blackmailing
the World Government, I heard.
Who wants to see
you guys running around?
Should I break her neck?
So we've brought you all our money.
Neck!
If you can't chop anybody up,
at least get yourself sliced and show people your blood!
They don't know what to do with me.
Or spine?
They can't handle me
because I'm not afraid of the Celestial Dragons.
Spine!
No matter how great
his or her personality is,
Because you've...
Or...
Since you know my status and what I'm capable of,
I'm just gonna cut to the chase.
...always cared about us
more than anything!
every human has a cruel side
and they all get excited when they see blood.
...arms and legs sound better?
Dressrosa's former soldiers
Much better!
I want my country back!
Blood and death.
and even the toys are bowing to him!
That's entertainment!
You guys are too sweet.
This Ill Weed-chan deserves...
If you refuse,
there's gonna be bloody mess in Dressrosa.
Pull yourself together!
What's going on?
I thought all the people hated King Riku!
...her whole body smashed up!
Don't you think so?!
But I'm not a devil.
I know you don't like to fight.
Yeah. Since they have this wide area here,
So...
I'm going to sell you this country
for 10 billion berries.
I think there is...
Because you were our pride and joy!!
...something more underground.
What a bunch of scum.
I see.
You're gonna sell this country for money?!
Keep looking.
Clank.
I can just...
Don't let them fight like that again.
...take it back from you
without giving you such an opportunity.
It's so irritating!
What's wrong with them?!
Y-Yes, Young Master!
If we can avoid a war by paying money,
I'd like to do so.
Kin'emon! Momonosuke!
Like I told you, that's how much they hate the former king.
Oh, Kanjuro!
But 10 billion berries is a lot of money!
We don't have that much...
I found a harbor.
Let's steal a ship there.
But it has nothing to do with her!
She's a great person!
King Riku has...
Yes, you do!
This country is too dangerous!
King Riku has trampled
on our feelings!
We all know that.
Scrape it up from your dear citizens.
Brother!
When I got seriously injured
and my life was hanging in the balance,
He's gonna take our money
and kill us all!
What?! What?!
What is it this time?!
I just realized Kanjuro is held captive
by that horrible man
What?!
I'm expecting to have it
by the break of dawn tomorrow.
To satisfy his own selfish desires,
and I can't stop worrying.
he's gonna toss us aside like trash!
You can't get aid from other countries.
Prove your worth as a king.
Enough with this annoying crap!
Whoever it is,
King Riku, you bastard!
I hope you're all right, Kanjuro!
And you can't tell your citizens about me.
if you hurt Sai, I'll carry my anger
even towards your grandchildren!
I hate you!
Rebecca sat up with me
and kept encouraging me.
You only have two choices.
You're...
What's this sticky thing?!
Collect money to avoid a war or...
Why are you looking like that?!
You're a low-down, dirty scumbag!
Depends on what they want
from you guys
Not just me!
Everybody here likes her!
...fight me and see
your citizens bathed in blood.
but often, hostages wouldn't be treated so badly
so he's gonna be alright.
Sai!
Pick the one that you want.
Brother!
You're not really concerned!
You're thinking about something else, aren't you?!
But the people outside will never forget...
Oh, which reminds me,
Violet-chan said she'd be alright, too!
The King Riku Army's coming!
...what happened that night.
Hey, move out of there! Get away!
What is this?! What's going on?!
Can't we fight Doflamingo, King-sama?!
That night?
I'll be alright.
Yeah, it's a long story but...
I talked to my friend
and the Government will protect me.
No! Fighting may sound good
but humans should not kill each other!
H-H-Help...
Never mind then.
What?!
Really?
Stay away! Hey, stop!
Who are you?! Hey!
Go for it, Rebecca!
Yes. I guess they've arrived at the harbor
to pick me up by now.
But it's hard to collect that much money!
There aren't that many rich people in this country!
Stop it!
Believe me.
All right. Should we start?
Okay. It's too bad
that I can't come with you
We shouldn't have to pay the family
that once abandoned this country in the first place!
but as long as you're safe...
Hey, hey!
Thank you.
I think I can go on thanks to you.
If it means war, we're gonna fight...
Rolling Logan has started attacking
with the momentum from the crowds!
It's done so you can go now.
For 800 years, Dressrosa has never fought a war.
It proves we're not beasts!
Do not harm any human
and follow any orders from the Family.
Well... But if you wanna thank me,
you can kiss me on my cheek...
Using his long reach,
he's going for Rebecca from both sides!
Don't become a brute! Be a human!
I won't let you kill anybody!
They say his max grip strength is over 500 kg! Rolling Logan!
Those are the rules.
Oh no!
Your ship is getting attacked by the Fighting Fish!
--But...
--Captain Tank!
If you go straight out that door,
there is a factory and a trade port.
What is a Fighting Fish?
Once she gets caught, it's all over for her!
I know you have a lot to say.
You better go help them!
Go.
But what we value the most is
the citizens' lives.
This is not good!
Nami-san!
Who are you people?
I know you feel the same way.
It's no use!
No talking! Just work hard!
I beg you!
We're here to save this country!
He calmly tracks her down
and narrows the space for her to run!
My name is Don Quixote Doflamingo!
Since the contenders were all so powerful,
they're not gonna break easily!
Th-They're pirates!
What's going on?!
I can't move my own body as I want!
We soldiers of the King Riku Army
truly believe in you
Pirates?
She's literally like a frog
in the sights of a snake!
and do as you tell us to.
I can only can move as he directed me!
--Damn, Rebecca, that little bitch!
--She's so persistent as always!
What is she gonna do now?! Rebecca!
What is going on?
Why are the pirates...
And we take pride in it!
What the hell is happening to me?!
Just go to hell already, you little tramp!
Tank, thank you for saying that.
No.
Your back is wide-open!
But they're gonna save us
from the King Riku Army.
Please forgive me for being disrespectful.
Both of you, go to hell!
Horse-san!
Listen! We don't have much time!
Split up in units and go to different towns!
Yes?
Take me to the palace!
Okay!
How cowardly are you to
try to attack me from the back?!
Collect 10 billion from all over the country.
If we can't do it,
this country will be taken over by the pirate.
Do you want me to break your bones?!
King Riku's here!
Watch this carefully, Ill Weed-chan!
THE FLOWER FIELD
THE KING RIKU ARMY HEADQUARTERS
We're going to lose the trust of the citizens
by collecting their money.
A long time ago, the ancestors of the Tontatta Tribe
kept going out to the sea...
But it's just for several hours!
Now's the chance!
When everything is over,
we'll make it up for them sincerely!
Oh? Taking advantage of him being off-guard,
Rebecca started to run!
Here comes a hero!
...looking for natural resources
that their land lacked.
That's the only way!
There's no fooling anyone to get out of this!
DRESSROSA - THE CORRIDA COROSSEUM
Collect as much as you can!
The country is on the line!
But Big Humans kept discovering them,
I like how you "dance"!
King Riku!
Rebecca is scurrying like a rat!
Yeah!
and they were facing extinction.
V-V-V...
Let's go! Follow my lead!
Vice Captain!
I found them! The Little People!
Yeah!
Rolling Logan is chasing her...
What? Vice Captain?
What are you talking about?
...mowing down the other contenders!
Catch them!
Y-Y-You're Zoro-senpai, aren't you?
Trebol! Pica! Diamante!
But one day, the king of Dressrosa,
one of the neighboring countries,
Stop running, Rebecca! Fight!
Luffy-senpai's right-hand man?
Fight and bleed!
--It's the Army.
--What are they doing this late?
What? Well...
Now, go and sweep out the trash
from the whole country!
offered them a deal...
Looks like you're not
disguising yourself too well.
That's Captain Tank!
...that he would provide
resources and guarantee
Let me just say this. I'm not Zoro!
Stop!
their safety in exchange
for a little bit of work.
Oh no!
Y-You don't have to hide it!
I'll never let anyone get away
once I've got them in my sights!
That king's name was Don Quixote!
I also know Luffy-senpai is fighting in this Colosseum
under the name "Lucy"!
Yes...
Yes!
Listen, everyone!
We did it!
We survived!
Bring all the money you have
in this town here!
Rebecca lost her precious sword!
She's totally cornered!
What?!
Doflamingo! Doflamingo!
I-I-I'm talking
to Zoro-senpai like it's nothing!
--Whoa-whoa, what's the matter?
--What's going on?
That led to the worst times of
the Tontatta Tribe's history...
Doflamingo! Doflamingo! Doflamingo!
--Just bring it!
--Hurry up!
I-I'm so thrilled!
...which continued on until 900 years ago.
King-sama will be furious with you
if he hears about this!
This is...
The slave era!
Why are you crying?!
Follow your doom! Embrace violence!
...the king's order!
There are some surviving manuscripts that
Rebecca finally got caught!
How do you know
about Luffy and my name?!
describe how cruel the royal family was.
They were literally like devils!
I'be albayz bween your ban!
Our ancestors were forced to work and work
Huh?
He can't even have a conversation.
deep underground unnoticed by anyone
King-sama will be furious with you
if he hears about this!
while the Big Humans were
living lavishly on the wealth
I gotta say it!
I finally get to meet him!
This is the king's order!
provided by the work of the Tontatta Tribe.
Hurry up! We can't tell you what's going on
and we don't have time!
A-A-Auto...
Just believe in King-sama
and bring all the money you have here!
--Stop crying!
--Y-Yes!
I just got scolded by Zoro-senpai!
That's too sudden.
Stop running! Fight!
Records from the subsequent Hundred Year Void
are lost
You coward!
It's impossible!
No one's gonna accept such a request!
C-Can I have your autograph?!
I'll never forgive your evil family!
--I said it!
--My autograph?
but 800 years ago,
a new king took the throne of Dressrosa.
The Video Transponder Snail?
If I bring Luffy-senpai here,
can I have your autograph?
Nation of Dressrosa!
King Riku-sama!
You can do that for me?
I'll be counting on you!
It was King Riku!
It's King Riku-sama!
I know it's too sudden
and an unreasonable request.
Now, Rolling Logan!
--Go to hell already, Rebecca!
--Chop her up!
What is he going to do from that position?!
H-He just said
he'll be counting on me, didn't he?
--You're a piece of shit!
--Drop dead!
But please let me borrow all of your money
from all of you people...
Zoro-senpai said he'll be counting on me!
Ill Weed-chan!
What do you want me to do?!
...without asking me for a reason!
Do you want me to throw you to the ground?
Or...
The king is bowing his head!
...like the guy earlier...
The country fell into hands of Doflamingo
King Riku-sama!
Why do you have to cry again?
When King Riku heard...
But why is he doing this?
I like the way you scream!
in just one night.
What are you doing?! Just go!
...that the Little People were being treated
as less than humans for centuries,
I'll do this then!
It's really too sudden!
Th-Th...
I'm gonna pulverize you slowly
so let me hear it more!
Th?
How awful!
It's like a nightmare!
King-sama, stop bowing your head!
Then!
he cried and apologized profusely.
You shouldn't be doing that!
You're the king!
Wait for me there!
How cunning of him!
I'm gonna bring him at the risk of my life!
--Please stop!
--Lift your head!
I-I-I can't stand that Doflamingo guy!
That bastard!
--This is it for her!
--Rebecca!
The successive kings will be ashamed of you
for doing such a thing!
Would the undefeated girl
lose here finally?!
Then, the new king devised
a form of compensation for them!
We believed that King Riku
went crazy at that time, too,
He doesn't have to risk his life for it...
--King-sama!
--Why do you have to do that!
Z-Zoro-senpai said
he'll be counting on me!
Pulverize! Pulverize! Pulverize!
You're humiliating yourself in front of the whole world!
Just stop!
so we got in touch with
the new king Doflamingo
He told them they
Pulverize! Pulverize! Pulverize! Pulverize!
and ended up like this.
could simply take anything
that they needed from the country.
King-sama!
H-He's really trusting me!
I'm so ashamed of myself
for distrusting King Riku!
Please! This is not some kind of joke!
Soldier-san... I...
It feels like...
They didn't have to work.
I see! It's really too bad!
...I became the right-hand man of
Luffy-senpai's right-hand man!
I don't mind cutting
my arm or leg off to prove it!
You let the innocent king that
--Oh, my bag is gone!
--So is my watch!
you all admired so much die for nothing.
Faster!
Use the lower half of your body!
It's great!
No, he's still alive!
I can't find my wallet!
It's amazing!
Oh no! My jacket got stolen, too!
Listen, Tank.
I've got to do this right!
What?!
Doflamingo loved the special ability
the former princess Viola-sama had.
If things go wrong,
I will kill even just Doflamingo.
My Shusui that was here a minute ago!
They stole from everybody.
King Riku-sama, is that...
I can't take it anymore!
It was fairies who took your stuff.
So she bargained with him!
The battle royal at the Corrida Colosseum!
Today's competition is a chance and I'll take it!
What are you talking about?!
Fairies are fairies.
All you can do is laugh it off and let it go.
If you promise me that
you won't kill my father,
You're out of your mind!
It's not a chance!
The heated match of Block D!
I'll leave the rest up to you.
Tough contenders are attacking fiercely
and the others are getting eliminated one after another!
It's impossible for you
to win that competition!
How can I laugh it off?!
I will obey you!
Those invisible fairies are
the guardian deities of
To live up to his expectations,
You're gonna die!
I won't allow you to enter it!
She still lives and works
under Doflamingo!
Dressrosa from ancient times.
I'll collect the money at any cost!
We have to turn a blind
eye to whatever they do.
Becoming an officer in his group
Even if I lose...
--Well, if fairies did it...
--We should just forget about it!
and changing her name to Violet!
The one that's standing out among them is...
...the trust of the people in me
as a military captain!
S-S-She's an officer?!
Let go of Rebecca!
...the military captain of the Scorchistan -
Rolling Logan!
Then, King Riku is still
alive thanks to her?!
The king called it the work of fairies and
Yes, I'm sure he's still living somewhere
in this country.
calmed his citizens down by laughing it off
ROLLING LOGAN - A MILITARY CAPTAIN OF
SOUTHERN KINGDOM OF SCORCHISTAN
and he established successfully the
legend of fairies in this country.
I am begging you!
But I can't imagine how much pain
he must've gone through over the last decade!
Let's see what happens if I go all out!
Hurry up, everyone!
Let's bring all the money we got as the king says!
How cool! The first King Riku!
And how hard it must've been for Viola-sama!
Oh, the smiling gladiator Agilia joins
in this fight!
Fear, anger, tears!
The country was governed by
the gentle Riku Family...
Yeah! King Riku is such a kind-hearted man!
He wouldn't do this out of ill intent!
Let's see what happens if I roll!
...unstintingly supporting its neighboring countries
when they were in trouble.
I wonder how she has spent
the last decade.
She saved Rebecca with a merciful smile!
That's right!
There must be a reason for this!
I can't say the country was wealthy
--Bring all your money!
--All right!
but it became renowned
and the people were always smiling.
She got away thanks to Agilia!
What you're seeing is
what Rolling Logan is famous for!
Our ancestors paid tribute
to King Riku's kindness
Way to go, happy-faced old woman!
And, on the same night,
other soldiers were
manipulated as the king was
It's a special attack - Rolling Cradle!
"Happy-faced old woman," you said?
and they voluntarily filled the country with
lots of greens and beautiful flowers.
and massacred the civilians unwillingly,
they must've been suffering so much, too!
Are you okay, Rebecca?
I'm okay! Thank you, Agilia-san!
I thought all of them must've
been killed that night!
That's how we Tontatta Kingdom and...
With that high-speed rolling,
his enemy's equilibrium gets thrown off!
It's too soon to say that!
Some got killed
...the successive Riku Family
deepened our bonds over 800 years.
You want to win the Flare-Flare Fruit, don't you?
but others surrendered to Doflamingo
And his finishing move is...
Then, have courage to fight!
Let's see!
The king's virtue made it possible!
and they're working for him as his guards.
But now, after 900 years,
The Leg Split!
They sold out to him?!
I believe they made an agonizing choice!
Here!
Doflamingo, the descendent of
the Don Quixote Family, has returned
Thank you!
How dare you!
I'm gonna finish both of you off
and send you straight to hell!
Screw you!
and he is trying
to repeat that horrible history!
I'm sorry!
The crowds are getting all excited!
They just followed the crazy king's order.
They're doing it out of their trust
in the eight centuries of the Riku Family's reign.
Oh? On the other hand...
Forgive me for welcoming them
to work under me.
This competition is nothing
like the other events!
How wonderful this country is!
It will be saved for sure!
If so, I can't help crying!
Everybody has been suffering so much!
You can't win this thing
just by running around!
Thank you!
King Riku-sama!
Agilia-san!
Long live King Riku-sama!
It's a tragedy! You poor people!
My daughter - Mancherie
They're fighting quietly
in contrast to Logan's showy style!
and 500 of our people already
fell victim to that man.
There were soldiers who got killed
and who surrendered.
Thank you all.
But when you sum it up,
We can't let him repeat history!
it doesn't add up to a
whole army for a country!
This is the great example of
ill weeds growing apace!
Angry Rolling Logan is overpowering Agilia!
No, we can't!
What do you mean by that?
So we fight!
The cursed princess - Rebecca!
I believe I have lost some memories!
Take all the money to the palace!
That's right!
The return of the Don Quixote line is
doing Dressrosa and Tontatta...
--Hurry up!
--Yes, sir!
The crowd is jeering loudly!
Agilia-san!
That's what I meant!
Lost some memories?!
Agilia-san, bend over!
--Captain Tank!
--What's wrong?!
...no good -- and much harm!
Fra-land.
--King-sama is in the town of Sevio!
--It's on the screen!
Remember what I've told you earlier?
Let me step on your back!
Even after we became toys,
What?!
We fight with the heroes!
we remember everything
about when we were humans.
Usoland will help us tremendously!
THE TOWN IN THE SOUTH - SEVIO
But people around us, even our own family,
forgot that we even existed.
Oh! No way! Rebecca is going to make an attack?!
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
King-sama!
You didn't have to come all the way! We're gonna...
It's not gonna work against me!
What?!
They don't even know
that they lost their loved ones.
Get away!
Th-That's exactly what I was thinking!
What?!
It's King-sama!
That's the biggest tragedy of Dressrosa
That's our hero!
King Riku-sama! We don't know what the deal is
but we trust you so...
and even we toys forgot some things, too.
King Riku is a good guy!
You mean, there might be your
friends among those toys
He has been so nice
even to these worm-like people!
You can do better than that
as a human!
Get away!
What?
that are walking on the streets
What did you just call us?!
Get away from me!
Bring out all your power!
but you can't recognize them
because you forgot about them?
I meant it in a good way.
What?!
It's okay, then!
King Riku-sama, what are you...
Get up, Rebecca!
Exactly.
In addition, they must've been feeling
Rot in hell, granddaughter of King Riku!
I don't wanna do it anymore!
Don't! There is a magazine!
angry since Doflamingo turned them into toys.
Drop dead, Rebecca!
No! This can't be true!
I don't wanna hurt anybody!
Commander-san.
Damn it all!
Why should I be a toy?!
That gladiator girl who is fighting
in the Colosseum is...
Even if you don't want to do so,
Get away from my wife!
Damn! I can't say what I wanna say!
I can't believe it!
Rebecca won an upset victory!
...being called King Riku's granddaughter
and getting insulted.
you have to become stronger,
Rebecca!
--Damn Doflamingo!
--I hate him so much!
She moved unbelievably fast
and fended off Rolling Logan's attack
It seems like the people
of this country hate King Riku.
Isn't there anybody
who can take him down?!
forcing him to fall out of the ring!
That's what I thought!
Doflamingo tried to bury all the dissidents
Usoland! Usoland!
King Riku-sama!
but that means...
...there are countless dissidents
dwelling in the shadows of this country!
You made him believe that you were gonna attack,
Soldier-san!
10 years ago,
drew his attack, and took advantage of it.
That unknown number of those poor people
is the key to our plan!
You're unbelievable.
there was an incident in which
King Riku lost the trust
King Riku-sama?
of all his citizens overnight.
Prepare to die!
The king was trying to protect
his country until the end but...
Stop! Don't make me do this!
I see!
Now you're facing the moment of truth!
That's why you think
there is a chance to win.
--King Riku-sama, please stop!
--What are you doing?!
You gotta move to the finals at any cost!
Y-You tramp!
The corrupted King Riku's family!
It's true that it seems foolhardy
Back off! Stay away from me!
Screw you, Rebecca!
Dammit! She's so persistent!
to fight the Warlord's group but...
Get away from me!
Uh-huh!
Cut her to pieces!
...if all the toys in this country are dissidents,
it'd be a powerful enough force!
That's Rebecca's favorite move -
the Back-to-the-Water Dance!
The people don't know
what really happened that day.
He cut the soldiers, too!
Hey, hey, hey! Wait a minute!
My body is moving on its own!
You have to become stronger,
Rebecca!
You seem like you're going for
taking down Doflamingo!
I'm sorry!
She did it!
She takes advantage of her
opponents' advancing momentum
We're only here to destroy the factory!
I couldn't protect your mother!
and draws them to the edge of the ring.
When it's done, we'll say
goodbye to the country!
Then she holds her sword in front of her
with her back against the water.
All right! Rebecca! Agilia!
Doflamingo tried to kill every
member of the King Riku Family
Right, Robin?!
I'm so mad at Doflamingo!
Finally, she moves unbelievably fast
utilizing her opponents' moves
Another one's coming!
Kick his ass, Rebecca!
You see?
What are you doing?
What?!
but I took Rebecca who has
King Riku's blood in her veins
and lets them fall into the water!
We're destined to fight
this decisive battle today!
King Riku-sama!
Hey, not Cabbage!
Show me Rebecca!
With the event of this morning,
they're challenging us!
and ran away for a very long time.
Yeah, we want Rebecca!
It's not a coincidence
that Usoland came to us today!
Boy... What kind of king he is!
I just realized it's hard to watch it from here.
But she got caught in the end
Somebody from above is telling us
to fight!
I'm gonna go closer to cheer for her!
and they keep her
on public display at the Colosseum.
Well, the night has just begun, soldiers.
--Yeah!
--What event?
Oh yeah. It seemed to me like everybody was happy in this country but...
That's it!
That is her Back-to-the-Water Dance!
Doflamingo's abdication
from the throne.
You should dance, too!
If I can regain the people's trust in King Riku
and save Rebecca's life,
Oh, the fact is we...
Yes! Remarkably, Rebecca has never hurt anybody
in all the battles that she took part in!
...by seeing you guys,
I noticed it's not true.
Can you imagine how happy we were
when we heard about it?!
I wouldn't mind sacrificing my life
anytime, anywhere!
What you saw was the bright side
where "winners" are living happily.
I thought it was a miracle!
Parasite String!
I put everything on the line for this war!
And then, we heard it was a false report.
Doflamingo labels...
Wh-What the hell? What's going on?!
M-My arm is moving on its own!
I didn't know
she used the Observation Haki!
...the people who obey him "winners"
and the people who disobey him "losers."
We felt like we were dropped
from heaven to the edge of hell!
Haki?
She has also never been
wounded by anybody
What?
So it was only natural for us to...
and she won it all by letting opponents fall out of the ring!
She has never been defeated!
Just like the World Government!
Who are you?
The soldiers are rampaging now, too!
I couldn't protect Rebecca's mother.
...decide to fight him today!
Rogue "Losers" are like trash
She's quite a fighter!
Go, Rebecca!
Stop it!
We're so sorry for what we did!
and once you hide that trash somewhere dark,
Her fighting style is not unbeautiful
Help me...
the country looks good, but only on the surface.
C-Captain!
Mother-sama...
It's not me!
Mother-sama!
and I don't dislike it to be honest!
I-I can't control my body!
Mother-sama!!
You're retired but you led your crew here?
I know!
That's what's happening to me!
We have no disciples
to succeed the Happo Navy.
Why does it move on its own?!
I'm sorry!
I wish I had a grandson.
Let's go treasure hunting!
I'm sorry!!
Is it what's happening to King-sama?!
I see. It's not so easy to be a pirate, eh?
King Riku-sama, why are you doing this?!
But would it work in this competition?!
I'll never forget what happened that day.
He's never done anything wrong up
til now!
Maybe it's just my imagination
but I feel like I'm forgetting something.
Tough contenders from various countries
all have different fighting style!
It's similar to the country I grew up in.
Did we do something?!
She doesn't remember me
after I turned into a toy but...
I felt the same way 10 years ago.
Once you start feeling something's wrong,
They're not your ordinary gladiator!
There's no way to justify myself!
you'll see there are so many strange things going on here.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, where am I going?!
We think there is an even darker part.
This country is finished!
Grandpa, help me!
Doflamingo set us up!
You better be careful, too.
What have they done to me -
Abdullah, the lone wolf?!
Okay! Bye!
--What happened to the king?!
--Please stop!
What have they done to me -
Jeet, the maverick warrior!
Let's see what happens
if I break your bones!
Soldier-san is a brave man
Hey, hey!
Can we do it already, Doffy?
Help!
Ill Weed-chan!
Where did Luffy-senpai go?
I can't find him anywhere!
He will always be by your side
Idiot. Don't rush.
Zoro!
I can't face Zoro-senpai like this.
Damn Crest Head!
He said he was gonna show me
the way but he's collapsed!
I have to make the people tremble
with fear more
...I'm...
Is Zoro really here?!
and get them hate King Riku
with all their heart!
Hey!
And then, the heroes will appear!
Zoro! Kin'emon!
...Rebecca's real father!
L-L-L-L....
Luffy-senpai!