Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"Coby-Meppo's Resolve!
Vice-Admiral Garp's Parental Affection"
I can't fall in a place like this.
I've got an important mission...
"An Ancient Island!
The Shadow Hiding in Little Garden!"
Oh!
The wind stopped again.
How pitiful...
...losing against just one swordsman...
Just when we should be rushing
straight for Little Garden, too.
Ah! I can see...
Mr. 5! Miss Valentine!
Why are you here?!
We're temporarily stopped again.
A million Little Garden residents
are out to greet Captain Usopp!
You really have no idea?
Time is running out as we speak, too...
There're criminals here that
are big enough for the boss
Don't worry.
The girls' high-pitched cheers...
Kisses being blown all over the place...
"Deliver Princess Vivi!
The Luffy Pirates Set Sail"
I know we need to get to Alabasta
as soon as possible, but...
to send us here to deal with.
Really, I'm so popular
that it's almost a crime...
Alright! Let's fish! Fish!
These're the boss' words:
"They've found out my secrets."
I wonder if it's not gonna snow anymore.
Don't fall in love with me, Mademoiselle.
It's not my fault if you get burned.
Damn, they're annoying!
Hey, anyone seen the bait?
There's no way it would.
What's their problem?!
Does too. You don't know since
you slept through it last time.
Of course, I don't even know what
kind of secrets they are, but...
Bait? Oh, the stuff in there? I ate it.
Are you stupid or what?
Hmm?
So, when we very carefully
investigated who learned his secrets...
Stupid? Hey, I heard that, Zoro!
You ate it?! Those were bugs, you know!
Hey, do you think it'll snow again?
Cut it out! Keep it down, you guys!
This can't be! What strength!
Yeah? They taste good!
It could snow, but the sea
we were in first is special...
Seriously....
Unbelievable!
Don't eat stuff like that!
Oh boy, we found out that a VIP
Sorry about that. So...?
Alright, then. Let's settle this!
Now what?! We can't fish now
that you've eaten our bait!
Oh, yeah, so it's like I was just saying.
...since the seven magnetic forces from
Reverse Mountain mess everything up.
from a certain kingdom
sneaked into Baroque Works.
Yeah!
Use this, then!
There aren't any islands, but it's easy
to hit reefs due to the elevated coral.
We can't catch anything with that!
They know! It's all over!
Really? We can't?
Then how about him?
I see...
Die! Igarappappa!
Oh. That sounds okay.
That doesn't mean you can relax
your attention here, though.
Thanks. That was helpful.
--Hey, you! Come here!
--Get back here, bait!
I won't let you lay
a finger on our princess!
It'd be rare for this sea to
be wild like the first journey,
You're welcome.
--Wow, it smells good.
--Yeah.
On my name as Squad Captain
of Alabasta Kingdom Security!
Dammit, you guys! Knock it off!
Thanks for waiting. This is
today's dessert, Tarte aux Poires.
but it's still true that this sea is a
lot more difficult than ordinary ones.
But can't you guys be
a little worried, at least?!
Igaram!
Bon appetit.
Igaram, Squad Captain
of Alabasta Kingdom Security!
Never underestimate this sea.
That's the ironclad rule.
Worried about what?
Wow! It looks delicious!
Oh! Nami-san is lovely
when she's angry, too!
And Princess Nefertari Vivi!
Hey guys!
Yours is over there!
In the name of the Baroque Works'
boss, we'll eliminate you two.
Honestly, now!
Hmm... Okay!
Wanna have my special drink?
But it's strange.
For someone with a
30 million-Berry bounty,
Geez... Hmm? Where's Luffy?
Yeah!
Knock that off!
he doesn't seem that
terrible of a person at all...
Oh, I asked him to go draw water earlier.
I want to take a shower.
Thanks!
Yeah, it might be hard to imagine,
but he's beaten many big names.
"All-Out Battle! Luffy vs. Zoro,
Mysterious Grand Duel!"
I think he's at the water-drawing machine.
No wonder he's been quiet.
Say, Usopp. Make a fishing tackle for me.
What the heck are you guys doing?!
Arlong, the fishman who was
bent on ruling the East Blue...
Fishing, huh? That's a good idea!
Damn...
It's just a good thing you
managed to keep the girl safe!
And I left Luffy down there, too.
Okay. Then I'll make an
artistic fishing rod for you.
Or not...
You almost let a billion
Berries get away from us!
Pirate Fleet Commodore, Don Krieg...
Ahhh... That scared me.
Quickly, Vivi-sama! Please escape!
That thing is dangerous!
Understand?!
Captain Kuro, an unknown pirate
notorious for his cunning methods.
Igaram!
Hey, it goes like this.
What? What happened?
What are you talking about?
Ahh! Luffy! Why'd you have to break it?!
Wow, you sure can drink.
Hey, is it good?
Why did you save me?
You forgot one.
I was just trying to
draw the water faster.
Right! We need to talk about that!
A navy freak who wields a huge axe-hand.
Oh, boy... The belt's
been burned and broken.
Whoa! Amazing!
It's like this...
Won't you make a contract with me?
Oh! Axe-Hand Morgan!
Axe-Hand Morgan?
I've heard of him before.
Yeah. I wonder how that happened.
Contract?
--Igaram!
--It's no use!
Quit fighting!
It's because of your ridiculous strength!
I heard he's a navy captain
who's feared in the East Blue
Geez...
for his overwhelming domination.
Is this really okay?!
Can't it be fixed?
You're saying he beat even him?!
Here, this is for you.
Well, we have to get
materials from somewhere.
What?
Oh! The old axe-hand guy!
I think it's fine.
Oh! You shoulda just said so, Zoro!
In any case, I probably
shouldn't ask him to do anything.
They'll work hard if it storms...
since they don't wanna die.
That reminds me, I wonder what
that guy with him is up to now...
I just figured you cut them all down
Usopp, could you get water from the
other water-drawing machine for me?
'cause they didn't
make any food you liked!
You monsters!
I wonder if he's still
at that navy base...
That's true, but it makes me feel
like I'm worked up over nothing.
You're a princess, Miss Wednesday?!
Don't compare me to you!
Yeah...
What? Nami! Have you ever
considered doing it yourself?!
This ship makes you feel like you don't
have to worry about anything, right?
Quit being dumb, Mr. 9!
C'mon! Don't sweat it!
Who's "he"?
Shut up, you two!
Yeah! His name's Coby!
This is one screwed-up night!
You guys can do whatever you want!
So there you have it!
I smell food!
He's my friend!
And you, show a little more remorse!
As compensation,
I'd like one billion Berries.
Attaboy! Go, go, go, go...!
V-Vivi-sama...
--I'm sorry. But there's another
one, so what's the big deal?
You saw how strong these guys are.
Igaram! Are you all right?!
--Nami-san, look.
--I'm sorry. But there's another
one, so what's the big deal?
--Nami-san, look.
--Saying something like that
shows you're not sorry!
"Try Hard, Coby!
Coby-Meppo's Struggles in the Navy"
Vivi-sama! Never mind me!
Just please... escape from here!
It's a pretty good offer, if you ask me.
--Oh, the newspaper courier.
--Shut up! I can't sleep!
Stupid Karoo!
I can't!
I do appreciate your
saving me. Thank you.
For our motherland...
Why can't you?! You're a princess!
That stupid Nami...
Sub-Lieutenant!
Preparations for departure are complete!
Without you, our kingdom
of Alabasta will be...
One billion shouldn't be much...
"Justice"
Yes... it's a lot easier this way...
At any rate, I can't believe they deliver
the morning paper at snack time...
Do you know of the kingdom
known as Alabasta?
Please! Hurry!
I see.
No.
All ships, move out!
You think you can escape from us?
That can't be helped since we're
traveling in the Grand Line.
Yes, sir!
Hey, everyone, look!
It's a dolphin!
We should feel lucky that
we can still get news.
Don't mess with me!
It's a peaceful kingdom known
as a great civilization and nation.
Whoa! He's cute!
Luffy-san! How are you?
It's me! Coby!
I guess you're right.
Well, it used to be.
I'm having a hard time
swallowing what's going on here,
Used to be? What about now?
After we parted ways back then,
I've worked my hardest!
but we've been a pair for a long time.
It's in the middle of a civil war.
I'll buy you some time!
For years now, signs of a
revolution have begun to appear.
Get going, Miss Wednesday!
Did something catch your eye?
There were plenty of hardships,
What? Ah, no, not really...
but now I've achieved my
dream of being a navy officer!
Mr. 9!
It's huge!!
The people revolted, and the
kingdom fell into total chaos...
Pretty manly, wouldn't you say?
I see.
Bye-bye, baby!
--Hot-blooded Bat...
--Mr. 9!
Then, one day, I heard the
name of an organization...
All we need is the will to
accomplish our missions.
...Baroque Works!
Ah!
Wh-What is it?
I learned that the populace was
being manipulated by this group.
Get out of here!
Here! Zoro, look!
A pathetic sense of camaraderie
will only bring about death.
Hm?
What? This is just
a picture of the Navy.
Time to learn that the
hard way! Nose Fancy...
But there was a tight lid on
any other information than that,
--Let's go!
--Okay!
C-Captain Morgan!
Yep!
Coby...
Yeah, but the guy in this
picture isn't just anyone.
...of Guts!
and there was nothing I could do.
...Cannon!
That's when I asked Igaram,
Go to Hell, Coby!
who always meddled in my business
since childhood, for help.
Alright!
Hm? Hey, it's Coby!
Take that side!
The old tube hair guy?
See?!
Got it!
Mr. 9!
Tube? Oh, yes.
Coby...? That friend you were
talking about the other day?
Everyone...
Luffy-san!
Whoa, now! That's some
dangerous snot he's got!
Completely unfurl the sails!
Heya, Coby!
I asked him if there was a way
I could infiltrate Baroque Works.
Yep! So what does it say?
What does it say? Let's see...
What the hell?!
Gum-Gum...
Because that would let us see
who was pulling the strings,
Sir Swordsman!
"Vice-Admiral Garp's warship has
arrived at Navy Headquarters.
...Tornado!
Upon seeing your skill, I have a request,
unreasonable as it may be!
and what their goal was.
You're a pretty high-spirited princess.
The picture was taken right after
they crossed over Reverse Mountain.
Yeah, right! Screw that! Let go of me!
So? Did you figure out
this goal of theirs?
Okay! Ride the wave
and shake him off!
As both of those people possess
Devil Fruit powers, I can't stop them!
Just as expected, Vice-Admiral
Garp had a relaxed, imposing look;
"The founding of an ideal nation."
however, there were some young
marines whose faces froze with fear."
Might I ask you to protect
the princess in my place?!
Wow! So pretty!
That's what Igaram-san said, anyway.
Please!
Oh, does that mean...
Whoa... So Coby has
entered the Grand Line.
Huh?!
Yes.
Oww!
The boss says it's to
create an ideal nation,
It said Navy Headquarters. Not so bad.
Nami! Which direction
should the ship take?
Karoo! Run!
but it's an enormous lie!
No matter what people say,
he's a man who'll be a Navy mayor.
I was dreaming!
Hold on a sec. Let me check.
The true goal is to
take over Alabasta Kingdom!
There she goes.
What the hell?!
Quit screwing around, you!
Why would he want to become a mayor?
Officer! A Navy officer!
She can't get away from us.
Let's get her, Miss Valentine!
--Shut up!
--Quiet!
I have to hurry back, tell everyone
the truth, and stop the fighting!
Right, Mr. 5!
Yeah, that's the one.
Go to sleep, you idiot chore boys!
If you can safely deliver the princess
I see... So he's trying hard, too...
Turn to port, full!
If I don't do something...
to the great kingdom of
Alabasta far east of here...
Okay!
"Chore Boy"
...I promise that you
will be rewarded immensely!
At any rate, Luffy-san,
I'm now working at the navy base!
I see.
I humbly beg of you!
Please, keep the princess safe!
So that's the deal.
Now everything finally connects.
"Navy"
Captain Morgan's son Helmeppo-san
was given chore duty, too!
Screw that! You were trying to
kill us until just a minute ago!
There'd be no money
during a civil war, huh?
--Hey! Quit slackin' off!
--Oww...
Don't make me cut you some more!
2,000 push-ups! Start!
Hey, chore boys! Wash the windows
when you're done cleaning!
Hey.
Is this "immense reward" for real?
Who is pulling the strings?
Yes, sir!
I'll take up that offer!
How does one billion Berries sound?
And don't forget to
clean up in the mess hall!
T-The boss' identity?!
Eh?! What about our meal?!
Rope-crossing, 100 round trips!
You shouldn't ask that!
Nami!
You're obviously not
gonna finish before lunch!
You know who it is, right?
Whoa!
O-One billion Be--?!
Don't ask me! Anything but that!
Run 200 laps!
You can eat after
you've finished everything!
Ma-ma-ma...
Your lives will be put in danger, too!
Those who can't finish within 1 hour
will be penalized with another 100 laps.
Eh?! But I'm starving to death here!
I thought you were asleep?
I think I'll pass on that!
Come on, now.
Helmeppo-san!
After all, these are guys trying
to take over an entire country!
There's no mistake.
Helmeppo! Coby!
Who in their right mind
would sleep carelessly
Practice matches!
Yes, sir!
That island and Cactus Island
are pulling against each other.
You're both aware neither of you
were qualified to join the navy...
They're obviously
insanely dangerous people!
Don't stop until you faint!
Our next stop is...
in an overly suspicious town
that welcomes pirates?
Yes! They are!
Are you okay?!
...yet you were given special
permission to join as chore boys, right?
It was all an act! A-C-T, act!
As strong as you people may be,
you'd never stand a chance
So this is Navy Headquarters...!
...that island!
I could keep on going if I wanted!
against one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea,
It's not like you let us join, though!
Crocodile!
That so?
Yes, sir! Of course! If there's
anything I can do, I'll do it!
Ma-ma-ma...
So, will you promise us the
one billion, Squad Captain?
Who, now?
"23"
Okay, they can't see us here.
Please rest a little.
Just give the order!
No... just making sure you realize that.
You just said it.
Yeah. Sorry.
If you don't ask for our help,
your princess probably will die...
Work hard, now!
So that's the one!
Yes, sir! You can count on us!
Our second island in the Grand Line!
We'll also be honored to do your laundry!
Say, Coby.
A mere soldier like me can't
promise such large sums of money...
--Are you an idiot?!
--Eh?
What is it?
You don't need to go out of
your way for even more work!
Maybe it was too early
for us to come here...
--What was that bird and sea otter?!
--I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
You're not suggesting a princess
is worth less than that, are you?
Are they going to tell someone?!
But we are chore boys,
after all! Okay! Work! Work!
Hey! A Warlord!
What?
You saw it earlier, didn't you?
Not too shabby!
"We"?
The way we are right now,
we won't make it here.
Pay it.
I-I'm very sorry!
It just slipped out!
If you wanna work that badly,
you can do it yourself!
Now she's threatening him!
Like that really fixes things now!
Huh?
One! Two! Three! Four!
Why did you have to
drag us down with you?!
There's a proper order for doing things.
In that case, if you're willing to
safely deliver the princess there,
Maybe we should try again after
we've at least trained ourselves more.
it would be best if you negotiate
the terms with her directly!
Being hunted by a Warlord the
moment we enter the Grand Line
Yep! That's right. Let's do that!
Even if we're missing,
no one will care...
Meaning I gotta start by saving her, huh?
is too much to handle!
I can't stand this. Forget Coby--
why do I hafta be a chore boy?!
Mr. 3...
--We're lucky we can see him so soon!
--I wonder what he's like!
Even as we speak, her life is in danger!
Hold on a second!
What is it? Hold on...
What're you thinking, Helmeppo-san?!
Shut up, you two!
Alright, then.
I'll save your princess for now.
How I wish I could go back to then...
It's been a short acquaintance,
but I thank you for everything!
I thought you said
you'd surpass your father!
There's just nothing like Earl Grey.
Where are you going?
W-Well, I did... but if I do
all those things, I'll die.
They don't know what we look
like yet! I'm running away!
Okay! Go get her, Zoro!
I'm bored.
Yeah, right, you idiot!
You say you're bored, but you
don't like working, right?
Helmeppo-sama. Your cocoa, sir.
Wouldn't you be happy
if that's the case?!
Why do I have to go along
with your money-making schemes?!
Oww!
Wow! That's so good!
Once you've decided
to become like that...
--Right.
--Then, why don't you try enjoying
this joyous free time a little?
Dammit! Are you trying to scald me?!
Geez, you're so stupid!
No, sir! I-I'm very sorry, sir!
I guess this means there's
nowhere to run now, huh?!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
My money is mine, but my
contracts belong to all of you!
Who do you think I am?!
I'm sorry!
Once you've decided
to become like that...
She's funny!
I'm Helmeppo-sama, only son of
the great Navy Captain Morgan!
Where was she planning
to run to, anyway?
Being able to take a long vacation
like this is a privilege to officer agents.
I've decided to be
King of the Pirates, so if...
That's the kind of logic a bully would use!
Guess that means all three of us
are on Baroque Works's hit list now.
If you can die fighting for that,
you should be happy!
What's the big deal?! All you
gotta do is cut those guys down!
And...
Yes, sir! Helmeppo-sama!
I don't like bein' used,
unlike that idiot cook!
stop calling me by my code
name in public like this.
That's exciting for some reason!
Fighting... That's going a bit far...
Man, things were good back then!
You're just afraid you can't beat them!
I-I do have 500,000
Berries in savings...
No, you fight!
People will find out that I'm Mr. 3.
What?! Just try saying that some more!
Against yourself!
So please don't ever say you'll run away!
Fear not!
Dammit! This is all
that Straw Hat's fault!
--You're just afraid you can't beat them!
--Bathroom.
It's...
You think?
Quit repeating that crap!
Ma-ma-ma...
Running away?!
He stripped Dad of his
position as a navy captain!
Hey, now. Have you forgotten?
You owe me money.
By the way, you've been looking at that
piece of paper for the past few days.
It's all right! I have a plan!
You idiots!
Igaram! What are those clothes?!
You sure aren't going to
bring disgrace on me, are you?!
Huh?! I don't owe you nothin'.
What on earth is it?
You look hilarious in those, old guy!
I lent you 100,000 Berries
for some swords in Loguetown.
An order from Boss.
You wimps!
It's all his fault!
It's idiot after idiot...
You should've told me sooner!
It's all because of Straw Hat that
I'm stuck doing this crap now!
Vivi-sama. Please listen to me carefully.
I gave you the 100,000 right back!
You two can be easily replaced.
If you wanna run away,
hurry up and do it.
Helmeppo-san.
Apparently, Mr. 5 has been taken down.
Once Baroque Works's intelligence
network learns of something,
Someone gave me some swords,
so I didn't use the money!
What do you want?!
Don't touch me all friendly-like!
pursuers may come after
you almost immediately.
Humph! If someone had to get taken down,
I wish it were someone like Mr. 2.
But you did agree to pay me back 300%--
300,000 Berries total.
Please wait! We won't run away!
I'm sorry. But I wanted to tell
you something, as a friend...
On top of that, if you
know the boss' secrets...
Hmm?
You know what happens.
We've come this far fully
prepared to die if necessary.
Friend?! Why would
me and you be friends?!
Then you could get a promotion.
A thousand or so people
will come after you.
Please give us any orders!
Well, we are both chore boys...
Mr. 5 being taken down isn't
worth making a big deal over.
There's something I wanna buy.
We'll carry out anything,
Vice-Admiral Garp!
Therefore, I will pretend
to be you, like so,
Sure, I can lend you money!
If you pay me back 300%!
I'm not the kind of guy who
does chores in a place like this!
After all, that man is just an
"idiot with devil fruit power"
You haven't paid back the
other 200,000 Berries yet.
and sail straight to Alabasta
with three dummies on board.
If it hadn't been for Straw Hat...
It's not good to blame Luffy-san
for everything like that.
I gave you the 100,000 Berries
back the same day! Gimme a break!
who was overconfident
of his own position.
Carry out anything...
These are us?
No matter how amazing the
devil fruit power one gains,
Blaming your fate on others
won't solve anything.
A decoy, huh?
Nope!
While the pursuers are busy with me,
Did you just say that?
if he can't fully utilize it,
his existence is a total waste.
Can't you keep even a single promise?
What? Uhm...
all of you will head to
Alabasta via the normal route.
Wouldn't you agree that's
the sign of a weakling?
You've come fully prepared to die...
W-What?!
Hold it!
Do what I say,
and maybe I'll call us even!
For a long time, you lived your
life using your father's power.
You definitely said that, right?!
Who said we were gonna
take the princess there?!
D-Dammit! You're not gonna
die a good death, you know!
Y-Y-Yes, sir!
We still haven't come
to an agreement, you know!
But from here on out,
we need to face forward
Superb criminals execute their
crimes using their superb brains.
Then stop slacking off here
and get to work!
Yeah. I'm going to Hell.
and search for our dreams on our own!
Take the princess there? What now?
Yes, sir!
--Damn woman!
--Thanks a bunch!
What are you...
You haven't heard?
I have a dream!
Let's teach whoever beat Mr. 5...
Pops here wants us to take her home.
Someday, I will be a navy officer
who cracks down on bad guys!
I'm so ashamed...
If you could continue watching them...
...the terror of making a criminal
organization their enemy.
Oh, that's what this is about? Sure!
If only I'd been stronger,
I could have protected the princess!
Yes, sir.
Crocodile is gonna
come after us, you know!
Don't worry about it!
He's insanely strong!
How can you be like that?!
Is Crocodile really that strong?
A wimp like you, being a navy
officer?! That'll never happen!
If anything should happen to
the princess-- to Vivi-sama...
He's one of the
Seven Warlords of the Seas.
He's a legally recognized pirate,
and thus has no bounty on his head.
It will!
...the kingdom of Alabasta
would be finished...
After seeing how Luffy-san lives
his life, I made up my mind!
However, the bounty he did have
long ago was 80 million Berries.
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!
So this is Little Garden!
She must live!
I've decided to be it, so if I die
fighting for that, that's fine with me!
What's "little" about it?!
80 million?! That's four times
Arlong's bounty! Say no!
Run! Run, Karoo!
This place doesn't quite fit its cute name.
What?! Navy Headquarters?!
So I decided to be like Luffy-san
and put my life on the line
Ahh... It's like a terra incognita.
It's a thick jungle!
Will you do it?
Yeah. As people say,
Vice-Admiral Garp seems quite eccentric.
Yeah! It sounds like fun!
to strive for my ambition!
There's a ship docked
behind the cactus rocks!
You see? So let's both
work hard together!
We have to be careful.
I am ever grateful!
We're going to use it
to escape from this island!
But he's higher up, right?
I'm worried about what
Miss All Sunday was saying.
Screw you!
And then we'll go to Alabasta!
Ma-ma-ma... Now, then.
I, Vivi, will leave from here.
You, lecturing me?! Since when
are you that high and mighty?!
Yeah, you have no idea.
Then those two must be promising.
But what's even unluckier is
the course your Log Pose indicates.
What could you possibly learn
from that despicable Straw Hat?!
That's a perfect imitation, old guy!
Much better! Now for more sleep!
Imitation of who?!
Hmm?
Don't talk bad about Luffy-san!
Now then, Princess.
Please give me the Eternal Pose.
I haven't said anything that's wrong!
What in the world?!
The name of the next island is...
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Even if that were true,
you still piss me off!
...Little Garden.
Hurry, Karoo!
We don't even need to do anything;
Eternal Pose?
Helmeppo-san!
Please come to your senses!
Why did you let them go
without saying anything?!
You've never heard of it?
you'll be wiped out long before
you can even reach Alabasta.
Like you're anyone to talk!
I suppose you could say it's a
permanent version of a Log Pose.
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Karoo! Stop!
--Take this!
--Wake up!
Whereas a Log Pose always
leads ships to the next island,
I... wanted to play with them more.
A-A-Are you saying
a monster may appear?!
What is it?! What's going on?!
Sir! The chore boys
are fighting on the roof!
an Eternal Pose will never forget
the magnetic energy of the island
Who knows?
I wanted to talk to them more...
Mr. 5...
What are you gawking for?!
Stop them already!
Let's go to our next destination
without going ashore on this one!
They've found us! Karoo!
This way! Hurry!
that is stored in it.
I was learning how to cook so that
I could make them a tasty lunch!
Meaning it will forever
point to that island alone.
But the Log can't be stored so quickly.
Also, we have to stock up on food soon.
And this one is set to Alabasta.
Such pointless struggling.
We didn't get anything in
the last town we were in.
I didn't even say... good bye!
You're going to use this to go to Alabasta?
Miss Monday!
There's a river mouth there.
Go on. You can get to
the ships through here.
Vivi-sama. Please take the indirect
island-hopping route to Alabasta.
What? Really?
Ahh, uhm...
Why did they leave?!
--I'll hold them off here!
--But...
Ahh, I'm sorry! Forgive me!
I've not taken the path myself,
Thanks to that
freakishly strong swordsman,
Rika, that's enough. Leave him alone.
but it should only be two or three
islands if you follow the Log.
I hope there's a BBQ restaurant in here.
You two!
we're all going to get punished
for failing our mission anyway.
As if there'd be one!
Don't worry. They'll surely come back...
after becoming fine officers.
W-We're sorry!
But you said we were going
to stock up on food.
We'll collect food to cook later!
Geez, what're you thinking?
Please take good care of the princess.
Plus I'd much rather get my
butt kicked shielding a friend.
Eh? That explosion earlier
was you guys' doing?
--Yeah!
--Igaram...
But it's dangerous to go ashore.
Did they kick you out
of the navy after that?
I expect it will be a harsh journey.
But at any rate,
Thank you for the food.
Just take a look at the
plants here to start with.
C'mon, what're you standing around for?!
No, we managed to
avoid being kicked out.
can we really become marines
by doing things like this?
Be careful on your way.
I've never seen anything like them,
even in encyclopedias.
If you get killed, Mr. 8 and Mr. 9's
sacrifices will be for nothing!
Iga--!
This might be that old
dog's hobby, you know.
We had to agree to work
for free for 50 years, though.
Get going!
Hobby?
That's right. A hobby called
"the retired geezer's torment of youths."
Ahh!
Being kicked out
would've been much better.
Thank you.
How cute!
Cheer up, you two!
You, too!
Don't you think that's possible
since he seems crafty and eccentric?
Oh, yeah! Look at this!
You mean me?
First Mr. 9, and now you...
Obviously I meant Nami-san!
"Straw Hat Luffy Wreaks
Havoc in Loguetown!
Shut up, birds!!
What was it I just heard?
Let us meet safely at our motherland.
Manages a Baffling Escape
from Captain Smoker!"
...Miss Monday?
I won't let you pass.
I bet my pride on it!
Luffy-san!
It's all right. It's just a bird.
This means Luffy-san
headed for the Grand Line!
And this is just a jungle. Don't worry.
You must save the kingdom
by your own hand!
You're so funny!
You're a disgrace...
There he goes.
What's the matter?
At last, he's taken a big step
toward realizing his dream!
He was a funny old guy, to the very end!
He really is reliable.
What was that for, you damn bird?!
...to Baroque Works!
That old geezer sure is
quick to resort to violence.
A lizard... I wonder if it tastes good.
His name is Vice-Admiral Garp!
Hey, do you know...
...that he's called "Garp the Fist"
and quite feared by everyone?
Is that a kind of noise you
hear from just any jungle?
Attention!
That sounded like a volcano erupted!
Miss Monday...
No wonder his fist was
heavier than Alvida's...
No, that's not the point!
Stop with the pointless chatter already!
I will now fill you in
on our current mission!
Especially while we're working!
--Hey!
--Whadya want?!
You get me in trouble, too.
No!
Don't be so coldhearted.
D-Dad...
It's our joint responsibility.
We're friends, right?
Former Navy Captain Morgan is
to be sent to Navy Headquarters
Miss Monday...
You say that only when
it's convenient for you.
That's impossible!
They're already after us?!
to face a court martial for the
crimes of military exploitation
Then please work more seriously.
I'm a "bomb man" -- I can
make my entire body explode.
and the tormenting of civilians!
Okay, okay.
His transfer and delivery to
Vice-Admiral Garp is today's mission!
Thanks to this Bomb-Bomb Fruit power,
there is no mission I haven't completed!
I am Navy Captain "Axe-Hand" Morgan!
You rankless, low-status scum
will kneel before me!
He was a great person!
Using my Kilo-Kilo Fruit power,
A tiger?!
Nami! What's the Log say?!
It's too huge!
On second thought, I quit!
We're okay! It's stored up!
I'll bury that backstabbing
Miss Monday into the ground!
What?!
Bring her with us!
We're setting sail!
I wanna go back to how I used to live.
Ah!
Vivi! Vivi!
I'm able to change
my body weight at will!
Hurry! If they find us,
it'll all be for nothing!
Right now I'm light enough
to be lifted by the wind!
It's no use saying
something like that now...
But now it's time to get heavy!
What?! What happened?!
...although it's a different story
if we became a Navy officer...
Don't worry! We will get you there!
2 kilograms... 3 kilograms...
This isn't normal!
This is definitely not normal!
There's no getting around it, huh?
--I know they don't look like it...
That's the thing!
Why does a tiger, king of the jungle,
fall covered in blood?!
5 kilograms... 10 kilograms... 100 kilograms...
He should get court-martialed
or whatever else.
--Luffy! Go wake those two up!
--I know they don't look like it...
What's the thing?
We can't run away, nor can we slack off.
--Luffy! Go wake those two up!
--...but they saved the East Blue!
--I'm going to the ship!
1000 kilograms!
--Just the four of them!
--Alright! Leave it to me!
He does get what he deserves and all...
If that's the case, there's only one
way to go back to how I used to live.
10,000 Kilogram Press!
Ah! It's decided that we're not
gonna go ashore on this island!
Baroque Works?! Crocodile?! Ha!
But to be honest,
I still respected him anyways.
That would be becoming important
quickly, don't you think?
We'll quietly wait on the ship
until the Log is stored and...
The Seven Warlords are nothing at all!
What?!
"Don't I think"? There's no
way things can be that easy.
--Right!
--...leave this island as soon as possible.
My dad...
Well? Do you still think
you could survive that?
...was my idol.
Right!
We have to work hard
and steadily with patience.
W... We have to go to Alabasta quickly...
There is no possible escape from us.
But I guess he did take
things too far, huh?
You wanna take an easy way? That's just...
Hmph!
What're you doing?
Doing only chores and continuing to
wait around won't get us anywhere.
I will survive... I will return...
So I think I'll strengthen my body.
I will return to Alabasta alive!
You're kidding, right?
You know that's not possible.
Sanji! Make lunch for me!
Damn it!
Lunch?
Let's go!
Why?!
Yeah! For replenishing energy!
We work so hard during the day
that we're physically a wreck.
A "pirate lunch" with
lots of meat and no veggies!
Take this! Nose Fancy...
What the--?! Oww! What the--?!
Let's go to bed now.
Tell me, do you think
they'll execute him?
I've already decided.
I can smell adventure in the air!
What the hell're you doing, Luffy?! Hey!
...Cannon!
What?
--My nose is coming off!
--Let go, dammit! What's goin' on?!
T-That's...
W-Wait a sec! Where're you going?!
I'll become important and go
back to how I used to live.
Maybe there's no getting
around that either, huh?
Adventure!
I'll surpass my dad, too.
I've decided just now!
Hurry, Vivi!
Wanna come along?
Adventure! Adventure!
Mr. Bushido!
R-Right!
Given how my dad is...
Karoo is missing!
It's useless... I can't stop him.
He's too enthusiastic...
Even so... There's no way
that your body can keep up!
T-The street!
Is he crazy? There's a monster
that beat up a huge tiger in here!
Impossible! Impossible!
Impossible! Definitely impossible!
Who's he?
Helmeppo-san...
If you do that, you'll die!
A decoy. How foolish...
I cut his booger!
All hands on deck!
Once you've decided
to become that way...
Sanji! Make lunch for me!
Damn you! You never give up!
Okay. Hold on a bit.
Fall in!
if you can die fighting for that,
you should be happy! Right?
Hey! I brought 'em!
Now, of all times!
Get on! We're ready to leave anytime!
Huh? These guys are still sleeping!
--It's Vice-Admiral Garp!
--It's Garp the Fist!
Say, can I come with you?
Don't get hasty. I'm here to rescue you.
I've... already decided.
Well, I don't wanna die, but...
--What?!
--Sure! Come, come!
There's no time to look for him!
Eh? Me?
Not you too!
--But I can't just leave him here!
--Still!
So he's Navy Headquarters
Vice-Admiral Garp the Fist!
Yeah... If I just sit around here, I may
start thinking about all sorts of things.
There's no turning back.
I'll go as far as I can.
Hey! What's the problem?!
She says her duck is missing!
Say...
I'll go out to take my mind off
things until the Log is stored.
The hero of the seas who
travels all over the Grand Line!
What is Baroque Works, anyway?
Later, Coby.
He won't come when we whistle for him!
Please wait!
No way! It may be okay for Luffy,
but it's too dangerous for you!
Hmm? What is it, Coby?
This him?
--You're there?!
--He was here even before me.
I'll be fine since Karoo will be with me.
I should've known better...
There's a tributary just up the river!
A secret crime syndicate.
I carelessly said wimpy
things like I used to...
We can use it to get
out to sea a little faster!
Vice-Admiral Garp! Thank you
for coming all this way personally!
He's too shocked to say a word, though.
None of its members knows
their boss' face or name.
Alright! Let's go!
You're right. The issue isn't
if we can do it or not,
We hereby deliver Morgan to you!
Then, I'll make a lunch
of love for Vivi-chan.
Hey.
Its main work is espionage, assassination,
larceny, and bounty-hunting.
but if we have the will to do it.
Mr. Bushido...
Could you prepare something
to drink for Karoo?
Just how many people are
gonna be chasing us down?
--Dad...
--Stop, Helmeppo-san!
I've decided just now, too.
It's all done at their boss' command.
Umm... Vice-Admiral Garp?
Of course! Please leave it to me!
I don't know.
Your motive is a little impure, but...
There are about 2,000
people in Baroque Works,
Vice-Admiral Garp!
Quiet!
Why would they listen to their boss,
whose identity they don't know?
I hear you.
I'll go along with your spirit!
and I've heard there are several
town-like bases like this one nearby.
I've been up for five days now...
Huh?
Okay.
Baroque Works' ultimate objective
is the founding of an ideal nation!
They really might send 1,000 people?!
Thank you for your hard work, sir!
H-Huh?!
No, I've been going for a
new doughnut-eating record...
It's fine by me!
Hey! The ship's leaving!
Now you're all set. Two pirate
lunches and a special drink for Karoo.
Then we'll compete
and see who drops first!
Everyone who does well
within the company now
Finally awake, I see.
Sir?
Wait! Let's stay just one more night!
But the lack of sleep and rest has
gotten me a bit drowsy at 842...
That's just what I want!
I'm telling you now that I won't lose!
will be guaranteed a high social
standing within the ideal nation
Yeah!
This town is great!
And the girls are cute!
Okay!
Ha! Say whatever you want!
See you later. I'm going ahead of you.
that the boss will be
creating before long.
There's no telling when
we'll have this much fun again!
Ah! That's not nice to go alone!
--Let's take it easy! We are pirates!
--Plus, it's not even morning yet!
This geezer's a joke.
I see...
Well, then. See you later!
Morgan! Vice-Admiral Garp is a
leading figure at Navy Headquarters!
Who cares? We're not friends.
The boss's codename is Mr. 0.
They have some nerve.
They don't even know anything...
All right! Let's go!
I don't have time
to be buddy-buddy with you!
We'll be back in a little while!
What're you saying?
That's not what you said earlier at all!
In other words, the closer a
person's codename is to zero,
Old man. Cut the sleeping act.
Hey! Explain to them!
Miss Wednesday sure is brave.
--Yep! I just did!
--That was fast...
the higher that person's
future standing will be...
As may be expected from someone
who infiltrated an enemy organization.
Yeah, I left out the complicated parts.
...and more than anything,
the stronger they are!
We should be able to
leave the island soon...
The strength of those from Mr. 5
and above is especially incredible.
Cool! There's fog now!
Well, I'm bored too,
so I'll go take a walk.
Don't move!
It's almost morning...
Take a walk?!
Heave ho!
It's good we managed to
escape the people chasing us!
Move and I'll hack this chore boy
up and feed him to the sharks!
So you're the swordsman who cut down
That's for sure!
Ah! Hey, Zoro!
all of the lowly employees in this town.
We need to be careful not to
crash the ship into the rocks.
Wait!
D-D-Dad!
Hmm?
Why would you want to protect
the princess of Alabasta?
We're short of food.
Just leave it to me!
Please stop this!
Helmeppo-san is your own son!
If you see animals that
appear edible, bring them back.
I got some circumstances
of my own, you see...
Ow, ow, ow...
Wait. Was that you, Luffy?
Okay, got it.
Son?! I don't need a son!
Well, no matter. You're our enemy,
one way or the other.
Nope.
I'll bring back one that
you can't possibly capture.
What I want is freedom!
His life means nothing to me!
You're in our way.
This is a nice ship.
Wait, you bastard!
Yeah! He is!
I'll toss him into a pool
of blood if I have to!
Hmm?!
I can't let that remark go unchallenged!
D-Dad...
Who're you?!
Y-You're...!
You can capture a bigger
one than I can, you say?!
There you are!
One, two! One, two!
H-Help me!
So long, fools!
One, two!
I ran into Mr. 8 a short while ago,
Of course.
Helmeppo-san!
One, two! One, two!
Zoro!
Ready the cannon!
Miss Wednesday.
Now what?!
One, two! One, two! One...
Load! Aim!
You killed Igaram!
Luffy! Thanks, but I don't need any help!
Target-- 16 degrees starboard!
Distance-- 8,263! Ready!
Then, it's a hunting match.
Who cares about that?!
What're you doing on this ship?!
Who are you?!
Or does that wench got you in debt, too?
So this is Straw Hat Luffy,
the 30 million-Berry bounty head!
Look! We'll compete over how
many kilos of meat we get.
What are you doing here...
P-Please wait!
...Miss All Sunday?!
We have to capture a vicious,
dirty pirate like him
--That's dangerous!
--What're you doing?!
Didn't you mean to say how many tons?
as soon as possible
and put him to execution!
You can talk cocky once
you've brought back some prey.
I'm gonna make you pay
for what you did! Let's fight!
Miss All Sunday?!
What number is she partner to?!
Indeed!
Humph! I'll take you up on that!
P-Please don't shoot! My friend...
Huh?!
What nonsense are you
spewing this time?!
She's the partner of Mr. 0... the boss!
My friend's onboard!
I wonder... why they're all like that?
Luffy-san is wanted for bounty...
Something is wrong, isn't it?
Move.
Shut up! I'm gonna kick your ass
for being such an ingrate!
The bo-- Crocodile?!
No!
I understand how you feel.
Is she bad?
Don't cry. I'm on your side.
Then I'll cut you down!
Stupid! A pirate is a pirate.
She was the only one
who knew the boss's identity.
Ingrate?!
--Stop, chore boy!
--Don't go against regulations!
Once he's caught,
he's set to be executed.
That's right!
We found out who he is by following her!
No! Helmeppo-san is my...
I know that!
Hey! What happened?!
Who did this to you?!
But it's not that easy
to accept it, you know!
More accurately...
I allowed you to follow me.
We're sitting ducks...
Your green-haired swordsman friend...
That's my line!
Luffy-san and I are friends.
...my...
...friend!
Oh! Then she's good!
Shhhh!
What?!
Idiot! No marine has
a pirate for a friend.
I know that!
You're also the one who told him
we discovered his identity, right?!
Everyone in town welcomed us
and gave us lots of yummy food!
But wait a sec...
Don't ever say that again!
That fool. Stirring up trouble, huh?
Correct.
Or you'll get fired from the Navy!
W-W-What's the matter?!
--So she really is bad!
--Pipe down, you!
But you cut down every last one of them!
I know that much!
N-N-N-N-Nami?!
What exactly is it you're trying to do?!
I won't say such a thing anywhere else!
Well, yeah, but...
You will pay for this.
This isn't it... This isn't, either.
That's much better than
just abandoning my friend!
You will pay for this!
Good question.
Ouch! Ow, ow...! H-Hey, Nami! Nami!
You swear? Geez...
Please! I'll go capture him myself!
W-What a dull-headed person!
You were all so intent and serious
that I found myself helping out.
Hey... what the heck
are you looking for?
V-V-Vice-Admiral Garp!
I remember reading about it in a book.
The idea of a princess trying
her hardest to save her kingdom
Internal strife, huh? Talk about lame.
A... About what?
What? You guys were talking
about something interesting.
while making herself
an enemy of Baroque Works...
Little Garden.
Let's just get rid of everyone
who interferes with our mission!
Let me hear it, too.
So who's your friend?
It was just so ridiculous, you see...
Oops!
Don't you mock me!
Hold on, Luffy.
You idiot! Come back!
There's no way you can catch him!
Come with me...
Listen to me.
They were actually bounty-hunt--
What's the matter?
Here, look at this!
There's a shellfish like a squid.
Don't make excuses!
Let's let him go.
Hey! Sanji! You do realize
what you're doing?!
What?!
He's either quite the fool, or...
I'll ask you again.
Are you trying to kill me?!
No, not really.
You two're friends
with that Straw Hat Luffy?
A squid shellfish!
Yeah! Die!
What do we do?!
I just sense that my beloved
Miss Wednesday is in danger...
It looks a lot like the ammonite.
I don't know if Helmeppo-san is, but I am!
Dammit! Listen to me!
I'd appreciate it if you wouldn't
point such dangerous objects at me.
It's a squid shellfish, right?
He said that we are friends
even if we're apart.
Hey!
What's with all the racket?
I'm finally awake...
You don't mean...!
That idiot!
I suppose you're aware of this,
A Devil--
He's serious!
Vice-Admiral Garp! I thought
for sure you'd been done in!
but we can't keep people
like that in the Navy.
A Devil Fruit?!
Mr. 5.
Which one?! What's her power?!
Huh?! Someone's been done in?!
But fortunately,
I'm the only one who knows it.
It doesn't seem like
they're here to stop us.
I feel like someone's been
following me for a while...
Oww...
I didn't see it because I was asleep!
Who was wounded?!
It would seem not.
Upon closer look,
you're actually a beautiful lady!
Well, it must be my imagination.
Do you wanna be a marine?!
Then let's accomplish our mission quickly.
Now, now. Don't be so hasty.
I haven't been given any orders.
Please wait a second!
It's true that I'm Luffy-san's friend,
but Helmeppo-san has nothing to...
Our mission to eliminate Princess
Vivi of the Kingdom of Alabasta.
--Why, you! Quit running away!
--H-Hold on, Luffy! Hear me out!
We do! That's why we're here!
Me?
I have no reason to fight.
Let's do it, Miss Valentine!
Helmeppo-san!
Yes, Mr. 5!
So you're the straw hat captain
I've heard so much about...
Idiot! He isn't someone
who'd listen to that now.
I'm free!
Quit screwing around, dammit!
Just you watch! The world will
kneel down before me once again!
...Monkey D. Luffy.
It's joint responsibility.
Joint responsibility.
How dare you mess with me?!
Today marks the new start of
the newly reborn Morgan Kingdom!
Hey, you! Gimme my hat back!
Are you tryin' to start a fight?!
Collier Shoot!
What about you, Coby?!
Don't you wanna be one?
I deem you an enemy! Leave this instant!
Now! Set our course to the west!
That dumbass!
I do!!
What're you doing?!
I said set our course to the west!
How unlucky you are...
Then, stop grumbling
and bring it on already!
You people who picked up a princess
Baroque Works is out to kill...
No!
I'll have no part in this!
Hm...
He covered for me after this happened!
And a princess being protected
by a mere handful of pirates...
Now you guys've really gotten in our way!
What the hell is this? Is it edible?
Even when getting kicked out of
the navy would destroy his dream!
But what's even unluckier is the
course your Log Pose indicates.
Ugh! What the heck's going on?!
He's protecting me, regardless of that!
If you two wanna kill
each other that badly,
I can do it, too!
Let me see... which one was it?
Dad! I'm going to capture you!
Just give up--
The name of the next island is...
then we'll kill you both
ourselves while we're at it!
I think I read it recently,
but it slipped my mind.
...Little Garden.
'Kay?
Are you stupid?! Who do you
think you're talkin' to, huh?!
We don't even need to do anything;
We're not done yet!
Yeah!
you'll be wiped out long before
you can even reach Alabasta.
What can a piece of
useless scum do to me?!
No good!
--Will not! Gimme my hat back!
--You wish! You big dummy!
Oh? Why is there a Sea King on the land?
Now I'm really annoyed!
Do as you're told, and I'll make
things nice for ya. So be quiet and--
Time to die at the hands
of my Kilo-Kilo Fruit power!
What are you, a kid?
Do you not think letting yourself
get wiped out is a bit foolish?
Shut the hell up, Dad!
Get ready! As I ride this explosive blast,
I weigh only 1 kilogram!
A dinosaur!
A dinosaur?!
Dammit!
Then, this is an ancient island!
Know your place, you pathetic insect!
An Eternal Pose?
Mr. Bushido! You have to dodge! She's...!
Huh?
As if I'd ever listen to you!
You can skip past Little Garden with that.
Shut up!
The land here is stuck in
the time of the dinosaurs!
I'm the one who decides how I live!
It points to an island just before Alabasta:
This isn't the time for that right now!
Hmm?
We're not done yet!
Quit getting the wrong idea!
What can scum like you possibly do?!
Since there were no exchanges
among islands in the Grand Line
Nothing At All Island.
We're not dead yet!
That was a good workout!
Finally managed to digest that food!
None of our employees know that course,
so no one will chase you.
He isn't alone!
due to the difficulties with sea travel,
You wanna die that bad?
M-Mr. 5?! No way!
each one established its unique culture.
--You!
--M-M-Morgan!
I've decided to be a marine.
What? She's a good person?
He took out a Baroque
Works officer agent?!
Hm?
Please give yourself up!
There are islands that have an
extremely sophisticated culture...
If I die fighting for it, I'll be happy.
Why are you giving this to us?!
As a member of the navy forces,
I'm going to capture you!
It's a trap, isn't it?
Now I can fight for reals.
No way we'd give it up yet!
and there're some others
that remain in the same form
Is it, now?
--Hold on, Luffy.
--Here I come!
I'm a man who will become a Navy officer!
--Calm down and hear me out.
--Here I come!
without progressing for several thousand
or tens of thousands years...
What do I do? I don't want to
accept this from someone like her.
--Calm down and hear me out.
--I can change to 10,000 kilograms!
--Everyone in town was a bounty hunter.
--Our enemy, in other words.
--I can change to 10,000 kilograms!
But now that they've let me onboard,
Huh?
Pathetic! Pathetic! Pathetic!
Hey! Don't ignore me!
taking the safest route might be best...
The random climate in the
Grand Line makes it possible.
Who cares about that?!
What can a couple of insects do?!
A Navy officer, huh? That's interesting.
Liar! Enemies wouldn't
give us food to eat!
That's why this island
exists in the dinosaur time.
Get in my way and I'll
chop you both into pieces!
Take this! 10,000 Kilogram Press!
I'm sorry it turned out this way
after you came to save me...
Are you an idiot?!
Amazing!
She just went out of her way
to show us a nicer course!
What are you talking about?
Luffy!
Luffy.
We're friends!
What if she's actually a good person?!
Coby...
Looks like trying to talk
sense into you is pointless.
Plus, I've made up my mind!
I've decided to live for my beliefs!
Don't jump on it!
You're not the one who
decides this ship's course!
Usopp! Usopp!
You dumb dimwit!
What? What's the matter?
Damn it...
In that case, I'm gonna fight to kill, too!
People here have been calling
me eccentric for quite a while,
A-And if I die fighting...
Did you find the book?
I see. That's too bad.
Don't regret it when you die!
Sounds great to me!
Urgh!
...if I die fighting for that,
that's fine with me!
Yeah...
and especially this time,
they said all sorts of things.
She blew up the old tube
hair guy, so I hate her!
Hold on! What's going on?!
Weren't these two people friends?!
Since I brought you here, I have to
train you so that you'll be very useful.
I don't hate high-spirited people.
You wanna die that badly, huh?!
Gum-Gum...
I'm not going to die!
If you survive...
I tested you two to see
what you are really like.
...let's meet again.
Humph! What a rude guy...
Not until I've become a
navy officer! But, when...
No!
Oni...
What we're really like?
When I do die...
Although it may appear that you've been
trying hard strengthening your bodies,
--...Bazooka!
--...Giri!
Let's go, Bunchi!
...it'll be...
...while I'm fighting!
I thought you might
still be weak mentally.
--W-What is that?!
--Don't tell me it's a Sea King!
So I tested you to see if you're
working with firm determination.
Playtime is over!
No...
Coby!
So what's the verdict?
A turtle!
This is the perfect chance
to see which is stronger,
You stupid idiot! Let Coby go! Coby!
What a huge turtle!
I'll acknowledge your determination.
brute force or swordsmanship!
But...
Yeah! Let's find out once and for all!
So we both use the Three-Sword Style...
Tatsu-Maki!
...you've still got a long way to go!
I can't tell what that
woman is thinking one bit!
When it comes to weakness,
you guys take the cake!
You damn insects
aren't even worth killing.
Gum-Gum...
Then there's no point
in thinking about it.
Never show yourself to me again!
You'll have an intense
special training every day.
...Pistol!
We already got someone
like that on this ship, anyway.
Morgan!
Be prepared!
Hey! Explain what's going on!
None of this makes sense!
I'll let you go for today!
Oh, Miss Wednesday!
Don't tell me you've joined the crew?!
But someday I will surpass you!
I'll overlook your friend situation.
Hey! Explain already--!
Whoa! There's an ostrich onboard!
But don't tell anyone.
Someday, I will catch you!
Just cherish that feeling.
--C'mon, what's going on?!
--Is it for food?
Just you wait!
Explain what's going on!
Yes sir! Thank you very much,
Vice-Admiral Garp!!
I see.
Please forgive my poor supervision!
What now?
I want to escape, but will we be
all right if we pass through here?
It's too bad I missed out on it,
Allowing the prisoner to escape
is the biggest blunder of my life!
but there's still opportunity
for me to shine, too.
We're very sorry, sir!
After what's happened,
these two will be kicked out for life!
Don't worry!
Now that this sleeping prince has awoken,
your safety is guaranteed!
Whoa! Good thing I slept through it!
What truly lost causes you are.
I doubt anyone anywhere
would take you in now.
--Nami-san. Jealous any?
--Nope!
This is bad. On this island...
And you'd only burden everyone
if we turned you loose...
Is it really all right
for me to be on this ship?
On this island...
You leave me no choice.
Come with me to Navy Headquarters!
I'll only trouble you all...
Vice-Admiral! You're going to
take them with you to Navy HQ?!
What're you talking about?!
We know who you are now!
Is that bad?
If you didn't want to trouble us,
you should've done so from the start!
N-No, not exactly...
Damn it!
I'm sorry.
Are you two against it?
Right, Luffy?
If you want to run away,
now's your chance.
The title of Baroque Works
Officer Agent will be shamed
Yeah! I'm hungry!
Ah!!
Though I have no intention
of letting you say no, anyway.
Maybe it doesn't matter at all?
if we let these guys make fools of us!
For now, looks like our
next destination is set.
My, oh, my.
What an odd day this has been!
Mr. 5! Let's show them how
truly terrifying we can be!
Little Garden, huh?
What? It felt like
Nami-san just called me...
H-Hey, now! Will we be alright there?!
Let's do it, Miss Valentine!
Who knows? Let's go, men!
Yes, Mr. 5!
Don't mock us!
We're Baroque Works Officer Agents!
Yeah!
"To those residents,
this island is as if a 'little garden.'
It'll be quite the sight...
And that's how we wound up heading
for the Grand Line, Luffy-san.
Quit being so damn annoying!
Little Garden...
You're interfering...
Alright! Let's go!!
That's what I'll call this place."
...with our fight!
Little Garden...
Louis Arnote, explorer.
I'm sure the day will come
when we meet again!
Yeah!
You've got me!
Ah, gentle song
Make it there for us
After a wave washed away
that little sand castle
You looked up at the passing
clouds with a sad smile
If you find the world is full of enemies,
I've got your back
Don't lose faith
You've got me!
Ah, my love
I'll hold you in my arms forever
You've got me!
Who decided she's coming with us?!
So this is Little Garden!
Ahhh! A giant!
Oh! Here we go! Check it out!
Next is Little Garden!
What do you think it's like?!
What's "little" about it?!
What is it? Oh, this is a navy photo!
Now we'll have lots
more people after us!
Pretend we're dead.
But we need to hurry to Alabasta!
Doesn't that only work on bears?
It's like an undiscovered land.
It's a thick jungle.
--I'm so excited!
--We're lucky!
That's no ordinary guy in it!
Know who it is?!
Whoa! It's huge!
Are you a human, old guy?
--Oh, that reminds me of him!
-- "Him"?
I hope there's a BBQ restaurant in here.
It feels like we've hit the big time now!
A friend of mine named Coby!
As if there'd be one!
--Whoa, it's Coby!
--Coby? Who's that?
Do you guys even understand?!
We're in big trouble!
With a big catch like this...
The guy at that axe-hand navy freak's place?
This isn't normal!
This is definitely not normal!
In this hunting match...
Oh, come on. We've already
decided to take Vivi with us!
My friend!
Axe-hand?! You mean Morgan?
I'm the winner!
It's decided that we're not gonna go
ashore on this island... Right, guys?
--He's gonna be a navy softener!
--You mean "officer"!
Think he's still at that guy's place?
You will compensate me in full,
just so you know!
Hey, old guy. Where're you going?
I can smell adventure in the air!
Man, talk about being careless...
On the next episode of One Piece!
Duel?!
"Try Hard, Coby!
Coby-Meppo's Struggles in the Navy"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Deliver Princess Vivi!
The Luffy Pirates Set Sail"
"Coby-Meppo's Resolve!
Vice-Admiral Garp's Parental Affection"
"An Ancient Island!
The Shadow Hiding in Little Garden!"
"Huge Duel!
The Giants Dorry and Broggy"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!