iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
Now, the detail of the
nightmare that Dressrosa faced
10 years ago is revealed.
I am the rightful king of this country!
And now, I'm...
...back!
I'm going to sell you this country
for 10 billion berries.
Please let me borrow all of your money!
Stop! Don't make me do this!
--King Riku-sama, please stop!
--What are you doing?!
Boy... What kind of king he is!
Well, the night has just begun, soldiers.
You should dance, too!
Parasite String!
Wh-What the hell? What's going on?!
M-My arm is moving on its own!
Why does it move on its own?!
Is it what's happening to King-sama?!
There's no way to justify myself!
This country is finished!
Doflamingo set us up!
Hey, hey!
Can we do it already, Doffy?
Idiot. Don't rush.
I have to make the people tremble
with fear more
and get them hate King Riku
with all their heart!
And then, the heroes will appear!
"A Nightmare!
The Tragic Night of Dressrosa!"
--What happened to King-sama?!
--The whole country is in chaos!
He didn't look right
when he left the palace earlier
but I didn't expect this!
It's more than we can handle within
the country so I called the Navy!
Captain Vergo said
he's gonna take care of it!
Oh, that's good!
Father-sama!
Father-sama...
Why?
Why are you doing that?!
Snow?
Monet! What are you doing there?!
You're a maid!
Why are you opening the gate of the palace?!
Princess Viola.
If you use your Clairvoyance,
you can see clearly...
...what is happening in this country!
I'm waiting to welcome
the new royal family.
Wh-What are you...
Now, shall we?
Viola-sama.
--The east tower has been bombed!
--Some pirates have breached the palace!
They took Viola-sama!
The palace is not too bad.
It's kind of nice.
Yeah, I love it-dasuyan!
It's perfect for Young Master-sama-in!
--Stop, you fools!
--Are you Doflamingo's clan?
Monet! Let go of Viola-sama!
Did you guys do something to King Riku-sama?!
Now, we have a lot to do!
We have to "clean up" the whole palace!
Father-sama!
Why are you doing such a thing?!
King Riku Army!
Please stop!
If there's no preventing me
hurting the citizens...
I'd rather be dead!
Somebody, please...
...kill me!
Why is it, King Riku-sama?
Did we do something wrong?
You were always just.
You were...
...the king we were proud of.
You told us that you needed our money.
So we've brought you all our money.
Because you've...
...always cared about us
more than anything!
Because you were our pride and joy!!
King Riku has...
King Riku has trampled
on our feelings!
He's gonna take our money
and kill us all!
To satisfy his own selfish desires,
he's gonna toss us aside like trash!
King Riku, you bastard!
I hate you!
You're...
You're a low-down, dirty scumbag!
The King Riku Army's coming!
Hey, move out of there! Get away!
H-H-Help...
Who are you people?
We're here to save this country!
My name is Don Quixote Doflamingo!
Th-They're pirates!
Pirates?
What is going on?
Why are the pirates...
But they're gonna save us
from the King Riku Army.
King Riku's here!
Here comes a hero!
I like how you "dance"!
King Riku!
Trebol! Pica! Diamante!
Now, go and sweep out the trash
from the whole country!
Yes...
Yes!
We did it!
We survived!
Doflamingo! Doflamingo!
Doflamingo! Doflamingo! Doflamingo!
Follow your doom! Embrace violence!
Stop running! Fight!
You coward!
I'll never forgive your evil family!
--Go to hell already, Rebecca!
--Chop her up!
--You're a piece of shit!
--Drop dead!
The country fell into hands of Doflamingo
in just one night.
How awful!
It's like a nightmare!
How cunning of him!
I-I-I can't stand that Doflamingo guy!
We believed that King Riku
went crazy at that time, too,
so we got in touch with
the new king Doflamingo
and ended up like this.
I'm so ashamed of myself
for distrusting King Riku!
I see! It's really too bad!
You let the innocent king that
you all admired so much die for nothing.
No, he's still alive!
What?!
Doflamingo loved the special ability
the former princess Viola-sama had.
So she bargained with him!
If you promise me that
you won't kill my father,
I will obey you!
She still lives and works
under Doflamingo!
Becoming an officer in his group
and changing her name to Violet!
S-S-She's an officer?!
Then, King Riku is still
alive thanks to her?!
Yes, I'm sure he's still living somewhere
in this country.
But I can't imagine how much pain
he must've gone through over the last decade!
And how hard it must've been for Viola-sama!
Fear, anger, tears!
I wonder how she has spent
the last decade.
And, on the same night,
other soldiers were
manipulated as the king was
and massacred the civilians unwillingly,
they must've been suffering so much, too!
I thought all of them must've
been killed that night!
Some got killed
but others surrendered to Doflamingo
and they're working for him as his guards.
They sold out to him?!
I believe they made an agonizing choice!
Screw you!
They just followed the crazy king's order.
Forgive me for welcoming them
to work under me.
If so, I can't help crying!
Everybody has been suffering so much!
It's a tragedy! You poor people!
There were soldiers who got killed
and who surrendered.
But when you sum it up,
it doesn't add up to a
whole army for a country!
What do you mean by that?
I believe I have lost some memories!
That's what I meant!
Lost some memories?!
Fra-land.
Remember what I've told you earlier?
Even after we became toys,
we remember everything
about when we were humans.
But people around us, even our own family,
forgot that we even existed.
What?!
They don't even know
that they lost their loved ones.
That's the biggest tragedy of Dressrosa
and even we toys forgot some things, too.
You mean, there might be your
friends among those toys
that are walking on the streets
but you can't recognize them
because you forgot about them?
Exactly.
In addition, they must've been feeling
angry since Doflamingo turned them into toys.
Damn it all!
Why should I be a toy?!
Get away from my wife!
Damn! I can't say what I wanna say!
--Damn Doflamingo!
--I hate him so much!
Isn't there anybody
who can take him down?!
Doflamingo tried to bury all the dissidents
but that means...
...there are countless dissidents
dwelling in the shadows of this country!
That unknown number of those poor people
is the key to our plan!
I see!
That's why you think
there is a chance to win.
It's true that it seems foolhardy
to fight the Warlord's group but...
...if all the toys in this country are dissidents,
it'd be a powerful enough force!
Hey, hey, hey! Wait a minute!
You seem like you're going for
taking down Doflamingo!
We're only here to destroy the factory!
When it's done, we'll say
goodbye to the country!
Right, Robin?!
I'm so mad at Doflamingo!
You see?
What?!
We're destined to fight
this decisive battle today!
With the event of this morning,
they're challenging us!
It's not a coincidence
that Usoland came to us today!
Somebody from above is telling us
to fight!
--Yeah!
--What event?
Doflamingo's abdication
from the throne.
Oh, the fact is we...
Can you imagine how happy we were
when we heard about it?!
I thought it was a miracle!
And then, we heard it was a false report.
We felt like we were dropped
from heaven to the edge of hell!
So it was only natural for us to...
...decide to fight him today!
We're so sorry for what we did!
You're retired but you led your crew here?
We have no disciples
to succeed the Happo Navy.
I wish I had a grandson.
I see. It's not so easy to be a pirate, eh?
Maybe it's just my imagination
but I feel like I'm forgetting something.
I felt the same way 10 years ago.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, where am I going?!
Grandpa, help me!
What have they done to me -
Abdullah, the lone wolf?!
Jeet, the maverick warrior!
Help!
Zoro!
Damn Crest Head!
He said he was gonna show me
the way but he's collapsed!
Is Zoro really here?!
Hey!
Zoro! Kin'emon!