Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass, We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
Running at full speed everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
We keep finding the things we want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou sora e to hikizuridashite
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
and if that makes you feel something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of burning, intense excitement!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho e sore ga adobenchaa
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition
- in which a winner will get the
Luffy entered a fighting competition -
in which a winner will get the
Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize -
Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize
- and won the first round.
and won the first round.
Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize
- and won the first round.
Tra-guy!!
but now, he's heading for the palace
to take back Law
Meanwhile, Usopp and the others
Meanwhile, Lightning Soldier and the
And what do you want, Zoro?
learned about the nightmare
in Dressrosa a decade ago...
However, after reuniting
with Zoro and Kin'emon,
who's been captured by Doflamingo.
Tontatta Tribe are having a rally underneath Dressrosa.
Zoro and Kin'emon finally
got to see Luffy again
I-I never imagined he'd be alive!
...from a toy soldier who is looking to
take down Doflamingo.
Law was shot by Doflamingo before their eyes.
and called the others through the Transponder Snails
"Operation Dressrosa SOP"!
I'm asking you! Who is that person?!
Please stop!
and checked how everybody was doing.
How dare you shoot Tra-guy!
M-My brother!
One of Doflamingo's subordinates
turned us into toys.
Law was originally my subordinate.
We are currently with the King Riku Army,
an anti-Doflamingo coalition in this country.
Ace was right!
If there's no preventing me
hurting the citizens...
Responsibility for dealing
with him falls to me!
We were always bonded together as brothers!
We have to knock out
this Hobby-Hobby Fruit eater!
An army?
Somebody, please kill me!
--Of Little People.
--Little People?
--Hobby-Hobby Fruit?
--You can imagine what will happen then.
And all the people here are looking to
take down Doflamingo this very day!
"A Burning Passion!
Rebecca vs. Suleiman!"
"Luffy Astonished!
The Man Who Inherits Ace's Will!"
Oh! It will break the spell?!
That's right!
Huh? A soldier?
All the toys in Dressrosa will change back into
their human forms at once!
He is willing to sacrifice his life
to destroy this kingdom!
We're here to save this country!
So if we can knock her out,
all the toys can change back?!
--Franky, stop the army!
--No way!
My name is Don Quixote Doflamingo!
This brave, little army...
That's right!
The country fell into the hands
of Doflamingo in just one night.
I can't...
We'll frighten her out of her wits
and make her pass out!
And that's Operation...
...let them down!
We believed that King Riku went crazy
at that time, too,
Sugar!
Oversurprised!
Panic!
Soldier-san's gonna die.
Oh! Sorry, sorry!
Y-You are...
Suleiman keeps attacking Rebecca!
so we got in touch with the new king Doflamingo
and ended up like this.
It's been a while!
I didn't want to make you suffer before
dying but I've missed a vital spot!
Franky!
You're free to go all out!
He even fended off her
Back-to-the-Water Dance!
I'm so ashamed of myself
for distrusting King Riku!
We'll be there as soon as possible!
I-I don't buy it!
Rebecca's struggling!
--Go!
--Go to hell, Rebecca!
I thought he died!
I see! It's really too bad!
What?!
Thanks!
I pledged my loyalty to Joker!
All right.
You let the innocent king that you
all admired so much die for nothing.
Let's go back!
Suleiman, chop her head off!
What?!
I thought you were gonna say that!
"Operation SOP Starts!
Usoland Charges Forth!"
No, he's still alive!
He was once a hero in the Dias Naval Battle
but after being exiled from
his country as a war criminal,
--What's going on?! The town is...
--It's coming this way!
Don't make things up, Dellinger!
There were soldiers who got killed
and who surrendered.
he became a grim reaper
walking on the dark side of the world!
But when you sum it up,
Spring Death Knock!
it doesn't add up to a
whole army for a country!
Doflamingo!
Uh-huh, uh-huh. I know how you feel.
In addition, they must've been feeling angry
Tra-guy!
since Doflamingo turned them into toys.
Stupid brat!
But we don't need...
Hey, Tra-guy! Why are you with Doflamingo...
That unknown number of those poor people
is the key to our plan!
SULEIMAN THE BEHEADER
A CLASS-A WAR CRIMINAL FROM THE DIAS NAVAL BATTLE
He has the lifeless bearing of a ghost!
Ouch!
Are you still crying?!
Because...
I did everything for my country.
You've pushed it too far!
I've never seen Luffy-dono crying like that.
"A Showdown Between the Warlords!
Law vs. Doflamingo!"
I used to love my country.
...a lame duck in our family.
He must be very happy to see that person alive.
What about you?
Hey! I'm here!
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
--Part of that evil family!
--Drop dead, Rebecca!
I'm asking you! Who is that person?!
--Zoro! Kin'emon!
--Luffy!
M-My brother!
Don't shout, idiot!
Somebody's gonna find us!
When people hate you so,
Brother?!
What?! Luffy-dono has a brother?!
--Shh! Shh! Please!
--Oh, sorry!
it must be hard for you
to even breathe in this country.
Damn! I can't believe
running is all I can do!
Cora-san...
I thought your brother was "Fire Fist" Ace!
Are you saying he is alive?!
But I'm glad to see you!
I wasn't so sure about that man
who talks so weirdly
Tra-guy!!
But I don't buy his words!
I don't care how hard it is.
It brings back memories!
I don't mind being hated!
but it seems like
he did what he had to do.
Answer my question!
"Two Great Rivals Meet Each Other!
Straw Hat and Heavenly Demon!"
I just want to...
Where is he?
He collapsed on our way here.
Where are you, Joker?!
I need to hear it from you!
I just want to live together
with Soldier-san!
Really? What is wrong with that guy?
I don't know.
There you are.
Rebecca!
She just won't give up!
Including the beautiful...
Straw Hat!
Hey! I heard some explosions and gunshots!
Joker wants me to kill Straw Hat?
...I mean, hateful Rebecca,
What happened to Tra-guy?!
Finish it up before the competition's over.
Can you hear me, Luffy?!
there are only about 30 contenders left
in Block D!
What's happening there?!
Then, you'll get promoted to be...
...an executive of the Family.
You just don't know when to give up.
Say something, Luffy!
I'm sorry, Straw Hat. But I...
When we become pirates,
we might not be on the same ship
but our brotherhood will always
be with us!
I wanna get on board Doflamingo's ship!
Don't cause Young Master-sama
any more trouble.
I'm sorry to bother you all.
Wherever you are, whatever you do,
we'll always be bonded together!
Hey, Bellamy! Don't give up!
He is a Warlord and a pirate - Trafalgar Law.
I'm not holding a grudge
against you anymore.
So from now on,
He was behind the false report of
my abdication from the throne this morning.
One more person,
I mean, animal down!
we're brothers!
I'm done picking on you.
ORLUMBUS - AN ADVENTURER
(AN ADMIRAL OF THE YONTA MARIA GRAND FLEET)
He defeated dozens of people
and let blood run on the ring
Goodbye, Bellamy!
He was?!
but now, the fighting lion Agyo has...
Ace was right!
We were always bonded together as brothers!
...been beaten by Orlumbus's whip!
I said "Who is that"?!
"Withdraws from the Seven Warlords"?
What's going on?
Yeah, and then
he suddenly collapsed...
Barrier!
Dressrosa is finished!
THE KING RIKU ARMY HEADQUARTERS
--How strong!
--Admiral!
What do you want?!
Hey, Luffy. What's wrong?
Your Majesty!
CAVENDISH - A PIRATE
Will one of the favorites win as expected?!
Nothing.
Your Majesty! Why did you resign?!
Everybody! Are you ready?!
Then, I got lost.
I didn't know which way to go, so...
Bartolomeo?
Or some dark horse?!
DAMASK - AN ARSONIST
It's none of your business!
Yeah!
THE FLOWER FIELD
(THEIR PRESENT LOCATION)
Please give us a reason, Your Majesty!
Yeah, you're right.
MUMMY - A SORCERER
We'll sneak into the port through the underground passage!
Only one winner can move to the finals!
THE TRADE PORT
I just created this barrier because I felt like it!
The life of King Riku's granddaughter...
He was trying to drag me down.
This is our family's problem!
I'll kill you, too, if you get in my way!
Our target is just one girl!
Ah! There you are, Bellamy!
Who's gonna take it?!
Hey, have you killed him already?
But don't worry!
I've just gotten rid of him!
Sugar!
She's just a girl
but it's not gonna be easy!
Try it!
But no one can break my barrier!
Is it what it was all about?!
You haven't, have you?!
Soldier-san, where are you now?
So he almost messed Dressrosa up!
We're gonna knock Sugar out
What do you want, Dellinger?!
so all the toys in the country will change back to humans!
Don't die!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
That's all I ask!
Now we're safe!
DELLINGER - A COMBATANT
THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY (THE DIAMANTE ARMY)
Yeah!
Well, I thought you were gonna mess it up.
Free our captive Tontatta friends
and take Dressrosa back for King Riku!
Clank.
What?! I'm in the middle of something!
The assassination of Straw Hat.
--Go to hell, Rebecca!
--Chop her up already!
It's me, Dellinger.
Hey, Mingo!!
What?!
Sounds like you haven't killed Bellamy yet.
Screw you, Rebecca!
Well, what can you do?
He's a strong guy.
Yeah!
It's gonna be fun
to turn those hisses and boos...
We, Yellow Cub Squad, and...
You're so dull.
But it doesn't matter
if you can get it done or not.
Shut up! I got interrupted!
We, Pink Bee Squad, will lead the way!
into a big round of applause
with my own hands.
Oh well, finish it up later.
What do you mean?
Let's go!
How dare you shoot Tra-guy!
I mean he wasn't that serious
about the assassination.
There's another order from Doffy.
He's different from the others!
His swordplay is faster and deadlier!
We're gonna go at high speed!
He doesn't want you to follow him about
Guard the Toy House with
Lao G. and the others.
I'm gonna show the audience
a picture of your pretty face...
so he told me to finish you off here.
It's urgent!
Straw Hat.
Wait a second, Diamante!
I can just finish him off first!
That's Young Master-sama's order.
...after slicing it off!
It's none of your damn business.
No way...
Knock it off!
Can't you follow Doffy's order?!
Will Suleiman be the one
who finishes off Rebecca?!
Law was originally my subordinate.
I shouldn't have told you that!
Clank.
Responsibility for dealing with him
falls to me!
Oh no! Sorry!
Kin, retrieve Tra-guy!
You've got to be kidding!
I got it!
"Another order"?
No more...
--It's finally starting.
--Yeah!
Vice Admiral-dono,
Pirate Hunter is in action!
That means...
...chitchatting.
...I've really been...
But this passage to the trade port is too...
Should we catch him?
Screw them...
Uh-huh, all right.
Hold on a minute!
Prepare to die!
...narrow!
Hey! Talk to us! What's going on?!
Screw you!
Robiland and I can barely fit in.
Law-dono's got shot in front of us!
ON THE IRON BRIDGE CLOSE TO DRESSROSA
What about me, then?
Get out of my way!
Fraland, why don't you take off your shoulders and arms?
By Doflamingo!
What?!
Room!
Did you just hear that?
I'm gonna kick the life out of Bellamy!
Okay, let me take them off... I can't!
Pirate Hunter and Foxfire Kin'emon, huh?
Go away!
Hey, me-land can't go in there!
No.
I saw a child who looked like
Momonosuke on the ship earlier!
Wh-What the...
I'm not gonna lower the barrier!
What's the matter, Law?
We weren't expecting big humans to use it when we made it.
Agilia has come to the defense of Rebecca!
You just got called, didn't you?!
Just go already!
I thought that you wanted to kill me!
Don't listen to him!
We won't let him take Momo away!
Agilia-san!
Room!
You have to enter from the Toy House!
Get out of my way, bitch!
Of course!
Damn your barrier shit!
Takt!
Is she trying to let her partner get away?!
The Toy House is
This is not over, you fools!
located at the base of the plateau that the palace is on.
I won't let you guys walk away
alive from Dressrosa!
That's where the toys go back every night.
The crowd is now jeering loudly at Agilia!
Just beat it, stupid brat!
Humans aren't allowed to go in.
You call it a "house" because the toys live?
That was certainly Diamante
on the Snail.
He is...
No, they just call it a "house."
There are no beds to sleep in, or anything.
Scalpel!
So was it really his order?
Excuse me.
Did Doflamingo really tell him to...
Inside, there is only a passage into the ground.
...kill me?
A passage?
Every night, the toys go down underground
You'll promote me to executive of the Family
if I win the competition?!
Agilia-san!
through the passage and work all night.
Law, that fool!
He looks exhausted!
What?!
Old man, you're so strong!
Who are you?
Yeah.
Doesn't that mean the toys in the town
are always exhausted?
You...
You can't get away from me, brat!
You can do it.
I should not tell you that
for the sake of both of us.
...must move to the finals...
I'm counting on you.
Yes, indeed.
As are, the Tontatta people...
Room!
I will win!
...at any cost!
...who are forced to work!
Shambles!
What the hell?!
Okay?
I can't believe it! It's horrible!
The power of the Op-Op Fruit, huh?
How annoying.
What's this heaviness?!
Let me take you to the medical room.
A-Anyway, through that place,
But if I'm correct,
your power has a limit, doesn't it?
Uh-huh!
Fraland can go down to the SMILE factory, right?
Mind your own business!
How can he create this much force?!
I've lost my reason to live!
Yes. There are four entrances in four directions.
You've dealt with the meteorite that Fujitora
brought down and fought me once
and then rescued Black Foot.
Why do you wanna save me
in the first place?!
However, all the entrances are tightly guarded!
I will behead you!
I wonder how much longer it'll last.
In the battle royal earlier,
It's more exciting that way!
Zoro!!
I was there in the ring
determined to kill you all!
If I have to go there anyway,
Zoro-dono?!
I'll create havoc!
What happened to Zoro, Kin'emon?!
Bullet String!
I know!
--What?
--Wh-Why do you wanna do that?
Suleiman the beheader is pressing Rebecca!
Zoro-dono has just vanished...
But when two men fight in the same ring,
they become war brothers!
--Because it's better for you.
--What do you mean?
While I'm drawing their attention,
finish your business with Sugar.
I wonder if Tra-guy is okay.
And I'll never walk out on my brother!
Kin'emon!
I'm coming!
Luffy-dono!
Room!
What's wrong?
Zoro-dono is gone.
Oh yeah... It's Sea Prism Stone...
Room!
He was with us a few moments ago.
DRESSROSA - THE FLOWER FIELD
Kin'emon-san?! Are you okay?!
So I've filled you in on the
history of this country.
I can't believe him!
We didn't make a turn or anything!
Oh no, don't tell me you're dead!
What are you gonna do now, Law?
Now, the plan to save those
UNDER THE GROUND -
THE KING RIKU ARMY HEADQUARTERS
Should we go look for him?
poor people from the darkness,
We don't have that much time!
Hm? Who is that?
I call it...
Dressrosa is right there.
Let's just go!
Swim briefs?!
..."Operation Dressrosa SOP"!
What's wrong with his head?!
--He's gonna catch up with us at some point.
--I guess.
--Is it a weapon?
--Or is he just an idiot?
"SOP"?
What does it stand for?
Oh! He's got two dimples on his chin!
There is a vast underground world
beneath this country that nobody knows.
Vice Admiral-dono!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
He can launch a sword attack from
a distance? That's dangerous.
There's no mistaking it!
He is Cyborg Franky of the Straw Hats!
Where am I?
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Down there is a trade port for a black market
and a mysterious factory...
Tell the civilians to evacuate
as far as possible from here!
Why did you make a turn
when the others didn't!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
--What?!
--You sure?!
Senor!
Yes, sir!
...where our friends of Tontatta and
What's that toy?
THE FACTORY AND THE TRADE PORT
the people who became toys
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
are forced to work 24/7.
Somebody's coming!
I can't believe the blind old
gambler was a Navy admiral!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Oh! So what does SOP stands for?!
A samurai-looking cat?
It's a samurai cat!
Oh, Senor! If you jam a tomato in your mouth  like that,
We'll sneak in there through
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
An admiral?!
Oh, it's a samurai cat!
an underground passage which
took us a year to dig,
it's gonna be messy around there!
Interesting!
Ring, ring, ring...
and rescue them all!
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Damn!
I see! Which means
The last thing I need now is annoying brats!
He is an admiral?!
Hey, Doffy.
there must be a deeper meaning to SOP, right?
Diamante.
You're a toy now!
I hear you, Kin'emon-san!
Oh, good! You're alive!
Don't cause any trouble with the Big Humans!
Franky, enough.
Then, we'll destroy all the facilities there
and bring down the Doflamingo Family
H-He's so...
Oh, sorry.
Are you in the middle of something?
Thank you for your help earlier.
I know!
No, it's okay. Go on.
You people were nice to me
so it feels like I'm repaying you
and take Dressrosa back for King Riku!
Oh, he has three swords!
...hard-boiled!
Violet betrayed us.
That is the goal of this operation!
They look so real!
Stop climbing all over me, you little tramps!
for kindness with ingratitude.
SENOR PINK - AN EXECUTIVE
THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY (THE DIAMANTE ARMY)
You make it sound so easy but...
Cool!
Life is full of ironies.
Don't touch my swords!
Of course, it won't go that smoothly!
Go hang out with younger guys!
Black Foot was here
so I thought something was wrong.
Don't be surprised!
No one can even predict what's
gonna happen in Dressrosa
Don't say that, Senor!
A-A cat punch!
A man who stands by Doflamingo is a...
Don't give me the cold shoulder, Senor!
We were gonna find out what the
10 or more minutes in the future.
...N...
Straw Hats were up to
with her Glare-Glare Fruit power
...Navy admiral!
I'm not into...
So there is one thing that
needs to be done first!
What?!
but we still don't know.
...fledglings.
What?!
Oh, don't worry about it.
This toy hit me!
A Navy admiral is there in Dressrosa?!
Oh! Senor!
Diamante.
One of Doflamingo's subordinates
turned us into toys.
Wh-What did he say?!
--Don't leave me, Senor!
--Senor!
Deploy Lao G. and others
at the entrance to the SMILE factory.
Maybe, Doflamingo has
the Navy on his side!
A toy hit a human?!
Senor!
Whoa-whoa, no way!
We have to knock out
this Hobby-Hobby Fruit eater!
That means there are hundreds of enemies!
Call the police!
They have to fight in the finals
and make the people happy.
Somebody, call the police!
Who is that pervert?
It's not a matter of the number!
--Hobby-Hobby Fruit?
You have no right to say that!
I'm sure you can handle it
by yourself.
You can imagine what will happen then.
Just one admiral is already a big problem to us!
Stop! Hey, you toy there!
This is the east entrance of the Toy House!
Oh! It will break the spell?!
Stop! You make it sound like
I'm some kind of genius.
The enemy's here!
I'll shoot you if you don't stop!
Only you can do it.
That's right!
You have to let me in!
Like I said, you make it sound like I'm...
All the toys in Dressrosa will change back into
their human forms at once!
Boy! I just patted his head a little!
Admit it. You are a genius.
Weapons Left!
Didn't I warn you?!
Okay, I'll do it if you insist!
But you...
And everybody will get their lost
memories back at the same time!
Oh no!
You really are a blockhead.
Clank!
S-Shoot him!
--Thank you very much!
--Wait!
Doflamingo... You bastard!
He's one of the Straw Hats -
Cyborg Franky!
We can't predict
what will happen after that!
Law.
While you're drawing my attention as a decoy,
Coup de...
Damn!
other members of the Straw Hats
are planning to destroy the factory.
...Vent!
How many people will fight together with us?
Even if you die here,
as long as the factory is destroyed,
What will people think and
what action will they take?
Luffy! Kin'emon!
Oh, Zoro!
Law-dono! Law-dono!
Kaido will kill me once
I lose all the SMILEs.
Zoro-dono!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Where are they going?!
What will Doflamingo do?
What will the Navy do?
Isn't it how your little scenario goes?
Are you okay?! Say something!
Oh! You have a Little Person there!
The only thing that's for sure is
the country will briefly destabilize!
But you can't buy time as you'd hoped
and the Straw Hats aren't doing so well.
I'm gonna guide you
to the entrance of the palace!
See?
Let's talk at the palace, Fujitora!
Where is the Hobby-Hobby Fruit eater now?!
Those idiots are causing trouble.
Who are you?
If you cooperate with me,
I'll let you catch those brats.
Is she your friend, Zoro-dono?
I thought it's the Navy's duty to
save countries affiliated
He or she must be strong, huh?
Well, she's kind of my friend or...
with the World Government.
I will listen to what you have to say,
Heavenly Demon.
You said you were just using them
According to Tontatta's scouting unit,
I'm Wicka, a member of the King
Riku Army's scouting unit!
but if you didn't trust them,
you couldn't plan something like that.
she's in the underground trade port now!
Then, I will decide what to do.
Excuse me for a while.
Anyway, let's hurry up!
I'm not gonna let them get away!
All civilians are evacuated!
The Don Quixote Family - the
Trebol Army - Special Officer...
How can you trust...
The operation is already underway!
...Straw Hat so much?!
Catch Roronoa Zoro!
They've started, huh?
...Sugar!
UNDERGROUND DRESSROSA - THE BLACK TRADE PORT
She is a girl
Because I know
the "D" will blow up a storm again!
They know who we are!
who can turn anything into
a toy merely by touching!
It seems like they do!
She looks like a child
but anyone who eats the
Let's run for now!
fruit stops aging from the
moment they ingest it!
What?!
They're attacking the Toy House.
Since she's the most important figure,
the top executive, Trebol,
is always guarding her!
Toy Soldier has gone already?!
I thought he's the commander!
Tra-guy!
Don't worry!
The Straw Hats are going
for the SMILE factory.
As soon as we've finished Operation SOP,
This is Kin'emon!
Law-dono has been abducted!
So if we can knock her out,
all the toys can change back?!
What?!
If they make it this far, then...
he'll carry out a major task -
killing Doflamingo while he's off-guard!
That's right!
Then?
We'll frighten her out of her wits
and make her pass out!
So he's heading for the palace
along with some Tontatta people!
Hey, Luffy! Look for the exit now!
Let's turn them all into toys, okay?
And that's Operation...
We're gonna wait for you
by running around here!
Good luck, Commander!
Sugar!
Oversurprised!
Uh-huh.
Yeah!
Panic!
Okay! We gotta hurry!
Tra-guy said something after being shot!
Nobody knows.
That's what Operation SOP stands for!
We have you, our hero - Usoland here!
Nobody knows your existence, right?
I'm sure he's alive!
Please take command of Operation SOP -
the plan to knock Sugar out!
What a great name for the operation!
It's Brook and the others!
What happened now?!
I guess.
If the enemy is just a girl,
follow me, you all!
W-W-We...
And what do you want, Zoro?
Whaaat?!
Sunny! What's wrong?!
You fool! Why didn't you tell me
there was this kinda competition?!
There they are!
Alright! I'm getting all fired up!
Damn! They've found us!
We have a problem!
Th-That's the most important part!
Sorry, sorry!
Franky Hair Salon!
You were having fun while I
was running around the town!
Combat Hair!
Hey, that's not what we're here for!
How could you let that old man beat you?!
What were you doing?!
Fraland!
--Usoland!
--You're so dependable!
I didn't get beaten!
That's right! Since you've got us...
THE UNDERGROUND PASSAGE
--Didn't you see my Gum-Gum Thor Elephant Gun?!
--That's... No mistake!
You're not gonna lose!
We're almost there at the trade port!
Take us to the underground passage,
little ones!
Big Mom's...
Vice Admiral Bastille!
That was the "Pirate Hunter" as I thought!
I feel bad.
The Usolanders!
...Pirate ship is here!!
You don't need to.
We're here now.
And the guy in the Colosseum is...
Helping our hero - Usoland is...
...probably Straw Hat Luffy!
All the bridges underground are movable.
Our Honor!
"SHARK SLICER" BASTILLE - A NAVY VICE ADMIRAL
So he was the winner of Block C, huh? Lucy?
Well...
And that building in the distance...
Commander! Fraland started wreaking havoc at the Toy House!
No wonder he was so strong-dara.
Okay!
As Smoker said, they are in this country.
...that looks like a sea anemone.
If I have to go there anyway,
I'll create havoc!
That's the Executive Tower
where our target Sugar is!
Should we catch them?
Meanwhile, Luffy is looking for the exit
in the Corrida Colosseum.
Is he gonna be okay?
No, leave them at large for now.
Don't worry! He's a super cyborg!
There are a bunch of
The Executive Tower, huh?
But I just received notice that four of the executives
infamous pirates, highly-skilled
bounty hunters and mercenaries...
I wonder if we can get there safely.
of the Family, are on guard of the Toy House!
Huh? Forget about the exit,
...from the New World
gathered in the Colosseum now-dara.
E-Executives?!
They're the formidable Diamante Army!
A group of fighters!
Oh no!
If we try to catch the Straw Hats
and make a scene,
where am I?!
Ship! Ship!
Hey, who is it?!
Are you goofing around?
So I will become
Luffy-senpai's henchman someday!
Are they... pretty strong?
they'll know that we're here-dara.
Their winning percentage in fighting events is 100%.
What is the ship of one of the Four Emperors
doing here?!
They've found us! We're finished!
We're gonna catch every one of these badasses
That's my dream.
Hey, you two!
Which ship do you belong to?!
What?!
as they come out of the Colosseum.
They're the big stars of the Colosseum!
Its figurehead is singing, isn't it?
Well, I'm just... a passer-by!
--Don't leave it open!
--Oh, this is the bathroom!
We wanna catch them
in one fell swoop-dara.
100%?
That means they've never lost!
Ship! Ship!
We don't allow anybody getting off a ship
except for the brokers!
Oh! Crest Head!
The ones that already got eliminated are
Don Chin Jao from Block C and...
Catch them!
That's right! Which means...
Glad to see you here!
--Inhel!
--Okay!
L-L-L-Luffy-senpai!
Sai? Boo? Abdullah?
Why did I write down these names
that I don't even know?
You sure?! Big Mom's ship?!
...nobody knows
how strong they really are!
Do you know any of these pirates?
We're gonna die!
Huh?! The fairies are here!
Hold on, Bartolomeo!
What's going on?!
Is Big Mom on board?!
What the hell are you talking about-dara?!
We've been robbed of all we have!
Do you wanna miss an opportunity
to talk to the King of the Pirates?!
They've messed around the New World!
They're very troublesome...
Tontatta Combat!
Tail Hammer!
--Luffy! Run with us while talking!
--Okay!
Oh, Bellamy!
Good! Formidable as he is, Franky is unaware
that Senor is coming from behind!
What were those names again-dara?
Oh, yes. Sai, Boo, and Abdullah.
I don't know!
Th-They've got wedged
into the ground!
But I see those two that we
met on the Fish-Man Island!
What?!
--Sai? Boo?
--Abdullah?
Here is your change of clothes,
Usoland, Robiland.
Who are they?
Damn! He's so dazzling -
I can't even look at him!
I can't believe how quickly you think!
I've never heard those names-dara.
Are you blind?
You drew their attention by acting scared!
Huh?! How did you emerge
from the ground like that?!
Luffy-senpai, did you get
to see Zoro-senpai?!
Oh? Who were we here to catch?
Mama! I see Caesar! Grr!
It was all your plan, wasn't it?
Strong Right!
Huh?!
In order for you two to sneak in,
Yes, I did! Thank you for that!
Ring, ring, ring...
They have him with them
as we thought-bon!
it's better to disguise
yourselves as the enemies!
My pleasure!
Is this how you use it?
Y-Yeah, sort of!
Let's sink their ship
and recover just Caesar-soir!
Now I gotta go somewhere
What are you doing?
Why did he show up in front of the enemy voluntarily?!
Sanji-dono told me to call
once we see Luffy-dono.
so I need to get out but
I can't find the exit.
By the way, are you all that strong?!
Senor!
There is no exit in this Colosseum.
Big Mom?! That's what I'm concerned about!
Yeah?
Oh yeah, Luffy!
Yes! We can manage that!
Luffy! You shouldn't have
picked a fight with her!
The Colosseum has been besieged
by the Navy.
What?
But Noland's family can even
Oh?
You're more wounded than before, aren't you?
Seems like they're here for Caesar!
take down Sea Kings so
you must be way stronger!
Caesar?!
You don't care?!
That was what we came here for!
Once a competitor
What do they want from him?!
OFF THE COAST OF DRESSROSA
steps into the Colosseum,
he can never get out!
Ring, ring, ring...
Why did I show up in front of the enemy?
Sanji! The Snail is ringing!
Everybody wants you, you mad scientist!
Must be Kin'emon.
It's no use looking for the exit!
--Really?! I'm gonna get it then!
--Oh no, you can't!
The only thing that a man does
behind someone's back is...
Did they come to rescue you, too?!
What?! What do you mean?!
Did you say "Never"?!
What kind of monster do they think I am?!
There's no exit?!
This is the Sunny.
Sanji? It's me!
However,
You're Doflamingo's subordinate, aren't you?!
Luffy!
maybe we can pull it off
without me fighting!
Alright, Chopper. Call
Usopp with the other one.
No!
Don't you know a way out?!
...undress a woman.
Okay!
Subordinate?
I couldn't even become his subordinate!
There!
All right, guys!
I, Usoland, am taking command now!
Ah, Senor! So hard-boiled!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Please help me!
I don't wanna get caught by Big Mom!
Our target is a girl!
Please! My friend is in danger!
--Clank.
--This is Usopp!
However,
a man stands in front of someone...
Let's go frighten her out of her wits!
Follow me!
Connected!
Because I...
Okay, now we have everybody
except Law on the line.
...only when he steals a kiss
from a woman.
...swindled research funds from them!
Yes, sir!
I'm gonna get out of here now.
This is Sanji on the Sunny.
Oh, I'm fainting...
I mean...
What?!
We have Nami-san, Chopper, Brook,
Momonosuke, and Caesar here.
If you follow me,
maybe you can get out, too.
Senor! You're the man!
You lead the way!
W-Well...
You guys are super stupid, aren't you? Huh?
Skip the details! They're gonna kill me
Tell me your situation.
Yeah? Thanks!
So are you gonna take me?!
Let's get to the Executive Tower!
once they catch me and confirm
that I've been fooling them!
This is Kin'emon.
I'm just saying if you choose to follow me,
Yeah!
I'm in front of the Colosseum
with Luffy-dono and Zoro-dono.
I don't care if you live or die!
you might be able to find
your way out by chance.
The Palace
The Toy House
The Trade Port
The Executive Tower
The Access Lift
The Factory
What kind of ability is that?!
Don't say that! Please!
Okay. What about you, Usopp?
You're not telling me
to betray my boss, are you?
Get in now! We have an
intruder at the Toy House!
This is Uso...
--This is Franky! I'm with Usopp and Robin!
--What are you doing?!
Because I can't betray Doflamingo!
We can't let anyone take
you anyway so shut up!
Listen, guys.
We are currently with...
How many key figures are there
in the Family, Leo?
I look up to him!
One of the Straw Hats is here!
...the King Riku Army, an anti-Doflamingo
coalition in this country.
Look! Look! Look!
10 executives currently lead 2000 subordinates
all over the country now.
Hey, a few moments ago,
you were...
He's fighting with Seor Pink-sama
at the east entrance!
Shut up!
--An army?
--Of Little People.
I've still got some principles
that I have to stick to!
He wants to get to the factory
on this floor!
Little People?
Okay! I'm gonna follow you!
And 3 top executives lead them,
Usoland, what are you doing?
They're gonna shoot at us!
Fraland!
This is a meeting for heroes only.
Don't listen!
If we take care of him,
they'll pay us a bonus!
But Luffy-senpai,
what about the Flare-Flare Fruit?
each with their own unique army.
--Really?! How much?!
--Well, we'll get a big reward for sure!
Yes, sir!
I wanna keep it out of
the hands of a few people
Excuse us!
but I don't have a choice!
My friend's gonna die!
First, the Trebol Army
THE TREBOL ARMY
(A TEAM OF MEMBERS WITH SPECIAL ABILITIES)
--Are you sure?!
--That's what they say!
Hey, Luffy, do you remember?
has members with special abilities.
Somebody, take the helm!
In that case, you can count on me!
Y-Y-Yes, I will!
We met the strange toy soldier
outside of the Colosseum.
Sugar!
Then, nothing's in writing yet!
Luffy-senpai! I was gonna
bring the precious keepsake
SUGAR
Uh-huh. Who are the Little People?
from Ace-sama to you once I
won it, from the beginning!
Violet!
VIOLET
He was actually
the commander of this army.
What?! I can have it?!
Giolla!
Of course! It belongs to you!
GIOLLA
Oh! The commander of the Little People?!
And all the people here are looking to...
Your accent is getting heavier
as you speak.
Damn! Why now?!
Next, the Diamante Army!
...take down Doflamingo this very day!
THE DIAMANTE ARMY (A GROUP OF FIGHTERS)
I promise you I will win
the Flare-Flare Fruit
A group of fighters!
We're rolling away from Dressrosa!
Huh? A soldier?
so you can go out without worry!
Lao G.!
He is willing to sacrifice his life
to destroy this kingdom!
Can you shake them off?!
LAO G.
Who are you talking to?
How do I know?!
Thanks! I appreciate it!
Machvise!
If nothing is done,
MACHVISE
Oh, that's it! The "Toy Soldier"!
Just pray!
we'll just keep going back and forth
between the Toy House and underground!
Rebecca wants to stop him!
Senor Pink!
SENOR PINK
Let's take over the lift!
--Franky, stop the army!
--No way!
You all stay here!
Dellinger!
DELLINGER
I was thinking the exact opposite!
Have you talked to that girl Rebecca?!
Freeze! I'm taking over this lift!
The last one is the Pica Army!
Uh-huh! She is a really nice girl!
THE PICA ARMY (A COMMANDO UNIT)
A commando unit!
He's the Lightning Soldier of the Colosseum!
How did he get here?!
--Brook! Keep trying!
--Yes, I'll keep trying!
She didn't have much money
but she bought me three lunch boxes!
Despite that, once she entered in the ring,
the audience jeered at her!
Gladius!
GLADIUS
Missed it!
You're too slow!
You okay, Sanji?!
Buffalo! Baby 5!
I couldn't agree more.
You bastard!
BUFFALO
BABY 5
I won't let you have the Flare-Flare Fruit.
But hey, don't bring the Emperor here!
Too slow!
It'll throw the whole country out of control
We've seen Buffalo and Baby 5!
Luffy, I...
"Straw Hat Luffy"!
and mess up the plan of Toy
Soldier and the others!
Too slow!
I can't follow Tra-guy's plan!
Soldier-san, you hit me!
That's domestic violence!
Who the hell are you?!
Hey, hey, hey! Where you from?!
Come to think of it,
why is Caesar on the Sunny?!
What're you saying, Franky?!
It's not domestic violence!
I don't want to hit you!
You can't talk to Luffy-senpai so casually!
This is how I remember his plan.
We know there are two others overseas.
He is the legendary pirate
"Fire Fist" Ace-sama's brother
Then stop yourself before you connect!
After destroying the SMILE factory,
VERGO - A TOP EXECUTIVE
The deal fell apart!
You need a sense of crisis
to improve yourself!
A top executive - Vergo!
we'll keep Doflamingo alive and
use him to take down Kaido.
If not, why would Tra-guy
have to go through it?!
and he will become the King of
the Pirates one day, you idiot!
You need to focus, Rebecca!
And an executive - Monet!
MONET - AN EXECUTIVE
But then,
Stop!
I've known that from way back.
Our target is Sugar, right?
what's gonna happen to these people
Law told us to take Caesar
to the next island!
Humans' instincts are much better than that!
who're looking to bring
down Doflamingo today?!
Of the team of members with special abilities?
We can't stop these Little People.
Uh-huh! That's right.
Let it all out!
Sanji-kun, I think we shouldn't
go back to Dressrosa!
It seems like everybody's happy at first
but this country has a very dark side.
Believe in your human power!
Then, we don't have to face the group of fighters!
Good luck, Franky!
Soldier-san, you're a toy!
What's your problem?!
I know you want to join them
and rescue Tra-guy
They're...
But they're all pretty strong!
You can't just appear and say
you won't let me have the fruit!
Stop whining!
...getting ready to fight a deadly battle
to get rid of that dark side!
What?!
and help the Little People's army
win the fight.
Give me a break!
Focus! Rebecca!
I'm not saying this because I'm scared!
They're pretty small
but they have big balls!
Bring out your human instincts!
Luffy, listen!
This brave, little army is going to challenge
There are three things that we and
Doflamingo are scrambling for!
their filthy, monstrous enemy!
Believe in your human power!
Caesar.
What's wrong with that guy?!
The SMILE factory.
I can't...
He's talking to Luffy-senpai
in such a cheeky manner!
And Momonosuke for whatever reason.
...let them down!
See? Luffy-senpai's mad!
Meadows is defeated!
I don't wanna learn to fight anymore!
We haven't destroyed the factory yet
so it's still in his control.
Do you still think it's better for us
if Doflamingo wins the battle?!
Rebecca is taking down Block D's potential winners one by one!
Protect me to the end!
But we have the other two with us here!
She, and Agilia who is backing her up,
are really pissing off the crowd!
Luffy!
Because you promised me!
Tra-guy was sacrificing himself and fighting
No matter what you say...
Now, who's gonna knock out Rebecca?!
You promised that
you'd protect me with your life!
to let these two get away from Doflamingo.
Maybe, he also wanted to buy time
for destroying the factory.
You said,
until the day I'm filled with happiness,
I'm gonna fight with them!
Oh?! Can he stop her?!
Suleiman the Beheader!
Y-You are...
Franky...
you'll always be by my side!
It's been a while!
Or are we gonna see Rebecca's Back-to-the-Water Dance again?!
Soldier-san's gonna die.
I'm a toy.
He went that far to save these two.
Rain and wind will rust my body!
Franky!
So if we go back and make it easier
for Doflamingo to catch them,
You're free to go all out!
We'll be there as soon as possible!
all his efforts will be ruined!
I don't know how long my body's gonna last!
Thanks!
Luffy!
All right.
Stand up, Rebecca!
Let's go back!
What?!
You're right. Okay!
Be strong!
I thought you were gonna say that!
Rebecca!
Whoa! He fended off
her Back-to-the-Water Dance!
We will take Tra-guy back at any cost!
THE PLAZA IN FRONT OF THE COLOSSEUM
What's that?!
What's happening there?!
My body is not made to fight!
You've finally made it out
so why are you crying?!
Issho-san, there is a big fight in the town!
What was the name of the next island?!
Maybe, toys are meant
to be broken after all...
It's Zou.
You can't find Pirate Hunter?!
We gotta hurry!
Here we are!
I told you not to let your
guard down repeatedly!
...before children become adults!
Sanji!
What's that? I heard something
loud from your side!
Call the Vice Admiral now!
Nami!
Damn you!
Yes, sir!
Chopper!
I'm sorry, Rebecca!
The Navy's totally believing
we're just toys in the town!
Brook!
Momo!
I'm sorry, Usoland!
You go ahead and sail for Zou!
Just barely!
You've chosen weird animals!
Since your father is clumsy,
--Thank you.
--No, no, no.
all he can do is
to teach you to become strong!
We're here! This is the underground world
If you say so... Roger that, Captain!
I thought these animals were kewl!
Especially, carps?
where the trade port and the factory are.
I didn't know he was this strong!
But how about giving us permission!
Why're you doing this?!
You're just a toy, what do you want?!
Permission?
Yeah?
--What's going on?! The town is...
--It's coming this way!
Stop crying already!
Don't you wanna save Tra-guy?!
Yes. Permission to...
It's kind of noisy here.
I want a peaceful country where...
I'll save Tra-guy!
And I'll kick Mingo's ass!
...launch a counterattack
against Big Mom's ship!
...my child can live happily!
What the hell?! I can't see a thing!
What's going on?!
Plus, the Flare-Flare Fruit is in good hands!
I will take Dressrosa back
for the King Riku Family!
What the...
Yeah, you got it.
In good hands?
Vice Admiral Bastille! Is that...
What?!
--What?!
--King Riku?!
Let's go-dara!
We're gonna head for the palace!
No!
What the hell are you talking about?!
I'm gonna leave the other task up to you!
Yes, I got it!
I already picked a fight with her!
I will sacrifice myself for that!
Wait for me, Doflamingo!
You're right!
--It's too dangerous!
--Please don't!
I'll take you down even if it means death!
I heard Robin-san's here
in this country, too.
I hope I can see her after such a long time.
All right, guys!
We'll be waiting for you at Zou!
Is it from above ground?
What's going on here-dara?
Okay!
Hey, who dropped the box?!
KOALA - AN ASSISTANT MASTER OF FISH-MAN KARATE
THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
Count on us to destroy the factory!
I'm glad that you got to see him.
A toy's been buried under it.
Yeah... I thought he was gonna punch me.
I-I'm sorry!
I'll keep working,
just let me see my family!
Idiot! Those who can't meet their quota will get scrapped!
All of you, be safe!
Are you crying?
Roger that!
I don't cry!
Take him!
Roger that!
W-Wait! I can still work!
If you were there, do you think...
Help!
Tra-guy's life...
...you could've changed something?
Wh-What just happened?!
Usopp.
Nobody knows.
Rebecca's wish...
Robin, I just...
That was fast.
Yeah.
What was that?!
I couldn't see anything!
Look.
Doflamingo!
Tra-guy!
I heard about it but...
--Let me know when you find
out about the underground.
I-I can't believe this!
Everybody's collapsed!
He holds the key to all of that!
Stupid brat!
Okay.
Hey, Tra-guy! Why are you with Doflamingo...
In any case,
I will win Ace's Flare-Flare Fruit!
The surviving top contenders
of Block D have gone down
We're gonna head for the palace!
What are you doing?!
one after another!
And...
...beat the hell out of Doflamingo!
If you don't like it, the deal is off!
And no one's left standing!
You jerk! You're taking advantage of my weakness!
Is this for real?!
If only Joker weren't on your side...
It all happened in a blink of an eye,
in the Block D match!
You've pushed it too far!
We will inherit his will!
I-I never imagined he'd be alive!
Who are you talking about?!
I-I thought...
...he died...
Oh, wait!
...he died at that moment!
Somebody is about to stand up!
THE STRAW HATS ARE BACK
Cora-san...
What the hell is this?!
It's a massive port town!
Tra-guy!!