Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
koukishin ni makasete
Go along with your curiosity
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
kokoro no chizu hirogete
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition
- in which a winner will get the
Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize
- and won the first round.
but now, he's heading for the palace
to take back Law
who's been captured by Doflamingo.
I-I never imagined he'd be alive!
I'm asking you! Who is that person?!
M-My brother!
Ace was right!
We were always bonded together as brothers!
"A Burning Passion!
Rebecca vs. Suleiman!"
Suleiman keeps attacking Rebecca!
He even fended off her
Back-to-the-Water Dance!
Rebecca's struggling!
--Go!
--Go to hell, Rebecca!
Suleiman, chop her head off!
He was once a hero in the Dias Naval Battle
but after being exiled from
his country as a war criminal,
he became a grim reaper
walking on the dark side of the world!
SULEIMAN THE BEHEADER
A CLASS-A WAR CRIMINAL FROM THE DIAS NAVAL BATTLE
He has the lifeless bearing of a ghost!
I did everything for my country.
I used to love my country.
What about you?
--Part of that evil family!
--Drop dead, Rebecca!
When people hate you so,
it must be hard for you
to even breathe in this country.
I don't care how hard it is.
I don't mind being hated!
I just want to...
I just want to live together
with Soldier-san!
Rebecca!
She just won't give up!
Including the beautiful...
...I mean, hateful Rebecca,
there are only about 30 contenders left
in Block D!
One more person,
I mean, animal down!
ORLUMBUS - AN ADVENTURER
(AN ADMIRAL OF THE YONTA MARIA GRAND FLEET)
He defeated dozens of people
and let blood run on the ring
but now, the fighting lion Agyo has...
...been beaten by Orlumbus's whip!
--How strong!
--Admiral!
CAVENDISH - A PIRATE
Will one of the favorites win as expected?!
Or some dark horse?!
DAMASK - AN ARSONIST
MUMMY - A SORCERER
Only one winner can move to the finals!
The life of King Riku's granddaughter...
Who's gonna take it?!
Soldier-san, where are you now?
Don't die!
That's all I ask!
--Go to hell, Rebecca!
--Chop her up already!
Screw you, Rebecca!
It's gonna be fun
to turn those hisses and boos...
…into a big round of applause
with my own hands.
He's different from the others!
His swordplay is faster and deadlier!
I'm gonna show the audience
a picture of your pretty face...
...after slicing it off!
Will Suleiman be the one
who finishes off Rebecca?!
Wh-What the...
Agilia has come to the defense of Rebecca!
Agilia-san!
Get out of my way, bitch!
Is she trying to let her partner get away?!
The crowd is now jeering loudly at Agilia!
Agilia-san!
You...
...must move to the finals...
...at any cost!
Okay?
Uh-huh!
I will behead you!
Suleiman the beheader is pressing Rebecca!
I wonder if Tra-guy is okay.
Luffy-dono!
What's wrong?
Zoro-dono is gone.
He was with us a few moments ago.
I can't believe him!
We didn't make a turn or anything!
Should we go look for him?
We don't have that much time!
Let's just go!
--He's gonna catch up with us at some point.
--I guess.
Where am I?
Why did you make a turn
when the others didn't!
What's that toy?
Somebody's coming!
A samurai-looking cat?
It's a samurai cat!
Oh, it's a samurai cat!
Interesting!
Damn!
The last thing I need now is annoying brats!
You're a toy now!
Don't cause any trouble with the Big Humans!
I know!
Oh, he has three swords!
They look so real!
Cool!
Don't touch my swords!
A-A cat punch!
This toy hit me!
Wh-What did he say?!
A toy hit a human?!
Call the police!
Somebody, call the police!
Stop! Hey, you toy there!
I'll shoot you if you don't stop!
Boy! I just patted his head a little!
Didn't I warn you?!
But you...
You really are a blockhead.
--Thank you very much!
--Wait!
Damn!
Luffy! Kin'emon!
Oh, Zoro!
Zoro-dono!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Oh! You have a Little Person there!
I'm gonna guide you
to the entrance of the palace!
Who are you?
Is she your friend, Zoro-dono?
Well, she's kind of my friend or...
I'm Wicka, a member of the King
Riku Army's scouting unit!
Anyway, let's hurry up!
The operation is already underway!
UNDERGROUND DRESSROSA - THE BLACK TRADE PORT
What?!
Toy Soldier has gone already?!
I thought he's the commander!
As soon as we've finished Operation SOP,
he'll carry out a major task -
killing Doflamingo while he's off-guard!
So he's heading for the palace
along with some Tontatta people!
Good luck, Commander!
Yeah!
We have you, our hero - Usoland here!
Please take command of Operation SOP -
the plan to knock Sugar out!
Whaaat?!
Th-That's the most important part!
We're here now.
All the bridges underground are movable.
And that building in the distance...
...that looks like a sea anemone.
That's the Executive Tower
where our target Sugar is!
The Executive Tower, huh?
I wonder if we can get there safely.
Oh no!
Hey, who is it?!
Are you goofing around?
They've found us! We're finished!
Hey, you two!
Which ship do you belong to?!
Well, I'm just... a passer-by!
We don't allow anybody getting off a ship
except for the brokers!
--Inhel!
--Okay!
Huh?! The fairies are here!
We've been robbed of all we have!
Tontatta Combat!
Tail Hammer!
Th-They've got wedged
into the ground!
Here is your change of clothes,
Usoland, Robiland.
I can't believe how quickly you think!
You drew their attention by acting scared!
It was all your plan, wasn't it?
In order for you two to sneak in,
it's better to disguise
yourselves as the enemies!
Y-Yeah, sort of!
By the way, are you all that strong?!
Yes! We can manage that!
But Noland's family can even
take down Sea Kings so
you must be way stronger!
What kind of monster do they think I am?!
However,
maybe we can pull it off
without me fighting!
All right, guys!
I, Usoland, am taking command now!
Our target is a girl!
Let's go frighten her out of her wits!
Follow me!
Yes, sir!
I mean...
You lead the way!
Let's get to the Executive Tower!
Yeah!
The Palace
The Toy House
The Trade Port
The Executive Tower
The Access Lift
The Factory
Get in now! We have an
intruder at the Toy House!
One of the Straw Hats is here!
He's fighting with Señor Pink-sama
at the east entrance!
He wants to get to the factory
on this floor!
Fraland!
If we take care of him,
they'll pay us a bonus!
--Really?! How much?!
--Well, we'll get a big reward for sure!
--Are you sure?!
--That's what they say!
Then, nothing's in writing yet!
If nothing is done,
we'll just keep going back and forth
between the Toy House and underground!
Let's take over the lift!
You all stay here!
Freeze! I'm taking over this lift!
He's the Lightning Soldier of the Colosseum!
How did he get here?!
Missed it!
You're too slow!
You bastard!
Too slow!
Soldier-san, you hit me!
That's domestic violence!
It's not domestic violence!
I don't want to hit you!
Then stop yourself before you connect!
You need a sense of crisis
to improve yourself!
You need to focus, Rebecca!
Humans' instincts are much better than that!
Let it all out!
Believe in your human power!
Soldier-san, you're a toy!
Stop whining!
Focus! Rebecca!
Bring out your human instincts!
Believe in your human power!
I don't wanna learn to fight anymore!
Protect me to the end!
Because you promised me!
You promised that
you'd protect me with your life!
You said,
until the day I'm filled with happiness,
you'll always be by my side!
I'm a toy.
Rain and wind will rust my body!
I don't know how long my body's gonna last!
Stand up, Rebecca!
Be strong!
My body is not made to fight!
Maybe, toys are meant
to be broken after all...
...before children become adults!
Damn you!
I'm sorry, Rebecca!
Since your father is clumsy,
all he can do is
to teach you to become strong!
I didn't know he was this strong!
Why're you doing this?!
You're just a toy, what do you want?!
I want a peaceful country where...
...my child can live happily!
I will take Dressrosa back
for the King Riku Family!
--What?!
--King Riku?!
What the hell are you talking about?!
I will sacrifice myself for that!
Wh-What just happened?!
That was fast.
What was that?!
I couldn't see anything!
I heard about it but...
I-I can't believe this!
Everybody's collapsed!
The surviving top contenders
of Block D have gone down
one after another!
And no one's left standing!
Is this for real?!
It all happened in a blink of an eye,
in the Block D match!
Oh, wait!
Somebody is about to stand up!