Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition
- in which a winner will get the
Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize
- and won the first round.
but now, he's heading for the palace
to take back Law
Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize
- and won the first round.
but now, he's heading for the palace
to take back Law
who's been captured by Doflamingo.
Meanwhile, at the Colosseum,
Meanwhile, in the last battle of
the first round - Block D match...
Meanwhile, underground Dressrosa,
the final round of the competition is about to start.
Meanwhile, at the Colosseum,
Usopp and the others started the
operation to take down Doflamingo!
the final round of the competition is about to start.
I know your background.
He's acting strange!
My background?
All right! The final round starts soon!
Who is that? He's not the Lucy that I knew.
Tail Hammer!
It's gonna get a little messy, maybe,
but I won't do you wrong.
This is the Rampart Tower B-2 -
in front of the main dining hall!
It's going to be a battle royal of the five
including Diamante the hero!
He fell asleep?!
It's no mistake!
One of the intruders is Straw Hat Luffy!
Maybe we can pull it off
without me fighting!
A scramble for the Devil Fruit!
A death match involving the Fighting Fish!
Launcher!
All right, guys!
I, Usoland, am taking command now!
Which one of them will win
the Flare-Flare Fruit?!
And Pirate Hunter Zoro!
Cyborg Franky of the Straw Hats!
And... V-Violet-sama!
Our target is a girl!
Everybody! We're going to
make a full-scale charge now!
Let's go frighten her out of her wits!
Follow me!
The Navy is putting the Toy House
under complete siege!
Th-There is one more person!
Capture or scrap
Cyborg Franky of the Straw Hats-dara!
Yes, sir!
Huh?! Why is the Navy doing that?!
I mean...
Lucy is showing it off!
What?
Somebody, tell me what's going on-in!
You lead the way!
Let's see how much the Navy can do.
I'm just a newcomer
picked through the World Military Draft
I'm not gonna run or hide! So...
Let's get to the Executive Tower!
Straw Hat Luffy has snuck in?
but since being appointed as a Navy admiral,
there is something I want to do.
Yeah!
Let's have a big party, Navy!
Freeze! I'm taking over this lift!
What is it?
Then, who is the guy
fighting at the Colosseum?!
She loves grapes - she's always eating them.
It is nothing less than...
Too slow!
...the complete abolition of
the Seven Warlord system!
--So what?
--We're gonna use that against her.
H-He's a sleepwalker?!
What the hell is going on?!
I don't wanna learn to fight anymore!
Yes-dara.
Take a look at this!
Hakuba is, indeed,
This is a clump of Tatababasco Sauce,
the hottest spice in the world!
an alter-ego of Cavendish
that awakens while he is sleeping.
We'll raise the prize on you, Heavenly Demon.
"A Moving Castle!
The Top Executive Pica Rises Up!"
Protect me to the end!
We made it look like a grape.
I'm a toy.
Don't tell me you're gonna let her eat it?!
It sounded like you were suggesting
that I'd better kill you now.
Where's Mingo?!
Rain and wind will rust my body!
It's the finals next!
I'm gonna go and put this in to the basket!
I'm gonna go now!
Let's save all our friends!
Why're you doing this?!
You're just a toy, what do you want?!
--Alright!
--What?
Who are you?
You're Straw Hat Luffy, aren't you?
Okay, see you guys!
Shoot! Shoot!
Yes, I am!
I want a peaceful country where...
Guys! You're too loud!
--Hurry up, Luffy!
--Get in now, Ninja Woman!
Shut up!
I've been waiting for you.
I'll help you enter to the palace!
...my child can live happily!
We will take back King Riku's kingdom!
What?!
I will take Dressrosa back
for the King Riku Family!
Wh-What just happened?!
"The Admiral's Decision!
Fujitora vs. Doflamingo!"
"Dragon Claw Strikes!
Lucy's Intimidating Attack!"
I-I can't believe this!
Everybody's collapsed!
It's him!
THE UNDERGROUND TRADE PORT -
IN FRONT OF THE EXECUTIVE TOWER
The man who has risen to
prominence in this competition!
It all happened in a blink of an eye,
in the Block D match!
Now, we're moving on to the finals!
Here comes our favorite - Lucy!
Oh, wait!
Somebody is about to stand up!
But I have sad news!
Are you okay, small person?!
Watch over me, Ace!
The four executives who were
going to fight in the finals
"The End of the Match?!
A Surprising Result of Block D!"
Thank you!
With this world's hottest grape
made of Tatababasco Sauce,
had to withdraw from the competition.
Kin'emon, you take care of her!
What?!
"The Final Round Starts!
Diamante the Hero Shows Up!"
I'm gonna knock Sugar out!
What?
But I have to find the
place called the Toy House
Here I come, Sugar!
This is a very bizarre ending for a battle!
I was expecting to see
the hard-boiled Señor!
where my friend Kanjuro is held!
I've wanted to see Lao G.!
I want to go there, too,
to take part in Operation SOP!
I wonder what kind of guy he is,
the Executive of Doflamingo's clan!
What about Vise's "Da-in"?!
All 20-some surviving tough
fighters have suddenly
I've wanted to see Dellinger's "High Heel"!
You do?! I didn't know that!
I'm pretty sure he's strong.
been knocked out for an unknown reason!
This is the first time Lucy has
entered into these competitions! But...
But don't worry!
Zoro-dono, we're gonna go to
the Toy House together, then!
It's never happened before
in the long history of the Corrida Colosseum!
Believe or not, the hero of the Colosseum,
...his likable character
captured the crowd's heart!
Do as you like.
Mr. Diamante is...
Now, where is the Toy house?
Oh? The next contender coming in
--It's beneath this building. But...
--Oh, it's down below?
...going to fight in the finals
in a last-minute substitution!
is the man who antagonized the crowds!
--Maybe, go down those stairs first and...
--Stairs?!
But, in the center of the ring,
Diamante!
The captain of a pirate group, Barto Club,
Bartolomeo the Cannibal!
Diamante-sama!
we can see the shadow of someone
who is struggling to stand up!
Oh, now I know which way to go!
Get deep inside so you don't fall out again!
Is that the winner?!
--Take him to the medic room!
--Hurry up!
What? Oh, wait a sec...
Luffy-dono! Zoro-dono! Ninja Woman!
That person of the shadow has done all this?!
I'll take my leave!
What was that?!
Blasted a hole in the wall!
Excuse me!
Here he comes!
The captain of the first ship of
Emperor Blackbeard's group -
What was it?
THE ROYAL PALACE B-1 -
THE RAMPART TOWER
Straw Hat Luffy
Hey somebody, bring some bandages!
has gone up to B-1 of the Rampart Tower!
Jesus Burgess!
What?!
This is...
There was a fly.
Which way?!
To the left!
He shot down a fly?!
Thank you, Agilia-san!
The Flare-Flare Fruit will be ours!
But good luck to you, Straw Hat!
Unbelievable!
He shot down a fly behind him!
No one's here!
I'll get to you soon, Mingo!
Because of you, I...
Their security isn't keeping up with us!
Who else would blast a hole in the wall
just to kill a fly?!
R...
Rebecca?!
It means it was just a
casual attack for him?!
It's Rebecca who just stood to her feet!
Let's not do this, Leo!
It's not too late!
Oh! Lucy!
He's totally ready and willing!
Wh-What's this?
I'm moving on to...
Leo, we'll be counting on you!
Uh-huh! Leave it up to me!
Huh? Lucy?
The well-known warriors who we thought
We'll carry through
Operation SOP at any cost!
would dominate the Block D match,
No, he's not!
they're all still lying down on the ground!
Hey, lady!
Don't talk to him like he's your friend!
Even if he can shoot a fly,
he can't shoot me because...
The Corrida Colosseum Battle Tournament -
...I'm quicker!
the last winner moving to the finals is,
Oh! Now coming in to the sound of
the crowd's boos and jeers is...
You're Rebecca, aren't you?
unbelievably, a convict gladiator
and a granddaughter of King Riku,
So fast! I can't even see him!
Maybe, he can pull it off!
I know your background.
...the "Phantom Princess" of
the heinous King Riku Family!
Something is in the wall.
My background?
the blot in the history of Dressrosa!
Rebecca!
We'll take back our friends
who're being held captive!
Rebecca!
It's gonna get a little messy, maybe,
but I won't do you wrong.
Rebecca is... What should we say?
The devil incarnate, maybe?
--Go for it!
--Leo!
You can do it!
How did she survive the Block D battle
against such tough contenders?!
Please! Make it through!
A face?!
--Screw you!
--I know she cheated!
It's still a mystery!
What kind of trick did you use, Rebecca!
Go!
Check her body!
G-Gyats-san, are you alright?!
You're getting too excited!
Wait, Leo!
I need some water...
Robiland?!
They're just putting up a good front.
You did it! Rebecca!
There's another blood-thirsty
Fighting Fish jumping out!
I thought I was gonna die!
What happened?
This country is like...
A cloud of dust enveloped the ring
all of a sudden.
It's going for Burgess!
And now, these four competitors who
Maybe he was off guard!
He isn't moving!
Who cares?!
In any event, Rebecca has won!
won each block by beating so
many strong contenders are...
No, maybe he can't move!
...going to fight another battle in the
What the...
Is he gonna fall victim
to the Fighting Fish?!
final round to be a champion
of the Corrida Colosseum!
...the country we grew up in, in some ways.
I can't believe it!
What did she do to Cavendish-sama?!
A stone monster?!
It's going to start soon!
Oh no! It's Pica!
Admiral Orlumbus couldn't be
beaten by such a little tramp!
He's huge!
What's up with him?!
Be careful!
He's a top executive of the Family!
It was The Slicing Winds of Rommel!
This stone monster?!
Shockwave...
THE KING'S PLATEAU
He's Pica, eater of the Stone-Stone Fruit -
a stone assimilation human!
The Slicing Winds?
...Elbow!
That's right.
I bet you've never heard of it-dara.
It's great that you can help us
getting into the palace but...
A stone assimilation human?
He doesn't look like a human to me.
There was a mysterious incident
that took place in the Rommel Kingdom...
We've just heard that we
THE LIFT TO THE ENTRANCE OF THE ROYAL PALACE
need a pass to enter the lift.
Are you really a human?
Who is that? He's not the Lucy that I knew.
H-How powerful!
I have the pass.
Now, let me introduce the man
who is going to fight these four!
--Oh! Then...
--But you shouldn't take the lift.
I'm asking you a question!
Say something!
The whole Colosseum is shaking!
What? Why?
Can't you talk?!
He saved this country along with our king,
Don Quixote Doflamingo,
It does take you
to the entrance of the palace
They say winds that cut people
blew there every night.
and is one of the top
executives of the Family!
but if they find out who you are,
it's all over.
It blasted a massive hole
in the spectator area!
If we get it in the teeth,
we'll be crushed with one blow!
Like I said,
let's kick the guards' asses and bust in!
What a bizarre story-dara.
Burgess's terrific Shockwave Elbow!
He is also the promoter of
the Corrida Colosseum Battle Tournament,
They dispatched the Navy soldiers right away.
That wouldn't do anything!
They'll stop us at some point!
The upstart pirate - Blackbeard!
and our hero!
Huh?! Yeah, you're right.
Damn! We can't advance if nothing is done!
The Ten Titanic Captains are supporting him!
And one of them is...
There he is!
But the winds killed a lot of them, too.
And more importantly...
Mr. Diamante!
Uh-huh. What is it?
...Jesus Burgess!
I don't care
if you're a top executive or something!
--That bastard!
--Don't involve the audience!
You guys look too strange.
No, we don't!
I gotta go kick Mingo's ass!
The only thing they found
out at the end was...
Oh, now I remember!
You took our chef away earlier.
Get out of my way!
Gum-Gum...
How destructive!
...that the wind was actually a man
who called himself Hakuba-dara.
Sanji?!
...Jet Gatling!
Black Foot!
My sweet Violet-chan!
There's another Fighting Fish
charging towards the ring!
He took off to save your ship.
He is still at large.
We know what happened.
You told him that the Sunny was in trouble?
Even after he left the Rommel Kingdom,
That's...! Here it comes!
It's the "01" Fighting Fish
carrying the Devil Fruit!
Hakuba kept terrorizing
people in various towns.
You gave him the map to the Toy House
that he passed on to us?
Alright, I did it! Let's go!
Yes, I did.
There it is!
But wherever Hakuba appears,
Why did you have it?
this pirate is always there
at the same time-dara.
That was too easy.
I was Doflamingo's subordinate!
Is it going for Bartolomeo?!
What?
What?! You were?!
Oh no, it's made a turn!
She was just pretending
that she was obeying him!
Who is it going for?!
Oh my, oh my! The other Fighting Fish are
surfacing one after another!
He's back for more!
Wicka!
Now you know it's not that easy to take down
You remember me?!
Is it going to be all-out battle between
the top executives of the Family!
Did you forget about my ability?
the contenders in the ring and the Fighting Fish?!
He's not just a stone man.
I've been watching what you all are doing.
He can merge with stones.
Which means he's practically...
Along with the one-legged soldier
who raised Rebecca after my sister died,
These fish will never learn!
It's no use!
Charging at me?
You must be out of your mind!
...taking control of this whole stone palace!
you people were preparing to fight!
They've come all at once!
Then, we'll destroy all the facilities there
and bring down the Doflamingo Family
I've no business with you!
and take Dressrosa back for King Riku!
You can't get away from me!
You little bitch!
I've been watching it all!
N-Now, they're all there!
Thank you for believing in my father!
I told you! It's no use!
It's the final here in the Corrida Colosseum!
DIAMANTE - A TOP EXECUTIVE
THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY
The four winners from the first round
The walls!
Who is the "01" Fighting Fish targeting?!
Viola-sama!
Go away!
and Mr. Diamante!
Oh! It's going for Rebecca!
THE TOY HOUSE
The winner of this round will get...
...a Logia Devil Fruit,
the most powerful type!
THE TOY HOUSE
He's acting strange!
It is the survival of the fittest!
Strong Right!
The Flare-Flare Fruit!
It's the mechanism of the natural world
that the weak fall prey first!
He fell asleep?!
It must've set its sights on her
from the beginning!
It's mine!
Bring it on, Navy!
I've gotta cut the chain at least!
Da-in!
It's dangerous-in!
Ton-Ton!
Hey, hold your fire, Navy!
Don't start!
Yes! I've got you!
How could you intrude in the
territory of the Family like this?
You can't have it!
Take Rebecca out of the ring!
Redo the Block D match!
What the...
He wants a fight.
Now is our chance!
All of you, go get him!
Here we go! The battle
between Lucy and Diamante!
Whoa! We have some kind of problem!
Our target is Cyborg
Franky of the Straw Hats!
Straw Hat!
How annoying!
We won't accept
such a confusing result, Rebecca!
Move aside if you don't wanna get shot!
Franky...
I'm gonna fight you next!
We couldn't have been beaten
by a little tramp like you!
You can't tell me what to do,
you stupid Navy!
I'm gonna have the Flare-Flare Fruit!
...Rocket!
We're gonna to get it right!
I'm gonna bring you down
along with that fish!
What?!
Yeah! Kick her ass!
Burgess is gonna do it again!
--He's brushing his teeth!
--With two shoebrushes!
--Run!
--He's gonna do it again!
How smart of you to stand behind me!
Señor is an executive of
the Don Quixote Family!
Wait.
...Launcher!
He's so strong!
Hey! Get out of our way!
It doesn't matter if I'm strong or weak.
It's a matter of a man's pride.
Don't be such a poor losers! It's over!
--Run!
--That guy's dangerous!
He's not gonna try to get away? Lucy!
Even though nothing comes out of
the pistol on his head!
You tramps should stay out of it!
Don't ruin my event!
Shockwave...
Oh! Scold us more, Señor!
We want more!
What the hell?!
Now, charge into this!
Whether you're an executive or not,
if you stand against the Navy, we...
--Is this a bullfight?!
--Screw you!
Señor! Please run!
Lock.
Hide in the ground with your ability!
Don't brush your teeth
with a shoebrush now!
Don't shoot him!
What?!
Regarding the Navy's involvement,
No way!
Dragon Claw!
That's so hard-boiled!
Issho-san and Doflamingo have talked
Oh, Señor!
Stop brushing your molars!
and come to an agreement-dara.
Although it ripples, it's a steel cape.
H-He's a sleepwalker?!
It's not the time to clean your tongue!
Yes-dara.
I don't like it but
if the Young Master is okay with it...
Hakuba is, indeed,
I ate the Ripple-Ripple Fruit
and became a flag human!
Señor!
an alter-ego of Cavendish
that awakens while he is sleeping.
I can't believe it!
Oh, Señor!
I can make any material
Señor Pink!
flap in the wind like a flag,
even my body, just by my touch!
Because Hakuba committed a crime,
Señor!
Why are you relaxing?!
Cavendish had no choice but set out to the sea
Why didn't you use your ability
to get away?!
I was super bored.
and became a pirate-dara.
Lock.
Now, listen to my song. "The Pirate Blues"!
Hey, you're making a mistake, punks.
Poor guy.
Corrida Glaive!
Don't feel sorry for him!
Lucy!
No thanks!
He's enjoying the situation!
He'd take advantage of your sympathies!
Everybody!
Oh my, oh my! Burgess's armor
has shattered into pieces!
We're going to make a full-scale charge now!
My Swim-Swim Fruit power which allows me to
swim through the walls or
the ground as I like, is...
Capture or scrap Cyborg Franky
of the Straw Hats-dara!
Yes, sir!
He is a great swordsman.
O-Only he could done that!
My great senpai!
...not meant for getting away
from enemies.
But Hakuba is far stronger!
Yeah!
They're not gonna just give up
the Flare-Flare Fruit, huh?
I'm super ready anytime!
Having said that, he falls asleep
when his alter-ego appears
You'd better go back, guys!
His fighting style has changed.
Huh?
I swim...
--He's swimming...
--...In the ground?!
We have special kind of Fighting Fish in the water
just for the final.
Is that really Straw Hat?
and that nature wasn't suitable
for a battle royal, I guess.
...when I feel like swimming!
--Señor, you must be tired!
--Take a good rest!
They're all in another league!
--Rebecca can't be a winner!
--I'm sure she used a pistol or something!
I'm sweating a little bit.
He's such a rebel!
Check her out already and eliminate her!
Let's see how much the Navy can do.
Huh? B-Brandy?
It's impossible for you
to win that competition!
They love the smell of blood.
--Oh, he's got blood all over his body!
--He must have some bones broken...
You're gonna die!
So hard-boiled!
What should we do?
Have courage to fight!
What do you mean?
I didn't expect the Navy to cut in but...
Should we inspect Rebecca?
Is he cleansing himself with brandy?
That's not necessary!
--No!
--What?
...it's becoming like a party and I like it!
We always check her
more strictly than the regulations demand.
Señor! You've just taken a hit to your face
at the risk of your life because...
I've got to attack like I'm willing to kill!
Weapons Left!
Or I have no chance of winning!
Her equipment is the poorest
among all the competitors.
...you knew...
And...
...your helpless colleague was behind you!
In the Corrida Colosseum,
the winner is the winner no matter who it is.
...Franky...
Soldier-san, I am...
...Rocket Launcher!
Oh my stomach-in!
It's not our job to manipulate the facts
and spoil someone's victory!
--Señor! Please!
--My heart's gonna explode!
It's flying...
...going to do it!
She won without landing a single blow!
Don't hold back! Keep shooting!
That was a long time ago.
I don't dwell in the past.
That's one way to win a fight.
Make love to me, Señor!
Plus, she wasn't just lucky -
she was the only one
Hey Vise, are you alright?
I'm alright-in!
who fended off Hakuba's attack.
Ha! That fool.
What?!
He's facing that many soldiers alone
but he doesn't budge an inch.
He's so hard-boiled!
I couldn't see anything!
Only you my great senpai could see it!
Da-in!
I like his gutsiness.
Ton-Ton!
No matter who it is, though,
I can't let anybody have the Flare-Flare Fruit.
--Use the new cannon-dara!
--Yes, sir!
--That's our commander!
--Alright! We're taking control of the lift now!
What kind of cannon is that?
It sounds exciting!
I couldn't wait any longer!
I can finally fight now!
I guess you do have some fight in you.
Oh my stomach-in!
Fire!
Did you guys see that?!
How the Fighting Fish attacked?!
Huh?!
I've missed it again-in!
MACHVISE - AN EXECUTIVE
THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY (THE DIAMANTE ARMY)
Cyborg Franky is on fire!
You move like a rat!
What?! I know that voice!
We did it!
Shut up!
Super who the hell are you?!
They're so evil! They're
not gonna follow the rules!
You've hijacked the lift
and what are you gonna do now?
They'll attack fighters
while they're still in ring!
That's it!
It's the finals next!
Cyborg Franky of the Straw Hats!
I will take down Doflamingo
and restore the King Riku dynasty!
They're so savage!
They're not like
the Fighting Fish we had in the first round!
That's ridiculous!
They're the deadliest Fighting Fish
from different schools!
The Navy is putting the Toy House
under complete siege!
Huh?! Why is the Navy doing that?!
What? Somebody, tell me what's going on-in!
And one of them has...
Here comes more trouble.
...the prize of this competition, the Flare-Flare Fruit,
on its back!
Shoot-dara!
Yes, sir!
We did it!
Even his steel body can't
take that much heat!
I guess their target is just me!
LAO G
THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY
(THE DIAMANTE ARMY)
Screw it!
I'm gonna fight the Navy, too!
He's gonna get all melted up!
Strong Right!
I'm... dying...
The rules of the final round are simple!
The one who gets it
and remains standing in the ring
will be the champion!
Or not!
He's doing it again!
What?!
So cool! He's totally messing around with
that mechanical guy!
All right! The final round starts soon!
You think I'm that weak?!
Did you think you could kill me
with those crappy toys?!
Commander!
It's going to be a battle royal of the five
including Diamante the hero!
Señor! Just kick that geek's ass already!
THE ROYAL PALACE
You bastard!
Super!
A scramble for the Devil Fruit!
A death match involving the Fighting Fish!
Cub-san!
You poor girls don't get
how cool cyborgs are!
THE SUIT CHAMBER
Dammit!
The Navy is going at it.
What has just happened?!
Oops!
Which one of them will win
the Flare-Flare Fruit?!
I'm glad that you've made the
right decision, Fujitora.
What should I use this time?
You fools!
You couldn't see what happened?
Okay! Here we go!
Give me just about three seconds.
I'll tell you if you wanna know.
The battle is on!
It doesn't mean I'm taking your side.
Look how pretty my mechanical body is!
This?
No.
Not this one either.
Commander!
Besides the Straw Hats, there are
Huh? I don't get it at all!
What's so cool about that?!
You bastard!
other suspicious parties agitating in this country.
This is it after all!
Señor's look is
ten-thousand times prettier than that!
He's playing with us!
We have no choice!
I'm not gonna run or hide!
So...
Shut your mouth.
That's what happened.
The Navy must fight
to minimize civilian damage.
I didn't expect one of the Executives
to be in the lift!
Don't make fun of the way a man is,
you immature flappers.
Let's have a big party, Navy!
Shoot-dara!
When I was ordered to stand guard
at the entrance of the Toy House,
If the Straw Hat's goal is to kill you,
he'll cause mass destruction in doing it.
The way a man is?!
That's right.
This pacifier!
I happened to take the lift downwards and
Now, the final battle finally begins!
And this drool bib!
waited ready at the entrance
of the underground trade port
I'm not wearing them to attract you tramps.
Ready or not, this is it!
THE CURRENT LOCATION
If so, my sense of justice tells me
I have to prevent it!
but got on the lift again.
In other words, I...
Who is going to win the prize -
the Flare-Flare Fruit?!
...took the wron"g" lift!
This is my style and...
There's "G"!
...it represents the way I am!
I will take care of you after that!
None of them are making a move yet!
I won't let you reach the palace! Intruders!
THE UNDERGROUND TRADE PORT
USOPP AND THE OTHERS
Who is gonna take action first?!
Oh, I'm sorry!
I guess we were wrong!
What do you say?
I kind of like the way you are!
Oh! Burgess is going at it!
No!
We must get there!
THE RAMPART TOWER B-1
LUFFY'S GROUP
I'm just a newcomer
picked through the World Military Draft
Because I am a man, too.
What are you...
Toys are coming out of there
one after another!
but since being appointed as a Navy admiral,
there is something I want to do.
But...
It means Sugar is there in the
Executive Tower at this moment.
Oh?! Lucy has started running
on the outer circle of the ring!
What is it?
What is he up to?!
What are those tentacle-like things?
A-Are you guys okay?
You're my enemy.
It is nothing less than...
There's an exclusive lift for
the executives in the middle.
I've still got to take you down!
...the complete abolition of
the Seven Warlord system!
Yes, barely!
Hold on a sec! I'm gonna...
And those pipes stretching on all side
I thought so.
DRESSROSA ROYAL PALACE
s are for Big Humans and broken toys to fall.
Here it comes.
There are chutes to the junkyard
coming from everywhere in Dressrosa.
THE SUIT CHAMBER
Gum-Gum...
...Storm!
When someone gets dropped from there,
There was a pirate who attempted to
take over some kingdom in the past.
Did you just see that?
he'll fall to the junkyard beneath the Executive Tower.
Your granddaughter sure is lucky.
This is not the one.
If he had succeeded, that kingdom would've
become a shady country such as this one.
--He's such a pain!
--Let me do it!
Tsk! We don't need the
ones that don't have it!
I didn't expect you to enter the competition
along with her.
The Navy.
Help!
The Seven Warlords.
Don't even show your face!
Hey, King Riku.
Are you trying to lure the one
with the prize out, Straw Hat?!
The Four Emperors.
I can't believe a man who was once a king
fought for the Devil Fruit.
What do you think will happen to
the balance of power?
I guess you're quite desperate.
I don't know.
What?
Who can tell before we upset it?
Let me tell you something.
Damn! It's horrible!
First, it was the piles of trash - now what?
Rebecca!
What?
What?!
This one doesn't have it, either.
Where am I?!
If you keep up your reign of terror...
Anyway, the members of your family are
going too far today.
You're a pirate - Cavendish, aren't you?
What the hell is that?!
--Yes, I am...
--We're gonna have to examine you.
There was also Violet's betrayal.
How annoying!
Examine me?! I'm totally healthy...
It's too much to be a coincidence.
...we'll raise the prize on you,
Heavenly Demon.
Three-Sword Style - 108 Pound Phoenix!
Is it some kind of anniversary?
I know you're not aware of it.
It sounded like you were suggesting
that I'd better kill you now.
Gum-Gum...
The final is fun!
...Gatling!
What the hell?! What's going on?!
Of course, it is!
This is the Corrida Colosseum!
But what you did this morning...
Don't rush it.
It's no use hitting those walls!
Let's be nice to each
other for the time being.
I'm running this show!
About the report on Doflamingo's abdication
Every little tool here is
for entertaining the audience!
from the throne and the Seven Warlords
that spread all over the world...
What the hell is going on?!
And what is this slimy stuff?
You mean we're "tools," too?
I'm just saying I'm going
to save your country.
It was a mistake. Just a false report.
I thought it was strange when
they took me to the medic room
Well, just enjoy.
even though I wasn't injured!
No matter what kind of "fault" this country has
that'd be revealed,
When I learned that the slight hope was
just a hoax,
THE RAMPART TOWER B-2
KIN'EMON'S GROUP
It's not "slimy," it's "sticky"!
The stairs that we were going down...
I'm a blind man.
...suddenly bent upwards like
they're leading to the heavens!
What? Wow, you're too close!
Who the hell are you?!
it made me want to fight for everything
in this country again.
I won't see it so don't worry.
You're in the Executive Tower.
INSIDE THE EXECUTIVE TOWER
This year, we have the
World Conference - Reverie.
That was it.
But for some reason, new toys
Oh!
keep coming out of here.
Oh, that's good!
What are you talking about?!
I see. That was why you made a move.
This factory-like room has...
We were heading to the Toy House underground!
...a special name besides
the "Executive Tower."
But Viola was different.
We can't go any farther like this...
There will be some changes in the world
whether you like it or not.
Sugar, what's the other name?
Unlike you, she is a calculating tramp.
It's actually good we were stopped here!
It seems like nobody's here.
What do you mean?
She'll never act purely on her emotions.
To get to the Toy House below,
What?!
The Executive Tower.
Alright, we made it!
I'm sure she's weighing her options.
we have to go up to the palace first
You were a princess?!
No!
Wait!
and then take the lift downwards.
That's the only way!
There is this top rookie
who came to challenge me.
--Ouch!
--You're too loud!
Snot comes out! It's hanging!
You mean you were
a princess of Dressrosa?
Could you close the door?
We have to go up in order to go down?!
A Warlord,
Yuck. Drop dead.
No, I'm not gonna die!
Trafalgar Law!
TREBOL - A TOP EXECUTIVE OF THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY
(THE STICKY-STICKY FRUIT EATER)
It means we didn't have to split up
from Luffy and the others!
I'm not gonna listen to a brat like you!
I used to be.
Rebecca is the king's granddaughter
so you're...
--No, we didn't!
--Why didn't you tell me?!
Plus, there is someone who has
demonic blood in his veins
Hey, I'm stuck, kid!
I tried to tell you many times!
...her mother?!
Rebecca is my niece.
Do something about this sticky fluid...
and grabbed all the limelight two years ago.
--To go down...
--Stay inside!
IN FRONT OF THE RAMPART TOWER
BENEATH THE "ROYAL PALACE"
Is that the entrance to the palace?
Monkey D. Luffy.
You're my guide!
I wouldn't know what to do
if you fell out of there
What?
That bitch is wishing those two
allied pirates will defeat me!
No, it's the entrance of the Rampart Tower
which stands under the palace.
while I was unaware!
Here is the contract.
Under?
She's my sister Scarlet's daughter.
Do not harm any human.
You didn't listen to me!
Yes. To reach to the palace,
we still have to climb up.
You guys are all such blockheads,
jumping to conclusions!
But Law is barely alive now.
Follow any orders from the Family.
What?! No, no!
We shouldn't be fighting here!
Oh! Don't tell me it's...
And Straw Hat Luffy will never come
out of the Colosseum as a human.
What are you talking about?
The Rampart Tower also has a secret entrance.
A hidden door?
Hey! What happened to my body?!
Change me back...
Let's go.
We have to go back now!
I didn't know you were a ninja!
Don't let the guards see you.
Stop talking and just go work!
Wait! We have a problem!
And right now, as for the other
members of the Straw Hats,
This way, you don't have to take the lift
to the entrance.
If we make a scene, they'll call the
executives and then we'll be stuck.
Even if we can get to the lift in the palace,
the security is tight!
What?! I can't talk!
Cyborg Franky is attacking the Toy House
on his own.
Follow me.
Why am I doing as he says?!
Particularly, if the executive
named "Pica" finds us,
I'm sure I can get on but
since you're a Big Human...
Follow any orders from the Family.
all hopes of facing Doflamingo will be lost.
The contract?!
So what if they couldn't figure out
who I truly was?
Where's Luffy-dono?
Hey! Look!
Nobody remembers you now!
This is an emergency passage kept
secret by the King Riku Family.
I even forget who you were!
Not even Doflamingo knows it's here.
Gum-Gum...
But I don't think he can beat
the executives of my family.
Poof!
You're gonna work and fight for Doffy
for the rest of your life!
What the hell is that carp doing?!
The rest - Pirate Hunter Zoro,
Foxfire Kin'emon, Nico Robin,
What is this huge basket for?
Hey, what's going on?!
I've become a toy!
What?!
...Giant...
It's a pulley system to
lift heavy loads. Look.
If you walk out the door at
the very end, there is a port!
It's going all the way up there.
Whaaat?!
and Sniperking are still here.
--What's wrong with this carp?!
--Is it a blowfish?!
There is a staircase, too.
...Pistol!
But I don't think they can even reach
the underground level.
If you go up the stairs,
you'll reach the Rampart Tower
where the entrance to the palace is.
THE TOY HOUSE - FRANKY
Oh, you're a newcomer?
Let me take you to your position.
--Hello, sir!
--Oh! New recruits?
Where am I?!
That was easy!
Luffy! Why don't you take this boulder
and go to the top?
Yes, sir!
Why are you guys taking such a long time
to kill one guy-dara?
Keep moving!
Good for you! The job here is easy -
you just push around the toys!
This is it! Now, work!
Oh, that's a great idea.
Finally, the big fish is coming in?!
Oh yeah? That's good to know!
I'm a pirate!
Prepare yourself-dara!
If you can grab the chains and come down,
I don't know anything about this place
so can you teach me?
This must be a bad dream! I wanna wake up!
we can go up.
What?!
What the hell is he doing?!
AT THE FOOT OF THE "KING'S PLATEAU"
That's our Bastille-san!
Just carry it!
It's impossible!
Huh?! Why is the Navy here?
No! I don't wanna work!
Along with these creepy moving toys!
There is a lift up there!
I'm not gonna work here
for the rest of my life!
What's going on?
Don't tell me it's over.
LUFFY IN A CARP SUIT
ZORO IN A CAT SUIT
--Alright!
--What?
Super!
--It's open!
--That's not the issue here!
Okay, see you guys!
I can't believe it!
KIN'EMON IN A FROG SUIT
What?!
So this is where they export the weapons!
But I can't disobey them!
--Hurry up, Luffy!
--Get in now, Ninja Woman!
Are you a bubblehead?!
You can't take me down that easily!
We have no choice! Let's go in!
Listen, you all!
The Palace
Since it comes to this, it's faster this way!
The palace where Doflamingo
is and the Toy House
Wh-What?!
I can't do anything!
You're so persistent!
The Palace
The Toy House
Can I take this thing off?!
I can't believe there is
such a port underground!
and the trade port where the
SMILE factory are located -
Do as you like!
It's my turn!
The Palace
The Toy House
The Trade Port
Whoa-whoa!
I wish I could make a call!
The Corrida Colosseum Battle Tournament!
they are all connected.
I'm gonna pay you back double!
Prepare for it!
Koala is waiting for my call!
You mean, if we can get into the palace,
Is there any way I can move on my own will?!
The final!
we can go to the Toy House and the factory?
Take this!
I'm the king of Prodence!
Damn Doflamingo!
That's...
That's right!
Coup de Vent!
To go to the factory,
you have to pass through
Live as a toy for the rest of my life?
No way! Somebody, help!
either the palace or the Toy House.
This is the front entrance
of the Rampart Tower!
But my colleagues must've
snuck into the trade port
We can't leave it to the Navy as I thought.
Straw Hat Luffy has snuck into the tower!
through the secret passage that we dug.
Swift!
I've made it!
That's what I wanted to hear!
Can I do it?
We gotta go to the palace first!
Don't get so cocky!
All right. Understood.
What's your problem?!
But I still can't get over how
The Fighting Fish attacks!
But Lucy dodges easily!
That must be Trebol and Sugar.
there are such small people
even though I see one now.
Although he's just a robot,
She really looks like a kid.
Only he can move like that!
Yes, she does.
he is a pervert, just as you are.
Yeah, she looks like a toy!
How interesting!
She loves grapes - she's always eating them.
There were tons of them.
What is he talking about?
--So what?
--We're gonna use that against her.
Oh! Let me meet them later!
Be very careful.
We don't do this often!
Take a look at this!
What?
We only show ourselves
to the Big Humans of the royal family
This is a clump of Tatababasco Sauce,
the hottest spice in the world!
The whole nation is watching
as the special ring locks into place!
Oh, Señor! You're so hard-boiled!
Was it really him?!
We made it look like a grape.
Yes, it was!
He has broken the gate and...
but you Usolanders, aka the Straw Hats,
are the exception!
Don't tell me you're gonna let her eat it?!
But it can't be him!
When "Fire Fist" Ace died,
it was reproduced!
Usolanders?
Straw Hat is fighting at the Colosseum
under the name Lucy!
I'm gonna go and put this in to the basket!
I'll explain everything later!
Operation SOP is already underway!
It's a Logia, the most
powerful type of Devil Fruit!
We tested it on 50 people of our tribe and...
The Flare-Flare Fruit!
...all of them got knocked out
and 18 of them almost died!
Look! There it is!
Now, who's going to win it?!
Let's run away from the stone man!
The five contenders will enter
at any moment!
That's the lift to the
entrance of the palace!
This is the Rampart Tower B-2 -
in front of the main dining hall!
You tested it?!
We left nothing to chance!
I'm gonna make her eat it!
It's no mistake!
One of the intruders is Straw Hat Luffy!
Alright! Leo, go!
I'm gonna be watching you!
We can go that high with it?!
To enter the lift, we have to show a pass
to a security guard.
It's getting exciting.
That's so encouraging!
I gotta be able to get away
if something goes wrong.
And Pirate Hunter Zoro!
Alright!
Let's go, Marine Colosseo!
Let's just kick his ass!
And... V-Violet-sama!
No!
My name is Bartolomeo!
What did you call me?
Good luck, Leo!
If you do such a thing, it's gonna be messy
He's not gonna go down easily!
and we'll have to face more enemies!
You guys are too loud!
Th-There is one more person!
What's so bad about that?
We're trapped!
--Watch out for Trebol!
--Watch out!
You bubblehead!
Alright!
The first contender to enter is...
I'm not sure about these people.
Lucy is showing it off!
I said you are too loud!
In addition to the blockhead who gets lost easily,
I'm with a witless bubblehead!
I can do this!
You all have to get ready!
Who did you call a blockhead?!
Straw Hat Luffy has snuck in?
When you hear Sugar scream,
that's when all the toys in the country will
There is somebody there.
change back into their human forms!
They already know that we're here?!
It's him!
Luffy, take her and go on!
And at the same time,
everybody will get their lost memories back!
Then, who is the guy
fighting at the Colosseum?!
The man who has risen to
prominence in this competition!
Who are you?
Here comes our favorite - Lucy!
All his evildoing will be revealed
You're Straw Hat Luffy, aren't you?
Leave him up to me!
and the pirate - Doflamingo - will...
What the hell is going on?!
Yes, I am!
Shut up!
You go ahead and kick Doflamingo's ass!
...show his true color!
I've been waiting for you.
I'll help you enter to the palace!
I'm gonna go now!
Let's save all our friends!
Watch over me, Ace!
Guys! You're too loud!
What?!
We will take back King Riku's kingdom!
This stone guy…
Where are you, Mingo?!
…is gonna get cut!
I said...
...you're being too loud!