iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition
- in which a winner will get the
Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize
- and won the first round.
but now, he's heading for the palace
to take back Law
who's been captured by Doflamingo.
Meanwhile, in the last battle of
the first round - Block D match...
He's acting strange!
He fell asleep?!
H-He's a sleepwalker?!
Yes-dara.
Hakuba is, indeed,
an alter-ego of Cavendish
that awakens while he is sleeping.
It's the finals next!
Who are you?
You're Straw Hat Luffy, aren't you?
Yes, I am!
Shut up!
I've been waiting for you.
I'll help you enter to the palace!
"The Admiral's Decision!
Fujitora vs. Doflamingo!"
Now, we're moving on to the finals!
But I have sad news!
The four executives who were
going to fight in the finals
had to withdraw from the competition.
What?!
I was expecting to see
the hard-boiled Señor!
I've wanted to see Lao G.!
What about Vise's "Da-in"?!
I've wanted to see Dellinger's "High Heel"!
But don't worry!
Believe or not, the hero of the Colosseum,
Mr. Diamante is...
...going to fight in the finals
in a last-minute substitution!
Diamante!
Diamante-sama!
--Take him to the medic room!
--Hurry up!
Hey somebody, bring some bandages!
Thank you, Agilia-san!
Because of you, I...
Oh! Lucy!
I'm moving on to...
Huh? Lucy?
No, he's not!
Hey, lady!
Don't talk to him like he's your friend!
You're Rebecca, aren't you?
I know your background.
My background?
It's gonna get a little messy, maybe,
but I won't do you wrong.
They're just putting up a good front.
This country is like...
...the country we grew up in, in some ways.
THE KING'S PLATEAU
It's great that you can help us
getting into the palace but...
We've just heard that we
THE LIFT TO THE ENTRANCE OF THE ROYAL PALACE
need a pass to enter the lift.
I have the pass.
--Oh! Then...
--But you shouldn't take the lift.
What? Why?
It does take you
to the entrance of the palace
but if they find out who you are,
it's all over.
Like I said,
let's kick the guards' asses and bust in!
That wouldn't do anything!
They'll stop us at some point!
Huh?! Yeah, you're right.
And more importantly...
Uh-huh. What is it?
You guys look too strange.
No, we don't!
Oh, now I remember!
You took our chef away earlier.
Sanji?!
Black Foot!
My sweet Violet-chan!
He took off to save your ship.
We know what happened.
You told him that the Sunny was in trouble?
You gave him the map to the Toy House
that he passed on to us?
Yes, I did.
Why did you have it?
I was Doflamingo's subordinate!
What?! You were?!
She was just pretending
that she was obeying him!
Wicka!
You remember me?!
Did you forget about my ability?
I've been watching what you all are doing.
Along with the one-legged soldier
who raised Rebecca after my sister died,
you people were preparing to fight!
Then, we'll destroy all the facilities there
and bring down the Doflamingo Family
and take Dressrosa back for King Riku!
I've been watching it all!
Thank you for believing in my father!
Viola-sama!
THE TOY HOUSE
Strong Right!
Da-in!
Ton-Ton!
What the...
Now is our chance!
All of you, go get him!
How annoying!
Franky...
...Rocket!
Wait.
...Launcher!
--Run!
--That guy's dangerous!
Even though nothing comes out of
the pistol on his head!
Señor! Please run!
Hide in the ground with your ability!
Don't brush your teeth
with a shoebrush now!
What?!
No way!
That's so hard-boiled!
Oh, Señor!
Stop brushing your molars!
It's not the time to clean your tongue!
Señor!
I can't believe it!
Señor Pink!
Señor!
Why didn't you use your ability
to get away?!
Hey, you're making a mistake, punks.
My Swim-Swim Fruit power which allows me to
swim through the walls or
the ground as I like, is...
...not meant for getting away
from enemies.
I swim...
...when I feel like swimming!
He's such a rebel!
Huh? B-Brandy?
--Oh, he's got blood all over his body!
--He must have some bones broken...
Is he cleansing himself with brandy?
--No!
--What?
Señor! You've just taken a hit to your face
at the risk of your life because...
...you knew...
...your helpless colleague was behind you!
Oh my stomach-in!
--Señor! Please!
--My heart's gonna explode!
That was a long time ago.
I don't dwell in the past.
Make love to me, Señor!
Hey Vise, are you alright?
I'm alright-in!
He's so hard-boiled!
Da-in!
Ton-Ton!
Oh my stomach-in!
Huh?!
I've missed it again-in!
MACHVISE - AN EXECUTIVE
THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY (THE DIAMANTE ARMY)
You move like a rat!
Shut up!
Super who the hell are you?!
That's it!
Cyborg Franky of the Straw Hats!
The Navy is putting the Toy House
under complete siege!
Huh?! Why is the Navy doing that?!
What? Somebody, tell me what's going on-in!
Here comes more trouble.
Shoot-dara!
Yes, sir!
I guess their target is just me!
Screw it!
I'm gonna fight the Navy, too!
THE ROYAL PALACE
THE SUIT CHAMBER
The Navy is going at it.
I'm glad that you've made the
right decision, Fujitora.
It doesn't mean I'm taking your side.
Besides the Straw Hats, there are
other suspicious parties agitating in this country.
We have no choice!
The Navy must fight
to minimize civilian damage.
If the Straw Hat's goal is to kill you,
he'll cause mass destruction in doing it.
If so, my sense of justice tells me
I have to prevent it!
I will take care of you after that!
What do you say?
I'm just a newcomer
picked through the World Military Draft
but since being appointed as a Navy admiral,
there is something I want to do.
What is it?
It is nothing less than...
...the complete abolition of
the Seven Warlord system!
There was a pirate who attempted to
take over some kingdom in the past.
If he had succeeded, that kingdom would've
become a shady country such as this one.
The Navy.
The Seven Warlords.
The Four Emperors.
What do you think will happen to
the balance of power?
I don't know.
Who can tell before we upset it?
Let me tell you something.
What?
If you keep up your reign of terror...
...we'll raise the prize on you,
Heavenly Demon.
It sounded like you were suggesting
that I'd better kill you now.
Don't rush it.
Let's be nice to each
other for the time being.
I'm just saying I'm going
to save your country.
No matter what kind of "fault" this country has
that'd be revealed,
I'm a blind man.
I won't see it so don't worry.
This year, we have the
World Conference - Reverie.
There will be some changes in the world
whether you like it or not.
What?!
You were a princess?!
--Ouch!
--You're too loud!
You mean you were
a princess of Dressrosa?
I used to be.
Rebecca is the king's granddaughter
so you're...
...her mother?!
Rebecca is my niece.
She's my sister Scarlet's daughter.
Oh! Don't tell me it's...
A hidden door?
I didn't know you were a ninja!
This way, you don't have to take the lift
to the entrance.
Follow me.
This is an emergency passage kept
secret by the King Riku Family.
Not even Doflamingo knows it's here.
What is this huge basket for?
It's a pulley system to
lift heavy loads. Look.
It's going all the way up there.
There is a staircase, too.
If you go up the stairs,
you'll reach the Rampart Tower
where the entrance to the palace is.
Luffy! Why don't you take this boulder
and go to the top?
Oh, that's a great idea.
If you can grab the chains and come down,
we can go up.
It's impossible!
--Alright!
--What?
Okay, see you guys!
--Hurry up, Luffy!
--Get in now, Ninja Woman!
Wh-What?!
The Corrida Colosseum Battle Tournament!
The final!
I've made it!
The whole nation is watching
as the special ring locks into place!
When "Fire Fist" Ace died,
it was reproduced!
It's a Logia, the most
powerful type of Devil Fruit!
The Flare-Flare Fruit!
Now, who's going to win it?!
The five contenders will enter
at any moment!
It's getting exciting.
Alright!
Let's go, Marine Colosseo!
My name is Bartolomeo!
What did you call me?
Alright!
The first contender to enter is...
It's him!
The man who has risen to
prominence in this competition!
Here comes our favorite - Lucy!
Watch over me, Ace!