Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass, We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass, We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed everyday, Go east, Go west!
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed everyday, Go east, Go west!
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we want to do and doing them all
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the morning (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
sore nara isso taiyou sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel something - that's the treasure
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel something - that's the treasure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of burning, intense excitement!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of burning, intense excitement!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
omoi no mama mezasu basho e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to go - that's the adventure
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
omoi no mama mezasu basho e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to go - that's the adventure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power will seize the "end of the dream"
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
However, no one has ever
fully explored it except for
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Luffy entered a fighting competition - in
which a winner will get the Flare-Flare Fruit
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
as the prize - and won the first round
but now, he's heading for the palace
to take back Law who's
been captured by Doflamingo.
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Special Attack: Green Star - Platanus...
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed
a pirate alliance with
...Shuriken!
and have come to Dressrosa.
Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition
- in which a winner will get the
Luffy entered a fighting competition - in
which a winner will get the Flare-Flare Fruit
Luffy entered a fighting competition
- in which a winner will get
"A Fateful Encounter!
Kyros and King Riku!"
Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize
- and won the first round
as the prize - and won the first round
the Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize - and won the first round
but now, he's heading for the palace to take
but now, he's heading for the palace
to take back Law who's
but now, he's heading for the
palace to take back Law who's
back Law who's been captured by Doflamingo.
been captured by Doflamingo.
Meanwhile, Usopp and the others put
--Let's make our way up!
--How we go up doesn't matter, right?!
Operation SOP into action
along with the Tontattas
We're gonna head for the palace!
Leo! Leo!
And...
but their plot has been uncovered.
What're you up to?!
Stay with me! That was too reckless!
...beat the hell out of Doflamingo!
That must be it!
We must complete Operation SOP...
At the Colosseum,
the final round of the competition started.
Where did they go?!
"The Last Light of Hope!
The Secret of Our Commander!"
Boy! We made it straight to our destination!
Usoland!
...as soon as...
...possible.
Usoland!!
Meanwhile, Usopp and Robin put Operation SOP
Shockwave...
I-I did it!
Then, the commander will...
into action along with the Tontattas. However...
There's only one girl left to beat!
...take down Doflamingo...
Sticky-Sticky Chain!
I don't wanna go rough on a little girl
but I've got no choice!
...for sure!
Are you still going on with this?
I have to put the Tatababasco grape
into Sugar's mouth somehow!
Rebecca, do you know
how your mother Scarlet died?
Making Sugar eat
this clump of Tatababasco Sauce is...
Dragon Claw!
Stick-Stickem...
...our responsibility!
Trebol.
Doce Fleurs!
I can't believe you got
beaten by a guy like him.
Meanwhile, at the underground trade port,
The Toy Soldier cried like a baby.
Do it now!
...Meteora!
You idiot. Drop dead.
Put the Tatababasco grape in her mouth!
the Tontattas started to
put Operation SOP into action.
He was so pathetic.
I'm not dead yet, you little shit!
What?!
You can't go after him!
Are you okay, Commander?!
With this world's hottest grape
made of Tatababasco Sauce,
Th-Thank you!
--Let's get going!
--Wait! They're gonna get beaten up!
I'm gonna knock Sugar out!
That's it!
Hey! Let go of me! You little bastards!
Even if he can shoot a fly, he can't shoot me
because...
Stop looking back, Commander!
...I'm quicker!
We were planning on
sacrificing ourselves from the beginning!
Wh-What's with this guy?!
Wait, Leo!
Hey, hey! If you'd just kept running,
you might have survived!
Don't be silly!
T-Trebol-sama is going crazy!
Stop wasting your time!
What will happen if you stop here?!
Robiland?!
But you took the trouble
to come back to be killed!
Even if
Leo and the others pulled off Operation SOP,
The Executive Tower has been destroyed!
if we let Doflamingo walk away,
he'll turn everything back again!
That's our commander!
"A Liar!
Usoland on the Run!"
Alright! We're taking control of the lift now!
You're the only one who can bring
down Doflamingo, Commander!
THE ROYAL PALACE 2ND FLOOR - THE SUIT CHAMBER
There was a report that you,
sir, were on the 1st floor!
I guess you do have some fight in you.
Huh? What're you talking about?
Does it mean somebody who
looked like him was there?
He's worth betting everything on!
Have you ever seen anybody
who looks like me in the palace?
Nobody remembers him now
King Riku-sama!
What the hell is going on?!
THE ROYAL PALACE B-1
but everybody knew him once!
They say there are some intruders.
This sword looks good.
When he was a Big Human, his name was...
But we have Trebol-sama on our side!
If I can turn back into a human,
I wanna use this!
...Kyros!
I feel sorry for them
because no one can get away from him!
Let's run away from the stone man!
He was the strongest gladiator
in the history of the Colosseum!
My father was fighting
in the Colosseum today.
He's not gonna go down easily!
What? Is it true?
We keep getting blocked!
That's who our commander is!
I couldn't believe Doflamingo's abdication
was a false report.
We're trapped!
I told you! Pica can manipulate
this whole stone palace any way he likes!
How many times do they have to challenge me?!
It was just this morning
and we all lost patience.
"The Rupture Human!
Gladius Blows Up Big Time!"
King Riku-sama was fighting
in the Colosseum?!
Straw Hat!
Luffy, take her and go on!
Is he really going to be okay?!
You mean Zoro?
A boy committed a murder!
Two people got killed in a squabble in the slum!
Leave him up to me!
THE ROYAL PALACE B-1 - THE RAMPART TOWER
You don't have to worry about him!
You go ahead and kick Doflamingo's ass!
I dropped my guard!
I've been turned into a toy!
The boy is now...
Everybody must've forgotten about me.
Stop resisting!
"Defeat Sugar!
The Army of the Little People Charges!"
He'll be fine no matter what!
Usopp!
Where did he go?!
Please, Usopp!
This stone guy is gonna get cut!
A BOY IN THE SLUM - KYROS (15 YEARS OLD)
All I have is you!
Change me back into a human!
Okay! I'll be counting on you!
How can he move like that?!
THE TOY HOUSE
We have no choice but to shoot him!
I'm gonna fight you!
--No way! He's just a boy!
--But...
It's gonna block our way!
It's coming from behind, too!
King Riku-sama!
Now is our chance! Shoot him dead!
What the...!
King Riku-sama! What are you doing?!
It's dangerous!
I said I'm gonna fight you!
Although he's just a boy,
he's an infamous thug!
Rebecca has never made an attack
before but she just did it!
Three-Sword Style!
Hey, wait a second! What are you doing?!
I don't care if you're the king or not!
Whoever approaches me will...
Onigiri!
What kind of sword is that?
He's mine to kill!
Its blade is blunt.
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp!
The ring is a place for killing.
Let's go!
The king is in danger! Open fire!
Okay!
If you can't cut anybody,
you'll have to shed your own blood!
Give yourself up, Franky, without resistance!
Wait! Don't shoot!
Put your guns down!
It's what the people want to see!
B-But...
Shut up...
Shut the hell up!
Lock!
I heard you fought dozens of hooligans
on your own.
Black Rope Dragon Twister!
That didn't make a dent, did it?
And more than the half of them got injured
I intend to keep wrecking the place for no reason!
and two of them got killed.
Prepare for it!
That's a direct hit!
They ganged up on my best friend
and killed him!
I can't see an end to this!
What?!
The undefeated girl couldn't do anything!
How and where do I have to attack
to finish him off?!
So I was just getting revenge for him!
If I go underground with these guys chasing me,
Are you a beast?
it's not gonna help the Little People!
Diamante!
Say whatever you like!
A royal person like you can't understand!
THE ROYAL PALACE 1ST FLOOR
THE SOLDIER AND THE LITTLE PEOPLE
I'll leave Operation SOP up to you, guys!
Damn!
Hey, Musclemelon!
He was the only person I trusted
in the whole world!
Bring it on!
No, I'm Bartolomeo...
Break him down!
Don't get in my way!
Protect her!
He was like a brother to me!
What?!
I'll take care of business here!
I'm counting on you, Usoland!
Rebecca, do you know
how your mother Scarlet died?
Now you're quiet all of a sudden?
THE ROYAL PALACE 2ND FLOOR
- THE SUIT CHAMBER
Your name is Kyros, isn't it?
Hey! How long do I have to wait like this?!
I'm gonna go buy something to eat.
What's wrong? You look pale.
The Toy Soldier cried like a baby.
The Little People of the Tontatta
He was so pathetic.
have been beaten up by Trebol,
a top executive of the Family!
Stay away from him, King Riku-sama!
King Riku-sama!
Rampo!
I'm sorry!
What?!
I couldn't protect your mother!
Come with me!
My friend should be with them!
Yes, there is he.
The one with a long nose...
Usoland!
--Are you okay, Rampo?!
--Commander!
But he's...
Then, let's wait!
As long as he's there, it's gonna be fine!
You alright?!
A 15-year-old murderer - Kyros!
No worries! It's nothing!
I'm sure Usopp will take care of it!
Our ship...
He's gonna fight against an experienced gladiator!
Once they pull off Operation SOP,
This Colosseum is a sacred place!
you can change back to being a great gladiator!
A murderer like you doesn't belong here!
One-Sword Style...
They were trying so hard to
make me eat this.
But we're responsible to help you
to reach Doflamingo before that!
Teach him a lesson!
...Iai...
The battle starts!
It must be poison.
Smells awful.
Are you gonna keep looking
at the sword, brat?
...Death Lion Song!
You guys...
Why did Trebol-sama do this all of a sudden?
The sword's blade may be blunt,
We can't do anything anymore...
but prepare to get some of your limbs broken!
Don't worry!
If something goes wrong,
I'll make everything right for you!
Don't tell me that's...
Usoland...
Commander!
There's another executive!
I can't believe them!
I-I can't believe it! Kyros wins!
Usopp!
Move!
Where're you going, buddy?!
The winner is the 15-year-old
murderer - Kyros!
Usopp! Wake up!
He's a member of the Pica Army!
Gladius!
--It's not over yet!
--That's enough! Stop!
Yes! I escaped!
What a relief!
He's so talented!
--Robi...
--Shh!
Forgive me, Tontattas!
If the blade wasn't blunt, he
would've killed his opponent!
You have no chance of winning now!
Usopp! Where are you?!
Where did you go?!
Wh-What just happened?!
I saw a big duck falling from the ceiling!
Barbarism looks a lot
like a talent here, huh?
Rampo and I are gonna draw his attention!
Oh yeah! I can write a picture book
to tell future generations how brave you were!
I'll explain to you later. We have a problem!
So please run ahead!
No, don't!
How is Kyros doing?
Are you guys gonna try to
sacrifice yourselves again?!
Leo and the others got caught!
He nearly killed all the convict
gladiators in his room.
"The Honest Tontattas"!
What?!
The title sounds great!
I need to survive!
Rampo!
Let's attack him from both sides, Cub-san!
He hasn't eaten for six days
and just keeps shouting "Call King Riku."
Okay!
Commander!
It's Franky's fault!
Why hasn't he come to help?!
Wait!
Dammit!
How arro"g"ant of you
to think you can invade the palace!
Why should I fight these little rats?!
What's wrong, Kyros?
I'm not gonna die for some stupid lie that I'm a hero! No way!
There's the "G"!
King Riku! What are you gonna do with me?!
If you're gonna execute me, do it already!
I'm gonna get there at any cost and...
Shoot me or hang me or whatever you like!
OK, I escaped from them
Take this!
...take down Doflamingo!
but the problem is how to get myself out of here!
Do you want to die so badly?
Or are you regretting what you did?
I don't think I can get out through
Regret? I thought you were different
and you understood me!
that tunnel we came in through by myself!
Oh yeah! He said there is a lift!
Your buzzing around is annoying me!
You prick!
Kill me! Just kill me!
Hey, all of you out there!
Drop dead! Right now!
Cub!
The gladiatorial contest that
you fought in the other day
I'm not gonna die, you little shit!
Hey, hey!
You didn't stop working, did you?
Rampo!
wasn't just a deadly competition or a show.
We're having a serious conversation now!
THE ROYAL PALACE 1F
It's not a show, you fools!
It has been going on for several centuries
in this country.
Commander!
Don't get in my way!
--Commander!
--Now is your chance!
Oh no!
It's a sacred event in which
fighters discipline their mind
Get back to work!
Stop lying!
and hone their sword skill.
Keep moving those boxes!
Don't take a break!
I'm not gonna tell you!
Do you want to become a gladiator?
I know someone is helping you - who is it?
Hurry up, you idiots!
Commander!
A gladiator? Me?
This is no good! If nothing is done,
not only can we not defeat Doflamingo,
Hey! Hey! What's his name?
Somebody's trying to
fight the Don Quixote Family!
King Riku-sama is planning
to release you on parole
I'll never tell!
but we won't be able to save our people
who're working at the factory as slaves!
This is the first time
since I became a toy eight years ago!
Yeah! Never, ever tell!
once you win 100 matches in
as much time as it takes.
Whoever it is, please bring down this place!
IN THE UNDERGROUND TRADE PORT
Let's run while we can, Robin!
FOUR MONTHS LATER
A show?! I've had enough of it!
We haven't had any new workers for a year.
Kick the murderer's ass!
Toys can't run that fast!
Bring down Kyros!
What should we do with them?
Even though he's actually my friend?
Yeah. I heard they don't even come to the palace.
LUMINOUS FLOWERS "ELEGANT SUNFLOWERS"
What?
...so...
If I remember correctly, his name is...
I ate the Pop-Pop Fruit
and became a rupture human!
...la...
Kyros wins 20 consecutive matches!
He's unbelievably strong!
Hey, hey! Are they saying something?
You mean Usoland?
Who is taking a break?!
THE MAN-MADE DEVIL FRUITS -
SMILE MANUFACTURING FACTORY
Hey!
N-Not us!
You idiot! He's not my friend!
I can detonate my own body.
--...so...
--...la...
Kyros wins 50 consecutive matches!
Oh no! I've been fooled!
And...
...d!
...la...d.
What?!
Is the one-legged soldier
your associate, too?
...Inorganic objects as well.
I-I'm not gonna tell you!
...sola...nd.
When 500 of your people didn't come back,
you'd think there's something wrong.
Kyros wins 100 out of 100 matches!
Well, I already know.
Oh, if you know, then it can't be helped!
He's our associate!
Uso...la...
I can destroy a thing like
a tin toy completely!
Even the star gladiator couldn't do anything!
U-Usola...nd.
He finally won his freedom
in such a short period of time!
--I thought so!
--Oh no!
L-Let go of me!
But the Tontattas don't think
somebody's doing something bad.
Dammit! Where is the lift?!
I have a...
Now, we see some connections!
That's why they're so dumb...
How could anyone be that strong?!
Uso...land.
I mean, pure.
Don't come out, murderer!
...responsibility!
Usolan...d.
It doesn't matter anymore!
You people are finished!
--Hey!
--Think about it!
Then, why don't they come
around here anymore?
If someone like him gets released,
he may kill more people again!
Usolan...d.
I don't know.
Usoland.
Today is the decisive day!
We will pull off...
--She's right.
--Uh-huh.
Rebecca!
Well, if they don't come,
we'll just keep making these 500 work like hell!
Usoland.
Yeah! Don't come back
on the street, murderer!
Enjoy being blown to pieces!
...this operation no matter what!
"Usoland"?
--Don't release him!
--Keep fighting until you die!
Too slow! Here's a lesson in tough-love!
I know someone is helping you - who is it?
Jet Stamp!
You mean Usoland?
And we will...
The name he said earlier.
...take back our friends at any cost!
Who is it?!
Run! Run!
You're gonna stay?
Usoland...
--Soldier! Where are Franky and the others?
--You're...
I won't go out where people don't want me.
Usoland...
Oh, you aren't with them?
Since when did you want to become
the person other people wanted?
Straw Hat! This is no time to talk!
Usoland...
Let me tell you something.
Shut up!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Usoland!
Violet!
--Usoland!
--Oh, everybody!
Gladius!
That sticky stuff is flammable!
People like beasts...
How could you...
...as long as they stay...
Usoland!
Hey, hey! This SMILE is unripe!
...in a cage!
How could you betray Young Master-sama!
Usoland!
Even if...
...I get out of the cage,
--Usoland!
--Uso...
--Alright! Bring it on!
--No! You have to run!
Are you okay?!
What're you doing?!
there is no place...
I thought you Tontattas could grow any plant!
Usoland!!
We don't have time!
And he's pretty strong, too!
...for me to go back!
W-We can!
There is nowhere for me to belong out there!
Let's just go to the Suit Chamber now!
But SMILEs are very unnatural fruits.
Viola-sama, why are you doing this?!
Usoland?
No excuses!
Whoa, whoa! Don't call my name!
You know who I am?
Could you give my brother
a few minutes to rest?
I do! Even if you don't remember me!
I've been watching over you
with my Clairvoyance, too!
Usoland? Hey, who is that?
Today's meal was a little spoiled.
His 200th win!
Now you're complaining about your meal?
You and Rebecca!
It's the name of their associate he mentioned earlier.
--Somebody, bring down Kyros!
--Defeat Kyros!
What?
Don't you wanna cure
your princess Mancherie's illness?
It must've been hard! Thank you!
What is it this time?!
You asked him.
Trebol-sama!
Idiot. Drop dead.
W-We do!
Violet!
His 300th win!
I will never let a traitor walk away...
Then, make more SMILEs!
I'm not gonna die, you little shit!
Nobody can stop Kyros!
It's the only medication for her illness!
The heroes have been brought
down one after another!
Drop dead.
Hey!
...alive!
Are you guys okay?!
Drop dead.
I didn't betray anybody!
Since that day a decade ago,
The average number of
acceptable fruits you produce
Finally!
I've never trusted you guys,
not even once!
Drop...
in one season is still less
than one out of every ten!
Finally - an unprecedented 1000th victory!
HIS 4TH YEAR AT THE COLOSSEUM
Either way, it's disrespectful
to the Young Master!
Use your head and
increase the production rate!
Usoland is our hero!
Kyros-sama!
Could we see Princess Mancherie?
Helmet Pop!
Way to go, Kyros!
Leo! Leo!
H-H-Hero?
No!
W-Why?!
The ire of the crowd
turned to adulation before I knew it.
He will save you guys, then?
Because...
That's right!
Everybody, are you okay?!
Not just us!
Viola-sama!
However...
Oh no!
Stay with me! That was too reckless!
He said he will make everything right!
If you pick up her disease,
It isn't a serious wound, is it?!
Sorry that I couldn't protect you!
The toys who are being forced to work here, day after day.
we would be devastated!
The operation is over! Let's run away!
It was just some shrapnel grazing by!
Let's make our way up!
You Tontattas are important partners to us!
I mean, you have to fall back!
--What?
--Is he talking about us?
How we go up doesn't matter, right?!
You guys did all you can!
But you can't beat Trebol!
Wait a second!
The staircase is not that way...
Our friends who are enslaved in the factory.
S-Sanshita-san!
The toys who look to be
walking down the street happily
We're gonna work very hard!
That's not an option!
but never stop crying inside.
--What?!
--What're you up to?!
Please take good care of our princess!
That must be it!
Alright!
We must complete Operation SOP...
The poor Big Humans who don't even know...
How could they believe in such a lie?
...that they've lost their loved ones.
...as soon as...
Wh-What are you doing, Robiland?!
Usoland will save them all!
...possible.
Where did they go?!
Leo!
I'm sorry.
He's the legendary hero!
But if I didn't stop you,
you would've been taken down.
Then, the commander will...
...take down Doflamingo...
What?
You're here again.
The fly that got shot...
Young Master?
Why're you here?
--Kyros.
--Go away!
DON QUIXOTE DOFLAEMON
KIN'EMON IN DISGUISE
...for sure!
You don't understand!
This is...
Hm? Young Master?
No matter where I go,
I'll be a beast...
Who is Young Master? I'm Don Quixote...
It was so tiny
but it was shot right between the eyes.
...who killed men for the rest of my life!
That's how they address Doflamingo!
Is that all you have to say?
The commander is...
Trebol's dynamic vision
and ability are exceptional.
I am the Young Master.
What?!
...waiting for us!
No, I don't wanna be a hero! Hell no!
I think it's too dangerous to approach Sugar
while he's protecting her!
You guys are so pathetic! That's all lies!
There are some intruders in the palace.
What should we do then, Robiland?
What?!
I wish...
Please wait upstairs until we wipe them out.
You guys got fooled again!
...everybody would forget about me!
We should separate Trebol from Sugar!
No, I can't do that...
Y-You really think so?!
He's not coming to help you
even though you're all hurt so bad!
I mean, I'll leave it up to you.
It's easier said than done.
I'm gonna go down underground
to see how Kanjuro is doing.
We must hurry!
Usoland! Tell us what to do!
That says it all, doesn't it?
Where's the hero?
Kanjuro?
What?!
The samurai who has disappeared
from the junkyard?
Our legendary hero - Usoland!
So, where?
Indeed. I'm gonna go see Kanjuro
who has disappeared from the junkyard...
Y-You can count on me.
But he said it himself!
What?!
I'm sure he's laughing at you fools somewhere now!
He disappeared?!
Put it there.
Since you guys are so honest,
Hey, what's wrong with that load?!
I bet you're not making it up and
There is a swarm of pink hornets!
there was actually somebody who told you
that he'd make everything right.
A mysterious tough man who
came into sudden prominence,
Boy! We made it straight to our destination!
Lao G, you bastard!
THE SUIT CHAMBER
going by "Ricky", is fighting Kyros!
But he just chickened out when the need arose.
I'm here to report, Trebol-sama!
Go, Kyros!
No, you'll have to wait!
So you'd better abandon your hope!
Lao G's "G"!
We have a problem with
Captain Yves' pirate group in
Hey, why do we have to hide?!
Mingo is there!
I'm sorry but he's kind of right!
You'd better run, too, guys! Good luck!
The odds are for Kyros who will mark
his 3000th win if he wins this match
"G"!
trade port district 4!
They're going wild saying they
want to talk to an Executive
Be quiet! Don't ruin their operation!
but Ricky isn't giving up an inch!
about the price!
--What operation?
--The Tontattas' Operation SOP!
Aren't they afraid of Joker's name?
They must have a lot of nerve!
Whoa! Ricky landed a blow against Kyros!
We can only make a move
after they pull it off.
So stay still for now!
Kyros has never taken a single hit
from an opponent before!
N-No...
Hey, did they change the person
in charge of reporting?
DRESSROSA - THIS MORNING
Kyros wins!
I thought you guys wanted to destroy
the SMILE factory and that's it.
DON QUIXOTE DOFLAMINGO
WITHDRAWS FROM THE SEVEN WARLORDS
He won 3000 out of 3000 in nine years!
He's never lost!
He's out to lunch now!
Doflamingo-sama withdraws
from the Seven Warlords?!
And it's an emergency!
Shut up...
The living legend - Kyros!
The word "invincible" truly only fits to this man!
Then why are the Straw Hats working with
the Little People of Green Bit?
We have a few casualties on our side!
Please help us!
Shut up!
I can't believe it!
Usoland doesn't lie!
Is he gonna step down
from the throne of Dressrosa?!
Casualties?
Yeah, Kyros!
Alright, I'm coming!
They're not acting on some casual whim.
Why did you enter secretly,
King Riku-sama?!
The Little People?
How did they sneak into the basement?
Yeah!
I became quite strong after you
taught me how to fight, didn't I?
He's nothing but an ordinary pirate now!
But you lowered your guard
when you noticed it was me.
Why do they wanna attack Sugar?
Shut up!
He's gonna be chased by the Navy!
You're not such a "beast" after all.
I don't know why but they keep doing things
Usoland doesn't lie!
We're gonna be free!
Isn't that enough now?
that are causing me a lot of grief.
Finally, we're free!
You've spent your life locked away
in this "cage" for nine years.
If it's not a coincidence, it means...
Hey, hey!
Yes!
Trebol-sama, are you gonna go somewhere?
You need to leave now.
There's something I need you to do.
Tighten security at the four doors
to the Executive Tower.
...they know what's behind
the darkness of this country!
Kyros.
Yes, sir!
Rather than regretting
what you did in the past,
But if something happens,
let me know immediately!
you can save many lives from now on.
Usoland said...
Y-Yes, sir!
I am a descendent of Noland!
That's one way for you to live.
Answer!
Cool!!
The Young Master is asking
you questions, Law!
Yes, sir!
Trebol-sama!
Usoland said he will save us
no matter what happens to us!
Thank you for your leadership!
Hey, hey!
Don't do it if it's gonna
make you cry-dasuyan!
Where is it? Where are they fighting?
That's what he told us!
District 4.
You two never change!
Kyros! We'll be counting on you!
A YEAR LATER
I told you.
Yeah!
Kyros! Thank you always for your service!
I have nothing to do with them anymore!
That's right!
What? Aren't you gonna fight for us?
--That's right!
THE COMMANDER OF THE DRESSROSA KING RIKU ARMY
KYROS (25 YEARS OLD)
Our alliance ended.
That's what he said!
I could easily handle this.
I don't know what you're
talking about at all.
Oh! Kyros-sama!
But I'd better do nothing!
Commander, did you see the newspaper?!
Protect me!
I'll just stay and watch
so you can build your self-confidence!
Are you trying to fool me?
It means we're gonna have our friends back,
doesn't it?!
He promised us!
Girls love you so much, huh?!
Kyros-sama!
Self-confidence?
Or do you really not know anything?
The hero would never lie to us!
I see!
Now we understand!
We no longer have to fight Doflamingo!
But you're a murderer!
Don't worry! If something goes wrong,
I'll make everything right for you!
Stop insulting Usoland or...
That's great!
I don't understand why Father-sama
lets you in to the palace!
...we'll make you pay for it!
That's good to know!
We'll follow you to the end!
P-Princess-sama!
The legendary hero - Usoland!
Big Sis, don't!
You can't bring up his old pain!
No.
Th-That's me.
I can't believe he even assigned you
to be the commander of the righteous army!
It was a false report.
What?!
If Violet were with us,
she could tell what's in your mind easily.
Big Sis!
Even if you can fool the whole
nation, you can't fool me!
No one's coming back!
Who is it?
Or...
THE PRINCESS OF DRESSROSA
- SCARLET (15 YEARS OLD)
You'll reveal your true colors someday!
...you didn't instigate them,
did you, King Riku?
No way!
Don't come near me and my sister!
The Tontattas once served you.
Don't touch us!
Understood?!
But Big Sis, he's kind of...
THE SECOND PRINCESS (THE YOUNGER SISTER) -
VIOLA (10 YEARS OLD)
I'm so glad that it was just a mistake!
You two had better prepare for it!
Father-sama?! Why is he here in the palace?!
Hey! Don't look into his mind!
He's a great man!
He's not gonna abdicate the throne!
I'm gonna go now!
Tra-guy seems alive.
His mind is corrupted!
But I'm responsible for protecting you two!
King Riku!
Doflamingo-sama!
Once Usoland gets here, you guys will...
I'm glad you're okay after a decade!
No thanks!
Oh! He did it!
I'm gonna enter today's competition
and win the Flare-Flare Fruit!
Now we wait for her to eat the
clump of Tatababasco Sauce,
Pigya!
And I will take down Doflamingo!
Your name is Kyros, huh? Come with me!
--Lady Scarlet has been kidnapped!
--They were pirates!
the hottest spice in the world!
"Pigya"? How funny!
Rebecca! Come to your senses!
--What happened to her bodyguards?!
--They all got beaten up!
I will save you at any cost!
--What?!
--What should we do?!
I know you're angry!
So am I! But don't jump the gun!
The Tontattas' death-cry is...
Hey, let's kick Mingo's ass already!
--Just calm down!
--Don't touch me!
We're gonna rise up! We're locked and loaded!
"Pigya"!
I said wait!
Leo!
--Leo!
Nobody's gonna come rescue you!
What are Leo and the others doing?!
No! I'm not gonna wait!
The moment that all the toys in Dressrosa
change back to humans will be...
How about we get a lot of
money from King Riku as ransom
Our hopes have been dropped
from heaven to the edge of hell.
Yeah! Leo is right!
Operation SOP will be okay!
and just sell her?!
No one here can take it anymore!
Their spirits are broken!
That's a good idea! She's a real princess!
We can make a good price!
...the one and only chance
to take down Doflamingo!
Usoland will...
I will finish him off at any price!
Usoland will pull it off for sure!
That's not it!
I won't let
Cub and the others' effort go to waste!
All there is left to do is
wait to be executed now.
Pigya!
I'm counting on you, Leo! Usoland!
Lady Scarlet!
That's right!
Eat the right one this time!
We'll be released if we
can win a thousand times?
Kyros!
It's you two who are pathetic!
Usoland will...
Who are you?!
Stay close behind me!
That's not hope!
Pigya!
That's a wall of despair!
THE RUINS OF THE "EXECUTIVE TOWER"
IN THE UNDERGROUND TRADE PORT
Pigya!
The legendary gladiator Kyros won
3000 out of 3000 matches?!
You bastards!
Pigya!
Just give it up already!
Everybody knows that statue is
just make-believe!
Pigya!
Dying prisoners must have made up
their ideal warrior and that's Kyros!
When we're in danger, the hero will...
They built the statue
wishing to be freed like him someday!
Pigya!
Then, call the hero now!
Idiot! Don't scream!
I'd rather not dream an impossible dream!
Your hero!
If Operation Sugar Oversurprised and Panic fails,
Today's competition is a
chance and I'll take it!
Are you all right, Lady Scarlet?
So...
it's gonna ruin all of our plans!
Leo! You...
It's not a chance!
It's impossible for you
to win that competition!
We have no choice!
You're gonna die!
I won't allow you to enter it!
Uh-huh!
I'm not that hurt. It's nothing.
Whoa! Something horrible is happening...
You're not thinking straight!
Everybody's trying their best!
I-I'm sorry!
Don't fight back, Sugar!
You're only 16!
Stop...
Do you think of yourself
as an adult now, Rebecca?!
To accomplish Operation SOP!
Stop!
I-I touched you!
Stop!!
Those fools!
You're still a kid!
You must listen to what I say!
We're here to take back our friends
who're working like slaves in the factory!
Enough already, you bastards!
Oh, please! You're not even my parent!
And we're gonna knock you out!
Kyros! I was scared!
Knock me down?
You're the one who's not thinking straight!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
But I don't know anything about your friends.
What's your plan?!
You have no chance to beat Doflamingo!
What?!
Really?!
Because you're...
H-Hey!
What?!
...just a one-legged toy!
Uh-huh.
Big Sis is cooking something!
All right, then!
It's not all right! Don't be fooled!
What's gotten into her?!
U-Usoland!
Oh, that was close!
Give us back our friends!
Usoland!
Are you still going on with this?
Who's putting this idea in your heads?!
Oh no!
There's no way that you dummies notice
that you've been fooled, yourself.
Of course, I am!
Uso...land!
Yeah...
If we can't knock Sugar out,
You're right!
Usopp! I'm glad he's here!
the commander and the Big Humans
who got turned into toys...
You Tontattas...
You haven't come to the palace
for a year or so, but...
N-No!
You guys! How can you trust me that much?!
...can't change back!
Sorry for being meddlesome
You little fools!
but I hope you're not gonna
enter the competition.
...I guess that's because
somebody talked you into something.
What?!
I didn't mean it! Soldier-san, don't go!
They're right! It was all lies!
Making Sugar eat this clump
of Tatababasco Sauce is...
Charge!
Restrain her and open her mouth!
What?!
Please! Soldier-san!
I'm not the legendary hero
and my name is not Usoland!
...our responsibility!
I was just afraid that
you were gonna sacrifice yourself!
I don't like it. They think I'm weak.
These guys...!
What?!
I'm sorry! Don't go, Soldier-san!
What did you say?!
I'm the deadly sniper of the Straw Hats!
You wanna resign as my daughters' bodyguard?!
Soldier-san!!
Why're you saying that all of a sudden?!
My name is Usopp!
Oh, well... I mean...
Do you still want something?
How annoying.
I'm a pirate!
Don't tell me you're in love with Scarlet?
Not just to rescue our captive friends
--O-Of the Straw Hats?!
--What is he doing here?!
Little Black Bears!
What?!
N-No, I'm not! I swear...
but also to save the whole of Dressrosa
and restore the King Riku dynasty, we must...
It's shaking!
Kyros!
...accomplish Operation SOP first!
It must be Pica! What is he doing?!
Here is the contract.
Oh no! She has turned us into toys!
I am, sir.
The greatest hero in the
history of the Colosseum
You must follow my orders until you die!
and the commander of the
army. And the princess.
You can't go after him!
Why...
Charge!
Are you okay, Commander?!
I know each individual will
celebrate your marriage
Why are you saying that?!
Did they forget about us?!
Th-Thank you!
--Let's get going!
--Wait! They're gonna get beaten up!
Oh? Oh?
Some toys have appeared from nowhere!
but social constraints
won't allow your criminal record.
Hey! Let go of me! You little bastards!
You may be a pirate
Don't bother!
What were we doing now?
but you're a hero, aren't you?!
That's how public life works.
Stop looking back, Commander!
Kill everyone in the Executive Tower!
I said I'm not! A pirate is a pirate!
Father-sama!
If I can't marry him, I'd rather die!
We were planning on
sacrificing ourselves from the beginning!
I can't help myself from following her orders!
Kill everyone? Including me?!
Don't be silly!
What will happen if you stop here?!
Don't make me repeat myself!
I was fooling you guys!
Even if Leo and the others
pulled off Operation SOP,
No! I don't wanna fight!
But you never stop believing in me!
if we let Doflamingo walk away,
he'll turn everything back again!
They must be Sugar's subordinates!
Lady Scarlet...
I didn't know there were bodyguards
other than Trebol!
It was a sudden illness.
You're the only one who can bring
down Doflamingo, Commander!
I'm sure she would've become
a great queen someday.
Stand up, little bears!
Leo! It's me! Flapper!
Take down the enemies!
So you have...
I don't wanna do this!
...taken the trouble to come and
tell them that you were lying?
Scarlet. As of today,
you're not a member of the royal family.
--I don't wanna fight our friends!
--Somebody, help!
Why do you care about the commander, Leo?
No! No!
Why do you guys count on him so much?!
No! Nooo!!
Now, go ahead and kill each other!
People think you're dead.
Yeah. Otherwise these fools will wait for me until they die!
Yes.
Trebol, come back here!
It was a trap!
C-Commander!
It feels like I'm repaying your kindness
with ingratitude, King Riku-sama.
Even if only he makes it...
Trebol!
It's unforgivable!
He's just a one-legged toy!
A trap?
If it were anyone else but you.
Normally, people who are turned into toys
are bound by the contract
Then I won't be able to sleep at night so instead,
Hey!
Kyros! I've never heard a story like this!
Look at that! Trebol-sama!
Thank you, sir!
I wanna thank them for believing in a guy like me
What are they doing?!
The pirates are running wild
and there's nothing we can do!
and they will become
workers who can't disobey.
They did their best already!
and I plan to sacrifice myself for them because...
The commander was the first person
Hey, hey! You guys!
...that's way cooler, isn't it?!
ever in this country to get turned into a toy
They are... helpless fools!
What?
What's the problem here?
Her name is Rebecca.
but the Hobby-Hobby Fruit eater, Sugar...
Trebol-sama!
My name is Usopp!
Hey! What is it?!
I agree.
Kyros, hold her in your arms.
She's your daughter!
...made a mistake forgetting
to make a contract!
Remember my name, Tontattas!
Well, it's just there was a swarm of bees
on a load!
If I die,
But I like them.
build a statue of me beside Noland's!
Just one mistake from ten
years ago made him...
We have no problem with the deal itself.
I shouldn't touch such an innocent thing!
Robin?!
I'm gonna become your legendary hero now!
My hands are tainted!
I don't wanna taint her!
That tramp!
...the only toy in this country who
can get back at...
Your father is a strange man, Rebecca.
...the Don Quixote Family!
Hey, hey! Wait up, wait up!
You're barely alive!
Doce Fleurs!
You bitch!
You're like an angel, Rebecca!
Hey! Who are you and
where did you come from? Hey?
That's why he's been fighting
on his own for a decade!
Usopp!
What's this?! What's this?!
I'll be watching over you!
I'll always be by your side!
Usopp of the Straw Hats?!
What's this?! It's so creepy!
Is he gonna save all of us?!
Peek-a-boo! Your grandpa is here!
She vanished!
--Leo!
--Robiland!
If it weren't for him,
toys would have no choice...
Hey! Hey!
Do it now!
Grandpa!
Put the Tatababasco grape in her mouth!
...but to put up with it!
Rebecca! You got big again!
Don't tell me she's... I know her face!
You're desperate!
I'll take my chances!
Father-sama, take off your disguise!
We Tontattas wouldn't know anything
Thank you!
Kill him.
All right!
Kyros!
Gloves, gloves!
and we all would have been enslaved by them!
Is she a member of the Straw Hats?!
How cute she is! How cute she is!
Special Attack: Green Star - Platanus...
How did she get here?!
You're crying again!
Trebol!
He can make it!
Why do they wanna attack Sugar?
Come back here now! You've been fooled!
Good-for-nothing idiot! Drop dead!
...Shuriken!
I'd never expected that
I could have such happiness.
If we ignore his rallying cry,
I'm losing it!
there'll be no chance of saving this country!
But it didn't last long.
Sticky-Sticky Chain!
He's worth betting everything on!
That's it!
Nobody remembers him now
That was 10 years ago...
but everybody knew him once!
Leo!
What?! What happened?!
When he was a Big Human, his name was...
I thought he was gonna make it!
Stick-Stickem...
How do you like that, monster?!
I'm the legendary hero
...Kyros!
What's going on?!
He was the strongest gladiator
in the history of the Colosseum!
and the sniper of the Straw Hats,
What's going on?!
Captain Usopp!
Usoland!
That's who our commander is!
Stop wasting your time!
No, Usopp!
Usoland!
...Meteora!
No, I said Usopp!!
The legendary hero...
King Riku-sama!
Usoland!!
10 years ago, the Toy Soldier was tragically torn
from his loved ones!
There is no salvaging Operation SOP now!
The Toy Soldier runs to reach Doflamingo
The furious Trebol's powerful attack
devastates Leo and the others.
Back in old days in Dressrosa,
there was a brutal man who people feared as a beast!
Merciless Trebol torments and
but a brutal enemy named Gladius stands
in his way!
squishes the Little People one after another!
The only hope left for the King Riku Army
is the Toy Soldier!
His name was Kyros!
When the Toy Soldierfs life is at stake
Shouldering the burden of
everybody's expectations,
But even though they hear their
When King Riku came face-to-face with this
Due to Gladiusfs overwhelmingly
destructive power
friends screaming and crying,
the Tontattas keep their spirits high...
Usopp fights Trebol to the full extent of his power!
Once known as "The Legend"
throughout Dressrosa,
wild man, a miraculous story of a legendary warrior began!
...believing in their last hope -
the legendary hero named Usoland!
Luffy rushes in like the wind!
Will he bring a miracle?!
his true identity is close to being revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Operation Failed! Usoland the Hero Dies?!"
On the next episode of One Piece
On the next episode of One Piece!
A Liar! Usoland on the Run!
Next on One Piece:
A Fateful Encounter! Kyros and King Riku!
!
"The Rupture Human! Gladius Blows Up Big Time!"
"The Last Light of Hope!
The Secret of Our Commander!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!