iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa
Luffy and the others formed
a pirate alliance with
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
and have come to Dressrosa.
but Law has been captured by Doflamingo.
Luffy entered a fighting competition
- in which a winner will get the
Luffy entered a fighting competition - in
which a winner will get the Flare-Flare Fruit
Luffy snuck into the Royal Palace
to take back Law.
Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize
- and won the first round
as the prize - and won the first round
but now, he's heading for the palace
to take back Law who's been
to take back Law who's
Sugar has passed out!!
Meanwhile, the toys who turned
back to their original forms
captured by Doflamingo.
been captured by Doflamingo.
Count on us to destroy the factory!
Meanwhile Kyros, who is now with Luffy,
channel their anger towards Doflamingo.
All of you, be safe!
Who are those bastards?!
remembers the gratitude he has for King Riku.
Roger that!
--Look! He's a Doflamingo operative!
--Thank you for turning us into toys!
Tra-guy's life...
Rebecca's wish...
What?!
He holds the key to all of that!
Take him down together with the factory!
Stay away from him, King Riku-sama!
We're gonna head for the palace!
Hey Sugar, what are you doing?!
King Riku-sama!
And beat the hell out of Doflamingo!
The fighting competition
came to a surprising end
Keep your senses!
Come with me!
At the Colosseum, the final round
of the competition started.
and the mystery man who were disguised as Lucy
finally disclosed his identity.
Finally!
Finally - an unprecedented 1000th victory!
Meanwhile,
the Tontattas' Operation SOP is...
The servants that we've been
collecting for a decade
Meanwhile, Usopp knocked Sugar out
Who are you really?
and freed the toys who had been
forced to labor as slaves.
You're here again.
Cyborg Franky has been silenced!
are turning back into humans!
Me?
--Kyros.
--Go away!
The spell of the Hobby-Hobby Fruit is
being removed!
U-Usopp! I know you can do it!
We accomplished Operation SOP!
You don't understand!
Mingo's dead!
Set off the panic already!
No matter where I go,
I'll be a beast...
My name is Sabo.
...who killed men for the rest of my life!
We're members of the Revolutionary Army.
Who is he?!
Disgusting!
Brother Kyros!
Don't worry, Young Master.
What? Then, the first Lucy, too?!
The toys were originally humans
Ow, it's hot!
I really can generate a fire!
He's not even conscious now.
The first Lucy has a bounty of 400 million.
Usoland!
but they were erased from our memories!
Ace!
He's the man who'll become
the King of the Pirates someday!
I take over your ability!
I wish...
Since the Devil Fruit eater Sugar
passed out now,
Straw Hat Luffy!
...everybody would forget about me!
You can have this poison grape back.
we got our memories back!
A pirate?!
--Oh, the Tatababasco grape!
--Our only hope!
Yeah, he's my brother. Take good care of him!
You are...
Her name is Rebecca.
Fire Fist!
You eat this.
He's the former commander of
the King Riku Army - Kyros!
At the same time, Luffy finally comes face-to-face
with Doflamingo. However...
I shouldn't touch such an innocent thing!
Drop dead.
My hands are tainted!
I don't wanna taint her!
You are...!
Tra-guy!
You're Kyros, aren't you?!
Your father is a strange man, Rebecca.
Yes, sir!
I'm here to save you!
I'm sorry to keep you waiting
for a decade!
I'm glad that you're alive!
You're like an angel, Rebecca!
Now, I'm here to save you!
Oh, the stone guy!
I'll be watching over you!
I'll always be by your side!
Pica!
I never thought I'd be taken in like this.
"The Legend is Back!
Kyros' All-out Blow!"
Mingo's alive!
I'm here to take back the real Dressrosa!
It's a difficult situation.
"Dashing onto the Scene!
The Chief of Staff of the Revolutionary Army, Sabo!"
I have no choice but to use the "Birdcage."
What's going on?!
"The Fire Fist Strikes!
The Flare-Flare Fruit Power Returns!"
The Birdcage?!
"The Operation Failed!
Usoland the Hero Dies?!"
The ring is disappearing.
Right, Law?
Who are you?
When Sugar passes out,
that's when all the toys in the country will
turn back into Big Humans!
"The Devil's Trap!
A Dressrosa Extermination Plan!"
Father-sama!
I got in touch with Hack.
Let's meet up with him!
A decade!
All his evildoing will be revealed
For a decade, we have suffered!
Where's Doflamingo?!
and the pirate - Doflamingo
- will show his true colors!
All right.
The palace is on fire!
Take everything away from him!
What's going on in this country?
What will Doflamingo do?
Doflamingo-sama!
Destroy the factory as well!
God Usopp! God Usopp! God Usopp!...
Young Master!
What action the Navy will take?
THE SMILE FACTORY
You bastard!
What will the people in this country think
and do?
What should we do?!
The ex-toys are coming to...
From now on,
I'm gonna rip the mask off of all your deceptions!
Will they go crazy and riot?
...raid the factory!
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
Or will they give up and surrender?
Well...
Mingo's dead!
Nobody can get in here
unless they have a key to the door!
I was gonna kick his ass...
Or will they...
Usoland! Usoland!
--There they are!
--I see them!
--You bastards!
--They found us!
Shoot!
...fight together with us?!
Guide us, God Usopp!
What are we supposed to do?!
Let's go rescue Tra-guy!
What?!
This factory means everything
to the Young Master!
I'm gonna go to the palace!
Alright, Scarlet? Rebecca?
Then, why don't you destroy
the factory behind me
S... S...
Even if the ceiling collapses,
there won't be a single scratch
Father-sama!
What in the world is going on?!
If it gets dangerous here,
go to the Red Flower Field and wait there!
Sugar has passed out!!
because the buildings are
made of Sea Prism Stone.
and rescue our little friends?
The toys in the Colosseum turned into
humans and animals all of a sudden!
And more importantly...
I'll come and get you at any cost!
Even I don't know how to
explain this situation...
Why is a gorilla here?!
Those two top executives are on guard now!
Run!
Be careful!
Devil Fruit eaters are
weakened by touching water.
I can't believe it!
Oh yeah.
Damn Trebol! He must've left Sugar unguarded!
That idiot!
How surprising!
God Usopp gave us guidance!
Destroy the factory!
Hey! How much longer are you gonna cry?!
Am I a babysitter?!
It's not that!
I've turned back!
It's no use!
I just remember!
What?!
Mother-sama, I picked so many flowers!
"Destroy the factory"?!
Wow, Rebecca!
Would you like to have one?
Lock!
Thank you. I would like to.
And this is from your mother to you!
Th-This is...
Sticky-Sticky Chain!
I won't let you do such a thing!
Don't push your luck, you scum!
Would you like to have one?
This is...
What happened?!
What is going on?!
They're transforming one after another!
Stick-Stickem!
God Usopp. Leave the rest to us.
The toys are...
...Getting bigger and bigger!
Let's eat!
More importantly... I want you to...
Go ahead. Dig in.
I've turned back!
...put me down.
Nobody can take down those two!
What's going on?!
This way!
This factory has
an impregnable two-pronged defense!
You bastard!
Sorry!
Thank you for pushing
me around all this time!
Open up!
It's me! Kyros!
That's...
Brother, don't use violence!
Oops, I've held the wrong one!
Is anybody there?!
Someone that I loved so much!
You son of a bitch!
Guard! Open the gate!
I need to talk to King Riku!
I'm gonna go to the palace!
Alright, Scarlet? Rebecca?
Flapper?!
We need to do something immediately.
Shit!
Leo!
Father-sama!
That guy was not Straw Hat!
If it gets dangerous here,
go to the Red Flower Field and wait there!
Leo! I'm so relieved!
How dare he eat the Flare-Flare Fruit
that was supposed to be mine!
Creepy!
I'll come and get you at any cost!
Damn!
How can I tell Doffy about this situation?
Finally!
Pirates?!
We accomplished Operation SOP!
Brother Kyros!
Lady Viola!
How are you still alive, Doflamingo?!
Father-sama is...
King Riku-sama is okay.
Sugar! Hey, wake up! Sugar!
Who are those bastards?!
Hey! Hey!
--Look! He's a Doflamingo operative!
--Thank you for turning us into toys!
Do you want me to teach you...
This is no good!
...how to kill a person?
What happened?!
Father-sama!
Take him down together with the factory!
It's...
Soldier!
Father-sama!!
Brother Kyros!
The new king is waiting for you,
Army Commander Kyros.
What's going on?!
I see! They were the toys underground!
What is it?
This is how you do it.
What is happening here-dara?
F-Father-sama!
The new king?!
What?
Kyros!
--Let me lead the way to him.
--What did you do to King Riku-sama?!
What the...!
I...
He's turned into a weird old man!
Please follow me.
...had a father!
What's going on?
Huh? What are you talking about?!
Straw Hat!
Here! I'm here!
I guess that's the plot that's been
undermining the country, Rebecca.
I've turned back!
Hack!
Wait!
Feels like I haven't seen
you for a long time.
Lady Viola, come with me.
It's strange.
No.
Oh?
You have to come on your own.
What happened to your hand?
Things always have a core.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring,
ring, ring... Clank.
This is...
I just fell down!
S-Sugar has...
And if you can strike it,
you can turn any situation around.
Fell down? You? Really?
Could I have your weapon?
I'm sorry, Doffy!
No, you can't!
There are two Young Masters!
You're too loud, Trebol!
Wh-Why would I have to tell a lie?
Pentachromatic Strings!
My great senpai!
What happened to Sugar?
Now I don't know what you are talking about!
Well done-in!
P... P...
You're really gonna save my brother-in-law's life, too, aren't you?
Passed out!
Even the ring has one.
She has passed out!
Of course, we are!
I can't believe there was a
space like this underground!
A core.
Young Master-sama said
he might be useful-in!
--What? What happened?
--Sugar has passed out?!
--Oh yeah! Here are your clothes.
--Thanks.
Let's just finish up this fight.
If not, we would've killed him already-in!
Sorry! I dropped my guard!
Hey...
Gum-Gum...
Is this some kind of joke?!
Armament!
The servants that we've been
collecting for a decade
Bloody hell!
are turning back into humans!
...Jet Gatling!
So you've been working for the pirates, haven't you?!
It caught fire! This is hard to control!
The spell of the Hobby-Hobby
Fruit is being removed!
What the...
--Excuse me...
--Hey!
The Tontattas' operation must've
been pulled off!
How could you leave me behind like that,
my great senpai!
There are cracks in the ring!
Did Lucy do something?!
We are here. Go on in.
See? I told you
Usopp would take care of it!
Yes, I'm a man and
I can create barriers but...
Young Master, look at the Colosseum!
That guy is...
Where's King Riku-sama?
Dragon Claw Fist!
Who are you really?
I've turned back!
--Honey!
--I remember now!
Dragon...
Me?
Wh-What is going on here?
...Breath!
Oh! Um...
What is happening here?!
The toys are...
The toys are turning into humans!
My name is Sabo.
Whoa! Lucy's unbelievable attack!
The ring is sinking!
Who are you?
He's here.
KOALA - THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
SABO - THE CHIEF OF STAFF OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
HACK - THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
Not just humans!
The ring has exploded!
We're members of the Revolutionary Army.
Oh no!
Don't tell me Sugar has...
What?
The Revolutionary Army?!
A decade of our hard work...
It's floating!
Sugar must've been beaten
by somebody-in!
You bastard! What did you do?!
How pathetic that shitty little tramp is!
I gotta go somewhere! I'm gonna win this!
Luffyland!
What? Then, the first Lucy, too?!
Sea Prism Stone?!
--Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
--Oh!
But...
The first Lucy has a bounty of 400 million.
...I hope she's not hurt.
I heard a huge noise up there!
He's the man who'll become
the King of the Pirates someday!
Boy!
You said such an unkind thing but...
Hack?
Did he do something reckless again?!
Straw Hat Luffy!
...you actually care about her!
So hard-boiled!
A pirate?!
He's gonna head underground now.
Yeah, he's my brother. Take good care of him!
--Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
--Palace, please answer!
King Riku-sama!
What is that clone?!
--Wh-What?!
--Yep, yep!
The ring has totally collapsed!
We keep getting emergency reports!
It seems like the water level is falling!
That hurts!
This is an emergency call
from Sevio in the south!
We can no longer guarantee
the safety of the Colosseum!
The toys working at the port
suddenly turned into pirates!
It's like a marionette made of strings!
Luffy is a nice guy, isn't he?
Everybody, please evacuate immediately!
--Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
--This is Carta in the east!
I've never seen such a technique!
It's driving to the center!
The toys turned into old Dressrosa soldiers!
There must be some cracks in
the foundation of the ring!
They turned into gov't officials!
You guys! Are you gonna become pirates?!
King Riku.
Navy soldiers and
senior officials from abroad!
Do you remember the feeling you had
on that night 10 years ago?
The water is flowing down into the ground!
What did you do...
Wild animals! This is Primula District!
I'm gonna become one, too!
...to this country and the king, pirate?!
The king set fire to the town.
Didn't you see it?
Give up, give up, give up!
You can't hold on to my neck! I'm choking!
Are they real?!
The day you sliced up your dear citizens
and burned down peaceful towns.
Young Master!
He'd never do such a thing!
Kyros!
This is nothing!
It's spirit! All about spirit!
Unlock these Sea Prism Stone chains!
I'm not a Devil Fruit eater!
Kyros. I've been hearing good things about you.
Please stop!
I've turned back into a human!
If there's no preventing me
hurting the citizens...
They say you're the strongest gladiator in the Colosseum.
I'm so glad!
That's...
I found it!
Swear fealty to me.
I'd rather be dead!
The king has been dethroned and all members of the old royal family will die!
Somebody, please...
...kill me!
He hasn't changed a bit.
I've already sent my men to your wife and daughter
I still have nightmares of it every night!
That son of a bitch!
--Stay with me, Usopp!
--Usoland!
Well, let's just leave
it until the time comes.
who are part of the royal line!
Yes, I remember it! So what?!
Usoland!
Maybe we'll set out independently.
I won't let you have it!
Watch what I'm gonna do!
Me and everybody else, we all turned
back into humans thanks to you!
The tragedy that will unfold soon
will not be small-scale like that.
I got wet!
The King Riku Family is
no longer governing Dressrosa!
Oh, you stole that from Dadan!
I'm losing my strength...
--Usoland!
Did you guys know?!
Don't!
We weren't gonna give anyone that prize!
You did it!
We can become brothers
if we exchange this cup of sake!
Don't be ridiculous!
He cut off his own leg!
What are you planning?!
I don't ever want to see such...
Operation SOP has been accomplished!
Brothers? Really?!
Now it's time to let you guys go.
Kyros!
When we become pirates,
we might not be on the same ship
Everybody turned back into a human
and they're all happy!
Pica!
but our brotherhood will always be with us!
What's the matter, Onepoko?
Wherever you are, whatever you do,
we'll always be bonded together!
Throw these nuisances out!
Hey Mom, Onepoko is acting strange!
Everybody's out of the ring!
I'm the winner!
So from now on,
What?! Onepoko!
What?!
One...poko? One...poko?
we're brothers!
You said the one who gets
this will be the winner!
One... No! My darling!
The Flare-Flare Fruit!
It's all mine, isn't it?
Yeah!!
I-I've turned back!
Th...
The champion! The champion!
Honey!
D-Dad! You're not Onepoko!
I know now isn't the time
--Yes, I'm your dad!
--Dad!
but the one who got
the Flare-Flare Fruit
Why have we forgotten about you
all this time?!
He's still reckless and everything.
by taking advantage of this mess is...
A toy?
The toy put the king on his shoulder and escaped-dasuyan!
...the biggest dark horse of
this competition - Lucy!
Sabo-kun, you do very reckless things, too!
That's how the spell worked!
I thought I was gonna live as a toy forever!
Do I?
I got turned into a toy!
What happened to me?!
He is the champion!!
Well, I think it through before I let loose.
Am I dreaming?!
--Hey Dad! Can you lift me up high?!
--Alright!
What do you mean?
Luffy, however, merely follows his instincts.
There you go!
What's the difference?
I'm Kyros! King Riku-sama!
But what brought you Revolutionaries
here to this country?
--Kyros?
--Yes!
Doflamingo!
Disgusting!
I'm sorry. It doesn't ring a bell. But...
Don't cause harm to...
I can't hold out... anymore...
...I'll never forget what you did for me!
You're a strange toy.
Those are...
Run!
Oh my great senpai! Help me, too!
These weapons that they export from this port
aggravate wars around the world.
Scarlet! Rebecca!
...this country anymore!
Wait for me at the rendezvous point!
You're a man.
You have to take care of yourself!
Gum-Gum Balloon!
Damn! You're quiet again?
We're here to...
What?!
Where did you go, stone guy!
But I knew that's what you would say...
...stop it!
TWO DAYS LATER
Usopp... Little People...
--I'm gonna make one more attack so watch out!
--What?!
The Revolutionary Army has sent soldiers
to this country many times
Operation Sugar Oversurprised
and Panic went...
Nobody knows my name.
...super well, I guess.
but because they all got turned into toys,
Did they all forget about me?!
Damn! He ate the Flare-Flare Fruit!
we couldn't find out about this black market.
--Usopp, stay with me!
--Usoland!
Isn't he the guy
from the Revolutionary Army?!
I think... I can't... carry on...
anymore...
Hey, that guy's troublesome!
Yeah, that's Sabo, isn't it?!
What is the number 2 of the
Revolutionary Army doing here?!
Now, let's bring an end to everything.
I've gotta get to the Red Flower Field!
Ow, it's hot!
I really can generate a fire!
Gotta tell the Young Master!
Scarlet and Rebecca are waiting for me!
His clothes! I forgot I have them!
But I guess they're manufacturing
weapons somewhere else.
Usoland! Please wake up!
No, it's just my imagination!
It's not hot!
--Don't die!
--I don't want you to die!
I am a fire now!
Where do they come from?
Usoland has died!
Ace!
I take over your ability!
If we can find that out,
Guys!
Dragon-san will be pleased.
Excuse me...
I'm... still alive.
Scarlet?!
Usolan...d?
Scarlet!
Ace!
I take over your ability!
He threw us out into
the garden of the Rampart Tower!
The hero's still alive!
Scarlet!
You are...
We can't get near Doflamingo
as long as Pica is there!
Usopp!
Usoland! Thank you for everything!
Fire Fist!
Everything... went as planned!
Scarlet!!
Things are getting messier!
I-It's started...!
So cool!!
The Birdcage!
Issho-san, what should we do?!
Leave the rest... to my friends.
The battle has...
...just begun.
Okay!
Son of a bitch!
Scarlet!
Somebody's got shot!
Is it the King Riku Army again?!
THE UNDERGROUND TRADE PORT
Why?!
Why didn't you wait for me?!
Damn you Straw Hats!
Tontattas!
THE KING'S PLATEAU - IN
FRONT OF THE RAMPART TOWER
Thank you for knocking Sugar out!
I see!
How dare you free our servants!
I must've slipped out of your mind, too!
Help!
There's no way
I'm letting you get out of here!
Our promises...
Quite a ruckus.
I guess something is going on down there.
What?
...and memories, as well!
Run!
Captain, what's that?!
Usoland!
Anyway, where did he go?
Are you okay?!
How do I know?!
Let's get off of the island now!
The stone man!
Guys! Please look after Usopp!
Hm? You!
Even if we stay here and hurl
our anger at Doflamingo,
What?!
Huh? Who are you?!
we'll just be crushed in return!
Okay!
Let's run!
I'm Onepoko, the dog you've
been pushing around!
Captain! Watch out! Something's there!
Don't let him lay a finger on Usoland!
Doflamingo!
Hey, sorry! Let me through!
Just carry it, Onepoko!
Scarlet!!
Ouch!
You jerk!
What?! You are?!
You guys want to destroy the SMILE factory!
How dare you boss me around...
A-Are they blades?
What the...
What are these bars?
Scarlet! Stay with me!
How dare you turn us into toys!
...Like I was your slave!
Isn't that right, Nico Robin?!
Scarlet! Scarlet!
Now I'm gonna get my revenge!
Prepare to die, Doflamingo!
I can forgive everyone else but you!
Sticky-Sticky Chain!
It didn't work! We can't break it down!
Palace! Send some backup ASAP!
The pirates are out of...
What the hell is that?!
Scarlet! Stay with me!
Hey!
It's not enough yet!
Wait!
I don't know who you are but...
The Birdcage?
Guys!
Beat the hell out of Doflamingo's men!
What do you mean by that, Tra-guy?!
...my daughter is waiting for me, hungry.
Before the truth behind
this country is exposed,
A Giant!
Please...
Doflamingo's gone!
It's me! Kyros!
Hey! What's wrong?! Answer me! Hey!
Doflamingo is going to...
No way! It's impossible!
Please...
How could you treat me so violently?!
Dammit! Where did he go?! Doflamingo!
...kill everyone on the island!
You guys are the Little People.
What?!
You bastard!
I bet he hasn't made it that far yet!
Look for him!
Let me borrow him for a sec.
Esta!
There's a fence all over as far as I can see!
--Oh yeah!
--What?
Scarlet?
Scarlet!
--I have a boyfriend!
--Huh?!
Where is the exit?!
Usoland!
That was close.
You cheated on me!
I'm sorry! I forgot about you!
I was forgotten for a decade!
I hate Doflamingo!
Scarlet!!
What is that-dara?
I thought this was Doflamingo's stronghold.
Why was I targeted?
I can't believe I'm losing her like this!
He's hurt so bad.
He must've fought so hard to save us...
This is hell!
Vice Admiral Bastille!
I can't reach the Headquarters!
It's terrible!
Could it be...?!
Guys, look!
The toys must've turned back to their original forms!
They accomplished Operation SOP!
With these tin arms,
The same here!
I can't make contact with the base!
Take down Doflamingo!
I can't even feel
your warmth as you're dying!
We were fooled by Doflamingo!
We haven't reported anything yet!
I heard some of you have been living
as a toy for a decade.
--What?! They pulled it off?!
--Yeah, yeah! They did it, they did it!
What are you talking about?
He's a good king.
--That's great!
--They did it!
You just don't know who he really is!
Scarlet!!
How painful is that?
He's... a devil!
You'd better turn back to yourself
or you'll be targeted again!
Kill Doflamingo!
Oh! You're right!
Come on out, Doflamingo!
I've gotta pay you back
10 years' worth of pain!
You...
"YOU" ARE HURTING ME  "DO"N'T MOVE ME
Soldier-san!
Do...
Issho-san, what is happening here-dara?
Soldier-san!
Poof!
This must be...
--Soldier-san!
--Oh yes, Lady Viola!
I guess the tides have changed.
If it weren't for you,
we would've lived as toys forever!
Kanjuro! I'm coming to save you!
Are you alright?
We have a problem!
The darkness of this country must be
much deeper than I thought.
I see some enemies coming from the 1st floor!
We would've lived as their slaves!
It feels like our lives have been spared!
Koala!
The darkness-dara?
Hey! What did you shoot somebody's house?!
It's unforgivable!
Robin-san!
Take a good look, warriors!
So that was someone disguised as the Young Master!
I thought it was you! How've you been?!
I-I didn't want to! I can't control my body!
The Straw Hats and the others must be above the 2nd floor!
Great!
Sabo! Hack!
You all haven't changed a bit!
Violet's blood was on the wall!
This man is...
It's no good.
...the hero who broke the spell on us!
Yo!
Rather than being surrounded by enemies on both sides,
Hey! Stop!
--Kill Doflamingo's men!
--Let them all shed their blood!
Ro... R-R-R-R-R... Robin senpai?!
should we make
a surprise attack on Doflamingo now?
Vi...
STOP MO"VI"NG ME, I SAI"D"
Wh-What the...?! M-My body's...
Beautiful!
Did you see Luffy?
D...
Uh-huh.
Oh! The guy from earlier!
Usoland and the others can't make it, I guess.
Daddy!
He's one of our crew! He's Usopp!
Let's take our country back!
His name is...
Stop me! Please duck, everybody!
Bring down Doflamingo!
Come to think of it,
you guys are all pirates, aren't you?
H-Hi'm Ohahho (I'm Usopp).
Captain Usopp!!
He can stay down.
Afterwards, I noticed Fraland and Usoland were as well.
Usopp?! One of their crew?
Is that a problem for you?
Parasite String!
No, no, no, no!
No, I'm a notorious criminal, too.
Captain Usopp!!
I didn't see such a name
on their wanted posters!
If we have a common goal, it's nice to work with you.
THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
Thank you!!
There are some cracks
in the basement of the Colosseum!
All those hundreds of incredibly strong competitors fighting before the finals!
Help!
The structure has taken a lot of damage today!
And now, with Burgess's attacks!
This place won't last until it's over!
D-D-Don't tell me he is...!
Damn those pieces of shit!
What the hell is going on-dara?!
Usoland!
Shockwave Elbow!
What is wrong with you?
Sir, I have report!
There are people causing
Soldier-san is a brave man
THE ROYAL PALACE
Elbow! Elbow!
harm to others randomly
in different parts of Dressrosa!
He will always be by your side
You bastard!
--What happened?!
--The ceiling collapsed?!
Some of us Navy soldiers
are running wild, too!
--That bastard!
--Stop shooting at us!
How dare you kill the Young Master!
Soldier-san is a brave man
Prepare to be blown away!
If nothing is done, many citizens will die!
He will always be by your side
Nice!
What is it this time?!
I'll tell you again and again, Rebecca!
A heavenly light!
The one who shot and
killed your mother Scarlet...
Th-The King's Plateau is sinking down!
What?!
Dasu...!
D-D-Don't tell me
he is a messenger from heaven!
...was me!
Hey! If you attack her verbally like that,
my barrier doesn't mean anything!
Buffalo!
You asshole!
H-H-Hey! The ground is descending!
What's going on?!
Soldier-san!
It's Pica!
I'm hopeless!
Damn!
Mother-sama, I'm hungry.
Are we...
I'm gonna go buy something to eat.
Since he can merge with stones,
he can even shift the geography!
Uh-huh!
...witnessing a miracle?!
I'm too angry to even move!
The Royal Palace is going somewhere!
I had been forgetting everything!
THE TOY HOUSE
Stop, Royal Palace!
Tra-guy!
I'm Kyros! King Riku-sama!
I'm here to save you!
--Kyros?
--Yes!
Straw Hat?!
I'm glad that you're alive!
I'm sorry. It doesn't ring a bell.
S-So divine! He's like god!
You have no business here, Straw Hat!
What about the factory?!
Did you destroy it?!
Cyborg Franky has been silenced!
Now, I remember clearly!
Here's the key to his handcuffs!
U-Usopp! I know you can do it!
You have everything prepared!
The factory is going up!
H-Hey everybody, listen!
Wait, Straw Hat! Violet!
What?! What the hell is happening here?!
Set off the panic already!
You can't lay a finger on the Young Master...
God Usopp is gonna say something!
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
THE UNDERGROUND TRADE PORT
What?!
Somebody!
You...
Young Master?
Please stop me!
...people...
...will...
What... happened?
Special Attack: Green Star - Rapid-fire!
...be... gui...
The plateau of the Flower Field is...
...ded... b...
...rising up and pulling in the whole town!
King Riku-sama! Sorry to keep you waiting!
...y...
...me...
Don't-know-what-it-is-but-it's-some-kinda Special Attack!
Give me a minute! I'm gonna rescue you!
What?! Wh-What did he say?!
Thanks, but the alliance
between me and you guys is over!
PUT ME DOWN, "YOU" IDIOT
There's a fierce fight in the Executive Tower!
Get out of here!
You...
Who is he?!
Huh?! How selfish!
Usopp of the Straw Hats, go for it!
"PEOPLE" LIKE YOU ARE THE WORST
...people...
Brother Kyros!
I'll make those decisions,
not you, so shut your mouth!
...will...
"WILL" YOU STOP
I don't even know your face
but go at it, Usopp!
Even I lost my memories of him!
That makes you more selfish than me!
...be... gui...
HEY "BE"EFY "GUY", OPEN YOUR BLIN"DED" EYES
If you win, I'll be grateful to you for the rest of my life!
Unlock it!
What are you talking about?!
What do you mean?!
Oh yeah.
...ded...
Go for it!
...b... y...
"B"LOOD IS ALL OVER M"Y" FACE
Oh? Where did the soldier go?!
Go for it!
I don't wanna live as a toy
for the rest of my life!
--It's him.
--Huh? That's a human!
"ME"ATHEAD
...me...
If there's no alliance,
we're not on the same side!
If you can turn me back,
I won't go after Straw Hat!
The toys were originally humans
If you set me free, I'll kill you!
I'll become your subordinate or whatever!
Stick to it!
but they were erased from our memories!
"YOU" "PEOPLE" "WILL" "BE"
"GUY" "DED" "BY" "ME"
"You people will be guided by me"?!
Stop moving!
You can have all my money!
I'm counting on you!
It's hard to unlock it
since I can't touch Sea Prism Stone!
Since the Devil Fruit eater Sugar
passed out now,
"You people will be..."
we got our memories back!
"...guided by me"!
You can do it!
Clank.
You two are not listening to me!
Citizens and guests of Dressrosa.
Trebol!
Bring Sugar to the palace now!
So you really are...
I can't!
He's the former commander of
the King Riku Army - Kyros!
Why don't you do it?!
...sent from heaven...
I can't! I'm a Devil Fruit eater, too!
Relax, Doffy!
There'll be no unexpected problems!
I could have reigned over you all
with terror from the start.
to be our savior!
The strongest gladiator
in the history of the Colosseum!
God Usopp! God Usopp! God Usopp!...
That's the old man the statue is of!
Don't worry, Young Master.
Yes, that's him!
He's not even conscious now.
And he's also...
...Rebecca's biological father!
Usoland!
What?! She said she didn't know him!
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
When people forget about you,
there's nothing you can do
to make them remember you!
After finding out the truth,
You can have this poison grape back.
Usoland! Usoland!
I bet a great number of you want
to kill me now.
That's why he's just been watching over
his beloved daughter for a decade!
Guide us, God Usopp!
What are we supposed to do?!
--Oh, the Tatababasco grape!
--Our only hope!
Oh, the stone guy!
Pica!
That's why I prepared a game for you.
--He's right!
--It's our turn to help you!
You eat this.
We want to work for you!
I never thought I'd be taken in like this.
It's a game to kill me.
He has always been by her side,
day after day, as a toy soldier!
Please! Guide us! Show us the way!
I'm in the Royal Palace. I won't run or hide.
Mingo's alive!
--Young Master-sama!
--Young Master!
Drop dead.
The action we must take!
If you can take my life,
How could he still be alive?!
the game ends there, of course.
The whole country is thrown into chaos
after the toys have been freed.
But there is another way to finish the game.
Then, why don't you destroy
the factory behind me
Hey, who the hell are you?!
Here is how. You kill all the
people that I'm going to name now.
and rescue our little friends?
You are...!
And for whatever reason,
the Revolutionary Army is here secretly, too.
You're Kyros, aren't you?!
Yes, sir!
Also, I will award a large prize
for killing each one of them.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting
for a decade!
And the Royal Palace is a mess.
Now, I'm here to save you!
At your command!
Kill or get killed.
Whaaat?!
Everyone in this country will become hunters!
It's a difficult situation.
Hey Sugar, what are you doing?!
Usopp!
I have no choice but to use the "Birdcage."
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
Keep your senses!
The Birdcage?!
The only way for you to survive is...
Right, Law?
S-Sugar has...
I'm here to take back the real Dressrosa!
to kill somebody!
What the hell is wrong with...
...passed out!!
...these people?
Usopp creates a never-before-seen miracle!
Luffy lands in a fight with
Doflamingo, risen from the dead!
The Fire Fist finally returns!
The all-out battle at the Colosseum was
only a beginning!
Kyros takes down Doflamingo!
The mysterious man Lucy who inherits Ace's
Toys are turning back into humans one after
This sends unprecedented shock
waves throughout the Royal Palace
Now, the whole of Dressrosa has
In the heat of the fierce battle,
the worst extermination plan in the history begins,
will and power comes down into
the darkness of Dressrosa
become a battlefield and the
horrifying, life-or-death game is on!
another which throws Dressrosa into chaos!
and at the same time, the fight
at the Colosseum is about to
and when his astonishing
true identity is revealed,
In the midst of all that, Kyros, winner of an unprecedented 3000 matches,
Faced with an extreme situation where
citizens turn violent and try to kill him,
reach its dramatic climax!
meant to hide the true history of the country
and plunge the island into terror!
a new history of the three
brothers will begin!
The battle for the Flare-Flare Fruit
finally comes to an end!
now challenges Doflamingo pouring
his heart and soul into it!
Luffy moves to take down Doflamingo!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Devil's Trap! A Dressrosa Extermination Plan!"
"The Fire Fist Strikes!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Legend is Back! Kyros' All-out Blow!"
"Dashing onto the Scene!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The 500 Million Berry Man! Target: Usoland!"
The Chief of Staff of the Revolutionary Army, Sabo!"
The Flare-Flare Fruit Power Returns!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!