iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition - in
which a winner will get the Flare-Flare Fruit
as the prize - and won the first round
but now, he's heading for the palace
to take back Law who's
been captured by Doflamingo.
Meanwhile Kyros, who is now with Luffy,
remembers the gratitude he has for King Riku.
Stay away from him, King Riku-sama!
King Riku-sama!
Come with me!
Finally!
Finally - an unprecedented 1000th victory!
You're here again.
--Kyros.
--Go away!
You don't understand!
No matter where I go,
I'll be a beast...
...who killed men for the rest of my life!
I wish...
...everybody would forget about me!
Her name is Rebecca.
I shouldn't touch such an innocent thing!
My hands are tainted!
I don't wanna taint her!
Your father is a strange man, Rebecca.
You're like an angel, Rebecca!
I'll be watching over you!
I'll always be by your side!
What's going on?!
"The Operation Failed!
Usoland the Hero Dies?!"
Father-sama!
The palace is on fire!
What's going on in this country?
I'm gonna go to the palace!
Alright, Scarlet? Rebecca?
Father-sama!
If it gets dangerous here,
go to the Red Flower Field and wait there!
I'll come and get you at any cost!
Th-This is...
What happened?!
Open up!
It's me! Kyros!
Is anybody there?!
Guard! Open the gate!
I need to talk to King Riku!
Pirates?!
Brother Kyros!
Lady Viola!
Father-sama is...
King Riku-sama is okay.
What happened?!
It's...
The new king is waiting for you,
Army Commander Kyros.
The new king?!
--Let me lead the way to him.
--What did you do to King Riku-sama?!
Please follow me.
Lady Viola, come with me.
No.
You have to come on your own.
Could I have your weapon?
No, you can't!
Well done-in!
You're really gonna save my brother-in-law's life, too, aren't you?
Of course, we are!
Young Master-sama said
he might be useful-in!
If not, we would've killed him already-in!
So you've been working for the pirates, haven't you?!
We are here. Go on in.
Where's King Riku-sama?
Who are you?
He's here.
Oh no!
Sea Prism Stone?!
King Riku-sama!
What did you do...
...to this country and the king, pirate?!
The king set fire to the town.
Didn't you see it?
He'd never do such a thing!
Kyros!
Unlock these Sea Prism Stone chains!
I'm not a Devil Fruit eater!
Kyros. I've been hearing good things about you.
They say you're the strongest gladiator in the Colosseum.
Swear fealty to me.
The king has been dethroned and all members of the old royal family will die!
I've already sent my men to your wife and daughter
who are part of the royal line!
Watch what I'm gonna do!
The King Riku Family is
no longer governing Dressrosa!
He cut off his own leg!
Kyros!
A toy?
The toy put the king on his shoulder and escaped-dasuyan!
I got turned into a toy!
What happened to me?!
Am I dreaming?!
I'm Kyros! King Riku-sama!
--Kyros?
--Yes!
I'm sorry. It doesn't ring a bell. But...
...I'll never forget what you did for me!
You're a strange toy.
Run!
Scarlet! Rebecca!
Wait for me at the rendezvous point!
TWO DAYS LATER
Nobody knows my name.
Did they all forget about me?!
I've gotta get to the Red Flower Field!
Scarlet and Rebecca are waiting for me!
Scarlet?!
Scarlet!
Scarlet!!
Somebody's got shot!
Is it the King Riku Army again?!
Why?!
Why didn't you wait for me?!
I see!
I must've slipped out of your mind, too!
Our promises...
...and memories, as well!
Scarlet!!
Scarlet! Stay with me!
Scarlet! Scarlet!
I don't know who you are but...
...my daughter is waiting for me, hungry.
Please...
It's me! Kyros!
Scarlet?
Scarlet!
Scarlet!!
I can't believe I'm losing her like this!
This is hell!
It's terrible!
With these tin arms,
I can't even feel
your warmth as you're dying!
Scarlet!!
Soldier-san!
--Soldier-san!
--Oh yes, Lady Viola!
Are you alright?
We have a problem!
I see some enemies coming from the 1st floor!
It's unforgivable!
So that was someone disguised as the Young Master!
The Straw Hats and the others must be above the 2nd floor!
Violet's blood was on the wall!
It's no good.
Rather than being surrounded by enemies on both sides,
should we make
a surprise attack on Doflamingo now?
Usoland and the others can't make it, I guess.
Come to think of it,
you guys are all pirates, aren't you?
Afterwards, I noticed Fraland and Usoland were as well.
Is that a problem for you?
No, I'm a notorious criminal, too.
If we have a common goal, it's nice to work with you.
THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
There are some cracks
in the basement of the Colosseum!
All those hundreds of incredibly strong competitors fighting before the finals!
The structure has taken a lot of damage today!
And now, with Burgess's attacks!
This place won't last until it's over!
Shockwave Elbow!
Elbow! Elbow!
--That bastard!
--Stop shooting at us!
Nice!
I'll tell you again and again, Rebecca!
The one who shot and
killed your mother Scarlet...
...was me!
Hey! If you attack her verbally like that,
my barrier doesn't mean anything!
Soldier-san!
I'm hopeless!
Mother-sama, I'm hungry.
I'm gonna go buy something to eat.
Uh-huh!
I'm too angry to even move!
THE TOY HOUSE
Cyborg Franky has been silenced!
U-Usopp! I know you can do it!
Set off the panic already!
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
THE UNDERGROUND TRADE PORT
Special Attack: Green Star - Rapid-fire!
Don't-know-what-it-is-but-it's-some-kinda Special Attack!
There's a fierce fight in the Executive Tower!
Usopp of the Straw Hats, go for it!
I don't even know your face
but go at it, Usopp!
If you win, I'll be grateful to you for the rest of my life!
Go for it!
I don't wanna live as a toy
for the rest of my life!
If you can turn me back,
I won't go after Straw Hat!
I'll become your subordinate or whatever!
Stick to it!
You can have all my money!
I'm counting on you!
Trebol!
Bring Sugar to the palace now!
Relax, Doffy!
There'll be no unexpected problems!
Don't worry, Young Master.
He's not even conscious now.
Usoland!
You can have this poison grape back.
--Oh, the Tatababasco grape!
--Our only hope!
You eat this.
Drop dead.
Whaaat?!
Hey Sugar, what are you doing?!
Keep your senses!
S-Sugar has...
...passed out!!
Usopp creates a never-before-seen miracle!
Toys are turning back into humans one after
another which throws Dressrosa into chaos!
In the midst of all that, Kyros, winner of an unprecedented 3000 matches,
now challenges Doflamingo pouring
his heart and soul into it!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Legend is Back! Kyros' All-out Blow!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!