iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass, We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed everyday, Go east, Go west!
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel something - that's the treasure
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of burning, intense excitement!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
omoi no mama mezasu basho e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
They freed the toys who had
been forced to labor as slaves
They freed the toys who had been forced to
labor as slaves
Usopp knocked Sugar out
They freed the toys who had been forced to
labor as slaves
and freed the toys who had been forced to labor as slaves
and freed the toys who had
been forced to labor as slaves
but Doflamingo trapped everybody
in the country in the Birdcage
but Doflamingo trapped everybody in the country
in the Birdcage
in the Birdcage.
but Doflamingo confined everybody in the country in the Birdcage.
and put prices on the heads
of Luffy and 11 others.
Cien Fleurs!
Now, let's bring an end to everything.
Think!
Now, those of you who rebel
against our family...
You have no time to wonder what to do.
You either come to kill me or
side with us Don Quixote Family
Spider Net!
People are falling and
towns are burning moment by moment.
What?
I-It's started...!
I'm gonna fight you!
The Birdcage!
and punish the 12 fools who rebel against me.
Either you kill me...
Bartolomeo-san! Hack-san!
...or kill the 12 criminals.
We can climb up from here!
His voice! It's so high!
I'm gonna crush you all at once!
If you make the wrong decision,
the game will not end.
Now the game is on!
Doflamingo is going to...
Hasshoken Secret Technique!
Drill Dragon...
I'll pay 100 million berries
for each star rating!
Run!
Our plan was to destroy the SMILE factory
...kill everyone on the island!
100 million berries?!
King...
and provoke a conflict between
Doflamingo and Kaido.
These are the criminals in Dressrosa!
Run! It's gonna crush you up!
"The 500 Million Berry Man!
Target: Usoland!"
...Punch!
But if we kill Doflamingo now,
...Nail!
First, the One-stars...
Kaido will direct all his anger over losing SMILEs,
Luffy!
REBECCA
A CONVICT GLADIATOR OF THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
(KING RIKU'S GRANDDAUGHTER)
NICO ROBIN - A PIRATE OF THE STRAW HATS
"DEMON CHILD"
Damn you!
...at us!
FOXFIRE KIN'EMON - A SAMURAI
FROM THE WANO KINGDOM
Then we'll have to fight face-to-face
with the angry Emperor!
VIOLA - THE FORMER PRINCESS OF DRESSROSA
Luffy!!
CYBORG FRANKY - A PIRATE OF THE STRAW HATS
That's not an issue now.
Damn! It's as steady as rock!
Move aside!
Next, the Two-stars...
"Gathering into a Powerful Front!
Luffy and a Group of Brutal Warriors!"
How about this?!
Take a good look at this country!
If I stop now, what's gonna happen to it?!
KYROS - THE FORMER ARMY
COMMANDER OF DRESSROSA
PIRATE HUNTER ZORO - A
PIRATE OF THE STRAW HATS
"Steady Progress!
Luffy's Army vs. Pica!"
How's that?!
Issho-san, don't we need
to capture Doflamingo?
And as for key figures of each group,
Restrain as many out-of-control people
as possible
What?! What?!
I give them three stars!
and focus on Straw Hat and
Law's pirate alliance!
M-My hand...
SABO - THE CHIEF OF STAFF
OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
STRAW HAT LUFFY - A PIRATE
THE CAPTAIN OF THE STRAW HATS
--My hand - it's slipping!
--What?!
Daddy!
What?!
TRAFALGAR LAW - THE CAPTAIN OF "THE HEART PIRATES"
THE WARLORD(TENTATIVE), "SURGEON OF DEATH"
Pica-sama!
Somebody! Stop me!
Send that message to all units!
RIKU DOLDO III - THE FORMER KING OF DRESSROSA
I won't let you fall!
Plus, there is the man who
pissed me off the most today!
It's all his fault that you people have to
play such a bloody game!
Stop it.
Usoland!
Nobody's gonna come to help.
Nobody can get out of this Birdcage.
--What a big piece of shit!
--There is nothing that my drill head can't grind!
He who shoots oft at last
shall not hit the mark.
The one who kills him will get...
Th-Thank you, Leo!
Hello? Hello?!
...500 million berries!
Run!
You can't make contact with
anyone out there.
That was close.
"GOD" USOPP - A PIRATE OF THE STRAW HATS
The Navy admiral!
You're all going to die
and no one out there will know it.
But what was that?
What caused the big shake?
These are nothing against my drill head!
The gambling old man!
--Your neighbors who are running wild...
--Don't! Daddy!
I got it back thanks to him.
"With a Rumbling of the Ground!
The God of Destruction - Giant Pica Descends!"
F... Five...
--...will keep harming others randomly.
--Somebody, please stop me!
Soldier-san?! He turned back
to a human, too, didn't he?!
Or I'm gonna kill my own kids!
That was close!
Go Moocy! To the Palace!
It doesn't matter if it's their family or close friends
Tell me, Lucy, what kind of a man is he?!
Don't get hit!
We're counting on you, Moocy!
What kind of a man?!
What are you talking about?!
or citizens who they swore to protect.
I can't believe it...
Hey! I told you not to come with me!
Get off of Moocy!
I'm scared!
Don't do it!
That one-legged soldier was...
I can't control my body!
Somebody, please! Stop me!
Whoa, don't say that! Please!
...your father!
Straw Hat-san! Please let us!
Until the day you are filled with happiness,
Get away from me! Everybody!
Moocy! We're counting on you!
I will always be by your side!
Where did he go?! Straw Hat!
I thought so...
The town got squashed.
I promise I'll kick Doflamingo's ass for you!
If he throws another one,
it'll be dangerous to be here!
Hey! Don't let them through!
They're heading to the Palace!
So stay with my friends!
Let's run!
To where?!
His fist can reach the edge of the town!
Outta our way!
I'm gonna bring an end to
this stupid game in no time!
Get out of our way!
I'm gonna go kick Doflamingo's ass!
Get out of my way!
So survive! Okay?!
Issho-san!
Sai and Boo?!
Uh-huh!
In the name of the Happosui Army,
we'll repay our debt!
You are quite brash. But...
Even if you run or hide,
"Breaking through Enemy Lines!
Luffy and Zoro Launch the Counter-Attack!"
...I'm not going to step aside.
there is no safe place in the cage.
I'm gonna fight you guys!
Ideo the champion fighter?!
The terror of the Birdcage will go on for days.
You wanna fight?
Don't let Straw Hat get away!
What an unpleasant chore this is.
It's a matter of which happens sooner.
You all die or you finish the game.
You better pay attention!
Destruction Cannon!
If you wanna stop me,
bring out some stronger guys!
What's wrong with these guys?!
With a single blow...
Luffy! Law!
C-Commodore Orlumbus!
Damn that Doflamingo!
You can't anticipate his next move!
Where are you?!
You're in my way! Commodore...
I can't believe it!
The factory went up and is gone now!
...Hug!
--But this is definitely a good chance for us!
--We can get out!
Luffy, who are you with now?
Hey!
Shoot Straw Hat!
Zoro!
I'm with Zoro and Tra-guy. And...
--We finally can get out from underground!
--Thank you, God Usopp!
Next, I'm gonna execute you!
Hey!
Riku Doldo III, and I'm Viola.
THE ROYAL PALACE
We're up here! Up here!
Advance!
--Why are they teaming up?!
--Execution is my repayment!
Doflamingo-sama!
--What?!
--King Riku-sama!
Luffy!
Robin-dono!
Straw Hat Luffy and the
others are clashing with
I got hanged!
Kin'emon!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Viola-sama's there, too?!
Wait, Hajrudin! If you kill Straw Hat,
you'll get a lot of money!
Let me down now!
Fujitora and Navy soldiers at this very moment!
Okay, so there are five of you.
On my side, we have...
That's just a pittance!
I almost had my pride stolen
A-An iron breast-band?!
This is quite a foreign culture.
What?!
Is that so? Let them fight.
Get off of me now!
What's wrong, Robin?
Sorry, sorry!
Love it!
but was saved by God Usopp!
The Navy and the pirates,
I can truly win my pride back,
only by repaying my debt!
What's wrong with you?!
Trying to hurt me?!
if you allow me to create havoc...
--Huh?
--Don't give me "Huh?"!
--The voice!
--His voice is...
Anyway, I'm going to move there
with Usopp and Rebecca.
I can take care all of them by myself!
--I will take down Doflamingo!
--No, I will!
Boy, how reckless can you be?
R-Robin-senpai, let me be your slave!
I mean, can I ask you something?
--No, it's me!
--No, me!
Laughing at Pica's voice means death.
PICA - A TOP EXECUTIVE
OF THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY
I said it's me!
Th-That guy's nose...
Do you know what you're doing,
Straw Hat-ya?
His voice is so high!
It looks like Sniper King-senpai's,
Cabbage!
How could a giant man like that
have such voice!
Our plan was to destroy the SMILE factory
I realized my destiny again.
who is known for shooting out the flag on the Tower of Law!
Oh no... I still can't get used to it
It's him. His name is Usopp.
even though I've heard it so many times!
I get a chance to bring down a Warlord.
and provoke a conflict between
Doflamingo and Kaido.
But if I burst out laughing, he'll kill me!
Look how far we've got!
I can get the better of
these annoying rookies all at once!
But if we kill Doflamingo now,
We're in no hurry.
Kaido will direct all his anger over losing SMILEs,
Where are we?
There'll be stories about me
in the newspapers everyday!
I don't know.
There he is!
You see, this game is like an
election to select the king.
I think we got even farther away
from the Royal Palace.
...at us!
And Robin-senpai was moved by
the action of her pirate group...
I'm destined to be a top star!
Then we'll have to fight face-to-face
with the angry Emperor!
...that turned the world against them
in order to save one of their friends!
Damn that stone assimilation human!
"Ah! When Cavendish-sama is
on the front page of the newspaper,
I asked the nation of Dressrosa.
Who is more fit to be their king?
Is it the Riku Family or the Don Quixote Family?
He ended up being even bigger than Oars!
That makes them
the Enies Lobby Shoot-out Duo!
it looks as gorgeous as a work of art!"
If only I knew how to beat him...
Oh yeah? How about having me on all pages,
not just the front page?
Yes! Yes! Oh, yes!
People choose their king.
It's their legitimate right.
Straw Hat.
What are you excited for?! You geek!
Shut your mouth!
"That's a good idea!
Only you could come up with that!"
Well, the problem is
whether they can take a good picture of me.
It's bothersome!
Cabbage!
That's not an issue now.
You idiot!
Do you want him to kill you?!
Because I'm brighter than
a camera flash, so...!
We should just get rid of all the pests!
You're Pirate Hunter Zoro, aren't you?
Take a good look at this country!
If I stop now, what's gonna happen to it?!
I got my arm broken by this fool?!
--Go away!
--Shut up!
And Trafalgar...
Hold it! You have to hold it!
Alright, I hand them over to you.
Good-bye!
...Law!
All we have to do is
repel the ones who are coming
Now! Shoot!
Although they're little, they're quite good warriors.
and sit back and watch the
others kill each other.
Blade of Beauty, Swan Lake!
Give me back...
Thank you, Topknot-land!
We found them passed out
in a hallway at the Palace!
...my glory, you scoundrels
of the Worst Generation!
Doffy! I...
Catch all the criminals and
bring an end to this game!
I guess they laid their lives on the line
for the commander.
Look for the criminals!
What are you doing?! He's with me now!
Catching them is the only
way for us to survive!
Cub-san! Rampo! I'm proud of you all!
No, I'm not!
What?! Do you still hold
a grudge against me?!
Whoa! I-I'm sorry, Pica-sama!
There they come!
--Did you find one?!
--No, I didn't see any of them!
Please forgive him!
What?!
He's new and he was sort
of taken by surprise...
Somebody, stop me!
My body's out of control!
--Go to sleep, weaklings!
--Do you want me to kick you to death first?!
When you find the criminals,
tell everyone immediately!
No, I'm not gonna go after
you Straw Hats anymore.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
--You guys are not strong enough!
--What?!
I'm gonna bury you alive!
You'll be stuck in stones...
Somebody!
Because one of your crew,
God Usopp, saved my life!
You need another 100 years of training to get strong enough
to repay your debt!
Somebody, stop me!
Wait, Pica-sama!
This is exactly like the incident
on that night 10 years ago!
I will take down Doflamingo!
Armsmorphosis!
That was close! Don't let your guard down!
Usopp did?
No, I'll take him down!
I'll get all the attention!
That's right! I won't ever
forget the brave image of him
I can't control my body!
Gatling Girl!
Let me return them the favor!
Now...
when he saved hundreds, sacrificing his life!
Don't follow me, I said! Go away!
I know!
Poor people...
On that night,
King Riku-sama was... the King Riku Army was...
Although I didn't see it.
--Back off, idiot!
--You back off, shithead!
Well, I'm happy when
somebody says nice things about my friends.
Keep walking!
Execution!
If you handle it,
you'll destroy his body completely!
Oh yeah!
It's my chance!
It's not your chance!
Issho-san, don't we need
to capture Doflamingo?
...manipulated by...
It's my chance to become a top star!
Trafalgar.
I said "Go away"!
This is your hat, isn't it?
I found it in front of the Colosseum.
Restrain as many out-of-control
people as possible
...manipulated by Doflamingo!!
I will kick Mingo's ass!
Then his family can't bury him.
Thank you, Baby 5!
Let me put it on you.
and focus on Straw Hat and
Law's pirate alliance!
What is wrong with these fools?!
Come closer, now!
Scream! Hate! Suffer!
What?!
I don't trust you!
Send that message to all units!
You people are innocent victims!
Well, who cares. I'm busy now anyway.
Alright, let's go!
Do you wanna know why I'm busy?
Wait! I'm still cuffed!
Help...
No.
They'll come off.
All right, I'll tell you if you insist!
No, they won't!
--I'm gonna get the key!
--Do you know where it is?!
I've decided to kill Doflamingo to
return you guys the favor!
You.
Stop me!
Y-Y-Yes, sir!
Do you have a family?
When we fell, I saw...
What? Yes, I do.
What?!
How about you?
Leave the rest to me and go hide somewhere...
Oh, yes, me too.
No thanks! I'm gonna do it!
I lost my mother when I was eight
and killed my father when I was ten.
Stop it... Doflamingo!
I have to return Rebecca the favor
for buying me lunch!
Your reason to fight was food?!
Think!
Cut it out! I know you're trying to fool me!
You either come to kill me or
side with us Don Quixote Family
You plan on stealing more attention
by killing Doflamingo, don't you?!
The members who are ranked
It must be somewhere on this plateau!
and punish the 12 fools who rebel against me.
as executives and above are
my family who I've been
The spotlight?!
What are you talking about?!
I'll find it and... What?!
through thick and thin with.
Think about it.
If you take down a vicious pirate like Doflamingo,
newspapers won't leave you alone!
If you make the wrong decision,
the game will not end.
They are all I've got!
How should we get there?
Go straight!
I won't forgive anyone who laughs at my family!
I'll pay 100 million berries for each star rating!
A flood of people will come to hear your story
from morning 'til night!
--Is he gonna jump off?!
--No way!
Got it?
100 million berries?!
Y-Yes, sir!
These are the criminals in Dressrosa!
"Hello, superstar!"
Look up!
Wait for me, Doflamingo!
The Five-star - Usopp is in the Colosseum!
Did you call me "superstar"? Oh, please!
He's gonna throw another one!
First, the One-stars...
That way! Go after him!
Straw Hat!!
"What do you want?"
REBECCA
A CONVICT GLADIATOR OF THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
(KING RIKU'S GRANDDAUGHTER)
Kill him!
"Cavendish-san! What do you think of
the situation regarding pirates in recent years?"
"Oh? You're there, aren't you?!
Cavendish-san?!"
--How annoying!
--I'll take him down again and again!
So many people are coming out of
the basement of the Colosseum!
NICO ROBIN - A PIRATE OF THE STRAW HATS
"DEMON CHILD"
Leave me alone!
Don't do it, guys!
Even if you break his arm again,
he can restore it!
What's wrong? I'm right in front of you!
Usoland is a man of 500 million!
Everybody wants him!
Wh-What the hell is going on?!
Because of the geographical shift,
the basement has surfaced to the ground above!
If you can't figure out how his power works,
it's just a waste of your energy!
"You are?! But I can't see you
because you're so bright!"
FOXFIRE KIN'EMON
- A SAMURAI FROM THE WANO KINGDOM
That's our legendary hero!
Then, what should we do?
I bet they are the ones who were forced
to work at the underground port!
Is it too shiny for you?! I'm sorry!
But I can't hide my brilliance!
It's not something to be proud of!
You're a military tactician, aren't you?!
Can't you come up with some tactics?
But I have to accept it.
Soldiers!
I'd say...
"Wow! You really are a star!"
VIOLA - THE FORMER PRINCESS OF DRESSROSA
Nobody can help chasing after a star...
Officials!
Alright.
Pirates!
I'd say...
like me.
Let's go.
I-I can't believe that many people
were enslaved, unnoticed by anyone!
So cool!
Run!!
A round of applause!
You're a tactician, aren't you?!
Come up with a better strategy!
Now, burn my image into your mind as
much as you want! I am a superstar!
CYBORG FRANKY - A PIRATE OF THE STRAW HATS
--You guys...
--Stop fooling around and hurry up!
Shut up!
Retreat is a viable strategy! Just run!
Robin-san, how can we get
to the King's Plateau?!
Where's Straw Hat?
Because of the geographical
shift, the outer wall of
Next, the Two-stars...
the Colosseum is connected to the plateau!
KYROS - THE FORMER ARMY COMMANDER OF DRESSROSA
If we climb from there,
we can meet up with the others!
Maynard!
Who told you to fight in
the competition-dara?!
Found them!
Let's see!
Dammit! This is nothing!
They're increasing in number!
That was out of line!
PIRATE HUNTER ZORO
- A PIRATE OF THE STRAW HATS
This is it! Prepare to be crushed to death!
You could have been killed!
I don't see Straw Hat's dead body!
That's good!
I'm gonna take care of them all at once!
But Bastille-san, I got to see everything
that's been going on here because of it!
--Hack-san?!
--Leave them up to me!
A-Army Commander Kyros!
Straw Hat!!
Get out of our way!
You money-blinded idiots!
I forgot about him, the invincible gladiator!
MAYNARD THE PURSUER
A VICE ADMIRAL OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
(A CONTENDER OF THE GLADIATORIAL COMPETITION)
If we can take Doflamingo into custody,
Maybe, it's been completely destroyed
or it got blown away.
I can't believe you people
knuckle under to Doflamingo!
the world may turn for the
better, even if only a little!
There are pirates, too! It's the Straw Hats!
Where's Issho-san?!
I didn't know the executive of the Family, Violet, was Princess Viola!
Four Thousand Brick Fist!
Or he got away.
IN THE UNDERGROUND TRADE PORT
--It's impossible to run through him head on!
--Maybe, we should just take a detour!
And as for key figures of each group,
He's really blocking our way!
Where did you go? Straw Hat!
We can't get to the Palace
unless we stop him!
There they are!
I give them three stars!
His voice! It's so high!
Hey! Where did Straw Hat go?!
--Rebecca, you go ahead!
--Robin-san!
SABO - THE CHIEF OF STAFF OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
--I can't see him anywhere!
--Maybe he got crushed along with the bull!
They are ours!
I'm glad to be back.
Where are you, Straw Hat?!
I can conduct investigations
without any interruption.
STRAW HAT LUFFY - A PIRATE
THE CAPTAIN OF THE STRAW HATS
Bartolomeo!
I'm thrilled to hear
Robin-senpai call my name!
What's that?!
I-I'm gonna hold the enemies back here
TRAFALGAR LAW - THE CAPTAIN OF "THE HEART PIRATES"
THE WARLORD(TENTATIVE), "SURGEON OF DEATH"
There he is!
so please go ahead with Sniper King-senpai!
These are...
Thank you!
RIKU DOLDO III - THE FORMER KING OF DRESSROSA
Robin-senpai thanked me!
Find him! Let me know if he's still alive!
I'm all fired up now!
I'm not gonna let anyone go after them!
This trading ship from the
Kingdom of Biggschots has been
disguised as a pirate ship.
I won't let him reach Doffy!
300 million!
This port seems like a place where
secrets from various countries come together.
Yeehaw!
Law and Straw Hat...
Their pirate alliance has just startled the world!
We're on the fast track! Yeah!
Luffy, you know that strange guy we just met?
What are we gonna do after all of that?!
What?! He's climbing up his arm!
Don't stand in my way!
King Riku!
There are a bunch of Navy soldiers out there!
Oh, you mean Cabbage?
Keep going! Moocy!
King Riku-sama... He was alive!
Cabbage?
Are you kidding? Is that a name?
We're in big trouble once they find out about
our trade with Doflamingo!
There's a big gun from the Revolutionary Army!
He's the Chief of Staff!
I met him at the Colosseum.
I know! That's why we came back!
There were a whole bunch of
strange people besides him!
--They knew about you already!
--I'm a target, too?!
You used the strange technique again!
But we can't get out of here with the ship
because of...
Oh yeah?
--Can't believe it!
--Is he crazy?! That fool!
There they are!
One 200-million and two 300-millions!
We just need to destroy all the evidence.
He's making a bigger scene than me!
Wh-What a relief.
They haven't found out about me.
Along with this ship!
Don't let them get away!
I can't believe it!
--Alright? Now get down to it!
--Yes, sir!
Let's get to the Palace like this!
Plus, there is the man who
pissed me off the most today!
Take this!
Gum-Gum...
That's right! Run, bull, run!
I won't let you do that!
...Whip!
Who are you?!
Two-Sword Style!
It's all his fault that you people have to
play such a bloody game!
Rhino Cycle!
Hey.
The one who kills him will get...
Yes?
--Cut the "Run, bull, run" crap!
--Yes?
There they are!
One Two-star and two Three-stars!
--Get off! You're making it harder for Moocy to run!
--Oh, yes.
Excuse us for not introducing ourselves sooner.
I'm Jeet and the big guy behind me is...
Oh no... We have no role to play here.
We got more!
Hey, Luffy!
If we fight them all, it'll take forever!
...500 million berries!
Let's go back to
the Young Master-sama for now-in!
I'm Abdullah.
"GOD" USOPP - A PIRATE OF THE STRAW HATS
--Did I ask your names?
--Whoa-whoa!
All right.
Oh? Where did Señor go?
--Let's go!
--Okay!
Take it easy, sir!
There you are, Straw Hat!
You know how he is-in.
Get out of my way!
He must be looking for that pervert
Hey!
Boy...
Don't stand in my way!
to have some kind of a hard-boiled face-off-in!
I said "Get off"!
Straw Hat-san...
--Get out of my way!
--That voice is...
You can't burn all this crucial evidence!
A hard-boiled face-off?
Wait, Garp's grandson!
500 million!
DON CHIN JAO - THE HAPPOSUI ARMY (A GANG)
--Straw Hat!
--He's pissed!!
I don't have to work for the rest of my life!
Wait for me, Little People!
SAI - THE LEADER OF THE
HAPPOSUI ARMY (A GANG)
I won't let you go any closer to Doffy!
We've been looking for you, you bastard!
Don't do it!
Five?!!
I'm gonna super destroy the SMILE factory
--I-I'm sorry!
--Honey!
BOO - THE VICE LEADER OF
THE HAPPOSUI ARMY (A GANG)
You can't get away from us!
F... F... Five...
and save you all!
Guys! Get away from me!
Oh! His arm!
Why, Issho-san?!
Ugh! I thought so!
Now we're here but...
Straw Hat! He has nowhere to hide
as long as he's on the giant's arm!
--Wait!
--Oh no! Run!
Oh... Oh no, Usoland is...
How do we climb up there?
Doflamingo can't keep his position
as a Warlord after this!
Huh? What's the matter?!
Straw Hat-san?!
We have to capture him now!
Why are you running?!
Count on me.
Third Gear!
The Five-star!
Cien Fleurs!
They are all persistent!
There are two One-stars
and one Three-star there!
--Wait!
--They just won't give up!
Spider Net!
Sabo-kun, what should we do?
Why can't you wait?!
Armament Hardening!
Let's go above ground! Everybody, run!
Head-Arms!
God Usopp! I'm sorry but I need to kill you!
The Five-star! 500 million!
I said wait, Garp's grandson...
The Navy has been doing
It's massive! We're finished!
the same thing over and
over again just like that!
Th-They were worshiping me
until a few minutes ago!
We have nowhere to run!
Awesome!
A round of applause!
Damn! Please run!
You have been in the Navy for a long time
haven't you, Vice Admiral-san?
Y-You guys did it again...
Yes, sir!
--Leo, you guys go first!
--Okay!
Robin-dono!
I'm gonna go look for Kanjuro so excuse me!
Bartolomeo-san! Hack-san!
Weren't you even listening all this time?
We can climb up from here!
Be careful!
To these screams filled with anger?
There comes the punch!
Let's go.
He can't ward it off in the air!
It's gonna hit him!
If I climb up there,
There's one, too!
They are not crying! They are angry!
I can see Luffy-senpai and
Zoro-senpai, can't I?!
The One-star samurai! 100 million berries!
Straw Hat!
I'm so excited!
Gum-Gum...
This is so annoying!
Don't get me wrong, Garp's grandson.
...Grizzly Magnum!
Does the World Government...
Th-The Little Person told me
there's a junkyard down there!
I don't hold a grudge against
your family anymore.
The key to Law's handcuffs
should be somewhere...
pretend to be God or something?!
Are you really there, Kanjuro?!
He did it!
What? Really?
He's breaking apart?!
We originally came to this country to
take down Doflamingo's business.
--100 million berries is mine!
--Okay, let's just go!
Pica-sama!
He fell! The samurai fell down into the hole!
There it is!
I need you to honor my decisions.
We don't care about prizes!
We don't work for
such a small amount of money!
Yeah!
Father-sama, Rebecca and
the others are down there!
You have no time to wonder what to do.
I was saved by not just you
but one of your crew, God Usopp.
What?!
There is the criminal!
People are falling and
towns are burning moment by moment.
Catch her!
--Usopp saved you?
--Indeed.
Either you kill me...
Stop it!
Therefore, I have made
up my mind to return you
...or kill the 12 criminals.
and God Usopp the favor
by taking down Doflamingo.
Law and the others' target
is the SMILEs, isn't it?
You're...!
Don't do it!
I'm gonna kick Doflamingo's ass!
Those infamous strong men
who came out of the Colosseum are...
Hey Doffy! Don't we have
to protect the factory?
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
(THE SUNFLOWER FIELD)
Now the game is on!
Tank!
...heading to the Palace where Doflamingo is,
along with Straw Hat.
Rebecca-sama!
I, Tank, will guard you with my life!
They can't open the doors.
I see.
They're all made of Sea Prism Stone.
What did you just say?!
I knew those notorious scoundrels
wouldn't play by the rules but...
I said "Don't do it"!
Because I'm gonna do it!
And I have the keys to the factory here.
Oh! That's Captain Tank!
What?!
Are you going to disregard my kindness?!
King Riku-sama!
...I didn't expect them to join forces.
--Young Master-sama?!
--You know what you're doing?!
I'm glad that he's okay!
HAJRUDIN - A WARRIOR OF ELBAPH
There you are! Straw Hat Luffy!
Excuse me.
Could I borrow that for a while?
Grandfather-sama!
The enemies don't need hope.
Oh! You!
Rebecca!
What?
Let's just forget what happened in the match!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
How powerless.
For my pride as a warrior of Elbaph,
I can't believe you couldn't even
protect this little girl, Trebol.
What should we do?!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring... Clank.
We just found out that
King Riku-sama was innocent!
I will kill Doflamingo and return you guys the favor!
Wait for me, everybody!
Vice Admiral Bastille!
There is an emergency call!
Shut up, "g"eezer!
She's not really a little girl!
I will take back the real Dressrosa!
--Now it's you...
--Cut it out!
I can't answer them all at once-dara!
If we citizens all act together,
maybe we can take down Doflamingo...
We keep getting calls from soldiers
who got blown away to distant places by Pica!
Hey hey, Doffy!
I'm really sorry about Sugar!
We of the Prodence Kingdom have...
ELIZABELLO II - THE KING OF PRODENCE
...long been in debt to King Riku!
Vice Admiral Bastille!
There is an emergency call for you!
I didn't expect a guy with his hands
and feet bound would knock out Sugar!
It's not just him!
I will bring down Doflamingo!
Who's that?! Can't this wait?!
In order to kill Doflamingo,
I-It's... It's me.
DAGAMA - A MILITARY TACTICIAN
Th-That's what he says!
we have to fight the 2000 soldiers of the Doflamingo Family!
I-Issho-san?!
--How could I see it coming?
--The same can be said for the Flare-Flare Fruit!
We don't want any prize!
Sir! How can I help you?! Where are you now?!
What are we supposed to do then?
Even King Riku-sama is in the 12 criminal list!
No, we are the ones who will kill that jerk!
I didn't expect the No.2 of the Revolutionary Army
Tough competitors from the Colosseum
JEET AND ABDULLAH
The heavenly light shone down on God!
have allied and are on the move, I heard.
was fighting in the competition.
Are we gonna do wrong by the innocent king again?
A-Are you okay?
How could I know?!
It's hard to forget after all!
Thank you.
The whole town is in chaos now
Right, right!
Let me make a confession!
and they're running wild
together! It's the worst-dara!
I think we don't have to kill them!
Wait, wait!
ORLUMBUS - A COMMODORE OF A FLEET
Don't make excuses!
How ungraceful! Idiots!
--Is this the junkyard?
--Yeah.
If you're talking about Doflamingo,
I will take him down!
No, actually, it's favorable for us.
We can just take them into custody!
Just 12 of them!
As its name suggests,
there's trash everywhere.
Un"g"raceful... There's the "G"!
"DESTRUCTION CANNON" IDEO
Destruction is my repayment!
We have no choice! Let's fight!
Wh-What do you mean-dara?!
Hey, what's going on out there?!
SULEIMAN
Let bygones be bygones.
It's my job to execute someone!
--Yeah!
--You're right!
I'm not sure either.
Even if I blame you two,
we can't change the past.
Vice Admirals all over the island,
I need reinforcements as soon as possible.
BLUE GILLY - THE LONGFEET TRIBE
No! I will take out Doflamingo!
Anyway, do you people know
a samurai warrior named Kanjuro?
One of the 12 criminals is
knocked out over here.
Right! That's our boss!
Where are all these idiots coming from?
Kanjuro?
It's time for us to take action.
Don't forget about me!
What?!
Nice try, Lao G!
Where did Cyborg Franky go?
He was down on the ground.
I'll let you forgive me if you insist!
Meet me at the foot of the Royal Palace!
What the...
Here comes the annoying one.
But Doffy, when it comes down
to it, the Navy is an obstacle.
There he is!
What should we do with Fujitora?
Show yourself, Kyros!
I'm back on my feet
with backup cola for destroying the factory!
I already talked to him.
The game won't be over until
we catch all of you criminals!
What the hell!
Hey, do you guys really wanna...
What's going on?!
The Navy won't come after us.
You have to leave the task of
killing Doflamingo up to us!
I have a family!
I beg you! Let me catch you!
Look! There's one of the Straw Hats!
What are they up to this time?!
But once we've done using Fujitora,
Wait!
I can't back out on that!
You guys are the ex-toys who were saved by Usopp, aren't you?!
he needs to be taken out.
I need to repay my debt!
I still have a long way to go, to the palace!
I will take care of you after that!
What the hell is going on here?!
Somebody, stop me!
It's nothing personal!
One-star, 100 million berries, Cyborg Franky!
I can't control my body!
What do you say?
Okay, how about this?!
I can't stand it anymore!
I'm just a newcomer
picked through the World Military Draft
We will take down Doflamingo!
And you guys will back us up!
100 million is mine!
This must be a nightmare!
We have to relive the tragedy
from a decade ago?!
but since being appointed as a Navy admiral,
there is something I want to do.
Bring it on!
How dare you guys be blinded by money!
No way! I will take down Doflamingo! Huh?!
If you think you can bring me down, try it!
I-It's happening again!
The complete abolition of
the Seven Warlord system!
I'll do it!
No good... There are too many egos.
There's no advantage of keeping him alive.
Silly big talkers!
Guys...
Th-There's the criminal!
I will take back Dressrosa at any cost!
I don't think it's gonna be easy though.
All of you! That's enough!
One of the criminals is here!
THE OLD KING'S PLATEAU
I said I will kick Doflamingo's ass!
Let's go!
What in the world is happening?!
Catch him, everybody!
What did you say?!
We said we'll return the
favor - don't you get it?!
Forget about us and just shoot!
Guys!
We're almost there at the King's Plateau!
Why don't you shut up or I will kill you,
you dimwitted savior!
Cut it out, guys!
I have no business with you town people!
Th-This is...
--Hurry up, everybody!
--We're almost there, Usoland!
Shoot already!
That's right! Back off...
--I'm counting on you all!
--Okay!
I will do it!
I will destroy him!
--Are you okay, Rebecca?
--Yes, I am, Robin-san!
Shoot!
I am the executioner!
I have no choice.
What's wrong with that guy?
Duty!
Popularity!
Pride!
Listen!
Restrain all those people who are out of control!
King Riku!
I'm so pleased!
Our God!
I'm being helped by
Robin-senpai's very hands now!
Find the Straw Hats and Trafalgar Law!
You'll have to try harder!
I feel like I'm dreaming!
I'm gonna climb up to the top gratefully!
Yes, sir!
We've made up our mind!
We've got to do it!
A spear?
Again, what's wrong with him?!
--There they are!
--Guys, let us help you!
The Navy is not antagonizing us-in, it seems!
Nice! How nice! It's so soft! I'm so happy!
There's no end if I fight them one by one!
Do they really wanna treat the
Young Master as a Warlord?
And I'll see Luffy-senpai
and Zoro-senpai up there!
One 200-million and two 300-millions!
That's a little too lenient, isn't it?
They are the ex-toys who were locked
up underground with us, aren't they?
Ah! Maybe they feel threatened by
the Birdcage, don't you think?!
We gotta kill all the criminals!
This would do!
You're right. They certainly are.
Everybody, hurry up! They're coming!
Usopp did his part so it's my turn!
That aside, that pervert,
What?!
What shameless assholes!
I'm gonna break the factory into pieces!
--We see a lot of money!
--Yeah!
I can't believe he still had
the energy to run away.
Catch them!
Rebecca!
Where the hell did he go?
100 million!
"Where did he go"? He's wounded so bad!
Nico Robin!
Hey hey, the factory went up on its own!
100 million!
God Usopp!
Go to hell! You ungrateful bastards!
He must've been taken out by
the people who are controlled
500 million!
It's Pica.
The total is...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
by the Young Master by now-in, I bet!
700 million berries!
Let's go!
--Let's go.
--Okay.
He's not that weak.
Trebol!
--Help!
--Climb up at full speed!
--What?
--Doffy?
Didn't you guys feel that guy's iron will?
Diamante, I didn't know you are there, too.
I got 100 million berries!
Moocy!
Dammit! Rebecca-sama!
I intend to keep wrecking
the place for no reason!
Y-Yes, I am.
A bull?
Oh no!
Doffy, about Sugar...
I got an idea!
Prepare for it!
Both of you, come back to the Palace!
--Is that...
--Finally, he shows up!
We'll talk later. Okay?!
--Slap!
--What?!
Clank.
What the hell is this?!
When that guy emerges, it's all over!
I'm not gonna let you harm that girl!
Half-hearted attacks won't bring him down.
I see a shadow behind the smoke!
No one can fight back anymore!
Oh, n-no!
We have to finish him off for sure this time!
Strong and beautiful!
A-A bull?
Only Robin-senpai could do it!
Wait!
Hey, Bartolomeo! Put up a barrier!
Barrier!
Oh! So hard-boiled!
Go!
--Robin-senpai, you're the best!
--You're not listening!
There they are! Pica-sama, I found them!
It's the Straw Hats!
Stop following us!
Go on! To the ground above!
--Are you okay, Rebecca-sama?
--Thank you!
They came back!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Don't let them get away!
--We're all here now, aren't we?
--Robin-san, there are still some pursuers!
That must be the SMILE factory!
They're riding a bull!
The three of them from earlier...
It's so defenseless!
It's practically begging to be shot at!
--Zoro?
--Yeah.
Once we get to the top, they're all ours!
What the hell is that?!
--Where are you now?
--Robin?
And four, five...
We're done with the net now.
We better put it away.
I'm with Luffy and the others.
We're on, what they call, the King's Plateau.
Six...
Oh?
Seven!
Wait, Straw Hat!
Things are getting messy, aren't they?
A balloon is falling from the sky-in!
Stop following me, I said!
A giant man?
--Yes!
--Sorry.
Is this Robin?!
He's gigantic!
Oh my Big Sis-sama!
A balloon?
Did you see it?!
Mingo's such a jerk, isn't he?!
Th-They are...
That is...
...increasing in number!
Pica!
But Usopp's bit was hilarious!
Pica-sama!
What did you say, Luffy?!
In...
I will take down Doflamingo!
Rebecca was also on the list.
I wonder if she's alright.
Enough! If you guys get in my way,
I won't hesitate to slice you all up to kill him myself!
If you don't wanna get hurt, stand back,
you little tramps!
Rebecca is...
I'm here! Lucy?!
Don't be so selfish!
We are the ones who'll do it!
Pica-sama!
Oh! It's good that you're there!
Law!
How could you show your face here
after everything, you shitty brat?
No way! It's me!
The soldier is here...
Now, those of you who rebel
against our family...
--Only you could do it, Straw Hat-san!
--Thank you for your work!
No, me!
Oh?
Brother Law?
Well, I barely remember him.
Luffy, what should we do about these fools?
Alright!
Let's go straight to the Palace!
What?
Where did the soldier go?
I'm gonna fight you!
Yes, sir!
Stop following us! I will
kick Doflamingo's ass!
No, I didn't say that to you guys!
I said it to Moocy!
What?!
--H-Hey!
--That's...
Don't tell me he is...
It's the criminal!
No, I'll do it!
His voice! It's so high!
Kill him!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Soldier-san?! He turned back to a human, too, didn't he?!
Trafalgar Law!
Luffy! The head you just
shattered was just a stone!
Pirate Hunter!
Tell me, Lucy, what kind of a man is he?!
--How did they get so many
guys on their side suddenly?!
What?!
What we're running on is just a stone shell!
What kind of a man?!
What are you talking about?!
--How do I know?!
They were the competitors from the Colosseum!
This is the worst spot to land!
We've lost him again?!
Hey, Straw Hat!
When I get uncuffed, I'm gonna kill you first!
That one-legged soldier was...
Where is he?
But it totally doesn't fit!
I tell you, there is no
good spot to land here
...your father!
P-Pica-sama?!
since everybody in this country is our enemy!
What a funny voice!
He's the old man the statue is of!
I know he hasn't gone far.
What's going on?
Anyway, we've gotta run!
Okay!
Chase them, chase them!
He's moving!
Zoro, that's not the way!
Straw Hat!
I... I couldn't protect her!
Straw Hat, it's not this way either!
P-P-P-Please stop!
--We found the criminals!
--Two Three-stars and one Two-star!
I'm sorry!
He's aiming at us!
I couldn't protect your mother!
Don't let them get away!
I'm gonna bring him down!
Hey, hey, stop laughing, Straw Hat!
Stop!
No, I'm gonna do it! Don't get in my way!
Pica-sama is sensitive about
his high-pitched voice!
Although I couldn't protect your mother,
Ah! Brother Law! It's so nice to see you!
That's absurd! Leave it up to me!
If he runs wild with that massive body...
I'm gonna protect you to the end, with my life!
Who is he? Do you know him?
That's Dellinger! Don't
underestimate him! He's...
Until the day you are filled with happiness,
He looks pretty pissed!
You idiot! You made Pica-sama mad!
I will always be by your side!
Not bad!
What?! Where?! Where is he?!
How can you guys not laugh at it?
You boneheads! Stop talking shit!
His real body is right there!
I thought so...
We can't!
Because we don't wanna die yet!
Run, Rebecca!
I got caught!
The strange guy came swimming in the ground!
I'm gonna save you now, Rebecca!
Do it, Vise!
Soldier-san is a brave man
Run! He's a super weight human!
What an unfitting voice!
He will always be by your side
What?! Damn! Let go of my feet!
Ton Ton! Ten-Ton Vise!
It's impossible! That voice!
Happy Birthday, Rebecca!
I can't pull them out! My feet are stuck!
I see something!
Let me teach you how to fight.
Run!
There's no need since I have you.
Three or three-hundred,
it doesn't matter to me!
I'm gonna teach you how to not get hurt!
I'm not gonna miss it this time!
What?! That's the stone man?!
It's not just a punch!
It's like a part of the town falling onto us!
Humans' instincts are much better than that!
Pistol High-Heel!
Here it comes!
This is the first time we've seen him
in a human-like figure!
Count on me!
No! Pica is pissed!
I'm gonna crush you all at once!
Let it all out!
Let's head for the Palace as we run-in!
Believe in your human power!
Too heavy!
I'm right behind you!
I'm a toy.
Ouch!
It's so thrilling!
Hasshoken Secret Technique!
Drill Dragon...
I don't know how long my body's gonna last!
I feel something terrible is happening!
Great! My feet were released!
He has a massive sword!
Watch out this time! Let's go!
Stand up, Rebecca!
Issho-san, please run!
A giant stone man is...
Although I'm not fully charged...
Turn away!
Be strong!
We'll take the money!
Your heads are worth 800 million in total!
Luffy! You have to stop messing
with your enemies...
A lite version of...
Prepare to die!
Shoot!
If you can't turn away, stop!
I won't let you get away!
...King...
See! You can't help laughing either!
...Punch!
It's too late!
You guys...
...Nail!
There are the Two-star and Three-stars!
I'm happy for you!
Damn! They're pains in the ass!
It's coming!
The bull is flying!
But is it okay to chop them up?
There are some civilians, too!
The soldier guy has gone somewhere now
but listen to me, Rebecca!
Damn you!
Okay, I'll use my Haki to...
After all, his voice is a riot!
Stop it.
Straw Hat!
Run! It's gonna crush you up!
Here he comes again!
He who shoots oft at last
shall not hit the mark.
I am running!
--I'll see you later!
--What?!
Don't cry yet!
I won't let the soldier die!
You have to be safe, too!
Yeah, leave it up to me!
I feel bad that I couldn't let you have
the Flare-Flare Fruit that you wanted.
Cool!
Luffy!
But instead,
Get out of my way!
I promise I'll kick Doflamingo's ass for you!
Only friends of God himself could do this!
So stay with my friends!
Zoro, I'm counting on you!
Pica-sama's arm!
I'm gonna go kick Doflamingo's ass!
I'm gonna bring an end to
this stupid game in no time!
Got it, Captain!
You did it! Grandpa!
So survive! Okay?!
Uh-huh!
That's my king!
I have business with Straw Hat! Go away!
We're gonna take down
Doflamingo just like this!
Our captain has no business with
a worthless rock like you!
Stop following us!
I'm all you've got. Live with it!
The Navy admiral!
Shut up, you idiotic savior!
Wait for me, Mingo!
Luffy!!
You soprano-voiced dumb-ass!
What did you say?!
The gambling old man!
Zoro faces Pica, who has taken his true form!
Luffy and Zoro clash with Fujitora!
The group of ruffians led by Luffy is
on their way to the Royal Palace!
The super-giant Pica smashes up
Luffy and the others!
Along with Law and Zoro, Luffy is on the move!
All the battles involving the Straw Hats
and the others begin to intensify,
The three single-mindedly make a dash
for the Royal Palace to confront Doflamingo,
And in the midst of the fierce fight,
Facing this worst-ever enemy,
However, giant Pica relentlessly throws down
the silent top executive Pica
emerges from the ground...
the warriors who once
fought against each other
his fist on them and blocks their way!
Law shares his true feelings,
which up until now have been a mystery!
but are surrounded by executives of the Family -
Machvise, Señor, Dellinger,
...with a rumbling that
shakes up heaven and earth,
to the death in the Colosseum
come together and join Luffy,
When everyone thinks it's all over,
just before Pica's devastating attacks,
showing, at last, the
extent of his strength!
and rowdy pirates who are looking to
claim their prize,
The stunning truth about
the hostile relationship
and the group of unique
characters who are looking to
His tremendous power that
can destroy the whole town
Luffy finally shows his
stunning ultimate technique!
and find themselves caught in a deadly battle!
take down Doflamingo, start
making a significant advance!
between Doflamingo and
Law is finally revealed!
bears down on Luffy and the others!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Shocking Confession! Law's Soulful Vow!"
"Steady Progress! Luffy's Army vs. Pica!"
"With a Rumbling of the Ground!
The God of Destruction - Giant Pica Descends!"
"Gathering into a Powerful Front!
Luffy and a Group of Brutal Warriors!"
"Breaking through Enemy Lines!
Luffy and Zoro Launch the Counter-Attack!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!