Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
We are the one! Go ahead!
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Freedom is our only compass, We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai koto subete kuria shite
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
We can't wait until the morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute uzukidasu (I can't wait)
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou sora e to hikizuridashite
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Oh
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
We are the one! Go ahead!
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
and become the King of the Pirates!
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of burning, intense excitement!
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
omoi no mama mezasu basho e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to go - that's the adventure
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power will seize the "end of the dream"
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
and have come to Dressrosa.
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
Doflamingo trapped everybody in the country
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
Doflamingo trapped everybody
in the country in the Birdcage
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
and put Dressrosa in chaos.
and set up a game to escape
from his domination.
They freed the toys who had been forced to
labor as slaves
On top of that, he put prices on
the heads of Luffy and 11 others.
On top of that, he put prices
on the heads of Luffy and
And while each member of the Straw Hats is
fighting the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
It's either take him down at the Royal Palace
but Doflamingo trapped everybody in the country in the Birdcage.
11 others, and now they're being
hunted by all the citizens.
or kill all 12 criminals
he named, including Luffy.
While the Don Quixote Family awaits,
Luffy and Law are heading for the Royal Palace
to take down Doflamingo.
Luffy is heading for the Royal Palace
to take down Doflamingo!
And with the Straw Hats
fighting the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
Now, let's bring an end to everything.
Everyone has become a hunter
going after Luffy and the others,
while he keeps running to the Palace
where Doflamingo waits!
I see no end to this.
Doflamingo stood in
Luffy and Law's way to the Royal Palace!
I-It's started...!
I'm gonna take out all of them!
His name is Corazon.
Gum-Gum...
The former top executive of
the Doflamingo Family!
Stop messing with Straw Hat Luffy!
You dumbshits!
...Gatling!
I'll pay 100 million berries for each star rating!
What?! Was he a member of his clan?
Rah-Rah-Rah-Rampage!
Outta my way!
And put prices on the heads of Luffy and 11 others.
Yes, he was.
I can't go on... like this!
He also saved my life and was...
I found a shortcut to
reach the higher levels.
What? Really?!
And while the members of the Straw Hats and
Wait, Hajrudin! If you kill Straw Hat,
you'll get a lot of money!
...Doflamingo's...
See? There's a shortcut!
the Don Quixote Family
are clashing everywhere,
...biological young brother!
That's just a pittance!
I almost had my pride stolen
"A United Front!
Luffy's Breakthrough to the Victory!"
Sabo faces Navy Admiral Fujitora.
Wait, Viola!
Now, go ahead, Straw Hat.
We'll guard the entrance!
Why are they so important to you?!
They're pirates!
but was saved by God Usopp!
Prior to the showdown, Sabo revealed...
Yes, they're unlawful men - who will break
this country's deceptive peace!
Alright, thanks!
I can truly win my pride back,
only by repaying my debt!
Is it the Revolutionary Army's job
to give cover to pirates?
Moocy, let's go!
What?!
--I will take down Doflamingo!
--No, I will!
Father-sama, I decided to trust them,
the Straw Hat Pirates!
Yes, it is.
Ring, ring, ring...
As a member of the Revolutionary Army,
I won't let you through.
--No, it's me!
--No, me!
--Luffy. It's me.
--Robin!
No, that's not true.
King Riku-sama!
Viola found the key to Tra-guy-kun's cuffs!
The Straw Hats aka Usolanders
are Dressrosa's hope!
THE ROYAL PALACE
I said "Go away"!
I'm feeling sentimental now...
I mean, it's my duty as his brother!
I will kick Mingo's ass!
Oh yeah?!
Let's meet up at the Sunflower Field
on the fourth level!
Just remember.
Even though they're pirates,
we're gonna trust them to the end!
It's massive! We're finished!
If Luffy ever calls for my help,
Stop! He's soaking in the water!
What did you come here for?
We have nowhere to run!
no matter where I am in the world,
I'll be there - forget my position!
Gum-Gum...
What?! It's a dead end!
...Grizzly Magnum!
Straw Hat-san, we're almost
at the first level!
BELLAMY THE HYENA
A PIRATE, BOUNTY: 195 MILLION BERRIES
Did you kill Straw Hat, Bellamy?
Go back! Hurry!
I never...
Yeah! We're the first to arrive!
No one's here yet!
Moocy! Don't panic!
ACE DIES
Why did you send Dellinger to kill me?!
Was it really your order?!
What?! That's the stone man?!
Gum-Gum...
--Sabo-kun!
--Sabo!
This is the first time we've seen him
in a human-like figure!
...Fire Salute!
I'll see you later!
Oh boy... What rubbish...
This is just a slanted water well.
There is no such shortcut in here.
Yeah, leave it up to me!
...wanna go through that again...
All right! Keep up the pace, Moocy!
Our captain has no business with
a worthless rock like you!
Isn't there any...
Let's go!
...hope left for me?
Luffy is...
I'm all you've got. Live with it!
You!
...my brother to save!
Doflamingo!
You soprano-voiced dumb-ass!
Don't make me say it straight, Bellamy.
"A Big Collision!
Chief of Staff - Sabo vs. Admiral Fujitora!"
"A Desperate Situation!
Luffy Gets Caught in a Trap!"
"A Shocking Confession!
Law's Soulful Vow!"
"A Great Escape!
Luffy's Tide-turning Elephant Gun!"
Your purpose was different from mine.
From long ago.
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
LEVEL 1
You always wanted to become a pirate.
Go! Go! Go!
But not me.
Anything was fine with me.
That's the Colosseum's Grim Reaper!
Anything?
Why does it have Straw Hat on its back?!
D-Don't chicken out!
Pica-sama stopped moving
after his head fell off!
As long as I could...
Doflamingo!
Everybody, aim for the bull!
Give it concentrated gunfire and stop it!
...destroy this world!
Doflamingo!
What happened?!
What about Straw Hat?!
It's odd!
We're no match for that jerk!
Ah! It's very odd!
Hey! The monster stopped moving! Is he dead?!
You weaklings are working together...
If we can stave them off, that's enough!
Bring the bull down and get him bucked off,
How could those idiots from the Colosseum
climb all the way up here?!
Looks like you're gonna get those
handcuffs off soon, aren't you, Law?
then he'll just be a prize in the game!
No, I don't think so.
But, whatever happened to him,
if he's not gonna throw those annoying punches,
Why the hell are you here?!
Don't mess with Moocy!
now is the chance!
I will bring down Doflamingo!
--It's me!
--No, me!
I thought there were thousands of Navy soldiers
down there!
I came to save you.
I thought there were-in!
How could you fall into such a stupid trap?
That crap about a shortcut!
Those jerks are coming again!
Stop them!
Don't let them get to the Palace!
As well as Vice Admiral Bastille
and Navy HQ Admiral Fujitora!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 2
THE COLOSSEUM ARMY VS THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY
Straw Hat!
Moocy! Go! Go!
Bullet String!
How did they make their way through?!
Move! Move! Move!
He's the Grim Reaper! Bow down!
You move, Ideo!
Outta our way! Outta our way!
Hey! What was that?!
The Don Quixote Family's military force?!
Moocy!
What?!
We're gonna go straight to the Palace!
Give him up! Straw Hat-ya!
I'll take down Doflamingo!
Back off, you bastard!
We'll reach their boss soon!
Bring out more worthwhile guys to fight!
The one who'll take down Doflamingo and
repay Straw Hat my debt is me!
Moocy...
Outta my way! I go first!
Oh! Cabbage!
Get out of my way, kid!
All right, go straight up, Farul!
This is the stairway to stardom!
I'm in a rush!
You have no sense of crisis...
I-It's impossible.
We can't stop the group of fighters from the Colosseum.
Stay... with me... Moocy...
In...
Straw Hat! I'm gonna go first!
Damn the Navy... So useless!
Hey, what do I look like?
Oh! How vigorous they are!
There are more coming!
So cheesy!
Hey, tell me, Suleiman!
What?!
I can't believe they still wanna mess with the Young Master!
I have a report!
Anyone could kill you guys like this.
Straw Hat Luffy's arriving at
the first level...
So quick!
So reckless-in!
Damn! I thought I was taking a shortcut!
That's right! Groups of Navy soldiers led by
Go way, way faster, Moocy!
Fujitora are coming together in front of the Palace!
Gum-Gum...
There are some idiots who
are saying they'll kill me,
...Gatling!
"G"roups of Navy soldiers! There's the "G"!
Humph... No matter how quick he moves,
I won't lose him!
rampaging out there...
No, everybody's catching up to us!
Outta my way!
Bastille's unit will join us soon.
It's Hajrudin!
You used to be a war executioner, right?!
It's amazing how you found
people who side with you
under these circumstances.
Half of all Navy soldiers are already
in front of the Palace!
--You're in Straw Hat-san's way...
--Don't stand in his way, you idiots!
I've been giving you due respect for
I knew it was Straw Hat and the others
that stopped Pica-sama.
that special quality of yours
since the War of the Best.
Don't you stand behind me, either!
Get off!
Those well-developed muscles...
There are four different groups or individuals
approaching the Palace.
But...
High heels...
His specialty must be...
Don't say that! Let us follow you!
...you're actually this dumb!
I love... executing people!
First, the group of tough men from around the New World,
Straw Hat-san!
Kicks!
Why did you choose him, Law?
What?!
who fought in the Colosseum.
What's wrong with these guys...
Second, the former commander of the King Riku Army and...
--Straw Hat!
--You can't go any farther!
You used to be a more promising man.
...the strongest man in the history of the Colosseum - Kyros.
Outta my way!
I have no business with you small fries!
Gum-Gum...
Even when you were a kid,
you were more ruthless
...Stamp Gatling!
I gotta keep moving!
and more cunning!
Just give yourself up, Kyros!
Oh, no!
They're gonna get ahead of me!
Am I right?!
Yeah! Nice! Straw Hat-san!
It's only a matter of time
Oh no... That's too bad.
It's over already.
Shoot, shoot!
before we're all dead
if we don't catch you all!
There they come, again!
Who made you... into such a coward?
We need you 12 criminals to
sacrifice yourselves!
Shut up!
Don't wimp out! Shoot the bull!
And, third, No.2 of the Straw Hats - Pirate Hunter Zoro!
Here I come, Mingo!
We're gonna fall!
We can't... c-compete with him...
I'm not willing to become like you!
I've been... saved!
Damn! I'm not gonna let them shoot him!
Here come the Executives of the Family!
Straw Hat!
Gum-Gum...
By my brother Corazon, you mean?
...Gatling!
Fourth, Straw Hat Luffy and the traitor - Law!
They're all getting knocked down!
...Whip!
If you haven't become a coward,
W-We also have
the Colosseum group coming up!
Even the Executives are showing
up now, it's too late!
why do you want to die in vain...
That's it! Keep going, Moocy!
I will repay my debt!
I see no end to this.
...alongside this dumbshit?
I'm gonna take out all of them!
--Yeah! Go, bull!
--Bull!
It's the former leader of the
Happosui Army - Chin Jao!
Guys, how much longer are you gonna stay on?!
Take him down and win fame!
Stop messing with Straw Hat Luffy!
You dumbshits!
Yeah!
Just get off!
I know you're kidding, Straw Hat-san!
Humph! It's not gonna work!
Rah-Rah-Rah-Rampage!
Get out of my way! Destruction Cannon!
Stop! Don't hurt Straw Hat-san!
I don't see Señor anywhere.
Who's that?
Get your hands off of him!
He was with us just a while ago.
I think he went to look for that pervert-in!
Alright! I'm gonna get
to the third level first!
Hey, don't say such a thing!
I was a contender in Block C, same as you.
Pervert?
THE FUNK BROTHERS - ASSASSINS FROM MOGARO
THE OLDER BROTHER: KELLY FUNK
(FUSED WITH HIS YOUNG BROTHER BOBY)
Straw Hat!
Kelly Funk!
What are these bulging stones?
Were you?
That place is dangerous. Mine...
Alright, here I am!
What are you guys doing-in, you idiots?!
Per...
...Pop!
Hey, hey, hey!
--What the hell is this?!
--What's wrong with his body?!
Do you wanna screw up
Young Master-sama's game-in?!
We were saved by God Usopp like the others!
...vert!
It's his clone as I thought.
SMILE factory! Ow!
Grandpa! I'm coming!
Can't they take down one guy at least?
I found a shortcut to
reach the higher levels.
Clone?
Da-in!
That's a string puppet.
Disappointin"g"!
You can make it directly
Floaty, floaty...
There's the "G"!
Now, break open, door to the factory!
to the Sunflower Field -
right in front of the Palace!
So depressin"g"!
Ten-Ton Vise!
What? Really?!
There's the "G"!
Radical Bea...
Han"g" in there! There's...
Yeah, follow me.
You guys...
I know that crappy attack won't even harm the factory but...
I wanna help you!
...the "G"!
--Straw Hat-san!
--Glad that you're safe!
Alright! We're gonna overtake Cabbage
and the others in a single spurt!
You see it, idiots?!
No matter how much he says "G"...
In any case, pull out Straw Hat-san!
That's how powerful our
Family's Executives are!
...I just came to finish up my business with you.
We're no match to them...
Let's catch up with him, Straw Hat-san!
Yeah!
Are you okay?! Straw Hat-san?!
We've got a great ally on our side!
No, it's just that these guys are...
...too fragile.
Oh no!
Too fra"g"ile! There's the "G"!
You jerk! You almost hurt me!
I still have to fight an enemy?!
Weaklings are meant to be cleared out!
That's what men do, boy.
Shut up, geezer!
Don't do it!
What did you say?!
Bye!
Oh! Señor!
My goal is just to repay my debt
to God Usopp and his friends!
Hey, Straw Hat-ya!
Please, Kyros!
Come on out and surrender yourself!
You freak!
When can I get these handcuffs off?
Doflamingo!
And...
With these Sea Prism Stone shackles,
We're gonna come get you if you don't!
...to make the headlines of the newspapers!
--He did it!
--They can't go any farther!
We're not doing this for money!
I'm just going there to
get killed by Doflamingo.
The guy with a hundred-million berry prize...
THE PIRATE NOBLE - CAVENDISH
OF THE WHITE HORSE
If nothing is done, we all have to kill each other until no one's left!
I found him!
If I can kill him, I'd be invited
to join the Doflamingo Family...
We have no choice!
Why don't you guys keep fighting
a little war over there?
We just wanna bring an end to this nightmare
as soon as possible!
I got you!
Well, it'll work itself out!
Let's just go!
Armsmorphosis!
How can you be so sure?!
--Dammit! I will...
--...Repay my debt!
Revolver Leg!
Go back to the plateau
where we were before, then!
That's...!
Why?
I'll look for the key!
This fight's gonna be win or die!
D-Damn!
THE TOWN IN THE SOUTH - SEVIO
What're you doing, old man?!
Let go of it!
Ah! Everybody's coming!
Even the Colosseum group!
You're gonna kill Kyros...
I see them, Dellinger!
This way!
I'm not gonna let a foreign pirate
do such a thing!
Darling... Please...
You want to bring an end to this fight!
All the Navy people are getting hung up!
See? There's a shortcut!
Don't do it!
You fool!
I don't blame you for your decision but...
What?!
You stupid old geezer!
How dare you bother me!
...that means I need to get going even faster!
I-I know...
There!
You know I wouldn't...
Kelly Funk! You're a nice guy!
A very nice guy!
...shoot you two...
No matter how I ask you,
you're not going to move out of our way?
--Shoot!
--Don't let him get away!
Now, go ahead, Straw Hat.
We'll guard the entrance!
But because of Doflamingo,
I'm sorry. You saved my life, elderly man.
There's something that I need to do, too!
my body...
Alright, thanks!
Thank you!
Moocy, let's go!
...is out of my control...
Let me think.
Please run! I beg you!
Take care.
Good job, Kelly Funk!
I-I beg you!
The Straw Hat Pirates,
Make sure to guard the entrance!
Thank you for your work!
You're doing great, Moocy! You're amazing!
and those warriors who support them.
S-Stay still, don't resist and...
No...
What?!
I can't let anyone who's trying to hurt them...
We'll get to Mingo before anyone else like this!
...let me capture you!
Don't...
Wait for me, Mingo!
I'm not gonna let them do it!
...go any farther!
They fell...
What did they want... after all?
I'm sorry but I can't do that!
I got him!
I'm gonna beat the hell out of you!
All right!
Don't worry and keep going, Moocy!
--Bring the rope now!
--And treat him! He's been shot!
Stay away!
You people are peaceful in nature
and don't wish to fight...
Straight to the Sunflower Field!
--The rest of you, put out the fire!
--Okay!
What are you guys looking at?
I'm sorry... I'm sorry... Thank you!
But Doflamingo forced you to do such a thing!
Straw Hat-san, your friend...
S-Straw Hat-san...
And I have to take him down for it!
I almost killed my family!
Is it the Revolutionary Army's job
to give cover to pirates?
M-May you be victorious...!
He stayed all by himself to
fight such a monster...
It was terrible!
How manly!
Yes, it is.
Ring, ring, ring...
As a member of the Revolutionary Army,
I won't let you through.
--Ring, ring, ring...
--Your Transponder Snail...
THE OLD KING'S PLATEAU
Oh, you mean Zoro?
I'm sorry!
--Ring, ring, ring...
--Get it.
He'll be alright! He's not gonna lose!
--Clank.
--Hello?
No, that's not true.
This is Luffy!
The man who'll become
the King of the Pirates!
What?!
You saved me... Thank you!
Luffy. It's me.
Do you want to cause the same
tragedy again, Doflamingo?
I mean, it's my duty as his brother!
Robin!
No, no, no, no...
We're still at the plateau
you were at before.
Now, is that his lower body?!
What's going on with that?!
Oh...
Where are you?
As long as our captain's here,
he won't let it happen.
I wonder who's brother you are.
All in all, we brought down
the big game, didn't we?!
We're at the first level of the other plateau
and heading to a place
called the Sunflower Field.
Idiot!
I told you before. That's a fake!
The Sunflower Field is on the fourth level.
He took the trouble to
send the string puppet...
I'm gonna kill you, you bastard!
Viola found the key to Tra-guy-kun's cuffs!
Earlier, Rebecca and the others
took off from around there, I suppose...
To tease us?
Oh yeah?!
Boy, your voice is so squeaky and annoying.
He said he came to save us.
Wait! He's out of your league-dara.
Nico-ya, get it to me as soon as possible!
Oh yeah!
Actually, that Kelly Funk guy from earlier...
--Is that... King Riku?!
--What?! Let me see!
It makes my ears tickle.
What do you want me to do?!
Hello, this is Leo of the Tontatta Tribe.
That bastard was fooling us!
Damn you!
We're gonna escort Rebecca-sama,
There's another big-timer!
Go to hell!
Rooster Big Human, and Robiland there...
But Vice Admiral-dono...!
It was me who set the
town on fire! I'm sorry!
...at a super high speed!
What a simple-minded fool...
He fell into our trap completely.
I sliced up my own friend!
Let's meet up at the Sunflower Field
on the fourth level!
Me, too! Dammit!
It's not your fault.
What? How will you guys catch up with us!
What are you doing, soprano-voiced old man?
We learned that and
when we tried to stop him...
Everything happened
because of Doflamingo's meddling!
Vice Admiral, huh?
I'll explain later!
See you at the Sunflower Field!
We gotta bring
an end to this game somehow...
We gotta do something!
Abdullah, can you get up?
He's right.
Clank.
Hey!
He made a vow! He'll never be defeated!
See? I told you it's gonna be alright!
Even if you all attack me at once,
We found out where King Riku is!
What?!
It's just a coincidence!
At any cost!
He's with the Five-star God Usopp!
you can't defeat me.
All right! Moocy, run!
You bastard!
Alright... Let's do it!
That infamous assassin Kelly got
taken out in a split second...
But we only capture them!
Hey.
You said "at a high speed"
but what's your plan?
Okay?
Yeah, if we don't do it,
this game will last until we die!
You did it!
Hey, Straw Hat-ya.
If it's true,
Don't mess with us Navy, brat!
Cub-san, please show them!
it's like we were really saved by that jerk!
I know the only way for us to survive now is to kill him.
Come on, Tontatta Airlines!
First, take King Riku and
God Usopp as hostages.
He's mocking us!
Yellow Cubs!
What's going on out there?!
How are Cabbage and the others?!
I've made up my mind, too.
And lure other criminals
using those hostages!
We're totally falling behind...
Yeah!
The plan that I suggested to you guys was
I bet everybody else reached the second level
by now!
It doesn't work.
Tell the people all over the country!
to take down Doflamingo indirectly.
I'm a Flare-Flare Fruit eater!
Damn! I thought we could take a shorter route
to the Sunflower Field!
But, to be honest, I...
You're pissing us off!
Head for Old King's Plateau!
We Navy can't be defeated by a single member of the Revolutionary Army!
We gotta go back! Hurry up!
...want to hurt him directly, too!
Yeah!
No...
I was beaten earlier but I won't be this time!
Wait! Don't do it-dara!
Let's go for it... A shorter route!
Shoot!
Capture King Riku and God Usopp!
What're you...
If there's no shortcut here,
I'll have to make one!
Bring an end to this game by ourselves!
Yeah!
S-Something's coming!
What?!
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF
THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 1
I said "Don't"!
BENEATH THE OLD KING'S PLATEAU - THE JUNKYARD
Kanjuro!
What the...?!
Tell me! Where are you?!
I guess everybody else is heading to
the second level already.
It's Kin'emon!
What a simple-minded fool...
Answer me if you're here! Kanjuro!
Gotta hurry up.
W-Wait a minute!
What are you up to, Straw Hat-san?!
It went so well, didn't it, Kelly?
This asshole!
He has extremely powerful fingers!
He fell into our trap completely.
Straw Hat?
Gum-Gum...
Let's go.
Wait!
They're "claws"!
It's Straw Hat.
I hear it again!
That beast-like voice...
Ah! There's not a single
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF
THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 2
Let him go all the way in
until there's no place to run,
--Where is it coming from?!
--No idea.
dropout on the first level!
13 years ago, there was a person I adored
It's impossible!
Is it some kind of a curse?
then, I'll kill him.
I see! You're such a badass!
and Doflamingo killed him!
Our subordinates can't match them-in!
Where is it?!
Where does it come from?!
Straw Hat and his group aren't here yet.
Let's take them out one by one.
Don't tell me this voice is...
Everybody, be quiet!
Sounds like fun!
Fire Fist!
What's wrong, Farul?!
What the...
What's going on?!
His name is Corazon.
Is that...
Right there?!
The former top executive of
the Doflamingo Family!
Something's coming!
What?! Was he a member of his clan?
Yes, he was.
He also saved my life and was...
Elephant Gun!!
...Doflamingo's...
Don't tell me...!
Fire Fist!
THE SMILE FACTORY
...biological young brother!
Beetles!
What are you guys doing?!
Elephant Gun!!
Keep going! Keep going!
Guys!
Did you knock over this SAD tank?!
Keep going! Keep going! Keep going!!
Pick it up!
He's a Logia eater!
Physical attacks won't work against him!
What's that?!
Are you okay?!
Please stop! There was a sudden earthquake
A fist?
--Logia?
--He's a devil!
Oh my...!
and the tank got knocked over!
How horrible it is-dara.
I see. That's smart!
--He's right!
--What caused that earthquake?!
Only Garp's grandson could do it!
Shut up! You guys don't
need to worry about it!
Thank you for your service!
To let the No.2 of the Revolutionary Army
have such a Devil Fruit.
All right!
But...
Now, we'd like the three of you,
Don't you guys wanna cure
Princess Mancherie's illness?!
Straw Hat did it, didn't he?
Rebecca-sama,
Rooster Big Human, and Robiland...
...to board these Yellow Cubs!
I bet you do!
Step back!
Of course, we wanna cure it!
How is she doing?!
You guys can't beat him-dara!
Look out!
Luffy-senpai!
Um...
I'm afraid the princess isn't
getting better at all!
Straw Hat!
At all!
Oh? What's wrong?
You bastard!
What?!
Luffy-senpai! Where are you?
I like this confusion!
Are you serious?!
Chin Jao and the others are
heading to the third level!
Stop them!
No...
Everybody, are you ready?!
I am serious!
Dodge!
What was that explosion?!
Huh? Luffy-senpai's not here!
Yeah!
Alright, all of you, hold on to these tight,
one for each of your hands!
--Oh no!
--There'll be another one!
Let's go!
Of course, he's not.
What do you mean "Of course"?!
They don't even know what it is!
How could they be freaked out by it!
Your Shark-Cleaver isn't just
for show!
Luffy wouldn't stay in the same place
even for five minutes.
Please! Let us see the princess!
Guys! Don't lose sight of the enemies!
Oh, damn! What a pain!
Oh! Freedom! Whew!
You little brat!
These...?
Shut up and work!
That's how the King of the Pirates should be!
No kidding...
You can't fly people with beetles!
I need to rush!
Let's run through the town!
Is that...
Yeah, yeah! I like her idea!
You fools, just stop grumbling
and keep making SMILEs!
Now, let me give you instructions.
Alright! Let's go, Tra-guy!
Aren't you even listening to us, small one?!
He really made a shortcut!
What is that stone monster?!
King Riku-sama!
FROM INSIDE, UNLOCK...
This is Tontatta Airlines' Jumping Service!
You're too reckless!
Guys!
Take care of Moocy, okay?!
Big Humans are too heavy
so they can't bear you!
What are you guys doing?!
I said work, idiots!
You run around like a cat.
Yes, sir!
See, we told you!
Alright! Let's go!
Quit zoning out! Can't you hear me?!
Did you know about this?
This big hole...
No, this must've been beyond my domain...
I'm gonna bring you down
including those claws
...THE DOOR!
What the... hell is going on...
Why is the Royal Palace up there?!
We don't have that much time anyway, so...
Those words...
that you're so proud of-dara!
...THE DOOR!
...just take off!
What?!
My fingers are...
...the claws of a dragon!
What's this?!
Gum-Gum...
It's the Pink Bees!
We told you we can't fly like this!
The claws that rip apart
those bigoted people...
...Rocket!
Bian!
Inhel! Wicka!
Leo, don't push them too far!
Hey, are you alright?!
...in power!
It's Straw Hat!
Bomba! Cotton!
Damn! Little People!
I'll pay you back for this!
They're gone!
I found it!
Oh! Viola-san!
Everybody!
Alright! I caught up with
them on the second level!
They noticed us! Bian!
Straw Hat!
Roger that!
Pink Bees, the next message!
Trafalgar Law!
--Let's get going! Straw Hat-ya!
--Yeah!
Am I... flying?!
Vice Admiral Bastille's Shark-Cleaver is...
Wait for me, Mingo!
They can't fly you but they can
slow you down when you fall!
WE GOT FOOLED!!!
You little shit!
What? "We got fooled"?
These claws can...
Viola.
So we can't fly like this, can we?!
...crush human skulls...
What do they mean?
I found it, Father-sama!
Hey, you guys! Can't you hear us?!
I'm falling! I'm falling! I'm falling!
The key to Trafalgar Law's handcuffs!
...like an egg!
Relax!
I finally found it with my Clairvoyance!
We got fooled?
Is it about the princess' illness?
How can I relax?!
I'm gonna crash into something!
I have to deliver it to them somehow!
Doflamingo has been fooling us?
Head for a rooftop!
Wait, Viola!
A rooftop?!
Why are they so important to you?!
They're pirates!
That's right!
And land on it smoothly!
FIGHT!!!
Yes, they're unlawful men - who will break
this country's deceptive peace!
"Fight"?!
I guess you need another beating
to understand things.
Father-sama, I decided to trust them,
the Straw Hat Pirates!
Now! Kick off!
Oh damn!
I don't know what's going on
but one thing I know is...
I have a problem.
Friends don't lie!
Dragon Claw Fist! Dragon...
Since that Bird Cage thing is in its way,
my meteor's going to be sliced, isn't it?
...Claw!
--Shut up!
--Sanshita!
The World Government gave him the title of the Warlord
I'm flying!
Kicking off rooftops helps you to rise!
and that pirate Doflamingo reigned this country with terror,
What a fight!
Oh yeah! We can get to the
Sunflower Field like this!
causing us so much pain!
That's right!
I see!
--Run!
--It's a meteorite!
I'm getting the knack of it!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF
THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 2
Commodore Hug!
I don't want the help of the Navy, that was supposed to be
Oh yeah. This smoke doesn't
slow you down at all!
You're too slu"gg"ish! There're the "Gs"!
supporting justice, or the Government after all these years!
Good! You're doing great!
I guess not.
One more coming-in!
They can't hear them!
That's what I'd expect from
No.2 of the Revolutionary Army,
This is it for this guy-in!
I feel like I'm a balloon!
The voices of the people who fell victim because of them!
leader of the next generation.
Ten-Ton Vise!
Your attacks are quite sharp.
--Are you okay?!
--Yeah! You alright, Grandpa?!
The angry voices of this country!
Watch out for attacks from below.
Oops! What a fine mess!
You don't mean that.
Head for the Sunflower Field
on the fourth level, everybody!
LEVEL 4
THE SUNFLOWER FIELD
That little brat!
It's all over the place...
People in authority often only hear
what they want to!
Roger that!
Mine Pop.
Got it!
I hope no civilians got hurt.
It's dangerous there, too.
And there.
When you plan to bring down a meteorite,
let us know, Issho-san!
At least, the words of Straw Hat and the others are humane
Oh, I'm sorry! I brought one down!
No! That's it?
and they take actions
out of the goodness of their hearts!
Before you do it!
I wanted to see more of the Longleg
tribe's kicking techniques!
IN FRONT OF THE SMILE FACTORY
Fraland!
It's too bad!
I promise I'll kick Doflamingo's ass for you!
Destruction Cannon!
Tontattas?!
Swim. Swiiim.
Listen to me, Fraland!
So stay with my friends!
Is it Ideo?!
We have an idea to unlock the door
to the Factory!
Swim. Swim.
Too slow!
Take a good look at this country!
Bastille-san!
What?! Really?!
If I stop now, what's gonna happen to it?!
This is like a gathering of comedians!
Do you know the position you're in?
Yes!
So please keep Señor busy like that!
I guess we're not supposed to
fight to get there first now.
Only a Navy admiral could do that.
What power...
-Yeah.
I got it!
Armsmorphosis!
Swim, swim, swim, swim... So annoying!
Count on me!
Revolver Girl!
You swimming bastard!
A lite version of King Punch!
King Riku-sama! King Riku-sama!
IN THE TOWN
Look! There are two people with a prize
I still haven't gotten used to my own power...
Take a look at him!
of a hundred-million!
Shoot!
So I tried to ward it off.
Dagama, we're gonna lose this battle
if nothing is done!
Oh no! They found us!
You're the Five-star man, aren't you?!
You bastards!
What are you gonna do if
you hit Robin-senpai?!
Ugh! What are you showing us,
you mechanical jerk?!
That's right!
Don't worry!
I'm gonna put up a barrier now!
His name is Usoland aka God Usopp!
Cut it out, you little tramps.
Vice Admiral Bastille!
This is how men fight.
Vice Admiral-dono!
This man risked his life
Barrier it is!
Oh! So hard-boiled!
and broke the spell of toys
that had been
Straw Hat!
Dammit!
I can't cross my fingers like this!
You've really created havoc...
overshadowing this country for a decade!
Let go of me, shithead!
Huh?! You've done most of it!
It's me, military tactician
Dagama's chance to show off!
Strong Right!
Shoot them down!
He's our hero!
Whoa! Watch out!
You assholes! Don't push your luck!
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
You said "brotherly duty" earlier...
Doflamingo's at the top of this place?!
When it comes to this,
Cabbage!
Do you wanna get in my way, again?!
I'm gonna do the same thing
that I did at the Colosseum!
Yeah.
Usoland! Usoland!
No...
The man who had the Flare-Flare Fruit power before you -
Where did he go this time?!
--Get on.
--What?
His bravery moved us to tears!
"Fire Fist" Ace who died in the War of the Best...
Hey, wait! What is he doing?!
I mean I'll give you a ride
because I have no other choice!
Really, really, really,
...claimed that he was Straw Hat's adopted brother but...
What?! Don't tell me...
You sure?!
You wanna get to Doflamingo ASAP, don't you?
he's gonna do it!
we were so touched by it!
Alright!
That wasn't so bad.
I'm ready! go!
He's a superhero!
Have you ever once in your life
been humble?!
...you're saying you're his brother, too?
Take this, fools!
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
Bring it on.
--Whatever, just go!
--Don't tell me what to do!
Let's go, Farul!
Fraland...
Humph! What a bunch of cowards!
Inhel, what should we do?!
Listen, if we get caught by the Executives,
we get stuck here.
Did you guys know?!
And Luffyland is the superhero's captain!
I have an idea.
I'm gonna cut the wall and make a path
We can become brothers
if we exchange this cup of sake!
An idea?
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF
THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 4
King Riku-sama!
so you kick the other enemies' asses!
The Straw Hats aka Usolanders are Dressrosa's hope!
Got it!
And we're gonna go straight to
the third level...
THE SUNFLOWER FIELD
Hey! That's one too many!
Who are you?!
Even though they're pirates,
we're gonna trust them to the end!
--Oh, Soldier!
--When did you get on?!
Yeah!!
Just now!
I followed the path that Luffyland made!
We three exchanged the cup of sake.
I see. That's how you followed Straw Hat
and got on Farul... Hey!
You asshole!
You just stepped on my sword!
This is great!
It's the Straw Hats' unforgettable moving scene!
--You followed too far!
--Great! I was looking for you!
So what?
You'll promote me to executive of the Family
if I win the competition?!
Our bond can't be broken
even if anyone tries.
How lucky I am to be here!
Even if you're his friend, we're overloaded!
I'm gonna kill you!
Get off!
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
We're gonna meet up with Rebecca!
Yeah.
Rebecca is in this enemy territory?!
Why didn't you stop her?!
Even when you're mad, your voice is soprano.
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
You can do it.
That's just a big-ass dull sword...
Listen to me!
He told me to finish you off here.
We'll rendezvous at the Sunflower Field
on the fourth level.
No matter how many times you try, it's no use!
Look, Viola-san,
can I go deliver the key to Lucy?!
She's on the criminal list, too!
That's Young Master-sama's order.
Rebecca!
I can't just stay here and wait!
Let me do it!
Don't worry! She's with my friends!
I can't go on... like this!
Two-Sword Style!
Listen! My dear horse Farul
only can run beautifully
Rebecca...
Alright, let's do it!
Let's go see Luffy-senpai!
with two people or less!
I see. That's how it works.
The bull's back had more space...
I'm coming with you, of course! Count on me!
By the way, pops,
why did you take off before I knew it?
Rebecca! You're a criminal in Doflamingo's game!
If you go down to the town,
What a terrible set of three brothers.
Whatever the situation is...
what I have to do is...
--they won't leave you alone!
--I'm gonna be okay!
What kind of brothers are they?!
Hey hey, Doffy!
...bring down Doflamingo
and take back the country!
Straw Hat's brothers...
Enough playing around.
Did you send String-Joker off somewhere?
One of them was
a commander of the White Beards!
Get ready!
But there's one more thing!
Yes...
There's one man in the
Family's Top Executives
I wanted to deliver something
but I guess he doesn't need it.
that I wanna kill with my
own bare hands at any cost!
And the other one is
No.2 of the Revolutionary Army?!
All right. Just be careful.
Deliver something?
Old dude, you're not willing to die,
are you?
Just remember.
Uh-huh!
If Luffy ever calls for my help,
You guys...
No way! I won't be defeated
with this human body!
It's about the right time, isn't it?
Do you remember the day we met Law
for the first time?
--Cub-san!
--Yeah!
Kelly, let's go!
no matter where I am in the world,
I'll be there - forget my position!
--Alright, then!
--Nothing's alright! Get off!
Okay!
Everybody!
Huh?! You get off!
That's nonsense!
You're the worst!
You really are part of the Worst Generation!
He was nuts!
Even his eyes were crazy...
Watch out, fool!
Look where you're going! Hey!
You guys?!
If you are planning on going,
let's use the rooftops!
Yeah, yeah!
Like I said, don't tell me what to do!
Cub-san and I will go along with you!
So don't worry!
I never...
He looked like me when I was a kid.
What?!
Hey, Straw Hat-ya.
--Rooftops?!
--Yes!
ACE DIES
Is that...
Inhel, can I leave the factory in your hands?
I sensed he would become my
right-hand man in 10 years or so.
Isn't this path going downward?
--Sabo-kun!
--Sabo!
No problem!
Come to think of it...
According to the scouting unit,
Fraland is fighting Señor Pink now!
Stop! He's soaking in the water!
It's a shame that I will have to kill him
with my own hands.
...wanna go through that again...
Along with Fraland, we Tontattas will all work together
to take back Princess Mancherie and our people!
Huh? But he told us this was a shortcut
to the Sunflower Field...
Uh-huh!
I'll see you guys later!
Go ahead, Straw Hat!
Everybody! We don't have that much time!
I'll see you all again here on the King's Plateau!
We're gonna keep them busy!
It's senseless to ask you
any more questions.
What?! It's a dead end!
What-in?! They're suddenly...
Let's go now!
Go back! Hurry!
They were disorganized before,
fighting each other!
Yeah!
Moocy! Don't panic!
You have no interest, anyway, do you?
We have an intruder!
What?! Why are you doing this, guys?!
I don't have a cup of sake
to go along with your stories.
Don't touch him!
He has explosives strapped to his body!
Straw Hat Luffy... What a strange man.
I'm Dagama, the military tactician!
This is a war!
Even in this desperate situation,
Hey! Who the hell is this kid?!
Who lets him in?!
Somebody's coming.
Even if we all run wild blindly,
no one can reach the top!
Luffy.
everyone finds hope in the Straw Hats without them realizing.
You're our little brother!
Let me join your pirate group.
I don't trust Dagama
but I agreed to his plan.
Keep the Executives here
and let Straw Hat go ahead!
I wanna destroy everything that I see!
Leave this mess here to us and go!
Pirates, huh?
Towns, houses, people...
I wanna destroy them all!
Make sure to take him there,
Cavendish!
--Straw Hat-san, we're almost at the first level!
--There are so many enemies there!
Hey hey,
I'm not public transportation!
I...
...grew up in the White Town - Flevance.
We gotta win this war!
--That's…
--Something's coming this way!
Yeah! We're the first to arrive!
No one's here yet!
Well done, Moocy!
It's not so long...
This is just a slanted water well.
...before I die.
There is no such shortcut in here.
--It's Straw Hat Luffy!
--Shoot! Shoot!
Gum-Gum...
...Fire Salute!
All right! Keep up the pace, Moocy!
Luffy is...
Interesting...
Mingo!
Let's go!
...my brother to save!
You!
Doflamingo!
Robin and the others, trying to join Luffy,
Getting stuck deep inside
the dark water well,
Luffy and the others keep making smooth progress!
The motley band of ruffians
quick offense and defense
The Executives of the Doflamingo
Family show themselves
before Luffy and the others
But the Navy led by Fujitora starts chasing,
go for a make-or-break mighty flight,
allows Luffy and the others to
get close to the Royal Palace!
Luffy bears the brunt of Doflamingo's attack
and is knocked into the water!
and a back-and-forth, full-scale
fierce fight begins!
and take Tontatta Airlines straight
to the Royal Palace!
Meanwhile, Kin'emon finally reunites
the other samurai
and when they close in on Luffy and the others,
After losing his way to the Royal Palace
Meanwhile, as the group of ruffians
When it seems their way to
the Royal Palace has been blocked up,
one man stands in the Navy's way on his own!
of the Wano Kingdom, Kanjuro!
and just when the situation couldn't
be more desperate than this,
makes a steady progress,
Luffy and the others fall behind
In order to get out of the
deep-underground junkyard,
the disorganized group of debtors finally
proves their real worth!
Luffy strikes a big come-back blow
that blasts away his adversity!
The strongest forces of the Revolutionary Army
and the Navy finally face off!
but suddenly charge into a secret shortcut
to the Palace trying to make a big comeback!
Kanjuro practices unbelievable sorcery!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A United Front! Luffy's
Breakthrough to the Victory!”
"A Great Escape! Luffy's
Tide-turning Elephant Gun!"
"A Desperate Situation! Luffy Gets Caught in a Trap!"
"A Big Collision! Chief of Staff - Sabo vs. Admiral Fujitora!”
"The Second Samurai! Evening
Shower Kanjuro Appears!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!