Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
Doflamingo trapped everybody
in the country in the Birdcage
and put Dressrosa in chaos.
On top of that, he put prices on
the heads of Luffy and 11 others.
While the Don Quixote Family awaits,
Luffy is heading for the Royal Palace
to take down Doflamingo!
His name is Corazon.
The former top executive of
the Doflamingo Family!
What?! Was he a member of his clan?
Yes, he was.
He also saved my life and was...
...Doflamingo's...
...biological young brother!
Wait, Viola!
Why are they so important to you?!
They're pirates!
Yes, they're unlawful men - who will break
this country's deceptive peace!
Father-sama, I decided to trust them,
the Straw Hat Pirates!
King Riku-sama!
The Straw Hats aka Usolanders
are Dressrosa's hope!
Even though they're pirates,
we're gonna trust them to the end!
Straw Hat-san, we're almost
at the first level!
Yeah! We're the first to arrive!
No one's here yet!
Gum-Gum...
...Fire Salute!
All right! Keep up the pace, Moocy!
Let's go!
"A Big Collision!
Chief of Staff - Sabo vs. Admiral Fujitora!"
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
Doflamingo!
It's odd!
Ah! It's very odd!
How could those idiots from the Colosseum
climb all the way up here?!
I thought there were thousands of Navy soldiers
down there!
I thought there were-in!
As well as Vice Admiral Bastille
and Navy HQ Admiral Fujitora!
How did they make their way through?!
Hey! What was that?!
The Don Quixote Family's military force?!
We'll reach their boss soon!
Outta my way! I go first!
All right, go straight up, Farul!
This is the stairway to stardom!
In...
Damn the Navy... So useless!
There are more coming!
What?!
I have a report!
Straw Hat Luffy's arriving at
the first level...
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Outta my way!
--You're in Straw Hat-san's way...
--Don't stand in his way, you idiots!
Don't you stand behind me, either!
Get off!
Don't say that! Let us follow you!
Straw Hat-san!
What's wrong with these guys...
--Straw Hat!
--You can't go any farther!
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp Gatling!
Yeah! Nice! Straw Hat-san!
Here I come, Mingo!
We can't... c-compete with him...
Straw Hat!
They're all getting knocked down!
W-We also have
the Colosseum group coming up!
Get out of my way! Destruction Cannon!
Straw Hat!
What are you guys doing-in, you idiots?!
Do you wanna screw up
Young Master-sama's game-in?!
Can't they take down one guy at least?
Disappointin"g"!
There's the "G"!
So depressin"g"!
Han"g" in there! There's...
...the "G"!
No matter how much he says "G"...
We're no match to them...
Oh no!
You jerk! You almost hurt me!
Weaklings are meant to be cleared out!
What did you say?!
Bye!
My goal is just to repay my debt
to God Usopp and his friends!
And...
...to make the headlines of the newspapers!
THE PIRATE NOBLE - CAVENDISH
OF THE WHITE HORSE
Why don't you guys keep fighting
a little war over there?
--Dammit! I will...
--...Repay my debt!
Ah! Everybody's coming!
Even the Colosseum group!
I see them, Dellinger!
All the Navy people are getting hung up!
What?!
No matter how I ask you,
you're not going to move out of our way?
Let me think.
The Straw Hat Pirates,
and those warriors who support them.
I can't let anyone who's trying to hurt them...
...go any farther!
Is it the Revolutionary Army's job
to give cover to pirates?
Yes, it is.
As a member of the Revolutionary Army,
I won't let you through.
No, that's not true.
I mean, it's my duty as his brother!
Oh...
I wonder who's brother you are.
Wait! He's out of your league-dara.
But Vice Admiral-dono...!
Vice Admiral, huh?
He's right.
Even if you all attack me at once,
you can't defeat me.
You bastard!
You did it!
Don't mess with us Navy, brat!
It doesn't work.
I'm a Flare-Flare Fruit eater!
You're pissing us off!
We Navy can't be defeated by a single member of the Revolutionary Army!
Wait! Don't do it-dara!
Shoot!
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot!
I said "Don't"!
This asshole!
He has extremely powerful fingers!
They're "claws"!
Fire Fist!
Guys!
He's a Logia eater!
Physical attacks won't work against him!
--Logia?
--He's a devil!
How horrible it is-dara.
To let the No.2 of the Revolutionary Army
have such a Devil Fruit.
Step back!
You guys can't beat him-dara!
You bastard!
Dodge!
Your Shark-Cleaver isn't just
for show!
You little brat!
You run around like a cat.
I'm gonna bring you down
including those claws
that you're so proud of-dara!
My fingers are...
...the claws of a dragon!
The claws that rip apart
those bigoted people...
...in power!
Vice Admiral Bastille's Shark-Cleaver is...
You little shit!
These claws can...
...crush human skulls...
...like an egg!
I have a problem.
Since that Bird Cage thing is in its way,
my meteor's going to be sliced, isn't it?
--Run!
--It's a meteorite!
Oops! What a fine mess!
It's all over the place...
I hope no civilians got hurt.
When you plan to bring down a meteorite,
let us know, Issho-san!
Oh, I'm sorry! I brought one down!
Before you do it!
Bastille-san!
Do you know the position you're in?
Only a Navy admiral could do that.
What power...
I still haven't gotten used to my own power...
So I tried to ward it off.
Vice Admiral Bastille!
Vice Admiral-dono!
You've really created havoc...
Huh?! You've done most of it!
You said "brotherly duty" earlier...
Yeah.
The man who had the Flare-Flare Fruit power before you -
"Fire Fist" Ace who died in the War of the Best...
...claimed that he was Straw Hat's adopted brother but...
...you're saying you're his brother, too?
Did you guys know?!
We can become brothers
if we exchange this cup of sake!
Yeah!!
We three exchanged the cup of sake.
Our bond can't be broken
even if anyone tries.
What a terrible set of three brothers.
What kind of brothers are they?!
Straw Hat's brothers...
One of them was
a commander of the White Beards!
And the other one is
No.2 of the Revolutionary Army?!
Just remember.
If Luffy ever calls for my help,
no matter where I am in the world,
I'll be there - forget my position!
I never...
ACE DIES
--Sabo-kun!
--Sabo!
...wanna go through that again...
It's senseless to ask you
any more questions.
You have no interest, anyway, do you?
I don't have a cup of sake
to go along with your stories.
Luffy.
You're our little brother!
Luffy is...
...my brother to save!
Robin and the others, trying to join Luffy,
go for a make-or-break mighty flight,
and take Tontatta Airlines straight
to the Royal Palace!
Meanwhile, as the group of ruffians
makes a steady progress,
Luffy and the others fall behind
but suddenly charge into a secret shortcut
to the Palace trying to make a big comeback!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Desperate Situation! Luffy Gets Caught in a Trap!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!