Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
Doflamingo trapped everybody in the country
and set up a game to escape
from his domination.
It's either take him down at the Royal Palace
or kill all 12 criminals
he named, including Luffy.
Everyone has become a hunter
going after Luffy and the others,
while he keeps running to the Palace
where Doflamingo waits!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Outta my way!
And while the members of the Straw Hats and
the Don Quixote Family
are clashing everywhere,
Sabo faces Navy Admiral Fujitora.
Prior to the showdown, Sabo revealed...
Is it the Revolutionary Army's job
to give cover to pirates?
Yes, it is.
As a member of the Revolutionary Army,
I won't let you through.
No, that's not true.
I mean, it's my duty as his brother!
Just remember.
If Luffy ever calls for my help,
no matter where I am in the world,
I'll be there - forget my position!
I never...
ACE DIES
--Sabo-kun!
--Sabo!
...wanna go through that again...
Luffy is...
...my brother to save!
"A Desperate Situation!
Luffy Gets Caught in a Trap!"
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
LEVEL 1
Go! Go! Go!
That's the Colosseum's Grim Reaper!
Why does it have Straw Hat on its back?!
D-Don't chicken out!
Everybody, aim for the bull!
Give it concentrated gunfire and stop it!
What about Straw Hat?!
We're no match for that jerk!
If we can stave them off, that's enough!
Bring the bull down and get him bucked off,
then he'll just be a prize in the game!
Don't mess with Moocy!
Moocy! Go! Go!
He's the Grim Reaper! Bow down!
Outta our way! Outta our way!
We're gonna go straight to the Palace!
Oh! Cabbage!
Straw Hat! I'm gonna go first!
Damn! I thought I was taking a shortcut!
Go way, way faster, Moocy!
No, everybody's catching up to us!
It's Hajrudin!
Outta my way!
I have no business with you small fries!
I gotta keep moving!
Oh, no!
They're gonna get ahead of me!
Shoot, shoot!
There they come, again!
Don't wimp out! Shoot the bull!
We're gonna fall!
Damn! I'm not gonna let them shoot him!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
...Whip!
I see no end to this.
I'm gonna take out all of them!
Stop messing with Straw Hat Luffy!
You dumbshits!
Rah-Rah-Rah-Rampage!
Who's that?
Hey, don't say such a thing!
I was a contender in Block C, same as you.
THE FUNK BROTHERS - ASSASSINS FROM MOGARO
THE OLDER BROTHER: KELLY FUNK
(FUSED WITH HIS YOUNG BROTHER BOBY)
Kelly Funk!
Were you?
Hey, hey, hey!
We were saved by God Usopp like the others!
I found a shortcut to
reach the higher levels.
You can make it directly
to the Sunflower Field -
right in front of the Palace!
What? Really?!
Yeah, follow me.
I wanna help you!
Alright! We're gonna overtake Cabbage
and the others in a single spurt!
Let's catch up with him, Straw Hat-san!
We've got a great ally on our side!
Hey, Straw Hat-ya!
When can I get these handcuffs off?
With these Sea Prism Stone shackles,
I'm just going there to
get killed by Doflamingo.
Well, it'll work itself out!
Let's just go!
How can you be so sure?!
Go back to the plateau
where we were before, then!
Why?
I'll look for the key!
This fight's gonna be win or die!
This way!
See? There's a shortcut!
There!
Kelly Funk! You're a nice guy!
A very nice guy!
Now, go ahead, Straw Hat.
We'll guard the entrance!
Alright, thanks!
Moocy, let's go!
Take care.
Good job, Kelly Funk!
Make sure to guard the entrance!
Thank you for your work!
What?!
They fell...
What did they want... after all?
All right!
Don't worry and keep going, Moocy!
Straight to the Sunflower Field!
S-Straw Hat-san...
M-May you be victorious...!
Ring, ring, ring...
--Ring, ring, ring...
--Your Transponder Snail...
--Get it.
--Clank.
--Hello?
This is Luffy!
The man who'll become
the King of the Pirates!
Luffy. It's me.
Robin!
We're still at the plateau
you were at before.
Where are you?
We're at the first level of the other plateau
and heading to a place
called the Sunflower Field.
The Sunflower Field is on the fourth level.
Viola found the key to Tra-guy-kun's cuffs!
Oh yeah?!
Nico-ya, get it to me as soon as possible!
What do you want me to do?!
Hello, this is Leo of the Tontatta Tribe.
We're gonna escort Rebecca-sama,
Rooster Big Human, and Robiland there...
...at a super high speed!
Let's meet up at the Sunflower Field
on the fourth level!
What? How will you guys catch up with us!
I'll explain later!
See you at the Sunflower Field!
Clank.
See? I told you it's gonna be alright!
It's just a coincidence!
All right! Moocy, run!
Hey.
You said "at a high speed"
but what's your plan?
Cub-san, please show them!
Come on, Tontatta Airlines!
Yellow Cubs!
S-Something's coming!
What a simple-minded fool...
It went so well, didn't it, Kelly?
He fell into our trap completely.
Let's go.
Wait!
It's Straw Hat.
Let him go all the way in
until there's no place to run,
then, I'll kill him.
I see! You're such a badass!
Is that...
Don't tell me...!
Beetles!
Keep going! Keep going!
Keep going! Keep going! Keep going!!
Thank you for your service!
All right!
Now, we'd like the three of you,
Rebecca-sama,
Rooster Big Human, and Robiland...
...to board these Yellow Cubs!
Oh? What's wrong?
Are you serious?!
No...
I am serious!
Alright, all of you, hold on to these tight,
one for each of your hands!
These...?
No kidding...
You can't fly people with beetles!
Let's run through the town!
Yeah, yeah! I like her idea!
Now, let me give you instructions.
Aren't you even listening to us, small one?!
This is Tontatta Airlines' Jumping Service!
Big Humans are too heavy
so they can't bear you!
See, we told you!
Did you know about this?
No, this must've been beyond my domain...
We don't have that much time anyway, so...
...just take off!
What?!
We told you we can't fly like this!
Leo, don't push them too far!
Hey, are you alright?!
Damn! Little People!
I'll pay you back for this!
They're gone!
Am I... flying?!
They can't fly you but they can
slow you down when you fall!
So we can't fly like this, can we?!
I'm falling! I'm falling! I'm falling!
Relax!
How can I relax?!
I'm gonna crash into something!
Head for a rooftop!
A rooftop?!
That's right!
And land on it smoothly!
Now! Kick off!
I'm flying!
Kicking off rooftops helps you to rise!
Oh yeah! We can get to the
Sunflower Field like this!
That's right!
I see!
I'm getting the knack of it!
Good! You're doing great!
I feel like I'm a balloon!
Watch out for attacks from below.
Head for the Sunflower Field
on the fourth level, everybody!
LEVEL 4
THE SUNFLOWER FIELD
Roger that!
Got it!
Swim. Swiiim.
Swim. Swim.
Swim, swim, swim, swim... So annoying!
You swimming bastard!
Ugh! What are you showing us,
you mechanical jerk?!
Cut it out, you little tramps.
This is how men fight.
Oh! So hard-boiled!
Let go of me, shithead!
Strong Right!
Where did he go this time?!
That wasn't so bad.
Bring it on.
Fraland...
Inhel, what should we do?!
I have an idea.
An idea?
You asshole!
You just stepped on my sword!
So what?
I'm gonna kill you!
Even when you're mad, your voice is soprano.
That's just a big-ass dull sword...
No matter how many times you try, it's no use!
Two-Sword Style!
I see. That's how it works.
Enough playing around.
Get ready!
It's about the right time, isn't it?
Kelly, let's go!
Okay!
Hey, Straw Hat-ya.
Isn't this path going downward?
Come to think of it...
Stop! He's soaking in the water!
Huh? But he told us this was a shortcut
to the Sunflower Field...
What?! It's a dead end!
Go back! Hurry!
Moocy! Don't panic!
Somebody's coming.
This is just a slanted water well.
There is no such shortcut in here.
You!
Doflamingo!
Getting stuck deep inside
the dark water well,
Luffy bears the brunt of Doflamingo's attack
and is knocked into the water!
After losing his way to the Royal Palace
and just when the situation couldn't
be more desperate than this,
Luffy strikes a big come-back blow
that blasts away his adversity!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Great Escape! Luffy's
Tide-turning Elephant Gun!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!