Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"Coby-Meppo's Resolve!
Vice-Admiral Garp's Parental Affection"
Ah! I can see...
A million Little Garden residents
are out to greet Captain Usopp!
The girls' high-pitched cheers...
Kisses being blown all over the place...
Really, I'm so popular
that it's almost a crime...
Don't fall in love with me, Mademoiselle.
It's not my fault if you get burned.
Are you stupid or what?
Stupid? Hey, I heard that, Zoro!
Cut it out! Keep it down, you guys!
Seriously....
Sorry about that. So...?
Oh, yeah, so it's like I was just saying.
There aren't any islands, but it's easy
to hit reefs due to the elevated coral.
I see...
Thanks. That was helpful.
You're welcome.
--Wow, it smells good.
--Yeah.
Thanks for waiting. This is
today's dessert, Tarte aux Poires.
Bon appetit.
Wow! It looks delicious!
Yours is over there!
Hmm... Okay!
Geez... Hmm? Where's Luffy?
Oh, I asked him to go draw water earlier.
I want to take a shower.
I think he's at the water-drawing machine.
No wonder he's been quiet.
Or not...
Ahhh... That scared me.
That thing is dangerous!
What? What happened?
Ahh! Luffy! Why'd you have to break it?!
I was just trying to
draw the water faster.
Oh, boy... The belt's
been burned and broken.
Yeah. I wonder how that happened.
It's because of your ridiculous strength!
Geez...
Can't it be fixed?
Well, we have to get
materials from somewhere.
In any case, I probably
shouldn't ask him to do anything.
Usopp, could you get water from the
other water-drawing machine for me?
Yeah...
What? Nami! Have you ever
considered doing it yourself?!
I smell food!
And you, show a little more remorse!
--I'm sorry. But there's another
one, so what's the big deal?
--Nami-san, look.
--I'm sorry. But there's another
one, so what's the big deal?
--Nami-san, look.
--Saying something like that
shows you're not sorry!
--Oh, the newspaper courier.
--Shut up! I can't sleep!
That stupid Nami...
At any rate, I can't believe they deliver
the morning paper at snack time...
That can't be helped since we're
traveling in the Grand Line.
We should feel lucky that
we can still get news.
I guess you're right.
Did something catch your eye?
What? Ah, no, not really...
I see.
Ah!
Wh-What is it?
Here! Zoro, look!
Hm?
What? This is just
a picture of the Navy.
Yeah, but the guy in this
picture isn't just anyone.
Hm? Hey, it's Coby!
See?!
Coby...? That friend you were
talking about the other day?
Yep! So what does it say?
What does it say? Let's see...
"Vice-Admiral Garp's warship has
arrived at Navy Headquarters.
The picture was taken right after
they crossed over Reverse Mountain.
Just as expected, Vice-Admiral
Garp had a relaxed, imposing look;
however, there were some young
marines whose faces froze with fear."
Whoa... So Coby has
entered the Grand Line.
It said Navy Headquarters. Not so bad.
No matter what people say,
he's a man who'll be a Navy mayor.
Why would he want to become a mayor?
Officer! A Navy officer!
Yeah, that's the one.
I see... So he's trying hard, too...
"Navy"
2,000 push-ups! Start!
Rope-crossing, 100 round trips!
Run 200 laps!
Those who can't finish within 1 hour
will be penalized with another 100 laps.
Practice matches!
Don't stop until you faint!
Are you okay?!
So this is Navy Headquarters...!
"23"
Okay, they can't see us here.
Please rest a little.
Yeah. Sorry.
Say, Coby.
What is it?
Maybe it was too early
for us to come here...
What?
You saw it earlier, didn't you?
The way we are right now,
we won't make it here.
Huh?
There's a proper order for doing things.
Maybe we should try again after
we've at least trained ourselves more.
Yep! That's right. Let's do that!
Even if we're missing,
no one will care...
Hold on a second!
What're you thinking, Helmeppo-san?!
I thought you said
you'd surpass your father!
W-Well, I did... but if I do
all those things, I'll die.
Wouldn't you be happy
if that's the case?!
Once you've decided
to become like that...
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
Once you've decided
to become like that...
I've decided to be
King of the Pirates, so if...
If you can die fighting for that,
you should be happy!
Fighting... That's going a bit far...
No, you fight!
Against yourself!
So please don't ever say you'll run away!
Running away?!
You idiots!
You sure aren't going to
bring disgrace on me, are you?!
You wimps!
You two can be easily replaced.
If you wanna run away,
hurry up and do it.
Please wait! We won't run away!
Hmm?
We've come this far fully
prepared to die if necessary.
Please give us any orders!
We'll carry out anything,
Vice-Admiral Garp!
Carry out anything...
Did you just say that?
What? Uhm...
You've come fully prepared to die...
You definitely said that, right?!
Y-Y-Yes, sir!
Then stop slacking off here
and get to work!
Yes, sir!
If you could continue watching them...
Yes, sir.
What?! Navy Headquarters?!
Yeah. As people say,
Vice-Admiral Garp seems quite eccentric.
But he's higher up, right?
Yeah, you have no idea.
Then those two must be promising.
Hmm?
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Why did you let them go
without saying anything?!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
I... wanted to play with them more.
I wanted to talk to them more...
I was learning how to cook so that
I could make them a tasty lunch!
I didn't even say... good bye!
Ahh, uhm...
Why did they leave?!
Ahh, I'm sorry! Forgive me!
Rika, that's enough. Leave him alone.
Don't worry. They'll surely come back...
after becoming fine officers.
But at any rate,
can we really become marines
by doing things like this?
This might be that old
dog's hobby, you know.
Hobby?
That's right. A hobby called
"the retired geezer's torment of youths."
Don't you think that's possible
since he seems crafty and eccentric?
Shut up, birds!!
That old geezer sure is
quick to resort to violence.
His name is Vice-Admiral Garp!
Hey, do you know...
...that he's called "Garp the Fist"
and quite feared by everyone?
No wonder his fist was
heavier than Alvida's...
No, that's not the point!
Stop with the pointless chatter already!
Especially while we're working!
You get me in trouble, too.
Don't be so coldhearted.
It's our joint responsibility.
We're friends, right?
You say that only when
it's convenient for you.
Then please work more seriously.
Okay, okay.
On second thought, I quit!
What?!
I wanna go back to how I used to live.
It's no use saying
something like that now...
...although it's a different story
if we became a Navy officer...
That's the thing!
What's the thing?
We can't run away, nor can we slack off.
If that's the case, there's only one
way to go back to how I used to live.
That would be becoming important
quickly, don't you think?
What?!
"Don't I think"? There's no
way things can be that easy.
We have to work hard
and steadily with patience.
You wanna take an easy way? That's just...
What're you doing?
Doing only chores and continuing to
wait around won't get us anywhere.
So I think I'll strengthen my body.
You're kidding, right?
You know that's not possible.
We work so hard during the day
that we're physically a wreck.
Let's go to bed now.
I've already decided.
What?
I'll become important and go
back to how I used to live.
I'll surpass my dad, too.
I've decided just now!
Even so... There's no way
that your body can keep up!
Impossible! Impossible!
Impossible! Definitely impossible!
If you do that, you'll die!
Once you've decided
to become that way...
if you can die fighting for that,
you should be happy! Right?
I've... already decided.
Well, I don't wanna die, but...
There's no turning back.
I'll go as far as I can.
Later, Coby.
Please wait!
Hmm? What is it, Coby?
I should've known better...
I carelessly said wimpy
things like I used to...
You're right. The issue isn't
if we can do it or not,
but if we have the will to do it.
I've decided just now, too.
Your motive is a little impure, but...
I'll go along with your spirit!
Huh?
It's fine by me!
Then we'll compete
and see who drops first!
That's just what I want!
I'm telling you now that I won't lose!
Ha! Say whatever you want!
See you later. I'm going ahead of you.
Ah! That's not nice to go alone!
Who cares? We're not friends.
I don't have time
to be buddy-buddy with you!
What're you saying?
That's not what you said earlier at all!
Ow, ow, ow...
One, two! One, two!
One, two!
One, two! One, two! One...
So this is Straw Hat Luffy,
the 30 million-Berry bounty head!
We have to capture a vicious,
dirty pirate like him
as soon as possible
and put him to execution!
Indeed!
Luffy-san is wanted for bounty...
Something is wrong, isn't it?
Stupid! A pirate is a pirate.
Once he's caught,
he's set to be executed.
I know that!
But it's not that easy
to accept it, you know!
Luffy-san and I are friends.
Shhhh!
Idiot! No marine has
a pirate for a friend.
Don't ever say that again!
Or you'll get fired from the Navy!
I know that much!
I won't say such a thing anywhere else!
You swear? Geez...
V-V-Vice-Admiral Garp!
What? You guys were talking
about something interesting.
Let me hear it, too.
So who's your friend?
Come with me...
I'll ask you again.
You two're friends
with that Straw Hat Luffy?
I don't know if Helmeppo-san is, but I am!
He said that we are friends
even if we're apart.
I suppose you're aware of this,
but we can't keep people
like that in the Navy.
But fortunately,
I'm the only one who knows it.
Do you wanna be a marine?!
Please wait a second!
It's true that I'm Luffy-san's friend,
but Helmeppo-san has nothing to...
We do! That's why we're here!
Helmeppo-san!
Idiot! He isn't someone
who'd listen to that now.
It's joint responsibility.
Joint responsibility.
What about you, Coby?!
Don't you wanna be one?
I do!!
Then, stop grumbling
and bring it on already!
We're not done yet!
Yeah!
No good!
We're not done yet!
We're not dead yet!
You wanna die that bad?
I've decided to be a marine.
Hm?
If I die fighting for it, I'll be happy.
No way we'd give it up yet!
I'm a man who will become a Navy officer!
Huh?
A Navy officer, huh? That's interesting.
People here have been calling
me eccentric for quite a while,
and especially this time,
they said all sorts of things.
Since I brought you here, I have to
train you so that you'll be very useful.
I tested you two to see
what you are really like.
What we're really like?
Although it may appear that you've been
trying hard strengthening your bodies,
I thought you might
still be weak mentally.
So I tested you to see if you're
working with firm determination.
So what's the verdict?
I'll acknowledge your determination.
But...
...you've still got a long way to go!
When it comes to weakness,
you guys take the cake!
You'll have an intense
special training every day.
Be prepared!
I'll overlook your friend situation.
But don't tell anyone.
Just cherish that feeling.
Yes sir! Thank you very much,
Vice-Admiral Garp!!
Alright! Let's go!!
Little Garden...
Yeah!
You've got me!
Ah, gentle song
Make it there for us
After a wave washed away
that little sand castle
You looked up at the passing
clouds with a sad smile
If you find the world is full of enemies,
I've got your back
Don't lose faith
You've got me!
Ah, my love
I'll hold you in my arms forever
You've got me!
So this is Little Garden!
What's "little" about it?!
It's like an undiscovered land.
It's a thick jungle.
I hope there's a BBQ restaurant in here.
As if there'd be one!
This isn't normal!
This is definitely not normal!
It's decided that we're not gonna go
ashore on this island... Right, guys?
I can smell adventure in the air!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An Ancient Island!
The Shadow Hiding in Little Garden!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!