Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
On top of that, he put prices
on the heads of Luffy and
11 others, and now they're being
hunted by all the citizens.
And with the Straw Hats
fighting the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
Doflamingo stood in
Luffy and Law's way to the Royal Palace!
I can't go on... like this!
"A United Front!
Luffy's Breakthrough to the Victory!"
THE ROYAL PALACE
I'm feeling sentimental now...
What did you come here for?
BELLAMY THE HYENA
A PIRATE, BOUNTY: 195 MILLION BERRIES
Did you kill Straw Hat, Bellamy?
Why did you send Dellinger to kill me?!
Was it really your order?!
Oh boy... What rubbish...
Isn't there any...
...hope left for me?
Don't make me say it straight, Bellamy.
Your purpose was different from mine.
From long ago.
You always wanted to become a pirate.
But not me.
Anything was fine with me.
Anything?
As long as I could...
...destroy this world!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 2
THE COLOSSEUM ARMY VS THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY
Move! Move! Move!
You move, Ideo!
What?!
I'll take down Doflamingo!
Back off, you bastard!
The one who'll take down Doflamingo and
repay Straw Hat my debt is me!
Get out of my way, kid!
I'm in a rush!
Hey, what do I look like?
Hey, tell me, Suleiman!
So quick!
Humph... No matter how quick he moves,
I won't lose him!
You used to be a war executioner, right?!
Those well-developed muscles...
High heels...
His specialty must be...
I love... executing people!
Kicks!
What?!
Oh no... That's too bad.
It's over already.
Here come the Executives of the Family!
Even the Executives are showing
up now, it's too late!
I will repay my debt!
It's the former leader of the
Happosui Army - Chin Jao!
Take him down and win fame!
Yeah!
Humph! It's not gonna work!
Alright! I'm gonna get
to the third level first!
What are these bulging stones?
That place is dangerous. Mine...
...Pop!
Grandpa! I'm coming!
Da-in!
Floaty, floaty...
Ten-Ton Vise!
You see it, idiots?!
That's how powerful our
Family's Executives are!
No, it's just that these guys are...
...too fragile.
Too fra"g"ile! There's the "G"!
Shut up, geezer!
You freak!
--He did it!
--They can't go any farther!
I got you!
Armsmorphosis!
Revolver Leg!
THE TOWN IN THE SOUTH - SEVIO
Darling... Please...
Don't do it!
I-I know...
You know I wouldn't...
...shoot you two...
But because of Doflamingo,
my body...
...is out of my control...
Please run! I beg you!
No...
Don't...
I got him!
--Bring the rope now!
--And treat him! He's been shot!
--The rest of you, put out the fire!
--Okay!
I'm sorry... I'm sorry... Thank you!
I almost killed my family!
It was terrible!
THE OLD KING'S PLATEAU
Do you want to cause the same
tragedy again, Doflamingo?
As long as our captain's here,
he won't let it happen.
Earlier, Rebecca and the others
took off from around there, I suppose...
--Is that... King Riku?!
--What?! Let me see!
There's another big-timer!
It was me who set the
town on fire! I'm sorry!
I sliced up my own friend!
Me, too! Dammit!
It's not your fault.
Everything happened
because of Doflamingo's meddling!
We gotta bring
an end to this game somehow...
Hey!
We found out where King Riku is!
He's with the Five-star God Usopp!
Alright... Let's do it!
But we only capture them!
Okay?
Yeah, if we don't do it,
this game will last until we die!
First, take King Riku and
God Usopp as hostages.
And lure other criminals
using those hostages!
Yeah!
Tell the people all over the country!
Head for Old King's Plateau!
Yeah!
Capture King Riku and God Usopp!
Bring an end to this game by ourselves!
Yeah!
BENEATH THE OLD KING'S PLATEAU - THE JUNKYARD
Kanjuro!
Tell me! Where are you?!
It's Kin'emon!
Answer me if you're here! Kanjuro!
I hear it again!
That beast-like voice...
--Where is it coming from?!
--No idea.
Is it some kind of a curse?
Where is it?!
Where does it come from?!
Don't tell me this voice is...
Everybody, be quiet!
Right there?!
THE SMILE FACTORY
What are you guys doing?!
Did you knock over this SAD tank?!
Pick it up!
Are you okay?!
Please stop! There was a sudden earthquake
and the tank got knocked over!
--He's right!
--What caused that earthquake?!
Shut up! You guys don't
need to worry about it!
But...
Don't you guys wanna cure
Princess Mancherie's illness?!
I bet you do!
Of course, we wanna cure it!
How is she doing?!
Um...
I'm afraid the princess isn't
getting better at all!
At all!
What?!
Everybody, are you ready?!
Yeah!
Let's go!
Please! Let us see the princess!
Oh, damn! What a pain!
Shut up and work!
Is that...
You fools, just stop grumbling
and keep making SMILEs!
FROM INSIDE, UNLOCK...
What are you guys doing?!
I said work, idiots!
Quit zoning out! Can't you hear me?!
...THE DOOR!
Those words...
It's the Pink Bees!
Bian!
Inhel! Wicka!
Bomba! Cotton!
Everybody!
They noticed us! Bian!
Roger that!
Pink Bees, the next message!
WE GOT FOOLED!!!
What? "We got fooled"?
What do they mean?
Hey, you guys! Can't you hear us?!
We got fooled?
Is it about the princess' illness?
Doflamingo has been fooling us?
FIGHT!!!
"Fight"?!
I guess you need another beating
to understand things.
I don't know what's going on
but one thing I know is...
Friends don't lie!
--Shut up!
--Sanshita!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF
THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 2
Commodore Hug!
You're too slu"gg"ish! There're the "Gs"!
One more coming-in!
This is it for this guy-in!
Ten-Ton Vise!
--Are you okay?!
--Yeah! You alright, Grandpa?!
That little brat!
Mine Pop.
It's dangerous there, too.
And there.
No! That's it?
I wanted to see more of the Longleg
tribe's kicking techniques!
It's too bad!
Destruction Cannon!
Is it Ideo?!
Too slow!
This is like a gathering of comedians!
I guess we're not supposed to
fight to get there first now.
-Yeah.
Armsmorphosis!
Revolver Girl!
A lite version of King Punch!
Dagama, we're gonna lose this battle
if nothing is done!
Straw Hat!
It's me, military tactician
Dagama's chance to show off!
Doflamingo's at the top of this place?!
Cabbage!
Do you wanna get in my way, again?!
No...
--Get on.
--What?
I mean I'll give you a ride
because I have no other choice!
You sure?!
You wanna get to Doflamingo ASAP, don't you?
Alright!
I'm ready! go!
Have you ever once in your life
been humble?!
--Whatever, just go!
--Don't tell me what to do!
Let's go, Farul!
Listen, if we get caught by the Executives,
we get stuck here.
I'm gonna cut the wall and make a path
so you kick the other enemies' asses!
Got it!
And we're gonna go straight to
the third level...
Hey! That's one too many!
Who are you?!
--Oh, Soldier!
--When did you get on?!
Just now!
I followed the path that Luffyland made!
I see. That's how you followed Straw Hat
and got on Farul... Hey!
--You followed too far!
--Great! I was looking for you!
Even if you're his friend, we're overloaded!
Get off!
We're gonna meet up with Rebecca!
Rebecca is in this enemy territory?!
Why didn't you stop her?!
Listen to me!
We'll rendezvous at the Sunflower Field
on the fourth level.
She's on the criminal list, too!
Don't worry! She's with my friends!
Listen! My dear horse Farul
only can run beautifully
with two people or less!
The bull's back had more space...
By the way, pops,
why did you take off before I knew it?
Whatever the situation is...
what I have to do is...
...bring down Doflamingo
and take back the country!
But there's one more thing!
There's one man in the
Family's Top Executives
that I wanna kill with my
own bare hands at any cost!
Old dude, you're not willing to die,
are you?
No way! I won't be defeated
with this human body!
--Alright, then!
--Nothing's alright! Get off!
Huh?! You get off!
That's nonsense!
You're the worst!
You really are part of the Worst Generation!
Watch out, fool!
Look where you're going! Hey!
Like I said, don't tell me what to do!
What?!
Is that...
Go ahead, Straw Hat!
We're gonna keep them busy!
What-in?! They're suddenly...
They were disorganized before,
fighting each other!
What?! Why are you doing this, guys?!
I'm Dagama, the military tactician!
This is a war!
Even if we all run wild blindly,
no one can reach the top!
I don't trust Dagama
but I agreed to his plan.
Keep the Executives here
and let Straw Hat go ahead!
Leave this mess here to us and go!
Make sure to take him there,
Cavendish!
Hey hey,
I'm not public transportation!
We gotta win this war!
Interesting...
Let's go!
The motley band of ruffians
quick offense and defense
allows Luffy and the others to
get close to the Royal Palace!
Meanwhile, Kin'emon finally reunites
the other samurai
of the Wano Kingdom, Kanjuro!
In order to get out of the
deep-underground junkyard,
Kanjuro practices unbelievable sorcery!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Second Samurai! Evening
Shower Kanjuro Appears!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!