Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
do I have to get up to make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
I don't want to settle for small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
Whiffing through the air, off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Mercilessly, beat me, hit me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal, we got to carry on the way
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without thinking of the consequences
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
Luffy and the others formed
a pirate alliance with
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
they were trapped along with the entire island.
On top of that, he put prices
on the heads of Luffy and
11 others, and now they're being
hunted by all the citizens.
I'll pay 100 million berries
for each star rating!
11 others, and now they're being
hunted by all the citizens.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
And with the Straw Hats
fighting the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
100 million berries?!
Luffy and Law are heading
to the Royal Palace!
On top of that, he put prices on
the heads of Luffy and 11 others,
Luffy and Law are heading
to the Royal Palace!
Doflamingo stood in
Luffy and Law's way to the Royal Palace!
Damn! Those meatheads were
disorganized before
and now they're being hunted
by all the citizens.
Is everybody okay?!
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
We all came to save you!
but now they've teamed up!
Isn't there any...
All right! Go straight to
the fourth level like this!
Diaper Bombs!
...hope left for me?
Luffy and Law are heading
to the Royal Palace!
You always wanted to become a pirate.
Horse!
Nipple Light Special!
Is that...
Don't worry, long-nosed goblin man!
They were having trouble so...
Sugar is awake now!
But not me.
Oh no!
"The Little People's Princess!
Captive Mansherry!"
Anything was fine with me.
It sent chills down my spine
I made a net for them!
What's the matter, Farul?
when I realized Robin had been
turned into a toy, too, earlier!
Why did you do such a thing, you fool?!
As long as I could...
--They're coming to get me!
--Was it unnecessary?!
I didn't even realize
I had forgotten about her!
...destroy this world!
If Sugar touches Luffy,
I'll forget about him like that!
Is that...
Princess Mansherry, where are you?
Roger that!
Pink Bees, the next message!
There was a room...
Your friend disappears
and you won't even know it!
I can't take it!
FIGHT!!!
I have no option left now!
I'll shoot her from here!
Well done. Guys!
I guess you need another beating
to understand things.
What are those giant dolls?!
There you are, Mansherry!
It's a robot!
I don't know what's going on
but one thing I know is...
Do you know the position you're in?
A robot came to save us!
"A Hard-Fought Battle Against Pica!
Zoro's Deadly Attack!"
Our bond can't be broken
even if anyone tries.
Friends don't lie!
Thank you!
"Invincible!
A Gruesome Army of Headcracker Dolls!"
--A robot!
--Cool!
--Shut up!
--Sanshita!
Is everybody okay?!
Just remember.
If Luffy ever calls for my help,
Go ahead, Straw Hat!
How are you?!
We all came to save you!
Leave this mess here to us and go!
no matter where I am in the world,
I'll be there - forget my position!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
To save... us?
Make sure to take him there,
Cavendish!
Hey hey,
I'm not public transportation!
Tin soldiers?!
Dodge, Farul!
We gotta win this war!
Oh, those are...
Farul!
...the Executives of the Doflamingo Family!
Stay with me!
What a powerful jaw!
It crushed his head!
I-I'm so happy for all of you!
Watch out. Don't let them see you.
Don't die on me, Farul!
"The Second Samurai!
Evening Shower Kanjuro Appears!"
--Thank you, Robot-san!
--His name is not Robot!
Okay!
Are they invincible?!
They're a little too big to be children's toys
but...
He's our savior, a Big Human - Fraland!
Pop Baller!
...more than that...
A Big Human?!
Princess Mansherry!
Is she alright?!
As for Princess Mansherry,
Mouji is...
We're almost at the Flower Field
on the fourth level!
They're in bad taste!
Oh no! My Yellow Cubs...
...looking now...
If we can see Luffy and the others there,
S... S... S...
Don't let Straw Hat and the others
proceed to the third level!
we can hand over the key to Tra-guy-kun's cuffs.
She's not here.
Robin-san!
Rebecca, take the key to the Sunflower Field!
Bring them down at any cost-in!
You guys!
Princess Mansherry is...
I can... I can see Luffy-senpai soon!
...nowhere to be found! No way!
I'll be fine!
Cien Fleurs!
Princess? Princess? Princess?
Where are you?!
Wing!
Luffy-senpai!
Not here!
Oh, Bartolomeo!
Robin!
The princess isn't here!
We won't let you go any farther from here!
I've been waiting for you!
Luffy! Tra-guy-kun!
You guys are here!
What? Y-You've been waiting for me?
We've been fooled! I can't believe it!
L-Luffy-senpai has been waiting for me!
She got away...
Let's shear through them all at once! Farul!
Stop!
Well, she's just one little tramp.
I can't help being emotional!
Go!
I know she can't do anything
even if she can get to the Palace.
Princess, please be safe!
I, Mouji, am coming to save you!
Hey, where are you going?
Luffy! Tra-guy-kun!
And Soldier-san, too!
Oh! One of them tripped!
--What?
--Are you okay?
--Don't bother us!
--Go away!
Just go now!
To the Sunflower Field on the fourth level!
Are they that clumsy?!
Princess!
Y-Yes. I'm sorry to be late.
Wait, Mouji!
You go away!
Princess!
That's right!
Where are you?!
Rebecca's waiting for you!
Just go!
Well, I wasn't worried a bit.
Not here! Not here!
What?
Princess? Princess? Princess!!
Because you're my friend!
Okay.
F-Friend?!
What the...!
It tried to chew on my head!
Destruction Cannon!
Prin...
...cess!!
Friend... Friend... Friend...
"Risking Their Lives!
Luffy is the Trump Card for Victory!"
Stay alert!
I don't care what happens anymore...
What?
Why are you crying?
Damn! Those meatheads were
disorganized before
We're gonna go like this!
Each of you, defend yourself!
Never you mind.
It has to do with the treasure in my heart.
Princess!
--Mouji, wait!
--Where are you?!
Okay!
but now they've teamed up!
Princess!
Everybody! You're getting so much better at using
Oh? I hear a strange noise.
the Tontatta Airlines' Jumping Service!
Oh, just rats!
--Leo! Can you hear me?
--Yes, Viola-sama!
I don't like it but I have no choice
but to count on you guys now!
--I found Princess Mansherry!
--What?! Really?!
Cavendish!
I gotta find her! Princess!
Take Straw Hat to the Royal Palace
at any cost!
The Palace!
Princess Mansherry's in the Palace!
Wait!
How could you even think
you were good enough to kill Straw Hat?
We all looked... but Princess Mansherry may not be here!
Great! Where in the Palace?
They're saying whatever they want!
The small room at
the back of the chapel...
What?!
You can't find Princess Mansherry?!
You bastard!
Remember?
What kind of person is Princess Mansherry?
--Chapel...
--The back...
Let's go, Farul!
Princess Mansherry is...
A small...
...room?
You fools!
I won't let you get away!
How dare you pay no notice to me
for such a long time!
I remember now!
Damn!
The naughty room!
It's the fourth level! We're here!
Yes! That's it!
Is she the princess?
Uh-huh! Thank you all!
No way!
The factory...
...is...
I guess he got away!
...my life!
Destruction Cannon!
What's wrong?
I'm the factory manager.
I'm the most powerful figure in this factory!
Thank you, Yellow Cubs!
I just remembered Scarlet-sama.
Yeah...
Thank you!
Your back was un"g"uarded!
There's the "G"!
My mother?
Pulpostone!
When we used to go to the Palace,
What?!
we were mischievous with Viola-sama
Why're you guys flying?!
You're Cyborg Franky of the Straw Hats,
aren't you?
Zoro!
and got scolded by King Riku-sama!
Z-Z-Z-Z-Zoro-senpai!
You're a One-star criminal.
How did you make it this far alive?
Prepare to be shattered into pieces!
Mine Pop.
Oh! D-Do you remember
you promised me your autograph?!
He wants you to stay in here
and think about what you've done.
Robin-san and Bartolomeo-san...
Are they okay?
What did you do to Pink-sama?
That's...
I know they are!
Usoland's friends are strong!
That fool?
No! No! Let me out!
Pica!
--He did it!
--That serves them right!
A FEW MINUTES AGO
I saw a weak old granny
Rebecca!
Not until King Riku-sama allows it!
You idiots, just go after Straw
Hat and the others already!
Who is it?
having trouble in the back street
Yeah! You're right!
He's one of the Top Executives of the
What? But it's almost dinner time!
Uh-huh!
Y-Yes, sir!
on the right!
Rebecca-sama!
We have to go save Princess Mansherry now!
Don Quixote Family along
with Trebol and Diamante!
I just remembered I have
Armsmorphosis!
Until King Riku-sama permits it,
you can't eat!
some minor business to attend to.
Oh no! If he attacks us now,
we can't avoid it!
Uh-huh!
Is it okay to leave you here alone?
Revolver Girl!
Wait!
I guess it's tough to live a hard-boiled life.
I'll be fine! Lucy and the
others will come soon!
Zoro! Keep the enemy there for us!
What're you talking about?
Go save her!
I thought you guys didn't believe in
teaming up with others!
We have to move beyond this stone figure!
Okay!
Rebecca-sama, you take care, too!
Viola-sama!
THE FLOWER FIELD
THE CURRENT LOCATION
While Viola-sama is locked up,
There's no old granny!
Uh-huh!
we gotta think about what we've done
in this naughty room.
Garp's grandson is worth
bending our beliefs!
I can do that but...
Anyway, I won't let you do as you like in this factory!
...that aside, why're you guys flying...?
Leo! Cub! Inhel!
I'm gonna take your life!
Here I go!
But it's good that we have each other!
Oh? The enemy got away, didn't he?!
Head-Arms!
Watch out! Run, Fraland!
--Why?
--It's sad to be all alone!
Oh boy!
Did he run because he's got frighten by
how strong Zoro-senpai is?!
You're right! This room is bleak so...
Hm? She got away?!
But...
No, he didn't get away!
Fraland hugged the factory manager!
Oh, I'm hungry.
I won't let you get to the Palace!
Yes...
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
LEVEL 3
--Big Sis!
--Scarlet-sama!
Entertain me, K-I-N-G!
He got in there...
What?!
--We're totally surrounded.
--Aren't they increasing?
H-He's targeting us!
Did you get scolded again?
You never learn.
Destroying them all is
the only way to advance, it seems.
Pistol High-Heel!
It's not my fault!
Leo and those two broke a plate!
--Oh yeah! Your barrier!
--It's impossible!
Soldier-san is a brave man
First, I can't use my hands!
Alright!
You told us we could "break" it!
Plus, I can't put up a barrier that
can cover us from that massive punch!
He will always be by your side
Kick all their asses, you mean?
No! I said you could "touch" it!
--Yes.
--That's right.
No!
But if nothing is done, we're gonna...
Huh?!
...get blown away!
I'll come and apologize with you later.
Gum-Gum Gatling!
Really?!
Yes. Anyway, aren't you hungry?
Father-sama must be
somewhere on this battlefield, too...
I guess a king's life is very valuable!
We are!
Then, let's eat these together!
Oh? My leg is stuck!
Three-Sword Style!
Thank you!
Thousand-and-Eighty Pound Phoenix!
We all loved Scarlet-sama so much...!
Whoa! Thank you! You saved me.
Kid, you give me a lot of trouble.
Uh-huh!
She was always kind and gentle to us...
It's coming.
I couldn't get him...
Thank you!
Humph!
I just wanted to kill that bastard!
--They're coming one after another!
--We can't spend too much time here!
I'll take care of them all at once!
--I will!
--No, me!
Ten-Ton Vise!
I still remember the naughty room well!
First come, first served, then!
Thank you for the information!
Somebody made it here, huh?
The Palace is now the enemy's headquarters.
Hajrudin!
Be careful, Leo!
Don't lower your guard-in! Dellinger!
Roger that!
We'll save our princess at any cost!
H-Hey, what's going on?!
What are you doing?! Let go of me!
I was just playing with him.
I can kill him anytime.
Clank.
Fraland hugged the manager!
I'm starting to see how your power works!
Did Fraland fall in love with her?!
Way to go!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
She's Fraland's type?
As my allies, they're all reliable warriors.
That cyborg idiot, how dare he fool me!
THE THIRD LEVEL - LUFFY AND THE OTHERS
--This doesn't mean I became your ally!
--Don't push your luck, Dagama!
Hey, you soprano-voiced fool!
There's no troubled old granny anywhere.
Well, I'm relieved to know that.
Keep them away from the Royal Palace!
I forgot to tell you one thing.
Oh! So hard-boiled!
Alright! Those creepy dolls are gone!
Bring down Straw Hat!
The Straw Hats are...
Señor Pink!
I'm ready! Bring it on anytime!
Let's go!
...not just Straw Hat Luffy and God Usopp.
Cabbage! Get on already!
It's you...
Why're you guys getting on before me!
Ready?! Bring it on?! You ready for what?!
Cut it out! Are you nuts?!
Dodge, Farul!
So manly!
Secure the way for Straw Hat!
Don't forget!
Horse!
He's so aggressive.
I'm the man who's destined to become
Is it still alive?!
That idiot!
Yeah!
Gum-Gum...
You bastard!
the greatest swordsman in the world one day!
--Luffy-senpai, let me take this!
--Crest Head!
Oh! So cool!
This battle... Now is the crucial point!
Gum-Gum Jet Pistol!
Barrier!
Farul!
Looks like that guy is taking command.
Hey, stop messing with
the morals in the factory!
Stay with me!
He's annoying!
What a powerful jaw!
It crushed his head!
That bastard has been throwing me around with suplexes!
Those are balls of explosives!
They'll explode before you deflect them!
Don't die on me, Farul!
Doro-tenpai!
Wow! Cool!
Was he...
...trying to dig up a hot spring or something
with the back of my head?!
Oh no! I don't deserve such praise!
Daruma!
What are you talking about?!
What the... I blew a hole in its stomach!
What the... Hey, let go off me!
You jerk!
Bartolomeo...
Drop dead!
Go!
You monster!
How could you do this to Farul?!
Cat-Ear Punch!
Gum-Gum...
Franky Southland Suplex!
Blade of Beauty! Round Table!
...Jet Whip!
Get to the top! Straw Hat!
Cool!! I just saw his Second Gear
and Jet Whip up close!
--The Little People are going crazy!
--Keep them down!
So impressive!
Hey, Straw Hat-ya, just get rid of them
and let's move along already!
You're taking too much time!
--Shoot, shoot!
--Keep them off at any price!
What?!
Ouch!
Hey, you!
Don't talk to Luffy-senpai like that!
I've got an idea!
Open the door to the factory
and let our friends in!
Barrier-bility: Stairs!
Blade of Beauty! Saint-Exupéry!
No! The manager is...
Yeah!
That hurt, you jerk!
How could you use my head like a hammer?!
Are they invincible?!
Let's go with them!
How dare you treat me so cruelly!
Gum-Gum Jet Gatling!
I'm the factory manager!
I'm the most powerful figure here!
Those toys...! Don't tell me...!
Oh no! Oh no!
You...
MOUJI - AN AIDE TO THE PRINCESS
Once she gets mad, nobody can stop her!
Is the princess okay?!
I-It's humiliating for us samurai
to get hit on the head!
Princess!
Please run, Fraland!
I'd rather take responsibility for providing
Now, what should I do with you?!
I can do anything I want!
Awesome!
You saved us a lot of trouble!
the enemies a net and commit hara-kiri!
Mouji! Seems like Princess
Mansherry's not here on this floor!
Please use it, Luffy-senpai!
I have the power to punish people
in this factory!
You're such a pain!
I said I'd forgive you with just a few bruises!
What?!
Why're you looking the other way?
Are... you... sure?!!
THE EXECUTIVE TOWER
Thank you, Crest Head!
You're sentenced to death! Death!
Because you deserve it!
Th...
THE JUNKYARD
...a...
Hold out, Kanjuro! Bear with it!
...n...
KIN'EMON
...k...
Insulting me is a grave crime!
...you?!
Then, where is she?!
What you've done was that sinful!
I'll cut up your body and
suck your guts up with my vacuum
The advance unit's making a dash for...
But, Usopp-dono,
why should I get hit, too?
That way?!
then pound them into pieces!
I am coming! Princess!
Why don't you cry like a baby, you...
You two are collectively responsible.
No, Mouji!
So creepy.
Is that...
Is there a beast or something?
Choo-choo! Huff-puff!
What's wrong?
You still looking for something, Viola?
It's coming from around here.
Sugar is awake now!
He's gone...
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you! Thank...
What?!
Hey! What are you talking about?!
Sugar had been...
...completely knocked out
with my Special Facial Jack in the Box
Not at all!
Fraland kissed the factory manager!
I'm the one who has to thank you
for being born!
I said I can't eat anymore...
and it seemed like
she wouldn't wake up for a couple days...
All right!
The Straw Hats and the others...
They don't know her, do they?!
We can go straight to the fourth level this way!
Let's go, Tra-guy!
Could it be...?
Go!
Or her ability.
Sugar is totally recovered!
Straw Hat and the others are in danger!
What?!
H-He kissed...
Manager!
This guy just stole a kiss from me...
W-We have a problem!
The Little People raised a revolt!
What?
--Now, get up, you swimming idiot!
--H-Hey!
E-Everybody with a long nose, stay away!
Everyone with a long nose, drop dead!
We're struggling to bring them
under control so we need you...
Wait a minute!
What are you thinking?!
Why did you do that?!
Issho-san! Ow! Ow!
What?! I thought you'd be hungry
so I brought...
B-Be a man about it
and become my boyfriend!
Is it morning already?
No good! We can't get closer
because of the fire!
...these.
What are you guys doing?!
How pathetic!
How's that possible?
You fool!
We can't go around either because
What?!
the collapsed buildings are blocking our way!
Somebody was in the wall?!
The manager just became a bit
more feminine...
They're just sausages.
I-I'm sorry!
Don't bring me stick-shaped things!
The Flare-Flare Fruit!
Snacks must be grapes!
Are you an idiot?!
The troublesome guy gained
a troublesome power!
You can't blame him, factory manager.
What useless pieces of shit!
What?
Fire Fist!
Turn into a Headcracker Doll like the others and go fight!
--You got involved. It's your fault.
--Pink-sama! But...
You cut in to a fight between grown men.
When a woman does that,
Stupid shrimps!
They're pushing their luck!
I feel bad for Young Master-sama...
K... K...
how else can we seal her mouth?
I'll turn everyone in this country...
Ka...
Kan...!
This is a good opportunity!
...into toys again!
Getting upset over a kiss or two makes you
Hey you...
What are you trying to do?
First, that damn, annoying long-nose
and his clan!
I'm gonna teach them a lot of lessons!
just an immature little tramp. So don't talk about...
I know Navy admirals are much more powerful!
The Straw Hats!
...love or relationships
or that sort of stuff!
If Sugar uses her ability,
That's right.
the people and the soldiers of Dressrosa
will get turned into toys again!
Love with a little chick like that...
Stop messing around!
You're an odd person.
...Would drive me nuts!
I thought you wanted to keep us Navy at bay.
Oh no!
Usopp-dono, is it that serious a problem?!
I missed you so much!
I'm glad that you're okay!
How long will you keep up with the act?
It sent chills down my spine
Kanjuro!
So hard-boiled!
when I realized Robin had been turned into a toy, too, earlier!
Oh boy...
As you can see,
I need people to go easy on me...
Señor! Franky!
How hard-boiled you two are!
I didn't even realize
I had forgotten about her!
Oh, Kin'emon!
This is great!
It's getting intense!
I don't discriminate.
If Sugar touches Luffy,
I'll forget about him like that!
Is that what "hard-boiled" is?
It's no good!
We can't get control of them!
Really!
I'm sorry.
I think I made you search for me a bit.
I won't let you destroy the factory!
Don't give up! Keep shooting!
You scare me.
Your friend disappears
and you won't even know it!
You're not known as No.2 of the Revolutionary Army
for nothing, I guess.
Humph! Prove it with your fists! If you're a man!
What?!
Some strange things happened
one after another
I can't take it!
Franky-sama! Pink-sama!
We're not gonna get hit by
bad people's bullets!
That'll send chills down on
my spine, too...
so I was planning to hide
myself in the wall for a while
A SAMURAI FROM THE WANO KINGDOM
EVENING SHOWER KANJURO
It's gonna start! The men's fight!
I won't let that happen!
but I fell asleep before I knew it.
Can't we tell them through the Transponder Snail?
Anyway, Kin'emon,
I can't believe you came back!
I've been calling them
but they haven't noticed!
The net-climbers are
getting pretty close, too!
What are you saying...
W-Wait!
But I'm in the position that
requires me to do this.
Aren't you worried about Princess Mansherry?!
Catch God Usopp and King Riku!
Oh no! Momonosuke!
What?
If you guys get out of here,
Princess Mansherry will never get cured!
Please understand.
I have no option left now!
Go after Momonosuke! Don't worry about me!
I'll shoot her from here!
But, Usopp-dono,
shooting her from this far is...
Th-That's not good!
Gravity Blade!
Right?! If you guys leave,
Sorry to keep you waiting for so long!
...impossible!
I'm sure Princess-san will be very sad!
I can barely see the Palace
with my naked eye.
I trusted you so I didn't mind even a bit.
Don't be so stiff and formal, friend.
Princess...
And the enemy is behind the wall.
I can't even see her!
No! Don't listen to them, Chao!
Diaper Bombs!
Raging Tiger!
No matter how tough, I gotta do it!
With my sorcery,
I didn't have a problem getting food.
Okay, if you understand,
quit fighting and just obey us...
Nipple Light Special!
We'll assist you!
Yeah, if I fail, Sugar will put up her guard
What?!
I put in earplugs so I can't
hear your stupid lies anymore!
and there will be no second chance!
Oh well, I'm not hungry at all but...
Tontatta Swing!
It's gonna take a lot of precision
to get her with one shot for sure!
Want some lettuce?
No, I don't.
With your Clairvoyance,
tell me Sugar's location in detail!
Your food never agrees with my stomach.
--Report Young Master-sama!
--O-Okay!
Well, as long as
you and Momonosuke are okay...
Yes, count on me!
You can't do that!
All right!
All right, now...
I beat up the most!
Tontatta: Tail...
Yes, we are, thanks to you!
...Four-man Hammer!
Good. I hope I can see Momonosuke soon.
Everybody! Release all
their Transponder Snails
Yeah, Momonosuke is looking
forward to seeing you, too!
into the wild so they can't call for backup!
So many things happened since I last saw you
Gravity Blade!
Are you listening?!
but I can't put it all in a nutshell!
IN FRONT OF THE PLATEAU -
LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
THE STATUE OF PICA
What?
You stop that assimilating with the stone crap?
We have a lot to talk about!
I'll tell you later!
What?
Raging Tiger!
Okay, got it! Let's get out of here!
Earplugs!
How dare you let Rebecca and
the others get away!
Get out?
Is there a way to get out of here?
Thank you!
I couldn't have done it without you.
How is he gonna do that?
Now, let's hurry up and open the door!
Don't think shitheads like you guys
can escape this country!
Help!
What?! Princess is...
Horizontal gravity?!
Princess Mansherry is not sick?!
Halt!
He never learns!
About face!
Inhel and the others outside said...
That's what I thought!
We've been totally fooled, haven't we?!
Is he...?
Yes, sir!
Drawing something?
Huh?! Why are we obeying him?!
Zoro-senpai!
Where's the princess?!
Yeah! This is just what I expected from him!
I'm still so impressed!
--U-Ummm...
--They split up and went to look...
Rooster-kun, get yourself together!
We're almost there!
I see!
That way, huh?!
This jerk! What is he up to?!
But Zoro-senpai was so cool!
Oh, wait!
Come on out!
It's good that her illness was a lie!
We're almost there at the second level!
Be careful where you land!
But she's been alone all
this time in the factory...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
I understand!
--Mouji... I Mouji understand your feelings!
--Wait!
--Hello, this is Leo.
--It's Mouji!
Spring Sparrow!
I know the princess is crying now!
Mouji! I'm glad to hear from you!
It means our friends have been released!
She's crying and calling out my name!
--What?!
--No way!
Armsmorphosis!
But Leo, we have a big problem...
Flying Disc Girl!
There's a Little Person!
What is it?
Calling "Mouji! Mouji!"
--His drawing started moving!
--Is he a Devil Fruit eater?
Humph! Bring it on!
The princess is...
Princess Mansherry is...
I'll accept the onslaught from all of your techniques!
...nowhere to be found in the factory!
Princess!
What?!
The poor dear...
Mouji!
She must be locked up somewhere
and crying "Mouji! Mouji!"
Princess!
That picture of a bird came to life!
No...
Please wait for me!
Get to the old King's Plateau!
But the drawing is terrible...
Oh, it says "Don't run" in this hallway.
Yeah!!
Although his ability is amazing,
because of his drawing skills,
Catch King Riku and God Usopp!
THE OLD KING'S PLATEAU
that sparrow doesn't seem
to be too good at flying...
Did you say "I'll accept all of you"?
We have to keep left.
N-No need to be afraid.
They can't climb up here that easily...
Mouji!
There is the isolation ward!
Princess Mansherry must be in there!
--Now, Kin'emon, let's go!
--Uh-huh.
Kill God Usopp!
I, the former leader of the Happosui Army, will fight you!
I'm gonna save you now!
Father-sama, I just got a call from
the Tontattas in the factory!
It's an all-or-nothing gamble.
Oh, wait a second!
Oh, are they alright?!
Why did you stop me?!
You young squirt!
Yes.
Look at that sign!
We can fly straight up to the ceiling
with this Spring Sparrow!
But they told me
they can't find Princess Mansherry anywhere.
I'm determined to bet my life on it.
Wait a sec!
It says "Keep out"! We can't go in!
What?!
What are you guys talking about?!
We're former King Riku
army soldiers and citizens
Gah! What?!
You should've told me earlier!
Everyone in this country is looking for us!
Don't call me "young squirt,"
you shit-bag twerp!
However...
that had been living as Toys all this time.
Let's run now!
If you lose your dice,
the game is over before you can even roll.
Where are you gonna go when
everyone in this country is looking for you?
We don't know what's going on
but is King Riku alright?!
I can't slow down now!
Shit-ba"g" twerp! There's the...
..."G"!
Mouji broke the door with
the "Keep out" sign!
It'll be fine.
Our families are in the town!
You called me a "shit-bag twerp"?!
They know the truth about the past.
I'm disappointed in you!
Take us out with you! I beg you!
They're not gonna harm Father-sama.
It means you're not allowed
to go in without permission!
Kanjuro!
--What about me?
--Viola.
I'm sorry...
Don't say another word! It's unnecessary!
--Yes.
--Am I being ignored?
If they're hiding Princess Mansherry elsewhere,
it must be in the Palace.
--Awesome!
--Thank you, samurai!
We can get out from here finally!
Search there with your ability.
No one's in here! Is it just storage?
Take turns climbing out!
Okay.
Awesome!
Since it's a pictorial
ladder, it breaks easily!
No... Can't believe it...
You can see inside of the Palace from here?
The lines aren't straight
so it's hard to climb!
Yes, with my Clairvoyance.
I can send my sight wherever I want.
Stop complaining!
You've got a lot of nerve!
P-Princess... Where is the princess?!
Sanji would kill for your ability.
THE COLOSSEUM ARMY
THE ROYAL PALACE
Are you ready?!
The Top Executives of our Family are
guarding this plateau...
Here we go!
They're...!
Hurry up!
Stop Straw Hat and the others!
Princess Mansherry, please be safe.
I didn't think anyone could reach it
but there was a slight chance, so...
Why don't you aim at us?!
IN FRONT OF THE SMILE FACTORY
I wonder what kind of person
Princess Mansherry is.
Oh! You're so relentless, Señor!
...I've been waiting but...
If I remember correctly, Leo said she's capricious,
selfish, and short-tempered.
Guillotine High-Heel!
Hurry up!
Rebecca!
There!
I can't believe you made it here.
Who the hell are you?!
We're flying over the third level, Rebecca!
There! I aimed at you!
Stop it!
Yes, Robin-san!
The Flower Field is on the next level!
K-Kin'emon!
Is that it?
--Oh, Usopp-dono!
--You know him?
Oh, the Longleg got beat!
What?
Yeah, you can let go of him...
Boy... You're such a tough guy.
Something's flying towards us
from below!
Don't look away, Straw Hat!
We must get to the Palace where
Doflamingo is, at any cost!
There's some kind of weirdo!
The real Straw Hats are beyond my imagination as I thought...
He's Kanjuro, who I've been looking for.
Almost!
I knew it when I heard Doflamingo's speech!
Oh, that was you!
Indeed!
Franky Ear.
Which is not to say...
I'm a samurai from the Wano Kingdom.
It's a game to kill me.
Rooster-kun, watch out!
...it's a special mechanism or something.
My name is Evening Shower Kanjuro.
Kill or get killed.
It's just Franky naturally has good hearing.
Pop Baller!
Everyone in this country will become hunters!
Hey, swimming guy...
What's that pathetic creature...?
Rooster-kun!
The only way for you to survive is...
It's none of your concern but...
...to kill somebody!
This is the Pop-Pop Fruit power!
...earlier...
Anyway, we surfaced earlier
and were surprised.
Oh no! My Yellow Cubs...
I saw a weak old granny having trouble
in the back street on the right!
This game called the Birdcage is all fake!
Tons of people are heading
towards this plateau
so I wondered what's going on.
That's right!
Soldier!
I think they can't climb up this high but...
Robin-san!
I'm gonna go first!
I can't believe there's a group
that is trying to get to the Palace like that!
Oh, wait, Soldier!
Don't worry, long-nosed goblin man!
They were having trouble so...
It's Gladius!
Cabbage!
Pop...
I made a net for them!
Diez Fleurs!
As soon as the weapon trafficking
and the secret with the toys were revealed,
I'll keep them here! Just go, Straw Hat!
What?
My beloved horse was harmed
on this level!
They will be here in any minute.
all the people currently in this country
were sentenced to extermination, I think.
Oh yeah? That's sad.
Rebecca, take the key to the Flower Field!
Why did you do such a thing, you fool?!
I can't go farther without
vengeance against those jerks!
Doflamingo won't let any
information out of the country.
I'll be fine!
Catch God Usopp!
Robin-san!
This rope sucks!
That's why he enclosed the island
in the Birdcage.
--They're coming to get me!
--Was it unnecessary?!
Go!
Señor?
Which means Dressrosa is...
I just remembered
I have some minor business to attend to.
How foolish I've been...
...is a solitary island,
cut off from the rest of the world!
Gum-Gum...
I made a blunder! I failed my savior!
...UFO!
I'll commit hara-kiri to show my regret!
Believing in miracles and
waiting for the end of the game...
Luffy, dodge! It's the bombs!
Oh! Wait a second!
Don't, Kanjuro!
Let me take care of it!
Okay, I won't.
Shut up! Do it!
...will get us all killed!
What are you gonna do about those climbers?!
Why not use your barriers?!
The only way to get out
of this island alive is
to move forward and kill Doflamingo.
Hey, Bartolomeo!
Turn the wheel and open the door!
There are a variety of troubles
in this country...
I don't see her anywhere.
--Let's help them!
--Yeah!
What were you doing?!
When I was living in the Palace as Violet,
So many unexpected things
are happening around him
There is a limit on the size of the barrier...
that I can produce at once...
but it seems like Doflamingo is enjoying it.
I never heard they'd captured
the Tontattas' Princess Mansherry.
Hold on! Shrimps!
And I used it up on that staircase!
Is she really here?
What?!
I don't know anyone
who's more cunning than Doflamingo.
KUWEEN (20 YEARS OLD, FEMALE)
FACTORY MANAGER OF THE SMILE FACTORY
But that's all right!
You're pushing your luck!
Doflamingo is a notch above
all the others on all fronts
If it helps Luffy-senpai...
I won't let you get out!
I'm happy to die!
but he made just one mistake:
No! It's the factory manager!
Father-sama,
I don't see her anywhere.
He brought in all those
odd, tough warriors from
You guys were slaves for manufacturing SMILEs
right from the start!
I am!!
She must be somewhere.
Search every nook and cranny.
all over the world for the
event at the Colosseum.
You son of a...
Didn't you notice until now?!
We're not gonna be defeated!
I don't think
Doflamingo has killed Mansherry.
Dammit! If only I had the key to these cuffs,
I'll fight with you until you're
able to use barriers so hang tough!
Stop making a ruckus like fools!
I could take care of them all!
I know he needs her ability.
Because, after all,
What? Something's falling from above!
I will take down Doflamingo!
Though we need that ability
more than him now...
These dolls have no delicacy!
Ouch!
What are you talking about?!
I said I'm gonna kick Mingo's ass!
Cinco Mano! Spank!
I said it would be me, Straw Hat-ya!
Princess Mansherry, where are you?
I wasn't paying attention...
--Crest Head!
--That must be Luffy-senpai!
I'm very impressed, but I'm gonna do it!
Watch out for the suction device!
Soldier! You said you wanna kill
one of the Executives!
There must be a place I haven't looked yet.
Nico Robin!
Cien Fleurs!
I know how you feel...
Wing!
A place that I haven't looked
in the last few years.
That's a personal thing!
Taking back King Riku's country is my inevitable duty!
Rooster-kun.
I had been living here since I was little.
She wants to suck us all up
and recapture us!
I used to explore all over the Palace.
I have to put an end to the tragedy
that started 10 years ago!
You can't get away!
Robin!
I snuck into places no one would enter
Luffy! Tra-guy-kun!
You guys are here!
Our captain is...
If you talk about time,
I have a grudge from 13 years ago!
Nico-ya, where's the key?!
Give it to me now!
and I created some mischief
and got scolded by Father-sama and...
Then, mine's from 30 years ago!
--Rebecca has the key...
--What?!
Don't lie! There's no way
that you're older than me!
She's heading for the Flower Field
on the fourth level!
Cleaning, cleaning!
Maybe...
...worth risking...
--You guys, get off!
--You get off!
I haven't looked at that room!
Rebecca...
...even our lives!
If nothing is done,
we're all gonna get caught!
--It's my horse!
--You told me to get on!
She got away...
Open the door already!
The road's ending!
Well, she's just one little tramp.
--Hurry up!
--I'll help you!
Won't let you do it!
Vacuuming power up!
I know she can't do anything
even if she can get to the Palace.
Almost there! The third level!
All right!
Go straight to the fourth level like this!
I'll go after her and kill her later.
You're persistent!
Just give up already!
At the back of the chapel,
You bastard!
It's you!
Horse!
there was a room...
My name is Gladius.
No, we won't! We're gonna
open the door no matter what!
I'm gonna take care of you all first.
--Leave them in my hands.
--Yeah!
Luffy is always
the trump card that leads us to victory!
What?
Luffy! Tra-guy-kun!
And Soldier-san, too!
What's the matter, Farul?
Just go now!
To the Flower Field on the fourth level!
Mil Fleurs! Gigantesco Mano!
That's right!
Robin?!
Rebecca's waiting for you!
Just go!
Here. Your food.
--I won't let you lay a finger on Luffy!
--That's right!
I want to go back to Green Bit!
Come and save me now!
What are those giant dolls?!
I'm coming now!
Wait for me, Mingo!
Well done. Guys!
Leo!
Okay.
There you are, Mansherry!
Got it!
The group of dolls stands in
Luffy and the others' way!
Clashing fiercely with Fujitora,
Sabo tries to figure out the admiral's true motive!
Finally released from the SMILE Factory,
the Tontattas are ecstatic!
Violet finally finds out
The Top Executive, Diamante,
launches powerful attacks while
Princess Mansherry's whereabouts
with her Clairvoyance
Meanwhile, Pica who's been fighting Zoro,
Rebecca struggles desperately to hold on!
and it gives Leo and the others hope but at that very moment,
But their princess
Meanwhile, Robin, Bartolomeo, and Cavendish,
placing their hopes in Luffy,
throws a punch with his gigantic
fist aimed at Robin and the
Mansherry's whereabouts is still a mystery
But she is finally driven into a corner,
moments from losing her innocent life,
Luffy and the others are completely surrounded by
and concerns and confusion spread among them!
others who're heading for the Royal Palace!
When it seems like his attack is unavoidable,
Meanwhile, the hard-boiled fight
between Franky and Señor
eerie Headcracker Dolls that keep up their
stand against Gladius' vicious attacks with their all their might
when the legendary, undefeated warrior,
Zoro's never-before-seen
sword attack strikes Pica!
relentless attacks, no matter how many times they get taken down!
Kyros, shows up at the Sunflower Field!
and clear the path for taking down Doflamingo!
grows to include Kuween
and gets even more heated!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Tearful Reunion! Rebecca and Kyros!"
"Invincible! A Gruesome Army of Headcracker Dolls!"
"A Hard-Fought Battle Against Pica! Zoro's Deadly Attack!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Risking Their Lives! Luffy is the Trump Card for Victory!"
"The Little People's Princess! Captive Mansherry!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!