Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air, off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari mae wo mita mono dake ga
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal, we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
a boy whose body turned
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance with
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
But caught up in the current king Doflamingo's agenda,
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
they were trapped in the Birdcage along with the entire island.
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
On top of that, he put prices on
the heads of Luffy and 11 others,
On top of that, he put prices on the heads of
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
On top of that, he put prices on
the heads of Luffy and 11 others,
Luffy and 11 others, and now they're being hunted by all the citizens.
and now they're being hunted
by all the citizens.
Luffy and Law are heading
to the Royal Palace!
and now they're being hunted
by all the citizens.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
Gravity Blade!
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
Raging Tiger!
Luffy and Law finally got to the Royal Palace
where Doflamingo is!
Luffy and Law are heading
to the Royal Palace!
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
Luffy and Law are heading
to the Royal Palace!
I'm gonna kick his ass now!
However, Sugar closes in on Luffy
and Law with her evil intention...
All right!
Let's go and kick Mingo's ass!
This jerk! What is he up to?!
We are birds of a feather.
He's pissing me off!
Wait!
We Navy and Doflamingo are both out of place.
Idiot! I told you it's our ultimate stratagem!
I also told you not to get heated!
What?!
Doflamingo isn't someone
that you can beat just by force of will alone.
Neither Trafalgar Law nor
Monkey D. Luffy know me.
I'm gonna do it now! Gum-Gum...
You need to cool down.
The Navy will never be a hero
in this country.
What?! How can I cool down
after getting this far?!
It's easy to approach them.
Shambles!
It's an all-or-nothing gamble.
I'm saying, if you don't,
you can't defeat him!
Hey, Luffy!
If somebody notices that's what you're thinking...
...Red Hawk!
The seas without you,
I don't ever wanna see that!
No.
I promised Rebecca!
I'm determined to bet my life on it.
I was just being blocked by you...
Radio Knife.
Stopping here won't change anything!
I see them!
Law and Straw Hat have shown up
in the yard...
Special Long-Range Attack! Bagworm!
It's like a gamble.
...nearby the pool.
Straw Hat-ya! You're the worst!
--Roger that.
--Clank.
I'm sort of a lucky man.
Father-sama must be
somewhere on this battlefield, too...
King Riku-sama!
What are we supposed to do?!
I spent such a long time,
increasing their number little by little.
What?
If you tell us to fight, we'll take up arms!
"A Noble Family!
The True Identity of Doflamingo!"
Those tens of thousands of toy slaves.
--King Riku-sama!
--We'll follow you!
Somebody made it here, huh?
But that idiot...
Shall we wait... for a while?
Sugar-sama!
...brought it all to naught in an instant!
Oh no! She passed out again!
What? Wait?
How do you like that, bastard?!
It won't be too late to choose death.
Not yet, Kanjuro?! We have no time!
If you're all right,
It's you...
Are you all right, Doffy?!
It's almost done!
Did you think you could take me down?
just go ahead!
L-Law, you fool!
You're not gonna get away with this!
We can go straight to the fourth level this way!
Let's go, Tra-guy!
Revenge is easy.
The fact that shitty brats like you guys got conceited
Go!
Just touch them with this hand.
We're here, Mingo!
and thought even for a second, that you could defeat me is...
Straw Hats...
I'm gonna go first!
Straw Hat...
...an unbearable humiliation to me!
Oh, wait, Soldier!
Let me just make sure.
Now I'll bring...
...your existences...
Listen.
Luffy, dodge!
...to naught!
Let me take care of it!
Just in case, I'm wrong.
I'm a descendent of the noblest bloodlines in the world...
You two, what did you come here for?
Hey, Bartolomeo!
"One Shot One Kill!
The Man Who Will Save Dressrosa!"
To kick your ass!
The Celestial Dragon!
If it helps Luffy-senpai...
The same here!
That was quite a blow!
See?! It didn't kill him!
We're admirable just by the fact of our birth.
I'm happy to die!
I'm disappointed...
That strategy will never work again!
I used to possess the most unobtainable power
in the world.
I know how you feel...
"Anger Erupts!
Luffy and Law's Ultimate Stratagem!"
Father! Where are the slaves-eh?!
Let's go buy some-eh!
Strategy?
Rooster-kun.
You shitty brats!
You're messing with me!
Father, why don't they fall down on their knees-eh?
Okay, this is it! It's done!
Father! Why do they come after us-eh?!
Our captain is...
Sorry to keep you waiting, Usopp-dono.
What?!
--It's a work after my own heart.
--Oh, it's done?!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF
THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 3
They're a Celestial Dragon family! Don't kill them...
A fake one, again?!
Make them suffer for the rest of their lives!
...worth risking...
...even our lives!
Looks good! Well done, well done!
O-Oh yeah?
I thought they were giant toys...
To me, it kind of looks terrible again...
By the age of ten,
I'd seen heaven and hell on earth.
"A Tearful Reunion!
Rebecca and Kyros!"
...but each of them was actually
made up of eight people.
Dammit! That jerk!
Terrible but fine!
I'll use it!
They turned their own soldiers into toys?!
Keep going, keep going!
Then, I killed my father
who caused all that
How could they do that to their own people?!
Don't fall!
and returned to Mariejois with his head!
Catch the king!
Damn!
No way...
I have no business with the fake-mingo!
It's done!
But...
I gotta hurry or
Soldier will kick Mingo's ass first!
Sugar passed out again?!
...the Celestial Dragons in heaven
would never accept a renegade family!
Straw Hat-ya!
That's your ammunition?!
What?!
Sugar-sama!
Yes, I'll call it "Bagworm"!
Sugar-sama, stay with us!
I knew there was no way to get out of this hell.
Sugar-sama!!
It's still here!
It's the special attack we need
to take down Sugar!
It's no use fighting it!
It's an all-or-nothing gamble.
I swore to myself at that moment.
We're almost at the fourth level!
Shake it off!
It was terrible!
That I will destroy...
We thought we'd live as toys
for the rest of our lives!
Okay!
I'm determined to bet my life on it.
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 4
THE SUNFLOWER FIELD
Viola!
...every single thing in the world
that they dominate!
I'm counting on your Clairvoyance.
That wouldn't be!
Tell me every move Sugar makes.
If you lose your dice,
the game is over before you can even roll.
We were gonna turn you back
as soon as the battle ended, of course.
Okay.
Th-That's what I thought!
The life I've lived was
on a very different level from yours!
--Good to hear that!
--I'm relieved!
Hello? Hello?!
Can you really do it
with only her Clairvoyance?
Hello?
Are you listening, Sabo-kun?!
Of course, we didn't even remember...
I am listening!
I have no time to play around...
Don't lie! You're not listening at all!
...their existences.
I have no other options.
Sugar is already on the move.
You've been absent-minded the whole time!
All right!
...with you brats!
My barrier is fully recharged!
Look! You have a position now!
I'm a sniper!
Covering someone is what I do best!
I won't let you guys ascend any farther!
You can't get emotional
and fight a guy like the Navy admiral!
"The Ultimate Power!
The Secret of the Op-Op Fruit!"
Shoot an enemy without being seen
to protect my friend!
Do you wanna lead
the Revolutionary Army into war?
You think you got the better of me
just because the toys are gone?!
My brother's in danger! I don't care!
A town located in
the Northwest part of Dressrosa - Primula.
Viola. I'm counting on you.
That groundless confidence of yours,
--You should!
--Nah!
PRIMULA - THE NORTHWESTERN TOWN
I don't wanna get dragged into a mess
by your recklessness!
I'll smash it into pieces!
Yes.
--Scrwew iwt!
--What?!
An' dat guy is...
I won't let you get in Luffy's way!
We are birds of a feather.
W-W-Wait a minute!
I'm gonna take down an Executive of
the Don Quixote Family
We Navy and Doflamingo are both
out of place.
Honey...!
What did you come here for?!
P-Please!
D-Don't do it! I'm begging you!
and become even more popular!
The Navy will never be a hero
in this country.
Please!
Don't tell me you're here to kill Doffy.
I don't wanna do this!
If somebody notices that's
what you're thinking...
But I can't... I can't control my body!
That can't be it.
No.
I was just being blocked by you...
You recklessly challenged me
with that blunt-edged sword
Sorry! I'm so sorry! Forgive me!
and disgraced yourself pathetically!
It's like a gamble.
THE TOP FLOOR OF THE ROYAL PALACE
With this much stuff,
we can rebuild our ship-yashi!
So you know you have no chance against Doffy!
I'm sort of a lucky man.
Sugar's walking towards those two!
Deshi, deshi!
Okay!
Wait, damn pirates!
--Captain Tank! Hack!
--Yes, King Riku-sama!
Bellamy!
Okay?!
Understood?! Were you listening?!
What're you guys doing
under the cover of fire?!
Or...
--Oh no!
--Deshi!
Give me a hand! We'll protect Usopp-kun!
...you came to challenge me again
believing in some miracle?
You...
Don't just stand there! Let's run!
Father-sama!
Do you care about him?
Sah... boh... -kun?!
I won't let you get away!
The people are getting really close.
I thought you two had a fight
in Mock Town.
You can't catch us!
Why're you always like that?!
Stop!
--No-way-poo!
--Puppuku-poo!
You do what you like
while others are worried
about you like hell!
Everybody's confused.
And Hack and I are forced
to clean up your mess!
They might come after me, too.
I'm not your babysitter!
To avenge your mother...
Stop! Please!
When did you guys become friends?
...on me!
Come on! Hack and I always get chewed out
Hey! Hey!
because of your selfish actions!
Shoot tranquilizer bullets!
Ouch!
When?! When?!
But don't hurt anyone.
Hey! When? When?
When?! Hey, hey!
That's very hard.
They got excited by the fire?
Or do they sense something?
But we've got to do it.
Navy Admiral Fujitora, huh?
Yes,
us hurting our people is
exactly what Doflamingo wants.
Damn! We're already short-handed!
You're such a delusional dumbass!
Okay, done.
I like the look in your eyes.
We'll lure the other criminals
using these criminals.
Listen. The era where pirates
dream about things is over!
All we need to do now is
buy time for the launch.
Please! Let go of me!
It's gonna die if we don't stop it!
Old king man, thanks!
I... I couldn't protect her!
Forget about the past!
Tranquilizer bullets!
Do we still have any?!
Let go of Bellamy!
--Let's move on with the luring plan!
--Okay!
That's...
What's going on?!
--Stop!
--Outta my way!
...up to the winner to decide!
You people are the Navy, aren't you?!
Sure! If you wanna challenge me,
I accept!
Usopp-kun!
It's pirates!
Do something about this situation!
Isn't there any way?!
Sugar is getting closer to those two!
Found him!
This fool came to get killed by me.
Now, she can see them!
We're short of tranquilizer bullets
as well as soldiers.
The 500 million prize - God Usopp!
Keep your eye on her!
Right, Bellamy?
What should we do?
We'll kill him and make a name
for our pirate group instantly!
If nothing is done...
You entered the competition at the Colosseum
Listen to me, Rebecca!
Vice Admiral Maynard!
Wait a sec! They're important hostages
to end the game!
to become an Executive of my Family.
Made it!
What's wrong?!
I promise I'll kick Doflamingo's ass for you!
The fight between Sabo of the Revolutionary Army and Issho-san in Acacia,
Don't kill them!
But you got defeated pathetically.
There!
Stop your hypocrisy!
King Riku!
winded up in a draw due to injury!
It's the same if you hand
them over to Doflamingo!
Viola-sama!
What?! Don't be silly!
Kin'emon!
God Usopp!
That's more than enough reason to be killed
The admirals from HQ are
the Navy's greatest military powers!
What a pain... Let's kick all of their asses!
but I gave you another chance.
--H-Help!
--Do it! Do it!
Why, Issho-san?!
Which was, if you kill Straw Hat,
I'll make you an Executive.
Don't get behind!
Doflamingo can't keep his position as a Warlord after this!
Catch them all and
hand them over to Doflamingo!
Get out of our way!
But you failed again so you shall be killed.
We have to capture him now!
--Coming!
--Yeah!
H-Help... Please don't...
Listen, don't hurt anyone!
Don't you think so, Bellamy?
Now they're here!
The Navy has been doing the same thing over and over again just like that!
--We have to stop them, too!
--Okay!
Don't hurt those citizens anymore!
THE ROYAL PALACE - THE POOL GARDEN
You have been in the Navy for a long time
haven't you, Vice Admiral-san?
If you want to do that, fight me first!
"Kicking someone's ass" is your answer
to everything!
You shithead!
Weren't you even listening all this time?
Guys! Get him!
What's wrong with that?!
It's easier that way!
Shame on you, Rebecca!
To these screams filled with anger?
What's the matter?! Why are you running?!
I'm gonna get on board Doflamingo's
ship to ride through
King Riku-sama...
They are not crying! They are angry!
Why aren't you fighting?!
Tank! Hack! I need your help!
the "wild wave" that will
come sooner or later.
You're a gladiator!
--Yes, sir!
--Roger!
Neither Trafalgar Law nor
Monkey D. Luffy know me.
I'm done picking on you.
I thought you came to kill me!
Dammit!
Doflamingo has been my pirate hero
since I was a kid.
Does the World Government...
It's easy to approach them.
I know I'm no match for Diamante.
Get away!
...pretend to be God or something?!
Those words... hang over my head...
K-King Riku-sama...
What I have to do now is
hand this key over to Lucy and the others!
--You didn't get hurt?
--N-No!
What should we do?!
But now isn't the time to think about it!
--Good!
--King Riku-sama...
I can't betray Doflamingo!
What the...
--Kill King Riku!
--Kick his ass!
We'll deal with the pirates that
headed for Doflamingo later!
I look up to him!
I won't let you guys lay a finger
on the citizens!
In any event, we'll keep trying to bring
the nationwide confusion under control!
Sugar came out into the yard!
The time has come!
Do your best not to harm
any citizens or animals!
At the Colosseum, I managed to put on
some good shows using you but...
Sedate those who are out of control
with tranquilizer bullets!
Excuse me, help!
This is how you take
responsibility, isn't it?
That's all we can do now...
...if you can't fight,
Why is a kid here?
--King Riku-sama, we got them all.
--Good.
Bellamy.
you've served your purpose!
Dad! Mom! Where are you?!
You idolized me of your own will
It hurts, doesn't it?
I'll give you first aid for now.
and got desperate when things
didn't go as you'd wished.
I see no end! Can we bring them under control?!
The old King Riku, he's awesome!
Don't tell me she's lost.
In such a place? No way!
People can't change their nature.
Dad!
I'm sorry! I really am! No! Help!
Mom!
--Are you lost?
--Don't pay attention to her.
What?
Wh-Why...?
Oh! I'm free!
I don't like this man!
No matter how far you go,
you're just a cheap thug.
Guys, is it okay to release us?
We shouldn't have done that.
Bellamy!
For a decade, we were holding
a grudge against King Riku-sama
Are you okay?
What are you saying?!
Bellamy has changed!
who was just manipulated by
Doflamingo for one night.
And we didn't even notice that
we had lost our loved ones.
It's okay now...
Let's go.
Just...
We praised the king who was a pirate
It's dangerous here
so hide somewhere.
...kill me... already...
I'll... put an end to you now.
No! Don't leave me alone!
and even after we learned the truth...
Damn! So annoying! Can't take it off!
even after we learned the truth...
No, wait...
It's no use!
We were still looking for salvation
in the game he started!
Hey, Straw Hat-ya!
You prefer a gun, don't you?
Let go of Bellamy!
We don't even know
what we're doing anymore...
Because Scarlet...
Mingo!!
...got killed by a gun!
Luffy!
What's gonna happen to us...?
Dodge, Straw Hat!
What's gonna happen to this country?!
Everyone, listen! None of us will run!
Sorry, Bellamy!!
--Stop right there!
--Father-sama!
Didn't we agree on this earlier?
Straw Hat-ya! If you show
your anger or hatred,
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
King Riku-sama... please save us!
you're giving the enemy what he wants!
Gum-Gum...
Hold back! Stirring our emotions is...
Wh-What the...
...Octopus Stamp!
--What happened to them?!
--What's going on?!
...his tactic.
If you lose your cool, you could get killed.
Help!
King Riku-sama!
What are we supposed to do?!
Soldier-san!!
If you tell us to fight, we'll take up arms!
Guys, come to your senses!
Like I almost did in the first battle.
That was close!
Rebecca!!
Behind you!
I won't let you get near Usopp-dono
at any cost!
--King Riku-sama!
--We'll follow you!
You guys have no idea...
Stop! Hold it, hold it!
You're...
Can you imagine what people would do
to a fallen Celestial Dragon?
--Stay focused!
--I'm sorry!
Kyros!
Tell me the exact location of the yard!
Shall we wait... for a while?
Doflamingo is
an ironhearted, ruthless man.
Won't let you take away...
See the windows on the upper
part of the Rampart Tower?
...another member of my family
from me!!
What? Wait?
He's always looking for
a chance to get you!
It won't be too late to choose death.
Yeah.
This man was a legend.
Why are they so important to you?!
They're pirates!
I see Straw Hat and Law
in the first window right of the center.
In the face of your dying friend...
He was the strongest gladiator
in the history of the Colosseum.
Yes, they're unlawful men - who will break
this country's deceptive peace!
People are all...
There are iron bars on the window.
You kicked him! Didn't you? Yes!
Father-sama, I decided to trust them,
the Straw Hat Pirates!
...cruel.
You just kicked him!
What are you talking about,
Fake-mingo?!
How many bars are there?
At least, the words of Straw
Hat and the others are humane
You idiot!
and they take actions
out of the goodness of their hearts!
What did you say?!
One vertical bar and
three horizontal bars.
Don't listen to him!
Although I couldn't protect your mother,
The length from the ground
of the yard to the bottom
I have been believing in Luffy-kun and
the others' victory without realizing...
I'm gonna protect you to the end,
with my life!
How dare you say I'm ironhearted!
All right then,
let's begin with the executions.
of the window is about 1.2 meters.
That's about Sugar's height.
Let me teach you how to fight.
My mother said I shouldn't hurt anyone!
Law, I'm not as ironhearted as you think.
I'm pretty mad.
You're the first, Law...
How big is the bottom pane
of the window?
I'm gonna teach you how to not get hurt!
50 wide by 40 high.
I'm a toy.
Hey!
Chop him up into bits and pieces,
like he did to me!
Rain and wind will rust my body!
Think what you guys have done.
It's about the size of the ammo...
I don't know how long my body's gonna last!
Navy Admiral Fujitora?!
I'm really... disappointed by you...
Be strong!
First, you began by destroying
the SAD manufacturing machine.
Rebecca!
There's something not quite clear to me.
Then, you laid your hands on
Vergo and Monet
Where is Sugar now?
You're a former Celestial Dragon, expelled from Mariejois.
Dressrosa was once the symbol of peace.
She's still behind the post.
and kidnapped Caesar.
Father-sama...
Why do you still have power?!
I won't let you get involved in a war.
I'm sorry, Rebecca.
Later, here in Dressrosa,
you freed the toys throughout the country.
Leave her.
As a toy with no future,
CP-0 works directly under the command of the World Gov't
Help, please!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Why the hell is he here?!
Sorry, we've got to get going.
all I could do was teach you how to fight!
but you brought them into action this morning!
Your associates are trying to destroy the SMILE factory
even now!
Even though you're a gentle person
like your mother!
No! Don't leave me!
I've had it enough already!
Do you still wish to know that
even though you're going to die soon?
You can have these!
I'm smiling just because
I can't get any madder!
But it ends today!
What?
It's because I know about
the important national treasure...
You...
Sugar is gonna get between
the two any minute.
...don't have to fight anymore.
...that they have inside
The Holyland of Mariejois!
King Riku, sir.
And what is worse, you think you can kill me.
I'm betting on the same one as you.
It's been disastrous since
you guys came along.
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
The national treasure in Mariejois?
Get out of our way!
Uh-huh!
Feels like I'm reliving the despair of
13 years ago!
Yes. It's something that could shake the world
by its very existence.
What do you mean by that, Kyros?!
Everybody, stop!
Kill Doflamingo-eh!
The target is behind the wall...
It means, today,
We can't keep that kid alive-eh!
I'll settle my score with all of you!
If I miss, we'll lose Luffy!
On the "Straw" and...
To them, I'm an escapee who has the most dangerous card to play.
That means...
If that hadn't happened,
...nothing else!
You can have these. They're good!
...it's the end of all of you!
They tried to kill me but I didn't die
I wouldn't have shown up
in front of you like this!
What?! Is it okay?!
so the Celestial Dragons became very cooperative.
Uh-huh!
Forget it!
If that hadn't happened,
What's your problem?!
She said I can have some!
Plus, if I could have had your Op-Op Fruit power
in my hands that day,
you would've been here as the third Corazon!
I would have taken the helm of the world
utilizing the national treasure in Mariejois!
Your power has such value.
Take a good look at this country!
If I stop now, what's gonna happen to it?!
As well as the "Personality Transplant Surgery,"
there's another usage!
Special Long-Range Attack! Bagworm!
Do you know about it?
You monster!
If a wise man utilizes the Op-Op Fruit, even the dream
Cien Fleurs!
Strong Right!
people have had since ancient times could come true.
Three-Sword Style!
Rebecca!
That's why quite a lot of people call it
the ultimate Devil Fruit.
Thousand-and-Eighty Pound Phoenix!
Is this...!
Yeah, I know...
Even though I have no interest in it.
The greatest power of this fruit is
to grant another person eternal life...
Rebecca!!
I'll take you down!
Lucy!
Mingo!!
...via the "Perpetual Youth Surgery"!
Black Knight!
Sugar came into the center of the pane!
The clone again?!
I'll take you down!
Then, I'll fight...
Mingo!!
The greatest power of this fruit is
to grant another person eternal life...
...the real one!
Rebecca!!
She's approaching them!
The key!
Bullet String!
Usopp-kun?!
Lucy!
...via the "Perpetual Youth Surgery"!
Bellamy?!
Great! We both made it!
But once it's performed,
the surgeon himself will die.
Hey, why're you doing this, Bellamy?!
Bullet String!
I said sorry for what I did!
Yeah, Doffy! That serves him right!
Indeed!
That's why I wasn't gonna let you eat it!
I-I can't...
How dare you repay kindness with ingratitude!
Law! I know all about your ability!
The key!
...stop shaking!
Straw Hat-ya!
Oh, I'm sorry!
He's being manipulated!
Give it to me now!
Because the ability of the Op-Op Fruit was
something we sought in the first place!
Here it is!
Diamante's swordplay!
Bullet String!
Hurry up!
I'm sorry, Straw Hat...
Rebecca!
Even if I got chopped up,
I'm gonna turn back to normal!
Please...
Dammit!!
...stop me!
Lao G's martial art!
Ready to fight back!
Room! Injection Shot!
Oh?
Commodore...
Gladius's gunnery!
Oh?!
...Hug!
You got all your fighting skills from us!
A lite version of King Punch!
Oh? Why is it?
Radio Knife is a different cutting method
from my regular Amputation.
Yeah!
And I'm still here thanks to Cora-san!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 2
THE COLOSSEUM ARMY VS THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY
What?
For several minutes, even with any
treatment or ability, your body...
I'm grateful!
Luffy!!
Room!
Because I can take you all down with this power!
...can't be reassembled!
What?! I'm in trouble!
Can't help my nose running!
Destruction Cannon!
Oh, wait, wait, wait!
I can't stop snotting!
Damn!
Guillotine High-Heel!
TRAFALGAR LAW (10 YEARS OLD)
A BOY FROM THE WHITE TOWN
Damn!
I'll hit her no matter what!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
You jerks!
Your Destruction Cannon can
destroy anything, right?
Here they are.
SPIDER MILES - A PORT TOWN IN THE NORTH BLUE
16 YEARS AGO
Ah! I love it, too!
Finally, we caught up with him!
Hey, Luffy!
Finally... I'm free!
The seas without you,
I don't ever wanna see that!
Destruction!
Go away, Law!
Who will save this country?!
Did you forget that I used
to treat you kindly?!
We're here!
The fourth level - where Mingo is!
Ton, ton...
Is that where he is?
You'll see it, Sugar!
Room!
Ten-Ton Vise!!
Yeah.
I won't let you guys...
Stop! You traitor!
Law! Straw Hat!
Don't kill him, Diamante.
...have it all your way!
Diamante.
This is just a try-out before we take him into our Family as an apprentice.
Injection!
Take this! Snot Blade-Catcher!
--You jerk!
--I know, Doffy.
I'm sorry, you two...
My hands are full with this guy.
Shot!
What's... going on?
If I beat him,
will you make me an Executive?
Here's the finisher!
Could you take care of Doflamingo for me?!
DIAMANTE AND TREBOL
EXECUTIVES OF THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY
Of course!
Can't help my nose from running!
Then, I'll leave that guy up to you, Soldier!
Fallbright!
Got it!
You're my target!
--Let's go, Straw Hat-ya!
--Okay!
Damn!
What?!
I see the aurac
Tra-guy!
I'll knock you out!
Oh yeah, Rebecca!
Are you serious?
I won't forgive anyone who
messes with my Family!
...of their presences!
Stop laughing! I'm serious!
I bet you're happy to see your dad!
There's Luffy!
Do you remember
what I hate the most, Law?
You can't kill a person
just with your spirit!
Uh-huh.
Here I go!
Super Grown-Up Great Black Kabuto!
I told you! I have explosives!
Thank you for the key!
Barrier-Barrier! Barrier Crush!
I'm gonna die soon anyway
so I'm not afraid of anything!
See you!
Special Long-Range Attack! Bagworm!
To be looked down upon!
Mil Fleurs!
Tra-guy!
Don't mess with pirates!
Gigantesco Mano!
Stomp!
Hey, Lucy!
Blade of Beauty! Round Table!
He was just a big talker-dasuyan.
Are you really going to...
Are you really going to
take down Doflamingo?!
The wind is blowing from west to east...
What? Suddenly, my body gets...
It's over! It's over! Let's play tag!
Wind force scale: 4.
Okay-dasuyan!
Seor!
Dammit...
THE SMILE FACTORY
S-Stop!
A slight tailwind.
Wait! Wait, wait!
THE WASTE PROCESSING PLANT
Come on!
No-dasuyan!
Great!
We got him!
Where's the captain?
Two...
One...
I'm not Lucy.
Stop it! You stay away!
Our captain Doffy doesn't have time
for a kid like you.
The first booster, Exploding Star!
Get away!
My name is Luffy!
The man who'll become the King of the Pirates!
Slight ascent, then,
release the rear section.
Uh-huh, uh-huh! We understand
you can't live long and you'll die soon.
Get away, Straw Hat!
That's pointless...
Two seconds later,
ignite the second booster.
Dodge!
So don't worry!
--Bella...
--Dammit!!
When? Hey, hey!
When are you gonna die?
I thought I felt a gentle breeze.
Straw Hat-ya!
The outer-cover comes off
and the ammo goes horizontally.
Three years and two months from now.
No!
A doctor said so?
It's gonna go through the lower left side of
--So hard-boiled!
--So cool, Seor!
My dead father was a doctor.
I found out by seeing my medical data.
The King of the Pirates?!
the window on the Rampart Tower!
You're too tough!
You're fighting me, Diamante!
It passes through the wall
and goes straight!
What a smart brat.
You bring it on this time!
Straight to the target!
They're all beaten!
Don't get in my way!
I wanna kill as many as I can
in these three years
and destroy everything!
What?
Did you think you could take me down?
What annoying bastards!
It trails off a little but
that special ammo is...
He must have a screw loose!
I won't allow you idiots...
The fact that shitty brats
like you guys got conceited
Can't help my nose running!
...to get to the Palace!
and thought even for a second,
that you could defeat me is...
Well, we accept kids, too.
Give me more than that...
That won't work against me at all!
We had about hundred kids come until now
...an unbearable humiliation to me!
You tremendous idiot! Traitorous brat!
but most of them escaped crying within two days.
Listen.
I thought a caterpillar was crawling
on my cheek!
...meant to retraumatize the enemy!
Room!
I'm a descendent of the noblest
bloodlines in the world...
--He's awesome!
--Fraland!
Shambles!
Are you gonna be okay?
AAAAARGH!
Nin! Trebol-sama!
Diamante-sama!
Dammit!!
The Celestial Dragon!
They're the only kids remaining.
What?!
Luffy, you don't even have to notice...
What is it? Buffalo? Baby 5?
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF
THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 4
Cora-san came back!
If you're all right,
We're admirable just by
the fact of our birth.
I used to possess the most
unobtainable power in the world.
just go ahead!
Is this... the palace?
Yeah, we finally made it.
But, Usopp-dono, what are you
going to do with this drawing?
What a useful ability!
It is but it also eats up my energy.
Can you turn it into a real object?
Maybe, having those Sea Prism Stone cuffs on
--He tripped!
--We knew he was gonna trip-dasuyan!
An object?
and getting carried by you to this
point wasn't so bad after all.
I don't know how you know him but...
Do it! It's gonna be an ammunition!
...if you wanna stop him,
you gotta knock him out!
I was able to save my energy.
Just do so! Straw Hat!
--You tripped! You tripped! You tripped!
--Dasuyan! Dasuyan! Dasuyan!
Sugar-sama!
Scalpel.
--You tripped! You tripped!
--Dasuyan! Dasuyan!
Oh no! She passed out again!
I can't do that!
However,
What's wrong?!
Dasuyan....
You're my friend!
one day, my father abandoned
the greatest power
I operated on myself.
What?!
in the world that we were born with,
They stopped!
and the four of us in the family...
...descended to this manure-pile world!
Doffy won't care if you're a kid or not.
--Why're they going down themselves?!
--The toys...
If you do it right, you can get promoted quickly
but if you're useless, that's it.
You're gonna die soon...
He purposely used lead bullets...
That jerk!
Screw that "live like human-beings" bull!
What happened?
Well, good luck.
You okay?
Not a bad way to die, huh?
--No need to worry.
--I see.
My father was an idiotic man!
Do you remember
what I told you once, Law?
All right!
Let's go and kick Mingo's ass!
I'm amazed, Usopp-kun...
You're such a brilliant sniper!
Cora-san, I brought you a cup of tea.
Let's live a humble life here,
all four of us as a family!
The weak have no choice about how they die!
Wait!
It's hot.
What?!
Doflamingo isn't someone that you can
beat just by force of will alone.
Viola-sama?
You need to cool down.
You did it!
You brought down Sugar!
What?! How can I cool down
after getting this far?!
That bastard!
Corazon, did you finish your work
without any trouble?
I'm saying, if you don't,
you can't defeat him!
We came this far
but you still don't fight us yourself?!
What do you think happened?
Usopp-kun!
Did he really?! I can't believe it!
I promised Rebecca!
Then, give me the earnings.
We have to be faithful when it comes to money.
Tra-guy!
Stopping here won't change anything!
I'm gonna kick his ass now!
Father! Where are the slaves-eh?!
Let's go buy some-eh!
He's pissing me off!
--I'm stunned!
--Did he really do it?!
Law and Straw Hat have shown up
in the yard...
Your name is Law, isn't it?
This guy who just returned is an Executive like us.
...nearby the pool.
Father, why don't they fall
down on their knees-eh?
Idiot! I told you it's our ultimate stratagem!
I also told you not to get heated!
--Roger that.
--Clank.
Great...
Father! Why do they come after us-eh?!
His name is Corazon.
CORAZON - A  EXECUTIVE OF THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY
How are they?
I'm gonna do it now! Gum-Gum...
He's an absent-minded idiot but...
They're a Celestial Dragon family!
They are both okay.
...he's strong, maybe because of his blood.
Don't kill them... Make them suffer
for the rest of their lives!
You fool!
I'll teach you a lesson later!
Captain Doffy's brother by blood.
Sugar-sama!
He can't speak because of a traumatic event
in his past, I heard.
He's going to attack Law!
Let's go!
Are you going nuts, Straw Hat?!
This is fun!
10 years... For 10 years.
In addition...
He doesn't like kids. Be careful.
I spent such a long time,
increasing their number little by little.
Room!
By the age of ten,
I'd seen heaven and hell on earth.
What the...?!
Then, I killed my father
who caused all that
We're here, Mingo!
Those tens of thousands of toy slaves.
Shambles!
Oh, he's dead!
and returned to Mariejois with his head!
He crashed into the mountain of scrap metal-dasuyan!
...Red Hawk!
But...
They've just made it there!
...the Celestial Dragons in heaven
would never accept a renegade family!
But that idiot...
To the top floor of the Palace
where the decisive battle will take place!
Doffy!
...brought it all to naught in an instant!
I see...
I knew there was no way
to get out of this hell.
You did it, Luffy!
Not yet, Kanjuro?! We have no time!
I swore to myself at that moment.
Radio Knife.
Let me just make sure.
What's wrong with him?! He must be nuts!
That I will destroy...
It's almost done!
Just in case, I'm wrong.
...every single thing in the world
that they dominate!
Damn! Damn!
Damn! Damn! Damn!!
Revenge is easy.
Straw Hat-ya! You're the worst!
You two,
Just touch them with this hand.
You, too, are...
what did you come here for?
The life I've lived was
on a very different level from yours!
I'm gonna kill him!!
Straw Hats...
...from that generation!
To kick your ass!
Now I'll bring...
The same here!
...your existences...
I have no time to play around...
...to naught!
I'm disappointed...
...with you brats!
Cora-san caught fire!
Flevance, the country Law was from,
was white and beautiful like a country of snow.
Facing Doflamingo, possessor of such
Luffy and Law finally come face-to-face with
their sworn enemy, Doflamingo!
Pulling off their tricky stratagem,
Luffy and Law go on an offensive!
A vengeful Sugar closes in on Luffy and Law.
great power that he can even move
the World Government to action,
However, when Doflamingo,
who's anger hits its peak,
"Won't let her turn him into a toy!"
Provoking the two cunningly and
leading them around by the nose,
People used to call it the dream country.
Luffy and Law are left helpless!
With this passionate thought in his mind,
launches horrific counterattacks
and corners the two again,
His beautiful homeland, however, became a
When their execution is
finally about to begin,
Doflamingo launches vicious attacks
against them manipulating Bellamy,
Usopp takes aim at Sugar in the distance,
beyond even his line of sight!
warzone suddenly and perished from the face of the earth!
the world-shaking, tremendous
secret of the Op-Op Fruit
and when Luffy's anger hits its peak,
Luffy and Law learn
the shocking truth of the Warlord Doflamingo!
Suddenly, everybody's fate depends on
Usopp's skill!
The extreme hardships that Law went through as a boy are now revealed!
and Law's shocking past will be revealed!
Luffy and Law strike a
blow with all their might!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sad Memories! Law the Boy from the White Town!"
"One Shot One Kill! The Man
Who Will Save Dressrosa!"
"Anger Erupts! Luffy and Law's Ultimate Stratagem!"
"The Ultimate Power! The
Secret of the Op-Op Fruit!"
"A Noble Family! The True
Identity of Doflamingo!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!