Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
On top of that, he put prices on
the heads of Luffy and 11 others,
and now they're being hunted
by all the citizens.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally got to the Royal Palace
where Doflamingo is!
I'm gonna kick his ass now!
He's pissing me off!
Idiot! I told you it's our ultimate stratagem!
I also told you not to get heated!
I'm gonna do it now! Gum-Gum...
Shambles!
...Red Hawk!
Radio Knife.
Straw Hat-ya! You're the worst!
"A Noble Family!
The True Identity of Doflamingo!"
How do you like that, bastard?!
Are you all right, Doffy?!
L-Law, you fool!
You're not gonna get away with this!
Straw Hat...
That was quite a blow!
See?! It didn't kill him!
That strategy will never work again!
Strategy?
You shitty brats!
You're messing with me!
A fake one, again?!
Dammit! That jerk!
I have no business with the fake-mingo!
It's an all-or-nothing gamble.
I'm determined to bet my life on it.
If you lose your dice,
the game is over before you can even roll.
Hello? Hello?!
Hello?
Are you listening, Sabo-kun?!
I am listening!
Don't lie! You're not listening at all!
You've been absent-minded the whole time!
Look! You have a position now!
You can't get emotional
and fight a guy like the Navy admiral!
Do you wanna lead
the Revolutionary Army into war?
My brother's in danger! I don't care!
--You should!
--Nah!
I don't wanna get dragged into a mess
by your recklessness!
--Scrwew iwt!
--What?!
An' dat guy is...
We are birds of a feather.
We Navy and Doflamingo are both
out of place.
The Navy will never be a hero
in this country.
If somebody notices that's
what you're thinking...
No.
I was just being blocked by you...
It's like a gamble.
I'm sort of a lucky man.
Okay?!
Understood?! Were you listening?!
You...
Sah... boh... -kun?!
Why're you always like that?!
You do what you like
while others are worried
about you like hell!
And Hack and I are forced
to clean up your mess!
I'm not your babysitter!
Come on! Hack and I always get chewed out
because of your selfish actions!
Ouch!
Navy Admiral Fujitora, huh?
Okay, done.
We'll lure the other criminals
using these criminals.
Please! Let go of me!
--Let's move on with the luring plan!
--Okay!
--Stop!
--Outta my way!
It's pirates!
Found him!
The 500 million prize - God Usopp!
We'll kill him and make a name
for our pirate group instantly!
Wait a sec! They're important hostages
to end the game!
Don't kill them!
Stop your hypocrisy!
It's the same if you hand
them over to Doflamingo!
What a pain... Let's kick all of their asses!
--H-Help!
--Do it! Do it!
Don't get behind!
Get out of our way!
H-Help... Please don't...
Don't hurt those citizens anymore!
If you want to do that, fight me first!
You shithead!
Guys! Get him!
King Riku-sama...
Tank! Hack! I need your help!
--Yes, sir!
--Roger!
Dammit!
Get away!
K-King Riku-sama...
--You didn't get hurt?
--N-No!
--Good!
--King Riku-sama...
--Kill King Riku!
--Kick his ass!
I won't let you guys lay a finger
on the citizens!
--King Riku-sama, we got them all.
--Good.
It hurts, doesn't it?
I'll give you first aid for now.
The old King Riku, he's awesome!
I'm sorry! I really am! No! Help!
What?
Wh-Why...?
Oh! I'm free!
Guys, is it okay to release us?
We shouldn't have done that.
For a decade, we were holding
a grudge against King Riku-sama
who was just manipulated by
Doflamingo for one night.
And we didn't even notice that
we had lost our loved ones.
We praised the king who was a pirate
and even after we learned the truth...
even after we learned the truth...
We were still looking for salvation
in the game he started!
We don't even know
what we're doing anymore...
What's gonna happen to us...?
What's gonna happen to this country?!
King Riku-sama... please save us!
Wh-What the...
--What happened to them?!
--What's going on?!
King Riku-sama!
What are we supposed to do?!
If you tell us to fight, we'll take up arms!
--King Riku-sama!
--We'll follow you!
Shall we wait... for a while?
What? Wait?
It won't be too late to choose death.
Why are they so important to you?!
They're pirates!
Yes, they're unlawful men - who will break
this country's deceptive peace!
Father-sama, I decided to trust them,
the Straw Hat Pirates!
At least, the words of Straw
Hat and the others are humane
and they take actions
out of the goodness of their hearts!
I have been believing in Luffy-kun and
the others' victory without realizing...
Navy Admiral Fujitora?!
Dressrosa was once the symbol of peace.
I won't let you get involved in a war.
Wh-Wh-Wh-Why the hell is he here?!
King Riku, sir.
I'm betting on the same one as you.
On the "Straw" and...
...nothing else!
Take a good look at this country!
If I stop now, what's gonna happen to it?!
Special Long-Range Attack! Bagworm!
Cien Fleurs!
Strong Right!
Three-Sword Style!
Thousand-and-Eighty Pound Phoenix!
I'll take you down!
Mingo!!
Bullet String!
Yeah, Doffy! That serves him right!
Law! I know all about your ability!
Because the ability of the Op-Op Fruit was
something we sought in the first place!
Even if I got chopped up,
I'm gonna turn back to normal!
Ready to fight back!
Oh?
Oh?!
Oh? Why is it?
Radio Knife is a different cutting method
from my regular Amputation.
For several minutes, even with any
treatment or ability, your body...
...can't be reassembled!
What?! I'm in trouble!
Can't help my nose running!
Oh, wait, wait, wait!
I can't stop snotting!
Damn!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Go away, Law!
Did you forget that I used
to treat you kindly?!
Room!
Stop! You traitor!
Injection!
Take this! Snot Blade-Catcher!
Shot!
Here's the finisher!
Fallbright!
Tra-guy!
I won't forgive anyone who
messes with my Family!
Do you remember
what I hate the most, Law?
To be looked down upon!
Tra-guy!
What? Suddenly, my body gets...
S-Stop!
Stop it! You stay away!
Get away!
Get away, Straw Hat!
Dodge!
--Bella...
--Dammit!!
Straw Hat-ya!
They're all beaten!
Did you think you could take me down?
The fact that shitty brats
like you guys got conceited
and thought even for a second,
that you could defeat me is...
...an unbearable humiliation to me!
Listen.
I'm a descendent of the noblest
bloodlines in the world...
The Celestial Dragon!
What?!
We're admirable just by
the fact of our birth.
I used to possess the most
unobtainable power in the world.
However,
one day, my father abandoned
the greatest power
in the world that we were born with,
and the four of us in the family...
...descended to this manure-pile world!
Screw that "live like human-beings" bull!
My father was an idiotic man!
Let's live a humble life here,
all four of us as a family!
What do you think happened?
Father! Where are the slaves-eh?!
Let's go buy some-eh!
Father, why don't they fall
down on their knees-eh?
Father! Why do they come after us-eh?!
They're a Celestial Dragon family!
Don't kill them... Make them suffer
for the rest of their lives!
By the age of ten,
I'd seen heaven and hell on earth.
Then, I killed my father
who caused all that
and returned to Mariejois with his head!
But...
...the Celestial Dragons in heaven
would never accept a renegade family!
I knew there was no way
to get out of this hell.
I swore to myself at that moment.
That I will destroy...
...every single thing in the world
that they dominate!
The life I've lived was
on a very different level from yours!
I have no time to play around...
...with you brats!
Facing Doflamingo, possessor of such
great power that he can even move
the World Government to action,
Luffy and Law are left helpless!
When their execution is
finally about to begin,
the world-shaking, tremendous
secret of the Op-Op Fruit
and Law's shocking past will be revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Ultimate Power! The
Secret of the Op-Op Fruit!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!