Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
a boy whose body turned
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of
the Pirates!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
and his friends venture into that sea.
they were trapped along with the entire island.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
Law's secret motive behind this fight was...
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Law, Doflamingo, and his brother Corazon.
Now, the relationship between
Law and Corazon unveils...
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
Their relationship began 16 years ago...
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo!
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
Trafalgar D. Water Law.
"Sad Memories!
Law the Boy from the White Town!"
they were trapped in the Birdcage along with the entire island.
they were trapped along with the entire island.
Law's secret motive behind this fight...
On top of that, he put prices on
the heads of Luffy and 11 others,
"D." is a secret name, "Water" is a true name.
For generations, my family...
Corazon,
in order to cure Law's White Lead Disease,
I'm grateful!
and now they're being hunted
by all the citizens.
took him out and went around various hospitals
for six months.
Because I can take you
all down with this power!
H-Hey, let go of me!
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
What the... Corazon!
What do you want?!
What's the Op-Op Fruit?
What are you gonna do to me?! Hey!
Luffy and Law finally clash with
Doflamingo at the Royal Palace!
It gives you the ability to
modify human bodies!
What you said before, was it true?
You can perform miraculous operations
THE NORTH BLUE - 16 YEARS AGO
You're still a rude little boy...
and cure even unknown diseases with it!
The secret name "D"...
Octopus Stamp!
Listen, we'll get a jump on Doffy
...and hearing you say "I'll die soon" is...
If it's true, you need to get out of here.
Get away from Doffy!
SPIDER MILES - A PORT TOWN
THE WASTE PROCESSING PLANT
and the others and steal the Op-Op Fruit!
...heartbreaking...
Law's secret motive behind this fight was...
Coming to Minion Island along with Law,
Law! You shouldn't be around him!
And I'm still here thanks to Cora-san!
You... stabbed me... that day but...
A BOY FROM THE WHITE TOWN
Corazon raided the hideout
of the pirate - Barrels
and managed to steal the Op-Op Fruit.
However...
TRAFALGAR LAW (10 YEARS OLD)
I'm grateful!
NO SOUND
...it didn't hurt at all!
Because I can take you
all down with this power!
"A Rocky Road!
Law and Corazon's Journey of Life!"
I got it, Law! It's the Op-Op Fruit!
I know you were the one who was in pain!
Law and Doflamingo.
Their relationship began 16 years ago...
Your disease will be cured!
You poor thing!
It's time to eat-dasuyan!
Law!
Knowing his days were numbered,
Law came to join the Don Quixote Family.
So this is it!
What the...?!
Who's this?! He freaked me out!
It's over, Straw Hat!
There, he met the silent,
child-hating Corazon.
Hey! A guy in a black coat
stole the Op-Op Fruit!
That crazy bastard!
Why?! Since when can you talk?!
There you are.
There he is! Corazon!
Go to hell!
It's him!!
My parents, young sister,
and everybody from the church were dead
Doffy wants to ask you something.
Since always.
I have a question, too!
"The Time is Ticking Down!
Seize the Op-Op Fruit!"
and that idiot is alive - it's not fair!
So you've been... fooling Doflamingo
all this time?!
They won't know if I keep quiet.
Hey, what are you doing?!
Nobody cares...
I've never told him that I became a mute.
He just thinks so.
...if a scumbag goes missing!
"The Moment of Resolution!
Corazon's Farewell Smile!"
That's... the same as fooling him!
What are you thinking...
You have no mercy, Corazon.
You hate kids so much...
Whoa-whoa-whoa.
"A Celestial Dragon!
Doffy's Stormy Past!"
Silence!
I'll kill him!
Tsk! It didn't cut it up!
What?!
It's too bad!
Huh? What the...
The sound of the streets is...
SWALLOW ISLAND - THE RENDEZVOUS POINT OF
THE DONQUIXOTE FAMILY ~ CORAZON
Tra-guy!
SPIDER MILES - A PORT TOWN IN THE NORTH BLUE
16 YEARS AGO
I shouldn't be wasting my time here
any longer!
Our next target is Rakesh.
Don't let your guard down.
Our enemy is Doflamingo!
What will you do then?
Those fools from that town
wag their tails at us
The sound of the streets is gone!
Yes, ma'am!
If it can't be cut by a sword,
how about this?!
while allying with other groups.
Why?!
Sengoku, that fool...
Looks like people are talking
but I can't hear anything!
TSURU
A VICE ADMIRAL OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
I'll make them pay for their betrayal.
You're loud so I put up a wall.
Where did he get the information
to deploy us like this?
A sound-proof wall.
You can't hear the sound from out there, huh?
They can't hear us, either.
--Vice Admiral Tsuru!
--Hm?
What do you want? We're having dinner.
They're a Celestial Dragon family!
We got a call from the look-out ship
at Minion Island!
It's my turn!
The wall is invisible.
Kill them!
Throw him out!
--It's fine.
--What?!
MINION ISLAND
THE ISLAND WHERE THE PIRATE BARRELS HIDES
They're "former" Celestial Dragons!
--I called him.
--You did?!
The Navy won't do anything
even if we kill them!
Barrels' hideout is on fire?
The admirals won't come, either!
I ate the Calm-Calm Fruit
and became a soundless human.
Yes! Some of us are heading
to see what's going on!
Hey, hey, Law! It's been a week now.
Don't you wanna get out of here?
Great! I got a chance to retaliate!
I thought I'd have to bear it silently all my life!
Idiot!
Once they find you guys,
the deal will be off!
You've been getting beaten by Corazon
since you came here.
--Break all their bones with a hammer!
--Shoot a thousand arrows!
A Devil Fruit eater?!
Check the coastal area now
and tell me if you see someone suspicious!
No! Don't kill them so easily!
Yes, ma'am!
Kids run away and so do adults.
That's why we only have the best here.
Keep them alive long enough
to make them suffer and suffer!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
What... What's wrong with you?!
You've lied about everything!
Don't tell me that...
making a blunder like an idiot is also...
--Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
--Hey, Cora-san! Cora-san!
Yeah! No slap-on-the-wrist!
How much longer
will a powerless brat like you last?
No! I wanna get my revenge on them now!
--Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
--I like how it sounds. Call me again!
I'm not gonna go anywhere!
Yeah, of course.
Listen, you jerks!
If so...
My sons were only five
and two years old...
Cut it out!
It's all acting.
Don't forget the "Blood Law"
no matter how you get harmed.
Don't lie! Your shoulder's on fire!
Don't be shy!
And all they did was cut across the
path of the Celestial Dragons...
Just pick it up! The Snail!
This Family will fall apart
if a member defies us Executives' authority.
But just for that reason,
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
they got killed!
It's me, Corazon.
I once laughed at Pica-sama
and almost died from torture.
My enslaved daughter came
home looking horrible
I've done those dumb things since I was a kid.
I can't change it. I'm dumb.
and without speaking a word,
THE GHOST TOWN
THE PIRATES' HIDEOUT
It doesn't scare me.
Hurry up and put out the fire!
she killed herself three days later!
Corazon, you're there, aren't you?
I've seen hell.
Shut up! The most ridiculous part of you
is the only thing that's not a lie?!
I was once your slave!
And my eyes...
Why do you hide things from
your friends?!
You can bluff as you like.
I don't consider them my friends.
Because of you jerks...
But Corazon is my precious,
biological, younger brother.
What I'm trying to do is stop my big brother Doffy
from going out of control.
Captain Barrels!
Give me back my wife!
If anyone so much as cuts him once,
I will...
You okay?
You guys don't give a damn about our lives!
It's been six months since you two left.
Let go of me!
I don't know how that beast was born
from our warm-hearted father and mother.
...put them to death!
Is Law with you?
Because of the Heavenly
Tribute we pay to you fools,
Forget about my wounds!
Doflamingo!
my country was destroyed by famine!
It's a five-billion berry deal!
Look at his skin!
Have you ever been hungry?!
It's White Lead Disease!
It's agonizing pain if you get infected!
Get back the Op-Op Fruit!
He has no... humanity.
Everyone became skin and bones, and died!
What?! It's contagious?!
You're disgusting!
You guys are like gods, aren't you?!
You're different from humans, right?
I see. I'm glad both of you are okay.
Get out of here now-dasuyan!
Then, I bet this won't kill you!
Have you found a good doctor?
Giolla, don't spread information
which is nothing more than a rumor.
Cora-san...
--Doffy!
--Brother!
I thought so.
Shame on you.
Look. Buffalo believed you.
Good. You are okay.
Help!
Bring Law and come back to the ship.
Dammit!
H-How dare you treat us humans...
White Lead Disease come from poisoning.
It's not contagious.
Silence.
We might be able to cure the disease.
worse than worms!
My children are innocent!
Aim all your arrows at me!
But stay away from me just in case-dasuyan!
Look! It's the Op-Op Fruit!
Do you know what it is like to
be in pain or grief or agony?!
I got information about the Op-Op Fruit.
I don't wanna catch such a disease-dasuyan!
Please! Don't harm my children!
Hey.
Hey, Celestial Dragons!!
The building is on fire and I heard some gunshots
Are there any other survivors
in the White Town, Flevance?
Offered a huge amount of money
by the Navy,
It hurts, Father!
I can't take it anymore!
some stupid pirates who don't know its value
will accept a tradeoff, it seems.
so I thought maybe something happened to you...
I don't know.
I was just desperate to escape.
How did you get out?
Hey! That's beside the point!
I crossed the border
hiding under a stack of dead bodies.
The Government must be pulling the strings
behind the scenes.
You gotta cheer up!
Hey! I'm eating!
This Devil Fruit will save your life!
It's risky but we'll seize it.
But even if I eat it,
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
What are you holding grudge against?
Once we get it,
because of the nature of its power,
you don't know if it will cure my disease...
Ring, ring, ring...
I'll get even...
I don't believe in anything anymore!
the person I trust the most should eat it.
I'll get even with you idiots!
What are you talking about?!
It will!
I'm not afraid to die!
--Now, eat it! Here! Eat it quickly!
--What are you doing...?!
Brother...
Corazon! Don't push your luck!
You eat it, Corazon.
I'm not gonna die!
Gross!
Ring, ring, ring...
I will get my revenge on you
at any cost!
And cure Law's disease.
There! Chew it like this!
Chew it up and swallow it down!
Hey, are you stupid?
Weren't you listening?!
I'm gonna survive no matter what you do to me
and I will...
They'll torture you if you do such a thing!
Clank.
Impalement!
Don't mess with pirates!
What do you guys think?
I will come kill
every single one of you jerks!!
Children are idiots!
Even including Tsuru who often smelled out where we were
and came after us,
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring...
They think their apologetic tears
will guarantee forgiveness!
RAKESH - A PORT TOWN
the Navy hasn't showed their face at all
in the past six months.
He was born to be evil-natured
and he's never afraid of anything.
Ring, ring... Clank.
H-Hey, Cora-san!
I wasn't even ready to become a...
What do you want?
Six months that Corazon was away.
Law did it?
The only people who know
about his true brutality are
...Devil Fruit eater!
Are you saying that
he was tipping the Navy off before?
Okay.
The Don Quixote Family!
the four Executives including me
Clank.
and the first Corazon - Vergo.
Cora-san? H-Hey!
It could be just a coincidence.
Vergo?
He's a strong man who's currently
Shoot! Shoot!
I hope so.
I don't want to distrust him...
It's good...
separated from the Family
on a secret mission.
THE HOLYLAND OF MARIEJOIS - 33 YEARS AGO
You can... cure yourself now...
The details of the mission have been kept secret
even from the Family members.
He's my biological brother.
Are you sure, St. Homing?!
We have outsmarted Doflamingo...
We won...
You have no business with him.
I thought you'd be the
last person to do that!
It's good news! Law!
Armsmorphosis!
Anyway...
You're saying you give
up your status as a god
Don't become a beast like my brother!
You gotta get out of here, Law!
What's wrong, Cora-san?
Are you just tired?
and reduce yourself to a human?!
You have a chance to survive!
Forget about foolish doctors!
ST. DON QUIXOTE HOMING
THE WORLD NOBLE (CELESTIAL DRAGON)
I am a human. Since I was born.
No way! I want to be like that!
What?!
If we can get the Op-Op Fruit,
we'd be able to cure your White Lead Disease!
Wait a minute!
Are you saying we are too-eh?!
That's sacrilege!
What's the Op-Op Fruit?
Who do you think we Celestial Dragons are?!
Ten-Ton Vise!
It gives you the ability to
modify human bodies!
Traitor! You've always been heretical!
You can perform miraculous operations
and cure even unknown diseases with it!
The secret name "D."!
It's no mistake.
You're covered in blood!
He's right, Traitor!
You're a part of that fated family -
the Family of D.
Cora-san, did you get shot?!
I don't believe in that magic crap...
I don't care what you think.
Humans are wonderful.
Back in my home,
children are disciplined like this.
No! It's no magic!
You need medical knowledge!
Yeah, I made a little blunder...
Damn!
What are you doing, Cora-san?!
It's way more satisfying to
live as a human.
"A badly behaving child will be
eaten up by D."
Oh yeah!
I know that you're the son of a doctor
who was trusted by the people of Flevance!
That's how I think.
Get better! Get better!
There have often been people
who have the name "D."
Hey, what kind of place is the White Town
where that kid was from?
who gained public notoriety
--Eek! What did you say?!
--So rude-eh!
Get better!!
Since the time you were able to understand,
People called the whole land Flevance.
and old people would frown and mutter,
Get out of Mariejois now!
Stop bleeding! Stop!!
you were learning medical knowledge and techniques,
weren't you?!
--Flevance?
--Yeah.
"'D.' will surely bring us another storm."
--Op-Op power! Heal him!
--That's foolish of you...
We can't take you farther than here.
The citizens were all rich
Yeah but...
what does it have to do with this?!
and the towns were all white,
from the soil to the plants,
I told you the ability doesn't work like magic.
What are you saying?!
Am I some kind of monster?
We're at the north end.
like a snow country in a fairy tale.
So, it's perfect for you to eat it!
A non-member nation of the World Government.
What am I supposed to do, then?!
Maybe.
I heard the country was out of this world.
An adequate house and assets
are ready for you there.
You... got shot because of me,
didn't you?!
Me?!
Doflamingo said you should eat it!
Nobody knows the truth but that name has been
Thank you. That's all we need.
One day, they discovered White Lead,
a type of lead, underground
ceaselessly and secretly inherited
throughout history all across the world.
I said it's not like that...
I just messed up...
Now, I'll collect
your Celestial Dragon ID chips.
A person will die
if he eats two Devil Fruits.
and found out that was the source of
the fantastic scenery.
And in some places, there are people
who call the Family of D...
Law... I'll be alright!
Doffy said that because he doesn't know
that I'm a Devil Fruit eater.
They made utensils, paint,
These wounds won't kill me...
sweeteners, cosmetics,
and even weapons out of White Lead.
Cora-san!
You and I...
We won't go back to the Family!
Let's live a humble life here,
all four of us as a family.
But I want to stanch the bleeding
for a while...
"Sworn enemy of the gods"!
People all over the world wanted to buy
their high-quality White Lead goods
What?
We need to unpack first.
Listen carefully, Law.
We sure did get the Op-Op Fruit.
and it became Flevance's major industry.
God?!
Father! Where are the slaves-eh?
Say the "god" means the Celestial Dragons,
Let the slaves put away stuff-eh.
But it won't stop
Doflamingo running wild yet!
The quick-eyed World Government went into
the purpose of your people might be
"destruction of this world."
the transport business
to ship that merchandise.
If there aren't any,
let's go buy some-eh.
I decided so when I noticed
this journey would take longer than I thought.
White Lead made people a fortune.
I'm sorry to use you when you're weakened
But it's completely different in meaning
from what Doffy is going for!
Doffy. Rocinante.
but I need you to do me a favor.
I think Doffy knows that
I'm a traitor by now.
We have to teach you from scratch.
I saw a Navy look-out ship
off the west coast of the island...
D.'s must have an idea
that's opposed to the god's.
But he didn't sound like it.
He said you should eat it...
I want you to hand this over to them...
You look great, Doffy.
There is another reason for Doffy to say
he wants me to eat the Op-Op Fruit!
No!
All the Navy soldiers will know what it is
once they see this cylinder.
I don't wanna wear these!
I look like a slave-eh!
FLEVANCE - THE WHITE TOWN
I don't know what you're talking about!
Stop.
I joined the Family to kill every single person
as violently as possible!
No, Father, I don't want them-eh!
I'll stink if I wear these-eh!
This one small package will save...
Doffy...
Since I won't refuse you,
...a far-off kingdom called Dressrosa.
I'm not your subordinate!
I am Doflamingo's subordinate!
Doffy, we're gonna live
as humans from now on.
you're looking to have eternal life
in exchange for my life, aren't you?
A kingdom? But I hate the Navy...
I'm gonna die in a year!
What should I do if I get out of here?!
Humans?
I'll get killed if I go back!
We'll lead a life far richer than
the life in Mariejois.
You're the son of a doctor, aren't you?
Listen, we'll get a jump on Doffy and the others
and steal the Op-Op Fruit!
--Get out of here and look for a cure!
--There is none!
Law, for this kind of surgery,
you use this blood vessel.
What I mean by "rich" is
not having so many things.
You'll be able to save more than just sick people from now on, Law.
I'm gonna tell Doflamingo that you can talk
and about your ability and all!
It's about heart.
Oh yeah!
You're a genius, Father-sama!
You eat the Fruit!
Don't do it!
When you get cured,
let's go hide somewhere!
Don't get so bent out of shape.
You can't get away with it
just by getting kicked out!
Brother-sama!
Let's go to the festival!
Here are your two apples.
As soon as you finish delivering this,
let's get off of this island!
Damn brat!
No! I'm studying now.
Excuse me.
I would like to purchase some food.
Prepare to set sail!
We'll get the Op-Op Fruit at any cost!
What?! No! No! Come on!
Oh? You don't look familiar.
Later.
Yes. I moved here from Mariejois recently.
I became stronger in the last two years!
That serves you right!
And let's travel all around the world,
just you and I!
--Clank.
--"Rice crackers"!
My name is Don Quixote Homing.
Law, studying is good but if you push
Hey, Law!
You broke the Blood Law again!
What?!
"Rice-cracker pellets"! It's me.
yourself too much,
it's not good for you.
Rosinante! It's been a while.
I've been worried about you!
M-Mariejois...
Hey, what are you two doing
by moving your mouths?!
Sometimes you need to
go out and have fun.
A-Are you a Celestial Dragon?
Hey, Garp!
Why don't you go out for a sec?!
Well, Mother-sama,
you're always working, too.
I'll buy you an ice cream so keep quiet.
What?! I just brought you senbei crackers!
Make green tea for me!
I've cast that title aside.
I am a human from now on.
I have an idea! Mother-sama,
let's go to the festival together!
I want the king size that costs
500 berries-dasuyan!
Baby 5, lend me some money.
Vice Admiral Garp...
No, I...
We want to become friends with you all.
Yeah. Why don't you three go?
Now isn't a good time, Sengoku-san?
What?! O-Okay!
The Navy soldiers...
What?
Get out! Idiot!
I gotta work! W-O-R-K!
Blush! He needs me!
All right. But just for 30 minutes.
We have so many patients to take care of.
Hey!
NAVY
Humph!
How dare he treat me like a nuisance! Sengoku!
Why don't you fall down on your knees?!
You fools are disrespectful!
Yeah!
Law! Let's go! To the festival!
Oh, Kuzan!
Do you wanna eat senbei crackers with me?
You just cut across in front of me, didn't you?
Somebody, get a gun!
Uh-huh!
Um... Can I talk?
Who do you think I am?!
Hey, you idiots!
Is this it?!
Yeah, sorry. Go ahead.
The White Town was
the land everyone longed for.
Do you have a deal regarding
the Op-Op Fruit?
Where are the Celestial Dragons?!
Oh, I wanna go there!
He's all by himself!
--Find them!
--Hang them up!
Lon"g"ed for! There's the "G"!
Dammit!
Father, why don't they fall down
on their knees-eh?
I trusted that little brat and
told him everything!
H-How did you know?!
But it's gone now.
What?
My brother knew it.
I think Doffy's not back yet today.
What?! But it's top secret!
Let's just pack up my stuff
and take off before he comes back.
Cora-san must be talking to...
Hey, take this!
They're not in here! They must've run!
Corazon!
I wanna know those pirates' activities.
Oh, it must be a secret letter.
Find them! I don't think
they got too far yet!
What?!
I don't think we can find them
before the trade...
I bet somebody asked you to deliver it.
About a century ago, when the White
Lead industry was established,
Don't kill them!
Keep them alive and let them suffer!
Thank you.
Even if Doflamingo is looking to
steal the Op-Op Fruit before the trade?
Yeah!
Get several centuries worth of revenge
out of that family!
the World Government performed
geological survey in the country
No! Why is he back already?!
I'll keep it. Don't worry.
Is it true?!
Yeah!
Oh? Hm?
and the fact is they had
already known the truth.
By the way, little boy,
you sound so weak...
I kind of feel dizzy...
The truth?
--It was poison.
--What?
When and where will the trade be?
You're back. We gotta set sail!
It's Tsuru from the Navy HQ again!
Can I trust you?
--Wait!
--Don't let them get away!
Poison that was not so harmful
unless you dig it up.
Three weeks from now,
at Rubeck in the North Blue.
Yeah, if you're talking about the letter,
I'll take responsibility and...
But if you handle it somehow,
it'll erode your body.
They know we're here!
Rubeck...
Hurry up!
I need you to help someone!
I'll meet up with Doffy and the others
at Swallow Island three days before the handoff.
Erode?
Hasn't he... told him yet?
H-He got shot and he's dying!
Doffy!
The poison will harm your body
just by touching it.
Please! Save him!
Three days before, huh?
Father! Why do they come after us-eh?!
So I guess all of the Family members
will wait for the fight there for sure.
What?!
I don't want him to die at any cost!
Knowing this but blinded by
the easy fortune to be had,
I decided not to tell him.
That's a good tip.
He got shot... because of me!
the Government and the royalty
of that country kept it secret.
I thought twice and remembered
That'll be it for Doflamingo!
We'll ambush at Swallow Island
I owe you for keeping quiet about
me stabbing you two years ago.
We should be thankful
to be out of the rain here at least.
The citizens kept digging up White Lead
knowing nothing.
and catch the Donquixote Family
in one fell swoop!
We're even now.
People around here haven't
heard about us yet.
If they did so, they would die.
You stay away from the island!
--Let's stay here for a while...
--No!
Yeah.
Cora-san!
I was planning on it.
How can I live in such a dirty place-eh?!
But the terrible part was
it only contained traces of poison.
The list of all Doffy's business partners
and the big names
He said he's gonna give you first aid!
There are bugs inside the house!
The smell here makes me sick-eh!
Corazon! Hurry up!
connected with him behind the scenes,
Cora-san!
Say, the Lead keeps building up
in a young person's body,
I'll give it to you sometime soon.
Corazon!
TSURU
when he has a child,
I think it's enough for you to uncover...
the dark side of the North Blue.
Cora-san!
the child will, actually,
have a shorter life expectancy.
Vergo!
Corazon?! What are you doing here?!
Okay. Thank you.
Corazon!
Clank.
Huh? Did you just talk?!
And when the kid grows up
and has his own child
Corazon!
Oh no! Don't tell me his secret mission is...
Hey, Law. Are you ready?
Where are Corazon and Law?
that child's life expectancy is
even shorter.
We gotta sail out...
Find the family!
Law!
THE NEGATIVE EFFECT
ON FUTURE GENERATIONS
Life expectancy got shorter
generation by generation
They should still be around here!
I saw them on board.
Aren't they here?!
Law! Hey! You gotta be kidding!
Stay with me!
and eventually, a generation doomed to die
Kill them as soon as you find them!
What's going on?
before adulthood, just like Law, was born.
Not now! We finally got a chance!
You two know each other?
We gotta run! Now!
Vergo... Is he...
When the world finally realized
White Lead is poisonous...
It's not been three years yet!
I thought you still had time left according to your calculation!
Vergo?
He's a strong man who's currently separated
Oh no! He has a very high fever!
What should I do?!
It was too late.
Young Master!
I found this on Corazon's hammock.
from the Family on a secret mission.
Doctors are all useless!
The details of the mission have been kept secret even from the Family members.
I'M LEAVING TO GO CURE LAW'S DISEASE
They packed their things and left, it seem.
Oh yeah! Let's give him some water!
You have no business with him.
What is he thinking?!
This is kidnapping!
I couldn't expect it'd turn out this bad.
Untie me! Hey!
Dammit!
What am I supposed to do?!
Tell me, Law!
Corazon! You jerk!
I'll make you pay for this!
I was too optimistic.
Please! I'll do anything!
Don't! That's...
Say something! Hey!
Just my wife and children are fine.
--Ring, ring, ring...
--Hey, pick up the Transponder Snail!
This way! This way! Hurry up!
So Vergo's mission is to infiltrate the Navy!
Please make it!
Would you let them go back to Mariejois?!
Brother-sama! Come on!
Isn't it Doflamingo?!
I'll talk! Pick it up!
If we stay here, we all get killed!
How unlucky!
Lammy, you don't have to rush like that.
Stay alive for another three weeks!
--Ring, ring, ring...
--I said pick it up! Pick it up!
There are thousands of Navy soldiers
and of all of them, he got the letter!
That was your choice-eh.
What if the festival ends!
--Ring, ring, ring...
--Doflamingo! Help!
Give me a chance!!
You can't take back something you gave up.
It won't end yet.
What are you gonna do to me?!
Don't ever call me again!
You're no more than a human!
Understood. Rosinante!
Hey!
Lammy?
THREE DAYS BEFORE THE TRADE
W-Wait! I beg you!
What? Lammy!
Dammit! Why does it have
to be so choppy now?!
Clank.
What's wrong? Are you alright?!
Cora-san...
Huh? What's wrong, Law?!
Give it back to me!
That's...!
The Government knew that we would die
You bread thieves!
Cora-san!!
At some point, people started
to collapse one after another.
but they kept making us dig up White Lead, for money!
Father! For the first time in my life,
Grandparents, parents,
and then children.
My family... and the people of Flevance...
I feel pain-eh!
Because of the differences in
The Government killed them!
their life expectancies,
all generations fell ill around the same time.
Their skin and hair got whiter rapidly
Father!
Po-pi-pu-pa-po-pi-pi.
So if you're a Navy soldier allied with them,
and people died one after another
with their entire bodies in pain.
For the first time in my life,
I'm hungry-eh!
--Ring, ring, ring...
--Are you calling Doflamingo?!
No doctor could stop that.
tell me the truth.
--Hey! Help me!
--Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Cora-san!!
That's absurd! I'm not a Navy soldier!
"Rice crackers"!
Eat fast, Rocy!
"Rice-cracker pellets"! It's me.
Somebody's gonna come!
Good!
Oh, it's Rosinante, isn't it?
In fact... You need to realize -
Stealing the Op-Op Fruit means...
Rosinante!
Mother, we brought you some food-eh!
I'm taking a break from
my mission for a while.
Stop it!
Doffy. Rocy.
You! You! Dammit!
...we'll make enemies of everybody...
Doflamingo, the Navy, and the Government!
Then, all the people in his country died?!
Mother!
You! You! You! You!
I'm sorry...
I don't feel quite...
NAVY
You're the Vergo guy, aren't you?!
I feel sorry...
We'll be chased by all of them!
...well...
--The real tragedy began after that.
--What?
--Are you in trouble?
--No, it's personal.
You better be prepared to fight to live!
Seeing the people in the White Town
all dying with the same symptoms,
The Vergo guy?
Okay, got it.
So I guess
you're Law from the White Town.
How are the kids?
Are they still there even though
you're giving them a hard time?
the people in the neighboring countries
I heard about you.
I heard you two went missing.
I don't think those three will leave
thought White Lead Disease was contagious.
Father...
Mother is dead-eh!
The Family's became quite ill-famed now.
Be careful.
So they blocked off the country completely
You have no sense of propriety!
and took quarantine measures
against the White Town.
If you know that I'm your great senpai, you call me...
Okay.
We got them!!
ADMIRAL SENGOKU
THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
"Vergo-san"!
Pardon my boys! Just take me!!
I entrust this case to you
so do whatever you like.
MINION ISLAND
The royalty got help
Have you found the pirates, Sengoku-san?
Keep me updated.
from the Government and escaped
the country at an early stage.
Please! I'm begging you!
Roger that.
I'll send you the details in writing.
Yeah, east of Rubeck
where we'll have a trade,
Law!
The citizens were abandoned.
You wrote down
a fair amount of information in here.
Clank.
People from the White Town who
were looking to get treated and...
If the Navy got this kind of letter,
that'd be it for the Family!
there's Minion Island which has a ghost town.
...immigrate to other countries,
Looks like that's where their hideout is.
COMMANDER DONQUIXOTE ROSINANTE
were feared as if they were
monsters escaping from the cage and...
Father!
Likewise for our future plans and everything!
Diez Barrels is the pirate's name.
Sounds familiar?
Admiral Sengoku!
BUDDHA
The man who wishes to transfer
who I told you about the other day, is here.
...they were shot dead.
Yeah, he's a former Navy officer...
Is the kid more important to you
than the Family?!
Oh, all right. Come in.
That's right.
Our look-out ship is staking out
Minion Island now.
They really "swept it under the rug."
The second Corazon!
So it's you.
I've been hearing about you.
Dammit!
You idiot!
The pain of the disease was
just somebody else's problem.
This is your first year after
you officially enlisted
It's all as Sengoku-san said.
Look what you've done-eh!!
and you've been quite successful...
I can't believe we had a rat like you in our Family!
Very human like...
Meanwhile, at Swallow Island
where you and Doflamingo were going to meet up,
But Flevance couldn't keep quiet.
Wishing to transfer to G-5, huh?
Young Master-sama, we caught Law!
Ironically, they had tons of lead bullets.
there are two warships.
First of all, I want to ask you about
the sunny-side up egg on your left cheek...
When you were eight, you went missing one day.
I guess he suddenly decided to escape.
I don't think anyone can see here...
Yes, sir! My name is Vergo, sir!
And you came back to us again...
Dammit! Let go of me!
Eventually, a war broke out!
I won't let Doflamingo steal the Op-Op Fruit!
...14 years later!
It was enough to be skeptical about you!
Where were you calling just now?!
He was already at the port-in.
Other countries justified their actions
as self defense so they showed no mercy!
You said "mission"!
Are you a Navy soldier or something?!
They'll start torturing him
for stabbing Cora-san-dasuyan!
Law, it won't be long. Wait here...
But merely because you're his brother,
Doffy didn't distrust you!
I'm sure you can imagine the rest.
But Law is a poor boy...
You don't like the Navy soldiers?
People tying to the Government
make me sick!
You should know what's coming,
shouldn't you, Rosinante?!
What?!
--I'm not a Navy soldier.
--Really?!
Hey! Let go of me! Corazon!
Hey! I don't wanna go to hospital!
Corazon...!
Damn! He didn't die!
Then, will I get killed for nothing?!
Stop acting so predictably like a normal kid!
Please stop...
Cora-san... He's gonna die!
I'm gonna cure your disease!
I'm gonna take you to every single hospital!
I shut Buffalo's mouth
by buying him an ice cream
Law-kun!
Come on, you gotta come with us!
but he told Doflamingo himself!
Look! It's a big hospital!
They'll cure you!
There are gentle soldiers who told us
I'm sure the blade went through his body!
they will let only the children escape!
Drie! Booze! Bring more booze!
Wh... White Lead Disease?!
Stop it, Vergo!!
--Law!
--We'll be safe!
How can he act like he's fine?!
It's been around for a while now.
Don't you have a good medicine for it, Doc?
Right away.
How much do you think
this one fruit would cost?
Law...
E-E-Excuse me but where are you from...?
I called you in for just one thing.
Sister! My young sister is dying!
They offered five billion!
I decided to welcome you to the
Doflamingo Family officially.
Flevance.
I can't go now!
--The White Town!!
--Yikes! No! I'm gonna get infected!
Lammy-chan is?! I see...
How ridiculous!
Did the Government go nuts?!
What?
H-Hey! Bring me antiseptic and gloves
and a gas mask now!
Once we got that much money,
there's no reason for us to be pirates!
Then, let's ask them to get you
on board the next ship to escape!
The Family-in!
And call security and the Government!
Hurry up!
I'll come back to pick you up!
--No! Nooo!!
--Forget it!
Law! Aren't you coming?!
Let's escape together!
Because you went through
such a horrible experience,
Right, right!
--Law!
--See?! I'm not even a human anymore!
I'm sure they'll save Lammy later, too!
you got that incomparable,
hateful look in your eyes.
It may sound too simple but...
Both my father and mother are dead!
...once a doctor eats this,
he'll become a famous doctor
in great demand all over the world.
You have the "quality."
But they told me to live!
Whoa-whoa,
you haven't killed them, have you?
White monster!
Please leave! I beg you!
So I'm gonna live no matter what!!
He sees potential in your future!
Young Master-sama is a visionary man!
There was a legendary doctor who ate this
and cured intractable or rare diseases...
They're still breathing...
Just barely though.
Hey, you!
How dare you bring such a kid here?!
Law! Law!
...by performing miraculous operations,
they say.
Doesn't he know
what I did to Corazon yet?
How many patients do you think we have...
Listen, Law-kun.
So, what do you know?
This is an emergency announcement.
Why? He can tell him by writing...
But it has nothing to do with us!
There is always hope.
We have a child with White Lead Disease
in the hospital.
Corazon was the Navy's spy
A merciful helping hand will...
--Yeah, getting money is way better!
--That's right!
and he was with the Family in order to frame you!
What is he up to?
...reach to you like this.
Be careful. They must know all of your plans!
Even if he sees future potential in me,
I will die in three years anyway!
Where are you now, Doffy?
Doctor, help!
I was watching the rendezvous spot, Swallow Island,
Doctor!!
That depends on your luck!
It's impossible! I can't go there!
from a distance earlier and two warships came.
The big guy is violent!
Luck?
We don't have enough doctors!
Same for blood and everything!
We specialize in the black market.
That's when I became convinced.
We'll sterilize the entire building now.
And we handle the Devil Fruits, too.
There must be a way to clear
away White Lead from bodies!
My once-lovely young brother shows me his teeth.
It was the worst hospital ever!
And some of those Fruits have
powers that are beyond human knowledge.
I'm sorry.
Did it bring back your old memories?
And it's not contagious!
Why doesn't the Government report that?!
And it reminded me...
Look at this, Law!
There might be a Fruit
that could cure your disease.
This is why I told you!
I don't wanna go to hospital!
Clank.
This will cause anything I interact with
to not make any noise!
...that you guys are...
Devil Fruits?
...the only "family" I got!
If you're lucky,
That one was terrible...
But I'm sure there'll be a good doctor
in the next one!
Brother-sama, my body hurts.
Sadly, what I thought was true, it seems.
Calm!
your life could be saved by
a Devil Fruit we come across
I don't wanna go!
My skin's getting whiter and whiter.
We just landed at
Minion Island where you guys are.
in the three years you have left.
White Lead Disease! No! Somebody, help!
NO SOUND!
I will train you to become my
right-hand man 10 years from now.
Hang on for a little more.
The survivor of the White Town!
That face...
But it was a bit too late...
Our father is the greatest
doctor in the country.
Let's go to the next!
You'll get cured in the next one!
We arrived and saw Barrels' underlings
He'll heal you!
Enough! I don't wanna go!
running around saying the Devil Fruit got stolen.
NO SOUND
What's wrong?
The direction of his eyes!
Hello?! World Government?!
Why is it so noisy outside?
We have a survivor from Flevance here!
NO SOUND
ENEMY
It must be Corazon!
Why didn't you kill all of them?!
Stinks!
There's a festival.
Flevance is always prosperous.
If he's there, don't let him go anywhere!
He has the Op-Op Fruit!
--What?
--An enemy hurt you?
See? You heard nothing, right?!
You assholes!
Did you take care of him?
Look, Law!
People in this town look kind!
What is that ability good for?!
Get well soon and
let's go to a festival together again!
Okay...
I FINISHED HIM OFF
Tsk! Those fools...!
No!!
It's not even cool!
That's good. Get it treated, okay?
Ugh! I'm gonna get infected! Go away!
Oh, did they run?
Uh-huh!
Look for White Lead Disease
patients and kill them!
Baby 5's Arms-Arms is
much better than that!
Well, no worries.
How dare you call yourself a doctor?!
Did he just... cover up for me?
Damn! You're right!
I wish I had that power!
Screw you!
As long as they're in the town...
--Eight hospitals were damaged.
Which way did those two go?!
Lammy, stay in here for a few minutes.
But no one can have a quiet sleep like me...
The boy with the disease is...
What is he thinking, really?!
I won't let them get away.
Uh-huh...
Corazon, not only have I not gotten cured
but I'm at my limit
Whatever!
Towards Reverse Mountain in the southeast,
we'll keep moving our base
Stop whining!
You'll get cured in the next one!
Got rid of two infected people!
It's either find the cure or death!
Your life is on the edge now!
and expanding our business.
Stay strong!
--White Lead Disease!
--Close the hospital! They're gonna come in!
I'm gonna killed y'all!
No, Corazon!
Corazon!!
What was that quake?!
What's that?! Something's coming down!
What the hell?!
Captain! Th-There wasn't any noise
but the compound's exploded!
What's going on
on this island?!
This ain't good!
SIX MONTHS LATER
What?! That can't be happening!
Law!
Law! Let's go! To the festival!
The treasure house is on fire!
Ouch!
--These strings are like blades!
--They're solid, too!
Put out the fire now!
What's going on?!
Mother-sama!!
Damn! We can't get out!
Father-sama!!
What am I doing...?
Is there an invader?!
There's still somebody!
--The lights went off!
--Pieces of glass are falling onto us!
I've been repeatedly making the kid from
the tragic town relive the tragedy...
Cora-san, what happened to us...
The lamps! The lamps are broken!
Oh, where is Vergo...?
And he hasn't gotten any better...
Somebody! Somebody put on a light...
Don't let him get away! Kill him!
What's that?
Am I doing it for "D."?
That's one of Doffy's abilities, I suppose.
No... I don't care about that anymore.
Hurry up and put on a light!
I've never seen it before but
there's one thing I know.
We have nowhere to run.
I have...
I have been feeling sorry for him...
What?
Somebody's here!
Law!
I'm sure you don't want...
Somebody! Stop me!
...this idiot who just keeps hurting you...
Listen, Law-kun.
There is always hope.
...to say something like this but...
NO SOUND
A merciful helping hand will...
TWO YEARS LATER
Using the Parasite String in the cage, huh...
...reach to you like this.
We told you our real names!
You're still a rude little boy...
--What the...
--Is that... what that guy did?!
So? I'm not interested!
Yeah, this is like hell...
...and hearing you say "I'll die soon" is...
Sister!!
You're so uncool! You're no fun!
...heartbreaking...
Everybody!!
Even if I have fun, I'll die anyway.
You have quite a lot of white parts now.
I got it, Law! It's the Op-Op Fruit!
You... stabbed me... that day but...
I don't know if
I can live another year...
Cora-san, what's going on?
Your disease will be cured!
I may die sooner than I calculated.
Let's escape together!
...it didn't hurt at all!
So I'm gonna live no matter what!!
That aside, if you have a real name,
tell us-dasuyan!
I know you were the one who was in pain!
Or I'll tell the Young Master
you stabbed Cora-san two years ago!
You poor thing!
Law!
Yeah, we will!
The hospital...!
Trafalgar D. Water Law.
Huh?
--What the...?!
--Who's this?! He freaked me out!
I shouldn't tell that name
to anybody, actually.
Where did he tumble down from?
Hey!
A guy in a black coat stole the Op-Op Fruit!
I don't go by a code name like you two
so it's just a little longer.
Don't let him get away!
Cora-san...
Lammy!!
"D." is a secret name,
"Water" is a true name.
A guy in a black coat?!
Hey, Cora-san!
Breakfast is ready.
For generations, my family...
--How boring! This is not fun at all.
--Yeah-dasuyan.
It's him!!
Flevance, the White Town, perished.
What is that face?!
You guys asked me repeatedly!
You just called me Cora-san...
Shut up and eat breakfast!
H-Hey, let go of me!
Maybe I can let Law get away, just him...
By people's hands, at last.
What the... Corazon!
What do you want?! Hey!
Oh, he's gonna get beaten again.
If a ten-year-old kid went
through such a thing...
Law, I can't take you with me from here.
I have no chance to survive now but...
Cora-san looked scarier than usual.
Cora-san!
Of course, it screws up his personality.
will you remember me even after I die?
I know it's hard but...
wait here for a while.
I'll die with a smile so...
Cora-san! The tears you shed for me!
I won't ever forget them!
There he is! Corazon!
What do you want, Corazon?!
Do you wanna fight?!
My parents, young sister,
and everybody from the church were dead
I'll be back in no time.
With the Op-Op Fruit!
and that idiot is alive - it's not fair!
What are you doing?! Bring it on!
Because... if you think of me someday,
They won't know if I keep quiet.
Nobody cares...
...if a scumbag goes missing!
What you said before, was it true?
I'd rather you remember my smile.
What?
Stop! Don't do this!
Huh? Oh? Who is it?!
Bellamy!
The secret name "D"...
So this is it!
If it's true, you need to get out of here.
Damn! He saw!
It's over, Straw Hat!
Get away from Doffy!
He... b-broke the... Blood Law!
Law, we gotta get going.
Law! You shouldn't be around him!
He deserves impalement-dasuyan!
I must inform...
...the Young Master-dasuyan!
Go to hell!
Let's go!
Corazon seized the Op-Op Fruit.
As Corazon gets driven into the corner by Donquixote Family,
Doflamingo was born as one of the
As Law's moment of death approaches,
There is only a little time left for Law!
Celestial Dragons who rule
everything in the world!
But when he reaches to Law,
his body has already exceeded its limit.
he and Corazon set off on a journey
to look for a cure for his disease.
he finally faces Doflamingo.
Corazon plans to steal the Op-Op
Fruit making enemy out of everyone,
Why did he lose his noble status?!
When Corazon takes a chance risking his life,
in order to save Law and
live together with him.
After the long, painful journey,
Corazon starts pouring out his heart in tears
To save Corazon,
Law desperately looks for help
When Doflamingo's unimaginable
past is revealed,
a single bullet is shot at him
At the fateful Minion Island,
Corazon's life-risking fight is now on!
but when a Navy soldier
shows up in front of him,
which starts the young Law
on a path towards freedom.
Law's life as a child changes in a big way!
which deepens the bond between the two!
the wheel of fortune begins to spin out of control!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Celestial Dragon! Doffy's Stormy Past!"
"Advance, Law! The Kindhearted Man's Final Fight!"
"The Time is Ticking Down!
Seize the Op-Op Fruit!"
"The Moment of Resolution! Corazon's Farewell Smile!"
"A Rocky Road! Law and
Corazon's Journey of Life!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!