Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo!
Now, the relationship between
Law and Corazon unveils...
"Sad Memories!
Law the Boy from the White Town!"
THE NORTH BLUE - 16 YEARS AGO
SPIDER MILES - A PORT TOWN
THE WASTE PROCESSING PLANT
A BOY FROM THE WHITE TOWN
TRAFALGAR LAW (10 YEARS OLD)
It's time to eat-dasuyan!
That crazy bastard!
There you are.
Doffy wants to ask you something.
I have a question, too!
Hey, what are you doing?!
You have no mercy, Corazon.
You hate kids so much...
I'll kill him!
Our next target is Rakesh.
Those fools from that town
wag their tails at us
while allying with other groups.
I'll make them pay for their betrayal.
What do you want? We're having dinner.
Throw him out!
--It's fine.
--What?!
--I called him.
--You did?!
Hey, hey, Law! It's been a week now.
Don't you wanna get out of here?
You've been getting beaten by Corazon
since you came here.
Kids run away and so do adults.
That's why we only have the best here.
How much longer
will a powerless brat like you last?
I'm not gonna go anywhere!
If so...
Don't forget the "Blood Law"
no matter how you get harmed.
This Family will fall apart
if a member defies us Executives' authority.
I once laughed at Pica-sama
and almost died from torture.
It doesn't scare me.
I've seen hell.
You can bluff as you like.
But Corazon is my precious,
biological, younger brother.
If anyone so much as cuts him once,
I will...
...put them to death!
Look at his skin!
It's White Lead Disease!
It's agonizing pain if you get infected!
What?! It's contagious?!
You're disgusting!
Get out of here now-dasuyan!
Giolla, don't spread information
which is nothing more than a rumor.
Shame on you.
Look. Buffalo believed you.
White Lead Disease come from poisoning.
It's not contagious.
But stay away from me just in case-dasuyan!
I don't wanna catch such a disease-dasuyan!
Hey.
Are there any other survivors
in the White Town, Flevance?
I don't know.
I was just desperate to escape.
How did you get out?
I crossed the border
hiding under a stack of dead bodies.
Hey! I'm eating!
What are you holding grudge against?
I don't believe in anything anymore!
I'm not afraid to die!
Corazon! Don't push your luck!
I will get my revenge on you
at any cost!
Hey, are you stupid?
Weren't you listening?!
They'll torture you if you do such a thing!
Impalement!
Don't mess with pirates!
Children are idiots!
They think their apologetic tears
will guarantee forgiveness!
RAKESH - A PORT TOWN
The Don Quixote Family!
Shoot! Shoot!
Armsmorphosis!
Ten-Ton Vise!
Hey, what kind of place is the White Town
where that kid was from?
People called the whole land Flevance.
--Flevance?
--Yeah.
The citizens were all rich
and the towns were all white,
from the soil to the plants,
like a snow country in a fairy tale.
I heard the country was out of this world.
One day, they discovered White Lead,
a type of lead, underground
and found out that was the source of
the fantastic scenery.
They made utensils, paint,
sweeteners, cosmetics,
and even weapons out of White Lead.
People all over the world wanted to buy
their high-quality White Lead goods
and it became Flevance's major industry.
The quick-eyed World Government went into
the transport business
to ship that merchandise.
White Lead made people a fortune.
FLEVANCE - THE WHITE TOWN
Law, for this kind of surgery,
you use this blood vessel.
Oh yeah!
You're a genius, Father-sama!
Brother-sama!
Let's go to the festival!
No! I'm studying now.
What?! No! No! Come on!
Later.
Law, studying is good but if you push
yourself too much,
it's not good for you.
Sometimes you need to
go out and have fun.
Well, Mother-sama,
you're always working, too.
I have an idea! Mother-sama,
let's go to the festival together!
No, I...
Yeah. Why don't you three go?
What?
All right. But just for 30 minutes.
We have so many patients to take care of.
Yeah!
Law! Let's go! To the festival!
Uh-huh!
The White Town was
the land everyone longed for.
Oh, I wanna go there!
Lon"g"ed for! There's the "G"!
But it's gone now.
What?
About a century ago, when the White
Lead industry was established,
the World Government performed
geological survey in the country
and the fact is they had
already known the truth.
The truth?
--It was poison.
--What?
Poison that was not so harmful
unless you dig it up.
But if you handle it somehow,
it'll erode your body.
Erode?
The poison will harm your body
just by touching it.
What?!
Knowing this but blinded by
the easy fortune to be had,
the Government and the royalty
of that country kept it secret.
The citizens kept digging up White Lead
knowing nothing.
If they did so, they would die.
Yeah.
But the terrible part was
it only contained traces of poison.
Say, the Lead keeps building up
in a young person's body,
when he has a child,
the child will, actually,
have a shorter life expectancy.
And when the kid grows up
and has his own child
that child's life expectancy is
even shorter.
THE NEGATIVE EFFECT
ON FUTURE GENERATIONS
Life expectancy got shorter
generation by generation
and eventually, a generation doomed to die
before adulthood, just like Law, was born.
When the world finally realized
White Lead is poisonous...
It was too late.
This way! This way! Hurry up!
Brother-sama! Come on!
Lammy, you don't have to rush like that.
What if the festival ends!
It won't end yet.
Lammy?
What? Lammy!
What's wrong? Are you alright?!
That's...!
At some point, people started
to collapse one after another.
Grandparents, parents,
and then children.
Because of the differences in
their life expectancies,
all generations fell ill around the same time.
Their skin and hair got whiter rapidly
and people died one after another
with their entire bodies in pain.
No doctor could stop that.
Then, all the people in his country died?!
I feel sorry...
--The real tragedy began after that.
--What?
Seeing the people in the White Town
all dying with the same symptoms,
the people in the neighboring countries
thought White Lead Disease was contagious.
So they blocked off the country completely
and took quarantine measures
against the White Town.
The royalty got help
from the Government and escaped
the country at an early stage.
The citizens were abandoned.
People from the White Town who
were looking to get treated and...
...immigrate to other countries,
were feared as if they were
monsters escaping from the cage and...
...they were shot dead.
They really "swept it under the rug."
Dammit!
The pain of the disease was
just somebody else's problem.
Very human like...
But Flevance couldn't keep quiet.
Ironically, they had tons of lead bullets.
Eventually, a war broke out!
Other countries justified their actions
as self defense so they showed no mercy!
I'm sure you can imagine the rest.
Law-kun!
Come on, you gotta come with us!
There are gentle soldiers who told us
they will let only the children escape!
--Law!
--We'll be safe!
Sister! My young sister is dying!
I can't go now!
Lammy-chan is?! I see...
Then, let's ask them to get you
on board the next ship to escape!
I'll come back to pick you up!
Law! Aren't you coming?!
Let's escape together!
I'm sure they'll save Lammy later, too!
Both my father and mother are dead!
But they told me to live!
So I'm gonna live no matter what!!
Law! Law!
Listen, Law-kun.
There is always hope.
A merciful helping hand will...
...reach to you like this.
Doctor, help!
Doctor!!
It's impossible! I can't go there!
We don't have enough doctors!
Same for blood and everything!
There must be a way to clear
away White Lead from bodies!
And it's not contagious!
Why doesn't the Government report that?!
Clank.
Brother-sama, my body hurts.
My skin's getting whiter and whiter.
Hang on for a little more.
Our father is the greatest
doctor in the country.
He'll heal you!
Why is it so noisy outside?
There's a festival.
Flevance is always prosperous.
Get well soon and
let's go to a festival together again!
Uh-huh!
Look for White Lead Disease
patients and kill them!
Lammy, stay in here for a few minutes.
Uh-huh...
Got rid of two infected people!
Law!
Law! Let's go! To the festival!
Mother-sama!!
Father-sama!!
There's still somebody!
Don't let him get away! Kill him!
Listen, Law-kun.
There is always hope.
A merciful helping hand will...
...reach to you like this.
Sister!!
Everybody!!
Let's escape together!
So I'm gonna live no matter what!!
The hospital...!
Lammy!!
Flevance, the White Town, perished.
By people's hands, at last.
If a ten-year-old kid went
through such a thing...
Of course, it screws up his personality.
There he is! Corazon!
My parents, young sister,
and everybody from the church were dead
and that idiot is alive - it's not fair!
They won't know if I keep quiet.
Nobody cares...
...if a scumbag goes missing!
Damn! He saw!
He... b-broke the... Blood Law!
He deserves impalement-dasuyan!
I must inform...
...the Young Master-dasuyan!
Doflamingo was born as one of the
Celestial Dragons who rule
everything in the world!
Why did he lose his noble status?!
When Doflamingo's unimaginable
past is revealed,
Law's life as a child changes in a big way!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Celestial Dragon! Doffy's Stormy Past!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!