Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of
the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
Law's secret motive behind this fight was...
Law, Doflamingo, and his brother Corazon.
Their relationship began 16 years ago...
Trafalgar D. Water Law.
"D." is a secret name, "Water" is a true name.
For generations, my family...
H-Hey, let go of me!
What the... Corazon!
What do you want?!
What you said before, was it true?
The secret name "D"...
If it's true, you need to get out of here.
Get away from Doffy!
Law! You shouldn't be around him!
"A Rocky Road!
Law and Corazon's Journey of Life!"
Why?! Since when can you talk?!
Since always.
So you've been... fooling Doflamingo
all this time?!
I've never told him that I became a mute.
He just thinks so.
That's... the same as fooling him!
What are you thinking...
Whoa-whoa-whoa.
Silence!
What?!
Huh? What the...
The sound of the streets is...
The sound of the streets is gone!
Why?!
Looks like people are talking
but I can't hear anything!
You're loud so I put up a wall.
A sound-proof wall.
You can't hear the sound from out there, huh?
They can't hear us, either.
The wall is invisible.
I ate the Calm-Calm Fruit
and became a soundless human.
A Devil Fruit eater?!
What... What's wrong with you?!
You've lied about everything!
Don't tell me that...
making a blunder like an idiot is also...
Yeah, of course.
It's all acting.
Don't lie! Your shoulder's on fire!
I've done those dumb things since I was a kid.
I can't change it. I'm dumb.
Shut up! The most ridiculous part of you
is the only thing that's not a lie?!
Why do you hide things from
your friends?!
I don't consider them my friends.
What I'm trying to do is stop my big brother Doffy
from going out of control.
I don't know how that beast was born
from our warm-hearted father and mother.
He has no... humanity.
Help!
My children are innocent!
Aim all your arrows at me!
Please! Don't harm my children!
It hurts, Father!
I can't take it anymore!
I'll get even...
I'll get even with you idiots!
Brother...
I'm not gonna die!
I'm gonna survive no matter what you do to me
and I will...
I will come kill
every single one of you jerks!!
He was born to be evil-natured
and he's never afraid of anything.
The only people who know
about his true brutality are
the four Executives including me
and the first Corazon - Vergo.
Vergo?
He's a strong man who's currently
separated from the Family
on a secret mission.
The details of the mission have been kept secret
even from the Family members.
You have no business with him.
Anyway...
Don't become a beast like my brother!
You gotta get out of here, Law!
No way! I want to be like that!
The secret name "D."!
It's no mistake.
You're a part of that fated family -
the Family of D.
Back in my home,
children are disciplined like this.
"A badly behaving child will be
eaten up by D."
There have often been people
who have the name "D."
who gained public notoriety
and old people would frown and mutter,
"'D.' will surely bring us another storm."
What are you saying?!
Am I some kind of monster?
Maybe.
Nobody knows the truth but that name has been
ceaselessly and secretly inherited
throughout history all across the world.
And in some places, there are people
who call the Family of D...
"Sworn enemy of the gods"!
God?!
Say the "god" means the Celestial Dragons,
the purpose of your people might be
"destruction of this world."
But it's completely different in meaning
from what Doffy is going for!
D.'s must have an idea
that's opposed to the god's.
I don't know what you're talking about!
I joined the Family to kill every single person
as violently as possible!
I'm not your subordinate!
I am Doflamingo's subordinate!
I'm gonna die in a year!
What should I do if I get out of here?!
--Get out of here and look for a cure!
--There is none!
I'm gonna tell Doflamingo that you can talk
and about your ability and all!
Don't do it!
You can't get away with it
just by getting kicked out!
Damn brat!
I became stronger in the last two years!
That serves you right!
Hey, Law!
You broke the Blood Law again!
Hey, what are you two doing
by moving your mouths?!
I'll buy you an ice cream so keep quiet.
I want the king size that costs
500 berries-dasuyan!
Baby 5, lend me some money.
What?! O-Okay!
Blush! He needs me!
Is this it?!
Dammit!
I trusted that little brat and
told him everything!
I think Doffy's not back yet today.
Let's just pack up my stuff
and take off before he comes back.
Corazon!
What?!
No! Why is he back already?!
You're back. We gotta set sail!
It's Tsuru from the Navy HQ again!
They know we're here!
Hurry up!
Hasn't he... told him yet?
I decided not to tell him.
I thought twice and remembered
I owe you for keeping quiet about
me stabbing you two years ago.
We're even now.
Corazon! Hurry up!
Corazon!
TSURU
Where are Corazon and Law?
I saw them on board.
Aren't they here?!
What's going on?
Young Master!
I found this on Corazon's hammock.
I'M LEAVING TO GO CURE LAW'S DISEASE
They packed their things and left, it seem.
What is he thinking?!
This is kidnapping!
Untie me! Hey!
Corazon! You jerk!
I'll make you pay for this!
Say something! Hey!
--Ring, ring, ring...
--Hey, pick up the Transponder Snail!
Isn't it Doflamingo?!
I'll talk! Pick it up!
--Ring, ring, ring...
--I said pick it up! Pick it up!
--Doflamingo! Help!
What are you gonna do to me?!
Hey!
Po-pi-pu-pa-po-pi-pi.
--Ring, ring, ring...
--Are you calling Doflamingo?!
--Hey! Help me!
--Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
"Rice crackers"!
"Rice-cracker pellets"! It's me.
Oh, it's Rosinante, isn't it?
I'm taking a break from
my mission for a while.
NAVY
--Are you in trouble?
--No, it's personal.
Okay, got it.
How are the kids?
Are they still there even though
you're giving them a hard time?
I don't think those three will leave…
The Family's became quite ill-famed now.
Be careful.
Okay.
ADMIRAL SENGOKU
THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
I entrust this case to you
so do whatever you like.
Keep me updated.
Roger that.
I'll send you the details in writing.
Clank.
COMMANDER DONQUIXOTE ROSINANTE
Admiral Sengoku!
BUDDHA
The man who wishes to transfer
who I told you about the other day, is here.
Oh, all right. Come in.
So it's you.
I've been hearing about you.
This is your first year after
you officially enlisted
and you've been quite successful...
Wishing to transfer to G-5, huh?
First of all, I want to ask you about
the sunny-side up egg on your left cheek...
Yes, sir! My name is Vergo, sir!
Where were you calling just now?!
You said "mission"!
Are you a Navy soldier or something?!
You don't like the Navy soldiers?
People tying to the Government
make me sick!
--I'm not a Navy soldier.
--Really?!
Hey! Let go of me! Corazon!
Hey! I don't wanna go to hospital!
Stop acting so predictably like a normal kid!
I'm gonna cure your disease!
I'm gonna take you to every single hospital!
Look! It's a big hospital!
They'll cure you!
Wh... White Lead Disease?!
It's been around for a while now.
Don't you have a good medicine for it, Doc?
E-E-Excuse me but where are you from...?
Flevance.
--The White Town!!
--Yikes! No! I'm gonna get infected!
H-Hey! Bring me antiseptic and gloves
and a gas mask now!
And call security and the Government!
Hurry up!
--No! Nooo!!
--Forget it!
--Law!
--See?! I'm not even a human anymore!
White monster!
Please leave! I beg you!
Hey, you!
How dare you bring such a kid here?!
How many patients do you think we have...
This is an emergency announcement.
We have a child with White Lead Disease
in the hospital.
The big guy is violent!
We'll sterilize the entire building now.
It was the worst hospital ever!
I'm sorry.
Did it bring back your old memories?
This is why I told you!
I don't wanna go to hospital!
That one was terrible...
But I'm sure there'll be a good doctor
in the next one!
I don't wanna go!
White Lead Disease! No! Somebody, help!
The survivor of the White Town!
Let's go to the next!
You'll get cured in the next one!
Enough! I don't wanna go!
Hello?! World Government?!
We have a survivor from Flevance here!
Why didn't you kill all of them?!
You assholes!
Look, Law!
People in this town look kind!
No!!
Ugh! I'm gonna get infected! Go away!
How dare you call yourself a doctor?!
Screw you!
--Eight hospitals were damaged.
Which way did those two go?!
The boy with the disease is...
Corazon, not only have I not gotten cured
but I'm at my limit…
Stop whining!
You'll get cured in the next one!
It's either find the cure or death!
Your life is on the edge now!
Stay strong!
--White Lead Disease!
--Close the hospital! They're gonna come in!
I'm gonna killed y'all!
No, Corazon!
Corazon!!
SIX MONTHS LATER
What am I doing...?
I've been repeatedly making the kid from
the tragic town relive the tragedy...
And he hasn't gotten any better...
Am I doing it for "D."?
No... I don't care about that anymore.
I have...
I have been feeling sorry for him...
Law!
I'm sure you don't want...
...this idiot who just keeps hurting you...
...to say something like this but...
You're still a rude little boy...
...and hearing you say "I'll die soon" is...
...heartbreaking...
You... stabbed me... that day but...
...it didn't hurt at all!
I know you were the one who was in pain!
You poor thing!
Law!
Cora-san...
Hey, Cora-san!
Breakfast is ready.
What is that face?!
You just called me Cora-san...
Shut up and eat breakfast!
Cora-san!
Cora-san! The tears you shed for me!
I won't ever forget them!
Stop! Don't do this!
Bellamy!
So this is it!
It's over, Straw Hat!
Go to hell!
There is only a little time left for Law!
Corazon plans to steal the Op-Op
Fruit making enemy out of everyone,
in order to save Law and
live together with him.
At the fateful Minion Island,
Corazon's life-risking fight is now on!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Time is Ticking Down!
Seize the Op-Op Fruit!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!