Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
Law, Doflamingo, and his brother Corazon.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
But caught up in the current king
Doflamingo's agenda, they were trapped
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along with the entire island.
along with the entire island.
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
Their relationship began years ago...
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Look! It's the Op-Op Fruit!
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
--Now, eat it! Here! Eat it quickly!
--What are you doing...?!
Here I go! Straw Hat!
Gross!
Spring...
Law, Doflamingo, and his brother Corazon.
What do you think of Monkey D. Luffy?!
Doffy's double!
There! Chew it like this!
Chew it up and swallow it down!
...Hopper!
Doffy's double has broken apart!
I didn't know that you were...
Their relationship began 16 years ago...
You got stronger but I got stronger, too!
...a Celestial Dragon until today!
Having a very short time to live,
Law jumped into the Donquixote Family
Shambles!
It must be Corazon!
This technique is far more destructive than
it used to be!
If he's there, don't let him go anywhere!
He has the Op-Op Fruit!
I guess the cage was a bit too small...
and with Corazon's help, he managed
to eat the Op-Op Fruit, however...
What do you think of "D."?!
...to keep it shut in.
Not yet...
"The Battle of Love!
The New Leader Sai vs. Baby 5!"
We have nowhere to run.
I'm gonna stay alive for a little bit more...
Maybe I can let Law get away, just him...
Because if I die now...
"A Decisive Battle Against the Executives!
Proud Hajrudin!"
the spell I cast on you
will be broken instantly...
It's none of...
Bellamy! Stop!
I have no chance to survive now but...
...your concern!
and your voice and noise you make...
will you remember me even after I die?
So are you saying Straw Hat Luffy was
led by destiny
...will be heard throughout the island.
I'll die with a smile so...
Hey, you!
You're gonna die if you move around that much!
Mingo!!
and come to kill me,
who has godly blood in my veins?!
Go, Law...
Shut up! Stop worrying about your enemy!
Quietly... without being noticed...
Because... if you think of me someday,
How idiotic!
Go farther... and farther...
In some places, there are people
who call the Family of "D."...
Bellamy...
There is nothing to bind you down anymore...
"Sworn enemy of the gods"!
I'd rather you remember my smile.
Whether it's the iron border
barrier of the White Town
I'm a "D." too!
Charlestone!
or a short life expectancy...
You're a "D."?!
Is it your secret name?!
Law, we gotta get going.
Nothing and no one will limit you.
You're destined to be here!
Is that what you're saying?!
Bellamy!
Pica-sama!
You think you can stop me
because you're a "D."?!
You are...
Why is he attacking randomly?!
...free now...
The Family of "D." is
the sworn enemy of the gods?!
Let's go!
That jerk!
He doesn't care if they're his allies or foes!
That's just a superstition!
"Advance, Law!
The Kindhearted Man's Final Fight!"
Bellamy!
TSURU
Bring it on, you piece of stone!
Injection...
--All right, come on!
--Okay!
...Shot!
I'm...
No! Don't do it!
I'm being needed!
You!
I don't know what's going on!
Cora-san was fully aware of it.
You don't have to yell like that.
I can hear you.
Say it more clearly!
I'm not gonna let you go!
Suddenly, the town is surrounded by
some kind of a giant cage!
Those are my orders! Until this is settled...
If I can defeat you just with my name,
it would've been so easy.
Hey, Mingo! Stop Bellamy! He's gonna die!
We can't get in!
I'll never let you go!
And as hard as it is to believe,
in the cage,
I'm here...
What?!
it seems the pirates had a falling out
and they're killing each other!
Is he still alive?
"I'll never let you go"?!
I love you!
He just proposed to me!
Drie!
How could you possibly
interpret it that way?!
"To Be Free!
Law's Injection Shot Blasts!"
...because the kindhearted Cora-san
couldn't pull the trigger that day!
Bellamy.
Where are you going? Help me!
Can't you do something about the cage?!
I'm only here to pull it on his behalf!
Straw Hat, I guess you won't change your mind
and finish off Bellamy.
Hey! Don't go!
"An Intense Battle!
Law vs. Doflamingo!"
It's an enemy raid!
All right.
Land. Ouch!
Oh, Bellamy!
D-Doflamingo!
Oh, he hurt his back?!
It's the Donquixote Family!
Ow, ow, ow...
Drie!
That's enough, Bellamy. I set you free.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Damn! Where did that brat go?!
Ow, ow, ow, ow... Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Doffy!
He isn't there when I need him the most!
Like you have always been.
He's stronger than anybody but has no guts!
--There you go! Lao G-sama's...
--...Back-Pain Stance!
What's the matter? Is that it?
That fool...
Was this crap...
You were just playing
into my hands after all!
...what you were referring
to as the "trigger"?
Take this!
Geo-Fist!
Eye-Jab Strain!
EYE-JAB STRAIN
Doflamingo!
It was you guys who stole
the Op-Op Fruit, wasn't it?!
You can't get away from me!
I came to see you...
If it were so,
I wouldn't have to go through all this!
...on my own will!
You guys are the Donquixote Family,
aren't you?
Icy Stiff Shoulder!
ICY STIFF SHOULDER
How dare you let it be stolen,
you drunken idiot!
"Will"?
I bet you're Doflamingo.
I told you!
Poor Circulation Impact!
POOR CIRCULATION IMPACT
I'm here to settle things
up from 13 years ago!
Who are you guys?
This is a treasure house-in!
Let us under your umbrella!
Chrysanthemum Chestnut Strained Back!
CHRYSANTHEMUM CHESTNUT STRAINED BACK
To attain that man's long-cherished ambition!
Hey, carry all the treasures out carefully!
This is great-in!
Immortal Warrior's Joint Pain!
IMMORTAL WARRIOR'S JOINT PAIN
That's what I meant when I said
you were just playing into my hands, Law!
Not bad, not bad!
They've got quite a lot!
Don't push your luck!
The crap that you call "your own will"
or your freedom...
I'm begging you! Doflamingo!
Stop fooling around, you guys!
Look for Corazon!
They're all mine!
Don't talk to Doffy so casually,
you little hoodlum!
Shut up!
I don't like it...
I've been admiring you since I was a kid!
Only Lao G-sama could've done it!
Room!
Cora-san...
He's overpowering Don Chin Jao
who has a 500 million bounty!
There is nothing he can gain from you
since you're like a child of destruction!
We want to follow you!
Buffalo!
How's your search from up there?!
Give us a chance! Doflamingo!
As you get older, you understand pain
and it becomes sharper!
Leave him alone now!
GEO-FIST
Geo-Fist!
He is free!!
Go away, you hoodlums!
It's all burnt - I don't think
there are any survivors-dasuyan!
THERE'S THE...
There's the...
..."G"!
Bzz...
When I truly become free will be...
Oh... Um... Lao G-sama...
I picked up a message!
We took a boy into protective
custody at the coast.
...when I fulfill your dream!
We'll keep searching to see
if there are other victims!
Not this way, h-he's behind you.
Room!
Where are you from?
We're all from Nortis.
It's when I stop Doflamingo!
They said the Navy took someone
into protective custody!
G!
It's a wealthy town.
What's your problem with it?
What are you doing?!
Get your lazy ass in gear and find Corazon!
That shitty town is boring!
Counter Shock!
The Donquixote Family is
the pride of the North Blue!
--Oh, Okay!
--Okay-dasuyan!
I'm on the other side of the fence!
Corazon, that fool...
That marriage!
We wanna become
a pirate band like you guys!
You're talking to them?!
Where is he hiding?
Were you listening, old man?!
I won't marry her!
Or has he already dropped dead?!
It was close, Law!
We're a little different from
those idealistic pirates around there!
What?!
Why are you that surprised?!
Why should I?!
Hey, hey!
How close do you think was it, Law?
Sai! You're arranged to marry Ooklicia,
the daughter of the Nihosui Army's leader!
I'll let you use our Jolly Roger
if that's what you want.
Here I go, Fake-mingo!
Doffy!
Hey! Are you trying to ignore me?
Hey, hey!
However, if you get defeated by someone,
you're no longer allowed.
Gum-Gum...
Doffy. This is our boss.
Sai!
Law! Law? Hey, hey!
You sure?! Yeah!
I know! I don't care who'll become my wife!
Pentachromatic Strings!
Everyone got knocked out?!
Hey, ignoring me?
Are you ignoring me, Law? Law!
Bullet String!
Arrange a political marriage
That must be "Haki"!
I don't need weaklings as my subordinates.
Damn!
to merge Nihosui and Happosui
together, or whatever you like!
Gum-Gum Jet...
We won't get defeated! By anyone!
Brother, don't!
Law, yo, what happened to
the momentum from earlier?
Brother!!
Oh no! Lao G-sama is getting ignored!
He'll get pissed!
Hey, hey! What's the matter, Law?
Why did you also take away the power I had?!
Stop it, please!
Hey, Bellamy!
Release Bellamy already!
Are you all right?! I don't think you are.
Come on, try harder, Law!
Do you want me to give you...
the strength to take revenge?
You bastard!
What?!
He didn't hear a thing!
Armament Hardening!
I'm really disappointed in you...
But wait! He is mad!
We can't undo what you've done now!
Look! He's letting off a steam of anger
from the top of his head!
What do you think of Monkey D. Luffy?!
I'm going back to the Holyland
by taking your head!
So, you're the 30 million bounty,
Straw Hat Luffy!
No! He's dying!
I didn't know that you were...
Takt!
...a Celestial Dragon until today!
--Of all days, he's dying a natural death today?!
--This shouldn't be how a battle ends!
Doffy! The Rampart Tower is...
Shambles!
Hey! Flying towards us!
What?! This can't be happening!
Lao G, don't die!
Doflamingo. Rosinante.
What do you think of "D."?!
Lao G-sama!
You're such a delusional dumbass!
I'm sorry that you had to have...
Come back!!
Spiderweb!
Back... back... back...
Listen.
The era where pirates dream about things is over!
...a father like me.
Huh?!
The big hidden treasure, One Piece...!
Those idiots who are blinded by dream treasure don't
notice the treasure around them.
What?!
He couldn't hear it clearly but he came back!
It's none of...
I'm glad!
...your concern!
They're misled by those illusions and die.
So are you saying Straw Hat Luffy was
led by destiny
The infamous Don Chin Jao got weaker, huh?!
That's just drivel by losers!
You have no right to say that!
and come to kill me,
who has godly blood in my veins?!
Shambles!
Oh no! Don Chin Jao is getting mad!
Scalpel!
What are you doing, Sai?!
Struggle all you want;
there's no escape from my Boing-Boing Fruit power!
How idiotic!
--They're not talking about the same thing!
--What?!
He's not hearing anything!
In some places, there are people
who call the Family of "D."...
What am I doing?!
It's crooked.
Spring...
Hey! Don't fix my collar!
Are you my wife?!
"Sworn enemy of the gods"!
Cut the pointless attacks!
...Hopper!
I'm a "D." too!
Stay away from me, Donquixote Family!
You became quite a gutsy,
passionate little shit!
You!
What's wrong?!
Wh-What's the matter with you?!
You creepy tramp! You're my enemy!
Doffy!
A city of gold?!
I think they found Corazon!
Why did you bring up
"marriage" all of a sudden?!
A sky island?!
How is the war situation, Viola?
Why not?! You need me, don't you?!
Law. This is a blind spot for the pirates.
The era of dreams is over,
you pathetic excuses for pirates!
In the decisive battle
at the top floor of the Palace,
What do you want me to do?! I'll do anything!
Straw Hat has been thrown
down to the lower level
They'll never find you. Stay still!
How idiotic! Then, do me a favor.
and Law cannot measure up against Doflamingo.
Bellamy!
Corazon went that way!
I'm sorry! You okay?!
Kill yourself!
Do I know how to throw a punch, you ask?
Lao G! This way!
The battles in this country
can be divided into three major parts.
Bellamy!
So long, Straw Hat!
If we leave you guys at large
and you interfere with Straw Hat and the others,
--Come on! Follow me!
--I'll crush you-in!
The plateau - location of the Royal Palace.
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
it'll ruin our repayment to them!
The statue of Pica.
THE STATUE OF PICA
Oh? I can't open it!
We got to take care of
you Executives at least!
Damn!
Something is on it!
The SMILE factory.
THE SMILE FACTORY
You rat! How much longer are you gonna
do this to him?!
Put out the fire!
Cora-san!
Prepare for it!
Don't do it!
Where are you aiming at?!
How much longer?
Restrain those who are rampaging!
Until this guy falls apart!
Is that it?
As long as the battle continues,
the number of victims keep rising.
Corazon!
Straw Hat.
V-Viola.
Vipera Glaive!
I visited the Sky Island.
I-It's all right! Kill me, Straw Hat!
Okay! I'm happy to kill myself!
I lost my crew but it turned my
view of the world upside down.
How many executives of the Donquixote Family
are left?
I can't do that!
The one I wanna beat up is him!
If it helps you!
What? N-No...
I'm not holding a grudge against you anymore.
There are still many of them.
I mean, the real Mingo!
I love helping people more than anything!
I'm done picking on you.
Please! I-I'm begging you!
One of the major battle areas -
the SMILE factory, the executive
who's protecting there is...
Idiot! Don't! What are you doing?!
It was just a tit-for-tat!
I said I can't!
Corazon!
Bellamy.
THE SMILE FACTORY
Kill me! Straw Hat!
...the free-swimming human, Señor Pink!
Why did you cheer me on?
It'll leave a bad taste in my mouth
if I gain victory through your self-destruction!
Sticky Launcher!
Please kill me... Straw Hat!
Leave her alone, Sai!
Why do you wanna stop your enemy from killing herself?!
That was so embarrassing!
I haven't changed a bit.
In the second zone, the statue of Pica,
there is the top executive...
I'm begging you! Do it, Straw Hat!
Are you out of your mind?!
THE STATUE OF PICA
You've changed, Bellamy.
Please! Please!
You're a leader of an army!
You got to be more ruthless!
The stone assimilation human, Pica!
Bellamy, don't talk.
Shut up, old man!
Don't tell me what to do like you're still my master!
I got you!
No, you have changed.
And the third part is
at the plateau - location of the Royal Palace.
You now use Haki that's far
greater than anyone can imagine.
Hey, you tramp!
Diamante!
On its top floor, there are...
That pisses me off!
You're useless, Bellamy.
Oh yeah!
...the current king of Dressrosa
Oh, I'm so happy...
You're losing your edge...
and the string human, Doflamingo!
I can help someone even
just by killing myself.
Hey, don't push yourself!
Stop, Fake-mingo!
You better stay down.
Hey, why don't you do as he wishes?
Why did you give birth to a child?
Joker wants me to kill Straw Hat?
And the chief of staff,
the mucus human, Trebol!
They're useless but they still eat a lot.
Doffy's too indulgent.
Ouch...
To reduce the number of mouths we have to feed,
go abandon her on a mountain.
In the Sunflower Field on the fourth level,
THE ROYAL PALACE - THE FOURTH LEVEL
He's giving the man who couldn't win the match
one more chance.
there's the hero of the Colosseum
and the flag human,
Aren't you happy, Bellamy?
Mom, where are we going?
Doflamingo!!
Diamante!
Hey! Mom!
Well, I thought you were gonna mess it up.
The rupture human who leads his underlings
on the third level is...
Mom?
THE THIRD LEVEL
The assassination of Straw Hat.
Mom!
What?!
Dammit!
Gladius!
Mom, wait! Please!
You jerk!
But it doesn't matter
if you can get it done or not.
Why have you been pretending
that you can't talk?!
Where did he go?!
There are four executives
on the second level.
THE SECOND LEVEL
Because I got nothing to talk about...
with you fools.
What do you mean?
Don't follow me.
He doesn't want you to follow him about
so he told me to finish you off here.
The half Fighting Fish Fish-Man, Dellinger!
No! Please! I'm gonna come with you!
Screw you!
The Geo-Fist user,
How dare you make a fool of the Young Master!
That's Young Master-sama's order.
You're useless.
Lao G!
It's unforgivable! I won't forgive you!
Useless people like you...
The super weight human,
I thought I was gonna die!
Oh? A big quake again!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
THE SECOND LEVEL
...aren't needed by anyone!
Machvise!
That's too much, Gladius!
He'll die before the Young Master gets here.
What did you come here for?
Even by you, mom?
The full-body weapon human,
Did the Pirate Hunter get killed?!
I'm not needed even by you, mom?
Baby 5!
Isn't there any...
It's no problem!
...hope left for me?
He was trying to force an all-out war
between us and the Navy today!
There are still 10
who are ranked higher than executives but...
He's alive!
Pica-sama!
Don't make me say it straight, Bellamy.
What a sinful bastard!
This "stone" doesn't know when to give up!
What? You want me to
subscribe 50 newspapers?!
Your purpose was different from mine.
From long ago.
You think you can take me down
just because you know my ability?
I'm needed by them!
What?! Do you want me to marry you?!
You always wanted to become a pirate.
What a simpleton!
Cora-san!
I'm needed by him!
Hey! The Young Master's here!
But not me.
Useless people like you
aren't needed by anyone!
Wait!
Take him down!
Anything was fine with me.
Don't move, Pirate Hunter!
We won't let you through here!
Anything?
What a nice breeze.
I'm needed by someone now...
As long as I could...
What a pain in the ass!
...destroy this world!
I said "Don't," you stupid tramp!
You are the stupid one!
Old man?!
Don't tell me you...
Commodore Dignity!
So powerful!
I can't do that!
That's...
You're my friend!
Atten-hut!
Sai!
You're bringing shame on the Happosui Army!
Count off!
It's been six months.
Bellamy. I set you free.
Like you have always been.
--One!
--Two!
--Three!
--Four!
--Five!
--Six!
Corazon.
--Seven!
--Eight!
The breeze is hurting my eyes.
We don't need a guy like you
in the Happosui Army!
--Nine!
--Ten!
Don't do it!
Oh! So hard-boiled!
No! No! Don't!
Hey, Bellamy!
I'm sorry but wait here.
I'm worried about Tra-guy!
Sai! Are you listening to me?!
Oh? Why are we lining up?
Mingo and Snot are up there.
Killer Bowling!
This is my problem! Stay out of it!
I gotta get there or Tra-guy's in trouble!
In most of the battles,
I'll kick Mingo's ass for you, too!
You fool!
everyone's heavily injured already!
Wait!
Hasshoken Technique!
Do you remember this technique?
The end of the battle is...
You're something!
--You can go ahead.
--Yeah, you're from the Colosseum, right?
Don't tell me he's gonna do the head-butt
that can break an ice continent?!
...not too far away!
That's right! My name is Orlumbus!
If this were the sea,
I'm gonna hammer both of you
with my drill head!
I would've backed you up
with my Yontamaria Fleet.
Drill Dragon...
...Nail!
I'm sorry to be short-handed!
I'll leave the stone monster to you!
Old man!!
Okay!
Where did that shithead go?!
THE ROYAL PALACE - THE FIRST FLOOR
Wujiaogen Heel!
Young Master!
Here I go! Straw Hat!
You can't get away now.
Spring...
Pentachromatic Strings!
...Hopper!
The face on the wall!
Pica-sama took over the plateau!
You have no place to go?
Then, do you wanna come with me?
--Now, can you get away from my attacks?
--Was that how you laugh?!
What?!
Hey!
Just attack already!
So what if that's how I laugh?
I'm surprised because it sounded so stupid!
You got stronger but I got stronger, too!
Marine Code 01746.
--You are stupid, Pirate Hunter!
--Don't piss Pica-sama off!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE
ROYAL PALACE THE FOURTH LEVEL
This technique is far more destructive than
it used to be!
Useless people like you
aren't needed by anyone!
Commander Rosinante of
the Navy Headquarters.
Pica-sama, don't!
I'm needed by someone now...
Charlestone!
Donquixote Family, captain, Doflamingo.
I have been undercover
to prevent a future tragedy of your doing.
Don't try to do such a silly thing!
I am a Navy soldier!
Father-sama!
It's good that you're giant!
It'll feel good to slice you in half!
How annoying...
I'm sorry that I lied you...
I lied because I didn't want you to hate me.
Hey, Pica!
Don't forget we're fighting here, too!
Why are you bringing it up now?!
Why...
Destruction Cannon!
Why did you stop me?
I already...
...knew it!
I just tried to help you!
Army Bandera!
You fool! Do you think it'll help you
to apologize now?!
You better pay attention!
By killing myself, I wanted to become a person
who is needed by someone!
Oh! You scare me.
Stop telling those insipid jokes and...
You have been living in a world
where nobody has ever told you...
...answer these two questions!
You're not looking at the big picture at all.
What's wrong with this guy?
Where's the Op-Op Fruit?! Where's Law?!
...that you're getting it all wrong?
You're forever getting hung
up on the meaningless things.
That's why you can't seize the moment.
The Devil Fruit...
What?! The ground is...!
The Op-Op Fruit... I let Law eat it!
I-I think you're serious, aren't you?
You haven't pulled the trigger yet.
He's a Devil Fruit eater now!
In fact, you haven't even put your finger
on the trigger yet.
How do you like it?!
The ground ripples like a flag!
You've been beating around the bush!
Don Chin Jao's drill head is bent
as I thought!
He managed to get out of the cage.
Seems hard to even just stand there!
Is it because we're each other's enemy?!
I bet he's been taken into protective custody
The weaker a person is,
the more he gets hung up
I can't believe it! Have I really done this?!
Why don't you say it straight?!
by a look-out ship from the Navy HQ by now.
on other people's pain and
then he self-destructs.
What are you talking about?!
You can't touch him now!
Sai! I'm surprised that
you bent my drill head!
If you really wanted to kill me,
you should've stuck to the plan
Don't pretend that you don't know!
Glance.
to provoke a conflict between Kaido and me.
Are they gonna fight among themselves?!
Young Master-sama!
We heard the Navy said on the radio earlier
they took a boy under their care!
Finally...
I'll shoot...
There are so many ways to get rid of an enemy
you're no match for.
...through your heart!
Clutch!
Finally, your power has awakened!
Why didn't you report that sooner?!
You said "I'll aim for your heart"...
Rebecca...
I let her go on her own but is she okay?
But by thinking of Corazon,
you got emotional,
--I rushed here even if I don't look like it-dasuyan!
--I'm sorry!
Your bloody, sweaty, and tear-filled training
has borne fruit at last!
It's a battlefield of monsters
above this point!
I won't let go of your hand!
and the moment you decided
to strike me yourself,
And "I'll keep holding your hand"!
Go ahead, Robin-senpai!
A boy?
Old man?
You did it!
Can you keep up with me?!
What?
What a strange coincidence!
I know how you feel!
Leave this place in my hands!
you fated yourself to die!
The Hasshoken Technique has succeeded!
And "Can you stick with me"!
Law is here!
Rooster-kun!
Sai! I'll give...
Now, go on!
...your kick attack the
name "Drill Dragon Nail."
Okay!
If you want me so much...
Check into that quickly!
I'll undo the Birdcage!
Do you remember the letter from that time?
Pierna Fleurs!
I don't care about the positions we're in!
What?!
This is an unbelievably great coincidence!
I'm sure your leg can even break the ice continent
into pieces now.
All the Navy soldiers will know what it is
once they see this cylinder.
As I thought, Law,
something compels you to stay alive.
You...
The Happosui Army is all yours now!
I'll cancel your arranged marriage!
This one small package will save...
...need me, don't you?!
Saviors keep descending upon you
one after another.
What an honor!
I'm protecting Robin-senpai!
...a far-off kingdom called Dressrosa.
A kingdom?
Prepare to set sail!
You can do whatever you want now!
Oh, it must be a secret letter.
I'm like the Straw Hats fighting
at Enies Lobby!
If what he said was true,
we'll sink the Navy's look-out ship
Ten-Ton Vise!
I bet somebody asked you to deliver it.
Thank you.
Old man!
and get Law back!
Well done! Well done! Sai!
Just kidding! How presumptuous I am!
I'm sorry!
I'll keep it. Don't worry.
Don't.
Why would you wanna go after Law?
Old man! You're embarrassing me!
Why would I wanna go after Law?
What a touching story!
Corazon was trying to
save this country, Dressrosa.
If he ate the Op-Op Fruit,
The truth is, after the
fight against Straw Hat,
he needs to be educated
in order to die for me!
I've been suffering from chronic pain
and I couldn't fight like I wanted.
If only you hadn't blown it that day...
I'm getting older.
I'm happy that you're now...
Boy! How you guys attack puts me to sleep!
Boy... You've done tons
of unnecessary things!
Vise-sama!
I'm sure you remember.
Get ready, Gladius!
Why do you wanna get in my way?!
Because you're sort of responsible
for Corazon's death.
Why do I have to kill another
member of my biological family?!
Here comes one more-in!
Seal of G!
THE THIRD LEVEL
THE SECOND LEVEL
100-Ton Vise!
With that letter,
Cora-san, are you sure you'll be alright?!
Old man!!
Lao G-sama!
maybe, the numerous tragedies
that fell upon this country
So tenacious-in!
wouldn't have happened.
I know you can't shoot me...
Destruction Cannon!
Go to hell! Ton-Ton!
You're so much like your father!
Missed me!
You think so?
Lao G-sama took down Don Chin Jao!
You told me you'll be alright,
didn't you?!
In addition, what happened to his body?!
Listen, Law.
You remained calm. That's smart.
Pirates can't resist taking treasure boxes
Geo-Fist's ultimate technique!
to their ships whenever they find them.
You're right!
Battle Insurance Fist!
BATTLE INSURANCE FIST
If you ask me,
whatever happened to that letter,
He shows no mercy!
Ten-Ton...
In preparation for illness
or injury or aging,
That means if you stay in here,
Even the warrior of Elbaph couldn't do a thing
against Vice-sama!
I would've changed my plans
and sat on the throne of this country anyway!
you'll definitely have a chance
to get out of the cage.
...Vise!
you reserve your muscle power
from your earlier years
Don't miss it.
What about you, Cora-san?!
This is good-in! A good foothold-in!
and save it. It's a qigong technique!
You silly...
So you'll have seasoned fighting skills
as well as power at a peak!
Doffy wants you and the Op-Op power.
I brought down Hajrudin the Giant-in
and my next target is...
Everything that Corazon did risking his life,
was all in vain after all.
Is there anyone who can beat me...
Doffy and I are brothers by blood.
Of course, he'd get pissed at me
but I'm sure he won't kill me.
...like this?!
I'll shoot...
It's all up to me now!
So that's Lao G-sama's true power!
That's Roronoa Zoro!
...through your heart!
Calm.
I was right!
Whatever I do before I die
is all attributable to Cora-san's legacy!
This will cause anything you interact with
to not make any noise.
He was just big and not quite strong!
You just...
You monkey from Kano,
what do you want from me?
...did it again!
You're in our way, you big shit!
Oh yeah?
What a tear-jerking sentiment!
Alright, see you in the next town.
How dare you do that to my old man...
I won't forgive you!
My dream was to become
the king of all Giants.
Hey, Law.
That's right!
Whatever the tragedy or the blunder is,
I love you!
What are you talking about?!
But look at me.
A weakling like you needs another
100 years of training to get
only the things that actually
happened are written in stone!
I lost in the competition.
strong enough to challenge me!
The fact that you ate the
Op-Op Fruit and ran...
Lao G!
To avenge my old man...
I got turned into a toy.
And to pay my debt to
Straw Hat and the others!
...or the fact that you are here now
after showing your teeth at Punk Hazard!
I had been saved
but I still haven't paid back my debt!
INSIDE THE ROYAL PALACE
This isn't what you told me, Cora-san!
You said he won't kill you!
What a foolish monkey!
Do you really believe that
Straw Hat can take down the Young Master?!
How pathetic!
Law won't obey you! Doffy...
We're on our way!
I do!
I was willing to die to pay my debt, then...
Princess Mansherry!
Affected by White Lead Disease,
...why am I still alive after I failed?!
Listen! Dressrosa belongs to the Young Master!
And everybody in this country is...
he was doomed to die in three years.
THE STATUE OF PICA
...slaves to the Young Master!
But he got over it.
Ton-Ton!
He did it!
Was my gratitude...
He's not the same Law...
String Saw! String Saw!
that shallow?!
Three-Sword Style!
...who lost track of himself and came
to visit a crazy pirate that day.
I... I...
No matter how firmly you believe in Straw Hat,
you guys can't...
108-Pound Phoenix!
I like how you scream, Law!
I can't help dripping snot!
There is nothing he can gain from you
since you're like a child of destruction!
...get out of this Birdcage for
the rest of your lives!
Here I go, Roronoa!
Birdca"g"e! There's the...
He's...
Second Gear!
Leave him alone now!
Destructive 1,000-Ton Vise!
..."G"!
He is free!!
That asshole... He always escapes!
No, it's...
You're quick, I'll grant you that.
Sorry, Bellamy!
It's far deeper than that!
IN FRONT OF THE PLATEAU -
LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
But, even Baby 5, I won't...
Gum-Gum...
--Run!
--The building is gonna collapse!
...let you have her!
...Red Hawk!
What?! Lao G!
Just wait, Baby 5!
He got up!
I'm "g"onna bleed this idiot dry
and save you! There's the...
Fire Fist!
I'm sorry but...
let me take care of that guy.
..."G"!
What am I supposed to do?
They're fighting over me...
Say it again!
Who did you call a monster?!
Hajrudin!
It's dangerous! Stay away!
Whoa! He tripped
and he's on fire at the same time!
Hey, hey-in!
I can't believe you're still alive!
Mingo!!
--See? You had a quiet sleep, didn't you?!
--Cut it out!
A monkey is a monkey after all!
Are you okay?
If you used Baby 5 as a shield,
you could've had the upper hand!
I'll kick his ass at any cost!
Yes! Thank you very much!
Then, I'll make it heavier-in!
Hey mister, thank you!
What?
Hellish 10,000-Ton Vise!
--Get to somewhere safe! Go!
--Okay!
I hope there are still bones left to be crushed!
Hey-in!
There's no such place...
Baby 5 is ours!
She'd even kill herself if she's needed by someone!
I don't know if you were influenced
by the other "D." or not,
but you coming to challenge
me yourself is something
Is there any other girl out there
who is as convenient as she is?!
that's written in stone, too!
A dead man can't be useful but...
That's why I forgive you!
...if at least one of his arms still moves,
a man can even rip off his enemy general's head.
Convenient?
Take this! I'll give it all my life!
Like I forgave my biological
father and brother...
The end of the battle is...
Gungir!!
I love you!
...not too far away!
I'll send you to hell with
this last secret technique!
I'll forgive you with your own death!
However, even if their battles
against the executives wrap up,
Gum-Gum...
Damn!
if they can't take down Doflamingo,
...Jet...
the fates of the people who are
in the Birdcage won't be changed!
...Gatling!
Not yet...
BATTLE INSURANCE FIST
Battle Insurance Fist!
Are you saying we must leave the fate
of this country to those pirates?!
I'm gonna stay alive for a little bit more...
Expiration Devil Withdrawal Immolation!
EXPIRATION DEVIL WITHDRAWAL IMMOLATION
This is "g"onna be the last! There's the...
Pull the ship over here!
..."G"!
It's no use-in. This is 10,000 ton!
Because if I die now...
Hey, how about this?
the spell I cast on you
will be broken instantly...
That tramp...
If I defeat you, I'll take her for my wife!
You're a "D."?!
Is it your secret name?!
and your voice and noise you make...
What?!
You're destined to be here!
Is that what you're saying?!
Twinge!
...will be heard throughout the island.
TWINGE
Executions should be done by
nothing other than lead bullets.
Go, Law...
I'm reassembled!
Get squashed, Hajrudin!
Quietly... without being noticed...
What's the matter?
Drill Dragon...
You think you can stop me
because you're a "D."?!
Fly away! To the kingdom of the gods!!
I thought you wanted to pull the trigger.
...Nail!
Go farther... and farther...
The Family of "D." is
the sworn enemy of the gods?!
There is nothing to bind you down anymore...
That's just a superstition!
Whether it's the iron border
barrier of the White Town
Whoa-whoa, Doffy, watch out!
or a short life expectancy...
What?!
Nothing and no one will limit you.
Vice-sama!
You're in the range of Law's power!
Young Master... I'm sorry!
Oh no! Above him!
Injection...
TSURU
It's Tsuru's warship! Dammit!
He's gonna hit the Birdcage!
...Shot!
Stop, Vice-sama!
Doffy's double!
He's gonna get slashed!
Mingo!
Cora-san was fully aware of it.
Show yourself!
Damn you, unfledged monkey!
Straw Hat-ya!
If I can defeat you just with my name,
it would've been so easy.
You are...
You "g"oofy monkey! There's the...
..."G"!
Doffy's double has broken apart!
...free now...
But that was just the catalyst.
I guess he can't fly out there...
I know you can't shoot me...
He's not even a bird.
Call me chieftain!
Fire!
You're so much like your father!
In the battle against the executives
on the second level of the plateau -
Vice-sama!
location of the Royal Palace;
I'm here...
LAO G - FELL
Lao G, fell.
I guess the cage was a bit too small...
I love you!
Baby 5,
BABY 5 - FELL
fell, too.
...because the kindhearted Cora-san
couldn't pull the trigger that day!
Take a good rest.
BABY 5 - FELL IN LOVE
...to keep it shut in.
When you wake up, the cage will be gone!
I'm only here to pull it on his behalf!
I'm not very competent but...
Didn't you hear me?!
please be patient with me!
Sai of the Happosui Army is baffled by
The savage attacks of Machvise,
one of the Family's executives,
With his passion for the
memory of the late Cora-san,
Backstabbed, manipulated,
and almost killed by
Sacrificing his own life,
Cora-san paved Law's path to the future.
Baby 5 who comes on strong
with her earnest feelings!
leave Hajrudin's whole body beaten
and pummeled into the ground!
Law keeps launching attacks
with his emotions laid bare.
his once hero, Doflamingo,
Bellamy still challenges Luffy.
While the both families fight fiercely to
defend their pride, her sad past is revealed
However, when Doflamingo on the receiving end of
those fierce attacks,
Law inherits his wish and
to become truly free,
However, when the Giant, covered with wounds,
When he makes a final resolution after wavering
between friendship and his principles,
gets on his feet again to pay his
debt to Luffy and the others,
puts a fearless smile on his face,
he fires a shot on behalf of Cora-san, who
couldn't take a shot on that fateful day,
and the passionate man, Sai blasts
a special secret technique which bests Don Chin Jao!
a horrendous counterattack pushes Law into
an abyss of despair!
a devastatingly destructive strike has
Luffy's name on it!
aiming straight at Doflamingo!
a deadly strike full of
Elbaph's spirit resounds!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To Be Free! Law's Injection Shot Blasts!"
"The Battle of Love! The New Leader Sai vs. Baby 5!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An Intense Battle! Law vs. Doflamingo!"
"The Man's Pride! Bellamy's Last Charge!"
"A Decisive Battle Against the
Executives! Proud Hajrudin!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!