Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
What do you think of Monkey D. Luffy?!
I didn't know that you were...
...a Celestial Dragon until today!
Shambles!
What do you think of "D."?!
It's none of...
...your concern!
So are you saying Straw Hat Luffy was
led by destiny
and come to kill me,
who has godly blood in my veins?!
How idiotic!
In some places, there are people
who call the Family of "D."...
"Sworn enemy of the gods"!
I'm a "D." too!
You're a "D."?!
Is it your secret name?!
You're destined to be here!
Is that what you're saying?!
You think you can stop me
because you're a "D."?!
The Family of "D." is
the sworn enemy of the gods?!
That's just a superstition!
Injection...
...Shot!
Cora-san was fully aware of it.
If I can defeat you just with my name,
it would've been so easy.
I'm here...
I love you!
...because the kindhearted Cora-san
couldn't pull the trigger that day!
I'm only here to pull it on his behalf!
"An Intense Battle!
Law vs. Doflamingo!"
Doffy!
Was this crap...
...what you were referring
to as the "trigger"?
I don't like it...
Room!
Counter Shock!
It was close, Law!
Hey, hey!
How close do you think was it, Law?
Hey! Are you trying to ignore me?
Hey, hey!
Law! Law? Hey, hey!
Hey, ignoring me?
Are you ignoring me, Law? Law!
Law, yo, what happened to
the momentum from earlier?
Hey, hey! What's the matter, Law?
Come on, try harder, Law!
I'm really disappointed in you...
Takt!
Doffy! The Rampart Tower is...
Hey! Flying towards us!
Spiderweb!
Shambles!
Scalpel!
Cut the pointless attacks!
You became quite a gutsy,
passionate little shit!
Bellamy!
I'm sorry! You okay?!
Damn!
You rat! How much longer are you gonna
do this to him?!
How much longer?
Until this guy falls apart!
I-It's all right! Kill me, Straw Hat!
I can't do that!
The one I wanna beat up is him!
I mean, the real Mingo!
Please! I-I'm begging you!
I said I can't!
Kill me! Straw Hat!
Please kill me... Straw Hat!
I'm begging you! Do it, Straw Hat!
Please! Please!
Bellamy, don't talk.
You're useless, Bellamy.
You're losing your edge...
Stop, Fake-mingo!
Hey, why don't you do as he wishes?
Doflamingo!!
Dammit!
Where did he go?!
I thought I was gonna die!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
THE SECOND LEVEL
Did the Pirate Hunter get killed?!
He's alive!
Pica-sama!
This "stone" doesn't know when to give up!
You think you can take me down
just because you know my ability?
What a simpleton!
Wait!
Take him down!
Don't move, Pirate Hunter!
We won't let you through here!
What a pain in the ass!
Commodore Dignity!
Atten-hut!
Count off!
--One!
--Two!
--Three!
--Four!
--Five!
--Six!
--Seven!
--Eight!
--Nine!
--Ten!
Don't do it!
No! No! Don't!
Oh? Why are we lining up?
Killer Bowling!
You're something!
--You can go ahead.
--Yeah, you're from the Colosseum, right?
That's right! My name is Orlumbus!
If this were the sea,
I would've backed you up
with my Yontamaria Fleet.
I'm sorry to be short-handed!
I'll leave the stone monster to you!
Okay!
Where did that shithead go?!
The face on the wall!
Pica-sama took over the plateau!
--Now, can you get away from my attacks?
--Was that how you laugh?!
What?!
So what if that's how I laugh?
I'm surprised because it sounded so stupid!
--You are stupid, Pirate Hunter!
--Don't piss Pica-sama off!
Pica-sama, don't!
Charlestone!
It's good that you're giant!
It'll feel good to slice you in half!
You're not looking at the big picture at all.
You're forever getting hung
up on the meaningless things.
That's why you can't seize the moment.
You haven't pulled the trigger yet.
In fact, you haven't even put your finger
on the trigger yet.
The weaker a person is,
the more he gets hung up
on other people's pain and
then he self-destructs.
If you really wanted to kill me,
you should've stuck to the plan
to provoke a conflict between Kaido and me.
There are so many ways to get rid of an enemy
you're no match for.
But by thinking of Corazon,
you got emotional,
and the moment you decided
to strike me yourself,
you fated yourself to die!
Do you remember the letter from that time?
All the Navy soldiers will know what it is
once they see this cylinder.
This one small package will save...
...a far-off kingdom called Dressrosa.
A kingdom?
Oh, it must be a secret letter.
I bet somebody asked you to deliver it.
Thank you.
I'll keep it. Don't worry.
Corazon was trying to
save this country, Dressrosa.
If only you hadn't blown it that day...
I'm sure you remember.
Because you're sort of responsible
for Corazon's death.
With that letter,
maybe, the numerous tragedies
that fell upon this country
wouldn't have happened.
You think so?
You remained calm. That's smart.
You're right!
If you ask me,
whatever happened to that letter,
I would've changed my plans
and sat on the throne of this country anyway!
Everything that Corazon did risking his life,
was all in vain after all.
It's all up to me now!
Whatever I do before I die
is all attributable to Cora-san's legacy!
Oh yeah?
What a tear-jerking sentiment!
That's right!
Whatever the tragedy or the blunder is,
only the things that actually
happened are written in stone!
The fact that you ate the
Op-Op Fruit and ran...
...or the fact that you are here now
after showing your teeth at Punk Hazard!
He did it!
String Saw! String Saw!
I like how you scream, Law!
I can't help dripping snot!
Second Gear!
Sorry, Bellamy!
Gum-Gum...
...Red Hawk!
Mingo!!
I'll kick his ass at any cost!
I don't know if you were influenced
by the other "D." or not,
but you coming to challenge
me yourself is something
that's written in stone, too!
That's why I forgive you!
Like I forgave my biological
father and brother...
I'll forgive you with your own death!
Gum-Gum...
Damn!
...Jet...
...Gatling!
Executions should be done by
nothing other than lead bullets.
What's the matter?
I thought you wanted to pull the trigger.
Doffy's double!
Mingo!
Show yourself!
Straw Hat-ya!
Doffy's double has broken apart!
I guess the cage was a bit too small...
...to keep it shut in.
Didn't you hear me?!
The savage attacks of Machvise,
one of the Family's executives,
leave Hajrudin's whole body beaten
and pummeled into the ground!
However, when the Giant, covered with wounds,
gets on his feet again to pay his
debt to Luffy and the others,
a deadly strike full of
Elbaph's spirit resounds!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Decisive Battle Against the
Executives! Proud Hajrudin!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!