Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current king
Doflamingo's agenda, they were trapped
along with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
Doffy's double!
Doffy's double has broken apart!
I guess the cage was a bit too small...
...to keep it shut in.
"A Decisive Battle Against the Executives!
Proud Hajrudin!"
Mingo!!
Bellamy...
Bellamy!
You!
You don't have to yell like that.
I can hear you.
Hey, Mingo! Stop Bellamy! He's gonna die!
Is he still alive?
Bellamy.
Straw Hat, I guess you won't change your mind
and finish off Bellamy.
All right.
Oh, Bellamy!
D-Doflamingo!
That's enough, Bellamy. I set you free.
Like you have always been.
You guys are the Donquixote Family,
aren't you?
I bet you're Doflamingo.
Who are you guys?
Let us under your umbrella!
Don't push your luck!
I'm begging you! Doflamingo!
Don't talk to Doffy so casually,
you little hoodlum!
I've been admiring you since I was a kid!
We want to follow you!
Give us a chance! Doflamingo!
Go away, you hoodlums!
Where are you from?
We're all from Nortis.
It's a wealthy town.
What's your problem with it?
That shitty town is boring!
The Donquixote Family is
the pride of the North Blue!
We wanna become
a pirate band like you guys!
We're a little different from
those idealistic pirates around there!
I'll let you use our Jolly Roger
if that's what you want.
Doffy!
However, if you get defeated by someone,
you're no longer allowed.
You sure?! Yeah!
I don't need weaklings as my subordinates.
We won't get defeated! By anyone!
Hey, Bellamy!
Are you all right?! I don't think you are.
So, you're the 30 million bounty,
Straw Hat Luffy!
You're such a delusional dumbass!
Listen.
The era where pirates dream about things is over!
The big hidden treasure, One Piece...!
Those idiots who are blinded by dream treasure don't
notice the treasure around them.
They're misled by those illusions and die.
That's just drivel by losers!
Struggle all you want;
there's no escape from my Boing-Boing Fruit power!
Spring...
...Hopper!
A city of gold?!
A sky island?!
The era of dreams is over,
you pathetic excuses for pirates!
Do I know how to throw a punch, you ask?
So long, Straw Hat!
Straw Hat.
I visited the Sky Island.
I lost my crew but it turned my
view of the world upside down.
I'm not holding a grudge against you anymore.
I'm done picking on you.
Bellamy.
Why did you cheer me on?
That was so embarrassing!
I haven't changed a bit.
You've changed, Bellamy.
No, you have changed.
You now use Haki that's far
greater than anyone can imagine.
That pisses me off!
Hey, don't push yourself!
You better stay down.
Joker wants me to kill Straw Hat?
Doffy's too indulgent.
He's giving the man who couldn't win the match
one more chance.
Aren't you happy, Bellamy?
Well, I thought you were gonna mess it up.
The assassination of Straw Hat.
What?!
But it doesn't matter
if you can get it done or not.
What do you mean?
He doesn't want you to follow him about
so he told me to finish you off here.
That's Young Master-sama's order.
Oh? A big quake again!
What did you come here for?
Isn't there any...
...hope left for me?
Don't make me say it straight, Bellamy.
Your purpose was different from mine.
From long ago.
You always wanted to become a pirate.
But not me.
Anything was fine with me.
Anything?
As long as I could...
...destroy this world!
I can't do that!
You're my friend!
Bellamy. I set you free.
Like you have always been.
Hey, Bellamy!
I'm sorry but wait here.
I'm worried about Tra-guy!
Mingo and Snot are up there.
I gotta get there or Tra-guy's in trouble!
I'll kick Mingo's ass for you, too!
Wait!
Do you remember this technique?
Here I go! Straw Hat!
Spring...
...Hopper!
You got stronger but I got stronger, too!
This technique is far more destructive than
it used to be!
Hey, Pica!
Don't forget we're fighting here, too!
Destruction Cannon!
You better pay attention!
Oh! You scare me.
What's wrong with this guy?
I-I think you're serious, aren't you?
You've been beating around the bush!
Is it because we're each other's enemy?!
Why don't you say it straight?!
What are you talking about?!
Don't pretend that you don't know!
Glance.
I'll shoot...
...through your heart!
You said "I'll aim for your heart"...
I won't let go of your hand!
And "I'll keep holding your hand"!
Can you keep up with me?!
And "Can you stick with me"!
If you want me so much...
I don't care about the positions we're in!
You...
...need me, don't you?!
Ten-Ton Vise!
Vise-sama!
Here comes one more-in!
100-Ton Vise!
So tenacious-in!
Go to hell! Ton-Ton!
He shows no mercy!
Even the warrior of Elbaph couldn't do a thing
against Vice-sama!
This is good-in! A good foothold-in!
I brought down Hajrudin the Giant-in
and my next target is...
That's Roronoa Zoro!
He was just big and not quite strong!
You're in our way, you big shit!
My dream was to become
the king of all Giants.
But look at me.
I lost in the competition.
I got turned into a toy.
I had been saved
but I still haven't paid back my debt!
How pathetic!
I was willing to die to pay my debt, then...
...why am I still alive after I failed?!
Ton-Ton!
Was my gratitude...
that shallow?!
I... I...
Here I go, Roronoa!
He's...
Destructive 1,000-Ton Vise!
No, it's...
It's far deeper than that!
He got up!
I'm sorry but...
let me take care of that guy.
Hajrudin!
Hey, hey-in!
I can't believe you're still alive!
Then, I'll make it heavier-in!
Hellish 10,000-Ton Vise!
I hope there are still bones left to be crushed!
Hey-in!
A dead man can't be useful but...
...if at least one of his arms still moves,
a man can even rip off his enemy general's head.
Take this! I'll give it all my life!
Gungir!!
It's no use-in. This is 10,000 ton!
Get squashed, Hajrudin!
Fly away! To the kingdom of the gods!!
What?!
Vice-sama!
Oh no! Above him!
He's gonna hit the Birdcage!
Stop, Vice-sama!
He's gonna get slashed!
I guess he can't fly out there...
He's not even a bird.
Vice-sama!
Take a good rest.
When you wake up, the cage will be gone!
Sai of the Happosui Army is baffled by
Baby 5 who comes on strong
with her earnest feelings!
While the both families fight fiercely to
defend their pride, her sad past is revealed
and the passionate man, Sai blasts
a special secret technique which bests Don Chin Jao!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Battle of Love! The New Leader Sai vs. Baby 5!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!