Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
There's the signal...
Broggy-san!
Today is very promising!
"Luffy Gets Angry!
A Dirty Trick Violates The Sacred Duel!"
What're you doing, old guy?!
Move this rock!
You're going?! Your wounds from
that last battle still haven't--!
Perfect timing!
Now, then! Accelerate, Candle Service!
It's nothing! The conditions
are the same for both of us!
What're you doing here, anyway?
What's the deal, Nami?
Turn these people into wax figures!
Dinosaur!
Making excuses during a
merciless fight to the death
There's someone on this island!
My hands won't move!
would spoil my name!
I don't wanna die this way!
Can't we do something?!
Who is it?!
Hey, old man.
Hey! Wait, old guy!
Whadya say we crush
these guys together?
Don't go!
You can't go, Dorry-san!
You need to keep still!
You'll die if you push yourself too hard!
I'll fight alongside you
and your fighting spirit!
Why, you...!
"Huge Duel!
The Giants Dorry And Broggy"
Don't be stupid!
What can you possibly do?!
I, Warrior Dorry, am here...
10,000 Kilogram Press!
At the very least...
Mr. 3. Please excuse the codename.
I'm a mere formative artist.
...I will fight to uphold the name of Elbaf!
So...
I'm gonna kick your asses,
just so you know!
What's the answer?
And this is my realist painter assistant,
Miss Golden Week.
Wh-What was that?
C-Could you repeat that?
What?
These guys spoiled
the old giant guys' duel!
Mr. 3?! The Wax-Wax Fruit man?!
"Broggy's Bitter Tears of Victory!
The Conclusion of Elbaf"
I asked you if you have any alcohol.
Master Broggy!
We've taken on your frustration!
He's a "candle man" who controls
the wax he secretes from his body.
H-He blocked the blow with his helmet!
We've got a little...
If he was off by even an inch,
he would've died instantly!
Usopp...
So you've got some?
For now, could you bust
this pillar for us, Luffy?
I-It's not for drinking.
It's for cooking and disinfection.
You guys are gonna pay for this!
I leave the rest to you.
But if you like, we'll give it all to you.
Alright, no problem!
I wouldn't be so sure.
Break the pillar, Luffy!
Dino...
Dinosaur?
What a fight...
"A Hex on Luffy! Colors Trap"
Each of their attacks is a mortal blow
aimed at the opponent's vital point!
"The Devilish Candle!
Tears of Regret and Tears of Anger"
Those two have continued this
duel to the death for 100 years?
Don't tell me he's--!
But this is good... We can use this
opportunity to get out of here.
I'm Broggy, the Elbaf's strongest warrior!
Curse you! What are you doing?!
Awesome! He picked up
that gigantic rock!
Now I've got meat, too.
I'll treat you, my guests.
What am I doing?
Usopp?
This is why I can't stand
unsophisticated dolts.
Luffy-san!
Zoro! What are you doing?!
I'm creating a work of art, obviously.
Incredible...
If I'm gonna be solidified,
I prefer this pose.
H-Hey...
This is no time to be playing around!
Reason?
P-Pretend we're dead...
No matter what happens...
I'm not playing.
I don't remember.
What're you doing, old guy?!
Move this rock! Hey!
Anyways, do something about your leg!
It's painful just looking at it!
D-Doesn't pretending to be
dead only work on bears?
Just be a good little girl.
It can't be stopped...
Did you honestly think you
could escape from Baroque Works?
Then quit looking at it.
Even without a reason,
they're fighting so seriously...
You're the idiot who suggested
cutting our legs off in this situation
It was over a hundred years ago...
This fight sure is a bother.
so we could escape!
...when we started the battle.
That ain't true!
Whoa! What a great view!
You idiot!
I was gonna cut 'em off
so we could fight.
This is what people mean
by a real battle between men!
Especially when someone with a
30 million-Berry bounty winds up like that?
That's even stupider! Get serious!
But running from a battle you've started...
I wanna have lunch here.
What's that about?
Just shut up!
To use an analogy, those two fly
a warrior's flag in their heart.
I'm happy I could thank them
for what happened at Whisky Peak.
Honestly! You have no common sense!
This isn't the time for idle chatter!
...is the same as running
from the title of "warrior."
You wannabe pirates should
never have stuck your noses
If I am no longer a warrior...
Ahhh... Oh? So there really are volcanoes.
We still haven't even escaped
from this situation,
This flag is even more
important than their life.
...I will no longer be me.
into such delicate issues as this.
And there's a mountain
with huge holes as well...
We've already captured your
swordsman friend and the other girl.
yet neither of them seems
to sense the danger at all...
I'm sorry I suspected you.
In no way do they want it
to be destroyed by others.
That's why they've continued to take
on each other for 100 long years!
It's dangerous! Come down already!
You caught Zoro?
This is the judgment given by...
Huh?
Even if it's well-behaved,
it's still a dinosaur!
Then you guys're gonna get cut down!
Hey, runt. Is that all
the struggling you got?
...Elbaf, the god of war.
This guy's no trouble!
Oh?
Do you get it? This is unmistakably
Yeah. Looks like it's
someone else's turn now.
You still talk big,
More importantly,
there're huge holes over there!
even after one of my
Kicky Bombs to the face?
a "proud duel" between "warriors"!
I didn't have his
divine protection. That's all.
That's one weird landscape!
You can't hurt me with that!
I see...
Forget about the landscape!
Just come down!
I'm gonna kick you guys' asses!
Whatever... Stuff like that
doesn't interest me.
Gods and divine protection and
all that have nothing to do with this!
Say, I have a favor to ask.
Will you take me over there?
Mr. 3. Those people don't
seem concerned at all.
Now, hurry up!
I'm gonna watch this a little longer.
If a god told you to die, would you?!
I could say the same about you,
Miss Golden Week!
Unbelievable.
This duel has been interfered with!
This is exactly what my goal is...
To be a "brave warrior of the sea"!
Hey, stop being so mean
and take me there.
Urgh!
A duel that's been interfered
with isn't a duel anymore!
Luffy-san!
Hey. If you're gonna do a pose,
now's your chance.
I wanna be a proud man like them!
Don't put me on your level.
Over that way! That way!
--Isn't that right?!
--Be quiet!
Mr. Bushido! Please be
more serious about this!
Die!
Not this way... Here! This way!
I'm always serious.
You've lived only a mere 10 or 20 years--
More like stupid.
Who'd do something like that?!
--Like you're one to talk!
--It seems we're being mocked!
you wouldn't understand
the grand words of Elbaf!
I see... So you wanna be a giant.
This is truly displeasing!
Ever since he showed up, they've been--
Who gives a crap about that?!
Hey! Move this thing! Hey! Old guy!
No!! Were you even listening to me?!
It couldn't be!
There! Don't you have
to watch them over there?
Hey! Old guy! Hey! Dammit!
--Fool!
--Luffy-san!
Alright!
He hardly seems to be
that reliable of a man.
Luffy-san! Luffy-san!
I can't move this!
Let's go, Miss Valentine.
Mr. 3!
Luffy-san!
If there's a village with
warriors like them in it,
We'll finish him off.
Usopp-san! Karoo!
Okay, Master Broggy! Go get 'im!
I wanna go there someday.
Finish him off?
Don't be silly.
Just look!
I've got a good view from here.
Oh... sorry. But, uhm...
He showed up here alive and well
because your attacks don't work.
You bet, Usopp!
They'll find you, Miss Valentine.
Come down already!
I'm gonna wipe the floor
with him for sure this time!
Don't worry, Mr. 5... After all,
they're absorbed in the fight.
At the very least, he's at a level
that's too much for you to handle.
Go get 'im, Warrior of Elbaf!
Amazing!!
They won't notice.
You can do it!
Just come down!
You two can take care of the others!
Luffy-san! Like I said, it's dangerous!
Come down already!
You're strong! Strong! Strong!
Okay, okay.
Damn you...
Give it up! Give it up!
I think I'll add Straw Hat Luffy
to my wax figure collection...
And those dinosaurs are taller,
so it looks like I'll have a better view.
Once solidified,
my Candle Jacket is as hard as iron!
You're big! Big!
Hey, do you really get it?
How can he keep doing
this pointless fighting?
This is a big job for 200 million Berries.
That's not the point!
Don't call it pointless fighting, you idiot!
Of course...
Broggy's a brave warrior of the sea,
like the kind I'm aiming to be!
You giants may have brutish strength,
Although I feel reluctant
to do as Mr. 3 tells us...
You guys are too damn annoying!
but it becomes all but useless
once you've been caught.
What gives you the right--
As I thought, I can see the holes better.
Anyways, let's return to the ship.
You've gone a bit too far!
Give yourselves up!
I know... Let's go.
Using your brain is the key.
Waiting a year for the Log to
store up is out of the question!
There's no need to
uselessly face you head-on.
Okay.
Hmph!
We need to wait on the ship for
everyone and come up with a plan.
Small fry.
Oops!
You lowered your guard
as you reveled in victory,
Hold it! Not so fast!
Let's do it!
Hmph!
Red Ogre Broggy.
I am absolutely useless in
a fight against dinosaurs!
Watch out!
Don't glare at me like that.
You're terrifying me so!
Alright! Preparations are complete!
We got your back, Luffy!
As such, we cannot possibly traverse
the jungle to reach our ship!
You should be happy! Your long,
long battle has come to an end!
What was all that "brave warrior
of the sea" stuff just now, then?
Did you say something?
Now you're mine!
Candle Lock!
We're both getting homesick,
aren't we, Dorry?
I meant that in the mental sense!
You fought for a whole century
for your so-called pride, right?
Vivi! Wanna come over here?! It's fun!
I want to be a man who's
proud of the way he lives!
Shouldn't the taste of victory
be especially sweet, then?
What is that?!
No choice.
That's why I'll beat you
and go back to Elbaf, Broggy.
Luffy's group is at the
other giant's house.
Even if it is the fruit
of others' assistance...
--Luffy-san!
--Damn. He's already gotten caught?!
Guess we'll head there...
Idiot!
Listen, Nami.
Am I wrong?
Even if I wind up
losing everything someday
What's this? It's heavy, like a mallet!
Damn you! You don't mean to say...!
and greet death all alone
on a deserted island,
How simple.
I'll proudly say this
about my life as I die:
But the final victory belongs to me!
Now for your hands!
"I am Usopp, brave warrior of the sea!"
Are you aware that the large
bounties on your heads from long ago
Oh! This is perfect!
73,466 duels...
Yeah, yeah.
Candle Lock!
come to 200 million Berries total?
Then will you hurry up
and be a dependable warrior?
Even today this holds true!
73,466 draws...
Whoa!
Oh...
Alright!
The view from here is especially good!
Why, you...!
I feel as if I've discovered
a long-lost treasure!
Old giant guy!
So that's what you're after, huh?!
Sorry to bother you!
Dorry! How was your drink?!
Hit the spot, didn't it?!
What?! What's he up to?!
Mr. 3!
We brought her.
Yeah... It tasted "godly"...
Our company's little traitor.
What took so long?
I was getting sick of waiting.
Your methods are too underhanded, Mr. 3!
You're so full of exaggerations! Let's go!
Ah!
He's been eaten!
Planting bombs in Dorry-san's alcohol...!
Gum-Gum...
...Mallet!
What?!
Where am I?
Alcohol?
The alcohol I gave him?!
What's wrong, Dorry?!
You're a bit sluggish!
He did it!
Yahoo!
Dorry! How was your drink?!
Hit the spot, didn't it?!
Don't be a fool!
I'm the same as always!
Yeah... It tasted "godly"...
That's what you meant, Dorry?!
Dorry! Actually,
I got alcohol from my guests.
Wretched little girl,
giving our tricks away.
Great! It's been a while since
I had a drink. Give me some.
Well, no matter.
There's nothing you can do now, anyway.
Lucky! The mallet on my legs broke, too!
Candle...
Move, you stupid thing! Come on!
...Lock!
Just when it seemed like
I met an awesome warrior!
Huh? Huh?!
Luffy-san...
Why would he go this far
for a giant he just met?
What was that?
Mr. 5!
Whoa...
I'm alive...
First a long, strange earthquake,
and now this? What is it this time?
Bring the swordsman and the girl!
He hardly seems like a criminal
with a bounty on his head...
We survived...
Are there weird creatures other
than dinosaurs in this jungle?
I was watching. What a lively human,
grappling with longnecks in this jungle.
We're about to begin!
That didn't help things at all!
Who is it?! Who's putting
a damper on the giants' fight?!
Well, that damn cook is
probably the only one
Whew, that was dangerous!
Why didn't you guys run?
You're the first guest in a long time.
who'd be happy to
capture things like that...
We can't move! Isn't it obvious?!
Extra Big Candle Set!
Come to think of it...
You're huge! Are you a human?
Were those bird cries?
...Karoo is gone!
Oh? Really?
Even so, those were vulgar,
unappetizing cries.
You're asking me if I'm a human?
But you guys told me to break the pillar!
Although we're competing to capture a
big prey, we're still looking for food.
Were you lying?
I'm Dorry, the Elbaf's strongest warrior!
Is it really a good idea to put our
lives in his hands, Mr. Bushido?!
Not only does it have to be big,
it also has to be tasty.
Don't look at me.
That's the only choice we got here.
G... Giant!
That guy doesn't get it at all.
Plus it looks like my arms are stuck now.
I've heard of them, but this is my
first time actually seeing one...
Please be serious about this!
Oh? Isn't this ugly bird the one
the princess always has with her?
I'm Luffy. I'm a pirate.
Yeah.
Hold on... It feels like my body
is hardening more and more now...
I see. His guests are your friends, huh?
A pirate?! Good for you!
I saw a man with a long nose and a woman.
Karoo! Wake up!
I can't move at all now...
We're getting out of here while we can!
That's Usopp and Nami!
Oh yeah, the ones over there are
Vivi and Karoo. Nice to meet you!
Hah! They said they
wouldn't get off the ship,
but they really do like
adventures after all!
Luffy-san had to open his big mouth...!
T-This is Mr. 3's ability?!
Then you could also say that
I got this alcohol from you.
Fools! With the candles closer,
your hardening has sped up!
I'll invite you guys to my home!
Don't run away!
Now you can become
wax figures even quicker!
What's going on?!
By the way, Dorry-san,
Here they are.
We were lucky enough
to meet out here, after all.
does it really take a year
for the Log to be stored?
There's something we'd like you to do.
That guy thinks he can act
all smug and arrogant!
Didn't you notice the
human skulls lying around?
That's right.
How naive.
Hey! You guys are gonna be wax figures?
Being ridiculed by people of
their caliber is so embarrassing
That's what we've been trying to tell you!
Those who come to this island die
before the Log is stored in most cases.
Just destroy this set, Luffy-san!
that I'm pissed at myself.
You can't help that you're weak.
R-Right! Okay!
Some become dinosaurs' food.
Some suffer from the heat and starvation.
Damn. I'm lost.
I told you, I won't let you interfere!
Huh? What was that?
Nothing! Just set
the candles up quickly!
I do recognize this tree, but...
Wax-Wax Arts! Harpoon!
Some others are killed because
they attack us. They all die...
It looks yummy.
Set?
Exploding Star!
It was, "Go left from the
tree wrapped in vines," right?
What is that?!
How long do we have
to pretend to be dead?
It seems that one year on this
island is too long for humans.
Nami-san... Mr. Bushido...
Oh! It's you, Nami!
After all, this strategy doesn't
seem to work against a giant.
Vivi! What happened?!
Weren't you with Luffy?!
Perfect timing!
I just lost my way, you see,
so I wasn't sure what to do...
What're we gonna do?
Even if we could survive for a year,
Yes, I was, but...
If you're wondering about Straw Hat,
I took care of him myself!
What're you doing here, anyway?
if that much time passes, I don't know
what will happen to my country by then.
Hey. What's the deal?
It was an easy job, too.
Hmm... I guess it was my imagination.
Yeah. I'd get bored, too,
if we stay here for a year.
You did?
Isn't there a good way, old guy?
Why'd you make a noise?
Dinosaur!
That was rather bland.
You don't use very good gunpowder.
I couldn't help it since there're
tons of skulls lying around!
Hmmm...
Dinosaur! Dinosaur! Dinosaur!
We do have an Eternal Pose,
but it's to our hometown, Elbaf.
I know, but...
He ate the Exploding Star!
Hey, you! You're too fast!
I wonder if we'll be
eaten like that soon...
In other words, we're fighting
for this Eternal Pose.
Don't give up!
Urgh, that guy...
This is bad. It really is fast.
But...
Do you wanna try taking it by force?
Luffy!
We don't have to wait here
like this just to be eaten.
What a relief!
--Good thing I posed beforehand.
--You idiot!
That's no good.
That's not where we wanna go.
What are you doing here?
It's yummy! It's yummy!
Dinosaur meat!
Luffy-san! Please, hurry!
We just wanna go to the island
after this one. Right?
Alright! That pumpkin's
the bad thing, right?!
Yes...
Grill it with red flame
and take a big bite!
If we lose the route to Alabasta,
there's no point in moving forward.
Hang on! Gum-Gum...
Welcome, friends, to my service set!
It's no use!
It's yummy! It's yummy!
Dinosaur meat!
Candle Wall!
See?
Then why don't you
move forward randomly?
...Bazooka!
--That way!
--It's yummy! It's yummy!
Dinosaur meat!
N-Nami?
If you're lucky, you'll get there.
--It's yummy! It's yummy!
- Dinosaur meat!
Dinosaur meat...
Hey, you! Don't get in my way!
That would be my line.
I'd appreciate it if you didn't
interfere with my creative activities.
Candle Lock!
Maybe we'll do that!
I got a mallet!
Is this how it feels to be
a candle stuck in a cake?
We may actually get there, huh?
Gum-Gum...
Nami! Nami! Nami! Nami!
Oh no! Candle Wall!
What's that spinning thing up there?
Come to think of it, there was someone
who left before the Log was stored.
...Mallet!
This is not good...
I-in any case...
we were able to escape...
Luffy!
And I can't move my legs...
What happened to him?
At least we got far away
from the giant's stomach!
How should I know?
Of course they're not gonna let us move.
He must've gotten to the next island.
They're the enemy.
That must be it!
Damn. It's hard.
What's so funny?
But it might've only gotten us closer
to a saber-toothed tiger's stomach...
Plus I can't put any strength
into it from this stance.
Hurray! Hurray!
--Mr. 3...
--Impossible!
Something's raining down!
I can't understand what they're thinking!
May you enjoy my "Candle Service"!
No! No! No! No!
Luffy!
Luffy! Hurry and break this
set while there's still time!
The wax haze falling from above you
Luffy! Luffy! Luffy! Luffy!
will eventually change
you into wax figures!
Luffy!
--No.
--Quit joking around and hurry!
You'll become perfect "human models"
No.
This is no time to be acting stupid!
Oww...
that not even I could
achieve with my skills!
Luffy-san! Please!
Terrible news! A dinosaur ate Nami!
Your wax figures will have
literally captured your spirit!
Seriously?!
We were running through
the jungle to get away from it,
Now die, in the name of art.
What should I do?
and then suddenly she was gone!
A brave warrior of the sea? What's that?
I don't feel like saving you guys.
Oh! What do I do now?!
I let my friend get killed!
Screw that!
I'm talking about you guys.
I wanna be like you guys someday!
Why do we have to turn
into your works of art?!
H-Hold on! Calm down, you two!
What are you saying?
Broggy-san! Quit sitting
there and go on a rampage!
Hm? You mean a giant?
You're gonna get turned into
a wax figure too, you know!
--See?
--That's not it!
Colors Trap.
In this jungle, no matter what we do,
our fate will always be the same!
If she suddenly disappeared,
does that mean you don't know for sure?
Man, talk about a huge person...
I hope to live proudly
just like the warriors of Elbaf!
It's just a matter
of whose stomach we end up in...
Anything you say to him is pointless!
Are you crazy?! I was too
terrified to check and make sure!
We did everything we could.
Let's accept our fate...
He just now realized he foolishly
shed proud, joyful tears of victory
If it wasn't a dinosaur,
it was a wild beast!
What else could it have been?!
I see!
Oh, you guys're awake?
Especially since our life span
is longer than you humans',
I don't know.
after killing his friend Dorry,
with whom he fought for 100 years,
But if people from Baroque Works
have followed us onto this island,
The meat is done. Have some!
It's in return for the alcohol.
we think about how we die.
but without even noticing that he
had suffered injuries beforehand!
then it'd make sense that only
Nami-san was targeted and not you.
Your assets, life...
Everything will eventually cease to exist.
Eh?! Baroque Works is on the island?!
But if we could die as a warrior of
Elbaf without destroying our pride,
Or did you perhaps cry
for your friend, instead?
But... why wouldn't they go after me?
that would be "dying with honor."
Whatever the case, there's no
undoing what you've done now, fool!
Now, eat! Dinosaur meat tastes good.
That pride is an everlasting treasure
that is passed on in the land of Elbaf.
Because you're most likely not on
Baroque Works's assassination list.
Hey! Luffy!
Oh, I see!
There's no time! Do something
about this thing already!
I-I have no appetite.
So pride is your treasure...
That's so cool...
Plus, that alcohol might've
been meant for us, too!
Yeah... I know.
Don't hold back!
I've just decided... that I'll
call you Master from now on!
--Then hurry!
--Yeah, Luffy!
I knew...
Alcohol?! What about alcohol?!
I don't want to eat.
Huh?
I knew about it.
Broggy brought your alcohol to Dorry.
I know, but...
Dinosaur meat tastes good,
I'm tellin' ya...
And when Dorry drank it,
it exploded inside his stomach.
But I don't feel like saving you...
Is he trying to get us to
eat the dinosaur meat first...
From the moment we
first exchanged blows...
Why do you keep saying that?!
What?! Alcohol exploded
inside his stomach?!
...in order to fatten us up a little...
We're the ones who're
about to be wax figures!
...I knew Dorry was hiding something.
...and then eat us?
Understand?! We're about to die!
You're saying he went to the
battlefield all busted up like that?!
Yeah, he's acting like a giant, all right.
You knew, huh?
Yeah. But for some reason,
I just can't get motivated.
I tried to stop him,
but I wound up like this instead!
When we're still so young...
You lie!
Giant old guy!
If so, then why didn't
you cease your fighting?
Maybe we taste best when we're young...
This isn't a motivation problem!
What a waste...
I didn't see a shred of pity in
the way you heartily cut him down!
You can't be serious!
What's going on?!
D-Dammit! What's happened to him?!
It's good, I'm tellin' ya...
Those two've fought evenly for
100 years with all their might!
Why did the alcohol explode?!
That was the alcohol
we had on our ship, right?!
If we somehow keep fasting until
the Log is stored and don't get fat,
Our friends're gonna die
if he doesn't hurry!
A pipsqueak who doesn't even
know the first thing about duels
we may be able to survive...
It exploded in his stomach!
His opponent must've laid the explosive!
But how long will it take
for the Log to be stored?
would never understand
the meaning of those tears!
I'll bring him back to his senses!
Let's go, Karoo!
If I don't eat for three days,
What would you know?!
What the hell were you watching?!
I'm sure I'll get tempted
by this smell of meat and eat it...
Are you saying I should shame a warrior
They've been fighting for 100 years!
No way they'd do something like this!
It's probably the most pride-filled
battle in the entire world!
W-When did you...?!
who hides the fact he's been
weakened and tries to fight anyway?!
Broggy-san! Can I ask you a question?
--Yeah...
--They can't settle the fight like this now!
Then who on earth...
Give it up. He's already
fallen into a trap.
Hmm? What's the matter, young lady?
A warrior who'll go that far to
keep fighting doesn't deserve pity!
H-How long will it take for the
Log of this island to be stored?
You bastards did...
That's right. See where he's standing?
Where he's standing?
It wasn't Broggy.
One year.
What?!
What's wrong?!
Let's see here...
And now... I know the reason behind it.
We're proud warriors of Elbaf.
Oh, no... There's no way
we can fast for a year...
What's that?
There's a strange black pattern...
Now that I know, I'm going to
finish things with my own two hands!
Who else besides you
should I be suspicious of?
I... definitely can't help eating...
What's so important about that?!
Well, make yourselves at home!
You're right. It's nothing.
It's just paint.
Let's get out of here for now! It's
probably no use saying anything to him!
He's still fighting.
It's probably no use even if we run.
Yes. Dorry the Blue Ogre
is quite stubborn indeed.
Paint?
That's the very least I can
do for my dear friend Dorry!
Hold this and stay back.
In other words,
both you and them are goners!
Don't tell me! Are you going to fight?
Perhaps I should assist one of them.
This is yummy, giant old guy!
Broggy-san!
I feel bad to do this to the old guy,
but I'll quiet him down.
Your pirate lunch thing tastes good, too,
although it's a little too small for me.
Of course it's good!
Both of you, stop! Please!
That's a special lunch
the chef on my pirate ship made.
Dorry-san, please listen!
We really don't know anything about it!
Karoo! Let's just run for now!
One century...
--Broggy-san!
If you say it's bad, I'll beat you up!
Anything about the alcohol that exploded!
So please don't fight!
What an annoying, talkative monster.
Beat me up, you said?
He's planning to escape on the bird!
You have to stay calm!
Your insides are in bad shape right now!
Let's get 'em.
It was a long battle!
What a funny squirt you are!
U-Usopp...
How dare you...
do something so insolent?!
Th-They're becoming awfully friendly...
Sprint at full speed!
Usopp...
By the way, why are you
living here alone, old guy?
Hey, you! Wait!
I haven't gotten on yet! Karoo!
Isn't there a village or something?
Can you let them get away with this?
Hmm? There is a village.
It's a warriors' village called Elbaf.
No... I can't...
It's somewhere in the Grand Line.
Hey! Alright! Stop! Let me get on!
Hm?
Gum-Gum!
But there're rules in the village.
Rules?
For example, if we start a fight in the
village and both sides can't back off,
What's the point in being scared of me?!
Can you... not stand this?
we are judged by Elbaf's god.
Elbaf's god always gives divine
protection to the righteous one
and lets the righteous one survive.
Alright! Let's all three of us
go beat them senseless!
Miss Golden Week!
I see... Elbaf's god, huh?
Gum-Gum!
This is your doing!
I caused a disturbance, and
this island is currently the site
Broggy-san!
Colors Trap: Betrayal Black.
How dumb!
for a duel between a
certain man and myself.
I underestimated how brutishly
strong these giants can be!
This is the judgment given
by Elbaf, the god of war.
Touch the black paint,
The righteous one will
win the duel and survive.
and you'll want to betray your friends,
no matter what they say.
I'm sorry.
I didn't have his
divine protection. That's all.
Rocket!!
But we haven't been able to
settle this for about 100 years.
It would seem you need
to be seized completely!
What does she mean?!
What happened?! Explain!
Wax-Wax Arts! Handcuffs!
You guys've been fighting for 100 years?!
She's a "realist painter" who can
even create real colors of emotion!
It's nothing surprising, since our life span
is at least three times as long as yours.
Eh?!
I'm just getting started!
--Luffy!
--Luffy-san?!
Her refined sense of color
can manipulate people's minds
Who was it?!
Even if it's three times,
through the use of her paints.
Show yourself!
your interest in fighting would
wane in 100 years, wouldn't it?
And now for the finishing touch!
Manipulate?! That's not good!
Take this!
Is there any point in continuing to fight?
That simpleminded idiot is
already easy enough to manipulate!
It's a duel to the death, right?!
Then doesn't he just need
to get away from that paint?
Well, I shouldn't be outdone
by Zoro with this one.
Mr. 3. I think I heard something.
Luffy! Get away from there!
Can't move now, can you?!
Luffy-san!!
No, don't!
It's decided that I'm the winner of the
competition to obtain kilos of meat.
Luffy-san! Whatever you do,
do not move from that black circle!
How funny! An underdog loser,
yelping out here in the jungle!
So he has... the powers of a Devil Fruit...
I'm begging you!
I'm the winner of the competition
to obtain tons of meat!
How can he be so horrific?!
Vivi! Why?!
I underestimated... him...
We don't want you to save us at all!
Now, then! Accelerate, Candle Service!
Turn these people into wax figures!
No.
Seventy-three thousand...
I get it.
Zoro!
Sanji!
You made him do the exact
opposite of what you said...
M-My chest is starting to hurt...
I win!
The wax haze is getting into our lungs!
Huh?
...four hundred sixty-seven fights...
At this rate, we're going to turn
into wax figures from the inside out!
I-I was kind of weird just now!
You lose!
Luffy-san! Hurry!
Yes! Yes! Make it look like
you're in as much pain as you can!
Alright! I'll save you right now!
Luffy-san! Are you all right?
Look! My prey is bigger!
73,466 draws...
Expressions of pain and agony
are the very things I seek in art!
What?! This competition is about how
many tons of meat we can get, right?!
How's the old guy?
He's probably okay.
Mine is obviously huskier than yours!
This is actually good.
Otherwise he wouldn't have calmed down.
May you solidify
while filled with terror!
...and one win!
But never mind you guys!
I just wanna laugh!
Ha! It's all a matter of if
we can use it for cooking.
You call this art,
you creepy topknot freak?!
I'm angry!
Your prey looks full of bones.
How dare you do that to Broggy-san?!
--Why?!
--Why, you...!
What?
It has no more than 5 grams
of meat for cooking!
Like the old guy said, this alcohol
explosion isn't the act of the other giant,
Now what?!
You guys are going to
regret this! You got that?!
There's no way we can eat
meat full of sinews like that!
Tsk! There's no use in
competing with such small prey.
and my friends would never
do a stupid thing like this!
Scream and holler all you want!
Colors Trap: Laughter Yellow.
I'll go capture a big one that'll silence you.
Then who on earth...
Okay then. I'll go capture a super big
one that you can't even touch this time.
You know you're not supposed to move.
There's someone else...
on this island...
Joyful tears of victory, huh?
Simpleminded people have it so easy.
For 100 years...
Now it's on his clothes!
Though, perhaps I'll
congratulate you for now.
Luffy! Hurry and take off that clothing!
N-Never mind that!
Joyful tears?!
Games are heavily influenced
by people's state of mind.
Okay. The next eruption is the
signal to end the competition.
What would you know?!
Just who are you?!
I just feel like laughing!
...day in and day out,
we fought and fought...
Bring back your prey
to the Going Merry by then.
Mr. 3. Please excuse the codename.
I'm a mere formative artist.
They are confused right now...
...and dueled only because of our
pride of Elbaf, village of warriors!
Yeah, I'll take you up on that!
...by the cryptic bomb service
from an invisible enemy...
Not good!
Whoa!!
If it keeps raining down at this pace,
we won't last one more minute!
And this is my realist painter assistant,
Miss Golden Week.
Yet... why are we being subjected
to this, Elbaf, god of war?!
That's a huge volcano eruption!
First, about our first target,
Dorry the Blue Ogre...
Well, time to go...
What's more, I've already captured you.
Hmm?
I knew it was impossible to finish him,
If this is how we're
to meet our end, Elbaf...
but the damage he received in his
stomach still must've been quite large.
Did you guys come here to play?!
W-What is this?!
Now we can drink some tea and
wait for the next duel to start...
...don't you think it's unfair?!
Why won't you let us die in battle?!
What's that?
Look! When Usopp ran into him,
the paint on his back smudged!
An eruption...
So we'll let the other giant take
care of the injured giant, huh?
What a look!
Hmm?
Did I wind up doing something again?
Yes! That sorrow!
That grief! That struggle!
That's right.
That's quite a roundabout
way of doing things.
His face suddenly got tense...
What a marvelous work of art!
The Warrior species is the
same as wild boars, after all.
Hey, you! Knock it off, you jerk!
Alright, Luffy!
Sorry... I have to head out for a bit.
I dunno who we're dealing with,
but I'll go take care of them myself!
Elbaf!
Was Laughter Yellow funny?
We don't have to fight seriously when
they're only good at going head-on
Oh no! My hands won't move!
What? Head out?
I'm coming, too!
Shut up! Are you stupid?! Stupid!
I don't wanna die this way!
Can't we do something?!
Yes! Please come with me!
That'd be reassuring!
Yeah. That was a signal for the duel
that I've been in for 100 years.
My body's already turning stiff!
since even if we can't win power-wise,
There's no need for that!
Anyways, I gotta break that pumpkin!
What do we do?!
we have brains that can make up for it.
Gum-Gum...
A duel?
Zoro! Do something!
With whom?
Where and for what reason?
Colors Trap: Bullfight Red.
You guys!
Hey, old man.
Reason? I don't remember.
You can still move, can't you?
...Bazooka!
So can I.
Where are you aiming?!
You're not allowed to break it!
You'll make Mr. 3 angry!
It became our routine
before we realized it.
Whadya say we crush these guys together?
What is this?!
The eruption of the central mountain
is the signal for the duel.
You can have him back.
We don't need him.
Just as bulls rush at red capes,
Hold on, Zoro! What are you doing?!
You're not seriously gonna--!
What?! To have such hatred that you'd
try killing each other for 100 years is...
you feel the urge to attack
that Bullfight Red mark.
Karoo!
Why, you...!
Yeah.
Geez... Get it yourself, Miss Golden Week.
You're gonna cut your own legs?!
Quit joking around!
Too bad.
Hey, who are they?
What on earth caused this fight?!
It's no joke.
It's the only way out of here.
I can't stand you anymore!
Get out of here!
The guys from that last town!
What are you doing here?!
Karoo has nothing to do with this!
Stop it.
By the way, what're we going
to do with the Straw Hat gang?
Gum-Gum Bazooka!
What're you two gonna do?
It's not like that.
What are you talking about?!
It's pointless!
Straw Hat? Oh yeah, the small fries
that found out the Boss's secret...
That's right. This bird has
absolutely nothing to do with this.
Even if you do get down from here
that way, they'll catch you again!
Having fun?
There's no way to
know that unless we try!
The only one we considered
dangerous was that "straw hat man."
It's no good.
Well, we can just lure them out one by
one starting with whoever's convenient
This isn't his kind of fight.
We're gonna kick the bucket
if we stay here anyway.
Right. It's because of our pride.
All his power is useless!
We were planning to lure you both
out by having this bird squawk,
So let's put up some ugly struggling!
to my "service set"...
Now to finish it with this!
I'll mix the Laughter Yellow on
your back with Sadness Blue...
There's no reason to die heroically
for these pieces of scum!
My motto is "big crimes via cheap tricks."
but he was just too obstinate.
Right?!
What the hell? Is he crazy?
Colors Trap: Tranquil Green!
I forgot...
Alright! Call for your owner!
He's bluffing!
There's no way he could do that!
There're many ways to defeat
enemies without actually fighting.
...the reason a long time ago!
Squawk especially loud
and we'll let you go!
He's merely acting tough!
Mr. 3, refill please.
Such nice tea...
Hey, me too.
You idiot!
What a cheeky runt.
You guys! Take time to savor it!
Fine! Want us to make you squawk?!
So... What happens now?
I'm pathetic. It seems I had
even lost the will to fight.
See? I told you you should've posed!
Call for the princess!
Ah!
That mountain is...
if I'm not mistaken...
Too bad for you!
I'll fight alongside you
and your fighting spirit!
How can you still be so calm about this?!
Call for help this instant!
What? Wh-What's wrong?
You can't be serious, right?!
Open your mouth, you damn bird!
How will you be able
to fight afterward?!
Oh, boy... What a huge duel!
This isn't good.
I'm running out of time...
Who knows?
But then we saw Straw Hat already
took himself out of the picture.
But... I plan to win.
Ah... Sorry.
Damn, they run away fast!
Who are these guys?!
They're off their rocker!
So we have no use
for that thing anymore.
Ahh! Let it go! I said sorry! Hey!
Karoo...
What kind of man is he?!
I don't have time to
mess around! Let it go!
But I've seen this
look somewhere before...
Nose Fancy Double Cannon!
The time-out signal has rung.
Hey, big lizard. You're in our way.
Princess Vivi!
What a stupid bird!
Having no prey isn't even funny... Damn...
Are you prepared not to die?
Why, you...!
You missed! Way to go, Karoo!
W-Wait! I'll fight, too!
Let me take care of it.
Are you the ones who
put a bomb in the alcohol?!
--Vivi!
--Alright, then.
10,000 Kilogram Press!
Let's do it, runt!
Yes, that was us. Who're you?
My turn! Special Attack: Lead Star!
There's the signal...
Don't be stupid!
What can you possibly do?!
Is he on the list?
No. He must be their friend.
But let's make him disappear, too!
It's quite active today.
We gotta go back to Luffy
and the others again!
You're going?! Your wounds from
that last battle still haven't...
So you interfered with the giants' duel!
It was them?! I'll kick their asses!
We're getting nowhere,
chasing them all around.
It's nothing!
We're both in the same condition!
Oh hello, Mr. 5.
Yeah.
You're the ones who
are going to disappear!
Hey, you guys!
I'm gonna kick your asses,
just so you know!
Ha! What an extravagant power you have,
building an improvised house in a jungle.
Oh? You're going to try
struggling, Miss Wednesday?
I didn't want to use it
on such small fries,
Making excuses during a merciless
fight to the death would spoil my name!
What?
Do you stand a chance
against us Officer Agents?
but there's no dodging this.
Let me tell you something, though.
This mission is still ours.
--Let's do it, Usopp!
--Yeah!
A .44-caliber,
six-shot flintlock revolver.
Peacock Slasher!
I don't want you to meddle in it.
Bird!
Take this! Special Attack: Exploding Star!
Luffy! Usopp!
We'll never goof up like that again.
Karoo!
A new South Blue model.
--Goof up?
--Hmm?
Master Broggy!
We've taken on your frustration!
That's not it. You two are weak,
Mr. 5, Miss Valentine.
It can fire continuously,
Yes!
Usopp...
and if I use it, the bullets are invisible.
Beat those guys up so much
they lose their original forms
Hey! Wait, old guy!
What a nice explosive blast!
Don't go!
and send them flying far off somewhere!
Nose Fancy Cannon!
You can't go, Dorry-san!
You need to keep still!
Luffy's acting that way because of
that paint the bad guys mentioned!
Yeah! I will!
Well, don't look so stern. Look at this.
You'll die if you push yourself too hard!
These guys spoiled
the old giant guys' duel!
They're related somehow!
I, Warrior Dorry, am here...
So you're the one with the
highest bounty in the East Blue?
I'd like to thank you for giving me
an opportunity to come to this island.
What a pity!
There was also some on his back
when I crashed into him earlier!
Usopp!
At the very least...
10,000 Kilogram Press!
No doubt about it!
My, how Navy Headquarters'
standards have fallen!
...I will fight to uphold the name of Elbaf!
If I can just do something
about the paint...!
--Whoa! What a weird head!
--Quiet, you!
Hurry!
Calm down, now!
Dorry the Blue Ogre and Broggy the
Red Ogre of the Giant Warrior Pirates.
--It's the number 3, and it's on fire!
--Shut up!
Break this pillar first, Luffy!
I've heard of them in an old tale.
We're about to turn into wax figures!
This is a wanted poster
from 100 years ago!
There's no need to be so upset.
We're not going to kill you just yet.
Oh? You're in trouble?
Yeah, but those guys
now live on this island.
No, there was no problem at all.
Hey! Your leg!
Yeah. I went about
halfway through, I'd say.
Their bounty then was
100 million Berries per head.
We only came to abduct you.
On Mr. 3's orders...
How is that no problem at all?!
200 million Berries
for the two of them.
Ahh. Such nice tea...
For now, could you bust
this pillar for us, Luffy?
200 million-Berry bounty heads?
But they're giants.
Such nice...
Mr. 3?! The Wax-Wax Fruit man?!
He's on this island?!
I leave the rest to you.
Superb criminals execute their
crimes by using their superb brains.
Alright, no problem!
Luffy! What are you doing?!
I wouldn't be so sure.
That's right.
He's a "candle man" who controls
the wax he secretes from his body.
Dunno what it is,
but let's break that thing!
Such... nice... tea...
All you have to do
is follow my instructions.
Alright! Got it!
If we give it a little thought,
we can cut through any mountain.
I'm a bit of a different person today!
A candle man?!
What are you doing, you idiot?!
Hurry it up! We're gonna solidify!
You've got me!
The world is awfully big
Ah, gentle song
so even if there is treasure somewhere,
Make it there for us
the odds are astronomical
So relying on dumb luck
won't get you anywhere
After a wave washed away
that little sand castle
So even...
...if someone stops me or
laughs at me from the shadows
You looked up at the passing
clouds with a sad smile
the ship will continue forward
If you find the world is full of enemies,
Bon voyage!
Forget about them!
I know I'm a fool, but I gotta go
I've got your back
The crazier the dream,
the cooler the ambition
Don't lose faith
I know I'm a fool, but I'm gonna fight
You've got me!
Ah, my love
The farther the sea,
the more heavenly it surely is
I'll hold you in my arms forever
Do everything you can, and you'll
get a little nearer to any horizon
You've got me!
Damn. I'm lost.
Gum-Gum Mallet!
Hey, you! Capture a big one this time.
Usopp! Can you let them
get away with this?!
Luffy! They've only just hardened!
There's still time to save them!
Nami has disappeared!
What am I gonna do?!
Alright! The pillar broke!
Ha! You'd better not bring back
a small lizard this time, either!
--Really?!
--We're gonna save you now, guys!
No...
Huh? Why didn't you run away?
Huh, Luffy?
A duel that's been interfered
with isn't a duel anymore!
We can't move!
I'm counting on you, Karoo! Run around!
Can you not stand this, either?!
Shut up, you two!
The wax has us stuck!
A man-to-man duel has just started!
Oh, that's why?
I refuse to let anyone else die!
Who is it?! Who's doing this?!
Show yourself!
Alright! Let's all three of us
go beat them senseless!
Hurry and break this set!
--It'll be hot, but endure it!
--Wake up, everyone!
O-Okay...
Hey, who are they?
No.
What?! The alcohol exploded!
Quit joking and hurry up!
Baroque Works!
Let's do it! Usopp! Bird!
So you're the ones...
It's damn strange.
Why hasn't anyone come back?
What should I do?
I don't feel like saving you guys!
That's the barrel we gave them!
What's going on?
How dare you violate the proud battle?!
You won't get away with it!
Yeah!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Devilish Candle!
Tears of Regret and Tears of Anger"
"Time to Fight Back!
Usopp's Quick Thinking and Fire Star!"
"A Hex on Luffy! Colors Trap"
"Luffy Gets Angry!
A Dirty Trick Violates The Sacred Duel!"
"Broggy's Bitter Tears Of Victory!
The Conclusion Of Elbaf"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!