Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
Here I go! Straw Hat!
Spring...
...Hopper!
You got stronger but I got stronger, too!
This technique is far more destructive than
it used to be!
"The Battle of Love!
The New Leader Sai vs. Baby 5!"
Bellamy! Stop!
Hey, you!
You're gonna die if you move around that much!
Shut up! Stop worrying about your enemy!
Charlestone!
Pica-sama!
Why is he attacking randomly?!
That jerk!
He doesn't care if they're his allies or foes!
Bring it on, you piece of stone!
--All right, come on!
--Okay!
I'm...
I'm being needed!
Say it more clearly!
I'm not gonna let you go!
Those are my orders! Until this is settled...
I'll never let you go!
What?!
"I'll never let you go"?!
He just proposed to me!
How could you possibly
interpret it that way?!
Land. Ouch!
Oh, he hurt his back?!
Ow, ow, ow...
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Ow, ow, ow, ow... Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
--There you go! Lao G-sama's...
--...Back-Pain Stance!
That fool...
Take this!
Geo-Fist!
Eye-Jab Strain!
EYE-JAB STRAIN
Icy Stiff Shoulder!
ICY STIFF SHOULDER
Poor Circulation Impact!
POOR CIRCULATION IMPACT
Chrysanthemum Chestnut Strained Back!
CHRYSANTHEMUM CHESTNUT STRAINED BACK
Immortal Warrior's Joint Pain!
IMMORTAL WARRIOR'S JOINT PAIN
Only Lao G-sama could've done it!
He's overpowering Don Chin Jao
who has a 500 million bounty!
As you get older, you understand pain
and it becomes sharper!
GEO-FIST
Geo-Fist!
THERE'S THE...
There's the...
..."G"!
Oh... Um... Lao G-sama...
Not this way, h-he's behind you.
G!
I'm on the other side of the fence!
That marriage!
You're talking to them?!
Were you listening, old man?!
I won't marry her!
What?!
Why are you that surprised?!
Why should I?!
Sai! You're arranged to marry Ooklicia,
the daughter of the Nihosui Army's leader!
Sai!
I know! I don't care who'll become my wife!
Arrange a political marriage
to merge Nihosui and Happosui
together, or whatever you like!
Oh no! Lao G-sama is getting ignored!
He'll get pissed!
What?!
He didn't hear a thing!
But wait! He is mad!
Look! He's letting off a steam of anger
from the top of his head!
No! He's dying!
--Of all days, he's dying a natural death today?!
--This shouldn't be how a battle ends!
What?! This can't be happening!
Lao G, don't die!
Lao G-sama!
Come back!!
Back... back... back...
Huh?!
What?!
He couldn't hear it clearly but he came back!
I'm glad!
The infamous Don Chin Jao got weaker, huh?!
You have no right to say that!
Oh no! Don Chin Jao is getting mad!
What are you doing, Sai?!
--They're not talking about the same thing!
--What?!
He's not hearing anything!
What am I doing?!
It's crooked.
Hey! Don't fix my collar!
Are you my wife?!
Stay away from me, Donquixote Family!
What's wrong?!
Wh-What's the matter with you?!
You creepy tramp! You're my enemy!
Why did you bring up
"marriage" all of a sudden?!
Why not?! You need me, don't you?!
What do you want me to do?! I'll do anything!
How idiotic! Then, do me a favor.
Kill yourself!
If we leave you guys at large
and you interfere with Straw Hat and the others,
it'll ruin our repayment to them!
We got to take care of
you Executives at least!
Prepare for it!
Is that it?
Okay! I'm happy to kill myself!
If it helps you!
What? N-No...
I love helping people more than anything!
Idiot! Don't! What are you doing?!
It was just a tit-for-tat!
It'll leave a bad taste in my mouth
if I gain victory through your self-destruction!
Leave her alone, Sai!
Why do you wanna stop your enemy from killing herself?!
Are you out of your mind?!
You're a leader of an army!
You got to be more ruthless!
Shut up, old man!
Don't tell me what to do like you're still my master!
Hey, you tramp!
Oh, I'm so happy...
I can help someone even
just by killing myself.
Why did you give birth to a child?
They're useless but they still eat a lot.
To reduce the number of mouths we have to feed,
go abandon her on a mountain.
Mom, where are we going?
Hey! Mom!
Mom?
Mom!
Mom, wait! Please!
Don't follow me.
No! Please! I'm gonna come with you!
You're useless.
Useless people like you...
...aren't needed by anyone!
Even by you, mom?
I'm not needed even by you, mom?
What? You want me to
subscribe 50 newspapers?!
I'm needed by them!
What?! Do you want me to marry you?!
I'm needed by him!
Useless people like you
aren't needed by anyone!
I'm needed by someone now...
I said "Don't," you stupid tramp!
You are the stupid one!
Old man?!
So powerful!
That's...
Sai!
You're bringing shame on the Happosui Army!
We don't need a guy like you
in the Happosui Army!
Sai! Are you listening to me?!
This is my problem! Stay out of it!
You fool!
Hasshoken Technique!
Don't tell me he's gonna do the head-butt
that can break an ice continent?!
I'm gonna hammer both of you
with my drill head!
Drill Dragon...
...Nail!
Old man!!
Wujiaogen Heel!
Useless people like you
aren't needed by anyone!
I'm needed by someone now...
Don't try to do such a silly thing!
Why...
Why did you stop me?
I just tried to help you!
By killing myself, I wanted to become a person
who is needed by someone!
You have been living in a world
where nobody has ever told you...
...that you're getting it all wrong?
Don Chin Jao's drill head is bent
as I thought!
I can't believe it! Have I really done this?!
Sai! I'm surprised that
you bent my drill head!
Are they gonna fight among themselves?!
Finally...
Finally, your power has awakened!
Your bloody, sweaty, and tear-filled training
has borne fruit at last!
Old man?
You did it!
The Hasshoken Technique has succeeded!
Sai! I'll give...
...your kick attack the
name "Drill Dragon Nail."
What?!
I'm sure your leg can even break the ice continent
into pieces now.
The Happosui Army is all yours now!
I'll cancel your arranged marriage!
You can do whatever you want now!
Old man!
Well done! Well done! Sai!
Old man! You're embarrassing me!
What a touching story!
The truth is, after the
fight against Straw Hat,
I've been suffering from chronic pain
and I couldn't fight like I wanted.
I'm getting older.
I'm happy that you're now...
Seal of G!
Old man!!
Lao G-sama!
Lao G-sama took down Don Chin Jao!
In addition, what happened to his body?!
Geo-Fist's ultimate technique!
Battle Insurance Fist!
BATTLE INSURANCE FIST
In preparation for illness
or injury or aging,
you reserve your muscle power
from your earlier years
and save it. It's a qigong technique!
So you'll have seasoned fighting skills
as well as power at a peak!
Is there anyone who can beat me...
...like this?!
So that's Lao G-sama's true power!
You monkey from Kano,
what do you want from me?
How dare you do that to my old man...
I won't forgive you!
What are you talking about?!
A weakling like you needs another
100 years of training to get
strong enough to challenge me!
To avenge my old man...
And to pay my debt to
Straw Hat and the others!
What a foolish monkey!
Do you really believe that
Straw Hat can take down the Young Master?!
I do!
Listen! Dressrosa belongs to the Young Master!
And everybody in this country is...
...slaves to the Young Master!
No matter how firmly you believe in Straw Hat,
you guys can't...
...get out of this Birdcage for
the rest of your lives!
Birdca"g"e! There's the...
..."G"!
You're quick, I'll grant you that.
But, even Baby 5, I won't...
...let you have her!
What?! Lao G!
Just wait, Baby 5!
I'm "g"onna bleed this idiot dry
and save you! There's the...
..."G"!
What am I supposed to do?
They're fighting over me...
It's dangerous! Stay away!
A monkey is a monkey after all!
If you used Baby 5 as a shield,
you could've had the upper hand!
What?
Baby 5 is ours!
She'd even kill herself if she's needed by someone!
Is there any other girl out there
who is as convenient as she is?!
Convenient?
I'll send you to hell with
this last secret technique!
BATTLE INSURANCE FIST
Battle Insurance Fist!
Expiration Devil Withdrawal Immolation!
EXPIRATION DEVIL WITHDRAWAL IMMOLATION
This is "g"onna be the last! There's the...
..."G"!
Hey, how about this?
That tramp...
If I defeat you, I'll take her for my wife!
What?!
Twinge!
TWINGE
Drill Dragon...
...Nail!
Young Master... I'm sorry!
Damn you, unfledged monkey!
You "g"oofy monkey! There's the...
..."G"!
Call me chieftain!
In the battle against the executives
on the second level of the plateau -
location of the Royal Palace;
LAO G - FELL
Lao G, fell.
Baby 5,
BABY 5 - FELL
fell, too.
BABY 5 - FELL IN LOVE
I'm not very competent but...
please be patient with me!
Backstabbed, manipulated,
and almost killed by
his once hero, Doflamingo,
Bellamy still challenges Luffy.
When he makes a final resolution after wavering
between friendship and his principles,
a devastatingly destructive strike has
Luffy's name on it!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Man's Pride! Bellamy's Last Charge!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!