Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air, off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari mae wo mita mono dake ga
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal, we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
a boy whose body turned
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy and the others formed
a pirate alliance with
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
and have come to Dressrosa.
Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
But caught up in the current king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along with the entire island.
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
Butterfly flowers that divert attacks!
Mil Fleurs!
The strong don't heed obligations!
Let me go back to Greenbit!
I know I'm an idiot but even an idiot has
his principles that he must stick to!
That's enough, Bellamy. I set you free.
Don't give me lip!
I'll squeeze the power out of you whatever it takes!
Butterfly Orchid!
Robin-san!
Straw Hat! This'll be my last fight!
Thank you for delivering the key.
Like you have always been.
I'll protect you from now!
Help me! Leo!
You gotta go along with me on this!
Now, come back!
Executives of the Donquixote Family!
Sticky Launcher!
I'll kick Mingo's ass for you, too!
"The Healing Princess!
Save Mansherry!"
Wait!
There's no need!
Do you remember this technique?
I'll sew you all up together
so you'll never get separated!
Here I go! Straw Hat!
He's still alive.
Spring...
Hey, hey, hey, Law.
Don't you think you have to give up by now?
Haute Couture!
...Hopper!
Patch Work!
Don't underestimate my Fighting Fish lineage!
What?!
Drill Dragon...
You better rest now, Law.
...Nail!
LEVEL 4 - THE SUNFLOWER FIELD
If you keep fighting, you
really are gonna die!
I'm very close to total victory...
Now, fight me, Gladius!
Even if I die, if I can take you down,
You annoying tramp! Nico Robin!
Young Master... I'm sorry!
Don't push your luck.
maybe I can remain in Doflamingo's memory
even a little bit!
Don't you think your opponents are
a little too disadvantaged?
Disadvantaged? Whoa-whoa...
Are you thinking this is a fair competition or something?
What the...
No! Don't tell me you... Gladius-sama!
I'm executing them here, Nico Robin!
There's a scary-looking guy
on the other side of the barrier!
Damn you, unfledged monkey!
I think you have that backwards.
You "g"oofy monkey! There's the...
..."G"!
"The Manly Duel!
Seor's Elegy of Love!"
The whole ground is inflating!
Commander-san,
you no longer need to look over your shoulder!
You know what'll happen, don't you?
I'll stay with Rebecca!
Call me chieftain!
You've been setting all of these up!
Thank you! I'm so appreciative!
I couldn't hold myself back from...
That jerk isn't worth risking your life!
--It's dangerous!
--Run!
"The Man's Pride!
Bellamy's Last Charge!"
becoming furious!
That's something I decide myself!
Hey, Bartolomeo! Everything'll
blow up along with the ground!
Let me get inside of your barrier!
--No way!
--What?!
What are you guys doing?!
If I open it, Robin-senpai and I'll be in danger,
plus, the enemies will enter, too.
Show us mercy!
Th-This is serious...
It's no use.
No matter how quick you are.
W-We're just carrying away the corpse of a defeated man!
Please let us go!
No, open it! I'm on your side!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 2
Lao G-sama got taken down!
Gladius-sama!
We'll be caught up in it, too...
You became very evil-looking.
He's not dead yet!
--It'll be fine. Because you guys are elite, right?
--What?!
Cabbage-kun.
Do you want something from me?
No! Even if it takes a couple days for him to wake up,
we want to treat him at least!
There's no need for us to stay here!
Open it!
How destructive...
Let's go back to Viola-sama and the others!
"Barrier-Barrier!
Homage Holy Fist Strikes!"
Please! Show some samurai-like mercy!
I heard that name before.
You're right.
Pop Rock...
Leo!
Please! Have mercy!
The Happosui Army from Kano.
...Fest!
Leo!
I'm begging you!
I'll keep it in mind.
Anyone can become our enemy anytime.
All right! Just go already!
I hurt my leg.
Thank you very much!
You can carry me on your back if you want!
Old man! Hey, old man!
I'm worrying about Rebecca
and I have to get up there now.
Don't die! Old man!
Carrying me in your arms is also okay!
"A Strong Wind and a Surge!
Hakuba vs. Dellinger!"
Then, I'll reserve two ceremonial halls, honey!
Boy...
Humph! He's pushing his luck! That idiot!
Here we go again! You're acting like a baby!
Ceremonial halls?! Honey?!
We'll teach him a lesson! He'll regret this!
If you really got hurt,
you can heal yourself!
For the wedding and...
THE FIRST FLOOR OF THE ROYAL PALACE
AT THE BACK OF THE CHAPEL
...the funeral...
You've always been a good runner
so let's just run to get out of here!
Not dead yet!
--Bring Dellinger-sama now!
--Hurry up!
Wow! Cool! She stopped him!!
Explode!
Then, I'll stay here!
Goodbye, Cavendish.
Dobin-senpai!
What?!
Here we go! You're being so fussy!
--You idiot!
--Put him on the stretcher now!
I knew it was too presumptuous
for a weakling like me
Ow, ow, ow...
I didn't ask you to help me!
Like I said, the way you laugh is weird!
Stop it!
You guys!
to try to protect you!
Grr! How dare you say such a thing!
How could you treat...
What?!
Do you want me to leave you here
for real?!
...an executive of the Family so poorly?
What's wrong with laughing while having fun?
Bah!
If you were outside,
it would've killed you instantly.
What in the world are you thinking?!
Charlestone!
GIOLLA
A  EXECUTIVE OF THE DONQUIXOTE FAMILY
Just carry her on your back already!
We gotta go!
Seems like you're not gonna stay quiet.
You jerk! If you were gonna let me in,
why didn't do so right away!
It hurts...
So sorry!
Humph!
I thought I was gonna die!
What's wrong with you?!
Is that how you thank someone who saved you?!
Honestly! You're selfish, capricious,
and short-tempered!
We're truly sorry!
Wait, Hakuba!
It's forgiven since you
apologize so genuinely!
You're really a troublesome princess!
I was covering you before that!
You gotta thank me, too!
What?!
No way!
Leo's back...
I won't forgive you like that!
She's nice to everyone besides him.
Who are you targeting?!
I didn't allow you to emerge!
Why doesn't he get it? Leo...
I've had enough!
I've gotta keep fighting!
Let me out!
What?! Now I let you in
and you wanna get out?!
I call this work "Penance"!
Oh, it's beautiful!
We have a problem!
They took Mansherry away!
Catch the Little People!
Tsk! He escaped!
Since you came in, why don't you
stay for a while, you selfish fool?!
You all! Put it somewhere people in
the palace can see!
They went that way! Don't let them get away!
One-trick pony fool!
Is this an inn?!
Offense must come after defense!
That's how it should be!
Yes, ma'am!
Sorry, Nico Robin. I almost cut you.
Wh-What a shame...
Anyway... I can't believe the executives
are getting defeated one after another...
But this is a crisis!
I won't let you in next time!
So that was Hakuba that
everybody is talking about.
I don't like it...
I have to let the Young Master know!
Let me in again when I'm in danger!
You're such an inflexible idiot!
Your alter-ego...
Giolla-sama!
Do you want me to assist you,
Pirate Hunter?
The Young Master includes
Mansherry's ultimate technique in his plan.
That's right...
I've just gotten word they'll carry in
Gladius-sama soon!
I'll teach you a lesson!
It's you.
He's bad news...
Why should I put up a barrier for you, jerk?!
Her ability to restore things
in exchange for shortening her life!
He just goes and attacks people at random...
My name is Elizabello.
Even Gladius?!
I have to get things going as soon as I can!
King Riku is an old friend of mine!
So this country belongs to my friend!
Oh yeah, Robin-senpai!
Even if something happens
to the SMILE factory,
Bring it to me!
Not just your limbs...!
Yes, ma'am! Right away!
My King Punch is a trump card
that I can resort to once an hour.
as long as we have the Heal-Heal
Fruit power on our side,
I will chop up your entire body, Nico Robin!
we can restore it. That must be what he thinks!
Did you figure out the stone man's ability?
Oh, great! She's alright!
What will she do?!
I will cut up everything!
I'll be there, Rebecca! Stay safe!
I did long ago.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Then, leave him to me.
--It's from the factory!
--Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Thanks but I will take him down.
What a cunning tramp! Nico Robin!
THE SMILE FACTORY
Oh, Seor!
If nothing is done, the... the...
I won't let you get in the way
of the top executives anymore!
You better save your "trump card."
The factory will be destroyed!
Seor! Defend the factory at all cost!
Go away, Hakuba!
I won't let you take control!
So hard-boiled!
We still don't know what's to come.
Catapult Pop!
Ouch!
Shut up! Stay asleep, Cavendish!
Franky...
Seor!
I'll save it as you say!
No! Dodge, Seor!
You don't know the meaning of this fight!
I'll take care of this!
Barrier-bility: Racket!
It's connected!
...Strong...
Viola-sama! This is the factory team!
I'll rip up everything!
...Hammer!
There's no point if I don't do it!
What's going on with Princess Mansherry
and Leo's group?!
Don't care! I'll let them
see a pool of blood!
I hope the modest and kindhearted princess is
not having a hard time...
What?! I won't let you do such a thing!
Oh! He dove into the ground again!
But I won't let you get
in Robin-senpai's way!
Fraland! He's gonna do it again!
It's like two people having a conversation!
Does he have a split personality?!
That stone jerk! What is he up to?!
Can't help worrying...
That fool! He's alive!
Dodge!
Well, things just took
a turn for the worse...
Advance! Robin-senpai! Go, go!
I will!
The worse?!
I will do it!
Meow-Meow...
No, I will!
Did something happen to her?!
Crest Head-kun!
No, me!
...Suplex!
I will, I will, I will!
Thank you!
Wait a moment!
I'll call Leo now so stay on the line!
S-She made a gesture with her eye,
a.k.a. a wink!
I will, I will, I will!
--I will!
Leo, can you hear me?
I will!
I'm sooo grateful!
I will! I will!
Oh, Viola-sama!
It's Leo!
I will!
Did it mean, "Good job, Crest Head-kun!
You can become my slave if you want"?!
We're on our way up the Rampart Tower now!
He's half-and-half!
Hm? What are you gonna do? What are you gonna do?
THE 4TH LEVEL - THE SUNFLOWER FIELD
Oh! Seor!
The ground is rippling like a flag!
Uggh! Shut up, Hakuba!
No no, you're being too presumptuous, Bartolomeo!
You're asking for too much!
We'll reach the chapel in the Palace soon!
How pathetic! Why don't you grovel in the dirt?!
Toy Soldier!
Leo, you have to hustle!
Mansherry is caught by Giolla
and is being forced to use her ability!
Buuut!
I'm the only Cavendish!
I'm starting to feel so high!
You were half-and-half just a minute ago!
Seor couldn't stay on his feet, either
What?! That's very bad!
I thought so! It's all connected!
Neither of them can keep this up!
Oh no! Hurry up, Leo!
Fraland!
Cavendish! You were in the barrier, too?!
The toy soldier who was crying and screaming
like a fool that day...
There they are! The Little People!
THE RAMPART TOWER
UNDERNEATH THE ROYAL PALACE
I know you can dodge that attack, Fraland!
Hey! I said you were half-and-half!
Too bad, Gladius! Blade of Beauty, Blue...
They're coming up!
That was you!
Shoot, shoot!
THE STAIRWAY TO THE ROYAL PALACE
Bracchium...
You've taken that same attack 30 times in a row now!
Why?!
Okay, it's all right now, Nico Robin...
Gladius-sama!!
Why don't you let go of me?
Stay out of this, Tontattas.
Are you telling me to
trust you after seeing that?!
Damn! They move like rats!
Yeah...
Seor has gotten the same punch 30 times, too...
Bring a bomb!
I'll blow them away along with the stairway!
Why is that?!
What?!
When somebody offers you a drink at a bar,
Let's settle this while you're at it.
if you're truly a man,
you can't pull your glass away!
We'll get there in a super hurry!
Hang on a little bit
more! Princess Mansherry!
Bartolomeo!
What?! Then, don't tell me you were...
This guy is one staunch dude. So I'm...
Barrier Bulls!
Do what I say already!
Scarlet!!
I'll blow you up along with the wall!
...not willing to shy away from his attacks!
You little princess!
The barrier is charging at us!
You're the late Scarlet's husband
and Rebecca's father.
You can't just get away by flying somewhere!
I'll receive all of his attacks
and still win at the end!
Robin-senpai! Your eye gesture is something
worth risking life for, to a man!
Don't think you can get away in one piece!
That's my Strong-style!
I can't do it anymore...
That bastard!
MANSHERRY
THE TONTATTA TRIBE -
CHIEF TONTA'S DAUGHTER (PRINCESS)
He'll rupture us along with the wall!
This is great!
I know you can't help being worried
but this is a manly fight!
We need to get down for now, Nico Robin!
There's nothing between us but hate, eh, Kyros?!
Let me go back to Greenbit!
Stop, Bartolomeo! Can't you see I'm here?!
No! Something could happen to Rebecca
while I'm doing that...
I'll win it at any cost so just you watch!
I can't help you anymore!
I won't let you guys become
their slaves again!
That's right!
Sorry, Cabbage!
But there's a reason I can't stop!
Leave it in my hands!
That's why I came here!
Shut up! Who did you call Boa Hancock?!
What is it?!
I won't let him harm Robin-senpai!
I'm feeling... so high!
Oh, oops... That was a good move!
I-I didn't say... even a
single word like that...
Good judgment.
I don't care!
Fraland!
Yes, if you take me down,
you can stop the rupture of the wall.
Feeling higher and higher, and
I'm running out of control!
But it's a steel cape. Watch out!
What are you talking about,
you fool?! Stop now!
Don't be such a baby!
You make me drunker than some cheap bar, kid.
I can't!
It's time to exercise your ability! Look!
Pop Hair!
Dellinger!
Don't forget what you just said!
Those executives that've been brought down!
Vipera Glaive!
Haven't you cleaned up the second level yet?!
Rebecca!
Gladius! What are you doing?!
It'll be over here soon!
This is nothing!
The people who fought against our executives,
however...
Come and help on the third level!
Nico Robin is trying to make her way up!
What's this?! It went numb!
Even though they gained victories,
they're terribly injured.
--Those hairs are poison needles.
--What?!
My hands are full with these two idiots!
--Bartolomeo!
--Crest Head-kun!
Ah! Roger! Sounds like fun!
Father-sama!
Damn! I let my guard down!
If you resuscitate the executives
with your Heal-Heal Fruit power,
I'm not...
Kyros!
I'm a Pop-Pop Fruit eater.
...that young now so let me finish
this up with my next attack.
all of the enemies will have no choice
but to face death!
I told you to...
There...
Seor! Can I say one thing before that?!
There'll be a big upset
in the battle situation!
In other words,
I'm a rupture human from head to toe.
...pay attention!
You're far away! Way too far away!
Boy... You're so persistent, you Longarm!
You know what I mean!
Now,
use the ability that recovered
Sugar earlier again!
What are you gonna do, Toy Soldier?
If you do something to me,
my body will burst up
I thought your body structure was odd.
You have something past your shoulders.
You said you'll receive all of my attacks!
He keeps targeting me...!
Take out the Watering Can
filled with magic water!
and tens of thousands of
times more poison needles
If you're as manly as your
word, take this and...
like the ones that just caught you...
Father-sama! I'll fight, too!
Now! Now!
...will pierce through those two up there!
You got a hole in your damn stomach
so why don't you drop dead already, Mr. Champion Fighter?
Now!
Yeah! Fight, Rebecca! I'll kill you!
...try staying alive!
But if you don't take me down,
you can't stop the rupture of the wall.
I happened to know something.
I can't do that!
They went outside!
Let's witness this manly fight to the end!
What are you gonna do?
You people are bad people who
trouble King Riku-sama.
I wanna see Kyros lose
both his wife and daughter!
You gotta have a sense of duty and obligation
in a man's world!
The explosion of my body will be so powerful
that you can't survive, of course.
Seor!
I don't wanna let down the guys
who got defeated already!
King Doflamingo is lying to us.
What?!
If you can get on your feet again by any chance,
it's my loss!
It means, either way,
Robin-senpai will get harmed!
Father-sama!
So what?!
You're nothing but the Tontatta Tribe!
I'll receive your final
attack with my entire body!
It's okay, Rebecca! Let me protect you!
I want to atone for Scarlet's death, too!
You're a fast learner, Bartolomeo.
I don't want to cure bad people anymore!
Oh! That doesn't sound like you.
Think, Bartolomeo!
All right!
What is my priority to protect now?!
Let me compensate for teaching you how to fight!
Cut the crap!
So...
That's obviously...
I've been living with regret and shame for it
until today!
He's swimming through the wall of the tower!
...Robin-senpai's body!
What is he up to?!
I can't let Robin-senpai fall from there!
So cute!
Since I got turned back into a human now,
I'll never let my daughter swing a sword!
To stop the rupture of the wall,
Cute!
Unluckily, today's weather
isn't so good but...
I must take that hedgehog down but...
Don't get fooled like that!
Who did you call
the once-in-a-millennium beauty?!
then, tons of poison needles
will hit Robin-senpai!
What happened to you all of a sudden?
...if I can keep flying upwards,
Again, I didn't say anything like that...
What should I do? Think!
I can see Russian...
Now!
Russian?
Think harder, Bartolomeo!
Now!
Yeah... I have a son named Gimlet, too.
Doesn't matter if it's up or down!
Just let go of me and run!
Help!
Well then...
But unfortunately, gravity persists.
I can't keep flying.
you don't mind if something happens
to your friends at the factory, do you?
Oh yeah!
There is somebody expendable
by Robin-senpai's side!
Hey! What are you talking about?!
I-If I heal your people's wounds,
they will harm somebody again, won't they?!
Cyborg, your back is flesh
and blood, isn't it?
Hey, Cabbage!
I'll bring down the hedgehog here so...
You're okay, now.
You son of a gun! You knew it - that's why...
...you protect Robin-senpai
using your whole body as a shield!
Here, drink this.
Don't give me lip!
I'll squeeze the power out of you whatever it takes!
Now, stop talking!
Or you'll bite your own tongue off!
Thank you very much!
Hey! Somebody!
Hey...
Help me! Leo!
Hey, Cabbage!
Even if Fraland is tough,
if he gets dropped from that height...
Somebody! Help me!
Shut up, Crest Head!
My friends are stuck in the cage at the Colosseum!
That bad one is taking over now!
Fraland!
Oh no... You're so persistent.
--Take me there.
--What?
He's so useless even at this crucial moment!
There are trapped prisoners, right?
Meow-Meow Suplex!
Shoot!
If you played dead or something,
I would've spared your life.
Y-Yeah... This way!
I got a hit!
Baby...
Robin-senpai is in danger from all sides!
How will getting on your feet help?!
Cub-san!
What should I do?! What should I do?!
...Buster!
Cub-san?!
Leo! What happened to him?!
Luffy...
Oh yeah!
Don't stop!
Maybe I can buy some time.
Go ahead, Leo!
I'll catch up with you soon! I'm okay!
THE ROYAL PALACE - THE FIRST FLOOR
Until Straw Hat beats the
hell out of Doflamingo,
You got stronger but I got stronger, too!
I got it!
we'll try to keep you guys from
getting in his way!
Let's get the second rat!
We'll do it together!
This technique is far more destructive than
it used to be!
What?! Where did it go?!
There is no victory in this world,
that somebody can win all by himself, brat!
Are you coming to attack, Bartolomeo?!
I can only put up one barrier at a time!
Hey, you!
You're gonna die if you move around that much!
That's the drawback but it won't matter!
Take out the Watering Can already!
Shut up! Stop worrying about your enemy!
I know now! That I admired the wrong man!
And how pathetic I am!
Robin-senpai!
If I can save you, I won't hesitate!
So you guys are trying to score a victory
by sacrificing your lives.
That hurts! You're hurting me!
Barrier Ball!
That's something losers would do!
The strong don't heed obligations!
Forget about the past!
Let go of Bellamy!
Blow up as much as you like!
That's...
We're in the unbreakable barrier!
...up to the winner to decide!
This fool...!
I'll give you the finishing blow!
This fool came to get killed by me.
Right, Bellamy?
Fraland!
Oh! He did it!
Crest Head-kun! Don't tell me you...?!
But turning around on the man
that I chose to admire
Are you willing to sacrifice yourself?!
You idiot!
because I couldn't get the response that I wanted,
is so disgraceful!
What happened to me?
His wounds got healed!
I know I'm an idiot but even an idiot has his principles
that he must stick to!
I think the Little Person's
teardrop fell on him...
Fashion Pop!
Her teardrop?
Straw Hat! This'll be my last fight!
Oh, so that's how it works!
I'm no ordinary human, either.
You gotta go along with me on this!
Crest Head-kun!!
That serves you right, Hedgehog!
Don't underestimate my Fighting Fish lineage!
You gave me your word...
This will stop the rupture of the wall!
...so it's my turn now!
Robin... senpai...
You got me there.
Sorry, Young Master.
Franky...
I see, little princess.
...Iron Boxing!
Stop, Bellamy!
I guess you can heal wounds
with your tears, too.
Shut up! This is...
He shows no mercy.
This is my way of settling things!
It's like a rain of punches.
Then, cry!
It was like this, huh?
Gladius! I'm here!
Russian...
Cry more!
The day that I met you
and the day that you stopped smiling...
Where are you?!
There's no reason for me to accept such a fight!
No!
A reason to accept a fight, huh...
Listen.
The era where pirates dream about things is over!
They were both nights of pouring rain
like this...
Come on! Shed more healing tears!
I did it! I saved Robin-senpai
successfully...
Gladius!
The big hidden treasure, One Piece...!
It hurts! Help!
Dellinger! Stay on the lower level!
It's dangerous here!
Those idiots who are blinded by dream treasure don't
notice the treasure around them.
We have a troublesome enemy!
Oh! That doesn't sound like you!
Leo, hurry up!
They're misled by those illusions and die.
Right away!
Gladius! Nobody can trouble us
when we fight together...
What's wrong, Viola?!
Nice try, you dumbass...
Giolla noticed
Mansherry's tears can heal wounds!
That's just drivel by losers!
When I see idiots chasing after dreams like that,
You missed by just a few centimeters...
What?!
She's beating her cruelly
to make her shed tears!
It wasn't my throat that you stabbed.
It was my shoulder.
I get disgusted!
What?!
Dellinger!
Princess!
I-I missed the crucial spot?!
I wasn't expecting rain, were you?
I'm all wet!
I, Mouji, will come save you now!
He was inflated and
Luffy!
I sure couldn't tell if it was
his neck or shoulder but...
You're soaking wet. What's so funny?
It's no use!
We have to count on Leo and Cub-san for now!
Get out!
Dammit!
Get outta this town!
You're a Devil Fruit eater, too,
so you know the deal.
I like... rain.
The princess of the Tontattas has power
to heal?!
Luffy! Zoro!
Forget the promise, beat them up already!
She's a Heal-Heal Fruit eater.
As long as I'm conscious...
--Do you like it?
--What?
The basis of its power is
healing wounds of living things.
Rain.
Zoro...
The rupture of the wall won't stop!
Don't take them on, no matter what happens.
No wonder the enemy wants it!
Watch as your friends getting blown away!
Dellinger!
That's right!
Giolla is trying to resuscitate the defeated executives
using that power now!
You were like that at that time, too!
Damn! How stupid am I?!
But...
Things that I don't like? Hmm...
If there's no reason to accept it, fine!
If she succeeds, there'll be a crisis!
Oh, pirates! I hate them to death!
What?!
Just stand there!
Nico Robin, I'm sorry!
That means, no matter how many times we beat them,
they'll come back endlessly!
What do you do for a living? Tell me.
I brought Hakuba under control!
I'm Cavendish now!
If you still think...
I-I work at a bank.
But I left half of me as Hakuba.
What...
...my determination is cheap!
There'll be... no end, will there?
I see...
What the hell is this...
Let go of me! I will kill you!
Wh-What's going on?!
I'll let you escape to the Sunflower Field
with Hakuba's quickness!
This is gonna be awful!
THE ROYAL PALACE - THE SUIT CHAMBER
I'll use Hakuba's capability!
--Leo, we're counting on you!
--Cub-san, go for it!
We have no other options! Let go of me!
Trust me!
D-Don't tell me...
Which of him is this?!
Wh... Who are you?
...Sugar is there, is she?
No time to think!
Hurry up!
She is!
Whaaat?!
Turn into a toy!
Is it you? Welcome home!
It's over.
Boy... You bought something again?!
D-Don't!!
Let me see it!
Pop Rock...
Oh, it's cute!
Thank you, honey!
Hey, what else did you buy?
...Super Arena!
They're coming back?!
You've got to be kidding!
You are...
Oh, this is cute, too!
All of our efforts will come to naught!
Robin-senpai!!
That's right!
You can do it! Leo!
How long will you keep up with
this pathetic little revenge game, Law?
So pathetic! You're so pathetic!
Go! Take back the princess!
That's right!
Move!
I like this barrier thing...
You never learn!
Do you wanna lose another arm?
No!
Honey!
All right.
I won't kill you right off.
I'll take time and torment you...
Damn! Dellinger...
Hey, honey, what should we name him?
Look.
Both of them are completely...
How about
There it is! The naughty room!
Huh?!
Gimlet.
I love that name!
What the... What has just happened?!
Trebol!
Why did you stop me?!
I found her!
It's your own body!
That shitty brat with horns
and all the other enemy soldiers...
Leo!
He gives you over to me!
Princess!
If so, why don't you...
...listen to me every now and then?!
He took down all of them...
You're too late!
Catch him!
Cien Fleurs! Spider Net!
There's a scary-looking guy
on the other side of the barrier!
I've been willing to give you one or both of my arms
from the beginning!
Now, come back!
Executives of the Donquixote Family!
You stopped Hakuba's sword for me,
didn't you, Cabbage-kun?
Wh-Who is that person?
He's really stupid! This jerk!
Honey!
Round 2 starts!
He looks like the cabbage guy
but his face looks totally different!
You're a complicated man.
Where did he go?
Pentachromatic Strings!
Oh, what's wrong? Good boy, good boy.
No way!
What am I supposed to do?
Oh, please don't cry!
How could they escape that rupture?!
Leo!
Outta my way!
You take care of Giolla!
I'm so relieved... Robin-senpai...
Room!
This is exactly the same
situation as what happened in the
Block D match at the Colosseum.
Counter Shock!
What?!
Beetle...
I couldn't save the one I had to save
so what am I doing here?!
...Uppercut!
Thank you for that one, you shitty brat!
What?
Gimlet died?
If it were him...
Fallbright!
A week ago today,
the day you left without notice,
What?!
If it were Luffy-senpai, he would have...
Sew, sew, sew, sew, sew, sew, sew!
his temperature went up suddenly
I'm the man who'll be King of the Pirates!!
I-I can't believe this!
Everybody's collapsed!
and I took him to hospital
but he couldn't make it!
Sew!
Sew...
--You're a liar!
--What?
Sew, sew, sew, sew, sew!
I'll send you to meet Corazon, Law.
You're a liar!
I called the bank repeatedly but they said
they don't have an employee like you!
I'll line them up and try again!
Please! Tell me the truth!
What do you really do for a living?!
There's no need!
Stop, Bellamy!
Sew, sew, sew, sew, sew, sew, sew!
What kind of money are we're living on?!
Sew, sew, sew, sew, sew, sew, sew...
Say it!
I'm still alive after all. I got lucky.
Hey! Can't you tell me?!
Is he the one who did it?
What?!
You're not worthy to be a father anymore!
Get out of my way!
Come to think of it,
he's still not coming yet. Straw Hat.
I'll sew you all up together
so you'll never get separated!
W-Wait!
Those outfits are undoubtedly Cavendish's.
Monkey D. Luffy! The Straw Hats!
Wait! Russian! It's still stormy outside!
But the face looks undoubtedly
somebody-else-ish!
Don't bother me!
His bounty went up again!
He's pulling ahead rapidly!
Stop following me!
What the hell is this?!
So what-kinda-vendish is he?
Haute Couture!
It's not what you think, Russian...
Patch Work!
The reason I can't tell you everything is...
What?!
The Gum-Gum Fruit techniques are like this?
How can you be so relaxed
in a situation like this?
Pirates! I hate them to death!
I-It scared me!
He was so fast and I couldn't see him!
Law!
Russian!
Where are you?!
Russian!!
Who the hell are you?!
Hey, stop it!
Luffy-senpai!
L... Leo came...
Doflamingo said he sets me free!
Go home now!
Hey! Aren't you Cabbage?
Leo came to save me...
Russian...
Do you know what it means?!
I got fired from the Family!
Ring, ring, ring...
He's like a prince!
That's a good thing! Mingo betrayed you!
Because of the rain,
Art... it... is...
there was a mudslide right above your wife
and she was caught.
So I should side with you now?!
Don't tell me it's... Luffy-senpai?!
I told you!
I can't betray my principles like that!
Her condition is quite serious and...
Gum-Gum...
...Thor...
In a vegetative state?
Principles that even an idiot like me must stick to!
Non-Drill Dragon...
Yes, she is unconscious and...
...Elephant Gun!
...I'm afraid if she stays like that,
...Non-Nail!
He made it! That was really close!
she'll never be able to
demonstrate her feelings again.
Bellamy!
R-Really?!
Ninja Woman-dono!
I don't know how long
her body can last, either...
Sticky Launcher!
No one has been revived
and he finished off Giolla!
Look at you!
Yeah!
You can't cut my barrier with a sword!
Small person! Great job!
Nice try, huh?! Huh?!
He's so strong!
I wasn't wrong about him!
Mansherry has been saved!
If only you hadn't met a guy like me,
you would've...
Yeah!
Ha! No matter how fast you can move,
it's useless against my ability!
Luffy-senpai is the man who'll become the
Thank you, honey!
King of the Pirates someday for sure!
He's still alive.
Princess!
Hey, hey, hey, Law.
Don't you think you have to give up by now?
THROB! THROB!
See, look! When I'm crossing my fingers like this,
nobody can break the barrier!
I'm sorry!
I didn't wanna lose you...
Compared to him,
I should be ashamed of myself!
So I lied!
You better rest now, Law.
Leo! I was scared...
Homage Holy Fist!
No! There's a hole!
We see that man often these days...
Princess! You gained some weight again.
Luffy-senpai...
--I heard he's taking care of his wife.
--Oh...
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 3
My skills aren't good enough now
THE TONTATTA PRINCESS - PRINCESS MANSHERRY
RESCUED
Stand up, Gladius!
but I'll become stronger and stronger and...
He's coming to see her
everyday bringing flowers...
Why are you crawling, slinking around?
What are you thinking?!
Barrier-Barrier...
The same old...
I'm envious.
What happened to you?!
If you carry your jokes too far...
--But she is...
--What?
I'm very close to total victory...
THE ROYAL PALACE
Now, fight me, Gladius!
Surely someday,
I wanna hear her response...
Don't push your luck.
I'll become a man who can help you!!
I wanna hear her voice...
Hey! Who did you just take glance at?!
Don't do anything stupid! Hey! Hey!
Once more...
...Pistol!
What the...
No! Don't tell me you... Gladius-sama!
Once more...
Don't!!
I want her smile.
The whole ground is inflating!
Y-Your body is all beaten up so...
I barely won with my senpai's power...
You know what'll happen, don't you?
You've been setting all of these up!
Once more...
Don't go after Robin-senpai!
...if you keep fighting,
you really are gonna die!
Anyway, I'll never team up with...
--It's dangerous!
--Run!
...such a troublesome guy!
Russian, look.
I found the same bonnet
that Gimlet used to wear!
Hey, Bartolomeo!
Everything'll blow up along with the ground!
You just keep taking hits without trying to attack
and still...
Don't you think this looks like him?
Since he resembled me.
Let me get inside of your barrier!
--No way!
--What?!
It's quite noisy down there, too.
you worry about your enemy!
How confident you are!
If I open it, Robin-senpai and I'll be in danger,
plus, the enemies will enter, too.
On an unstable battlefield like this,
But I'm sure even you must've gone through
some unexpected event...
even a gladiator from the
Colosseum would totter and fall!
Once more...
No, open it! I'm on your side!
Please smile!
Gladius-sama!
We'll be caught up in it, too...
...that shattered your confidence!
Right, Rebecca?
--It'll be fine. Because you guys are elite, right?
--What?!
Vipera Glaive!
I-I'm sorry! I've gone way out of line...
Don't!
Run, Rebecca!
You can't defend yourself from it!
Open it!
If someone sees me wearing this...
Even if I die, if I can take you down,
Butterfly flowers that divert attacks!
Mil Fleurs!
maybe I can remain in Doflamingo's memory
even a little bit!
Pop Rock...
Oh! Robin-senpai!
...Fest!
I'm relieved! I'm so relieved!!
Butterfly Orchid!
Robin-san!
Once more...
That tramp...
Robiland!
Once more...
Your mission is accomplished, Rebecca.
It's no use.
No matter how quick you are.
You became very evil-looking.
Thank you for delivering the key.
Cabbage-kun.
Do you want something from me?
Russian...!
I'll protect you from now!
Goodbye, Cavendish.
As the top executive Diamante's
merciless attacks rain down on him,
Seor Pink's life-changing meeting with
his beloved woman,
While Robin and the others carry on
the heated offensive-and-defensive battle against Gladius,
Falling into the massive trap that
Gladius, the rupture human, set up,
With their executives getting
defeated one after another,
the Donquixote Family starts
getting driven into the corner!
Kyros gets driven to the verge of death!
Robin is in an inescapable fix!
Dellinger, the executive, joins in,
changing the tide of the battle.
and his entire melancholic, romantic,
eventful life are revealed
However, Giolla put a hideous
secret maneuver in motion,
But just as Diamante, the man
who killed his wife in the past,
When it seems like
they can't avoid falling into a deadly crisis,
To save his idol who is
in a desperate situation,
which will resuscitate all the executives!
is about to take his beloved
daughter Rebecca away from him,
as the fight between Franky and Seor,
each staking their lives on the line, comes to a climax!
With this great danger that will turn
the tide of the battle closing in,
Bartolomeo who is covered all over with wounds,
the sleeping weapon, Hakuba, awakens and
an extreme-speed battle begins!
risks his own life and
launches a deadly attack!
the undefeated warrior Kyros'
unyielding spirit flares!
the little warrior Leo's
courageous fight begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Strong Wind and a Surge! Hakuba vs. Dellinger!"
"The Manly Duel! Seor's Elegy of Love!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Barrier-Barrier! Homage Holy Fist Strikes!"
"The Healing Princess! Save Mansherry!"
"Stardust of Death! Diamante's Storm of Vicious Attacks!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!