Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed
a pirate alliance with
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
Meanwhile, Zoro and Pica, too, are...
The tragedies that fell on Dressrosa...
Compared to them,
Death Enjambre!
Meanwhile, Zoro goes after Pica
who is closing in on King Riku...
This is Donquixote's country!
I'm sorry!
I didn't wanna lose you... So I lied!
this is not even pain!
Commodore...
That bastard!
I'll become a ball of the
anger of this country
Father-sama!!
Is he going to kill the king?!
...Killer...
Russian, look.
I found the same bonnet that Gimlet used to wear!
...Bowling!
Look out for what's falling onto you, Kyros!
How silly are you to stumble now?
Don't you think this looks like him?
Since he resembled me.
and bring you down!
The nine mountains and eight seas,
Half Moon Glaive!
...constitute one world!
I won't forgive you!
A thousand of them form a small chiliocosm!
I won't forgive you! Diamante!
And when I gather and cube that chiliocosm,
Trueno...
Once more... Please smile!
Well said, Rebecca! Don't forgive me!
there's nothing I can't cut!
...Bastardo!
I'll save you now! My friend, King Riku!
Fight me! I'll kill you with these hands!
Wait a sec, you king of somewhere!
Three-Sword Style Secret Technique!
I-I'm sorry! I've gone way out of line...
Like your mother!
Drop...
If someone sees me wearing this...
Hey!
Give me two minutes.
...your sword!
The Billion-fold World...
For a decade, you...
...Trichiliocosm!
The one that Zoro was keeping off!
Pica!
...have followed your mother's wish!!
"Stardust of Death!
Diamante's Storm of Vicious Attacks!"
Is King Riku there?!
Diamante...
You've been fighting in the Colosseum
but you still haven't hurt anybody!
A top executive of the Family shouldn't look
so pathetic like that.
The nine mountains and eight seas...
There's nothing I can't cut!
Plan 5.
Go to hell!
Your hands are still clean!
Fly in the sky and chop him up!!!
Three Thousand Worlds!
Let's do that!
Those are the hands...
But, it's falling onto us anyway!
...in which your mother
Scarlet's spirit lives!
King...
"A Decisive Battle in Midair!
Zoro's New Special Secret Technique Blasts!"
...Punch!
"Moving Across the Ground!
The Giant Statue Pica's Surprise Maneuver!"
Mother-sama...
There's no need to bathe those
hands with the blood of a
devil like him after all these years!
Good work!
"So Long!
Bellamy's Farewell Blow!"
Good morning, Russian.
Rebecca!
Stop, Bellamy!
Or you really are gonna kill yourself!
I won't let you wield a sword!
Straw Hat! You bastard!
You're still saying that?!
"Trueno Bastardo!
Kyros' Furious Strike!"
I'll say it again and again!
Your body's reaching its limit now!
Stop fighting...
No way!
Nobody can move in this deadly stardust!
Bellamy! That's enough!
Has your sword ever broken?
Shut up! I decide where I'll die myself!
You're gonna become the King
of the Pirates, right?!
Well, maybe, several times...
Kyros!
You broke mine, too!
Then you shouldn't get
stalled by crap like this!
Is your body a ball of iron?!
--If nothing is done...
--Grandfather-sama and the others will...
If you were clad in Haki,
it wouldn't have broken,
even if it's the same sword.
Sniper King-senpai! Run!
That's so cool, old man!
He lost his son and
his wife got in a big accident.
Straw Hat!
You must feel ashamed of
having even a nicked edge.
No, it must be painful enough
to make you wanna scream...
No wonder his spirit has broken...
Every sword could become the Black Blade.
This guy is crazy...
Black Blade?
Until you master it, no drinking.
Pink! What the hell has happened to
your sense of fashion?!
Pirate Hunter!
Are you a ball of stupidity?!
What?!
How long will you make me wait?!
Hey, Director!
Hey! You're trying to be funny, aren't you?!
Father-sama!
Huh? If you mean Commodore, that's me.
It was obvious.
Whatever! You threw a person
like a bombshell earlier, didn't you?!
What happened to your luxury suits?
Feeling pain...
We're not here to have a one-on-one match!
That's embarrassin"g"! There's the "G"!
Feeling pain is proof that I am a human!
As long as there's an enemy,
the fight won't end!
I'm going out.
I know you people don't understand!
Prepare yourself, King Riku!
--Look! There goes a pervert!
--A pervert is passing by!
Don't push yourself, Father-sama!
You can't even move!
Disgusting!
The hopelessness of being forgotten
by somebody you love!
Fall back, Rebecca!
Don't walk around wearing that!
Even if it means death,
I have to bring down all of them
Oh, please! He's so creepy.
No nicks on the edge.
Pica-sama!
Scarlet!
He's still wearing that?
and put this country back
in the hands of King Riku-sama!
Just go ahead and crush up
King Riku and God Usopp!
Why?! Why didn't you wait for me?!
Oh! There's a freak!
Hey! No!
Zoro! Zoro, are you alright?!
I have to ask.
I see!
--I won't let him do it!
--Shoot! Shoot!
What is King Riku to you people?
I must've slipped out of your mind, too!
Of course, I am!
Rebecca. You have been cursed at repeatedly
because of him.
Our promises...
...and memories, as well!
Scarlet! Stay with me!
Kyros. You lost your leg
because you were serving him,
--R-Retreat!
--Run!
I don't know who you are but...
and you were forced to live as a toy!
Did anybody get hurt?
If it weren't for him...
...my daughter is waiting for me, hungry.
No, thanks to you, Issho-san!
Screw you! You people framed him!
King...
Please...
To me, King Riku-sama is a
father-in-law and someone
...Punch!
It's me! Kyros!
Please...
I owe so much to for taking care
of me since I was a bad kid!
The King Riku Family was
known as a venerable family
that understands the true meaning
of peace, even worldwide!
I'm sorry, Russian! I'm late!
The debris is falling onto us!
Stop it!
Scarlet!!
--Get away now!
--Run!
This country wasn't as wealthy
and prosperous as it is now.
Russian...
But that doesn't mean
the people were unhappy!
I can't believe I'm losing her like this!
Your target is me, isn't it?!
This is hell!
Don't create any more havoc!
It's terrible!
With these tin arms, I can't even feel...
The sky is clear and
flowers are blooming proudly.
Tank! Get everyone out of here!
...your warmth as you're dying!
A great country filled with gentle hearts!
Yes, sir!
Everyone! Get out of here now!
Get off of this plateau!
That's what Dressrosa really is!
Scarlet!!
Money and jewels are nothing but stones
and they have no heart or soul!
The act of living is true happiness.
That is what he told us!
Issho-san...
--Now, evacuate the people quickly...
--Y-Yes, sir!
That's who King Riku-sama is!
--Run!
--Hurry up before it's too late!
You people don't understand!
Kicking you bastards out and having
him sit on the throne again
Just run!
The agony of being unable to feel
whatever you touch!
is what the whole nation wants now!
Hey, honey, what should we name him?
The tragedies that fell on Dressrosa...
Compared to them,
Everyone! Retreat!
I understand.
King Riku-sama, you need to leave now!
How about...
Gimlet.
this is not even pain!
What? He disappeared?
I love that name!
Hurry up, Father-sama!
What's going on?
Issho-san! The evacuation is complete!
Viola! Tank!
Take everyone and go down now!
You called me a ball!
Okay.
His target is me! Go!
I'll become a ball of the
anger of this country
Russian...
That's why you need to run, King Riku-sama!
Charlestone!
To me,
Please hurry!
No! If everyone else can get away
while he's targeting me,
and bring you down!
these outfits are worth more than
any expensive suit.
Wh-What is that?! It scared me!
He went to the third level this time!
that's fine!
How powerful this guy is!
Thanks to you, Issho-san, for
letting them float temporarily,
Damn, that fool!
He's supposed to fight me!
Your glory is like something
from 20 years ago!
Your Majesty...
we have no casualties.
Doesn't he wanna fight?!
Luckily, we had set downtown
as an evacuation zone, too.
I see! Then, I'll do as you like!
That's good.
Because only while I'm wearing these,
Don't underestimate my true sword skill!
Did you see it?!
Either way, I can't get him
if he moves around in the plateau!
That giant statue got cut completely in half!
you smile...
Does it mean the top
executive got taken down?!
Be ready to die
once you enter my range again!
Half Moon Glaive!
Pica-sama got taken down!
Charlestone!
He's that strong but he didn't
enter the competition...
Pica-sama, please stop!
His palm is as wide as a town!
--Pica-sama!
--Help!
Kyros!!
What a humble guy.
That strong man works under Garp's grandson?
Diamante!!
I wasn't expecting rain, were you?
I'm all wet!
You're soaking wet. What's so funny?
He's good!
We managed to protect King Riku in
the end so I'll let it go but...
That jerk! He's harming the injured!
I like... rain.
It's coming! Watch out!
Okay, honey!
D-Don't cling to me!
Do you like it?
Zodo-senpai!
Boy! We're gonna be husband and wife
so don't be shy like that...
Did something happen to Kyros and Rebecca?
Rain.
--King Riku-sama!
--I'm glad!
Viola...
You betrayed us, Baby 5!
Rebecca is fine.
Steel Mill!
Look out!
What the hell?
It's a very intense fight.
Pirate Hunter, Orlumbus!
What are you gonna do?!
What? The factory is...!
The factory that came out
of the ground exploded!
Sai!
I can even feel it through my Clairvoyance...
You're really sure about this?!
Honey!
What's going on?!
This technique isn't meant
for throwing someone safely!
Brother Kyros' pain and anger...
Just do it already! We don't have time!
Oh, you're okay! Let me help you out!
You haven't dropped dead yet?!
You monster!
--Let's go for one more!
--Yeah!
I'll crush you up along
with the King's Plateau!
No, you fool! Old man, behind you!
There!
You pieces of crap!
Seems like the rain that you liked so much...
Charlestone!
Yeah!
Blow it to bits!
The factory that made us suffer!
...stopped.
We'll never be fooled and
forced to work again!
That jerk!
He's only going for people
who aren't willing to fight!
That son of a gun!
--You ready?!
--Yeah!
Seems like you've reached your limit!
The stone jerk!
Kyros!
Hey, hey, Pica got taken down
and the factory got blown away, Doffy.
That's enough, you fool!
How could you mess with the wounded ones?
Roronoa.
Just as the iron balls stopped raining down.
Bite Stone!
One-Sword Style Demon Horse!
But the losers will come back!
The factory will be rebuilt!
Honey!
I'll finish you off myself
to end this for you!
Say, Roronoa Zoro.
King Riku! You're not a king!
Do you know who's on the old King's Plateau?
Just keep being excited over nothing!
Like Scarlet that you two loved so much!
You're not cut out to be a king, either!
We have the Heal-Heal Fruit power eater,
Mansherry on our side!
The king of this country!
"Former"!
Commodore...
What's your point, you jerk?!
Señor!
Don't you think it's unfair?
Fraland!
What's unfair?!
Invasions always happen in the world.
Why does only Doffy have to take blame?
Diamante! What a jerk!
Rebecca-sama!
He mentioned Sister-sama again!
Cut the crap!
Robiland! Are you okay?!
Damn you, Diamante!
That's pathetic...
I'm sorry! King Riku-sama!
Your Majesty, if you won't
run, neither will we!
On the old King's Plateau,
What are you thinking of, crying?
there aren't only the former
senior officials of this country
Our desperate search ended in vain.
--Your Majesty!
The man named Diamante was ahead of us and...
but also, those samurai and God Usopp.
Brother.
...Scarlet-sama was found in the town and...
Commander!
You must be Commander Kyros!
I heard the whole nation seeks
King Riku's restoration.
--Your Majesty!
Yeah! So you rescued the princess, Leo!
...got shot...!
You look so gallant!
You're looking just like the statue!
So what?!
That pisses me off! Doffy is the only king!
You killed Sister-sama?!
King Riku! Did you clear up the
decade-long misunderstanding
It's the other way around.
Oh yeah, she was your older sister!
Oh, you're hurt so bad!
I'll heal you right away!
and win back your popularity?
She was buying food at a market in the town.
If we see each other again someday somewhere,
Wait!
If she could've controlled her hunger,
she didn't have to die! What a fool!
Why did you come back?! Run! Now!
You must be Princess Mansherry.
let's have a drink.
I heard a lot about your power
but there must be a limitation for it.
And tell me...
Let go of me, Tank!
Don't use it on me.
Please don't jump the gun!
...about the woman named Russian.
But you're bleeding all over!
I can't take it anymore!
How cheesy!
THE BATTLE AT THE SMILE FACTORY
We'll stay in the Palace, too!
I'm fine. I'm conscious, as well.
A pacifist like you...
To protect you!
THE WINNER - FRANKY
Most importantly, I'm glad that you're okay.
It must've been tough.
...couldn't protect a country!
Did you forget that?!
If you're willing to use your power,
A country is all about armed might!
What the...!
What's going on?!
A guy who can't destroy
an enemy of his country...
there are people who need
it all over the country!
Look at that!
...is not qualified to be king!
What?! This is...
I'll pulverize you along
with your cheap ideal!
You...
...and you!
King Riku!!
I won't let any of you survive!
Now, you guys! Are you all ready?!
You guys lost to us a decade ago!
Th-The town is falling onto us!
Losers should accept their lot
and face their demise miserably!
Yeah!!
This damn factory that gave
you Tontattas a hard time!
Is this Dressrosa?!
...Killer...
I heard so much about the situation
from Leo and the others
Destroy it!!
...Bowling!
Diamante!!
but I didn't expect it was this bad...
My strike will rend even the ground!
But looks like they destroyed
the factory successfully.
Let's go!
The battle is coming to a crucial point now!
Thank you, Fraland!
That jerk...
Inhel and the others, they pulled it off!
There! There!
There!! There!
This country has been taken over
by Doflamingo's trap.
There!!
Whether we can restore it
to King Riku's hands...
I hope you can dodge it
with your one leg that's been shot!
...or we let it fall as a
hopeless country again...
Tontattas, good luck...
I won't dodge!
Our hope is in the hands of some pirates now!
If you won't dodge, you're just an idiot!
I'll leave all the mess
up there in your hands...
Pirates?
You're right!
Luffy...
I couldn't protect the
country so I'm incompetent!
With all my heart and soul!
I'll never sit on the throne again!
This sword carries a decade worth
of pain that this country suffered!
King Riku-sama!
At the top of...
It started to move again!
Wh-What will he do?!
I'll take back peace!
...that Royal Palace...
But...
Half Moon Glaive!
...I tried my best to be a good man!
Luffyland... Lawland...
This is Donquixote's country!
Trueno...
Help the injured first! Call the rescue team!
Those two are our last resort.
...Bastardo!
Yes, sir!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
Luffy... Tra-guy-kun...
The nine mountains and eight seas,
...constitute one world!
Lucy...
A thousand of them form a small chiliocosm!
Showtime!
And when I gather and cube that chiliocosm,
there's nothing I can't cut!
Now, let's have showtime together!
Three-Sword Style Secret Technique!
You got to show me already!
To be a good man?!
It's gonna walk! Run!
The image of a father and a daughter
dying miserably together!
If you say I'm not allowed to live
without committing a murder,
The statue started to move! Run! Run!
I'd rather choose to die voluntarily!
There's no future for a mass-killing nation!
Half Moon...
Your Majesty! You're our only king!
...Glaive!
That's why the good can't make history!
Whoa-whoa, don't tell me...
Kyros!
I thought you were furious earlier...
Because they will die like you!
...forgetting your place!
Wh-What the hell... What is he up to?!
Did you think that I'm just a talented matador
who can make things ripple?!
Don't think that you'd be the strongest
in the Colosseum's history forever!
I just got into the Rampart Tower.
Something bad is gonna happen, it seems.
I have a solid strength.
Sabo-kun, can't you get here? Where are you?
The current hero of the Colosseum is
me, Diamante-sama!
I'm helping trapped prisoners run
at the Colosseum.
That bastard!
The Billion-fold World...
Is he going to kill the king?!
That place is too far from here.
...Trichiliocosm!
There aren't that many things
that you can handle by yourself, are there?
If I could handle it, I
wouldn't have called you!
It might affect Luffy-kun!
--I'll be right out!
--Boy!
The current hero of the Colosseum is
me, Diamante-sama!
I don't care about the title!
But I can make things ripple as well!
Zoro! Are you alright?!
Army Bandera!
Zoro! Do you need a hand?!
Thank you! Robiland!
I'm okay! I didn't get a scratch!
That's great!
--Run!
--It's gonna crush us!
Father-sama!
Nice try! You almost got me!
Can't be helped!
Good! He got away into the upper body!
You've been running around
the country all day today
Roronoa!
and fighting while protecting your daughter's life
on this wavering ground!
Father-sama!!
With just one leg! If you
were an ordinary person,
Zoro! Thank you! I thought that was it!
you would've been unable to move already!
Father-sama, you need to get treatment now!
Zoro-dono! Well done!
Father-sama...
Pirate, thank you!
I couldn't believe my eyes
when I saw you cutting that giant statue
Viola-sama, how's Kyros-sama doing now?
with your swords!
He's totally exhausted...
Wait a sec, you guys!
You'd better wait to get excited
until that suffocating cage disappears!
Zoro!!
Brother Kyros is almost
reaching his limit, too.
Prepare to fire!
Please avenge Scarlet-sama...
Shoot!
Dead stones...
Shoot! Shoot!
You don't have to concern yourself about
my having one leg!
Active stones...
Although I couldn't protect your mother,
No matter how many pieces they divide into,
his main body will definitely...
Oh?
I'm gonna protect you to the end,
with my life!
It's still there, which means
the key man hasn't got taken down yet.
...be in one of them!
If I wanted to use it as an excuse,
I wouldn't have come to this battlefield!
Until the day you are filled with happiness,
It won't be divided up!
I dedicated my missing leg to someone
I owed a lot to and I'm proud of it!
That jerk!
I will always be by your side!
That's why he drove me out this far!
Okay. Then, I don't have to hesitate
to strike your weak point!
I can't catch up to him!
It's too boring for me to just deliver a
final blow to the already-fatigued you!
I totally got played!
Gotta do something or else...
How about a game?!
It'll take him just one punch
to shatter the King's Plateau!
Whaaat?!
Usopp and the king will be crushed
and die in an instant!
Stop! Stop, Bellamy!
The last showtime!
Is there any way to prevent it?!
Stop!!
Pirate Hunter!
We won't let you get in Pica-sama's way anymore!
--Those are...
--...Confetti?
So annoying!
Viola-sama!
There's no ground he can
get away to, in midair!
That's right! They look
like just paper but they're
Don't tell me Army Commander Kyros got...
Zoro!
actually something that I made to ripple.
It's no good!
He took down Diamante!
Come on out, Pica!
If we let him go!
Now, I'll undo my power.
But there's no way to stop that thing!
Ripple Release!
He took down the formidable Diamante?
Bellamy! Why...
Spiked iron balls!
Why do you wanna go that far?!
You are...
Look how beautiful they are!
It's like stardust!
--Grandfather-sama!
--Usopp!
How long are you gonna stay hiding?!
You are fooled and used by Mingo!
--Robin-san!
--I guess we have nowhere to hide.
By cornering me,
That bastard!
Is it true, Viola-sama?!
Robiland! Please protect Rebecca!
He said he set you free but...
you think you already win?!
Yes... Brother Kyros won!
Commander-san, you're in danger, too!
PLAN 1
That's enough, Bellamy. I set you free.
Plan 1.
I'm going to be fine!
Rebecca is okay, too.
PLAN 1
LONG-DISTANCE SLASH
Long-distance slash.
I bet you're upset. You know what's coming.
Nico Robin protected her...
You think you can beat me if you
can cut those stones, don't you?!
Like you have always been.
Yes, those are stardust that
can kill an entire army!
I can't believe he took
down the top executive of
You didn't run, and fight me to death...
the Donquixote Family...
I won't get cut when I'm clad in Haki!
No, it has to travel too far
so it won't be powerful enough.
He took down the hero of the Colosseum...
It's extremely difficult to stay alive!
I can't take him down.
That's absurd!
I'm glad we're at the Sunflower Field!
He knew that's what you would do, didn't he?!
Kyros was the original undefeated hero
of the Colosseum!
PLAN 2 - JUMP UP AND GET ON TOP
Plan 2. Jump up and get on top!
Mil Fleurs!
Haki, huh?
If I knock you off from here, you'll lose!
I think so! But so what?!
You're blooming beautifully, I'm sorry!
We thought no one can beat the
Donquixote Family but they've
I respect that man!
If he at least recognizes how I die,
been taken down one after another!
Only if your Haki is stronger than mine!
Struggle as you like!
I can't ask for more!
Of course, mine's stronger!
You're no match for me!
Adios!
Don't lie! You just have no choice!
Kyros!
Death Enjambre!
It's impossible.
Because you're a man!
Army Commander Kyros!
PLAN 3
If you know that much, shut up and fight!
SHOUT OUT, WARNING USOPP AND THE OTHERS
Plan 3.
Flower Umbrella!
Shout out, warning Usopp and the others.
Do you know what they call people like you?
But you'll die for nothing!
That was close!
Not just Señor Pink at the factory...
Oh, she handles it quite well.
Usopp!!
Pay attention!
No, I can't ask for more.
but the other executives have been
brought down by the warriors
Frog in the well...
Know how big the world is.
If I'll be sent to kingdom come...
who side with Straw Hat Luffy.
Kyros!
Oni... Giri!
There are four major fighters of
the Donquixote Family left!
...by another man that I admire!
There's no way he can hear me from this far.
An army that gets defeated by an attack
like this mustn't be that good!
Bellamy the Hyena and...
There's no way that it's this far...
...two top executives - Pica and Trebol!
That's so crazy!
PLAN 4 - CALL HIM BY THE TRANSPONDER SNAIL
AND TELL HIM "HURRY UP AND RUN"
Plan 4.
Call him by the Transponder Snail
and tell him "Hurry up and run."
He's smacking away every
single spiked iron ball!
The world's strongest!
And...
...the current king, one of the Seven
Warlords of the Sea, Doflamingo!
Don't tell me he can even
avoid getting wet in rain!
Why aren't you withdrawing?
There are only four of them left!
Dammit!
I'd rather die.
Oh, I don't have it...
Kid!
I didn't expect them to make it that far!
State your name.
Don't come towards us!!
They're amazing! The Straw Hats!
Roronoa Zoro.
I can't believe we were trying to save ourselves
by killing those great people!
Father-sama!!
Well, like they say, we all make mistakes!
I'll remember it.
Straw Hat...
Look out for what's falling onto you, Kyros!
I haven't seen anyone like
you in a while, strong one.
Even I can tell him that, there's no
time for all of them to get away anyway!
If you understand it now, it's okay!
I'll forgive you!
How silly are you to stumble now?
Thus, as a swordsman's courtesy,
I'll sink you using the world's
strongest Black Blade.
Damn you, Diamante! I'll never forgive you!
Old man King Riku, where are you going?
No, Rebecca! There are still iron balls!
I don't think anyone will try to kill me now.
--Go for it!
--Pica-sama!
Father-sama!!
I'll go down to the town.
I think there is still something I can do.
He's looking to kill King Riku!
Three-Sword Style Secret Technique!
This is the gun that I shot
your wife Scarlet with!
I'll come with you!
It's none of our business
but I don't like it!
I don't wanna depend on
the Government or the Navy!
Three Thousand Worlds!
Hey, Straw Hat! Where're you going?!
What should we do?
Everybody's feeling hopeless.
The sky!
They think they can't get away from
this Birdcage and this deadly game!
You should be happy!
You'll get killed with my gun like your wife!
Stop! You stone monster!
I lost...
Sniper King-senpai is on that plateau!
We should all go!
What are you saying?!
Bellamy has changed!
I won't forgive you!
Stone! Come back here! I'll fight you!
I won't forgive you! Diamante!
Let's tell everybody in the town
that there is hope!
You've changed, Bellamy.
You're my friend!
I never imagined I'd ever lose...
Well said, Rebecca! Don't forgive me!
Thank you, Straw Hat!
Fight me! I'll kill you with these hands!
Things are turning in our favor, it seems.
No!!
Like your mother!
It's still too early for you to die.
Straw Hat!
Let go of me, Robin-san! I gotta kill him!
If you're not gonna accept my
challenge to a duel, I'll just...
My name is Dracule Mihawk!
Where did the Navy admiral go?
Learn about yourself!
Learn about the world!
Didn't you notice?
I see!
He went down a while ago.
...kill you!
I'm glad that I saved my King Punch
as Pirate Hunter told me to!
And become strong!
How long will it last?!
The Flower Umbrella can't take it anymore!
Try to surpass me! Roronoa Zoro!
I'll kill you!
How is the situation?
I don't have time to stumble over you here!
The capture of those running
out of control is going well
Diamante!!
I'll save you now! My friend, King Riku!
but we haven't taken care of everything yet.
Cut that crap!
Prepare yourself, Straw Hat!
Wait a sec, you king of somewhere!
Gather all the citizens in one place.
The nine mountains and eight seas...
Somewhere?!
I'm the king of Prodence, Elizabello! Pirate Hunter!
I'll end this with this one blow!
There's nothing I can't cut!
Within a defensible perimeter.
Why are you just standing there?!
Take a fighting pose, you coward!
Go to hell!
No way...
Roronoa Zoro!
I told you it's no use just destroying it.
Yes, sir!
If by any chance,
you know how to throw a punch!
Three Thousand Worlds!
He'll keep coming back
unless you beat his flesh and blood!
What should we do, then?!
Stop causing innocent people trouble!
This is my fight! Rebecca!
Mingo!
Zoro-senpai!!
Straw Hat!
Doro!
Go to hell!
Drop...
...your sword!
Ripple!
For a decade, you...
So long, Straw Hat!
Flash!
Tower Climb!
Father-sama!
Get under the umbrella! You'll die!
Thank you for saying that I'm your friend!
Tower Climb Return!
...have followed your mother's wish!!
Pirate Hunter... saved
my friend, King Riku...
My mother said I shouldn't hurt anyone!
Two-Sword Style...
Seems like we're out of time!
...Nigiri!
I'm gonna teach you how to not get hurt!
Fight, Rebecca!
But, it's falling onto us anyway!
She has never hurt anybody
Help!!
We're gonna die!!
and she won it all by letting
opponents fall out of the ring!
Roronoa Zoro...
She has never been defeated!
Pirate Hunter!
Help! Boro!!
I have something to do now.
This is it for our fight.
You can't even cut your enemy
and you call yourself a winner?!
You fool! You can't just do as you like!
Shed your blood, Rebecca!
You coward!
That was a horrible match!
Your turn!
Tsk! Is that...?!
You brought shame to all of us gladiators!
I know now! That I admired the wrong man!
That bastard...
--Drop dead, Rebecca!
--A corrupted family!
King...
...Punch!
And how pathetic I am!
You foul-blooded wench!
Father-sama, it's shaking!
I know I'm an idiot
Hey!
Give me two minutes.
but even an idiot has his principles
that he must stick to!
You've been fighting in the Colosseum
but you still haven't hurt anybody!
Rebecca!
That's...
...the one that Zoro was keeping off! Pica!
Your hands are still clean!
Those are the hands...
Doflamingo!!
...in which your mother
Scarlet's spirit lives!
Diamante...
A top executive of the Family shouldn't
look so pathetic like that.
W-We've been saved!
Is King Riku there?!
Mother-sama...
The beast is roaring.
There's no need to bathe
those hands with the blood
Plan 5.
PLAN 5
of a devil like him after all these years!
Just come on up here.
That brat... He used my King Punch...
Fly in the sky and chop him up!!!
FLY IN THE SKY AND CHOP HIM UP!!!
PLAN 5 - FLY IN THE SKY AND CHOP HIM UP!!!
...to clean up the stones! How rude!
He'll regret this!
I'm sure he'll be surprised, Law.
When he sees your dead body...
Rebecca!
PLAN 5
ACCOMPLISHED
I won't let you wield a sword!
Good work!
ZORO VS. PICA
THE WINNER
Let's do that!
ZORO
Even though he's on the verge of death,
Pica's giant fist that almost
seems to cover up the sky,
One of the top executives
- Pica finally falls,
His entire body assailed by
countless deadly iron balls,
Pica tears up his tough opponents
one after another with
Law continues trying to get his revenge
Kyros reaches his limit!
comes down onto King Riku!
and only Doflamingo and Trebol remain!
his tremendous power and Zoro
stands to challenge him!
but after the ruthless Doflamingo's
bullets riddle his body,
But when he thinks of the pain and grief
When the lamp of hope that
That, however, was Pica's grand trap!
Leaving Zoro stranded in a distant place,
However, while everyone is placing
all their hopes on Luffy,
has been lit in Dressrosa is
about to be crushed,
that Doflamingo caused to the citizens,
he finally meets his end!
and another age of being ruled
by force looms in sight,
When Luffy who witnesses that
horrific outcome roars with anger,
and gets filled with resentment,
Pica treads on the ground and begins a major
Bellamy stands in his way putting his pride as a man on the line!
his wholehearted attack which will
Zoro and Pica's final battle breaks out!
The two men now clash,
having their minds racing with emotion!
counterattack to eliminate King Riku!
the final battle in Dressrosa begins!
tear up the misfortune
of Dressrosa is launched!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Law Dies! Luffy's Raging Onslaught!"
"Trueno Bastardo! Kyros' Furious Strike!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"So Long! Bellamy's Farewell Blow!"
"A Decisive Battle in Midair!
Zoro's New Special Secret Technique Blasts!"
"Moving Across the Ground!
The Giant Statue Pica's Surprise Maneuver!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!