Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed
a pirate alliance with
Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
Death Enjambre!
Father-sama!!
Look out for what's falling onto you, Kyros!
How silly are you to stumble now?
I won't forgive you!
I won't forgive you! Diamante!
Well said, Rebecca! Don't forgive me!
Fight me! I'll kill you with these hands!
Like your mother!
Drop...
...your sword!
For a decade, you...
...have followed your mother's wish!!
You've been fighting in the Colosseum
but you still haven't hurt anybody!
Your hands are still clean!
Those are the hands...
...in which your mother
Scarlet's spirit lives!
Mother-sama...
There's no need to bathe those
hands with the blood of a
devil like him after all these years!
Rebecca!
I won't let you wield a sword!
"Trueno Bastardo!
Kyros' Furious Strike!"
No way!
Nobody can move in this deadly stardust!
Kyros!
Is your body a ball of iron?!
No, it must be painful enough
to make you wanna scream...
This guy is crazy...
Are you a ball of stupidity?!
Feeling pain...
Feeling pain is proof that I am a human!
I know you people don't understand!
The hopelessness of being forgotten
by somebody you love!
Scarlet!
Why?! Why didn't you wait for me?!
I see!
I must've slipped out of your mind, too!
Our promises...
...and memories, as well!
Scarlet! Stay with me!
I don't know who you are but...
...my daughter is waiting for me, hungry.
Please...
It's me! Kyros!
Scarlet!!
I can't believe I'm losing her like this!
This is hell!
It's terrible!
With these tin arms, I can't even feel...
...your warmth as you're dying!
Scarlet!!
You people don't understand!
The agony of being unable to feel
whatever you touch!
The tragedies that fell on Dressrosa...
Compared to them,
this is not even pain!
You called me a ball!
I'll become a ball of the
anger of this country
and bring you down!
How powerful this guy is!
Your glory is like something
from 20 years ago!
Don't underestimate my true sword skill!
Half Moon Glaive!
Kyros!!
Diamante!!
Did something happen to Kyros and Rebecca?
Viola...
Rebecca is fine.
It's a very intense fight.
I can even feel it through my Clairvoyance...
Brother Kyros' pain and anger...
You haven't dropped dead yet?!
You monster!
Seems like you've reached your limit!
Kyros!
Just as the iron balls stopped raining down.
I'll finish you off myself
to end this for you!
Like Scarlet that you two loved so much!
Diamante! What a jerk!
He mentioned Sister-sama again!
Damn you, Diamante!
I'm sorry! King Riku-sama!
Our desperate search ended in vain.
The man named Diamante was ahead of us and...
...Scarlet-sama was found in the town and...
...got shot...!
You killed Sister-sama?!
Oh yeah, she was your older sister!
She was buying food at a market in the town.
If she could've controlled her hunger,
she didn't have to die! What a fool!
Let go of me, Tank!
Please don't jump the gun!
I can't take it anymore!
We'll stay in the Palace, too!
To protect you!
You...
...and you!
I won't let any of you survive!
You guys lost to us a decade ago!
Losers should accept their lot
and face their demise miserably!
Diamante!!
My strike will rend even the ground!
There! There!
There!! There!
There!!
I hope you can dodge it
with your one leg that's been shot!
I won't dodge!
If you won't dodge, you're just an idiot!
With all my heart and soul!
This sword carries a decade worth
of pain that this country suffered!
I'll take back peace!
Half Moon Glaive!
Trueno...
...Bastardo!
Thank you! Robiland!
Father-sama!!
Father-sama, you need to get treatment now!
Although I couldn't protect your mother,
I'm gonna protect you to the end,
with my life!
Until the day you are filled with happiness,
I will always be by your side!
Viola-sama!
Don't tell me Army Commander Kyros got...
He took down Diamante!
He took down the formidable Diamante?
Is it true, Viola-sama?!
Yes... Brother Kyros won!
Rebecca is okay, too.
Nico Robin protected her...
I can't believe he took
down the top executive of
the Donquixote Family...
He took down the hero of the Colosseum...
That's absurd!
Kyros was the original undefeated hero
of the Colosseum!
We thought no one can beat the
Donquixote Family but they've
been taken down one after another!
Kyros!
Army Commander Kyros!
Not just Señor Pink at the factory...
but the other executives have been
brought down by the warriors
who side with Straw Hat Luffy.
There are four major fighters of
the Donquixote Family left!
Bellamy the Hyena and...
...two top executives - Pica and Trebol!
And...
...the current king, one of the Seven
Warlords of the Sea, Doflamingo!
There are only four of them left!
I didn't expect them to make it that far!
They're amazing! The Straw Hats!
I can't believe we were trying to save ourselves
by killing those great people!
Well, like they say, we all make mistakes!
If you understand it now, it's okay!
I'll forgive you!
Old man King Riku, where are you going?
I don't think anyone will try to kill me now.
I'll go down to the town.
I think there is still something I can do.
I'll come with you!
I don't wanna depend on
the Government or the Navy!
Everybody's feeling hopeless.
They think they can't get away from
this Birdcage and this deadly game!
We should all go!
Let's tell everybody in the town
that there is hope!
Things are turning in our favor, it seems.
Where did the Navy admiral go?
Didn't you notice?
He went down a while ago.
How is the situation?
The capture of those running
out of control is going well
but we haven't taken care of everything yet.
Gather all the citizens in one place.
Within a defensible perimeter.
Yes, sir!
Ripple!
Flash!
Tower Climb!
Tower Climb Return!
Two-Sword Style...
...Nigiri!
Roronoa Zoro...
I have something to do now.
This is it for our fight.
You fool! You can't just do as you like!
Tsk! Is that...?!
That bastard...
Father-sama, it's shaking!
Rebecca!
That's...
...the one that Zoro was keeping off! Pica!
Diamante...
A top executive of the Family shouldn't
look so pathetic like that.
Pica tears up his tough opponents
one after another with
his tremendous power and Zoro
stands to challenge him!
That, however, was Pica's grand trap!
Leaving Zoro stranded in a distant place,
Pica treads on the ground and begins a major
counterattack to eliminate King Riku!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Moving Across the Ground!
The Giant Statue Pica's Surprise Maneuver!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!