Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
The tragedies that fell on Dressrosa...
Compared to them,
this is not even pain!
I'll become a ball of the
anger of this country
and bring you down!
Half Moon Glaive!
Trueno...
...Bastardo!
The one that Zoro was keeping off!
Pica!
Diamante...
A top executive of the Family shouldn't look
so pathetic like that.
"Moving Across the Ground!
The Giant Statue Pica's Surprise Maneuver!"
Stop, Bellamy!
Or you really are gonna kill yourself!
Straw Hat! You bastard!
You're still saying that?!
I'll say it again and again!
Your body's reaching its limit now!
Stop fighting...
Bellamy! That's enough!
Shut up! I decide where I'll die myself!
You're gonna become the King
of the Pirates, right?!
Then you shouldn't get
stalled by crap like this!
Straw Hat!
Father-sama!
It was obvious.
We're not here to have a one-on-one match!
As long as there's an enemy,
the fight won't end!
Don't push yourself, Father-sama!
You can't even move!
Fall back, Rebecca!
Even if it means death,
I have to bring down all of them
and put this country back
in the hands of King Riku-sama!
I have to ask.
What is King Riku to you people?
Rebecca. You have been cursed at repeatedly
because of him.
Kyros. You lost your leg
because you were serving him,
and you were forced to live as a toy!
If it weren't for him...
Screw you! You people framed him!
To me, King Riku-sama is a
father-in-law and someone
I owe so much to for taking care
of me since I was a bad kid!
The King Riku Family was
known as a venerable family
that understands the true meaning
of peace, even worldwide!
This country wasn't as wealthy
and prosperous as it is now.
But that doesn't mean
the people were unhappy!
The sky is clear and
flowers are blooming proudly.
A great country filled with gentle hearts!
That's what Dressrosa really is!
Money and jewels are nothing but stones
and they have no heart or soul!
The act of living is true happiness.
That is what he told us!
That's who King Riku-sama is!
Kicking you bastards out and having
him sit on the throne again
is what the whole nation wants now!
I understand.
What? He disappeared?
What's going on?
Charlestone!
Wh-What is that?! It scared me!
He went to the third level this time!
Damn, that fool!
He's supposed to fight me!
Doesn't he wanna fight?!
Either way, I can't get him
if he moves around in the plateau!
Be ready to die
once you enter my range again!
Charlestone!
Pica-sama, please stop!
--Pica-sama!
--Help!
That jerk! He's harming the injured!
It's coming! Watch out!
Okay, honey!
D-Don't cling to me!
Boy! We're gonna be husband and wife
so don't be shy like that...
You betrayed us, Baby 5!
Steel Mill!
Look out!
Sai!
Honey!
Oh, you're okay! Let me help you out!
No, you fool! Old man, behind you!
You pieces of crap!
Charlestone!
That son of a gun!
The stone jerk!
That's enough, you fool!
How could you mess with the wounded ones?
Roronoa.
Bite Stone!
One-Sword Style Demon Horse!
Say, Roronoa Zoro.
Do you know who's on the old King's Plateau?
The king of this country!
"Former"!
What's your point, you jerk?!
Don't you think it's unfair?
What's unfair?!
Invasions always happen in the world.
Why does only Doffy have to take blame?
Cut the crap!
On the old King's Plateau,
there aren't only the former
senior officials of this country
but also, those samurai and God Usopp.
I heard the whole nation seeks
King Riku's restoration.
So what?!
That pisses me off! Doffy is the only king!
What the...!
What's going on?!
Look at that!
That jerk...
It started to move again!
Wh-What will he do?!
This is Donquixote's country!
It's gonna walk! Run!
The statue started to move! Run! Run!
Whoa-whoa, don't tell me...
Wh-What the hell... What is he up to?!
That bastard!
Is he going to kill the king?!
--Run!
--It's gonna crush us!
Prepare to fire!
Shoot!
Shoot! Shoot!
That jerk!
That's why he drove me out this far!
I can't catch up to him!
I totally got played!
Gotta do something or else...
It'll take him just one punch
to shatter the King's Plateau!
Usopp and the king will be crushed
and die in an instant!
Is there any way to prevent it?!
Pirate Hunter!
We won't let you get in Pica-sama's way anymore!
So annoying!
Zoro!
It's no good!
If we let him go!
But there's no way to stop that thing!
--Grandfather-sama!
--Usopp!
That bastard!
PLAN 1
Plan 1.
LONG-DISTANCE SLASH
Long-distance slash.
No, it has to travel too far
so it won't be powerful enough.
I can't take him down.
PLAN 2 - JUMP UP AND GET ON TOP
Plan 2. Jump up and get on top!
It's impossible.
PLAN 3
SHOUT OUT, WARNING USOPP AND THE OTHERS
Plan 3.
Shout out, warning Usopp and the others.
Usopp!!
There's no way he can hear me from this far.
PLAN 4 - CALL HIM BY THE TRANSPONDER SNAIL
AND TELL HIM "HURRY UP AND RUN"
Plan 4.
Call him by the Transponder Snail
and tell him "Hurry up and run."
Oh, I don't have it...
Don't come towards us!!
Even I can tell him that, there's no
time for all of them to get away anyway!
--Go for it!
--Pica-sama!
He's looking to kill King Riku!
It's none of our business
but I don't like it!
What should we do?
Stop! You stone monster!
Sniper King-senpai is on that plateau!
Stone! Come back here! I'll fight you!
No!!
I see!
I'm glad that I saved my King Punch
as Pirate Hunter told me to!
I'll save you now! My friend, King Riku!
Wait a sec, you king of somewhere!
Somewhere?!
I'm the king of Prodence, Elizabello! Pirate Hunter!
I told you it's no use just destroying it.
He'll keep coming back
unless you beat his flesh and blood!
What should we do, then?!
Seems like we're out of time!
Help!!
Pirate Hunter!
Hey!
Give me two minutes.
Is King Riku there?!
Plan 5.
PLAN 5
Fly in the sky and chop him up!!!
FLY IN THE SKY AND CHOP HIM UP!!!
PLAN 5 - FLY IN THE SKY AND CHOP HIM UP!!!
Let's do that!
Pica's giant fist that almost
seems to cover up the sky,
comes down onto King Riku!
When the lamp of hope that
has been lit in Dressrosa is
about to be crushed,
and another age of being ruled
by force looms in sight,
Zoro and Pica's final battle breaks out!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Decisive Battle in Midair!
Zoro's New Special Secret Technique Blasts!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!