trapped along with the entire island.
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
do I have to get up to make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
I don't want to settle for small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
Whiffing through the air, off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Mercilessly, beat me, hit me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
Only those who get back on their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari mae wo mita mono dake ga
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
We're still far from our goal, we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
and keep going without thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
But caught up in the current king Doflamingo's agenda, they were
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
The executives of the Donquixote
Family have been taken down
Their allies have been bringing down
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
the executives of the Donquixote
Family one after another.
one after another, after hard
battles, by the Straw Hats,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
Luffy and Law's fight against Doflamingo
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
and finally, there is only Doflamingo left!
at the Royal Palace is about
to come to a climax, too.
The time has come for a one-on-one duel
between Luffy and Doflamingo
Gum-Gum...
Your death is inevitable.
H-How is it possible?
This country has been taken over
by Doflamingo's trap.
Go to hell! Together with Law!
that shakes up Dressrosa!
Inside my body now,
strings are repairing my inner organs.
Die in vain like a dog!
I'm a captain of a ship, too!
Whether we can restore it
to King Riku's hands...
Shambles!
But, if you're gonna die anyway,
...or we let it fall as a
hopeless country again...
If I leave both you and Doflamingo
in Straw Hat-ya's hands,
How smartly you can use your ability is important.
You're the one that'll perish! Doflamingo!
wouldn't you rather make something out of it?
Our hope is in the hands of some pirates now!
I'll lose my prestige!
You can't even move! What can you do?!
It's meaningful for both of us.
This operation will destroy you
from inside your body!
Pirates?
What?! The Color of the Supreme King, colliding?!
You damn worm!
Lucy...
I'm only gonna say this once so listen carefully,
Trafalgar D. Water Law.
Go to hell!
He uses it, too?!
Gamma Knife!
I respect that man!
If he at least recognizes how I die,
Takt!
What're you...?!
Perform the Perpetual Youth Surgery
Go to hell!
I can't ask for more!
The arm?!
Sterben Blade!
Mingo!!
which is the ultimate Op-Op
technique on me and...
Don't lie! You just have no choice!
Doffy! You're a king!
Don't fall on your knees anymore!
Gum-Gum...
...die.
Because you're a man!
In exchange, I'll grant
your wish, whatever it is.
Gum-Gum...
Doffy's madness will...
If you know that much, shut up and fight!
Oh, that's great!
...Jet Stamp!
...destroy everything!
Then,
I can't believe you used...
But you'll die for nothing!
bring Cora-san back to
life for me, right now!
Doffy!!
...Eagle...
...your disembodied arm...!
No, I can't ask for more.
...Bazooka!
When you finish with that,
go lick all the butts of the people in this country!
How annoying...!
That bastard is my responsibility...!
If I'll be sent to kingdom come...
The Straw Hats have worked so many miracles
up until today.
...by another man that I admire!
Athlete!
Room!
When it comes to this...
You can't take down Straw Hat-ya!
So long, Straw Hat!
You can't take back Caesar from him as well!
Thank you for saying that I'm your friend!
Cora-san...
I finally can attain your ambition!
Don't get in my way!
Straw Hat!
Law...
It's over. Doflamingo!
You die with me!
Doflamingo!!
"Unassailable!
The Stunning Secret of Trebol!"
"A Collision of Haki!
Luffy vs. Doflamingo!"
Oh no! He's gonna set fire!
Hey, Tra-guy!
Why are you bleeding so much?!
I'll take you along!
What happened to your arm? Hey!
Stick-Stickem!
Stay with me! Tra-guy! Hey!
He's dead... It's obvious.
Look! Even Trafalgar Law who has
What's this?!
How dare you bastards!
the same title of Warlord
as Doflamingo, is...
You have no chance to survive now.
You idiot! Don't think a weakling like you can beat Doffy!
Let's bring an end to this game.
...in quite bad shape!
Mingo!!
The Gamma Knife destroys your internal organs
without an external wound.
Lawland!
Damn! Let go of me! You bastard!
--Wait.
--What?
Luffy! Hand me Tra-guy-kun!
Listen carefully, Straw Hat-ya.
Robin! That'll help!
Just wait here struggling!
We'll kill you in turn!
Take him! Tra-guy cornered
Mingo enough already!
Doflamingo!!
"A Blade of Tenacity!
The Gamma Knife Counterattack!"
When a doctor says so, there's no doubt!
Oh no! His arm...!
First,
Cien Fleurs! Spider Net!
Law, we'll start with you.
Now, Doffy, I'll stall Straw Hat.
Law!
The beast is roaring.
You fool! What did you do to Doffy?!
Crush Law's head while you have a chance.
Just come on up here.
Lawland's arm is...
Look...
How could they do this?!
Tra-guy-kun, stay with me!
I'm sure he'll be surprised, Law.
Hey! Don't do it, Mingo!
Nico Robin!
Fight me! Tra-guy can't move even one millimeter now!
Don't do anything unnecessary!
He's still breathing.
Don't get in his way!
"Law Dies!
Luffy's Raging Onslaught!"
I said "In turn"...
He hasn't been dismissed yet.
Shut up! This jerk is so icky!
I'm sticky!
Doflamingo!
That jerk! He's still going for Tra-guy!
Straw Hat has just taken down Bellamy...
Here's a finisher!
Gum-Gum...
You just...
That brings the number
of the tough enemies of
the Donquixote Family down to two.
...gathered up people who were convenient for you
and called it a Family.
Bullet String!
...Hawk Whip!
There are only two left;
Damn!
the top executive and the chief of staff,
Trebol, and the boss of the Family,
And your biological younger brother, Cora-san,
who tried to stop your rampage, got...
Oh, you got me...
Robiland!
Donquixote Doflamingo!
It's moving as I thought!
As Roronoa Zoro said,
we can't lower our guard
...or not! Not a chance!
Tra-guy! Robin!
He is free!!
but the tide is turning for us in a big way!
It's no use!
The wall of strings is moving!
What?! Why's that?!
Almost...
A little more to go and
this nightmare will end!
I thought I could hit a Logia eater with the Color of Arms!
Well, now, do you think my power is the Logia type?
"Anger Erupts!
I Will Take Everything upon Myself!"
Yeah, that was a shame...
Either way, that crap doesn't work against me!
No!
What's the matter, Viola-sama?
He betrayed me and
even pointed a gun at me...
You rubber idiot!
Straw Hat-ya!
He's right - it's no use.
He's a papier-mâché bastard!
You knew!
Viola?
Our force has been reduced as well!
That Cora-san wasn't gonna pull the trigger!
What?!
P-P-Papier-mâché?!
The houses and the buildings are being sliced
"Our force" means one of us got taken down?!
More than anything,
I didn't want to sit on the Heart throne
Precious Metal Axe!
and they're collapse!
I could pull it.
Run!
Who in the world could it be?!
because I didn't want to be grouped together with idiots like them!
Cabbage-kun!
It's Trafalgar Law!
I'm sorry. I'd been sleeping
until a while ago.
What?!
I-Idiots?!
Can't believe it! Law-dono?!
I bet so.
Hasn't this all been settled yet, Straw Hat?!
Did you call us top executives idiots?!
Seems like you still can talk.
You're the same as me.
What're you saying, you half-dead moron?!
Not even the edge of the town is safe!
I wanna destroy everything that I see!
We top executives are
the foundation of the Family!
--Hurry up!
--Run! Run!
Towns, houses, people...
I wanna destroy them all!
I'll never forgive anyone for making fun of us!
To the downtown!
Cabbage!
This is the northern town!
We have an emergency!
Stick-Stickem...
Take everyone and get off of this plateau!
Yeah, whatever you say.
The Birdcage started moving all of a sudden
and cutting up the town!
...Launcher!
No way!
Since I stand before Doflamingo here,
But on that day,
It's the same in the west!
I wanna land at least one blow, too!
Stop! Tra-guy can't even move!
This is the eastern town, Carta!
I leave everybody in your hands!
...you were the one who was supposed to die!
As they say, the Birdcage
is shrinking it seems!
Law, you bastard!
L...
I'm sure he'll be surprised, Law.
I gotta teach this brat something!
Leave them in my hands?!
Law, I have something to say
that's as evil as you think I am.
Move, Doffy!
When he sees your dead body...
Trust...
The islanders are running towards
the downtown at once!
Listen, Law!
Corazon was a drag and an eyesore to me.
Respect...
THE ROYAL PALACE
Doffy will always be the absolute king!
Popularity!
Everybody'll die.
He started to have a cheesy sense of justice
and let out his worthless feelings.
Sooner or later.
A FEW MINUTES AGO AT THE ROYAL PALACE
Straw Hat is my fan.
But...
...there is no gap between him
and us current top executives!
Sticky Launcher!
Straw Hat. Did you notice?
He was an incompetent man.
My fan is asking me a favor!
When I killed him that day,
it was a great load off my mind...
That's because...
The plot of the game has been changed.
...one day 30-something years ago,
I can't turn it down!
The game?!
Counter Shock!
What are you saying after all this time?!
I know Bartolomeo is on the lower level!
You better rest now, Law.
we four picked up this immense gift
that fell from heaven!
Let's go down there now using his ability!
Go to hell, you demon!
Well, just listen.
The Birdcage that is surrounding the town
started shrinking little by little.
We gave him power and brought him up
to be a charismatic force for evil!
Doffy!
You must've learned enough.
Can you treat him somehow, Leo?!
The difference in our strengths
that you can't make up no matter
The cut is ragged!
It's like an umbrella closing slowly...
what kind of cheap trick you play.
If I can manage to sew them together...
Everyone got knocked out?!
You're no match even for me alone.
What?!
Then,
I can heal him with my Watering Can!
Why would you want to
challenge the two of us?
That must be "Haki"!
The Haki of the Color of the Supreme King!
Thank you, Princess Mansherry!
In any case, we'd better
go down now as Lucy said!
You're the man who was chosen by heaven!
Straw Hat won't make it up here that easily.
It'll cut up everything in this country.
That was kick-ass!
Do you want me to give you...
the strength to take revenge?
If he had the nerve to beat up
his "friend" right off the bat,
Within...
How he took down Pica was awesome!
...an hour or so.
he could've saved you but...
I'm going back to the Holyland
by taking your head!
Hey, Bartolomeo!
Make stairs with your barrier!
He's such a naive idiot so...
Wherever you run, it's no use.
Zoro-senpai!
...it's no use laying your hopes on him!
Forever!
Tra-guy!
You almost got killed
in the Holyland of Mariejois?!
No use! No use!
Are you even listening, you fool!
Hey! Stay with me!
Even bringing them your father's head?!
You're really a poor soul.
You were born in the hellish White Town...
I don't take orders from
strange, dual-natured creeps!
Run! If you stay here,
you'll get cut up into pieces!
Tra-guy!
Oh, Straw Hat-ya...
But I'm glad that you came back alive!
It's a miracle!
Doflamingo!
How dare he do such a terrible thing!
In your youth, your future
seemed just plain darkness...
Make stairs for Nico Robin
and the others! Hurry up!
It's horrible! So cruel!
I don't wanna die! Run!
Then you met my young brother,
Corazon, and...
You don't have to worry about me.
Oh, is it for Robin-senpai?!
Go save the people who are at the
edges of the country quickly!
Doffy...
More importantly, how's Doflamingo...?
...he extended your life expectancy but...
Yes, sir!
Doffy, you have the quality of a king.
...you've been holding a grudge against me
as if you're the ghost of him
and living to get your revenge.
What a fool!
We swear to support you in everything.
Are you okay?!
Th-Thank you...
For a man who is already dead,
you've honed your skills,
The Birdcage is closing in!
Hurry to the downtown!
Doffy, in return, let us have a dream!
That's enough.
allied with Straw Hat, and
even come to Dressrosa...
Straw Hat.
That's our king!
We helped the weakest ones evacuate
the farthest end of the town! Hurry up!
What an astounding obsession...
Law is suffering because he can't die.
Now, Doffy...
But...
Hurry to the center of the town!
...it's over now.
It's better to put him out of his misery.
Run! The strings are coming!
What a worthless 13 years you've spent.
H-How is it possible?
If that's what you wanna do,
do it after you beat me!
Hey, somebody, help!
I feel sorry for you.
Just undoing the rope on my feet is fine!
If I have enough time,
I can apply first aid to myself.
Untie it! I don't wanna die!
Your death is inevitable.
Seems like you're quite wasted away already.
Th-Th-The Birdcage is shrinking?!
Inside my body now,
strings are repairing my inner organs.
Die in vain like a dog!
So are you!
Hm? What's the matter, Doffy?
But, if you're gonna die anyway,
THE OLD KING'S PLATEAU
I don't think such destructive attacks by Tra-guy
would leave you unscathed!
Is it for real?!
What?!
Oh my...
How smartly you can use your ability
is important.
What should we do?! What can we do?!
What is that wound?
It's a bit different from recovery, though.
Hey, Zoro!
Some hoodlum did this. I wish he'd die.
wouldn't you rather make something out of it?
The cage closing in?!
What will happen to us?!
Thank you for your suicide attack.
It's meaningful for both of us.
Okay. I got it.
I thought we finally got out of bars
but we're behind bars, again?!
What?!
I'm only gonna say this once so listen carefully,
Trafalgar D. Water Law.
Sticky-Sticky Chain!
Bazooka!
Where are we supposed to run?!
Stop!
How could he do such a dirty thing?!
Perform the Perpetual Youth Surgery
What the hell do you want?
Stick-Stickem!
Haven't you had enough yet, Doflamingo?!
Hey, hey, is it you who hurt Doffy?
which is the ultimate Op-Op
technique on me and...
If the cage keeps shrinking like this...
...die.
Oh, that brat!
I just teased him a little bit!
Dressrosa will be finished!
In exchange, I'll grant
your wish, whatever it is.
You surely move fast but...
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF
THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 2
...you're lacking heaviness!
I can stop your breath at least.
Oh, that's great!
What is that smoke and that rumbling?!
He just hurt that kid a little bit!
Overheat!
What's going on?!
Ow! Ow!
What's wrong with you bastards?!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
- LEVEL 4 THE SUNFLOWER FIELD
This brings back memories!
We are the Donquixote Family.
Ever since you drove that ill-famed Crocodile
to be stripped of the title,
Damn!
No... You got to be kidding!
Whatever it is?
I've been keeping an eye on you!
What's really happening?!
Don't do it!
That's right.
I'm sure that guy set up something again!
If you really mean it,
He passed out!
Crocodile got defeated?
Damn...
Doflamingo!
By a captain from the Navy Headquarters?
it is a good idea.
It's meaningful for both of us.
Wh-What's with this brat?!
You gotta be kidding. There must be a catch.
All right. I'm in!
Luffy! Hurry up! Kick Doflamingo's ass!
Look! It's got to be him!
How dare you stop me?!
His bounty jumped up!
You're a very understanding man!
Finally, Doffy can have eternal life...
--That's all we can do now!
--That's right! Indeed! Certainly!
Find out about this pirate group.
I've never heard their name.
But that's too much to ask.
Monkey... "D."?!
Then,
All lives throughout the country
are down to Luffy-dono.
bring Cora-san back to
life for me, right now!
I was just looking to smash up Law's head!
Doffy likes your turf.
We need you guys to go away.
And the Paramount War in which
you fell from the sky!
I'm counting on you! Luffy-dono!
When you finish with that,
go lick all the butts of the people in this country!
P-Please don't kill me...
I'm counting on you, too!
Help!
No match for you?
It's no use laying my hopes?
Adios!
What?!
The Color of the Supreme King, colliding?!
I can't believe you survived
and made it this far!
He uses it, too?!
No kidding!
I'm not willing to save anybody.
It's you who is not seeing
the picture, Doflamingo!
What happened?!
Did somebody hurt you again?
No, I just fell because the road was uneven.
The Straw Hats have worked so
many miracles up until today.
An uneven road?! Which town was it?
What's the advantage of letting people
who learned the secret
of the country survive?
Oh, I see. This needs to be fixed.
You can't take down Straw Hat-ya!
You can't take back Caesar from him as well!
Law! How could you say such a thing to Doffy!
Towns, people, animals...
What?! What the hell is going on?!
Wait!
And your allies...
It's your future that's hanging by a hair...
You woke up, Trafalgar!
And you! Everything!
Leave me... here!
What are you saying?!
It's a butterfly!
Straw Hat-ya...
For past 13 years...
He can use it as I thought!
So your friends died just a little before...
The Doflamingo Family!
I've been living just to kill Doflamingo!
What an idiot!
You never stop rebelling against me!
Right, Straw Hat-ya?
That's what he used to call you.
You're the man who was chosen by heaven!
The letters on your back... "Corazon"?
Listen, Doffy.
He died so miserably.
I've done... everything I can!
Who are you aiming the satire at?!
You're a king.
Oh, Law, he shouldn't have messed with us...
Do you want me to give you...
the strength to take revenge?
First of all, your pirate group
is called the Heart Pirates!
No one must be allowed to rebel against you.
I have to leave the rest to Straw Hat-ya!
People who I wanna kill...
There are tons of them!
Who are you aiming the satire at?!
You're the man who will...
You don't even sit on the Heart seat
Today, Dressrosa will...
If he's gonna win,
...become the king of the sea someday!
then why are you bearing
the mark of the Heart?!
I wanna see it through with my own eyes here!
...perish.
Law!
Straw Hat!
You're not good enough
to compete with Doffy!
Oh, you don't have to worry.
I'll build a country again.
If he loses, I need to be here and...
Mingo! If I kick your ass,
everything'll be okay!
We set up Doffy as a king
and showed our dignity to our subordinates!
...die along with him!
I was trying to suggest
that you can't do that!
How irritating!
But Doffy and we four have been thinking of
the Family equally and
brought it to its present level!
Law... Corazon... This is it...
Like a true family!
Understand, Law?!
No one else will succeed
your stupid obsession...
Fallbright!
Do you remember that
my mucus is flammable?
You never learn! Bullet String!
I can shut your annoying mouth up instantly...
Your curse has been broken now!!
Gum-Gum...
A true family?
Go to hell! Together with Law!
Equally?
Tra-guy died? You've got to be kidding!
Shambles!
What happened to you?
It's only you guys who are thinking
like that, Trebol.
After getting riddled by so
many bullets, he can't be...
Law!
--Don't forgive them!
--Kill them!
His own ambition is everything to him.
You're the one that'll perish! Doflamingo!
He doesn't give a damn about you guys!
Go!
Great! I got a chance to retaliate!
I thought I'd have to bear it silently all my life!
What... What did you say?!
How pathetic.
--Doffy!
--Brother!
To me, even you, who acts like you're the chief of staff, only look like...
This operation will destroy you
from inside your body!
Help!
...Doflamingo's foolish puppet!
I...
...got him involved in this conflict...
F-F-Foolish puppet?!
My children are innocent!
Aim all your arrows at me!
Gamma Knife!
I won't forgive you!
I gotta see it through with my own eyes here!
Leave me!
Please! Don't harm my children!
Hey! Don't fall for it, Trebol!
Room!
It hurts, Father!
I can't take it anymore!
Trafalgar...
You're inside the Room!
This brat was barely alive already but I
Tra-guy-kun...
Captains of allied pirate groups
have to be on an equal footing.
restrained his movement with my mucus in addition!
What can he do in these circumstances?!
Luffy is here...
...of his own free will.
I'm not gonna blow it up!
I'll shut your smart-ass mouth
in the cruelest way I can think of!
He doesn't fight if he has no will to.
Leave me here!
Now, open your mouth!
I'll get even...
King Riku-sama.
Gamma Knife!
If we're in an unpredictable situation,
Stop!
I'll get even with you idiots!
You insolent brat!
it's even more necessary for us
to save the citizens who are in danger.
I'm begging you!
Brother...
I'm not gonna die!
I'll shove this into your throat
and impale you!
--Yes, sir! Let's go!
--I-I'll go, too!
--I'll go with you, too!
--Me, too!
Doffy!
All right! Let's go down to the town now!
I'm gonna survive no matter what you do to me
and I will...
It's not too late to minimize casualties!
Law! How are you still alive?!
Yeah! Even though we can't fight,
there are things we can do!
How did you make an OP-OP attack
without creating a Room?!
Yeah! Let's go!
I will come kill
every single one of you jerks!!
No, we're in a Room now!
I don't think I can talk you out of it...
I'm not gonna blow it up!
I'll shut your smart-ass mouth
in the cruelest way I can think of!
Nico Robin, you go ahead.
It'll shorten my life somewhat
but I've put up a Room
Cabbage-kun!
Now, open your mouth!
which is so big you can't even see it!
Robin-senpai! I will help you now!
What?!
Stop!
You insolent brat!
Barrier-bility:
Stairs!
Doffy...
I'll shove this into your throat
and impale you!
For this moment and for this attack!
I can't listen to a suicidal wish.
Stop!
I'll stay here, too.
I'm a captain of a ship, too!
You need to come to terms with it.
Well, it's okay.
We can get hold of the Op-Op Fruit again.
If I leave both you and Doflamingo
in Straw Hat-ya's hands,
If you're gonna die,
Yeah, you're right.
it's got to be after me.
Wh-Wh...
I'll lose my prestige!
What?!
Robin-senpai!
You can't even move! What can you do?!
Then, all there is left to do is...
Everyone got knocked out?!
Come down now!
You damn worm!
Robin-san!
Yeah.
It wasn't a fatal wound!
Go to hell!
That must be "Haki"!
Bartolomeo made us stairs!
Take care...
Shambles!
Haki?
Go.
And on top of that,
that's the Haki of the Color of the Supreme King!
...of everything.
Takt!
You can wear this.
What're you...?!
You have to go, Nico Robin.
Let me look after him.
The arm?!
That's the proof that
you have the quality of a king.
First of all, your pirate group
is called the Heart Pirates!
Sterben Blade!
Who are you aiming the satire at?!
Doflamingo!
Thank you, Cabbage-kun.
You don't even sit on the Heart seat
You're the man who was chosen by heaven!
then why are you bearing
the mark of the Heart?!
Law!
Robiland!
We'll stay here, too!
I'm sorry, body double...
We can't leave
the wounded Lawland here like that.
Now,
Something wrong, Leo?
I'll return once it's over.
if you're a man,
you'd better put yourself to a test.
Doflamingo!!
THE SMILE FACTORY
What should we do?! What should we do?!
Shambles.
Are there any people who you wanna kill?
What can we do to stop it?!
Do you want me to give you...
the strength to take revenge?
What's the matter, you guys?
You turned to the town all of a sudden.
Hey, Tra-guy!
Why are you bleeding so much?!
I-I don't know why but...
Doflamingo!!
What happened to your arm?
Zoro-dono, where are you going?!
He's dead... It's obvious.
--It's dangerous!
--You guys! Come with me!
...it feels like a huge load has been
lifted off my chest...
Hey, Zoro!
Seems like he has some kind of idea.
Let's go!
There you are!
Mingo!!
People who I wanna kill...
--Wait.
--What?
Hey! We don't have time for that nonsense!
There are tons of them!
Mingo!
I'm alive.
You're late, Straw Hat.
Since I emancipated him,
We finished destroying the factory!
Why did you also take away the power I had?!
Listen carefully, Straw Hat-ya.
Now let's run from the approaching Birdcage!
Don't turn around! I have a plan!
We can't undo what you've done now!
Bellamy became free, didn't he?
Don't play dumb! You knew full well!
I'm going back to the Holyland
by taking your head!
We gotta hurry or...
What?! What happened?!
Nobody can defend an attack
that comes from inside their body!
That he wasn't gonna run away!
Doflamingo. Rosinante.
Blood! He got slashed and bled!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
I'm sorry that you had to have...
Spiderweb!
Even you can't counteract this technique!
...a father like me.
I see. So Bellamy didn't run away.
What's so funny?!
Doffy's different!
He's of a totally different caliber!
Gum-Gum...
Doffy! You're a king!
Don't fall on your knees anymore!
His birth nurtured madness in him!
His fate fed him anger!
...Hawk Gatling!
What?! What the hell is that?!
Where did it come from?!
And they changed this man
into a perfect demon!
A slim guy came out of the mucus!
You'd better know what you've done!
No less, the ultimate evil!
Second Gear!
It's no use!
This is why my punch got through his body!
Even if you kill me, it's
too late for you to...
Gum-Gum...
I won't let you get away with this!
...Red Hawk!
Doffy is...
...the true king who was chosen by heaven!
Law!!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Stamp!
So what?!
Break White!
Doffy!!
Oh, shoot!
Damn! How about this?!
Doffy! Are you alright?
Third Gear!
Damn you, Law...
Hey, Tra-guy!
Why are you bleeding so much?!
This can't be happening!
Gum-Gum...
Our king has been brought down
by such small-fry pirates like them!
What happened to your arm?
Hey!
...Grizzly Magnum!
Stay with me! Tra-guy! Hey!
Tra-guy!!
What an idiot!
--You jerk!
--Wait! Straw Hat-ya!
You're wide open!
I can't believe you used...
He's dead... It's obvious.
You're lying!
...your disembodied arm...!
I'm not. It seemed like he trusted
you so much but what a shame.
How annoying...!
So you don't wanna
let Law's attack go to waste, huh?
He said you can work miracles.
Can you, Straw Hat?
Tra-guy...
When it comes to this...
How long will it take you...
I didn't think you were that strong
when I fought you, though...
Mingo!!
...to take me down?
Doffy won't care if you're a kid or not.
Now, bring it on! There are the two of us!
If you do it right, you can get promoted quickly
but if you're useless, that's it.
How dare you bastards!
Law...
You die with me!
By a one-hour time limit, I mean...
Well, good luck.
Gum-Gum...
Pentachromatic Strings!
...the Birdcage will take that long
to completely collapse.
Your name is Law, isn't it?
Oh no! He's gonna set fire!
This guy who just returned
is an executive like us.
...Battle-Axe!
I'll take you along!
His name is Corazon.
He's an absent-minded idiot but...
...he's strong, maybe because of his blood.
Gum-Gum...
Cora-san...
...Giant Whip!
The Royal Palace burst into flames!
Armament Hardening!
Nooo!
What's going on?!
White monster!
Please leave! I beg you!
I'm sure there are people
who have a leg problem.
Wh-What happened this time?!
What the hell is that?
There are also bedridden old people
and babies at the breast.
Corazon, not only have I not gotten
cured but I'm at my limit...
Luffy!
Hey, Viola! What's going on at the Royal Palace?!
Gum-Gum...
Stop whining!
You'll get cured in the next one!
Doffy is a charismatic evil.
...Spring Bullet!
Who will fall victim first?
Go to hell!
You... stabbed me... that day but...
After 30 minutes,
people start dying somewhere.
Mingo!!
Gum-Gum...
One of the executives, Trebol got defeated!
After 40 minutes, we will hear screams here.
...it didn't hurt at all!
Is Luffy okay?!
I know you were the one who was in pain!
After 50 minutes,
Doffy's madness will...
the whole country will be covered in red
as if tomatoes have been crushed.
Doflamingo!
You poor thing!
...destroy everything!
Straw Hat!
Law!
--Great! He's alive!
--Yes!
It makes Doflamingo the only one remaining!
You almost got me.
After an hour,
there will be no voice whatsoever.
Luffy! Doflamingo!
Luffyland!
I know what will happen to Dressrosa
is none of your concern but...
Is he all right?
We got to back him up somehow!
Yeah!
You'd better not do anything.
You might give him trouble to be honest.
...people who are going to die will
hold a grudge against you guys.
Look! Even Trafalgar Law who has
the same title of Warlord as Doflamingo, is...
If only you guys hadn't come here,
Dressrosa could have been peaceful!
That bastard is...
Is there something wrong?
Hey, can you even move?!
…in quite bad shape!
No...
Cut the crap! It was only on the surface!
Lawland!
Luffy!
Luffy! Hand me Tra-guy-kun!
Hey, Law.
Robin! That'll help!
...Eagle...
Take him! Tra-guy cornered Mingo enough already!
I love you!
...Bazooka!
Oh no! His arm...!
You see unlucky people everywhere
in the world.
Wait! Stay where you are!
Cien Fleurs! Spider Net!
What?
If you try to save them all, there's no end.
That bastard is my responsibility...!
You're just a passing pirate.
Are you trying to be a hero?
Athlete!
How dare you get in my way!
No! You got in my way!
--I hear something.
--Wh-What is it?
What?
What's wrong?
You made my friends cry and
made my crewmates mad!
Lawland's arm is...
How could they do this?!
Tra-guy-kun, stay with me!
No, it was just my imagination.
Nico Robin!
Don't do anything unnecessary!
He's still breathing.
But you still haven't fallen
so I will take everything upon myself!
No, it is moving!
Don't get in my way!
Straw Hat!
He hasn't been dismissed yet.
--Oh, please...
--The wall of strings is...
I won't let anybody die!
Doflamingo!
Room!
That jerk! He's still going for Tra-guy!
Shrinking!
Here's a finisher!
Gum-Gum...
You and the Birdcage are standing in my way!
Bullet String!
...Hawk Whip!
I'll let you follow Law in death shortly.
Cora-san...
I finally can attain your ambition!
Damn!
Let's bring an end to this game.
Robiland!
Mingo!!
Tra-guy! Robin!
--Wait.
--What?
It's over. Doflamingo!
Fourth...
Listen carefully, Straw Hat-ya.
...Gear!
Doflamingo's cold-blooded extermination
plan is finally put in motion!
Luffy clashes with Trebol,
the last top executive standing!
Carrying on Law's ambition and with everybody's hopes
on his shoulders, Luffy fights!
Luffy's secret stratagem, the new,
strongest-ever special technique finally blasts!
Doflamingo received a mortal
wound from Law's attack!
However, none of his attacks with Haki of the Color of Arms work against Trebol,
The shrinking wall of strings cuts up Dressrosa!
There is only one hour left!
However, the absolute king never falls!
Doflamingo's powerful techniques squarely target him!
Luffy's ability, that has evolved
and he gets driven into a corner!
Red Hawk blasts!
When he is about to give a
final blow to a paralyzed Law,
unimaginably in power, speed, and
everything, overwhelms Doflamingo!
While time is ticking away until all people
in Dressrosa get wiped out,
When it seems like every
hope has been dashed,
When Trebol exercises his secret technique which will
Luffy stands in his way,
a tenacious attack that takes a
one-and-only chance, rings out!
and the Supreme King vs. the Supreme King -
the battle of the ultimate Haki - finally begins!
the all-out decisive battle
between the two now begins!
burn up everything, Luffy and Law are pushed to the extremes!
A breathtaking fierce onslaught
to turn the whole thing around, begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Anger Erupts! I Will Take Everything upon Myself!"
"Unassailable! The Stunning Secret of Trebol!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Collision of Haki! Luffy vs. Doflamingo!"
"Fourth Gear! The Phenomenal Bounce-Man!"
"A Blade of Tenacity! The
Gamma Knife Counterattack!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!