Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Donquixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
Your death is inevitable.
Die in vain like a dog!
But, if you're gonna die anyway,
wouldn't you rather make something out of it?
It's meaningful for both of us.
I'm only gonna say this once so listen carefully,
Trafalgar D. Water Law.
Perform the Perpetual Youth Surgery
which is the ultimate Op-Op
technique on me and...
...die.
In exchange, I'll grant
your wish, whatever it is.
Oh, that's great!
Then,
bring Cora-san back to
life for me, right now!
When you finish with that,
go lick all the butts of the people in this country!
The Straw Hats have worked so many miracles
up until today.
You can't take down Straw Hat-ya!
You can't take back Caesar from him as well!
Doflamingo!!
Hey, Tra-guy!
Why are you bleeding so much?!
What happened to your arm? Hey!
Stay with me! Tra-guy! Hey!
He's dead... It's obvious.
How dare you bastards!
Let's bring an end to this game.
Mingo!!
--Wait.
--What?
Listen carefully, Straw Hat-ya.
"A Blade of Tenacity!
The Gamma Knife Counterattack!"
Look...
It's moving as I thought!
The wall of strings is moving!
The houses and the buildings are being sliced
and they're collapse!
Run!
Not even the edge of the town is safe!
--Hurry up!
--Run! Run!
To the downtown!
This is the northern town!
We have an emergency!
The Birdcage started moving all of a sudden
and cutting up the town!
It's the same in the west!
This is the eastern town, Carta!
As they say, the Birdcage
is shrinking it seems!
The islanders are running towards
the downtown at once!
THE ROYAL PALACE
Everybody'll die.
Sooner or later.
Straw Hat. Did you notice?
The plot of the game has been changed.
The game?!
What are you saying after all this time?!
Well, just listen.
The Birdcage that is surrounding the town
started shrinking little by little.
It's like an umbrella closing slowly...
What?!
It'll cut up everything in this country.
Within...
...an hour or so.
Wherever you run, it's no use.
Run! If you stay here,
you'll get cut up into pieces!
Doflamingo!
How dare he do such a terrible thing!
It's horrible! So cruel!
I don't wanna die! Run!
Go save the people who are at the
edges of the country quickly!
Yes, sir!
Are you okay?!
Th-Thank you...
The Birdcage is closing in!
Hurry to the downtown!
We helped the weakest ones evacuate
the farthest end of the town! Hurry up!
Hurry to the center of the town!
Run! The strings are coming!
Hey, somebody, help!
Just undoing the rope on my feet is fine!
Untie it! I don't wanna die!
Th-Th-The Birdcage is shrinking?!
THE OLD KING'S PLATEAU
Is it for real?!
Oh my...
What should we do?! What can we do?!
Hey, Zoro!
The cage closing in?!
What will happen to us?!
I thought we finally got out of bars
but we're behind bars, again?!
Where are we supposed to run?!
How could he do such a dirty thing?!
Haven't you had enough yet, Doflamingo?!
If the cage keeps shrinking like this...
Dressrosa will be finished!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF
THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 2
What is that smoke and that rumbling?!
What's going on?!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
- LEVEL 4 THE SUNFLOWER FIELD
What's really happening?!
I'm sure that guy set up something again!
Doflamingo!
Luffy! Hurry up! Kick Doflamingo's ass!
--That's all we can do now!
--That's right! Indeed! Certainly!
But that's too much to ask.
All lives throughout the country
are down to Luffy-dono.
I'm counting on you! Luffy-dono!
I'm counting on you, too!
I'm not willing to save anybody.
What's the advantage of letting people
who learned the secret
of the country survive?
Towns, people, animals...
And your allies...
And you! Everything!
So your friends died just a little before...
Right, Straw Hat-ya?
That's what he used to call you.
He died so miserably.
Oh, Law, he shouldn't have messed with us...
Today, Dressrosa will...
...perish.
Oh, you don't have to worry.
I'll build a country again.
Mingo! If I kick your ass,
everything'll be okay!
I was trying to suggest
that you can't do that!
Fallbright!
You never learn! Bullet String!
Gum-Gum...
Go to hell! Together with Law!
Shambles!
Law!
You're the one that'll perish! Doflamingo!
Go!
This operation will destroy you
from inside your body!
Gamma Knife!
Doffy!
Law! How are you still alive?!
How did you make an OP-OP attack
without creating a Room?!
No, we're in a Room now!
It'll shorten my life somewhat
but I've put up a Room
which is so big you can't even see it!
What?!
For this moment and for this attack!
It wasn't a fatal wound!
Shambles!
First of all, your pirate group
is called the Heart Pirates!
Who are you aiming the satire at?!
You don't even sit on the Heart seat
then why are you bearing
the mark of the Heart?!
Law!
I'm sorry, body double...
I'll return once it's over.
Doflamingo!!
Shambles.
Hey, Tra-guy!
Why are you bleeding so much?!
What happened to your arm?
He's dead... It's obvious.
Mingo!!
--Wait.
--What?
I'm alive.
Listen carefully, Straw Hat-ya.
Don't turn around! I have a plan!
Nobody can defend an attack
that comes from inside their body!
Even you can't counteract this technique!
Doffy! You're a king!
Don't fall on your knees anymore!
You'd better know what you've done!
It's no use!
Even if you kill me, it's
too late for you to...
I won't let you get away with this!
Law!!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Stamp!
Doffy!!
Doffy! Are you alright?
This can't be happening!
Our king has been brought down
by such small-fry pirates like them!
--You jerk!
--Wait! Straw Hat-ya!
Tra-guy...
Doffy won't care if you're a kid or not.
If you do it right, you can get promoted quickly
but if you're useless, that's it.
Well, good luck.
Your name is Law, isn't it?
This guy who just returned
is an executive like us.
His name is Corazon.
He's an absent-minded idiot but...
...he's strong, maybe because of his blood.
Cora-san...
Nooo!
White monster!
Please leave! I beg you!
Corazon, not only have I not gotten
cured but I'm at my limit...
Stop whining!
You'll get cured in the next one!
You... stabbed me... that day but...
...it didn't hurt at all!
I know you were the one who was in pain!
You poor thing!
Law!
That bastard is...
Hey, can you even move?!
Hey, Law.
I love you!
That bastard is my responsibility...!
Room!
Cora-san...
I finally can attain your ambition!
It's over. Doflamingo!
Doflamingo received a mortal
wound from Law's attack!
However, the absolute king never falls!
When he is about to give a
final blow to a paralyzed Law,
Luffy stands in his way,
and the Supreme King vs. the Supreme King -
the battle of the ultimate Haki - finally begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Collision of Haki! Luffy vs. Doflamingo!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!