I don't hold a grudge against you guys but...
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to make my dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for small success, making excuses
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air, off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit me, and even if I fall again
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari mae wo mita mono dake ga
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal, we got to carry on the way
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without thinking of the consequences
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
But caught up in the current king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along with the entire island.
The executives of the Donquixote
Family have been taken down
However, by the actions of the Straw Hats,
The executives of the Donquixote
Family have been taken down
However, by the actions of the Straw Hats,
one after another, after hard
battles, by the Straw Hats,
the executives of the Donquixote Family
have been taken down one after another,
one after another, after hard
battles, by the Straw Hats,
the executives of the Donquixote Family
have been taken down one after another,
The executives of the Donquixote Family have been taken down
one after another, after hard battles, by the Straw Hats,
and finally, there is only Doflamingo left!
and Doflamingo alone remains.
The time has come for a one-on-one duel
between Luffy and Doflamingo
But he has caused the Birdcage to constrict
in order to kill all the people in the country.
The time has come for a one-on-one duel
between Luffy and Doflamingo that shakes up Dressrosa!
and finally, there is only Doflamingo left!
that shakes up Dressrosa!
The time has come for a one-on-one duel
between Luffy and Doflamingo that shakes up Dressrosa!
Fourth Gear?
As the moment of Dressrosa's
destruction closes in,
I have to leave the rest to Straw Hat-ya!
Muscle Balloon!
the deadly battle between Luffy and Doflamingo
finally enters the final phase.
If he's gonna win,
The unknown gladiator Lucy...
It's time for you to drop dead.
I wanna see it through with my own eyes here!
Muscle Balloon!
It was you, wasn't it?
Gum-Gum...
I'm running out of time!
Uh-huh.
...Grizzly Magnum!
Doflamingo's on his way!
What are you gonna do about your duel?!
Is there something I can do?!
Billow-White!
You're wide open!
I need ten minutes...
Fourth...
...Gear...
Ten minutes?
You see unlucky people everywhere
in the world.
If I regain my Haki, I'm sure I
can finish him off with one blow!
Mingo!
...Bounce-Man!
If you try to save them all, there's no end.
You're just a passing pirate.
Are you trying to be a hero?
Get blown away!
Hey, if we give you ten minutes,
will you get us out of the Birdcage?!
...Bounce-Man!
Rhino Schneider!
How dare you get in my way!
Damn brat!
Gum-Gum...
Hey, Straw Hat!
No! You got in my way!
This is it!
...Kong...
...Culverin!
Gum-Gum...
You made my friends cry and
made my crewmates mad!
Athlete!
...Gun!
I promise!
A crappy attack like that...
Come on, Straw Hat!
...won't work!
...Leo Bazooka!
I'll make you regret it all!
But you still haven't fallen
so I will take everything upon myself!
Gum-Gum...
Rhino Schneider!
"Tears of Miracles!
Mansherry's Fight!"
I won't let anybody die!
...Culverin!
Athlete!
You and the Birdcage are standing in my way!
Armored but still rubbery?!
The Birdcage isn't gone!
It won't work!
Damn!
That jerk, Doflamingo will go
to any lengths at this point!
Enough! Fall on the ground already!
Gum-Gum...
Fourth...
What else can he do?!
...Gear!
"A Massive Counterattack!
Doflamingo's Awakening!"
He created the Birdcage
and he's turning the town into strings!
...Culverin!
This is it for Dressrosa!
"Fourth Gear!
The Phenomenal Bounce-Man!"
Just run! The only way to survive is
to get away from the downtown area!
H-Hey, what's the matter, Straw Hat Luffy?!
The whole area is a battlefield now!
If you get caught up in it, you're gonna die!
Everybody, listen.
I'm...
...the former king of Dressrosa - Riku Doldo III.
--A rubber ball is...
--...Overwhelming...
I'm not gonna get cut up
by that Birdcage crap!
...Doflamingo!
You're right!
Hurry to the downtown area!
Wh-What is it?
The Donquixote Family
that we thought nobody could match has...
"Flame Dragon King!
Protect Luffy's Life!"
--Hey, don't push!
--Watch out! I'm gonna get crushed!
...almost been wiped out by the hands of the tough warriors
who only happened to be here in this country!
I have children!
Stop! Stop!
All of the Family's executives are
already taken down!
Stop! Don't push!
Hey, why are you running
in the opposite direction?!
Really?!
The only enemy there is left to beat...
We gotta get to the downtown area!
...is the current king of Dressrosa - Doflamingo!
--The downtown area is a battlefield now!
--What?!
Who is it?!
A battlefield?
Doflamingo is running wild
looking for Straw Hat!
It doesn't matter!
And the one who is fighting him is
the pirate - Straw Hat Luffy!
--Go for it!
--You can do it!
If you go to the area,
you'll get slashed by the strings!
I believe he is the man
who will destroy the Birdcage for us!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
Did you see that?!
Yeah...
Whether he wins or loses,
it'll only take several dozen minutes!
Can't believe how he changed.
Is it really Straw Hat?
--What?! Then...
--Where should we run to?!
I don't want any one of you to get crushed
by the constriction of the country!
He's overpowering the formidable Doflamingo!
He's amazingly strong!
King Riku-sama,
what are we supposed to do?
Keep running!
But he's using Haki too much.
Even if you run out of breath!
Or even if your leg breaks!
Just for several dozen minutes,
try to survive!
Using Haki too much?
There is hope!
Please don't give up!
"Luffy!
An All-Out Leo Bazooka!"
How are they doing?!
Not good! They've been knocked down
and can't even stand on their feet!
Straw Hat, where did he go?!
Even the proud warrior of Elbaph
used up all of his energy?
Oh, there he is.
They went to play somewhere else.
Run! Run!
I took the trouble to come see them!
How annoying!
Run to the center of the island!
The captain of the first ship of the Blackbeard Pirates -
Jesus Burgess.
What's that?
I was wondering where he went
after the battle in the Colosseum but...
He's right!
Yeah!
...I found him here.
Don't give up!
Chase them or wait...
Either way, I won't let them get away!
Run!
I'll get what I wanna get for sure!
S-Straw Hat Luffy...
Hurry up! Run to the downtown!
B-Buildings that haven't been cut apart...
He's going after Luffy-kun
and the others as I thought.
I gotta live! For my baby's sake, too!
What does he want?
THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
Hajrudin!
There's still hope!
...are getting pushed by the Cage
and closing in on us!
M-Maybe, he can't fight anymore...
Viola.
Believe!
Armament!
All that remains is the decisive battle
between him and Luffy-kun?
If you go near, you'll get
caught up in it and die!
The country's getting smaller!
Yes, that's right, Father-sama.
Don't get involved!
Get away from the pirate!
Doflamingo is the only one remaining now,
That guy will save this country!
from their forces from the
rank of executive or above.
If Luffy-kun takes down Doflamingo,
the Birdcage that is slicing up the town will vanish
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF
THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 2
There's no time to lose!
and the Doflamingo Family falls apart.
Is that what you mean?
The Birdcage is shrinking?!
That's what is causing this confusion.
Yes.
This is the real threat of the Birdcage.
What are you doing, Zoro-dono?!
Trying to stop it with your swords?!
The full account of how he robbed the country
has been revealed to the nation.
It isn't something you can stop
by just pushing!
Where did they go?! Did they get lost?
How do you know that?!
Things won't go as he pleases anymore.
Zoro-dono!
You're going the wrong way!
That's why he wants to destroy everything.
If you have time to chat
away that it's impossible,
The Young Master does such things
without hesitation, honey!
What?!
help me, you half-baked idiots!
You're bad at directions so if we just follow you,
we'll never get there!
It's just the ability of one person!
I can't believe this!
This is a really big deal!
Now, why don't you ride on this?
There's no rational reason for me
to believe I can't stop it!
It won't work!
What is that weird vehicle?
--Let's do it, Kin'emon!
--Yes, let's go!
Oh! I called him "honey" again!
Here we go with our hot and sweet married life!
Tsk! He's so tenacious!
It's a Spring Sparrow.
Kanjuro called it over
from the King's Plateau!
I can't just wait for death to come
sucking on my thumb!
Don't hesitate.
Now, hurry up and get on!
Damn! The strings are in my way
and I can't get near!
Rouse the fallen allies right away, too!
Me getting on this Stupid Sparrow?
Alright!
Oh, he's taking control of the tough ones.
It's a Spring Sparrow.
I don't feel like it but I have no choice.
He's developing as a leader more and more.
Straw Hat the pirate!
I gotta hurry...
Let's go!
Oh! And I'm the one
who takes control of things at home!
Stay with me! Hey! Can you still fight?!
Mingo!
If the battle lasts long,
this plateau will be cut into pieces, too.
IN FRONT OF THE SMILE FACTORY
What?! I thought this is the center of the country!
Isn't it the safest place?!
Do you recognize me?
Are you ready?!
It's Gyats!
We are!
I'm the announcer at the Colosseum, Gyats!
The factory is made of Sea Prism Stone!
It won't be damaged!
Look at the sky!
Spring Sparrow! You can do it!
The center of the Birdcage is
moving little by little.
Show me everything that you got!
The unknown gladiator Lucy...
Damn!
The center of the contraction
is probably the plateau -
All right! Get ready!
It was you, wasn't it?
the current location of the Royal
Palace, where Doflamingo is!
Uh-huh.
I thought so!
Push the factory!
THE CURRENT LOCATION
THE ROYAL PALACE
There aren't many small
guys who are that strong!
That means eventually, this place will...
Break White!
That was close!
Hurry up, Hack! Please hurry up!
Push! Push!
Stop shaking me!
Push!
Doflamingo's on his way!
You're annoying!
It finally got here.
Not yet, not yet! Push, push!
What are you gonna do about your duel?!
Is there something I can do?!
Push!
Now we're down here and it's quite chaotic.
Get out of the factory, Tontattas!
THE SMILE FACTORY
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF
THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 2
That way, huh!
Okay!
I need ten minutes...
--Zoro and the others are pushing the Birdcage?
--Yes.
We gotta escape!
Super hurry up and come on out!
Zoro-dono!
Where are you going?!
Ten minutes?
Is it possible to stop it?
I don't know. I didn't even think of that.
It's obvious, isn't it?
After I use the Bounce-Man,
I can't use my Haki for ten minutes.
What?!
I'm going to stop it, of course!
Okay! That's so like him!
It's time for you to drop dead.
It!
We completed the rescue of
our stranded friends in the factory!
"It"?!
B-Boun...?
I'm running out of time!
I need to keep my distance
No!!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
THE SOUTH SIDE
Good!
but I don't know what he's
gonna do during that time.
The factory is tilting!
If I regain my Haki,
What a surprise.
Fall to the ground! Straw Hat!
I'm sure I can finish him off with one blow!
Fraland!
I didn't know there were
Dwarves in Dressrosa.
This is what the Young Master-sama wants!
Why is the SMILE Factory
alone not getting cut?!
On top of that,
their princess even has power to heal.
What?! Get out of our way!
Only the factory?
--Oh yeah, it's the Sea Prism Stone!
--Sea Prism Stone?
I hope your arm gets reconnected properly.
Yeah, the outer walls of the factory are
made of Sea Prism Stone.
The whole town is turning into strings!
How rude.
They said when blood starts
flowing, it'll be cured.
Billow-White!
I know. I'm a doctor.
That's why it doesn't get cut by the strings
that the Devil Fruit eater created.
Stay away! This is the New King's Plateau!
When I saw the underground trade port,
I understood...
Only the Donquixote Family members
are allowed in here!
But, look!
Are you gonna bounce up and down
like a rubber ball again, Straw Hat?
What Family?!
Even the executives are gone!
Mingo!
This is the safest place! Let us climb up!
I'm...
It's starting to get pushed!
...back!
Shut up! You fools are condemned criminals!
Hm? That's...
--Franky!
--Oh, Robot-dono!
Get blown away!
This battle... Even if we can take down Doflamingo,
it won't be over.
By the Young Master-sama's judgment,
this country will be completely renewed!
Ten minutes!
Then, his horrible reign will be over?!
Zoroland! Topknot-land!
Barrier-Barrier...
It'll cause tremendous ripples
across the world.
Damn brat!
Hey, if we give you ten minutes,
will you get us out of the Birdcage?!
Hey, Zoro! Kin'emon!
...Pistol!
The center of the country is
in the direction you flew from!
And you guys will be
the object of everyone's attention.
If you wanna run, go straight back!
What?! We aren't running!
We'll go stop the strings!
Yeah...
Go away, you left-overs!
I'm well aware that's what'll happen.
Stop them?
Oh, I didn't even think about that!
The fighters from the Colosseum!
What?! That's cool!
Bartolomeo!
Until Luffy settles this, we gotta buy time!
Mingo!
Hey, Straw Hat!
Hajrudin!
Stop the strings... But how?
You little squirt! Don't put on airs!
Don Chin Jao!
I promise!
Fourth Gear?
Punch!
That's right.
Oh yeah!
In order to kick your ass,
THE DOWNTOWN
LUFFY VS. DOFLAMINGO
All right!
I'll get stronger!
Ten minutes!
We'll leave it up to you guys!
This is it!
Army Commander Kyros is here, too!
Gum-Gum...
It's neither Second...
...nor Third!
Why am I able to move?
So am I. I didn't think I
could move with that injury.
Count on us!
Ten minutes will pass by like a flash!
You gotta come back quickly
and bring down that Dofla-guy, Lucy!
Don't let your guard down yet!
...Leo Bazooka!
He's controlling the expansion
and contraction of rubber
This is a life-support procedure for Dressrosa,
that Princess Mansherry chose to take!
We'll do our best!
as he wants, with the Color of Arms...
They're all the competitors
from the fighting event!
Life-support?
What do you mean, dwarf?
The ones who wouldn't help you earlier!
Muscle Balloon!
Harmonizing the Armament and rubber, huh?
In any case, everybody,
claw your way to this plateau!
Sorry, Lucy!
We were blinded by greed over
the prizes on your heads!
The center of the Birdcage
is moving this way!
--Yeah!
--You saved us, Kyros-sama!
We didn't even dream of cornering Doflamingo!
Hey, men! Don't depend on others!
I'm sorry!
As a token of our apology,
we'll believe in you and risk our lives!
Those who have the physical strength,
come with us!
If I take too much time, Fourth Gear will...
Sorry if we happen to beat him first!
What?! He wants me to come with him?!
Seems like you're using your abilities pretty well
but it must be quite a burden...
There must be some risks.
Gum-Gum...
Straw Hat, how many more
seconds can you stand?
--Hey, where are you going?!
--Doflamingo!
If he's not gonna come out,
I'm gonna pull him out!
...Double...
My strings, however, won't run out!
Fourth...
...Gear...
Straw Hat!
...Culverin!
Off-White!
H-How did the strings
come out of the ground?!
...Bounce-Man!
Thank you for everything,
Mr. Heavenly Demon!
What did you do to this town?!
Why don't you hang out with us for a while?
Listen, fledgling!
Devil Fruit abilities have...
I said "Don't push"!
...yet another stage to
them called "Awakening"!
What is that noise?
Whoa-whoa, is this some kind of a joke?
Wh-What the...
You got quite big...
Look at that inflated body of yours!
--Here he comes! Here he comes!
--Kick his ass!
I thought you had a secret
stratagem or something...
The buildings turned into strings!
Okay, now is the chance!
D... D...
Can't you be more serious?!
The remaining half of you, follow me!
Hey, that's...
The ability will awaken rarely and begin to
affect things other than its user's body!
This is my secret stratagem and I am serious!
Doflamingo!
Yeah!
--Isn't it getting faster than before?!
--Yeah, it sure is!
You can't even stand straight
since you're bouncy because you're rubber.
Listen, guys! Ten minutes!
Ten minutes to go!
The speed of the contraction
of the Birdcage increased!
Various things are turning into strings!
It doesn't look like the power of a Paramythia!
How can you kick my ass like that?
It's over... This is really it this time!
Let's get through it at any cost!
Everything that surrounds
you turns into strings!
Yeah!
For two years,
I fought against monstrously-big,
savage beasts!
You can't even come near me!
Watch out!
Please help us, King Riku-sama!
Go to hell, Straw Hat!
And when your strength gives out,
my body will...
We can't make it through!
To wrestle them to the ground,
B-Burgess?!
H-He did it!
I needed this giant body and bounciness!
Stop it! Doflamingo!
He really took down Doflamingo!
How would bounciness help you...?
Shut up!
You won't...
Armament!
Sabo!
...be able to do anything!
Take this!
That's...
Gum-Gum...
That guy... Don't tell me he's...
...Kong...
Those moves!
...Gun!
Luffy!
The body that stretches like rubber!
His Haki is fading.
Ow! Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch...!
Yeah, it's no mistake!
He did it!
You're such a canny guy!
Dressrosa has been saved now!
I can say the same about you!
The rubber ball!
No, he isn't just a rubber ball.
How persistent!
Go to hell, Straw Hat!
According to King Riku-sama, he is...
...the pirate - Straw Hat Luffy!
Hope this tires you out!
Is it speeding up?!
Lucy the gladiator!
We don't have much time, Luffy.
When your Haki gives out,
I'll give you the finishing blow!
Thank you, Straw Hat!
The way the strings move has changed.
It's getting faster!
No, wait a minute...
What?! That's not fair! What should we do?!
His face looks scarier and his body is rounder
than the guy on the newspaper.
We'll get cut! Run!
--Th-That guy is...
--Oh, the Three-Star criminal!
--Is it really him?!
--What?
Wh-What happened?
We can't make it!
It fell from the sky.
Wh-What?!
He's the Chief of Staff of
the Revolutionary Army!
It's getting faster?!
Are you Straw Hat Luffy?!
I-It sure is!
Sabo!
I'm Sabo from the Revolutionary Army!
Straw Hat Luffy is my brother!
What? Yeah.
The pressure is increasing!
I heard he's like an eight-meter-tall monster.
Push! Put more power into it!
What was it?
--Can't believe it!
--What?
What? What?!
Get to the downtown!
--He's not more than four meters tall.
--That means he's a fake?
What do you want from him, Burgess?
What's wrong, Viola?!
Did you see something?!
Hurry up or we'll get cut!
Straw Hat is your brother?!
Hey, rubber ball.
Are you Straw Hat himself?
Straw Hat turned into a
never-before-seen form and...
Come on!
Oh, grandma!
You guys are bugging me!
I've heard someone say that before.
Grandma, stand up! The strings will cut you!
...made Doflamingo...
Why do you keep bouncing up and down?
Can't you stop?
I can't...
I can't.
D-Doflamingo!
I can't run anymore...
Why is he here?!
Leave me here and go ahead!
Push!
No! No! I can't do such a thing!
I bet "Fire Fist" Ace said it, too.
We're three brothers.
Hey, what was that?!
I just heard something loud!
What?!
What's the matter?!
I won't survive this anyway.
What?!
We're getting pushed back!
Please get up!
Viola?
It's speeding up! Don't let
it get the better of you!
Back off! Back off!
Even if I get up, I definitely
can't run to the downtown!
Ace? I see.
Why are you here?! Doflamingo!
Push harder than you've ever pushed before!
Straw Hat... won!
I get it now.
Okay!
Push!
You sure?!
I'd like to know that myself.
Push!
After the duel on Banaro Island,
you Blackbeard Pirates captured Ace
Somebody! Help us!
Yes, it's our chance to show off!
There are still patients in the hospital!
Yeah!
Run! He's gonna kill us!
and it triggered the ugly Paramount War!
We can't carry them all by ourselves! Please!
Amazing!
How destructive that was!
There's no way he's still alive!
P-Pl...
There's nowhere to run!
There's the Birdcage out there!
Please...
Die in darkness!
Hey, look up in the sky!
Fire Emperor!
Come on out, Straw Hat!
The sun or the darkness --
there'll be only one winner!
My son's missing! Didn't anybody see him?!
I'm in the downtown, huh?
I really got flung pretty far...
I'm gonna make Whitebeard the king!
He's wearing a Kuma shirt!
He's five years old!
Help!
Hurry up! The shrinking speed is increasing!
Somebody! Did you see my son?!
It's no good.
My son...
Outta my way!
Three minutes to go until
the Birdcage reaches
the downtown area and completes the massacre.
You've got to be kidding!
We can't make it!
Four minutes to go until
Luffy's Haki is regained.
Ace made the choice himself.
He's flying using the elastic force!
Everybody's gonna die anyway...
There is a one-minute difference between
the time the Birdcage will close completely
and the time Luffy will wake up.
Let's give up...
...I'm watching Luffy's back hereafter!
Remember that!
Overheat!
No matter how far we run, we're in the cage.
The Birdcage isn't gone!
We'll only get killed by Doflamingo.
It's easier...
...to just give up.
Gum-Gum...
How dare that bastard do that?!
No way...
Before Lucy comes back,
this country will be shredded to pieces!
...Rhino Schneider!
That means Doflamingo is...
I have no interest in
your relationship to him!
We gotta do something about it ourselves!
Not dead yet.
Take down Doflamingo and
make the Birdcage go away!
Don't get in my way!
Straw Hat-ya...
I have no business with you
or the Revolutionary Army!
Somebody else has come!
I only have business with...
He's big! He kicked Doflamingo away!
Damn! One more strike!
Why can't you guys get it?
You have no business with me?
Not even personally?
It's my message to you:
"Give me Straw Hat."
It's all mine, isn't it?
Barrier!
Damn! He ate the Flare-Flare Fruit!
Who is that ball-like guy?!
Ace!
Gum-Gum...
I take over your ability!
King Riku-sama...
It's holding out!
What's going on?! Is Luffy winning?!
Only you could've done it! Rooster-kun!
Fire Fist!
Oh! Robin-senpai!
I don't deserve such words of praise!
Amazing...
L-L-L-L-L-L-L-Luffy-senpai!
So strong!
Now, let's do it, guys!
What is that?! A new technique?!
Must be a new technique!
Everybody, listen.
My barrier will never break! Push!
I see it now. That was you!
I'm...
What?! Flare-Flare?!
Hey, you!
Do you know how awesome this is?!
...the former king of
Dressrosa - Riku Doldo III.
Hey, Luffy. You've been hurt badly.
H-Hey, what's the matter, Straw Hat Luffy?!
Witnessing such a rare moment!
We couldn't be luckier!
Doflamingo is on his way and I think
my hands will be full with Burgess.
Follow Zoro-senpai!
Wh-What is it?
K-King Riku-sama...
Oh, I can't stop shaking!
This country is now, by the game
that the current king Doflamingo started,
I'll be okay.
Can't see!
Cats and the others will buy me some time.
Lucy...
It's Gyats!
King!
I'll take down Mingo no matter what!
in a giant Birdcage with no visible escape.
Make a collective effort and push!
You've become so dependable!
On top of that, that vicious Birdcage
keeps shrinking, slicing up the town.
Leave that one in my hands!
Sabo!
It's strange.
You ate Ace's Fruit, didn't you?
Damn!
How could they exert that much power
with those injured bodies?
By hardening his skin with the Color of Arms,
he's multiplying the tension of his skin!
Jesus Burgess!
Why was he here at the Palace?!
I wouldn't let anybody else have it.
It's a memento of him!
Just a few minutes ago, they were burned out
and couldn't even stand up.
King Riku-sama...
No kidding! He jumped down!
I can't believe how far he can jump!
Yeah!
You fell on this reality too suddenly.
That's great!
Hello? Sabo-kun?
I'll be taking that ability!
I'm sure your emotions can't even catch up
That ball-looking bastard!
He's nothing but rubber!
What were those fluffs?
Come in! Hello?!
Okay, look after him, Pets!
and you're just trying to save your own,
or somebody else's, life now!
That bastard Straw Hat is barely alive!
Now's my chance!
It's Gyats! I got it!
--They were Dandelixers.
--Dandelixers?
Yes!
Galleon...
They are dandelions made from
the components of Princess Mansherry's tears.
But this is not a dream!
...Lariat!
Nor a tragedy that has begun today!
What?! That's...
For a decade,
The captain of the first ship of
Emperor Blackbeard's pirate group -
we have always lived in the
Birdcage called Dressrosa
under the reign of the pirates!
"Champ" Burgess!
Wait for me! Wait for me!
--Hurry up! Or you'll get cut!
--Run faster!
Straw Hat! Stop messing with me!
Wait for me!
I'll kill you and rob it from you now!
I can't! Damn!
For a decade, we have always been puppets
that live under their manipulation.
Burning Dragon Claw Fist!
I can't believe I twisted my ankle now!
The Gum-Gum Fruit!
That is reality!
You can do it!
Pentachromatic Strings!
It's hot!
What?! I can run!
But that will end soon!
Bullet String!
So fast! What's going on?!
What?
--Are you okay?
--Don't.
The Donquixote Family
that we thought nobody could match has...
The fluffs of Dandelixers can give people
over a wide area miraculous ultra-recoveries.
Flame Dragon King!
Don't go near him blindly. He's a pirate, too.
...almost been wiped out by the
hands of the tough warriors
I told you!
You're no match for me in Fourth Gear!
You don't know what he's thinking.
How could you say that?!
He fought against Doflamingo for us!
who only happened to be here in this country!
Princess Mansherry is worrying about
what's happening to Dressrosa
All of the Family's executives are
already taken down!
Here I come, Mingo!
Really?!
I-I can't believe it! He blew away
the subordinate of one of the Four Emperors!
and is shedding tears now.
She's right!
At least, he isn't our enemy!
--Those executives have...
--...Brought down, he means?!
Prepare yourself!
I believe that will save so many lives!
So strong! That's what I'd expect from
the No.2 of the Revolutionary Army!
Don't push your luck!
Still, I can't trust him!
The only enemy there is left to beat...
So that's why those immobile fighters are...
...is the current king of
Dressrosa - Doflamingo!
He's a pirate like Doflamingo is!
But the drawback of this ability is
that it's only a temporary ultra-recovery!
Just for a few minutes!
As soon as he saw the Flare-Flare Fruit power,
he changed his focus to me.
I'm afraid they'll revert to their
former state when the time comes!
So his objective is,
So this is just a life-support procedure to
survive for now!
And the one who is fighting him is
the pirate - Straw Hat Luffy!
as they say,
hunting down Devil Fruit eaters.
What?!
The pain is gone suddenly!
I believe he is the man
who will destroy the Birdcage for us!
I can run! I can get away!
But...
It's a miracle, doctor!
Gum-Gum...
Hey, Lucy! What's going on?!
...King Riku-sama said he is our hope!
I feel very impotent
because although I'm a former king,
The gods must've descended
to save the day for this country!
I thought you won the competition
and got the Flare-Flare Fruit...
Hey you! Is the battle over?!
all I can do is to stake this country's fate
on some strange pirate!
You can do it, Dressrosa!
The Lucy in the final wasn't me.
What happened to Doflamingo?!
...Culverin!
What?!
However, I can't help crying out like this!
I had to go somewhere so Sabo took my place.
Whether he wins or loses,
it'll only take several dozen minutes!
Athlete!
Oh, so that's what happened.
That's against the rules!
It's not over yet.
I still see the light of hope.
But it all worked out. Yeah!
Until then, try to survive,
whatever it takes!
Taking over your late brother's
ability is a nice story to hear.
Dressrosa will never perish!
I don't want any one of you to get crushed
by the constriction of the country!
Armored but still rubbery?!
Well, okay! In any case, your recovery is
the only hope that Dressrosa has now!
A crappy attack like that...
--Cub-san...
--Yes, Princess Mansherry?
Keep running!
...won't work!
Even if you run out of breath!
Or even if your leg breaks!
This is how I fight!
Can't believe this!
Just for several dozen minutes,
try to survive!
You can get away, Mingo! I'll kick your ass!
I don't know how to use weapons
and I can't bring down bad people but...
Why is it?! It keeps stretching this time!
...tears keep filling my eyes endlessly.
There is hope!
Yes, it's very you!
What an honorable way to fight!
Keep going after him! Python!
Please don't give up!
Damn!
Gyats-san, Lucy still needs
more time to recover!
But I think many people will die before that!
Let's do our best even without any help!
How far can it stretch?!
I know! But I can't send an
incapacitated fighter into the ring!
Okay!
Doflamingo is still alive!
Alright! Let's run, granddaughter!
Get away from the town!
What?!
I won't hand him over until he regains his Haki,
no matter what!
The fight between the pirates is still going on!
Uh-huh! Grandma!
We'll get caught up! Get away!
Enough! Fall on the ground already!
Me, too!
Who is it?!
Even the downtown is in danger!
--As King Riku-sama said...!
--We'll run to the downtown without giving up!
Gum-Gum...
The Birdcage is closing in!
There's no place to run!
What's with that bastard?!
He still has the energy to do this?
T... T-T-Trafalgar Law!
Carry the sick people!
Take those beds!
The W-W-Warlord...
Don't hesitate!
We gotta stall him as much as we can!
...Culverin!
You guys, I think you're running too far.
Oh, that's because... Um...
Annoying weaklings!
I don't need energy to wipe you out!
Will he regain his Haki?
Min... go...
O-Oh, the thing is...
Mommy!
Come on, Straw Hat!
He told me that he needs ten minutes
and now we've got three minutes
and twenty seconds to go!
I'll make you regret it all!
Try to survive until the battle ends!
There is no time to lose.
Straw Hat!
Straw Hat Luffy will take
down Doflamingo for us!
I'll take him under my care from here.
Okay!
Uh-huh!
There are already less than three minutes to go
until the Birdcage closes completely.
Mingo!
The tough fighters, revived by Mansherry's ability,
and the Navy get together with
Doflamingo strikes back against Luffy
who used up all his energy and can't even move!
The tremendous power of Fourth Gear
drives Doflamingo into a corner!
Zoro and Franky stand
up to stop the Birdcage!
With his awakened Devil Fruit
abilities, Doflamingo turns objects
in the town into strings and
launches a full-scale attack!
But the constriction
keeps increasing in speed
the Straw Hats who have
been tackling the Birdcage,
When it seems like Dressrosa will finally be liberated,
Doflamingo starts fighting back!
It takes ten minutes for his Haki to be regained,
In a desperate situation where there
and an all-out battle to
save Dressrosa begins!
as if it's trying to crush their hope
and an intense battle begins
is nowhere to run,
and as the time limit for Fourth Gear closes in,
and when the moment of destruction
to protect the incapacitated Luffy during that time from
Doflamingo, who has become the embodiment of anger itself!
is about to come before Luffy's recovery,
a miraculous light shines on Dressrosa!
Viola and Rebecca also take action, risking
their lives, to support Luffy's recovery!
The whole new aspect to the Devil Fruits --
their formidable true power is revealed!
Luffy initiates a deciding deadly charge!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Flame Dragon King! Protect Luffy's Life!"
"A Massive Counterattack! Doflamingo's Awakening!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Tears of Miracles! Mansherry's Fight!"
"Luffy! An All-Out Leo Bazooka!"
"As Long as We Breathe!
Stop the Deadly Birdcage!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!