Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
The executives of the Donquixote
Family have been taken down
one after another, after hard
battles, by the Straw Hats,
and finally, there is only Doflamingo left!
The time has come for a one-on-one duel
between Luffy and Doflamingo that shakes up Dressrosa!
I have to leave the rest to Straw Hat-ya!
If he's gonna win,
I wanna see it through with my own eyes here!
Gum-Gum...
...Grizzly Magnum!
You're wide open!
You see unlucky people everywhere
in the world.
If you try to save them all, there's no end.
You're just a passing pirate.
Are you trying to be a hero?
How dare you get in my way!
No! You got in my way!
You made my friends cry and
made my crewmates mad!
But you still haven't fallen
so I will take everything upon myself!
I won't let anybody die!
You and the Birdcage are standing in my way!
Fourth...
...Gear!
"Fourth Gear!
The Phenomenal Bounce-Man!"
Run! Run!
Run to the center of the island!
B-Buildings that haven't been cut apart...
...are getting pushed by the Cage
and closing in on us!
The country's getting smaller!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF
THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 2
The Birdcage is shrinking?!
That's what is causing this confusion.
This is the real threat of the Birdcage.
The full account of how he robbed the country
has been revealed to the nation.
Things won't go as he pleases anymore.
That's why he wants to destroy everything.
The Young Master does such things
without hesitation, honey!
I can't believe this!
This is a really big deal!
Oh! I called him "honey" again!
Here we go with our hot and sweet married life!
I can't just wait for death to come
sucking on my thumb!
Rouse the fallen allies right away, too!
Alright!
Oh, he's taking control of the tough ones.
He's developing as a leader more and more.
Oh! And I'm the one
who takes control of things at home!
If the battle lasts long,
this plateau will be cut into pieces, too.
What?! I thought this is the center of the country!
Isn't it the safest place?!
Look at the sky!
The center of the Birdcage is
moving little by little.
The center of the contraction
is probably the plateau -
the current location of the Royal
Palace, where Doflamingo is!
THE CURRENT LOCATION
THE ROYAL PALACE
That means eventually, this place will...
Hurry up, Hack! Please hurry up!
Stop shaking me!
Now we're down here and it's quite chaotic.
That way, huh!
Zoro-dono!
Where are you going?!
It's obvious, isn't it?
What?!
I'm going to stop it, of course!
It!
"It"?!
No!!
What a surprise.
I didn't know there were
Dwarves in Dressrosa.
On top of that,
their princess even has power to heal.
I hope your arm gets reconnected properly.
They said when blood starts
flowing, it'll be cured.
I know. I'm a doctor.
When I saw the underground trade port,
I understood...
This battle... Even if we can take down Doflamingo,
it won't be over.
It'll cause tremendous ripples
across the world.
And you guys will be
the object of everyone's attention.
Yeah...
I'm well aware that's what'll happen.
Fourth Gear?
That's right.
In order to kick your ass,
I'll get stronger!
It's neither Second...
...nor Third!
Muscle Balloon!
Fourth...
...Gear...
...Bounce-Man!
Whoa-whoa, is this some kind of a joke?
You got quite big...
Look at that inflated body of yours!
I thought you had a secret
stratagem or something...
Can't you be more serious?!
This is my secret stratagem and I am serious!
You can't even stand straight
since you're bouncy because you're rubber.
How can you kick my ass like that?
For two years,
I fought against monstrously-big,
savage beasts!
To wrestle them to the ground,
I needed this giant body and bounciness!
How would bounciness help you...?
Shut up!
You won't...
...be able to do anything!
Gum-Gum...
...Kong...
...Gun!
Wh-What happened?
It fell from the sky.
What was it?
--Can't believe it!
--What?
What's wrong, Viola?!
Did you see something?!
Straw Hat turned into a
never-before-seen form and...
...made Doflamingo...
D-Doflamingo!
Why is he here?!
Back off! Back off!
Why are you here?! Doflamingo!
I'd like to know that myself.
Run! He's gonna kill us!
There's nowhere to run!
There's the Birdcage out there!
I'm in the downtown, huh?
I really got flung pretty far...
He's flying using the elastic force!
Overheat!
Gum-Gum...
...Rhino Schneider!
Somebody else has come!
He's big! He kicked Doflamingo away!
Who is that ball-like guy?!
What's going on?! Is Luffy winning?!
Amazing...
L-L-L-L-L-L-L-Luffy-senpai!
So strong!
What is that?! A new technique?!
Must be a new technique!
Hey, you!
Do you know how awesome this is?!
Witnessing such a rare moment!
We couldn't be luckier!
Oh, I can't stop shaking!
Can't see!
Lucy...
Damn!
By hardening his skin with the Color of Arms,
he's multiplying the tension of his skin!
That ball-looking bastard!
He's nothing but rubber!
Straw Hat! Stop messing with me!
Pentachromatic Strings!
Bullet String!
I told you!
You're no match for me in Fourth Gear!
Here I come, Mingo!
Prepare yourself!
Don't push your luck!
Gum-Gum...
...Culverin!
Athlete!
Armored but still rubbery?!
A crappy attack like that...
...won't work!
Can't believe this!
You can get away, Mingo! I'll kick your ass!
Why is it?! It keeps stretching this time!
Keep going after him! Python!
Damn!
How far can it stretch?!
Enough! Fall on the ground already!
Gum-Gum...
...Culverin!
The tremendous power of Fourth Gear
drives Doflamingo into a corner!
When it seems like Dressrosa will finally be liberated,
Doflamingo starts fighting back!
The whole new aspect to the Devil Fruits --
their formidable true power is revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Massive Counterattack! Doflamingo's Awakening!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!