Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
The executives of the Donquixote
Family have been taken down
one after another, after hard
battles, by the Straw Hats,
and finally, there is only Doflamingo left!
The time has come for a one-on-one duel
between Luffy and Doflamingo
that shakes up Dressrosa!
Fourth Gear?
Muscle Balloon!
Fourth...
...Gear...
...Bounce-Man!
Rhino Schneider!
Gum-Gum...
...Culverin!
Athlete!
A crappy attack like that...
...won't work!
Gum-Gum...
...Culverin!
"A Massive Counterattack!
Doflamingo's Awakening!"
--A rubber ball is...
--...Overwhelming...
...Doflamingo!
You're right!
Who is it?!
It doesn't matter!
--Go for it!
--You can do it!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
Did you see that?!
Yeah...
Can't believe how he changed.
Is it really Straw Hat?
He's overpowering the formidable Doflamingo!
He's amazingly strong!
But he's using Haki too much.
Using Haki too much?
Straw Hat, where did he go?!
Oh, there he is.
They went to play somewhere else.
I took the trouble to come see them!
How annoying!
The captain of the first ship of the Blackbeard Pirates -
Jesus Burgess.
I was wondering where he went
after the battle in the Colosseum but...
...I found him here.
Chase them or wait...
Either way, I won't let them get away!
I'll get what I wanna get for sure!
He's going after Luffy-kun
and the others as I thought.
What does he want?
THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
Viola.
All that remains is the decisive battle
between him and Luffy-kun?
Yes, that's right, Father-sama.
Doflamingo is the only one remaining now,
from their forces from the
rank of executive or above.
If Luffy-kun takes down Doflamingo,
the Birdcage that is slicing up the town will vanish
and the Doflamingo Family falls apart.
Is that what you mean?
Yes.
Where did they go?! Did they get lost?
Zoro-dono!
You're going the wrong way!
What?!
You're bad at directions so if we just follow you,
we'll never get there!
Now, why don't you ride on this?
What is that weird vehicle?
It's a Spring Sparrow.
Kanjuro called it over
from the King's Plateau!
Don't hesitate.
Now, hurry up and get on!
Me getting on this Stupid Sparrow?
It's a Spring Sparrow.
I don't feel like it but I have no choice.
Let's go!
Spring Sparrow! You can do it!
It finally got here.
Get out of the factory, Tontattas!
THE SMILE FACTORY
Okay!
We gotta escape!
Super hurry up and come on out!
We completed the rescue of
our stranded friends in the factory!
Good!
The factory is tilting!
Fraland!
Why is the SMILE Factory
alone not getting cut?!
Only the factory?
--Oh yeah, it's the Sea Prism Stone!
--Sea Prism Stone?
Yeah, the outer walls of the factory are
made of Sea Prism Stone.
That's why it doesn't get cut by the strings
that the Devil Fruit eater created.
But, look!
It's starting to get pushed!
Hm? That's...
--Franky!
--Oh, Robot-dono!
Zoroland! Topknot-land!
Hey, Zoro! Kin'emon!
The center of the country is
in the direction you flew from!
If you wanna run, go straight back!
What?! We aren't running!
We'll go stop the strings!
Stop them?
Oh, I didn't even think about that!
What?! That's cool!
Until Luffy settles this, we gotta buy time!
Stop the strings... But how?
Oh yeah!
THE DOWNTOWN
LUFFY VS. DOFLAMINGO
He's controlling the expansion
and contraction of rubber
as he wants, with the Color of Arms...
Harmonizing the Armament and rubber, huh?
If I take too much time, Fourth Gear will...
Seems like you're using your abilities pretty well
but it must be quite a burden...
There must be some risks.
Gum-Gum...
Straw Hat, how many more
seconds can you stand?
...Double...
My strings, however, won't run out!
...Culverin!
Off-White!
H-How did the strings
come out of the ground?!
What did you do to this town?!
Listen, fledgling!
Devil Fruit abilities have...
...yet another stage to
them called "Awakening"!
The buildings turned into strings!
The ability will awaken rarely and begin to
affect things other than its user's body!
Various things are turning into strings!
It doesn't look like the power of a Paramythia!
Everything that surrounds
you turns into strings!
You can't even come near me!
And when your strength gives out,
my body will...
How persistent!
Hope this tires you out!
When your Haki gives out,
I'll give you the finishing blow!
We'll get cut! Run!
Get to the downtown!
Hurry up or we'll get cut!
Oh, grandma!
Grandma, stand up! The strings will cut you!
I can't...
I can't run anymore...
Leave me here and go ahead!
No! No! I can't do such a thing!
I won't survive this anyway.
Please get up!
Even if I get up, I definitely
can't run to the downtown!
Somebody! Help us!
There are still patients in the hospital!
We can't carry them all by ourselves! Please!
P-Pl...
Please...
My son's missing! Didn't anybody see him?!
He's wearing a Kuma shirt!
He's five years old!
Somebody! Did you see my son?!
My son...
Outta my way!
Everybody's gonna die anyway...
Let's give up...
No matter how far we run, we're in the cage.
We'll only get killed by Doflamingo.
It's easier...
...to just give up.
King Riku-sama...
Everybody, listen.
I'm...
...the former king of
Dressrosa - Riku Doldo III.
Wh-What is it?
K-King Riku-sama...
This country is now, by the game
that the current king Doflamingo started,
in a giant Birdcage with no visible escape.
On top of that, that vicious Birdcage
keeps shrinking, slicing up the town.
King Riku-sama...
You fell on this reality too suddenly.
I'm sure your emotions can't even catch up
and you're just trying to save your own,
or somebody else's, life now!
But this is not a dream!
Nor a tragedy that has begun today!
For a decade,
we have always lived in the
Birdcage called Dressrosa
under the reign of the pirates!
For a decade, we have always been puppets
that live under their manipulation.
That is reality!
But that will end soon!
What?
The Donquixote Family
that we thought nobody could match has...
...almost been wiped out by the
hands of the tough warriors
who only happened to be here in this country!
All of the Family's executives are
already taken down!
Really?!
--Those executives have...
--...Brought down, he means?!
The only enemy there is left to beat...
...is the current king of
Dressrosa - Doflamingo!
And the one who is fighting him is
the pirate - Straw Hat Luffy!
I believe he is the man
who will destroy the Birdcage for us!
I feel very impotent
because although I'm a former king,
all I can do is to stake this country's fate
on some strange pirate!
However, I can't help crying out like this!
Whether he wins or loses,
it'll only take several dozen minutes!
Until then, try to survive,
whatever it takes!
I don't want any one of you to get crushed
by the constriction of the country!
Keep running!
Even if you run out of breath!
Or even if your leg breaks!
Just for several dozen minutes,
try to survive!
There is hope!
Please don't give up!
Let's do our best even without any help!
Okay!
Alright! Let's run, granddaughter!
What?!
Uh-huh! Grandma!
Me, too!
--As King Riku-sama said...!
--We'll run to the downtown without giving up!
Carry the sick people!
Take those beds!
Mommy!
Try to survive until the battle ends!
Straw Hat Luffy will take
down Doflamingo for us!
Uh-huh!
Mingo!
With his awakened Devil Fruit
abilities, Doflamingo turns objects
in the town into strings and
launches a full-scale attack!
In a desperate situation where there
is nowhere to run,
and as the time limit for Fourth Gear closes in,
Luffy initiates a deciding deadly charge!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy! An All-Out Leo Bazooka!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!