I don't hold a grudge against you guys but...
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along with the entire island.
However, by the actions of the Straw Hats,
the executives of the Donquixote Family
have been taken down one after another,
and Doflamingo alone remains.
But he has caused the Birdcage to constrict
in order to kill all the people in the country.
As the moment of Dressrosa's
destruction closes in,
the deadly battle between Luffy and Doflamingo
finally enters the final phase.
It's time for you to drop dead.
I'm running out of time!
Billow-White!
Mingo!
Get blown away!
Damn brat!
This is it!
Gum-Gum...
...Leo Bazooka!
The Birdcage isn't gone!
Gum-Gum...
H-Hey, what's the matter, Straw Hat Luffy?!
"Flame Dragon King!
Protect Luffy's Life!"
S-Straw Hat Luffy...
M-Maybe, he can't fight anymore...
If you go near, you'll get
caught up in it and die!
Don't get involved!
Get away from the pirate!
Straw Hat the pirate!
Stay with me! Hey! Can you still fight?!
Do you recognize me?
It's Gyats!
I'm the announcer at the Colosseum, Gyats!
The unknown gladiator Lucy...
It was you, wasn't it?
Uh-huh.
I thought so!
There aren't many small
guys who are that strong!
Doflamingo's on his way!
What are you gonna do about your duel?!
Is there something I can do?!
I need ten minutes...
Ten minutes?
After I use the Bounce-Man,
I can't use my Haki for ten minutes.
B-Boun...?
I need to keep my distance
but I don't know what he's
gonna do during that time.
If I regain my Haki,
I'm sure I can finish him off with one blow!
Are you gonna bounce up and down
like a rubber ball again, Straw Hat?
I'm...
...back!
Ten minutes!
Then, his horrible reign will be over?!
Hey, if we give you ten minutes,
will you get us out of the Birdcage?!
Hey, Straw Hat!
I promise!
All right!
Ten minutes!
We'll leave it up to you guys!
Count on us!
Ten minutes will pass by like a flash!
You gotta come back quickly
and bring down that Dofla-guy, Lucy!
We'll do our best!
They're all the competitors
from the fighting event!
The ones who wouldn't help you earlier!
Sorry, Lucy!
We were blinded by greed over
the prizes on your heads!
We didn't even dream of cornering Doflamingo!
I'm sorry!
As a token of our apology,
we'll believe in you and risk our lives!
Sorry if we happen to beat him first!
Thank you for everything,
Mr. Heavenly Demon!
Why don't you hang out with us for a while?
--Here he comes! Here he comes!
--Kick his ass!
Okay, now is the chance!
The remaining half of you, follow me!
Yeah!
Listen, guys! Ten minutes!
Ten minutes to go!
Let's get through it at any cost!
Yeah!
Watch out!
Go to hell, Straw Hat!
B-Burgess?!
Sabo!
Luffy!
His Haki is fading.
Go to hell, Straw Hat!
--Th-That guy is...
--Oh, the Three-Star criminal!
Wh-What?!
He's the Chief of Staff of
the Revolutionary Army!
Sabo!
I'm Sabo from the Revolutionary Army!
Straw Hat Luffy is my brother!
What? What?!
What do you want from him, Burgess?
Straw Hat is your brother?!
I've heard someone say that before.
I bet "Fire Fist" Ace said it, too.
We're three brothers.
What?!
Ace? I see.
I get it now.
After the duel on Banaro Island,
you Blackbeard Pirates captured Ace
and it triggered the ugly Paramount War!
Die in darkness!
Fire Emperor!
The sun or the darkness --
there'll be only one winner!
I'm gonna make Whitebeard the king!
Ace made the choice himself.
...I'm watching Luffy's back hereafter!
Remember that!
I have no interest in
your relationship to him!
Don't get in my way!
I have no business with you
or the Revolutionary Army!
I only have business with...
You have no business with me?
Not even personally?
It's all mine, isn't it?
Damn! He ate the Flare-Flare Fruit!
Ace!
I take over your ability!
Fire Fist!
I see it now. That was you!
What?! Flare-Flare?!
Hey, Luffy. You've been hurt badly.
Doflamingo is on his way and I think
my hands will be full with Burgess.
I'll be okay.
Cats and the others will buy me some time.
It's Gyats!
I'll take down Mingo no matter what!
You've become so dependable!
Leave that one in my hands!
Sabo!
You ate Ace's Fruit, didn't you?
I wouldn't let anybody else have it.
It's a memento of him!
Yeah!
That's great!
I'll be taking that ability!
Okay, look after him, Pets!
It's Gyats! I got it!
Galleon...
...Lariat!
Burning Dragon Claw Fist!
It's hot!
Flame Dragon King!
I-I can't believe it! He blew away
the subordinate of one of the Four Emperors!
So strong! That's what I'd expect from
the No.2 of the Revolutionary Army!
As soon as he saw the Flare-Flare Fruit power,
he changed his focus to me.
So his objective is,
as they say,
hunting down Devil Fruit eaters.
Hey, Lucy! What's going on?!
I thought you won the competition
and got the Flare-Flare Fruit...
The Lucy in the final wasn't me.
What?!
I had to go somewhere so Sabo took my place.
Oh, so that's what happened.
That's against the rules!
But it all worked out. Yeah!
Taking over your late brother's
ability is a nice story to hear.
Well, okay! In any case, your recovery is
the only hope that Dressrosa has now!
What's with that bastard?!
He still has the energy to do this?
Don't hesitate!
We gotta stall him as much as we can!
Annoying weaklings!
I don't need energy to wipe you out!
Come on, Straw Hat!
I'll make you regret it all!
Straw Hat!
Zoro and Franky stand
up to stop the Birdcage!
But the constriction
keeps increasing in speed
as if it's trying to crush their hope
and when the moment of destruction
is about to come before Luffy's recovery,
a miraculous light shines on Dressrosa!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Tears of Miracles! Mansherry's Fight!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!