Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
There's the signal...
Today is very promising!
You're going?! Your wounds from
that last battle still haven't--!
It's nothing! The conditions
are the same for both of us!
Making excuses during a
merciless fight to the death
would spoil my name!
Hey! Wait, old guy!
Don't go!
You can't go, Dorry-san!
You need to keep still!
You'll die if you push yourself too hard!
I, Warrior Dorry, am here...
At the very least...
...I will fight to uphold the name of Elbaf!
"Broggy's Bitter Tears of Victory!
The Conclusion of Elbaf"
Don't tell me he's--!
Awesome! He picked up
that gigantic rock!
Luffy-san!
What're you doing, old guy?!
Move this rock! Hey!
It can't be stopped...
It was over a hundred years ago...
...when we started the battle.
But running from a battle you've started...
...is the same as running
from the title of "warrior."
If I am no longer a warrior...
...I will no longer be me.
I'm sorry I suspected you.
This is the judgment given by...
...Elbaf, the god of war.
I didn't have his
divine protection. That's all.
Gods and divine protection and
all that have nothing to do with this!
If a god told you to die, would you?!
This duel has been interfered with!
A duel that's been interfered
with isn't a duel anymore!
--Isn't that right?!
--Be quiet!
You've lived only a mere 10 or 20 years--
you wouldn't understand
the grand words of Elbaf!
Who gives a crap about that?!
Hey! Move this thing! Hey! Old guy!
Hey! Old guy! Hey! Dammit!
I can't move this!
Okay, Master Broggy! Go get 'im!
You bet, Usopp!
I'm gonna wipe the floor
with him for sure this time!
Go get 'im, Warrior of Elbaf!
You can do it!
You're strong! Strong! Strong!
You're big! Big!
How can he keep doing
this pointless fighting?
Don't call it pointless fighting, you idiot!
Broggy's a brave warrior of the sea,
like the kind I'm aiming to be!
What gives you the right--
Anyways, let's return to the ship.
Waiting a year for the Log to
store up is out of the question!
We need to wait on the ship for
everyone and come up with a plan.
Hold it! Not so fast!
I am absolutely useless in
a fight against dinosaurs!
As such, we cannot possibly traverse
the jungle to reach our ship!
What was all that "brave warrior
of the sea" stuff just now, then?
I meant that in the mental sense!
I want to be a man who's
proud of the way he lives!
No choice.
Luffy's group is at the
other giant's house.
Guess we'll head there...
Listen, Nami.
Even if I wind up
losing everything someday
and greet death all alone
on a deserted island,
I'll proudly say this
about my life as I die:
"I am Usopp, brave warrior of the sea!"
Yeah, yeah.
Then will you hurry up
and be a dependable warrior?
Oh...
Alright!
Dorry! How was your drink?!
Hit the spot, didn't it?!
Yeah... It tasted "godly"...
You're so full of exaggerations! Let's go!
What's wrong, Dorry?!
You're a bit sluggish!
Don't be a fool!
I'm the same as always!
Move, you stupid thing! Come on!
Just when it seemed like
I met an awesome warrior!
Luffy-san...
Why would he go this far
for a giant he just met?
He hardly seems like a criminal
with a bounty on his head...
Who is it?! Who's putting
a damper on the giants' fight?!
Come to think of it...
...Karoo is gone!
Oh? Isn't this ugly bird the one
the princess always has with her?
Yeah.
Don't run away!
We were lucky enough
to meet out here, after all.
There's something we'd like you to do.
That's right.
Damn. I'm lost.
I do recognize this tree, but...
It was, "Go left from the
tree wrapped in vines," right?
Oh! It's you, Nami!
Perfect timing!
I just lost my way, you see,
so I wasn't sure what to do...
What're you doing here, anyway?
Hey. What's the deal?
Dinosaur!
Dinosaur! Dinosaur! Dinosaur!
Hey, you! You're too fast!
Urgh, that guy...
Luffy!
What a relief!
What are you doing here?
N-Nami?
Nami! Nami! Nami! Nami!
This is not good...
Luffy!
Luffy! Luffy! Luffy! Luffy!
Oww...
Terrible news! A dinosaur ate Nami!
Seriously?!
We were running through
the jungle to get away from it,
and then suddenly she was gone!
Oh! What do I do now?!
I let my friend get killed!
H-Hold on! Calm down, you two!
If she suddenly disappeared,
does that mean you don't know for sure?
Are you crazy?! I was too
terrified to check and make sure!
If it wasn't a dinosaur,
it was a wild beast!
What else could it have been?!
I don't know.
But if people from Baroque Works
have followed us onto this island,
then it'd make sense that only
Nami-san was targeted and not you.
Eh?! Baroque Works is on the island?!
But... why wouldn't they go after me?
Because you're most likely not on
Baroque Works's assassination list.
Oh, I see!
Plus, that alcohol might've
been meant for us, too!
Alcohol?! What about alcohol?!
Broggy brought your alcohol to Dorry.
And when Dorry drank it,
it exploded inside his stomach.
What?! Alcohol exploded
inside his stomach?!
You're saying he went to the
battlefield all busted up like that?!
I tried to stop him,
but I wound up like this instead!
You can't be serious!
Those two've fought evenly for
100 years with all their might!
It's probably the most pride-filled
battle in the entire world!
--Yeah...
--They can't settle the fight like this now!
What's wrong?!
He's still fighting.
Yes. Dorry the Blue Ogre
is quite stubborn indeed.
Perhaps I should assist one of them.
One century...
It was a long battle!
This is the judgment given
by Elbaf, the god of war.
I didn't have his
divine protection. That's all.
--Luffy!
--Luffy-san?!
Who was it?!
Show yourself!
Mr. 3. I think I heard something.
How funny! An underdog loser,
yelping out here in the jungle!
Seventy-three thousand...
...four hundred sixty-seven fights...
73,466 draws...
...and one win!
Joyful tears of victory, huh?
Simpleminded people have it so easy.
Though, perhaps I'll
congratulate you for now.
Joyful tears?!
What would you know?!
Just who are you?!
Mr. 3. Please excuse the codename.
I'm a mere formative artist.
And this is my realist painter assistant,
Miss Golden Week.
What's more, I've already captured you.
W-What is this?!
Alright, Luffy!
I dunno who we're dealing with,
but I'll go take care of them myself!
I'm coming, too!
Yes! Please come with me!
That'd be reassuring!
There's no need for that!
You guys!
You can have him back.
We don't need him.
Karoo!
Why, you...!
Hey, who are they?
The guys from that last town!
What are you doing here?!
Karoo has nothing to do with this!
That's right. This bird has
absolutely nothing to do with this.
The only one we considered
dangerous was that "straw hat man."
We were planning to lure you both
out by having this bird squawk,
but he was just too obstinate.
Alright! Call for your owner!
Squawk especially loud
and we'll let you go!
Fine! Want us to make you squawk?!
Call for the princess!
Call for help this instant!
Open your mouth, you damn bird!
But then we saw Straw Hat already
took himself out of the picture.
So we have no use
for that thing anymore.
Karoo...
What a stupid bird!
Why, you...!
Are you the ones who
put a bomb in the alcohol?!
Yes, that was us. Who're you?
Is he on the list?
No. He must be their friend.
But let's make him disappear, too!
So you interfered with the giants' duel!
It was them?! I'll kick their asses!
You're the ones who
are going to disappear!
Oh? You're going to try
struggling, Miss Wednesday?
Do you stand a chance
against us Officer Agents?
Peacock Slasher!
Take this! Special Attack: Exploding Star!
Yes!
What a nice explosive blast!
Nose Fancy Cannon!
What a pity!
Usopp!
10,000 Kilogram Press!
Calm down, now!
There's no need to be so upset.
We're not going to kill you just yet.
We only came to abduct you.
On Mr. 3's orders...
Mr. 3?! The Wax-Wax Fruit man?!
He's on this island?!
That's right.
He's a "candle man" who controls
the wax he secretes from his body.
A candle man?!
You've got me!
Ah, gentle song
Make it there for us
After a wave washed away
that little sand castle
You looked up at the passing
clouds with a sad smile
If you find the world is full of enemies,
I've got your back
Don't lose faith
You've got me!
Ah, my love
I'll hold you in my arms forever
You've got me!
Usopp! Can you let them
get away with this?!
No...
Can you not stand this, either?!
Alright! Let's all three of us
go beat them senseless!
Let's do it! Usopp! Bird!
Yeah!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Devilish Candle!
Tears of Regret and Tears of Anger"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!