Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
However, by the actions of the Straw Hats,
the executives of the Donquixote Family
have been taken down one after another,
and Doflamingo alone remains.
But he has caused the Birdcage to constrict
in order to kill all the people in the country.
As the moment of Dressrosa's
destruction closes in,
the deadly battle between Luffy and Doflamingo
finally enters the final phase.
The unknown gladiator Lucy...
It was you, wasn't it?
Uh-huh.
Doflamingo's on his way!
What are you gonna do about your duel?!
Is there something I can do?!
I need ten minutes...
Ten minutes?
If I regain my Haki, I'm sure I
can finish him off with one blow!
Hey, if we give you ten minutes,
will you get us out of the Birdcage?!
Hey, Straw Hat!
I promise!
Come on, Straw Hat!
I'll make you regret it all!
"Tears of Miracles!
Mansherry's Fight!"
That jerk, Doflamingo will go
to any lengths at this point!
What else can he do?!
He created the Birdcage
and he's turning the town into strings!
This is it for Dressrosa!
Just run! The only way to survive is
to get away from the downtown area!
The whole area is a battlefield now!
If you get caught up in it, you're gonna die!
I'm not gonna get cut up
by that Birdcage crap!
Hurry to the downtown area!
--Hey, don't push!
--Watch out! I'm gonna get crushed!
I have children!
Stop! Stop!
Stop! Don't push!
Hey, why are you running
in the opposite direction?!
We gotta get to the downtown area!
--The downtown area is a battlefield now!
--What?!
A battlefield?
Doflamingo is running wild
looking for Straw Hat!
If you go to the area,
you'll get slashed by the strings!
--What?! Then...
--Where should we run to?!
King Riku-sama,
what are we supposed to do?
How are they doing?!
Not good! They've been knocked down
and can't even stand on their feet!
Even the proud warrior of Elbaph
used up all of his energy?
What's that?
Hajrudin!
Armament!
What are you doing, Zoro-dono?!
Trying to stop it with your swords?!
It isn't something you can stop
by just pushing!
How do you know that?!
If you have time to chat
away that it's impossible,
help me, you half-baked idiots!
It's just the ability of one person!
There's no rational reason for me
to believe I can't stop it!
--Let's do it, Kin'emon!
--Yes, let's go!
IN FRONT OF THE SMILE FACTORY
Are you ready?!
We are!
The factory is made of Sea Prism Stone!
It won't be damaged!
Show me everything that you got!
All right! Get ready!
Push the factory!
Push! Push!
Push!
Not yet, not yet! Push, push!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF
THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 2
--Zoro and the others are pushing the Birdcage?
--Yes.
Is it possible to stop it?
I don't know. I didn't even think of that.
Okay! That's so like him!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
THE SOUTH SIDE
This is what the Young Master-sama wants!
What?! Get out of our way!
How rude.
Stay away! This is the New King's Plateau!
Only the Donquixote Family members
are allowed in here!
What Family?!
Even the executives are gone!
This is the safest place! Let us climb up!
Shut up! You fools are condemned criminals!
By the Young Master-sama's judgment,
this country will be completely renewed!
Barrier-Barrier...
...Pistol!
Go away, you left-overs!
The fighters from the Colosseum!
Bartolomeo!
Hajrudin!
Don Chin Jao!
Punch!
Army Commander Kyros is here, too!
Why am I able to move?
So am I. I didn't think I
could move with that injury.
Don't let your guard down yet!
This is a life-support procedure for Dressrosa,
that Princess Mansherry chose to take!
Life-support?
What do you mean, dwarf?
In any case, everybody,
claw your way to this plateau!
The center of the Birdcage
is moving this way!
--Yeah!
--You saved us, Kyros-sama!
Hey, men! Don't depend on others!
Those who have the physical strength,
come with us!
What?! He wants me to come with him?!
--Hey, where are you going?!
--Doflamingo!
If he's not gonna come out,
I'm gonna pull him out!
Straw Hat!
I said "Don't push"!
What is that noise?
Wh-What the...
Hey, that's...
--Isn't it getting faster than before?!
--Yeah, it sure is!
The speed of the contraction
of the Birdcage increased!
It's over... This is really it this time!
Please help us, King Riku-sama!
We can't make it through!
Stop it! Doflamingo!
Armament!
Take this!
Ow! Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch...!
You're such a canny guy!
I can say the same about you!
Is it speeding up?!
We don't have much time, Luffy.
The way the strings move has changed.
It's getting faster!
What?! That's not fair! What should we do?!
We can't make it!
It's getting faster?!
I-It sure is!
The pressure is increasing!
Push! Put more power into it!
Come on!
Push!
What?!
What's the matter?!
We're getting pushed back!
It's speeding up! Don't let
it get the better of you!
Push harder than you've ever pushed before!
Okay!
Push!
Yes, it's our chance to show off!
Yeah!
Come on out, Straw Hat!
Help!
Hurry up! The shrinking speed is increasing!
Three minutes to go until
the Birdcage reaches
the downtown area and completes the massacre.
You've got to be kidding!
We can't make it!
Four minutes to go until
Luffy's Haki is regained.
There is a one-minute difference between
the time the Birdcage will close completely
and the time Luffy will wake up.
How dare that bastard do that?!
Before Lucy comes back,
this country will be shredded to pieces!
We gotta do something about it ourselves!
Take down Doflamingo and
make the Birdcage go away!
Why can't you guys get it?
It's my message to you:
"Give me Straw Hat."
Barrier!
It's holding out!
Only you could've done it! Rooster-kun!
Oh! Robin-senpai!
I don't deserve such words of praise!
Now, let's do it, guys!
My barrier will never break! Push!
Follow Zoro-senpai!
King!
Make a collective effort and push!
It's strange.
How could they exert that much power
with those injured bodies?
Just a few minutes ago, they were burned out
and couldn't even stand up.
What were those fluffs?
--They were Dandelixers.
--Dandelixers?
Yes!
They are dandelions made from
the components of Princess Mansherry's tears.
Wait for me! Wait for me!
--Hurry up! Or you'll get cut!
--Run faster!
I can't! Damn!
I can't believe I twisted my ankle now!
You can do it!
What?! I can run!
So fast! What's going on?!
The fluffs of Dandelixers can give people
over a wide area miraculous ultra-recoveries.
Princess Mansherry is worrying about
what's happening to Dressrosa
and is shedding tears now.
I believe that will save so many lives!
So that's why those immobile fighters are...
But the drawback of this ability is
that it's only a temporary ultra-recovery!
Just for a few minutes!
I'm afraid they'll revert to their
former state when the time comes!
So this is just a life-support procedure to
survive for now!
What?!
The pain is gone suddenly!
I can run! I can get away!
It's a miracle, doctor!
The gods must've descended
to save the day for this country!
You can do it, Dressrosa!
It's not over yet.
I still see the light of hope.
Dressrosa will never perish!
--Cub-san...
--Yes, Princess Mansherry?
This is how I fight!
I don't know how to use weapons
and I can't bring down bad people but...
...tears keep filling my eyes endlessly.
Yes, it's very you!
What an honorable way to fight!
Gyats-san, Lucy still needs
more time to recover!
But I think many people will die before that!
I know! But I can't send an
incapacitated fighter into the ring!
I won't hand him over until he regains his Haki,
no matter what!
Who is it?!
T... T-T-Trafalgar Law!
The W-W-Warlord...
You guys, I think you're running too far.
Oh, that's because... Um...
Will he regain his Haki?
O-Oh, the thing is...
He told me that he needs ten minutes
and now we've got three minutes
and twenty seconds to go!
There is no time to lose.
I'll take him under my care from here.
Okay!
There are already less than three minutes to go
until the Birdcage closes completely.
The tough fighters, revived by Mansherry's ability,
and the Navy get together with
the Straw Hats who have
been tackling the Birdcage,
and an all-out battle to
save Dressrosa begins!
Viola and Rebecca also take action, risking
their lives, to support Luffy's recovery!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"As Long as We Breathe!
Stop the Deadly Birdcage!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!