Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa governed by
the Warlord - Donquixote Doflamingo.
and have come to Dressrosa.
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
They took down the executives of
the Donquixote Family one after another.
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
they were trapped along
with the entire island.
While the Straw Hats were
However, by the actions of the Straw Hats,
taking down the executives of
the Donquixote Family one after another,
However, by the actions of the Straw Hats,
While the Straw Hats were
And...
taking down the executives of
the Donquixote Family one after another,
the executives of the Donquixote Family
have been taken down one after another,
Doflamingo has caused the
Birdcage to constrict
and Doflamingo alone remains.
Doflamingo has caused the
Birdcage to constrict
in order to kill all the
people in the country.
But he launched a counterattack,
making the Birdcage constrict,
in order to kill all the
people in the country.
As the moment of Dressrosa's
destruction closes in,
I don't criticize my associates
for their mistakes.
Luffy and Doflamingo delivered
in order to kill all the
people in the country.
As the moment of Dressrosa's
destruction closes in,
ultimate attacks against each other
putting forth their last strengths
But I don't condone betrayals.
As the moment of Dressrosa's
destruction closes in,
the deadly battle between Luffy and Doflamingo
finally enters the final phase.
and finally, the dust settles.
Luffy has used up all his energy
and become incapacitated.
King Kong...
Look at the sky, Dressrosa!
It stopped once!
We can hold it back again and again!
Rebecca!
Viola-san... My body is moving on its own...!
If you don't obey, I'll just kill you!
What are you doing, Zoro-dono?!
Trying to stop it with your swords?!
Sixteen Holy Bullets!
It isn't something you can stop
by just pushing!
Stop the cage!
It's just the ability of one person!
Doflamingo has caused the
Birdcage to constrict
There's no rational reason for
me to believe I can't stop it!
With all your efforts, we successfully
delayed the constriction of the Birdcage!
God Thread!
The Birdcage is...
Push the factory!
in order to kill all the
people in the country.
Push!
The winner is...!
As the moment of Dressrosa's
destruction closes in,
...Gun!
It won't be long before
Lucy, the star who was born
Push! Push!
...Lucy!
Push!
Luffy has used up all his energy
and become incapacitated.
in the Colosseum, comes back!
Now, let's do it, guys!
Hold on until that moment!!
My barrier will never break! Push!
I need ten minutes...
Follow Zoro-senpai!
Ten minutes?
Luffy-senpai! Here we go!
If I regain my Haki, I'm sure I
can finish him off with one blow!
T... T-T-Trafalgar Law!
Hey, if we give you ten minutes,
will you get us out of the Birdcage?!
Will he regain his Haki?
No! I don't wanna do this!
O-Oh, the thing is...
He told me that he needs ten minutes
I'll...
Now, kill her...
and now we've got three minutes
and twenty seconds to go!
...destroy everything!
I promise!
No!!
There is no time to lose.
I'll take him under my care from here.
Lucy!
"Dead or Alive!
A Fateful Countdown!"
Viola-san!
Close your eyes, Rebecca!
"The Unheard-of!
Admiral Fujitora's Surprising Decision!"
You can do it, Dressrosa!
I won't hold a grudge against you so...
Don't fall behind! Hurry up!
just forget it!
"As Long as We Breathe!
Stop the Deadly Birdcage!"
Here! Take my hand!
No!!
Come up here on the plateau!
It's not your fault at all!
The Birdcage is closing in on us!
I'm sorry, Rebecca!
It stopped once!
We can hold it back again and again!
This will leave a deep scar in your mind!
Yes!
Doflamingo got taken down!
--Oh? Huh?
--Hey, can you move?
Guys, give it everything you've got!
Now we're free!
Mom! Dad!
Y-Yeah.
No!!
Now is the time to reward Luffy-dono
for his hard fighting!
Why?! The injured are
recovering one after another!
We made it!
We're samurai of the Land of Wano!
Who cares why?
"To Be Free!
Dressrosa's Delight!"
Let's just run!
Show them what we Navy are made of!
Gyats-san!
Hey, wait a minute!
Yeah, he did it!
Listen to what I have to say!
I can't believe Lucy really
took down Doflamingo!
What is it, Hundredth-Degree Hack?!
No! I'm behind him!
Clank.
--The Five-star, God Usopp!
--What kind of crime did he commit?!
Stop the cage!
--Shut up! We don't have time!
--Oh, okay!
"Attack on a Celestial!
Luffy's King Kong Gun of Anger!"
Listen, guys! Those of you who are strong,
go to the east and west side of the town!
Every time these hands and feet back down,
My friends are pushing the Birdcage there!
Please help them!
L...
L... L...
Go help people who are pushing the Birdcage?
our defeat in this battle
and sure demise inch closer!
Lucy appeared!
It's impossible to stop that thing!
Yeah, we have no chance!
Aren't you gonna finish me off?
Prepare yourselves and keep hanging on!
No chance?
Don't need to.
Luffy-senpai!
Stop making excuses! Trust my friends!
Shut up! You're distracting us!
Seems like it's all over.
Luffy!
You don't have to tell us!
This very moment is the time to fight!
The god is angry!
We got it!
Luffy!
Luffyland!
You brothers are too lenient!
That's the spirit, guys!
Keep pushing with all your might!
Are you okay?
Oh, what a pain...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Okay, honey!
Straw Hat...
I wonder if they're really heading off
to push the Birdcage.
Don't cling to me!
Yeah...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Viola, use your Clairvoyance and...
I have no intention of
making this place my grave!
Oh? Oh? Where did she go?
She was here until a minute ago.
I have a goal I want to achieve!
Anyway, we don't have time.
Let's go ask other islanders, too.
After losing to our captain
at the Banaro Island,
If that's so,
Ace had something to say
before he got handed over to the Navy.
We've got to hold out until Luffy comes back!
until our bodies are broken,
Wanna hear it?
Finally! Finally...
let's make the greatest
effort of our lifetimes!
Hmmm... How interesting.
Hey, hurry up!
Straw Hat and Doflamingo's duel is over!
Lucy came back!
I ended up looking like this old man.
--The Navy'll get here soon!
--I know!
Straw Hat!
All of your "shields" have been broken!
I like this statue! It's so manly!
--Did you call the chief?
--I'm trying now!
Lucy! Lucy! Lucy! Lucy!...
Show yourself already!
I like it, too.
--He's not picking up.
--He only picks up when he feels like it.
That battle was amazing!
I was surprised at your strength!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Too bad for you. This "shield" is...
Please... Please be safe...
Now, please, Lucy!
I'm...
Knock him out with a single blow!
...going to win today's competition
no matter what it takes...
As many lives as possible...
...still alive.
Get your dirty hands off me!
and kill Doflamingo
with the Flare-Flare Fruit power!
What a showy comeback!
Are you okay?
But you just managed to get your Haki back.
Stay with us!
You'll laugh when you hear it!
Not yet... Not yet!
You're barely able to stand, are you?
We'll keep you busy until Lucy comes back!
He realized he was gonna
get executed and he said...
I don't mind! Just stab him like this!
Stop it! Don't involve Rebecca!
I know...
What am I... going to do?!
...you're in the same boat!
If you promise me that
you won't kill my father,
You scum never learn!
Prepare to die a second death!
Viola-san!
Don't tell my brother.
Rebecca!
I will obey you!
Straw Hat! I'm here! Come on out!
Now, kill her...
Lucy!
Wait, Viola!
Why are they so important to you?!
They're pirates!
What an idiot!
Yes, they're unlawful men - who will break
this country's deceptive peace!
He didn't know how much he was worth!
Shambles!
Viola-san! Why am I doing this?!
Hey, we've come all the way! Let us through!
If "Fire Fist" Ace got caught by the Navy,
the news would spread all over the world!
Father-sama, I decided to trust them,
the Straw Hat Pirates!
The Birdcage is right there!
Rebecca!
They say there's danger ahead
and we can barely advance, too!
The Navy would make 120% use of
his pathetic life...
I don't want the help of the
Navy, that was supposed to be
People all over the country gathered
here at once and we can't even move!
supporting justice, or the
Government after all these years!
At least, the words of Straw
Hat and the others are humane
Oh, please...
Humph. There you are.
Everybody! Don't stay here!
and they take actions
out of the goodness of their hearts!
That's enough.
No!
Advance towards the plateau -
location of the Royal Palace!
Well, watch closely.
No! I don't wanna cut Viola-san!
Stop talking!
You're Rebecca!
As your hope gets crushed.
We gotta run there?!
Is it really safe?!
How he felt when he passed away...
Yes!
The center of the Birdcage is moving
towards there!
FIRE FIST ACE DIES
Please hurry up! It's dangerous here!
No!
Doflamingo!
I've thought about it repeatedly
every single night since that day!
Okay! I take your word for it!
Everwhite!
No!!
Me, too!
--Me, too!
--Let's go!
So you don't have to tell me
because I know it all!
Th-The entire area turned into strings!
Alright, everyone!
Did you hear that?! The plateau!
Run towards the plateau!
Room!
Shambles!
It won't be much longer!
Everybody! Evacuate to the plateau
- location of the Royal Palace!
Oh! He got saved!
Lucy!
The downtown area is a battlefield
and it's dangerous!
Damn! Dammit!
Lucy!
We don't have time! Just go!
Wh-Who's talking?!
Let it sink in, fool!
--Run!
--Hurry up!
--Is he okay?
--Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
It's no use.
Everybody! Don't abandon hope!
The Devil Fruit you got!
There are people who haven't given up yet!
Straw Hat...
If I can't steal it here,
Thousand Arrows...
--Who is it?! Now isn't the time!
--Where is he speaking from?!
it'll damage my reputation as
a hunter of Devil-Fruit eaters.
There are people who are trying
desperately to stop the Birdcage!
...Flapping...
Our star will return!
I won't give it up! The Flare-Flare Fruit!
You go guide citizens
to the plateau - location of the Royal Palace!
Oh! Hey! There he is!
You're regretting it, aren't you?!
...Thread!
Because you didn't go rescue your brother
We'll take this one!
Armament!
Come on! Hurry up!
even though you had the title and the power!
You're the announcer from
the Colosseum, Gyats!
Thank you, Rebecca!
You weren't there, were you?!
They're all trying so hard
to stop the Birdcage!
--How long have you been there?!
--What are you up to?!
Were you taking a nap or something?!
Everyone, do you remember?!
You couldn't get there when
he needed you the most
Now isn't the time to fool around!
and you call yourselves
brothers?! How pathetic!
The country is on the verge of destruction!
What's the matter?
I thought you made your comeback.
You're not King Riku-sama!
But if the Birdcage is something
that'll never stop, no matter their strength,
That's why I don't want any more regrets!
Yes, I know you remember!
all of their efforts will be wasted!
What?!
Did you really regain your Haki, Lucy?!
About that funny and bold star
who burst onto the scene...
Fire Fist!
Damn!
...in the tournament at the
Corrida Colosseum today!
I-Is he gonna be okay?!
Look! Nobody's up there now!
Star?!
--What?
--You're right.
Don't tell me he's talking about...
How did it go?!
...me!
What just happened?!
Tell us, Gyats!
Hey, I told you I'd stay here with you
but do you mind if I go now?
Gyats!
Tell us, Gyats!
--Gyats!
--Hey, Gyats!
--You've been watching, right, Gyats?!
--Just tell us, Gyats!
Trafal...
Gagh! Law! He's gone!
I don't care but Ace is
saying he won't forgive you!
I know I'm no match for him but...
--Gyats!
--What happened?!
What?! Where did he go?!
Gyats!
But everybody's fighting desperately!
I've got to do something, too!
I remember!
Lucy!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Gyats-san!
He tamed the killer bull
that everybody feared
Clank.
Father-sama!
When push comes to shove, I'll...
You can't speak loudly anymore!
Oh! Hello? Sabo-kun?
Where are you?!
Don't push yourself!
I-It's no good...
and mowed down the towering Giant!
I saw Burgess went after Luffy-kun earlier
Don't be silly!
I guess he has too many injuries...
...kill Doflamingo!
He even knocked down the
living legend, Don Chin Jao!
so I called you right away
but you didn't pick up at all!
The people of Dressrosa
are waiting for my words!
--Oh yeah? I didn't care at all.
--You didn't what?!
What?
Viola-san!
He's the little gladiator
who made the Colosseum...
That was pretty loud!
What kind of announcer am I
if I can't announce
Rebecca! Why are you here?!
--Don't worry. I took care of it already.
--What?
--It's too dusty - I can't see clearly.
I mean, the whole of Dressrosa
bubble over with excitement!
Viola-san, I...
What happened to the fight?
the winner or the loser?
That aside, Koala, have you found the list?
Did Lucy win?
Don't be silly!
I've never before seen anyone fight so freely
Boy! Yes, I have!
Look, you two!
If I let you die, I can't face Brother Kyros
or my late sister!
The Birdcage is still there!
What?!
--Then, just call the ship and...
--I did!
and make a competition
as thrilling as he did!
Look at the sky, Dressrosa!
Hurry up, Lucy!
Well, let's meet up with Hack underground.
Okay, let's hang on a little more!
Until Lucy gets rid of the Birdcage!
Walk away!
I'm with Hack and the others
underground waiting for you!
So, what did you come to see me for, Viola?
Clank.
I was watching that!
He's talking about that guy, isn't he?!
Yeah!
--I saw it at the Colosseum!
--I watched it on a screen in the town!
The Donquixote Family is about
to be obliterated.
His name is...
Why did he hang up?! That selfish jerk!
...Lucy!
If I do nothing to take responsibility
as a former executive, it's too selfish.
Stop taking it out on me, Koala-san!
So what?! He's just a gladiator!
No!
Lucy...
Damn!
Help me, Lucy...
There he is!
Yes! He's Lucy!
Either I will die, or you will!
But that was just his temporary alias!
The Donquixote Family!
His real name is...
Doffy!
What's fading?
You're very passionate, Violet!
Wh-What the...
The Birdcage...
The pirate - Straw Hat...
...or Doflamingo's domination?!
My body's moving on its own.
...Luffy!
The eight executives! And...
What?!
What?! That's who Lucy was under his mask?!
That's the guy King Riku-sama
mentioned earlier!
...the three top-executives, confirmed!
Since we've been fooled by
and been under the control of a pirate,
You're a puppet now,
that I can manipulate as I please!
maybe it's hard for us
to trust another pirate!
Watch out!
The toy's broken! It's got "Humanitis"!
Most of the executives
are Devil Fruit eaters!
But...
Listen to me! It's not that!
Viola-san!
...he's different from the Donquixote Family
who appeared in disguise
Come here!
Don't you remember, Esta?!
Bind them securely with Sea Prism Stone!
It's me!
Get away from me!
You're freaking me out!
as heroes on that night a decade ago!
I can't believe you're still alive!
Should I impale you?
THE SMILE FACTORY
Yes, sir!
No! Let go of me, you bastards!
Straw Hat Luffy is someone
that the real king,
I'm a human!
Or let you and your friends kill each other?
You gotta push more! Push harder!
King Riku-sama, called "our hope"!
It's over even for a great pirate group
when they end up like that.
Okay!
I'm totally free now!
The Birdcage will definitely stop!
Keep pushing!
He fought Doflamingo earlier
to within an inch of defeat!
Good work.
My... dar... ling...
We got it!
Wh-What?!
That little boy did that?!
Is that why you came back running?
He sure was very strong
at the Colosseum but...
IN FRONT OF THE BIRDCAGE
- NEAR THE SMILE FACTORY
You escaped death again, Luffy.
I want to believe!
Humph! Next time I'll win!
What?!
I want to trust him!
How is it?!
It's slowing down... I think!
What happened to that Kong Gun
that you're so proud of?
Me, too!
Oh well, Rayleigh!
You stay with me.
We ended up like this because
This one was much, much
bigger than the other one
Now that you mention it,
it seems like it's slowing down!
we couldn't trust King
Riku-sama a decade ago!
Okay.
and it didn't work!
--Whoa! Wh-What're you doing?!
Get away from me!
--You said "Stay with me"!
That means we'll be together forever!
No! It hasn't changed at all!
This time, I'll trust!
You got a problem!
Stop grumbling and just push!
But if Kong Gun isn't working,
you have to come up with something else.
--That guy...
--Lucy will...
...Save...
Did we call the Navy HQ?
...Our country!
What?! The factory is...
Something else?
Well, actually...
Why are you here?!
Oh no... I don't know who
it is because I can't see.
...Issho-san said "Don't file a report yet."
Kong Gun isn't powerful enough
to take this guy down, either!
He's now knocked out
after getting hurt in the battle but...
--Honey!
--Yeah!
What?
That jerk! He's the last
person we wanted to see now!
...it's not over yet!
Dance with joy, Dressrosa!
Lucy...
It's so funny.
The Birdcage is...
...promised me!
Damn!
All those fools,
they should've stayed in my cage
and submitted to my manipulation.
Vice Admiral Maynard!
The Video Transponder Snail is ready!
That he'll knock out Doflamingo...
Okay, I'll do the talking.
It's hard to walk away from foolish people.
Cage?
The strings...
Take another Transponder Snail
and follow Issho-san as we were ordered!
Manipulation?
...are gone!
Although my ability is limited,
let me help you, if even a bit!
Humans are mere scum.
...with a single blow!
Yes, sir!
They only deserved to live
when I, who possess divine power,
I see the sky! The sky!
Procession - halt!
was manipulating them.
The sky!
Deserved to live as scum.
--Give support to those unknown people pushing the cage!
--Yes, sir!
The Navy!
But you guys cut those puppet strings!
And this is what it comes to.
Oh, we got so much help!
It's encouraging!
If you guys hadn't done
such unnecessary things,
--Those of you who can't use Haki, head for the factory!
--Yes, sir!
I wouldn't have had to
carry out a massacre like this!
I-Is the scenery that was
outside of the cage...
Are we okay now?
Yes, we are.
Huh? The Navy?!
a town that's been sliced up?
Push the Birdcage!
Enough...
Or...
...a free land where no one
will manipulate us anymore?!
Enough, already!
Run!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Nothing'll change if we just keep running!
Knock him out with a single blow, huh?
The Birdcage is gone!
I'm gonna push it, too!
Oh! Hey!
JUSTICE
That means...
--Push!
--Okay!
What a big talker!
Damn! I'll push, too!
That's what I'd expect from Luffy-senpai!
--I have the greatest muscular strength here!
--Yeah, that's the spirit!
Gyats-san!
The "Dressrosa Defensive War"!
No, I do!
That's so Luffy!
--We're gonna push it, too!
--We wanna protect our own country at least!
2,000 members of the Donquixote
Family, the pirate group...
You've got to do it. Otherwise, we
can't hold out much longer, Luffy!
Let's push it together!
...versus...
All right! Guys!
Give it everything you've got!
...the fateful warriors
who happened to arrive!
APPLENINE ISLAND - AN NEIGHBORING COUNTRY
This is Applenine Island,
a country near Dressrosa.
The King's Plateau is getting cut!
Yeah!
SEVIO
It'll be too late! Hurry up!
--What the...?
--What's wrong?
There they are!
I heard there'll be a
broadcast from Dressrosa!
Warriors! Let us push, too!
--That's great!
--Lucy!
Will it be a speech by King Doflamingo?
--Just do it already!
--Yeah!
I'm scared...
This is Dressrosa...
The duel between their leaders!
--We'll do it, too!
--We can't just let it cut us without doing anything!
Hurry up, Luffy!
ANOTHER NEIGHBORING COUNTRY
The Warlord - Donquixote Doflamingo...
--I'm sorry, everybody! Help us!
--Yeah! Let's work together!
Robiland, if it goes on like this...
Are you listening,
We're broadcasting to the three
neighboring island countries
...versus...
--It's gonna be okay!
--What?
--Here we go, guys!
--Yeah!
Doflamingo?!
...the gladiator - Lucy!
within the range of a Video
Transponder Snail's psychic waves.
Let's do it!
You...
AND ANOTHER NEIGHBORING COUNTRY
Trust Luffy!
...puppeteered our king, deceived the world,
Yeah!
Push!!
Dah vinner...
Okay!
and stayed here in Dressrosa as a false king!
What?
I'm a vice admiral of the Navy HQ, Maynard!
This is the place where you'll receive...
Dah vinner...
...your punishment!
--What is he saying?!
--It's "the winner"!
The Navy?!
This is Dressrosa.
Dah vinner...
Do it again?
We're broadcasting to the three
neighboring island countries
--Come on, Gyats!
--You can do it!
Gyats!
within the range of a Video
Transponder Snail's psychic waves.
Push!!
Turn into the Bounce-Man thing,
Dah vinner is...
Why?!
I see everything you're up to, Doflamingo!
I'll let you kill all the citizens,
I want you to take a look at these images!
You can do it, Gyats-san!
let alone your friends!
Come get me if you want!
What are those piles of rubble?
Stay away from Viola-sama and Rebecca-sama!
What you're seeing is
the current state of Dressrosa!
Dah vinner...
It's not working! It's not stopping!
--You can do it!
--Hang in there, Gyats!
It's too early to give up!
With all your efforts, we successfully
delayed the constriction of the Birdcage!
--What?!
--What does he mean?!
I trust Zoro-senpai!
I know you're surprised.
We'll stop the Birdcage at any cost!
Who are you?
But we must let many people know
what happened here!
It won't be long before
Lucy, the star who was born
Don't try to scream or call for help.
Fourth Gear!
in the Colosseum, comes back!
I want you to keep calm as I tell you...
Push!!
My name is Donquixote Doflamingo.
...all the details of what the Warlord,
Hold on until that moment!!
Donquixote Doflamingo did
here in this country today!
Cut the strings?!
I am the rightful king of this country!
And now, I'm...
Issho-san... Are you ready?
...back!
Did we do something?!
You've only got a little
bit of strength left.
There's no way to justify myself!
How long can you stay in that form?
Luffy-senpai! Here we go!
I'm begging you, King Riku-sama!
This country is finished!
Many citizens who knew the truth
got turned into toys and couldn't speak out!
Doflamingo set us up!
Lucy!
And you only committed the act of violence
Dah vinner...
because you were manipulated by Doflamingo!
He chose to fight me in the air?
He's got a lot of nerve!
Enough already!
Speak clearly!
Please!
Hajrudin!
D-Damn... Not now...
No... Please... Stop saying that.
What the...
Listen to me, Rebecca!
The injured who recovered earlier
are collapsing again!
Don't cry yet!
Will I get to see how you're gonna
knock me out with a single blow?!
I won't let the soldier die!
You have to be safe, too!
--Time's up.
--What?!
Even if the misunderstanding
about me gets cleared up,
I promise I'll kick Doflamingo's ass for you!
The effect of the Dandelixers
on those who got it first, is wearing off.
I can't go back to being a king again.
No! You're the only king
we have for this country!
It's not gonna work twice!
Lucy...
That's right!
--We're sick and tired of violence!
--King Riku-sama!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Because my ability isn't good enough,
Dah... Dah... Dah...
What if all the citizens of this country are
on the same page with you?!
Dah...
it's like I gave them a glimpse
of happiness for a moment,
We wanna go back to the time when,
despite our poverty, we enjoyed a peaceful life...
and then, disappointed them! It's terrible!
The winner is...
No, Princess Mansherry!
It's annoying to have you over my head!
King Riku-sama! Please come back!
We don't know how many people
He said it!
would've been killed by the Birdcage
if it weren't for the Dandelixers!
I'll drag you down and
manipulate you as a puppet again!
It stopped...
Gyats! Say the winner's name!
But...
The Birdcage...
--Look!
--What?
Mingo!
The winner is...!
You worked a miracle!
Wow! I can't believe it!
The Birdcage stopped!
Wait.
Oh, please! What weaklings!
...Lucy!
The Riku Family's philosophy falls apart
when faced with turmoil.
People in the back take the collapsed ones' places!
Get more people!
You always try to strangle
everything within your hands...
It's been proved to us now.
It's gonna move again!
Lucy!
Okay!
But it did stop for a moment.
We'll hold out at any cost!
Until Lucy gets rid of the Birdcage!
Thank you, Lucy!
So it's stoppable!
Doro-senpai is as awesome as ever!
We don't care if we go to ruin!
This is great!
Yeah!
The Birdcage... stopped?!
We're happy to go to ruin
if we can hope for peace together with you!
Yes!
They've stalled it enough!
Super!
That way, we can buy time
until Straw Hat comes back.
Luffyland will take over from there
and get rid of the Birdcage!
As a king who doesn't fight,
please renounce war!
...and try to manipulate everybody!
Luffyland!
Luffy!
Yes! Even if it makes our country fall,
Damn fools...
Finally! Lucy will come back in ten seconds!
Keep pushing!
Let's stall the contraction of the Birdcage!
that'd be fine with us!
We don't mind being poor!
Make Dressrosa a peaceful country again!
Stay focused!
Hold on! More!
Ow, ow, ow...
He should be listening somewhere!
Call out the name of the star!
I'm so impressed by Straw Hat!
--King Riku-sama!
--King Riku-sama, I'm begging you!
Yeah, we saw him act like a true man!
And I'm impressed by him, too!
What? King Riku-sama?!
Army Commander Tank?!
Lucy! Lucy!...
Good job!
It makes me feel like I'm suffocating!
What?! You're impressed by me?!
If it weren't for you people,
we would've lost thousands already!
Lucy! Lucy! Lucy!...
Blame your own birthright!
Oh! Straw Hat! What an extraordinary guy!
You all, who were born as trash,
are only fit to be manipulated!
Screw this Birdcage!
You humans and I are different!
People are meant to be free! Keep pushing!
Robiland!
Luffyland is really, really amazing!
Shut up!
Okay!
I'll kick your ass and get out of here!
More!
Okay!
Yes, I already knew that quite well.
Push the Birdcage back!
Do your worst, brat!
I'm a king who fights
so that makes my ears burn!
Luffy!
Spiderweb!
Elizabello!
He finally did it!
King Riku-sama!
Please go back to the palace now!
No matter how many seconds you buy,
it's useless.
But if Kong Gun isn't working,
you have to come up with something else.
Kings from our neighboring
countries keep calling us
and the Transponder Snail won't stop ringing!
Nothing has changed.
What?!
Gum-Gum...
Boy! Well done!
You think so?
I was quick to inform them!
It's unbelievable!
That's our Luffy-dono!
That King Riku will come back.
They're all very happy to hear that!
Something else?
That's right. Fourth Gear
taxes your body too much.
The king of Prodence!
Three seconds to go!
Princess!
You'd better think of something else.
I'm so glad!
Hierro Lagrima!
It was merely a decade.
How could you get so much older?
Fraland!
How about this, then?
Tearwhales!
You showed a fierce face to the world
like you'd kill them in order to avoid war.
All of you did great, too!
Two!
You're hurting us!
What?!
Where did that man go?
That'll be even harder...
They're all waiting for you...
What I wanted to show you is...
...this country is filled
with both the forgotten
Enough already!
Come back.
and those who forgot them!
Gyats-san!
King of miracles, Riku Doldo!
Lucy! Lucy!
King Kong...
Don't stop! Keep calling out!
All of us toys were once humans!
He's right, King Riku-dono!
Commander!
One!
We're gonna fight with them!
How absurd...
That's enough! Viola-san!
Go to hell, Doflamingo!
They're Dwarves from the Tontatta Kingdom!
If you don't obey, I'll just kill you!
Our star Lucy will...
Is it really okay?! That girl was crying!
Sixteen Holy Bullets!
...drop you with a single blow!
I'm just a toy but I have something
that I want to protect!
Viola-san!
That's the Navy admiral!
But I can't even shed
tears from these tin eyes.
God Thread!
Zero!
Did you think...
...I'll hesitate just because
we spent a decade together as a Family, Violet?
That's why he's been fighting
on his own for a decade!
...Gun!
This whole trouble that Doflamingo caused...
I don't want you to take the responsibility.
It seems like everybody's happy at first
but this country has a very dark side.
Hesitate to kill you?
What?! Where's Lucy?!
That vicious pirate was approved
as a king of a country
This brave, little army is going to
challenge their filthy, monstrous enemy!
I don't criticize my associates
for their mistakes.
under the Seven Warlord system
I can't...
Straw Hat isn't coming back!
and allowed to reign over this island
by none other than...
...let them down!
But I don't condone betrayals.
Franky!
...the World Government!
You're free to go all out!
Thanks!
All citizens...
It quieted down finally.
All members of the royal family...
Fraland, thank you!
Lucy!
Now, next up is...
You can do it!
Viola, it's your turn to go quiet...
Forever!
On behalf of the Government,
Look at her, Violet!
No!!
What did you do to this country
and the king, pirate?!
I'll...
I most humbly apologize!
...destroy everything!
The king set fire to the town.
Didn't you see it?
Rebecca!
He'd never do such a thing!
Viola-san... My body is moving on its own...!
Viola-san!
Watch what I'm gonna do!
Close your eyes, Rebecca!
The King Riku Family is
no longer governing Dressrosa!
Poor girl. She's scared.
You don't have to see a thing!
This is a bad dream!
What?!
No matter what happens, forget everything!
He cut off his own leg!
No!
Don't...
I won't hold a grudge against you so...
Luffy-senpai!
Luffy!
Luffyland!
I'm Kyros! King Riku-sama!
just forget it!
Straw Hat!
I'm sorry. It doesn't ring a bell. But...
Luffy!
No!!
Luffy-dono!
...I'll never forget what you did for me!
We deeply regret what we did!
Please!
It's not your fault at all!
You're a strange toy.
Luffy!
Straw Hat!
I'm sorry, Rebecca!
This battle is to restore the honor
Now, come this way!
Lucy!
What are you...
This will leave a deep scar in your mind!
of King Riku who was dethroned
in disappointment ten years ago
Stop it! Don't involve Rebecca!
and to take back our freedom!
What am I... going to do?!
No!!
Viola-san!
Rebecca!
The Navy admiral is kneeling
down on the ground?!
No! I don't wanna do this!
No kidding!
Now, kill her...
Your name is Kyros, isn't it?
The Navy is under the direct
control of the Government!
And one of the Navy admirals, their
greatest military powers, is...
Come with me!
...kneeling down to apologize to
King Riku and the nation!
I wish...
Viola-san!
...everybody
Why am I doing this?!
What's going on in Dressrosa?!
would forget about me!
LAW AND STRAW HAT'S PIRATE ALLIANCE
That pirate alliance took down
"Heavenly Demon" Doflamingo?!
Rebecca!
Take a picture! Write it up now!
It feels like I'm repaying your kindness
with ingratitude, King Riku-sama.
I've never heard something like this before!
Kyros, hold her in your arms.
She's your daughter!
I-I don't wanna do this!
Go!
The mighty country Dressrosa's fake glory
and the truth behind it.
Viola-san!
There he is!
And the world's greatest underground broker,
Doflamingo's downfall!
Lucy!
With these tin arms, I can't even feel...
It's starting to slice up
the old King's Plateau!
...your warmth as you're dying!
Damn! It stopped once!
If it keeps constricting,
In addition, Navy HQ Admiral
Fujitora's prostration!
people will start dying one after another!
Soldier-san!!
--Don't give up! Keep pushing!
--Stall it even for a second!
Lucy! Lucy! Lucy! Lucy!...
Won't let you take away...
In some places, there are people
who call the Family of D...
...another member of my family from me!!
"Sworn enemy of the gods"!
How long till Lucy comes back?!
Let me see...
The Birdcage slowed down
but it will close completely in...
This major incident had been confined
within the cage...
A country that's going to collapse
isn't always unfortunate.
...60 seconds.
But finally,
the news has been released to the entire world!
And also, 60 seconds to go
until Lucy's comeback!
This day, the people of this
country rejoiced and cried
among the piles of rubble.
The Birdcage has started
shredding the King's Plateau!
Sabo burns with anger against Burgess
who makes fun of Ace's last words!
Luffy comes back and
enters a final battle against Doflamingo!
The end of one era comes to Dressrosa.
Navy Admiral Fujitora's
prostration shocks the world!
While the voices of the people rise in prayer
Each with their own feelings,
Rebecca, Kyros, and
The formidable Doflamingo
tries to manipulate people
and continue his reign over them,
As the waves of time surge on,
Meanwhile, in front of King Riku, entrusted
with Dressrosa's restoration,
for Luffy, their only hope,
as Dressrosa crumbles,
the citizens watch as the Birdcage fades!
the rookies that astonished the world
along with Luffy two years ago,
but when Luffy launches Fourth Gear's
Fujitora shows up with a serious decision,
Rebecca's sword, manipulated
by the hands of Doflamingo,
most powerful attack
with a soulful scream, Dressrosa's fate is finally settled!
Over the heads of those who have been
freed from the reign of terror,
Kid, Capone, Bonney, and the others,
and a major incident that
startles the world unfolds!
hangs precariously over Viola's body!
finally take action to bring
down the Four Emperors!
the name of the winner, "Lucy," rings out!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Dead or Alive! A Fateful Countdown!"
"To Be Free! Dressrosa's Delight!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Unheard-of! Admiral
Fujitora's Surprising Decision!"
"Attack on a Celestial! Luffy's
King Kong Gun of Anger!"
"Sending a Shock Wave! The Worst
Generation Goes Into Action!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!