Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
While the Straw Hats were
taking down the executives of
the Donquixote Family one after another,
Doflamingo has caused the
Birdcage to constrict
in order to kill all the
people in the country.
As the moment of Dressrosa's
destruction closes in,
the deadly battle between Luffy and Doflamingo
finally enters the final phase.
It stopped once!
We can hold it back again and again!
Stop the cage!
With all your efforts, we successfully
delayed the constriction of the Birdcage!
It won't be long before
Lucy, the star who was born
in the Colosseum, comes back!
Hold on until that moment!!
Luffy-senpai! Here we go!
No! I don't wanna do this!
Now, kill her...
No!!
Viola-san!
Close your eyes, Rebecca!
I won't hold a grudge against you so...
just forget it!
No!!
It's not your fault at all!
I'm sorry, Rebecca!
This will leave a deep scar in your mind!
No!!
"Attack on a Celestial!
Luffy's King Kong Gun of Anger!"
L...
L... L...
Lucy appeared!
Luffy-senpai!
Luffy!
Luffyland!
Straw Hat...
Finally! Finally...
Lucy came back!
Lucy! Lucy! Lucy! Lucy!...
Now, please, Lucy!
Knock him out with a single blow!
What a showy comeback!
But you just managed to get your Haki back.
You're barely able to stand, are you?
I know...
...you're in the same boat!
Lucy!
Shambles!
Rebecca!
Humph. There you are.
Well, watch closely.
As your hope gets crushed.
Everwhite!
Th-The entire area turned into strings!
Lucy!
Damn! Dammit!
It's no use.
Thousand Arrows...
...Flapping...
...Thread!
Armament!
What's the matter?
I thought you made your comeback.
Did you really regain your Haki, Lucy?!
I-Is he gonna be okay?!
Lucy!
I-It's no good...
I guess he has too many injuries...
That was pretty loud!
--It's too dusty - I can't see clearly.
What happened to the fight?
Did Lucy win?
The Birdcage is still there!
Hurry up, Lucy!
Okay, let's hang on a little more!
Until Lucy gets rid of the Birdcage!
Yeah!
Damn!
Wh-What the...
My body's moving on its own.
You're a puppet now,
that I can manipulate as I please!
Come here!
I can't believe you're still alive!
Should I impale you?
Or let you and your friends kill each other?
Is that why you came back running?
You escaped death again, Luffy.
Humph! Next time I'll win!
What happened to that Kong Gun
that you're so proud of?
Oh well, Rayleigh!
This one was much, much
bigger than the other one
and it didn't work!
You got a problem!
But if Kong Gun isn't working,
you have to come up with something else.
Something else?
Kong Gun isn't powerful enough
to take this guy down, either!
It's so funny.
All those fools,
they should've stayed in my cage
and submitted to my manipulation.
Cage?
Manipulation?
Humans are mere scum.
They only deserved to live
when I, who possess divine power,
was manipulating them.
Deserved to live as scum.
But you guys cut those puppet strings!
And this is what it comes to.
If you guys hadn't done
such unnecessary things,
I wouldn't have had to
carry out a massacre like this!
Enough...
Enough, already!
The King's Plateau is getting cut!
It'll be too late! Hurry up!
Hurry up, Luffy!
Robiland, if it goes on like this...
--It's gonna be okay!
--What?
Trust Luffy!
Okay!
Do it again?
Turn into the Bounce-Man thing,
I'll let you kill all the citizens,
let alone your friends!
Fourth Gear!
Cut the strings?!
You've only got a little
bit of strength left.
How long can you stay in that form?
Lucy!
He chose to fight me in the air?
He's got a lot of nerve!
Will I get to see how you're gonna
knock me out with a single blow?!
It's annoying to have you over my head!
I'll drag you down and
manipulate you as a puppet again!
Mingo!
You always try to strangle
everything within your hands...
...and try to manipulate everybody!
It makes me feel like I'm suffocating!
Blame your own birthright!
You all, who were born as trash,
are only fit to be manipulated!
You humans and I are different!
Shut up!
I'll kick your ass and get out of here!
Do your worst, brat!
Spiderweb!
But if Kong Gun isn't working,
you have to come up with something else.
Gum-Gum...
Something else?
That's right. Fourth Gear
taxes your body too much.
You'd better think of something else.
How about this, then?
What?!
That'll be even harder...
King Kong...
If you don't obey, I'll just kill you!
Sixteen Holy Bullets!
God Thread!
...Gun!
Lucy!
You can do it!
I'll...
...destroy everything!
Luffy-senpai!
Luffy!
Luffyland!
Straw Hat!
Luffy!
Luffy-dono!
Please!
Luffy!
Straw Hat!
Lucy!
In some places, there are people
who call the Family of D...
"Sworn enemy of the gods"!
The end of one era comes to Dressrosa.
Each with their own feelings,
Rebecca, Kyros, and
the citizens watch as the Birdcage fades!
Over the heads of those who have been
freed from the reign of terror,
the name of the winner, "Lucy," rings out!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To Be Free! Dressrosa's Delight!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!