Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
While the Straw Hats were
taking down the executives of
the Donquixote Family one after another,
Doflamingo has caused the
Birdcage to constrict
in order to kill all the
people in the country.
As the moment of Dressrosa's
destruction closes in,
Luffy and Doflamingo delivered
ultimate attacks against each other
putting forth their last strengths
and finally, the dust settles.
King Kong...
If you don't obey, I'll just kill you!
Sixteen Holy Bullets!
God Thread!
...Gun!
I'll...
...destroy everything!
"To Be Free!
Dressrosa's Delight!"
Hmmm... How interesting.
I ended up looking like this old man.
I like this statue! It's so manly!
I like it, too.
That battle was amazing!
I was surprised at your strength!
I'm...
...going to win today's competition
no matter what it takes...
and kill Doflamingo
with the Flare-Flare Fruit power!
If you promise me that
you won't kill my father,
I will obey you!
Wait, Viola!
Why are they so important to you?!
They're pirates!
Yes, they're unlawful men - who will break
this country's deceptive peace!
Father-sama, I decided to trust them,
the Straw Hat Pirates!
I don't want the help of the
Navy, that was supposed to be
supporting justice, or the
Government after all these years!
At least, the words of Straw
Hat and the others are humane
and they take actions
out of the goodness of their hearts!
Room!
Shambles!
Oh! He got saved!
Lucy!
--Is he okay?
--Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
Straw Hat...
Look! Nobody's up there now!
--What?
--You're right.
How did it go?!
What just happened?!
Tell us, Gyats!
Gyats!
--Gyats!
--Hey, Gyats!
--You've been watching, right, Gyats?!
--Just tell us, Gyats!
--Gyats!
--What happened?!
Gyats!
Gyats-san!
You can't speak loudly anymore!
Don't push yourself!
Don't be silly!
The people of Dressrosa
are waiting for my words!
What kind of announcer am I
if I can't announce
the winner or the loser?
Look, you two!
What?!
Look at the sky, Dressrosa!
What's fading?
The Birdcage...
...or Doflamingo's domination?!
The toy's broken! It's got "Humanitis"!
Listen to me! It's not that!
Don't you remember, Esta?!
It's me!
Get away from me!
You're freaking me out!
No! Let go of me, you bastards!
I'm a human!
I'm totally free now!
What?! The factory is...
--Honey!
--Yeah!
The Birdcage is...
The strings...
...are gone!
I see the sky! The sky!
The sky!
I-Is the scenery that was
outside of the cage...
a town that's been sliced up?
Or...
...a free land where no one
will manipulate us anymore?!
The Birdcage is gone!
That means...
Gyats-san!
The "Dressrosa Defensive War"!
2,000 members of the Donquixote
Family, the pirate group...
...versus...
...the fateful warriors
who happened to arrive!
The duel between their leaders!
The Warlord - Donquixote Doflamingo...
...versus...
...the gladiator - Lucy!
Dah vinner...
What?
--What is he saying?!
--It's "the winner"!
Dah vinner...
--Come on, Gyats!
--You can do it!
Dah vinner is...
You can do it, Gyats-san!
Dah vinner...
--You can do it!
--Hang in there, Gyats!
Who are you?
Don't try to scream or call for help.
My name is Donquixote Doflamingo.
I am the rightful king of this country!
And now, I'm...
...back!
Did we do something?!
There's no way to justify myself!
This country is finished!
Doflamingo set us up!
Dah vinner...
Enough already!
Speak clearly!
Listen to me, Rebecca!
Don't cry yet!
I won't let the soldier die!
You have to be safe, too!
I promise I'll kick Doflamingo's ass for you!
Lucy...
Dah... Dah... Dah...
Dah...
The winner is...
He said it!
Gyats! Say the winner's name!
The winner is...!
...Lucy!
Lucy!
Thank you, Lucy!
This is great!
Yes!
Super!
Luffyland!
Luffy!
Ow, ow, ow...
I'm so impressed by Straw Hat!
Yeah, we saw him act like a true man!
And I'm impressed by him, too!
What?! You're impressed by me?!
Oh! Straw Hat! What an extraordinary guy!
Robiland!
Luffyland is really, really amazing!
Yes, I already knew that quite well.
Luffy!
He finally did it!
Boy! Well done!
It's unbelievable!
That's our Luffy-dono!
Princess!
I'm so glad!
Fraland!
All of you did great, too!
You're hurting us!
What I wanted to show you is...
...this country is filled
with both the forgotten
and those who forgot them!
All of us toys were once humans!
Commander!
We're gonna fight with them!
They're Dwarves from the Tontatta Kingdom!
Is it really okay?! That girl was crying!
I'm just a toy but I have something
that I want to protect!
But I can't even shed
tears from these tin eyes.
That's why he's been fighting
on his own for a decade!
It seems like everybody's happy at first
but this country has a very dark side.
This brave, little army is going to
challenge their filthy, monstrous enemy!
I can't...
...let them down!
Franky!
You're free to go all out!
Thanks!
Fraland, thank you!
What did you do to this country
and the king, pirate?!
The king set fire to the town.
Didn't you see it?
He'd never do such a thing!
Watch what I'm gonna do!
The King Riku Family is
no longer governing Dressrosa!
He cut off his own leg!
I'm Kyros! King Riku-sama!
I'm sorry. It doesn't ring a bell. But...
...I'll never forget what you did for me!
You're a strange toy.
This battle is to restore the honor
of King Riku who was dethroned
in disappointment ten years ago
and to take back our freedom!
Your name is Kyros, isn't it?
Come with me!
I wish...
...everybody
would forget about me!
It feels like I'm repaying your kindness
with ingratitude, King Riku-sama.
Kyros, hold her in your arms.
She's your daughter!
With these tin arms, I can't even feel...
...your warmth as you're dying!
Soldier-san!!
Won't let you take away...
...another member of my family from me!!
A country that's going to collapse
isn't always unfortunate.
This day, the people of this
country rejoiced and cried
among the piles of rubble.
Sabo burns with anger against Burgess
who makes fun of Ace's last words!
Meanwhile, in front of King Riku, entrusted
with Dressrosa's restoration,
Fujitora shows up with a serious decision,
and a major incident that
startles the world unfolds!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Unheard-of! Admiral
Fujitora's Surprising Decision!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!