Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa governed by
the Warlord - Donquixote Doflamingo.
They took down the executives of
the Donquixote Family one after another.
And...
Look at the sky, Dressrosa!
The Birdcage is...
The winner is...!
...Lucy!
Lucy!
"The Unheard-of!
Admiral Fujitora's Surprising Decision!"
Yes!
Doflamingo got taken down!
Now we're free!
Mom! Dad!
We made it!
Gyats-san!
Yeah, he did it!
I can't believe Lucy really
took down Doflamingo!
Clank.
Aren't you gonna finish me off?
Don't need to.
Seems like it's all over.
You brothers are too lenient!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
After losing to our captain
at the Banaro Island,
Ace had something to say
before he got handed over to the Navy.
Wanna hear it?
Hey, hurry up!
Straw Hat and Doflamingo's duel is over!
--The Navy'll get here soon!
--I know!
--Did you call the chief?
--I'm trying now!
--He's not picking up.
--He only picks up when he feels like it.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
You'll laugh when you hear it!
He realized he was gonna
get executed and he said...
Don't tell my brother.
What an idiot!
He didn't know how much he was worth!
If "Fire Fist" Ace got caught by the Navy,
the news would spread all over the world!
The Navy would make 120% use of
his pathetic life...
That's enough.
Stop talking!
How he felt when he passed away...
FIRE FIST ACE DIES
I've thought about it repeatedly
every single night since that day!
So you don't have to tell me
because I know it all!
Let it sink in, fool!
The Devil Fruit you got!
If I can't steal it here,
it'll damage my reputation as
a hunter of Devil-Fruit eaters.
I won't give it up! The Flare-Flare Fruit!
You're regretting it, aren't you?!
Because you didn't go rescue your brother
even though you had the title and the power!
You weren't there, were you?!
Were you taking a nap or something?!
You couldn't get there when
he needed you the most
and you call yourselves
brothers?! How pathetic!
That's why I don't want any more regrets!
Fire Fist!
Damn!
I don't care but Ace is
saying he won't forgive you!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Oh! Hello? Sabo-kun?
Where are you?!
I saw Burgess went after Luffy-kun earlier
so I called you right away
but you didn't pick up at all!
--Oh yeah? I didn't care at all.
--You didn't what?!
--Don't worry. I took care of it already.
--What?
That aside, Koala, have you found the list?
Boy! Yes, I have!
--Then, just call the ship and...
--I did!
Well, let's meet up with Hack underground.
I'm with Hack and the others
underground waiting for you!
Clank.
Why did he hang up?! That selfish jerk!
Stop taking it out on me, Koala-san!
There he is!
The Donquixote Family!
The eight executives! And...
...the three top-executives, confirmed!
Watch out!
Most of the executives
are Devil Fruit eaters!
Bind them securely with Sea Prism Stone!
Yes, sir!
It's over even for a great pirate group
when they end up like that.
Good work.
My... dar... ling...
Wh-What?!
You stay with me.
Okay.
--Whoa! Wh-What're you doing?!
Get away from me!
--You said "Stay with me"!
That means we'll be together forever!
Did we call the Navy HQ?
Well, actually...
...Issho-san said "Don't file a report yet."
What?
Vice Admiral Maynard!
The Video Transponder Snail is ready!
Okay, I'll do the talking.
Take another Transponder Snail
and follow Issho-san as we were ordered!
Yes, sir!
Are we okay now?
Yes, we are.
JUSTICE
APPLENINE ISLAND - AN NEIGHBORING COUNTRY
This is Applenine Island,
a country near Dressrosa.
--What the...?
--What's wrong?
I heard there'll be a
broadcast from Dressrosa!
Will it be a speech by King Doflamingo?
I'm scared...
This is Dressrosa...
ANOTHER NEIGHBORING COUNTRY
We're broadcasting to the three
neighboring island countries
within the range of a Video
Transponder Snail's psychic waves.
AND ANOTHER NEIGHBORING COUNTRY
I'm a vice admiral of the Navy HQ, Maynard!
The Navy?!
This is Dressrosa.
We're broadcasting to the three
neighboring island countries
within the range of a Video
Transponder Snail's psychic waves.
Why?!
I want you to take a look at these images!
What are those piles of rubble?
What you're seeing is
the current state of Dressrosa!
--What?!
--What does he mean?!
I know you're surprised.
But we must let many people know
what happened here!
I want you to keep calm as I tell you...
...all the details of what the Warlord,
Donquixote Doflamingo did
here in this country today!
Issho-san... Are you ready?
I'm begging you, King Riku-sama!
Many citizens who knew the truth
got turned into toys and couldn't speak out!
And you only committed the act of violence
because you were manipulated by Doflamingo!
Please!
No... Please... Stop saying that.
Even if the misunderstanding
about me gets cleared up,
I can't go back to being a king again.
No! You're the only king
we have for this country!
That's right!
--We're sick and tired of violence!
--King Riku-sama!
What if all the citizens of this country are
on the same page with you?!
We wanna go back to the time when,
despite our poverty, we enjoyed a peaceful life...
King Riku-sama! Please come back!
Wait.
The Riku Family's philosophy falls apart
when faced with turmoil.
It's been proved to us now.
We don't care if we go to ruin!
We're happy to go to ruin
if we can hope for peace together with you!
As a king who doesn't fight,
please renounce war!
Yes! Even if it makes our country fall,
that'd be fine with us!
We don't mind being poor!
Make Dressrosa a peaceful country again!
--King Riku-sama!
--King Riku-sama, I'm begging you!
I'm a king who fights
so that makes my ears burn!
Elizabello!
King Riku-sama!
Please go back to the palace now!
Kings from our neighboring
countries keep calling us
and the Transponder Snail won't stop ringing!
What?!
I was quick to inform them!
That King Riku will come back.
They're all very happy to hear that!
The king of Prodence!
It was merely a decade.
How could you get so much older?
You showed a fierce face to the world
like you'd kill them in order to avoid war.
Where did that man go?
They're all waiting for you...
Come back.
King of miracles, Riku Doldo!
He's right, King Riku-dono!
That's the Navy admiral!
This whole trouble that Doflamingo caused...
I don't want you to take the responsibility.
That vicious pirate was approved
as a king of a country
under the Seven Warlord system
and allowed to reign over this island
by none other than...
...the World Government!
All citizens...
All members of the royal family...
On behalf of the Government,
I most humbly apologize!
What?!
We deeply regret what we did!
What are you...
The Navy admiral is kneeling
down on the ground?!
No kidding!
The Navy is under the direct
control of the Government!
And one of the Navy admirals, their
greatest military powers, is...
...kneeling down to apologize to
King Riku and the nation!
What's going on in Dressrosa?!
LAW AND STRAW HAT'S PIRATE ALLIANCE
That pirate alliance took down
"Heavenly Demon" Doflamingo?!
Take a picture! Write it up now!
I've never heard something like this before!
The mighty country Dressrosa's fake glory
and the truth behind it.
And the world's greatest underground broker,
Doflamingo's downfall!
In addition, Navy HQ Admiral
Fujitora's prostration!
This major incident had been confined
within the cage...
But finally,
the news has been released to the entire world!
Navy Admiral Fujitora's
prostration shocks the world!
As the waves of time surge on,
the rookies that astonished the world
along with Luffy two years ago,
Kid, Capone, Bonney, and the others,
finally take action to bring
down the Four Emperors!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sending a Shock Wave! The Worst
Generation Goes Into Action!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!