Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to make my dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for small success, making excuses
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air, off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit me, and even if I fall again
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal, we got to carry on the way
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without thinking of the consequences
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and brought down the Warlord -
Donquixote Doflamingo.
and have come to Dressrosa governed by
the Warlord - Donquixote Doflamingo.
and have come to Dressrosa
governed by the Warlord - Donquixote Doflamingo.
Now, peace has returned to Dressrosa.
They took down the executives of
the Donquixote Family one after another.
DOFLAMINGO FALLS
They took down the executives of
the Donquixote Family one after another.
And finally...
And finally, Luffy brought down Doflamingo!
King Kong...
Let's hurry up!
So you'd lost your memory
until two years ago?
...Gun!
"The Birth of the Legend!
The Adventures of the Revolutionary Warrior Sabo!"
Yeah...
If it was that serious,
how did you get your memory back?
"The Strongest Creature!
One of the Four Emperors - Kaido, King of the Beasts!"
Isn't this warmer?
Yes, it's much warmer!
Ace helped me.
A HILL IN CARTA - A TOWN IN THE EAST OF DRESSROSA
Soldier-san is a brave man
That's what I think now.
FIRE FIST ACE DIES
He brought down Doflamingo!
He will always be by your side
The timing couldn't be any
worse than that but...
KYROS' HOUSE
Come back.
King of miracles, Riku Doldo!
...that was why...
So you've been living on top of a hill.
...he awakened my memory.
"Fujitora Takes Action!
The Complete Siege of the Straw Hats!"
He's right, King Riku-dono!
It was convenient for me and Scarlet.
His brother was just here but
he's sleeping peacefully, totally unaware.
Sorry but my place is not as good as the Palace.
"The Brothers' Bond!
The Untold Story Behind Luffy and Sabo's Reunion!"
THE SOUTH SHORE OF DRESSROSA
It'll do.
Three days after the end of the battle...
He'll be disappointed when he wakes up.
There's one for each. Help yourself.
...between the Straw Hats
and the Donquixote Family...
Law-dono.
Who is this man that you brought here earlier?
This whole trouble that Doflamingo caused...
He's somebody Straw Hat-ya knows.
I picked him up.
What a nice brother...
I don't want you to take the responsibility.
Damn! I can barely fix myself...
I'm sorry but I'm gonna turn in first.
TWO YEARS AGO - SABO (20 YEARS OLD)
We finally arrived!
That vicious pirate was
If you're hungry,
you can eat anything in the house.
Do you want me to help you?
NAVY BRAND RICE CRACKERS
approved as a king of a country
under the Seven Warlord system
He really is a nice brother.
I think there's only dried meat though.
Did we wake you?
Is Straw Hat Luffy still
here in this country?
When Luffy wakes up, it'd be gone in a second.
Oh, were you listening to Sabo's story?
and allowed to reign over this island
by none other than...
Meat... Meat...
Yes, from about halfway through.
Yes. It's confirmed. He's badly wounded.
Hey, you fell asleep so quickly!
...the World Government!
We must've been speaking...
I see.
...quieter than our captain's snoring.
We've placed lookout units
in every port of Dressrosa.
You, too?!
All citizens...
Should we wake him up?
All members of the royal family...
We won't let them escape
under any circumstances.
No, let him sleep as much as he likes.
You fell asleep in an instant, too.
Sabo!
I'm sure everybody was tired.
Our camp is that way.
I brought him here for just that reason.
I guess they're not gonna wake up for a while.
We better get going, girls.
Sabo-kun!
Zoroland, maybe there is alcohol
in the cellar under the kitchen floor.
Yes, ma'am!
We should let them have a good rest now.
You're all fired up, Tsuru-chan!
On behalf of the Government,
There you are!
What?! You think so?!
Shut up! Let's go!
I most humbly apologize!
Something wrong?
No, I was just looking out at the sea.
No matter how much I thank Luffyland,
it could never be enough.
Boy, he has no booze here...
Yeah?
There's no way of knowing how much he
encouraged the people of Dressrosa.
Who is it?!
Issho! I heard what you did!
We're back in Baltigo
for the first time in a month.
This country will change.
"BUDDHA" SENGOKU
THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS INSPECTOR GENERAL
Here!
The prostration and the clash with Sakazuki!
Thanks to all of you, of course.
Sabo!
We deeply regret what we did!
Yo!
The pain from the wounds that
you're all suffering from...
I hope everybody's doing fine.
I'm glad that I'm not a
fleet admiral anymore!
You know him?
...is the result of injuries you sustained
on behalf of us, the citizens of Dressrosa.
He's Luffy's... brother!
Yeah, we've been tied up with missions.
Cut it out, rice-cracker man.
"GREAT ADVISOR" TSURU
THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS VICE ADMIRAL
What?!
An inspector general has barely
any responsibility - quite nice.
Let's make a report to Dragon-san first.
"Sending a Shock Wave!
The Worst Generation Goes Into Action!"
We have to repay you somehow.
Admiral Fujitora.
Why aren't you catching that pirate?
Do you wanna have a drink?
You know where Straw Hat is, don't you?
BALTIGO
THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY'S GENERAL HEADQUARTERS
So you know him from the Revolutionary Army?
"The deeply-wounded pirate
who saved the country."
Yes.
Luffy...
Robin, you don't have to wake him up.
It's so hectic.
Should I consider him an enemy?
Oh, Chief of Staff! You
came at the right time!
I just came to see his face before I leave.
Come to the situation room now!
Or should I let him go
since he's a hero to this country?
Aren't you gonna sleep?
The Paramount War between the Navy
and the Whitebeard Pirates has ended!
JUSTICE
--Am I disturbing you?
--No.
I can't decide.
Are you leaving the country already?
Yeah. Because some troublesome people are
headed back here.
I wanna spar with you someday.
Th-The admiral from the
Navy HQ is prostrating!
A die?!
Whitebeard lost?!
Who are they?
I can't believe a famous swordsman
such as you said that...
The Video Transponder Snail is running, too!
CP-0.
So, one of the Four Emperors has
been taken down...
What an honor.
This is no laughing matter!
Maybe someday when our wounds heal...
The Navy has a lot of casualties, too.
Seems like it was a hard battle as expected.
They played a part in Doflamingo's deception.
Yeah.
You can have the rest.
A die...
--What?! That's the Navy admiral, isn't it?!
--It is!
Thanks.
What about Ivan-san?! Is she alright?!
Well, it was mine to begin with...
That's enough!
It doesn't say she died or anything.
Oh, how scary.
I'll take a rest, too.
--What? What happened?
--Something's going on in Dressrosa!
The ones who died in the war were...
Boy!
Is that how you've been deciding whether to go after him?!
Give me some meat...
...the Emperor - Whitebeard...
I decided to leave Straw Hat and the others' fate
in the hands of providence.
And...
Raise your head, Fujitora.
...Fire Fist Ace!
But Tsuru-san.
They're targeting us!
Fujitora...
If he's just an ordinary person,
Rebecca...
But more importantly, Dragon-san, look...
would he have been saved by
providence two days in a row?!
Is it true?!
Is Straw Hat Luffy your son?!
Soldier-san!
Today's the third day and I'm not cheating.
Dressrosa will get crowded in a day or two.
Rebecca.
Fujitora, don't you mind
the world seeing this?!
Hm? Yes, he is.
You guys should leave as soon as possible, too.
I saw the list in the Colosseum.
What?!
You entered the competition as I thought.
I told you not to!
Thank you for telling us.
Hey! I want soba noodles, too!
Yes, sir! Coming right up!
Either way,
we're not gonna stay here for long.
No way!
I...
Thank you for assisting with the
transportation of Heavenly Demon.
I'll do it! I'll win it!
But maybe...
And what's more, I didn't know he
had another brotherbesides Ace.
Soldier-san!
Is this why you didn't touch Doflamingo?!
But I'm still in charge here.
So...
You're right. I've never heard of it.
So... Hey, can we live together?!
I bet so.
FIRE FIST ACE DIES
So let me handle it as I like.
I think it surprised Luffy the most.
Fujitora!
The world needs to know the truth!
Alright. But we Navy can't leave a pirate
with a bounty at large forever...
What do you mean by that?
I left all the fighting to them.
I took chances.
I was presumed dead for a long time.
I'm gonna become a pirate...
Please become Dande-donors!
We were the ones who let the
Warlord do as he pleases.
People of the Navy!
Please become Dande-donors!
...and defeat others and become infamous!
I was always with Luffy and Ace
when I was a kid.
How could we point our swords towards him
Oh, you came again today.
It'll be the only proof of my life!
and preach justice unashamedly?
Yes, I did.
We ran around like wild
and had it hard because of that old man, Garp.
Oh, look how cute she is!
And we dreamed about becoming pirates...
She's a Dwarf!
It doesn't matter if all the people in the world
reject me or despise me!
JUSTICE
This country won its victory
by the hands of pirates, warriors, and citizens!
I'm Mansherry from the Tontatta Tribe!
I'll become a great pirate
and show them what I can do!
She's cute!
Now, the so-called Twirly Hat Crew
who headed for Zou,
a mysterious island in the New World, is...
Oh! How rare!
We exchanged cups of sake
to become brothers.
Ouch! Wh-What the...?!
Show your respect, you guys!
Princess Mansherry is Chief
Tonta-sama's daughter!
Hey! Luffy!
But I got involved in an accident one day.
She's a princess!
Sabo-kun, what's wrong?!
Why don't you bow your head?!
Everyone!
I mean, an incident.
I want you to take him and head for Zou!
Luffy!
That's okay, Mouji.
Oh, how merciful she is!
You're acting strange!
Zoro!
D-Do you know...
12 YEARS AGO - SABO (10 YEARS OLD)
To tell you the truth, we mustn't
show ourselves in Dressrosa
The Twirly Hat Crew took Caesar,
the scientist from Punk Hazard
Oh! Usopp-dono!
that there will be a fire in the Gray Terminal tonight?
So you guys are okay!
to anyone but members of the royal family.
who ate the Gas-Gas Fruit, with them...
This is great! Luffy took down Doflamingo!
We all have to keep quiet about the plan!
...as they set out to meet
Luffy and the others at Zou.
So I wanted to heal everybody's
wounds without being seen...
Yeah!
Well, everything went as I planned though.
We're special!
But they were targeted by Big Mom, one
of the Four emperors, on their way.
Hmm. How?
Huh?
Usopp-dono, can you walk now?
Ace! Luffy!
I can't believe that Ace
was Gold Roger's son...
Yes, I can! As soon as Luffy won,
I felt the life come back into me!
There's something wrong with this town!
Everybody's crazy!
Her desire was to capture Caesar.
He was the biggest threat to the Navy
Even though they know that people will die soon,
they act normally and even smile!
so they wanted to get rid of him at any cost.
I don't wanna get caught by Big Mom!
Because I...
Rebecca! Rebecca!
Super!
I don't wanna stay here!
I gotta tell them quickly!
She has to put on her dress.
Where did she go?
...swindled research funds from them!
It's quite a super victory!
Don't scare me!
You bikini-clad, perverted, cyborg jerk!
We can't let anyone take
you anyway so shut up!
Did you guys know?!
Ace! Luffy! Run!
What's going on?
--Whoa-whoa, don't talk me up so much.
--I didn't!
They say Akainu punched a hole right
through his body!
Why did he make up such a lie?
You go ahead and sail for Zou!
--I'm blushing.
--You are?!
I'm a robot inside...
That's what Kyros wants.
Let's let everybody know
that Straw Hat's here.
What happened to you, boy?
The time has come!
Uh-huh.
Yeah! I've been waiting for this moment!
THE DOWNTOWN AREA
Me, too!
This town smells worse than Gray Terminal.
Take it away, Gyats!
Gyats!
We can become brothers
if we exchange this cup of sake!
Ladies and gentlemen!
It smells like rotten people!
Brothers? Really?!
The long, hard battle is over.
Today, our dream will finally come true!
Damn!
When we become pirates,
we might not be on the same ship
After all the struggle
to shake up Big Mom's ship...!
If I stay here... I'll never be free!
Today, on this very day,
the king will return!
but our brotherhood will always be with us!
You're all really great warriors!
Why did you wanna get into trouble again?!
Wherever you are, whatever you do,
we'll always be bonded together!
I'm proud of you!
That's right! After a decade,
King Riku-sama will announce...
You have no choice! Just do it!
Thank you all...
So from now on,
Don't tell me what to do!
Thank you for your hard work!
Ace... Luffy...
we're brothers!
...his return to the throne today!
The anti-Doflamingo coalition,
the little King Riku Army!
I wish I could see you.
We have no time for grumbling!
Yes, Commander!
King Riku! King Riku!
This place is like a birdcage!
How dare you kick me?!
Yeah!!
All operations are finished!
I'm saying it for the sake of you guys!
I don't think I can stand living in this country
filled with stale air.
King Riku! King Riku! King Riku!...
As of today, we're...
Don't stick your nose in their business!
We should've waited on the ship quietly!
Are you alright, Sabo?!
You're pretty stupid to be
rushing ahead like this!
Shut up and do what I say!
Are you gonna do it?!
...disbanded!
What is freedom?
The whole nation is excited.
Commander!
They got fooled by a pirate,
held a grudge against their king,
Or do you just want your
heart to be crushed?!
Where can I find it?
What a nice day!
It's perfect for setting sail!
and praised wealth and violence at one point,
--Sabo-kun!
--Sabo!
Fine! But I won't forget this!
but since they experienced fear of death,
The ship is huge!
they're staking their lives on hoping for
a peaceful country now.
It was the right call to come ashore!
Now I know!
We can still save them! We need your help!
The one who died wasn't
some unknown pirate...
It's like a joke but I can't
bring myself to laugh.
In that case,
why don't you treat me more nicely...
No one would find that funny!
I'm really happy that they survived!
How rude is that!
He wasn't just some threat in the Pirate Era
that needed to be eliminated!
Did you say something?!
Damn! The ship is on fire!
Stop taunting me with that!
Hurry up, Caesar!
Will I be able to make them happy?
Why did they shoot me like that?
We have guardian deities here
in Dressrosa.
I said "Don't tell me
what to do"! You raccoon!
Saint Jalmack!
There is a child on the ship!
Ace is my...
When someone flies a black flag,
he's a pirate regardless of who he is.
I'm a reindeer!
...brother!
What's the difference?!
They're little people who
some might call fairies.
Shut up! Just hurry up!
But most importantly...
If they die because of you,
I'll make you pay for it!
A commoner shouldn't cross
the path of my ship!!
It's you all.
I wish I could become a god-like king
who could even fend off natural disasters...
We need your help!
Hey! Don't say such dangerous things!
The little King Riku Army will be disbanded
I'm kidding...
but we still have so much work to do.
I'm not gonna run from anybody!
I'm not gonna lose to anyone!
We'll continue our efforts.
What else can we do?
It's hard to run here!
I can't believe we got separated
from Sanji-san and the others...
Work to take back...
We're in trouble!
our beautiful Dressrosa.
You're right.
We paid too much attention
to the mystery girl.
Until the day Rebecca inherits the throne...
--The chief woke up!
--Really?! That's great!
Oh, watch out! Nami-san!
Please continue looking after this country!
--Watch out! I gotta save myself!
--What?!
Ace... Luffy...
No, how could you?!
How could you?! How could you?!
Help me... Somebody...
Oh, about that... Is it going to be okay?
Help...
I remember how stubborn Scarlet was
when she was young.
Thank you, Brook.
I thought you were gonna die! Sabo-kun!
Onami! They're coming!
Issho-san!
Don't you think Rebecca will leave, too?
You had quite a high fever, Sabo.
The video transmission to the three
neighboring islands is completed!
You've been sleeping for three straight days!
What do you mean by that?
Yeehaw!
Okay, thank you for your work.
What?!
And I've been worrying!
Tank!
The Navy has their position to consider, too.
Hide the pirates and the warriors
who fought for us in the Palace.
What?! You got your memory back?!
He's late! He's too late!
Take those without shelter there as well!
I'm sorry but could you do that?
Yeah, I remember everything now.
I wonder what he's doing!
There! You're all set.
Of course, my pleasure, Your Majesty!
Including who I am and
why I left home and sailed out to sea.
Oh, how cute!
Ivankov-san, please relax!
Girls look better in dresses than armor!
I'm so frustrated and...
You think so?
Is this it, invaders?
You look great, Rebecca-sama!
I see. That's good.
Hey! Where did you hide that girl?!
My head's gonna explode...
Thank you.
RED LINE
When you wear that dress,
you look exactly like Scarlet-sama!
Are you gonna quit
the Revolutionary Army, then?!
Explode...
How did you guys invade the island?!
What?!
Or not!
Answer me! This place is quite atypical...
Oh yeah, we heard about your father!
That was a joke?!
No, I'm not.
THE HOLYLAND OF MARIEJOIS
Heehaw!
So,
What?!
What?! What's going on?!
reporting Doflamingo's resignation
from the Seven Warlords
They say that Scarlet-sama ran away with
a prince of a far-off foreign country.
--Is Dragon-san still here?
--He is.
What is it this time?!
and revealing it was a false report...
Was it all by the order
of those above you people?
You're late, Dragon!
I need to talk to him.
You kept us waiting for so long!
And that left King Riku-sama no choice
but to announce that she was dead.
It's a Rain-Ruption!
THE FIVE ELDERS
THE HIGHEST AUTHORITY OF THE WORLD GOVERNMENT
Sorry.
Oh, hey, that's...
Again?!
What?!
Get down!
That's like a romance novel!
SAKAZUKI (AKAINU)
THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS FLEET ADMIRAL
Why does the world have to
be thrown into confusion...
That's awful...
I can only dream about it!
What is that?!
Hey, treat him! Hurry up! It's urgent!
...for someone like Doflamingo?!
Rain?! No! It's a huge water spray!
Call the ship's doctor! Now!
If something like this ever happens again,
it'll bring shame on me as a fleet admiral!
At that moment, I felt Ace said to me,
THE DOWNTOWN AREA
"You're Sabo.
You're Luffy's and my brother."
Don't ever do that again on any account!
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming,
it's coming! It's coming this way!
A prince from where?
Don't give us any of your cheek, Sakazuki.
--No!
I heard he was from a lush country
with beautiful lakes.
Your honor is completely inconsequential!
Go away!
He woke up!
Don't surprise him.
The Navy is only the public
face of the Government!
I'll protect you no matter what!
But the country was in a war at that time.
I wasn't gonna do that!
Boy! How rude!
We left this case entirely up to Cipher Pol.
She fell for someone she shouldn't have
and had a baby - that was Rebecca.
That's why I...
Wait a sec!
Humph! Cipher Pol, huh?
What do you want?! Don't interrupt now!
Oh yeah?
Oh?
No!!
To put it simply,
But sadly, the prince died in the war and...
You...
Where am I?
you people also have been walked over by the
Nami-san!
What?
You're on board our ship.
Why did you finish the bottle?! It's empty!
Momonosuke-san!
Celestial Dragons' puppets, haven't you?!
...Scarlet-sama and Rebecca...
I mean, Rebecca-sama, were left behind
How dare you eat all the meat as well!
Help me!!
Watch your mouth, Sakazuki!
I can't listen to such a
story without drinking!
It says Sabo on your possessions.
Is it your name?
What about Kuzan?
so they were living in this country quietly.
Help me, too!
Whoa-whoa, both of you...
Sabo...
Boy! You Devil Fruit eaters
are such pains in the butt!
I see. So she only has pure
noble blood in her veins.
Well, we don't need alcohol
I can't believe a very powerful man
like him sides with Blackbeard now!
I don't know.
but we'll be in trouble without food
when Luffy wakes up.
You don't know?
What's your name, then?
I'm sorry that I couldn't protect you!
That's a strange rumor.
That's a dishonor to the Navy for sure!
All of our crew eat so much!
Kyros-dono is Rebecca-dono's
father, isn't he?
That idiot resigned from the Navy!
No idea...
I'll go and get groceries
later with Kin'emon.
I won't let you get away! You damn invaders!
Don't tell me he's...
Hm, I don't know.
Do you want some lettuce?
Where he is and what he's doing are
none of our concern!
Probably...
No thanks.
Thank you!
Get some booze, too.
He doesn't remember a thing?
Five Elders! Fleet Admiral Sakazuki!
Luffy's friends are funny.
Soldier-san is a brave man
Yes, even his own name...
You'll never get bored.
I first met him
at the Highland of the Goa Kingdom.
Hey, I wanna hear the rest already!
He will always be by your side
I'm here to report!
Okay.
The Warlord - Donquixote Doflamingo
and his Family got defeated
Come on! Brace up!
I'm sure he's one of the nobles from there.
Thank you as always...
Then, let's take him home.
Search for his parents...
by Straw Hat and Law's pirate alliance
You, too, Momo!
She must be feeling cold.
Thank you...
and Dressrosa has been
destroyed - nothing's left!
With this tin body, I don't feel anything.
No...
I don't wanna go back!
What?!
Why?!
Let me teach you how to fight.
I don't know!
There's no need since I have you.
But...
It's...
If something happens to
me, what are you gonna do?
...That brat again.
...that's the last thing I want!
When in doubt...
Come on!
My mother said I shouldn't hurt anyone!
Just kill!
But we can't have you on this ship forever!
To let you know I'm here all the time,
We have things to do!
I finally... managed to get here... Ace.
I'll drop a new flower
petal through the crack...
And there's another thing...
In that case!
In that case, just take me someplace else!
...in the window every morning.
Look at this. Luffy started to make his way
to become the King of the Pirates again.
You're just a kid! Don't be ridiculous!
That's our younger brother!
I'm begging you!
THE STRAW HATS ARE BACK
SOLDIER-SAN
COUNTRIES ACROSS THE NEW WORLD
The video and the story
that've been sent to...
When in doubt...
...Dressrosa's neighbors, spread
from one island to another.
Just kill!
What should we do, Dragon?
Breaking news!
It ran like wildfire through the whole world
and had some dire repercussions.
DOFLAMINGO FALLS
--Brook!
--Bonekichi!
I finally managed to protect you!
Joker got defeated!
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Your Majesty! We don't have
any other way to get weapons!
Sabo-kun?
I want you to ask the entire
Revolutionary Army a favor.
Leave the rest up to me!
Announce surrender.
Yes!
Tsk! How arrogant!
There's a Devil Fruit that
I want to get at any cost.
Sheep's Horn!
But Luffy-senpai,
what about the Flare-Flare Fruit?
Oh, they're distributing
Mansherry-dono's medicinal flowers!
The war is over!
What?!
I wanna keep it out of
the hands of a few people
--What are those arms?!
--Bonekichi!
Those are great!
They'll help people today again!
but I don't have a choice!
My friend's gonna die!
We've already paid! We have a deal!
Take this!
Get in a line and wait your turn.
Soul Parade!
Joker, that bastard!
Each person gets one.
I promise you I will win the Flare-Flare Fruit
so you can go out without worry!
Thank you! This medication works really well!
It heals a wound in an instant!
I know they still have weapons in Dressrosa!
You're not gonna run into the Navy here.
And we've already called in a town doctor, too.
No! The Navy admiral is there!
Wow! Bonekichi, that's awesome!
Thanks! I appreciate it!
The deal involving the Devil Fruits!
Oh, thank you!
What'll happen to the deal with SMILEs?!
Here.
What kind of ability is that?
What about booze?
Thank you!
We'll hold a banquet at a later date.
If only these fools weren't there!
What? We have to wait?
Dad! I got one for you!
I won't let you have the Flare-Flare Fruit.
Brook!
Sorry...
I'll use it for the wound on my head.
--Keep stalling him like that!
--What?!
We'll sleep in a huddle here tonight.
TSURU
What, Tsuru-chan!
You didn't need to come with us!
Diable! Mouton...
"Straw Hat Luffy"!
Wait a sec!
...Mallet!
Hey, hey, hey! Where you from?!
That's what I'm supposed to say,
Inspector General!
--Wow! It healed beautifully!
--It's like magic!
Cabbage! Are you gonna sleep here, too?!
You can't talk to Luffy-senpai so casually!
Well, they're the pirate group that you've
Of course, I am!
Why don't you just go to sleep, too?
I'm so grateful!
been chasing after
all this time, aren't they?
He is the legendary pirate
"Fire Fist" Ace-sama's brother
Somebody! Bring me a chain! A strong one!
Yes, by your order.
Want some rice crackers?
No thanks!
and he will become the King of
the Pirates one day, you idiot!
Or we'll see a monster!
The number of Navy soldiers has
been increased as I thought!
Sheepshead-sama!
Go faster without getting us noticed
by the Navy, Spring Sparrow!
I've known that from way back.
Wh-What are you doing?! Bartolomeo!
Sanji-kun!
Oh, Nami-san!
Now we can have a good sleep!
THE NAVY CAMP
Who are you people?!
Is that how you joined the Revolutionary Army?
Who are you people... Oh!
Sort of.
What's your problem?!
One thing that I knew for sure was
that I didn't wanna go back to my parents at any price.
What?! How creepy!
You can't just appear out of nowhere
and say you won't let me have the fruit!
The big news from Dressrosa
sped around the world and the
Gin-Rummy-sama!
pirates from the Worst
Generation learned of it, too.
Guys! Retreat!
Sheepshead-sama has been taken down!
The Worst Generation includes 11
rookies with bounties over 100 million
Other than that, I didn't remember a thing.
What?!
Here.
But we haven't found the samurai yet!
Okay.
who gathered at Sabaody
Archipelago two years ago.
It's me, Luffy.
BALTIGO
THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY'S GENERAL HEADQUARTERS
Although we cornered them this far,
he didn't show himself!
They're the troublemakers who
were born at the change of the
Thank you!
So cute!
The samurai's not here! Tell him so!
What do you mean "It's me"?!
era and hold the key to the
future of this war-torn world.
I see. We can donate our healing
properties like a blood donation.
Listen! The Flare-Flare Fruit
is a keepsake from Ace!
Lower your center of gravity!
Yes, ma'am!
People call them "the Worst Generation."
There's no point in
keeping those who can't fight with us!
If you want it, you're my enemy!
What a wonderful ability
that the Heal-Heal Fruit grants.
A TOWN SOMEWHERE
And you called me "Luffy" but...
This will soften my muscles.
Hey, look at that!
Alright, you can take some from me, too.
...look at this beard!
Where are you going, Sabo?! Stop for a sec!
I'm Lucy!
How's this? This is our special
today - supreme pizza.
You'll get enough to cure
10 heavily-injured people!
You think I can't tell my brother's face
just because he's in disguise?
Oh, we can always count on you!
I'm gonna go train myself!
The water's draining away...
Oh! A thief!
"Brother"?!
Hey, old lady, stop!
Then, I'll donate enough for 15 people!
Listen, the only people who
can call me their brother
What was that all about?
What?! Then, I'll donate
enough for 20 people!
Crap! Where did she go?!
are the late Ace and
It's a strange island.
How's that kid?
the guy who died much earlier...
I'll donate enough for 25 people!
Even though he lost his memory,
his body remembers how he used to move.
I hope that girl's okay, too...
Alright! Enough for 100 people then!
Tsk! A little girl!
Old lady, where are you?!
She moves quicker than
us so she'll be alright.
D-Died...
Thank you but I don't think that's possible.
Oh, they took down Doflamingo.
I don't know what he'd been doing before
but obviously, he has a lot of experience in fighting.
You're right.
Good job. I'm happy to be in
the same generation with them.
I bet he used to be quite a naughty kid.
I already don't know what to do with him.
Tsuru-san.
"GLUTTON" JEWELRY BONNEY FROM THE SOUTH BLUE
THE CAPTAIN OF THE BONNEY PIRATES
Hey! Guys!
Go ahead and roll it for today.
SOMEWHERE IN THE SKY
Get over here now!
That's Chopperemon!
From the forest down below!
Sabo!!
If it's anything other than "one,"
we'll go after Straw Hat and Law right away.
Let's go now! There's no time to lose!
Monk Urouge!
I don't believe you!
S-Somebody's here! High Priest!
We stole a bottle of sake from Dadan
and made a toast...
THE KID PIRATES' SAFE HOUSE
"MAD MONK" UROUGE FROM A SKY ISLAND
THE CAPTAIN OF THE FALLEN MONK PIRATES
Don't be silly. We're on a Sky Island.
You haven't won yet!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
It's also an abandoned lonely cloud island.
Sabo?!
No one else is...
Food?!
What was that?
What?
I thought you were sleeping!
The Navy might come at any time.
Let's hurry and eat.
What happened?!
Captain! There's a massive hole!
What the...
Where have you been all this time?!
Kuma-san's next? Here I go!
A SEA SOMEWHERE
--Y-Yeah!
--Yeah!
Whoa-whoa, they have some
nerve, the pirate alliance.
--A hole?
--Something landed!
Alright!
I thought you were dead!
--Arm yourselves!
--Yeah!
Looks like my friends are kicking butt.
CAPONE "GANG" BEGE FROM THE WEST BLUE
THE CAPTAIN OF THE FIRETANK PIRATES
We'll capture Caesar at any cost, guys!
Damn!
Thank you, Luffy!
Boy oh boy... And all they kept
talking about was how Rebecca-dono's
That's it!
Yes, Father!
I'm glad that you're alive!
We gotta go out to sea someday...
THE KID PIRATES' SAFE HOUSE
father is a prince of some country.
Right?
They went ahead of us before we knew it.
That's right.
...and live as we like.
Freer than anyone else.
It's a huge victory!
But Sabo, I...
WHAT'S THAT?! THAT'S A STRANGE STORY!
Vat's ghat?! Ghat's a ftranni wtory!
Uh-huh!
Doflamingo is connected to Kaido
behind the scenes for sure.
Let's go out to sea at 17!
I let Ace get killed in front of me...
AND I'M SAD BECAUSE SABO'S GONE!
Ond U'm wad fegause Abo'z mon!
Then, it'll make Kaido mad.
And we will become... pirates!
It sure is big.
I know! Even though Ace died, I'm...
EUSTASS "CAPTAIN" KID FROM THE SOUTH BLUE
THE CAPTAIN OF THE KID PIRATES
If they planned this, their target must be...
Where did it fall from?
Ee molla ketchupom Wanji'z
froup, woo, ina buwwy!
WE GOTTA CATCH UP WITH SANJI'S
GROUP, TOO, IN A HURRY!
Who in the world did this?!
"MAGICIAN" BASIL HAWKINS FROM THE NORTH BLUE
THE CAPTAIN OF THE HAWKINS PIRATES
Peel these, too!
...so happy that you survived!
10 YEARS AGO - SABO (12 YEARS OLD)
...The Four Emperors as we thought.
What?!
Hey, doesn't it look like
the shape of a human?
I almost helplessly lost both of my brothers!
"ROAR OF THE SEA" SCRATCHMEN APOO
FROM THE GRAND LINE (THE LONGARM TRIBE)
THE CAPTAIN OF THE ON-AIR PIRATES
Get mad or cry or rush or sleep or eat!
Do one at a time!
"King of the Beasts" Kaido.
I once heard...
You want some?
"MURDER MACHINE" KILLER FROM THE SOUTH BLUE
A COMBAT CREWMAN OF THE KID PIRATES
...a legend about a Sky Island
where some monster lives...
If you had also died,
I would've been left on my own!
Take it seriously!
You're so restless!
I'm glad that our target
is different from theirs.
I'm orrwy!
Rebecca's father is that soldier man...
We don't have to fight each other
and waste our military power.
...somewhere in the sky around here.
Have you ever heard that?
You're not fully recovered!
Don't be greedy and get more sleep!
Our target is the other one of the Four Emperors,
"Red-Haired" Shanks!
Are you saying that
it was pushed off of a Sky Island?!
Sabo-kun!
Sabo!
BY THUNDER! WHO MADE UP SUCH A LIE?!
Ay dunder! Oo wradap dacha eye?!
Captain Kid!
And Drake who once provoked a
battle in Kaido's territory...
One of our ships was capsized by the impact!
But I understand how you can't buy that.
AN ISLAND SOMEWHERE
What?!
Your father got killed?! By Doflamingo?!
Are you sure about it, Kin'emon?
Thank you!
Damn it all! Who did this?!
Yes, I really heard it with my own ears!
The strong live and the weak die.
Thank you for being alive, Luffy!
Me, too, for certain!
That is just how this world is.
It was a long time ago.
I'm not holding a grudge.
"RED FLAG" X.DRAKE FROM THE NORTH BLUE
THE CAPTAIN OF THE DRAKE PIRATES
What?! How could you be so cold?
A few minutes ago...
Then, why don't you help us?
I started the rumor.
It's an emergency!
If we don't let him know quickly, he'll snap!
Can I eat the Flare-Flare Fruit?
A SKY ISLAND - THE RUINED
CITY OF BALLOON TERMINAL
What?!
Oh?
Kaido-sama! Where are you?!
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
That fool - Joker messed it up!
Oh, boy...
That'd be nice!
That's the only option we've got!
The only people who know
about Rebecca's birth are...
Although it was just training,
he fought bravely against the higher-ups.
We can't get SMILEs anymore!
...some people in the royal family
What are you doing?
and some people in the Donquixote
Family who did the research.
Stop playing dumb, Issho!
Let's leave him alone, Monk!
The only thing that the whole
nation knows is about her mother.
You just wait! I'll make my name soon!
FIVE YEARS AGO - ACE (17 YEARS OLD)
He must be insane!
Luffy... He's laughing.
We're at a height of 10,000 meters...
You know how important it is
for a Navy admiral to admit an oversight!
Good luck, Ace!
I wonder what kind of a dream he's having.
SOLDIER-SAN
I started the rumor
before they found out I'm her father.
Why didn't you report to HQ first?!
--I'm leaving now.
--Already?
A BATTLEFIELD IN SOME COUNTRY
He was looking for a place to die.
Why?
If I'd reported it, you would've changed
the details of the news again, wouldn't you?
I got to see his face so...
Here, I made a Vivre Card
of Luffy's just in case.
Fire!
I have a criminal record.
If he's serious, why bother to stop him?
Oh, when did you have time for that?
I'm ill-bred as well.
What did you say?!
No, I can't reach them!
I'll take a piece of it.
I wasn't supposed to marry
a member of the royal family in the first place.
To sum up his life,
The arrangement was they'll open the front gate, wasn't it?
Those who snuck in first - what are they doing?
he had been defeated seven times as a pirate
All right. Luffy might be a
bit much for you to handle,
So...
I think the Seven Warlord
system must end, too.
but take good care of him.
Ring, ring, ring...
and was captured
by the Navy or his enemies 18 times.
...this is how it should be.
Clank.
I'll figure something out!
No, it's not!
Yeah! You can count on us!
Sabo! Where are you?!
Does Rebecca know that?!
Clank.
He underwent torture repeatedly
and had been living as a criminal.
Is that it?!
Two years ago, I was there at the scene
when Crocodile showed his true nature!
SABO (17 YEARS OLD)
It's natural for a big brother to worry
about his bungling kid brother.
She must've gotten the letter.
Sabo-kun!
Sabo!
I wrote everything about my life truthfully.
We Navy couldn't do anything!
He's pushing it too far again!
He might be a bit much for you to handle,
What's with him?!
I made her suffer for a long time.
Shoot him up!
but take good care of 'im.
If it weren't for the Straw Hats,
He wanted to kill himself...
I want her to cut her connection
to a person like me
Alabasta would've become a country
governed by a pirate like Dressrosa now.
Why can't we hit him?!
and live happily in the light hereafter.
...by jumping off a Sky Island
which is rather out of the ordinary...
He said the same thing Ace said.
But the Government reported
that it was the Navy's achievement!
So that's the only way I can make it up
to her as a father.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
That's what led up to this.
I'm thinking about leaving this country
when you guys do.
Clank.
If I had a higher status at that time...!
Is this Sabo? This is Hack.
Follow Sabo!
Yeah, I just left the
house. I'll be back soon.
It bears repeating.
She's still a child.
Roger that.
He challenged the Navy and the
Four Emperors single-handedly
So how was it? Luffy-kun was quite...
I don't want her to ruin her chance
to be happy by being caught up in the moment!
Clank.
Sabo-kun, we freed the citizens and our allies
who were captive!
and was captured 18 times;
sentenced to death 40 times.
I convinced King Riku-sama, too!
We'll leave the rest up to you!
All right!
Why did he hang up?! That selfish jerk!
When he was hanged, the chain broke.
Clank.
I can't believe he really
did it... Fujitora...
Whoa-whoa! Hack-san!
Stop!
When he was sent to a guillotine,
the blade shattered.
You can't get away!
It reminds me of the frustration I felt
at Alabasta Kingdom two years ago.
He's not buying it at all.
When sentenced to impalement,
the spear crumbled.
The Straw Hats' achievement was
covered up that time, too...
Consequently, he sank
nine giant prison ships.
What is it? Could you look at it?
He's all by himself! How idiotic!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
It's like he paid them back for us.
That means no one could kill him.
It's "one"...
Even if I had the same status,
I couldn't have done such a thing.
What now?
I see... The only side that
would be in Straw Hat's favor -
Even himself.
Commander! Oh I mean, Kyros-sama!
This is Leo!
Here it is.
I could feast on this feeling for days.
that's what we agreed on, isn't it?
Dragon Claw Fist!
Yes, it is but...
Oh, we have muffins.
Want some coffee?
Zoro-senpai!
Then, he won this one.
--Didn't mean I wanna eat something, idiot!
--What?
Oh, Luffy-senpai! You're up! Good morning!
Dragon...
What is it this time?!
...Breath!
--Sis! I'm hungry!
--We're hungry!
We won't arrest him tonight.
You can't determine that
with a die roll! Issho-san!
We have muffins. Want some coffee?
We ran across the entire country
and finally found where he is!
You can't give kids coffee!
--I want a muffin!
--Where's Dekapants (big underwear)?
You lashed out against
Fleet Admiral Sakazuki like that!
When there are five members of the
Straw Hats gathered together,
You've gone too far, Sabo-kun.
"Vegapunk," that is.
If you wanna take down Law and
Straw Hat, now's the chance!
It'll take a few more days
to Dr. Vegapunk's lab.
they're too bright to even look at!
It's like a laser beam of greatness!
Maynard-san!
What is that monster?!
Achieving such a feat at your age
is really something.
How lovely!
Captain-chan's sweet to the kids!
A man shouldn't grumble like that
after a die has been cast.
If I see all the stars of the Straw
Hats someday, I'll get dissolved!
Damn! My head hurts!
I wish I were a kid!
It won't be so long before
you lead the Revolutionary Army.
Oh, you guys!
There is tons of work to do!
You're pathetic.
I guess it's hard to die.
Oh yeah. I heard a rookie who refused to join
the Seven Warlords is around your age.
Just say what you're here for already!
--Okay!
--Scold me more, Captain-chan!
I survived again!
Oh yeah!
THE ROYAL PALACE
There's a lot of commotion at the Navy camp!
Oh, you mean "Fire Fist"?
Did anybody see Lucy after that?
They're gonna be here at any minute!
"Fire Fist"?
He managed to pull off dying...
That old man, Whitebeard...
I heard he's a very hot-blooded guy.
--No, nobody did.
--I wanna say "Thank you" to him at least!
"Great Advisor" Vice Admiral Tsuru
and the former fleet admiral - Sengoku arrived!
Well, I wonder how much he can do
in the New World...
There's already quite a fuss out there.
Tsuru and Sengoku?!
Even if they truly are pirates or criminals,
If I'm correct, his name is Portgas D.--
What are such heavyweights
doing here?! Go away!
they're our saviors without question.
Ace.
That's right, Ace! Oh, you knew!
Sengoku...
Cover-ups happen all the time!
Leo, what did you call me for?
No, d-did I say something?
Oh, the Navy is going into action now!
I don't wanna be made into a hero with lies.
The man looking for a place to die -
Kaido, King of the Beasts.
Grandfather-sama!
You've lost your memory again?
It was our boss - the
World Government who hired
Rebecca...
Father-sama, Lucy,
and the others aren't here at the Palace!
It's "six."
pirates to maintain the balance of the world.
Yeah but don't worry. I
got a call from Kyros.
TWO YEARS AGO
It's a mandate from heaven!
All Navy units!
Catch the Straw Hats, Trafalgar Law,
It's a matter of credibility
and dignity for the Navy HQ!
LUFFY (17 YEARS OLD)
"If it's one-on-one, Kaido will win."
That's what people say.
They're together.
What nice day for setting sail!
I-Issho-san, y-you're talking to...
Okay.
and all the criminals who've been hidden
at the Palace in one fell swoop!
Your selfish action dishonored
the face of justice!
That aside...
On land, sea, and air, he
is a pirate who is known
You don't know who you're messing with.
Rebecca.
Yes, sir!
If you don't want it to be dishonored,
keep it close to you all the time!
Look at this technique
I've been training for 10 years!
as the strongest creature
among all living things.
If I go back to being a king again,
If we lose credibility just by admitting fault,
we didn't have any in the first place!
you'll be a princess, you know?
Admiral-dono! Do we have
permission to enter the Palace?!
What?
You don't need to worry about anything.
I'll take full responsibility!
I have no choice now, do I?!
SABO (20 YEARS OLD)
Roger!
So you'd lost your memory until two years ago?
Yeah...
If it was that serious,
how did you get your memory back?
You have to clean up
after yourself, Fujitora!
Ace helped me.
Can we depart anytime?
Dammit!
Yeah, anytime.
Straw Hat and Law...
Until you bring their heads,
Hurry up, Joker!
All right! Once we go back to Baltigo,
That's what I think now.
Make preparations for the final battle!
I gotta tell Dragon-san so much about Luffy!
FIRE FIST ACE DIES
you can't set foot in any Navy base
in the world!
The timing couldn't be any worse than that
but...
It was...
...really nice to see you again!
I don't care if this boring
world is destroyed!
Yes, that's exactly what I wanted!
Let's hurry up!
...that was why...
Let's start the greatest war
the world has ever seen!
...he awakened my memory.
Meat...
Sanji, Nami, and the others who were
being chased by Big Mom's ship,
Dressrosa celebrates King Rikufs
restoration to the throne
On that fateful day, Sabo set sail towards
what seemed to be certain death.
To save the Straw Hats from
being penned in by the Navy,
The Paramount War in Marineford
that became legend.
after a decade and the debut
of their new princess, Rebecca.
have already been on a whole
What happened to Sabo when Ace died?
How did he survive and grow up
the cadre of tough warriors from the
Colosseum start their escape plan.
new adventure on the strangest island ever!
to be a warrior in the
Revolutionary Army under Dragon?
However, when the Navyfs heavyweights,
"Inspector General" Sengoku
And what did he have on his mind
when he showed up in front of Luffy?
At the same time,
in front of Kid and the others who
are aiming to defeat the Four Emperors,
Meanwhile, Luffy dashes towards
the palace on his own and
and "Great Advisor" Tsuru,
show up in front of Fujitora,
Sabo's untold stories of eventful adventures -
his unknown days are finally revealed!
That shocking truth and the story of
the brothers' strong bond will finally be revealed!
a pirate who is known as the
strongest among all creatures
the die that will determine Luffy
and the others' fate is cast!
starts some big trouble which
shakes up the whole country!
on land, sea, and air, descends from the sky!
On the next episode of One Piece!
On the next episode of One Piece! "The Brothers' Bond!
The Untold Story Behind Luffy and Sabo's Reunion!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A State of Emergency! Rebecca Is Kidnapped!"
"Fujitora Takes Action! The
Complete Siege of the Straw Hats!"
"The Birth of the Legend!
The Adventures of the Revolutionary Warrior Sabo!"
"The Strongest Creature!
One of the Four Emperors - Kaido, King of the Beasts!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!
Ifm gonna be the King of the Pirates!