Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa governed by
the Warlord - Donquixote Doflamingo.
They took down the executives of
the Donquixote Family one after another.
And finally...
King Kong...
...Gun!
He brought down Doflamingo!
Come back.
King of miracles, Riku Doldo!
He's right, King Riku-dono!
This whole trouble that Doflamingo caused...
I don't want you to take the responsibility.
That vicious pirate was
approved as a king of a country
under the Seven Warlord system
and allowed to reign over this island
by none other than...
...the World Government!
All citizens...
All members of the royal family...
On behalf of the Government,
I most humbly apologize!
We deeply regret what we did!
"Sending a Shock Wave!
The Worst Generation Goes Into Action!"
JUSTICE
Th-The admiral from the
Navy HQ is prostrating!
The Video Transponder Snail is running, too!
--What?! That's the Navy admiral, isn't it?!
--It is!
--What? What happened?
--Something's going on in Dressrosa!
Raise your head, Fujitora.
Fujitora...
Fujitora, don't you mind
the world seeing this?!
No way!
But maybe...
Is this why you didn't touch Doflamingo?!
Fujitora!
The world needs to know the truth!
I left all the fighting to them.
I took chances.
We were the ones who let the
Warlord do as he pleases.
How could we point our swords towards him
and preach justice unashamedly?
JUSTICE
This country won its victory
by the hands of pirates, warriors, and citizens!
Hey! Luffy!
Luffy!
Zoro!
Oh! Usopp-dono!
So you guys are okay!
This is great! Luffy took down Doflamingo!
Yeah!
Well, everything went as I planned though.
Huh?
Usopp-dono, can you walk now?
Yes, I can! As soon as Luffy won,
I felt the life come back into me!
Super!
It's quite a super victory!
Don't scare me!
You bikini-clad, perverted, cyborg jerk!
--Whoa-whoa, don't talk me up so much.
--I didn't!
--I'm blushing.
--You are?!
I'm a robot inside...
Let's let everybody know
that Straw Hat's here.
Uh-huh.
The long, hard battle is over.
You're all really great warriors!
I'm proud of you!
Thank you all...
Thank you for your hard work!
The anti-Doflamingo coalition,
the little King Riku Army!
Yes, Commander!
All operations are finished!
As of today, we're...
...disbanded!
Commander!
We have guardian deities here
in Dressrosa.
They're little people who
some might call fairies.
It's you all.
The little King Riku Army will be disbanded
but we still have so much work to do.
Work to take back...
our beautiful Dressrosa.
Please continue looking after this country!
Issho-san!
The video transmission to the three
neighboring islands is completed!
Okay, thank you for your work.
Tank!
The Navy has their position to consider, too.
Hide the pirates and the warriors
who fought for us in the Palace.
Take those without shelter there as well!
I'm sorry but could you do that?
Of course, my pleasure, Your Majesty!
RED LINE
THE HOLYLAND OF MARIEJOIS
So,
reporting Doflamingo's resignation
from the Seven Warlords
and revealing it was a false report...
Was it all by the order
of those above you people?
THE FIVE ELDERS
THE HIGHEST AUTHORITY OF THE WORLD GOVERNMENT
SAKAZUKI (AKAINU)
THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS FLEET ADMIRAL
Why does the world have to
be thrown into confusion...
...for someone like Doflamingo?!
If something like this ever happens again,
it'll bring shame on me as a fleet admiral!
Don't ever do that again on any account!
Don't give us any of your cheek, Sakazuki.
Your honor is completely inconsequential!
The Navy is only the public
face of the Government!
We left this case entirely up to Cipher Pol.
Humph! Cipher Pol, huh?
To put it simply,
you people also have been walked over by the
Celestial Dragons' puppets, haven't you?!
Watch your mouth, Sakazuki!
What about Kuzan?
I can't believe a very powerful man
like him sides with Blackbeard now!
That's a dishonor to the Navy for sure!
That idiot resigned from the Navy!
Where he is and what he's doing are
none of our concern!
Five Elders! Fleet Admiral Sakazuki!
I'm here to report!
The Warlord - Donquixote Doflamingo
and his Family got defeated
by Straw Hat and Law's pirate alliance
and Dressrosa has been
destroyed - nothing's left!
What?!
It's...
...That brat again.
And there's another thing...
COUNTRIES ACROSS THE NEW WORLD
The video and the story
that've been sent to...
...Dressrosa's neighbors, spread
from one island to another.
Breaking news!
It ran like wildfire through the whole world
and had some dire repercussions.
DOFLAMINGO FALLS
Joker got defeated!
Your Majesty! We don't have
any other way to get weapons!
Announce surrender.
The war is over!
We've already paid! We have a deal!
Joker, that bastard!
I know they still have weapons in Dressrosa!
No! The Navy admiral is there!
The deal involving the Devil Fruits!
What'll happen to the deal with SMILEs?!
If only these fools weren't there!
TSURU
What, Tsuru-chan!
You didn't need to come with us!
That's what I'm supposed to say,
Inspector General!
Well, they're the pirate group that you've
been chasing after
all this time, aren't they?
Yes, by your order.
Want some rice crackers?
No thanks!
The big news from Dressrosa
sped around the world and the
pirates from the Worst
Generation learned of it, too.
The Worst Generation includes 11
rookies with bounties over 100 million
who gathered at Sabaody
Archipelago two years ago.
They're the troublemakers who
were born at the change of the
era and hold the key to the
future of this war-torn world.
People call them "the Worst Generation."
A TOWN SOMEWHERE
How's this? This is our special
today - supreme pizza.
Oh! A thief!
Hey, old lady, stop!
Crap! Where did she go?!
Tsk! A little girl!
Old lady, where are you?!
Oh, they took down Doflamingo.
Good job. I'm happy to be in
the same generation with them.
"GLUTTON" JEWELRY BONNEY FROM THE SOUTH BLUE
THE CAPTAIN OF THE BONNEY PIRATES
SOMEWHERE IN THE SKY
Monk Urouge!
S-Somebody's here! High Priest!
"MAD MONK" UROUGE FROM A SKY ISLAND
THE CAPTAIN OF THE FALLEN MONK PIRATES
Don't be silly. We're on a Sky Island.
It's also an abandoned lonely cloud island.
No one else is...
A SEA SOMEWHERE
Whoa-whoa, they have some
nerve, the pirate alliance.
Looks like my friends are kicking butt.
CAPONE "GANG" BEGE FROM THE WEST BLUE
THE CAPTAIN OF THE FIRETANK PIRATES
We'll capture Caesar at any cost, guys!
Yes, Father!
THE KID PIRATES' SAFE HOUSE
They went ahead of us before we knew it.
It's a huge victory!
Doflamingo is connected to Kaido
behind the scenes for sure.
Then, it'll make Kaido mad.
EUSTASS "CAPTAIN" KID FROM THE SOUTH BLUE
THE CAPTAIN OF THE KID PIRATES
If they planned this, their target must be...
"MAGICIAN" BASIL HAWKINS FROM THE NORTH BLUE
THE CAPTAIN OF THE HAWKINS PIRATES
...The Four Emperors as we thought.
"ROAR OF THE SEA" SCRATCHMEN APOO
FROM THE GRAND LINE (THE LONGARM TRIBE)
THE CAPTAIN OF THE ON-AIR PIRATES
"King of the Beasts" Kaido.
"MURDER MACHINE" KILLER FROM THE SOUTH BLUE
A COMBAT CREWMAN OF THE KID PIRATES
I'm glad that our target
is different from theirs.
We don't have to fight each other
and waste our military power.
Our target is the other one of the Four Emperors,
"Red-Haired" Shanks!
And Drake who once provoked a
battle in Kaido's territory...
AN ISLAND SOMEWHERE
Your father got killed?! By Doflamingo?!
It was a long time ago.
I'm not holding a grudge.
"RED FLAG" X.DRAKE FROM THE NORTH BLUE
THE CAPTAIN OF THE DRAKE PIRATES
What?! How could you be so cold?
Then, why don't you help us?
It's an emergency!
If we don't let him know quickly, he'll snap!
Kaido-sama! Where are you?!
That fool - Joker messed it up!
We can't get SMILEs anymore!
Stop playing dumb, Issho!
You know how important it is
for a Navy admiral to admit an oversight!
Why didn't you report to HQ first?!
If I'd reported it, you would've changed
the details of the news again, wouldn't you?
What did you say?!
I think the Seven Warlord
system must end, too.
Two years ago, I was there at the scene
when Crocodile showed his true nature!
We Navy couldn't do anything!
If it weren't for the Straw Hats,
Alabasta would've become a country
governed by a pirate like Dressrosa now.
But the Government reported
that it was the Navy's achievement!
If I had a higher status at that time...!
I can't believe he really
did it... Fujitora...
It reminds me of the frustration I felt
at Alabasta Kingdom two years ago.
The Straw Hats' achievement was
covered up that time, too...
It's like he paid them back for us.
Even if I had the same status,
I couldn't have done such a thing.
I could feast on this feeling for days.
Oh, we have muffins.
Want some coffee?
--Didn't mean I wanna eat something, idiot!
--What?
--Sis! I'm hungry!
--We're hungry!
We have muffins. Want some coffee?
You can't give kids coffee!
--I want a muffin!
--Where's Dekapants (big underwear)?
"Vegapunk," that is.
It'll take a few more days
to Dr. Vegapunk's lab.
How lovely!
Captain-chan's sweet to the kids!
I wish I were a kid!
Oh, you guys!
There is tons of work to do!
--Okay!
--Scold me more, Captain-chan!
Cover-ups happen all the time!
I don't wanna be made into a hero with lies.
It was our boss - the
World Government who hired
pirates to maintain the balance of the world.
It's a matter of credibility
and dignity for the Navy HQ!
I-Issho-san, y-you're talking to...
Your selfish action dishonored
the face of justice!
If you don't want it to be dishonored,
keep it close to you all the time!
If we lose credibility just by admitting fault,
we didn't have any in the first place!
You have to clean up
after yourself, Fujitora!
Straw Hat and Law...
Until you bring their heads,
you can't set foot in any Navy base
in the world!
Yes, that's exactly what I wanted!
Meat...
On that fateful day, Sabo set sail towards
what seemed to be certain death.
How did he survive and grow up
to be a warrior in the
Revolutionary Army under Dragon?
Sabo's untold stories of eventful adventures -
his unknown days are finally revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Birth of the Legend!
The Adventures of the Revolutionary Warrior Sabo!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!