Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and brought down the Warlord -
Donquixote Doflamingo.
Now, peace has returned to Dressrosa.
Isn't this warmer?
Yes, it's much warmer!
Soldier-san is a brave man
He will always be by your side
"Fujitora Takes Action!
The Complete Siege of the Straw Hats!"
THE SOUTH SHORE OF DRESSROSA
Three days after the end of the battle...
...between the Straw Hats
and the Donquixote Family...
We finally arrived!
NAVY BRAND RICE CRACKERS
Is Straw Hat Luffy still
here in this country?
Yes. It's confirmed. He's badly wounded.
I see.
We've placed lookout units
in every port of Dressrosa.
We won't let them escape
under any circumstances.
Our camp is that way.
We better get going, girls.
Yes, ma'am!
You're all fired up, Tsuru-chan!
Shut up! Let's go!
Issho! I heard what you did!
"BUDDHA" SENGOKU
THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS INSPECTOR GENERAL
The prostration and the clash with Sakazuki!
I'm glad that I'm not a
fleet admiral anymore!
Cut it out, rice-cracker man.
"GREAT ADVISOR" TSURU
THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS VICE ADMIRAL
An inspector general has barely
any responsibility - quite nice.
Admiral Fujitora.
Why aren't you catching that pirate?
You know where Straw Hat is, don't you?
"The deeply-wounded pirate
who saved the country."
Should I consider him an enemy?
Or should I let him go
since he's a hero to this country?
I can't decide.
A die?!
This is no laughing matter!
A die...
That's enough!
Oh, how scary.
Boy!
Is that how you've been deciding whether to go after him?!
I decided to leave Straw Hat and the others' fate
in the hands of providence.
But Tsuru-san.
If he's just an ordinary person,
would he have been saved by
providence two days in a row?!
Today's the third day and I'm not cheating.
Hey! I want soba noodles, too!
Yes, sir! Coming right up!
Thank you for assisting with the
transportation of Heavenly Demon.
But I'm still in charge here.
So let me handle it as I like.
Alright. But we Navy can't leave a pirate
with a bounty at large forever...
Please become Dande-donors!
People of the Navy!
Oh, you came again today.
Yes, I did.
Oh, look how cute she is!
She's a Dwarf!
I'm Mansherry from the Tontatta Tribe!
She's cute!
Oh! How rare!
Ouch! Wh-What the...?!
Show your respect, you guys!
Princess Mansherry is Chief
Tonta-sama's daughter!
She's a princess!
Why don't you bow your head?!
That's okay, Mouji.
Oh, how merciful she is!
To tell you the truth, we mustn't
show ourselves in Dressrosa
to anyone but members of the royal family.
So I wanted to heal everybody's
wounds without being seen...
Hmm. How?
Rebecca! Rebecca!
She has to put on her dress.
Where did she go?
What's going on?
Why did he make up such a lie?
That's what Kyros wants.
The time has come!
Yeah! I've been waiting for this moment!
THE DOWNTOWN AREA
Me, too!
Take it away, Gyats!
Gyats!
Ladies and gentlemen!
Today, our dream will finally come true!
Today, on this very day,
the king will return!
That's right! After a decade,
King Riku-sama will announce...
...his return to the throne today!
King Riku! King Riku!
King Riku! King Riku! King Riku!...
The whole nation is excited.
They got fooled by a pirate,
held a grudge against their king,
and praised wealth and violence at one point,
but since they experienced fear of death,
they're staking their lives on hoping for
a peaceful country now.
It's like a joke but I can't
bring myself to laugh.
No one would find that funny!
I'm really happy that they survived!
Will I be able to make them happy?
I wish I could become a god-like king
who could even fend off natural disasters...
Hey! Don't say such dangerous things!
I'm kidding...
We'll continue our efforts.
What else can we do?
You're right.
Until the day Rebecca inherits the throne...
Oh, about that... Is it going to be okay?
I remember how stubborn Scarlet was
when she was young.
Don't you think Rebecca will leave, too?
What do you mean by that?
There! You're all set.
Oh, how cute!
Girls look better in dresses than armor!
You think so?
You look great, Rebecca-sama!
Thank you.
When you wear that dress,
you look exactly like Scarlet-sama!
Oh yeah, we heard about your father!
What?!
They say that Scarlet-sama ran away with
a prince of a far-off foreign country.
And that left King Riku-sama no choice
but to announce that she was dead.
That's like a romance novel!
I can only dream about it!
THE DOWNTOWN AREA
A prince from where?
I heard he was from a lush country
with beautiful lakes.
But the country was in a war at that time.
She fell for someone she shouldn't have
and had a baby - that was Rebecca.
Oh yeah?
But sadly, the prince died in the war and...
...Scarlet-sama and Rebecca...
I mean, Rebecca-sama, were left behind
so they were living in this country quietly.
I see. So she only has pure
noble blood in her veins.
That's a strange rumor.
Kyros-dono is Rebecca-dono's
father, isn't he?
Hm, I don't know.
Do you want some lettuce?
No thanks.
Soldier-san is a brave man
He will always be by your side
She must be feeling cold.
With this tin body, I don't feel anything.
Let me teach you how to fight.
There's no need since I have you.
If something happens to
me, what are you gonna do?
Come on!
My mother said I shouldn't hurt anyone!
To let you know I'm here all the time,
I'll drop a new flower
petal through the crack...
...in the window every morning.
SOLDIER-SAN
Yes!
Oh, they're distributing
Mansherry-dono's medicinal flowers!
Those are great!
They'll help people today again!
Get in a line and wait your turn.
Each person gets one.
Thank you! This medication works really well!
It heals a wound in an instant!
Here.
Thank you!
Dad! I got one for you!
I'll use it for the wound on my head.
--Wow! It healed beautifully!
--It's like magic!
I'm so grateful!
The number of Navy soldiers has
been increased as I thought!
Go faster without getting us noticed
by the Navy, Spring Sparrow!
THE NAVY CAMP
Here.
Okay.
Thank you!
So cute!
I see. We can donate our healing
properties like a blood donation.
What a wonderful ability
that the Heal-Heal Fruit grants.
Alright, you can take some from me, too.
You'll get enough to cure
10 heavily-injured people!
Oh, we can always count on you!
Then, I'll donate enough for 15 people!
What?! Then, I'll donate
enough for 20 people!
I'll donate enough for 25 people!
Alright! Enough for 100 people then!
Thank you but I don't think that's possible.
Tsuru-san.
Go ahead and roll it for today.
If it's anything other than "one,"
we'll go after Straw Hat and Law right away.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Food?!
What?
I thought you were sleeping!
The Navy might come at any time.
Let's hurry and eat.
--Y-Yeah!
--Yeah!
Alright!
Boy oh boy... And all they kept
talking about was how Rebecca-dono's
father is a prince of some country.
Right?
That's right.
WHAT'S THAT?! THAT'S A STRANGE STORY!
Vat's ghat?! Ghat's a ftranni wtory!
AND I'M SAD BECAUSE SABO'S GONE!
Ond U'm wad fegause Abo'z mon!
Ee molla ketchupom Wanji'z
froup, woo, ina buwwy!
WE GOTTA CATCH UP WITH SANJI'S
GROUP, TOO, IN A HURRY!
Get mad or cry or rush or sleep or eat!
Do one at a time!
You're so restless!
Rebecca's father is that soldier man...
You're not fully recovered!
Don't be greedy and get more sleep!
BY THUNDER! WHO MADE UP SUCH A LIE?!
Ay dunder! Oo wradap dacha eye?!
But I understand how you can't buy that.
Are you sure about it, Kin'emon?
Yes, I really heard it with my own ears!
Me, too, for certain!
I started the rumor.
What?!
The only people who know
about Rebecca's birth are...
...some people in the royal family
and some people in the Donquixote
Family who did the research.
The only thing that the whole
nation knows is about her mother.
SOLDIER-SAN
I started the rumor
before they found out I'm her father.
Why?
I have a criminal record.
I'm ill-bred as well.
I wasn't supposed to marry
a member of the royal family in the first place.
So...
...this is how it should be.
No, it's not!
Does Rebecca know that?!
She must've gotten the letter.
I wrote everything about my life truthfully.
I made her suffer for a long time.
I want her to cut her connection
to a person like me
and live happily in the light hereafter.
So that's the only way I can make it up
to her as a father.
I'm thinking about leaving this country
when you guys do.
She's still a child.
I don't want her to ruin her chance
to be happy by being caught up in the moment!
I convinced King Riku-sama, too!
He's not buying it at all.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
What now?
Commander! Oh I mean, Kyros-sama!
This is Leo!
Zoro-senpai!
Oh, Luffy-senpai! You're up! Good morning!
When there are five members of the
Straw Hats gathered together,
they're too bright to even look at!
It's like a laser beam of greatness!
If I see all the stars of the Straw
Hats someday, I'll get dissolved!
Just say what you're here for already!
Oh yeah!
There's a lot of commotion at the Navy camp!
They're gonna be here at any minute!
"Great Advisor" Vice Admiral Tsuru
and the former fleet admiral - Sengoku arrived!
Tsuru and Sengoku?!
What are such heavyweights
doing here?! Go away!
Sengoku...
Leo, what did you call me for?
Oh, the Navy is going into action now!
It's "six."
It's a mandate from heaven!
All Navy units!
Catch the Straw Hats, Trafalgar Law,
and all the criminals who've been hidden
at the Palace in one fell swoop!
Yes, sir!
Admiral-dono! Do we have
permission to enter the Palace?!
You don't need to worry about anything.
I'll take full responsibility!
Roger!
To save the Straw Hats from
being penned in by the Navy,
the cadre of tough warriors from the
Colosseum start their escape plan.
Meanwhile, Luffy dashes towards
the palace on his own and
starts some big trouble which
shakes up the whole country!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A State of Emergency! Rebecca Is Kidnapped!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!