Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to make my dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
do I have to get up to make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for small success, making excuses
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
I don't want to settle for small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air, off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
Whiffing through the air, off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit me, and even if I fall again
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Mercilessly, beat me, hit me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
Only those who get back on their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari mae wo mita mono dake ga
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal, we got to carry on the way
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
We're still far from our goal, we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without thinking of the consequences
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
and keep going without thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
After an unbelievably hard fight,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
Luffy and the others defeated
the Warlord - Donquixote Doflamingo
and brought down the Warlord -
Donquixote Doflamingo.
and were about to finally leave
the fateful island, Dressrosa...
Now, peace has returned to Dressrosa.
However, the Navy admiral
finally takes action...
Admiral Fujitora.
Why aren't you catching that pirate?
Do you think he doesn't wanna live with me?!
...to catch all the pirates on the island
in one fell swoop!
Hold on a second, citizens!
You know where Straw Hat is, don't you?
Past this point are only criminals!
Zoro-senpai!
"The deeply-wounded pirate
who saved the country."
Am I annoying to him?!
Prepare yourself, Lucy!
You and your friends should stand back!
Leave it...
"No Way Out!
Admiral Fujitora's Ruthless Pursuit!"
How do I know?! Think for yourself!
I gotta leave this country already!
--Don't let him get away!
--We won't forgive you, you damn pirates!
Should I consider him an enemy?
I only came here to ask
"Are you really okay with things this way?"!
...Up to us!
Or should I let him go
since he's a hero to this country?
Lucy!
We'll catch you no matter what!
I can't decide.
Get ships under way!
Let's chase him out to sea!
It's Straw Hat, Hajrudin!
Of course not!
I'm not okay with it!
If we follow Lucy,
One day, a Navy soldier died.
Then, do you wanna come with me?!
Fujitora won't be able to drop the rubble from the sky!
Oh yeah, we heard about your father!
Uh-huh! I do!
He was someone special to me.
A big troop of 5,600 people in total!
What?!
They say that Scarlet-sama ran away with
a prince of a far-off foreign country.
Hey, let go of me, Giant!
Luffy-senpai! Will you exchange cups of sake as father and sons...
I met him when he was a kid
and I thought of him as my son.
"The Bond Between Father and Daughter!
Kyros and Rebecca!"
Take him to the ship!
...with us seven representatives?!
But sadly, the prince died in the war and...
He was honest and
had a stronger sense of justice than anyone.
Father and sons?!
That's right! You'll be the boss and we'll be your followers!
Alright, Luffy! It's my turn!
A pirate is a pirate after all!
So he was a subordinate
that I could trust as well.
...Scarlet-sama and Rebecca...
I mean, Rebecca-sama, were left behind
No no! Please stop, Zoro-senpai!
Will you take us under the umbrella of
the Straw Hat Pirates?!
I'll never trust a pirate again!
But he lied to me just once in his lifetime.
We have our own arrangement!
I thought that you were a hero!
so they were living in this country quietly.
Arrangement?
Catch Lucy!
That's a strange rumor.
Let go of Rebecca-sama!
This is the landing unit.
Hey, you said you had a ship for us at the port
but there are probably too many ships...
Kyros-dono is Rebecca-dono's
father, isn't he?
Free her!
There is an executive of the Donquixote Family
among the dead.
You can't get away!
Look carefully!
No one wants to moor their ship in such a dangerous port!
"Sons' Cups!
The Straw Hat Fleet is Formed!"
I started the rumor.
His code name: Corazon.
I have a criminal record.
What?!
Catch Lucy!
I'm ill-bred as well.
Rosinante!
I-Is that...?!
I wasn't supposed to marry
a member of the royal family in the first place.
Straw Hat, that bastard!
They're so persistent!
Why were you there on the island?!
All our dealings with Doflamingo
came to nothing now!
So...
T-The ships are all lined up!
Look how many there are!
...this is how it should be.
Don't let him get away from Dressrosa!
But he must've had a reason.
Our target is Straw Hat!
No. it's not!
If King Riku has returned to the throne,
That's right!
The others' ships are in the fog five kilometers ahead!
Does Rebecca know that?!
Four things were lost during that incident.
we want him to pay the price for that, too!
The Barrels Pirates. My subordinate.
After we wipe out
Straw Hat Luffy and all of his allies...
She must've gotten the letter.
What now, Lucy?!
Charge!
I wrote everything about my life truthfully.
--Let's go!
--Okay!
Take this connecting bridge made by us, the Yontamaria Fleet,
and go across the sea!
We'll rampage all over Dressrosa!
The Op-Op Fruit.
And the boy who was with the Donquixote Family
at the time
It's "six."
All right! From now on,
Capture him!
Connecting bridge?!
It's a mandate from heaven!
Mm-hm! It's a bridge on the water,
that's...
let's form an allied fleet
built on our mutual hate of Straw Hat!
who was suffering from White Lead Disease!
All Navy units!
Catch the Straw Hats, Trafalgar Law,
Aim carefully!
Cut off his head at any cost!
...connected to our 50 Nitamarias by ropes!
Yeah, that's me!
and all the criminals who've been hidden
at the Palace in one fell swoop!
Oops! Oh no!
It's Sea Prism Stone!
"Men's Pride!
Luffy vs. Fujitora, Head-to-Head!"
Are you okay, Lucy?!
Now, we'll exchange cups of sake
as a parent and sons!
Lucy!
"A State of Emergency!
Rebecca Is Kidnapped!"
That's right!
It came off!
That's it! Straw Hat!
Hey! I'm still fighting!
Let go of me!
Stop it already! I beg you!
Give up the princess without a fight!
I thought so.
Hey, let go of me! I wanna fight!
Maybe, some other time!
We have something to do now!
Lucy!
Thanks.
Rosinante took a half-year break from his mission
because of you?
Thank you.
NAVY
They have to sail out to sea anyway!
Okay, it's all set on this side.
We already deployed soldiers to all ports
and took control of them-dara!
Yes, he took me to so many hospitals.
--Get on!
--Okay!
Now...
Catch him!
Then, he went for the Op-Op Fruit
There's no place left to
run in this country now!
Gum-Gum...
and he sacrificed himself to save your life?
So, go get them, but watch yourselves!
...Whip!
BIG BOSS
Yes, sir!
Alright, we'll exchange father-and-son vows
I know you're trying to
escape but I won't allow it.
Gatling!
I'll leave the rest to you.
to inaugurate Luffy-senpai as our boss
Yes, sir!
I wanna know what exactly he died for.
and us seven as his followers...
The Navy's coming! Hurry up and get ready!
Please, take the cup, Luffy-senpai.
Son of a...!
They're coming finally!
Yeah, you're right.
You don't have to tell us that.
I'm not gonna drink this!
No!
We've been prepared to escape
at the drop of a hat.
What?!
We were gonna escape together actually.
Lucy!
We were just waiting
for Luffy-dono to wake up.
He gave me back my life and spirit.
Yes, it's rather strange
that they didn't come after us until now.
I thought so.
I don't like this sake much.
I'm forever in his debt!
No, it's not about the taste!
It's about the vow!
But we have a problem. We don't have a ship.
--Whoa! What's going on?!
--Lucy?!
That's why I've single-mindedly lived
to kill Doflamingo on his behalf!
You're right!
From now on, you'll be targeted by
--That's my meat!
--I'm sorry!
Where can we get a ship to escape?!
big names because of the incident on this island!
Leo! Did you do what I asked you?!
When that happens,
But...
it doesn't matter how strong you all are,
it's gonna be a tough battle!
...I don't know if this is how he wanted me, bearing the name "D."
to live...
It's already too late, Straw Hat.
Rebecca!
I'll leave you behind the hill and lure them away!
But since you saved us,
we can help you at those times!
Sure! I did everything as you said!
"D."?!
So go off on your own!
It's dangerous! Keep out of our way!
Yes! Yes!
Like Straw Hat, I have that secret name, too.
The whole nation is trying to protect you!
But if I drink this,
We're gonna go catch pirates!
If you get caught, they'll take you back to the Palace!
I'll become the grand captain
of this grand fleet, right?
Clear the way!
Be careful!
Since you used to be the fleet admiral,
Uh-huh! But where should I go?!
--What?! They'll catch Lucy, too?!
--No...
don't you know something
about the meaning of that "D."?
That's right.
Soldier is at the small house
in the Flower Field!
If you have 5,600 subordinates in total,
The Flower Field?!
you'll finally be one of the greatest pirates!
Crest Head-san! Seems like they're
heading to the Palace as well!
You'll become the King of the Pirates eventually!
The warriors are in danger!
Okay, I got it!
Okay! Thank you for your concern, little guy!
If you wanna conquer the world,
this won't be enough though.
You gotta hurry or he'll be gone.
We've been keeping an eye on
the Navy the whole time, too!
Thank you!
You'd better stop!
Thank you for everything, Lucy!
Everything'll be alright!
That line of reasoning won't work on him.
I see!
No idea.
Luffy-senpai and everybody!
I'll lead the way!
Hey! Don't play dumb!
Wh-What is that?
Okay! But don't worry about it!
Anyway, pour this into a beer mug.
At least,
Run straight to the port in the east!
I know Rosinante had no idea.
I'll drink it.
But there are lots of Navy
soldiers in town, right?!
Like I said we're not doing this to enjoy the taste!
So that wasn't the reason he saved you.
Why, Straw Hat?!
What should we do about them?!
Don't worry!
Why aren't you happy to amass such a great military force?!
Our allies have already been standing by
at strategic points for quite a while...
Don't try to find a reason...
Doesn't matter how strong your enemy is -
...for somebody's love!
he can't compete against the force of numbers!
...to help you all to escape from this country
whenever you wake up!
I'm sure you'll need our help someday
like we needed you!
We'll clear the way for you!
I love you!
I need my space!
What?! He looks so annoyed!
We have a ship for you at the east port!
So he is one, too.
Her name is Rebecca.
We appreciate that!
That aside, aren't they preparing for a banquet in the back?
The people with the name "D."
always lead a checkered life.
Kyros, hold her in your arms.
She's your daughter!
We let Nami and the others take the Sunny
so we didn't know what to do!
He's interested in eating at a time like this?!
If I were still on active duty,
Screw you, Straw Hat!
Don't mention it!
I'm a star and more experienced than you
I would've imprisoned you
to have more time to talk but...
I shouldn't touch such an innocent thing!
but I'm saying I'll fly under your flag!
We all fought together as a team!
My hands are tainted!
I don't wanna taint her!
Let's force him to drink it!
...ironically, you're the only person who I can share
the memory of Rosinante with,
We can't let them capture our "king" now!
You don't know how strong we are,
you damn liberator!
You're like an angel, Rebecca!
even though you're a pirate.
You can't talk to him like that
if you're his follower!
I'll be watching over you!
I'll always be by your side!
If you really wanna do something in his memory,
both you and I...
--So what?!
--Cut the crap!
That admiral is serious!
Bellamy! Can you get up?
Here they come! Here they come!
Sorry...
Yeah. I can even run now.
Listen! I just wanna become the King of the Pirates!
How cute she is! How cute she is!
...should always remember him.
Okay, that's good!
I don't wanna become someone important!
You're crying again!
That's good enough.
And you live your life as you like.
Trafalgar, why didn't
you leave me to my fate?
That was supposed to be the place I died!
That's what...
Hey, what is he talking about?
Straw Hat-ya insisted you were his friend
so I carried you just in case.
...he would say.
Scarlet.
This is pretty good stuff.
I fulfilled my role.
You can die here if you want!
Use a cup! You have bad manners!
I'm fully recovered thanks to that dwarf!
Forgive me for telling a lie about your husband.
Oh! Let me try! Give me some!
How could fighting the Navy
possibly lead to me dying?!
Hey!
Oh! The rubble started moving!
I did it all so that Rebecca can live a happy life.
I'd like to have a little bit, too.
Just find some way to drop dead, idiot.
Okay, I'll have some, too!
My barrier! Break it if you can!
--You're right! It's good!
--Isn't it?!
What did you say?!
You can't even say "Thank you"!
Luffy-senpai, what did you mean by that?
That's...
It's following after
Straw Hat and the others!
Guys!
When we think we're in danger,
we'll shout for you
Hey, hey! We don't have time to think!
I need to hurry!
Let's just run, war buddies!
so come save us!
Alright, let's go!
Lucy...
I don't have to be the boss
or a great pirate, do I?
They're coming out!
Mother-sama!
Catch them all!
When you guys are in trouble, call us!
We'll come help you no matter what!
Mother-sama, I picked so many flowers!
Shoot!
Oh, is that a barrier?
Looks like this'll be real toughc
--Wow, Rebecca!
--Would you like to have one?
I'll never forget
that we fought together against Mingo!
Thank you. I would like to.
Oops! Let me handle this!
And this is from your mother to you!
Barrier!
How is that, Straw Hat?
What?! What?!
Don't stop! Shoot, shoot, shoot!
Although I can't see it,
I know it's right before your eyes.
Okay, this way, everybody!
Would you like to have one?
The dark sky is telling you
that you have nowhere to run.
Thank you!
Once you set sail,
this huge rubble cloud will fall on you.
What's going on?!
You'll be in deep trouble
if you run into Fujitora!
I'm starting to understand what he's saying
This must be...
Whatever you do, don't get separated!
All the ships will sink.
We sold all the flowers today!
and what it means to be the King of Pirates to him!
Yes, we did. Maybe people bought them
because you're so cute!
So he's on it now...
Can't you see?
--What?! What?!
--Oh, the rubble...
He'd rather be free than just important!
If by any chance you get away from me,
the Four Emperors will take action.
Get away from it!
You helped your mother!
Good girl, Rebecca!
What in the world is going on?!
The broken buildings are
rising up into the air!
What's going on?!
By taking down Joker,
you'll be targeted for execution.
--Somebody's firing at us!
--Is it the Navy?!
All the rubble in the country is...
...Flying towards the east port!
And your future from now will be hell.
It can't be! We've sewn their warships together tightly!
What in the world is...
...going on here?!
You had pity for my blindness but...
Shoot! Shoot!
What?! Luffy-senpai?!
Is it the work of a god?!
Or some mysterious birds?!
I'm gonna go to the palace!
Alright, Scarlet? Rebecca?
...I asked for this.
Father-sama!
There's only one person who's capable of this
on the island now!
I blinded myself
Let Columbus take command!
We're still busy here!
I've got something to do so just go ahead!
because I have seen so many things
that I wish I hadn't.
What?!
--Whoever it is, get rid of them!
--Yes, sir!
Luffy! We don't have much time!
Go finish your business in a hurry!
Navy Admiral Fujitora's doing this!
I know you have Monkey D. Luffy,
a rookie who's worth over 100 million, on your ship!
--We'll wait for you at the east port!
--Got it!
Let's hurry!
Hand him over to us without a fight!
Now...
Zoro-senpai, you're heading south!
But even that aspect of you is cool!
I... I couldn't protect her!
Well...
I guess nobody's using all of this.
People of Dressrosa! Get back to the land!
--Straw Hat!
--Shoot! Shoot!
I'm sorry!
It's dangerous!
I couldn't protect your mother!
It's what's left after those
hideous pirates fought!
But if we're not here, Fujitora will attack him!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Fire back!
Don't tell me he's gonna use it as a weapon?!
Although I couldn't protect your mother,
I'm gonna protect you to the end,
with my life!
A barrier that only covers a limited area
won't stand a chance against this!
Shoot! Let them sink!
Is he crazy?!
Gum-Gum...
That's not fair!
I want my mother!
What?
...Gatling!
What's going on?!
I don't like you, Soldier-san,
because you couldn't protect my mother!
We can't stay surprised forever!
We gotta go help the Usolanders!
Soldier-san!
Is he going to take down
the pirates like that?!
King Riku-sama.
Tank.
Could you go and fetch Viola and Rebecca?
Isn't this warmer?
No one will survive that!
Yes, it's much warmer!
Yes, sir.
Let's go down to the town.
I can't believe this!
The rubble's only falling where the enemy ships are!
Soldier-san is a brave man
Is their escape plan over now?!
We'll declare the King Riku Family's
return to the throne to the nation.
What's going on?!
He will always be by your side
Lucy!
Yes, right away, sir!
I've been looking forward
to this moment for so long!
Vice Admiral Bastille.
Don't go...
Let's start over...
I... haven't told you... told you anything yet!
Where should we run?!
Bastille!
What? Oh, oh, Tsuru-san! I'm sorry!
What?! Lucy?!
I don't wanna get defeated by garbage!
I couldn't believe my eyes so I...
Do you still need reinforcements?
Yes, he's being chased by the Navy soldiers.
I guess he'll leave soon.
Let me at least guide you to hell!
No!
All Navy units!
We no longer need reinforcements
in the east-dara!
Oh no! I haven't really had a
chance to say "Thank you" to him!
This is my farewell gift to you, Straw Hat.
Everybody, retreat from the east port!
Evacuate
while leading the citizens to somewhere safe!
Freedom... Freedom...
That's what Luffy-senpai wants...
Let's see if he's running out of luck.
Don't get in the way of Issho-san...
I mean, the Navy admiral!
This is it!
In that case, I admire you even more, Luffy-senpai!
Rebecca...
Let's put it to the test.
With all my might!
I want to live with you one day,
in the same house.
What the hell is that?!
From now on, on behalf of Issho-san,
So do I!
Hey, Bartolomeo! Make the oath!
I'm taking command of all units!
He doesn't have to drink out of the parent's cup.
Continue to go after the criminals
who were hidden at the Palace-dara!
Give us back Rebecca, Lucy!
Weren't you a hero, Lucy?!
He's right.
Yes, sir!
Soldier-san!
How's it going with Straw Hat and the others
who ran away from the hill in Carta-dara?!
Hey, guys!
You can do whatever you want - so can we.
Let me teach you how to fight.
Is that...
Wherever you are, we're all at risk!
Go to the port and set sail!
This country has done a lot of harm to her!
Hey! This way, everybody!
My mother said I shouldn't hurt anyone!
You can't take away our freedom, either!
Don't further her misery!
Okay! Trafal...
Gagh! Law!
I'm gonna teach you how to not get hurt!
Oh yeah?
We've been waiting for you and Straw Hat!
Where were you?!
Hold on a second, citizens!
Sniper King-senpai!
Past this point are only criminals!
Stand up, Rebecca!
Even when you fall down, you look cool!
Everybody, run to the ship!
Prepare to sail out!
You have to become stronger!
Stop right there! I'll put an end to...
Yeah!
Is it really safe to run
through the town like this?!
--Hurry up! Prepare to sail out!
--Run! Run!
Outta our way, Navy!
Don't worry! Let's hurry up!
We don't need your help!
Because you were a member of the royal family,
you've been running around,
I don't mind running to the ship but...
Luffy-senpai!
Allow me to make a brief oath!
We'll shake off the pirates ourselves!
We're chasing the pirates now!
I don't think he'll let us get away!
getting insulted for a decade.
It seems that they're
heading to the east port!
That's why, this time...
Okay. Put me through to the east port!
An oath?
I want you to have your chance at happiness
as a member of the royal family.
Here it goes, Luffy-senpai.
Oh?
Yes, this is the Navy lookout
unit at the east port! Over!
It's not coming down!
We now become
Straw Hat Luffy-senpai's followers
I can't stay here, either.
and we'll be his shield or pike in all weather!
All serene! Over!
There! There he is!
Luffy!
To repay him for what he did this time,
we seven will...
All serene?!
Luffy-senpai! Hurry up!
How can you take this so lightly?!
The pirates are heading there!
...drink out of these Sons' Cups of our own volition,
devoting our lives and souls!
--Straw Hat!
--Everybody's here! Run to the ship!
Rebecca!
Oh no, it's so peaceful out here.
Luffy-senpai!
Watch out for Fujitora right there!
We don't need any more backup! Over!
Sons' Cups?!
Don't lie!
Over!
You idiot...
Give me your name and Navy Code.
Oh, about the letter?
That guy is...!
You are quite brash. But...
I wasn't lying!
Huh?
I really was...
Oh, ummm...
...a worthless guy who fought all the time
in the past.
You wanna fight?
Father-sama! The people of the town are...
Dammit-dara!
What an unpleasant chore this is.
Hm? What's wrong?
The east port has been seized!
Send reinforcements to the east!
And whatever the reason was,
They're running to the port!
There are thousands of them!
I really killed people.
Yes, sir!
What?!
So...
What is it?! It's noisy back there!
Go ahead! Straight to the port!
It's the people of Dressrosa!
What do they want?!
Luffy-senpai! Hurry up!
Dodge him somehow!
Thank you!
I'm not a daughter of some prince!
What the...
Don't waste my time telling me
about your gratitude!
Hey, Giant! Let go of me!
Dodge?!
I don't know anyone like that!
Hey, you old gambler man!
Do you remember me?!
Just give it up already.
Debt after debt!
We have too much to repay!
I'm not gonna fight anymore!
I was expecting you, Straw Hat!
It doesn't matter if he killed hundreds of people
or how tainted his hands are!
No! Is it a roadblock ahead?
I'm gonna punch you!
Gum-Gum...
I only have one father!
What?!
...Elephant Gun!
I'm Kyros' daughter!
What are you guys doing?!
--Go!
--Thanks!
L-L-L-L-L-L-Luffy-senpai!
Now we're formally...
What are they doing?
Hurry up and prepare for the banquet!
He's one of the Navy HQ's greatest military powers -
a Navy admiral!
It's all ready!
Don't lie!
Celebrate the formation of the Straw Hat Fleet with over 5,600 crew in total!
Until the day you are filled with happiness,
The criminals who were
supposed to be at the Palace
Yeah!
showed up in the ruins of the eastern town!
They just do whatever they like!
I will always be by your side!
What?!
Then, is the Palace empty?!
Sons' Cups?! What the hell is that?!
Prepare yourself, Lucy!
Big Boss Straw Hat! Thank you in advance!
--Don't let him get away!
--We won't forgive you, you damn pirates!
Gum-Gum...
What?!
Save Rebecca-sama!
Stay by my side like you promised, Soldier-san!
...Elephant Gun!
Hey! I didn't drink that, okay?!
Lucy!
Oh? What the...?!
Although it's empty for some reason!
Come on! Damn! Come on!
Lucy!
Man, that was good!
Yeah, that's okay!
We'll catch you no matter what!
My arm got stuck!
Nothing has changed for you.
Get ships under way!
Let's chase him out to sea!
--Straw Hat!
--Why's he here?!
I-Is it okay with you that I'm your father?!
We just decided to go ahead
and swear our loyalty to you.
Luffy-senpai!
He's a Navy admiral!
What are you doing?!
And when something happens to you,
Yeah! Let's live together!
we'll be there risking our lives of our own will.
My head's spinning!
Are they...
You'll lose nothing by having us, right?
"Take him down someday" isn't
good enough anymore!
Dad!
Yeah... Yeah...
Now, why don't you remember
our names and faces...
Even if he's a Navy admiral,
why should I run?!
Lucy!
Honey!
You can't get away, you jerk!
I would've done that until two years ago
but not anymore!
There is not a trace of
resentment in their voice.
Look.
Luffy! The main dish is Fighting Fish Steak!
Everyone focus on escaping!
Wait, Lucy! Give us back Rebecca-sama!
Looks good!
Hey, that's dirty! Don't climb on food!
As we are now, we can't beat these guys!
Hey, everybody!
I saw Rebecca-sama at the house on the top of the hill...
Hey, stop crying already.
No, I can't bear to get up...
I'm so moved...
...with Kyros-sama!
Even a Navy admiral or an Emperor,
Oh yeah? But everyone knows that.
I gotta beat them all! Otherwise...
Leo, we're gonna leave the port
and start the banquet.
What?!
We're in front of the Palace!
What are you guys gonna do?
If Kyros-sama gives in, they'll stay together
Rebecca will never come back here,
Father-sama.
We're gonna attend the banquet!
I can't become the King of the Pirates!
S-Straw Hat is...
because they're actually father and daughter.
And we'll get home by Yellow Cubs afterwards.
Viola... I thought so.
Don't worry about us!
Gum-Gum...
Yes. That's what she wants.
Are we sailing out?
All adults have known that
ever since 16 years ago.
...Fireworks!
Okay! An order from the boss!
Hoist the sails!
Well, that's kind of true.
I'm sorry, Viola-san!
But could you take my place and become a princess?!
We've known of the family of three,
Okay, Luffy!
Since it has come to this, just fight it out!
including Scarlet-sama,
living happily on the top of the hill.
I'm not your boss and I didn't give you an order!
What?! Usopp-senpai, even you?!
We've known about the true identity of the fairies, too!
We've all been watching them.
I'm sorry, Viola!
But could you take my place and become a princess?!
Are you sure?! He's a Navy admiral!
HAPPO
Big Sis-sama?!
I see!
This is the second time in my life
that someone asked me such an odd favor.
Anyway, we gotta run faster!
Rebecca!
I'll go all out! Old man!
We must help the ones who
saved this country escape!
Rebecca! Where are you?!
I see. Rebecca is really like her mother.
Fine, I'll do all I can to capture you, too!
If we follow Lucy,
Fujitora won't be able to drop the rubble from the sky!
Vice Admiral Bastille! I have a report!
Why is Straw Hat in front
of the Palace-dara?!
Prepare yourself!
Luffy isn't here yet?!
The rubble's finally raining down, huh?
Trafalgar Law's not here, either!
I'm gonna punch you!
Wait, Lucy! Give us back, Rebecca-sama!
--Don't let him get away at any cost!
--Yes, sir!
THE RUINS OF THE FOREST TOWN - CARTA
THE EAST PORT
Have Straw Hat and the others been wiped out?!
What are both of our bosses doing?!
Gum-Gum...
No, it's all missing the target!
Wait, you bastard!
There are some enemies that can't be held back
even by us...
...Hawk Bullet!
What do you mean-dara?!
Alright, everybody! Go to the east port!
Why does he have to have a serious fight
at times like this?!
Gum-Gum...
It's our turn to help the heroes
who saved our country!
That's...
--Are you crazy, Straw Hat?!
--Should we go help?!
...Giant Pistol!
Go, go! Keep running!
I'm gonna tread on you!
Now, go! Run and run!
Wh-What was that?!
Rubble, then sunny skies.
Fujitora!
Gum-Gum...
Rebecca!
Quite unusual weather was observed
off the coast of Dressrosa this day.
The unwanted one's here!
...Hawk Axe!
Luffy-senpai, hurry up!
Hey! Rebecca!
I'm totally on board with what Luffy said
but why is he fighting in such a strange way?
Somebody's calling me!
I actually had no right to chase you all.
What are you doing, Luffy?!
Lucy?!
"Fools rush in where angels fear to tread"-dara!
I shouldn't say this out loud but...
Lucy! I'm up here!
Lucy!
I've already sent reinforcements
to the east port where Straw Hat's heading!
...thank you very much for
cleaning up the Government's mess!
I'm gonna punch you so many times!
No, Rebecca-sama!
You cannot talk to a pirate!
Wow! Can't believe it!
There are a whole bunch of people!
The warships on the sea
and Issho-san will pincer them!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Gatling!
There she is!
What?!
And we'll catch the Straw Hats and the other criminals
in one fell swoop-dara!
Rebecca!!
I heard you!
Lucy!!
I'm gonna kick you!
Alright, guys!
Lucy!
You're foolishly honest Straw Hat Luffy.
Straw Hat! What did you come here for?!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What should we do?!
I'm gonna kick and punch you!
We only have one choice!
In the battle against the Mingo Family,
I guess everyone wants to help you.
we...
What'd'ya do?!
...won!
Luffy!
Zoro-senpai!
Yeah!
Oh yeah, old man, you're a Devil Fruit eater!
Lucy...
What kind of person are you, really?
Please get back, Rebecca-sama!
You and your friends should stand back!
Leave it...
Straw Hat?
We did it!
What color is your hair?
What is the shape of your eyes?
Lucy!
Great! I really wanted
to say "Thank you" so...
...Up to us!
Good job, guys!
A head-butt!
Fraland!
Shut up!
--Zoroland, thank you!
--No problem!
I'm not here for that!
What do you look like?
Are you really okay with things this way?!
Hey! What happened to the reinforcements
for the east port-dara?!
Crest Head!
What?
I'm gonna kick you!
About Soldier?!
I wish I hadn't blinded myself.
Yes, sir!
Well, most of the units became incapacitatedc
Luffy-senpai!
You'll never see him again!
Oh, my mistake! I meant "punch"!
I want to see your face.
What do you mean-dara?!
Lucy... I got a letter from him.
Sorry, old man!
Honey!
The bullets and gunpowder are missing
from their rifles!
Don't worry.
I bet you look kind.
--Let's make a toast!
--Okay!
And all their other weapons like
swords, pistols, axes, spears, and knives...
It didn't even graze my body.
Cheers!
...went missing, too!
Soldier-san is trying his best
to distance himself from me.
They must've been stolen...
And at the port,
Here I go, old man!
He's trying to make me a stranger.
We made it! It's Dressrosa!
the warships are stuck together
as if they got sewn to one another
Now, what should I do
with the weapon that I raised?
Oh, please! You're not even my parent!
so they can't sail out!
Smells good!
I'm gonna punch you!
How could the iron be sewn together?!
It's embarrassing.
Cut the string! Cut it!
I'm gonna kick and punch you!
Why? Because I said terrible things to him?
But we don't have a knife!
A lot of...
All soldiers have retreated!
But citizens are running to the port!
I want it! The Flare-Flare Fruit!
...punching!
Meanwhile, the soldiers who suddenly collapsed
are still paralyzed...
Hmmm... It's so mysterious but...
You have no chance to beat Doflamingo!
Push you!
What's Issho-san doing-dara?!
Head!
What are you doing, you idiots?!
...I like this statue! It's so manly!
Because you're...
Tread on you!
How long will he keep the rubble in the sky?!
...just a one-legged toy!
I'm sorry!
Now, look at that!
Are you gonna let the Straw Hats and the other criminals walk away?!
Oh, it's huge!
Do something!
W-We'll do our best!
Is it really okay to get this much healing properties today,
Mouji?
Do you think he doesn't wanna live with me?!
You guys are the last people I want,
to have Ace's power!
The donors will be paralyzed
if we take too much out of them...
Am I annoying to him?!
It's okay! We got permission!
How do I know?! Think for yourself!
Even if she's the former king's granddaughter,
it had nothing to do with her!
My body gets lighter and heavier...
What's going on?!
From Kyros-sama.
I gotta leave this country already!
Just do as I say, Princess!
Isn't the ship great?!
THE YONTAMARIA
THE FLAGSHIP OF THE YONTAMARIA FLEET
Franky!
I only came here to ask
"Are you really okay with things this way?"!
You're free to go all out!
Okay! Then, I won't hesitate!
We still have so many heavily-injured people!
Straw Hat!
It's not yours!
I told you! Luffy-senpai, run!
We'll be there as soon as possible!
Okay! Hurry up and get on board!
This is a state of emergency!
Of course not!
I'll show you my ship later!
You'll be surprised!
I'm not okay with it!
Don't cry yet!
Then, do you wanna come with me?!
I know you're in the middle of it
but we gotta go...
I won't let the soldier die!
You have to be safe, too!
I'm not gonna...
Uh-huh! I do!
It's massive!
It'll be finished soon!
...run anymore!
But instead,
--What?!
--Rebecca-sama!
THROB
Right.
Seems like you're strong enough to say so.
I promise I'll kick Doflamingo's ass for you!
Then, I'll wait!
Straw Hat!
I have four Giant mercenary friends!
Rebecca! Straw Hat! Wait a minute!
According to the citizens,
I like that spirit but...
all these strange occurrences are
the work of fairies.
So survive! Okay?!
I wanna pull together all the Giant tribes with them
eventually
Viola-san!
Can I ask you a favor?!
I'm gonna punch you!
and we'll revive the Giant Pirates
that once terrorized the world!
You fool! Cut the fairy crap-dara!
Let's go!
What exactly have you been doing
all this time?!
I-I-I-I'm sorry!
To kick your ass!
The Giant Pirates!
Those were the glory days of Master Dorry and Brogy!
Announcing "Kick you" or "Punch you"...
Hang on tight!
B-Barrier!
Are you taking pity on me?!
Okay!
Oh yeah? You'll be a tough enemy to fight!
He's escaping!
Will your barrier work?!
I'm a Navy HQ admiral!
Everyone says I'm like a monster!
Then, I guess we'll see you
again someday somewhere!
There's no reason for me to accept such a fight!
W-We have a problem!
If it were breakable,
it wouldn't be called a barrier!
I wanna go to Elbaph!
Tell King Riku-sama!
Keep holding on
until Luffy-senpai and Trafalgar come!
Doflamingo!!
Our Yontamaria Fleet numbers 56 ships!
I know we can really help you out!
I don't want anybody to go easy on me
after all these years!
Yeah!
Tra-guy!!
Does it bother you
that a blind man is on the battlefield?!
King Riku-sama!
Help us?
Luffyland! We got permission from Chief Tonta!
Let us join, too!
What's wrong?!
Fourth...
Are they fighting?!
Rebecca-sama has been kidnapped by a pirate!
...Gear!
If you wanted to make me mad, you succeeded!
Join?
We won't lose in a fair fight
What?!
I'll chop off your head before you know it!
NAVY BRAND RICE CRACKERS
A pirate from where?! What was he like?!
Want some rice crackers?
but we can't say we're champions
without fighting pirates!
I promise!
Shut up!
No thanks. Just start talking.
So Ideo and I joined hands
and decided to get out to sea!
Is he one of the competitors
from the Colosseum?!
I just can't attack a blind man like you
without saying a word!
Sabo!
You ate Ace's Fruit, didn't you?
S... Stra... Straw...
Hey, we're with you, too!
Don't forget about us, bro!
Straw Hat Luffy!
This fool's gonna let
me be on board his ship.
Because I kind of like you!
A boy with White Lead Disease?!
Rebecca-sama has been abducted
from the Palace!
I'm doing you a favor
so you'd better call me "Captain"!
It makes me feel like I'm suffocating!
So there was a survivor
from the White Town?!
And you, too!
Don't forget that I'm more experienced than you!
--Straw Hat Luffy did it!
--No kidding!
He hates everything in this world.
Even if I go along with you,
I'll be the most popular one!
King Kong...
--It's probably for ransom!
--What?!
Feels like I'm watching my older brother
when he was a kid.
What are you guys talking about?
Do whatever you want!
...Gun!
I can't believe Lucy did it! How audacious!
I feel sorry for him but there's no way to
cure White Lead Disease.
Well, the fact is we totally hit it off
while we were staying at the Palace for two days!
Don't get involved too much
or you'll give yourself away.
--Even so,
--Clank.
I still...
Yes, I know.
I'll explain!
For your information, we decided the order by lot.
...like you!
I'm here to stop my brother.
What's so funny?! You jerk!
What are you saying, Gyats?!
I'm gonna kick you!
Seems like they managed to set sail.
Doflamingo is a violent man.
SULEIMAN A CLASS-A WAR CRIMINAL
FROM THE DIAS NAVAL BATTLE
See?! This is what happens when you
believe in pirates and let them stay!
First, the Beautiful Pirates, 75 members!
That sympathy of yours!
WHITE HORSE CAVENDISH - THE PIRATE NOBLE
I'm glad. Lucy...
I'm not gonna let him go to Dressrosa.
Catch Straw Hat as quickly as possible
and rescue Princess Rebecca!
What is it good for?!
THE BEAUTIFUL PIRATES
The representative is its
captain, White Horse Cavendish!
Do you think we'll see them again?
I'm gonna punch you so many times!
One day, a Navy soldier died.
I'm disappointed in you!
This isn't sensible at all!
He was someone special to me.
MAN-EATING BARTOLOMEO
THE CAPTAIN OF THE BARTO CLUB
Next, the Barto Club, 56 members!
I'm gonna punch you...
Isn't this warmer?
There he is!
The captain is Man-Eating Bartolomeo!
Special sniper unit!
Take careful aim and shoot him!
...with all my might!
I met him when he was a kid
and I thought of him as my son.
Yes!
When men fight,
It's much warmer!
DON SAI - THE 13TH LEADER
OF THE HAPPOSUI ARMY
He was honest and
had a stronger sense of justice than anyone.
The Happosui Army, about 1000 members!
they should fight in a way
that fits their position.
THE HAPPOSUI ARMY
So he was a subordinate that I could trust as well.
The 13th leader is...
You can't...
...Don Sai!
Oh? You're crying again!
...show pity or say what
you like so honestly!
But he lied to me just once in his lifetime.
I-I'm not crying! Don't be ridiculous!
--Not bad.
--Honey! You look great!
Do you have a deal regarding
the Op-Op Fruit?
What?
I just said "Honey"...
BLUE GILLY - A LONGLEG JIAOKUNGDO MARTIAL ARTIST
IDEO - A LONGARM XXX RANK BOXER
My brother knew it.
The XXX Gym Fighting Alliance, four members!
Shut up!
What?! But it's top secret!
BLUE GILLY - A LONGLEG JIAOKUNGDO MARTIAL ARTIST
IDEO - A LONGARM XXX RANK BOXER
ABDULLAH AND JEET - FORMER BOUNTY HUNTERS
Wait!
I don't care at all!
The Navy soldiers suddenly...!
THE XXX GYM FIGHTING ALLIANCE
Cora-san must be talking to...
The representative is
"Destruction Cannon" Ideo!
Soldiers collapsed?!
Was it the Color of the Supreme King?!
You're such a fool!
That'll be it for Doflamingo!
We'll ambush at Swallow Island
No, seems like they're conscious...
I'm fighting as befits my position
even though I don't want to!
LEO - FROM THE DWARF TRIBE (TONTATTAS)
The Tontatta's Tonta Corps, 200 members!
Whatever it was, they're gonna
escape from the east port-dara!
and catch the Donquixote Family
in one fell swoop!
Gravity Blade!
THE TONTA CORPS
Hey, come here!
Send warships, too!
All units, head for Carta in the east-dara!
You stay away from the island!
The leader is Leo the Warrior!
I was planning on it.
Stop it!
Oh no! Get away!
Yes, sir!
Having enough?
Raging Tiger!
HAJRUDIN - A PIRATE MERCENARY
This is the landing unit.
Oh, thanks!
Just five members now!
The future Giant Pirates!
There is an executive of the Donquixote Family
among the dead.
Dammit!
Press and hold for more than three seconds.
THE GIANT PIRATES
His code name: Corazon.
The captain is Hajrudin!
JUSTICE OVER ALL
I've sent a picture of him.
Could you confirm?
And I'm...
ORLUMBUS - THE SURMOUNTER
Keep running! We'll be there soon!
...the commodore of the Yontamaria
Fleet, 4,300 members!
Rosinante!
Cheers!
THE YONTAMARIA FLEET
Why were you there on the island?!
Say, Robiland,
we can see you again, can't we?
The "Adventuring Pioneer" - Orlumbus!
Of course! Along with everyone else!
Stay with me. The rescue team
will get here any minute.
Yeah!
He betrayed me.
--Good for you!
--Oh, when did you get in there?
Y-Yes...
H-Hey...
Want some rice crackers?
A big troop of 5,600 people in total!
BIG BOSS
No thanks...
But he must've had a reason.
After the hard fight in Dressrosa,
Luffy-senpai!
Will you exchange cups of sake as father and sons...
the very unconventional Sons' Cups
were exchanged in secrecy.
Four things were lost during that incident.
...with us seven representatives?!
That's him.
The Barrels Pirates. My subordinate.
Father and sons?!
By a quirk of fate or by chance,
That's right! You'll be the boss
and we'll be your followers!
Oh, there he is!
these seven extraordinary men gathered together
The Op-Op Fruit.
Will you take us under the umbrella of
the Straw Hat Pirates?!
Stop!
and insisted on becoming Straw Hat Luffy's followers.
And the boy who was with the Donquixote Family
at the time
They will develop themselves individually hereafter
who was suffering from White Lead Disease!
and will eventually cause a major incident
that will go down in history, but...
Catch Lucy!
I'd like to see you try!
...that's a story no one could have known at this time.
Yeah, that's me!
Luffy and the tough Colosseum
warriors now overcame
Admiral Fujitora, with his overwhelming strength,
Kyros wishes for his daughter's
happiness as he leaves
The Straw Hats run desperately to get out of
Dressrosa has finally won peace.
for a journey from which
he will never come home.
stands in the way of the Straw Hats and the others who are trying to escape!
Dressrosa under the dark sky!
the deadly battle against
Doflamingo together!
Meanwhile, while being conveyed to the great prison, Impel Down,
Meanwhile, Rebecca shakes off
her pursuers with Luffy's help
But the enraged Admiral Fujitora doesn't
give up the chase! In a hopeless situation
When the seven formidable
and extraordinary men,
But Luffy fights against him with all his power
all of them troublemakers,
combine their hearts
and his firm resolve to become the King of the Pirates!
Doflamingo makes a chilly statement!
and rushes to see her father!
where they have nowhere to run,
and raise their sake cups
to their big boss Luffy,
Who will rule all the seas next?!
Will the father-and-daughter
of fate who overcame
When the two men's inflexible determinations collide
the finishing attack
against Luffy and the others finally rains down!
an unbreakable bond that will
go down in history is built!
Now - the curtain rises on an all new stormy era!
numerous hardships be able
to see each other again?!
with each other, their all-out special attacks crackle!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sons' Cups! Straw Hat Fleet is Formed!"
"No Way Out! Admiral Fujitora's Ruthless Pursuit!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Men's Pride! Luffy vs. Fujitora, Head-to-Head!"
"The Numerous Rivals Struggle Amongst Themselves!
"The Bond Between Father and
Daughter! Kyros and Rebecca!"
The Raging Monsters of the New World"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!