Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and brought down the Warlord -
Donquixote Doflamingo.
Now, peace has returned to Dressrosa.
Admiral Fujitora.
Why aren't you catching that pirate?
You know where Straw Hat is, don't you?
"The deeply-wounded pirate
who saved the country."
Should I consider him an enemy?
Or should I let him go
since he's a hero to this country?
I can't decide.
Oh yeah, we heard about your father!
What?!
They say that Scarlet-sama ran away with
a prince of a far-off foreign country.
But sadly, the prince died in the war and...
...Scarlet-sama and Rebecca...
I mean, Rebecca-sama, were left behind
so they were living in this country quietly.
That's a strange rumor.
Kyros-dono is Rebecca-dono's
father, isn't he?
I started the rumor.
I have a criminal record.
I'm ill-bred as well.
I wasn't supposed to marry
a member of the royal family in the first place.
So...
...this is how it should be.
No. it's not!
Does Rebecca know that?!
She must've gotten the letter.
I wrote everything about my life truthfully.
It's "six."
It's a mandate from heaven!
All Navy units!
Catch the Straw Hats, Trafalgar Law,
and all the criminals who've been hidden
at the Palace in one fell swoop!
"A State of Emergency!
Rebecca Is Kidnapped!"
NAVY
They have to sail out to sea anyway!
We already deployed soldiers to all ports
and took control of them-dara!
There's no place left to
run in this country now!
So, go get them, but watch yourselves!
Yes, sir!
I'll leave the rest to you.
The Navy's coming! Hurry up and get ready!
They're coming finally!
You don't have to tell us that.
We've been prepared to escape
at the drop of a hat.
We were just waiting
for Luffy-dono to wake up.
Yes, it's rather strange
that they didn't come after us until now.
But we have a problem. We don't have a ship.
You're right!
Where can we get a ship to escape?!
Leo! Did you do what I asked you?!
Sure! I did everything as you said!
It's dangerous! Keep out of our way!
We're gonna go catch pirates!
Clear the way!
--What?! They'll catch Lucy, too?!
--No...
Crest Head-san! Seems like they're
heading to the Palace as well!
The warriors are in danger!
Okay! Thank you for your concern, little guy!
We've been keeping an eye on
the Navy the whole time, too!
Everything'll be alright!
I see!
Luffy-senpai and everybody!
I'll lead the way!
Run straight to the port in the east!
But there are lots of Navy
soldiers in town, right?!
What should we do about them?!
Don't worry!
Our allies have already been standing by
at strategic points for quite a while...
...to help you all to escape from this country
whenever you wake up!
We'll clear the way for you!
We have a ship for you at the east port!
We appreciate that!
We let Nami and the others take the Sunny
so we didn't know what to do!
Don't mention it!
We all fought together as a team!
We can't let them capture our "king" now!
Bellamy! Can you get up?
Yeah. I can even run now.
Okay, that's good!
Trafalgar, why didn't
you leave me to my fate?
That was supposed to be the place I died!
Straw Hat-ya insisted you were his friend
so I carried you just in case.
You can die here if you want!
I'm fully recovered thanks to that dwarf!
How could fighting the Navy
possibly lead to me dying?!
Just find some way to drop dead, idiot.
What did you say?!
You can't even say "Thank you"!
Hey, hey! We don't have time to think!
Let's just run, war buddies!
Alright, let's go!
They're coming out!
Catch them all!
Shoot!
Oops! Let me handle this!
Barrier!
Don't stop! Shoot, shoot, shoot!
Okay, this way, everybody!
You'll be in deep trouble
if you run into Fujitora!
Whatever you do, don't get separated!
What?! Luffy-senpai?!
I've got something to do so just go ahead!
What?!
Luffy! We don't have much time!
Go finish your business in a hurry!
--We'll wait for you at the east port!
--Got it!
Let's hurry!
Zoro-senpai, you're heading south!
But even that aspect of you is cool!
--Straw Hat!
--Shoot! Shoot!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
...Gatling!
King Riku-sama.
Tank.
Could you go and fetch Viola and Rebecca?
Yes, sir.
Let's go down to the town.
We'll declare the King Riku Family's
return to the throne to the nation.
Yes, right away, sir!
I've been looking forward
to this moment for so long!
Let's start over...
What?! Lucy?!
Yes, he's being chased by the Navy soldiers.
I guess he'll leave soon.
Oh no! I haven't really had a
chance to say "Thank you" to him!
Let's see if he's running out of luck.
Let's put it to the test.
With all my might!
From now on, on behalf of Issho-san,
I'm taking command of all units!
Continue to go after the criminals
who were hidden at the Palace-dara!
Yes, sir!
How's it going with Straw Hat and the others
who ran away from the hill in Carta-dara?!
Hey! This way, everybody!
Sniper King-senpai!
Even when you fall down, you look cool!
Is it really safe to run
through the town like this?!
Don't worry! Let's hurry up!
We're chasing the pirates now!
It seems that they're
heading to the east port!
Okay. Put me through to the east port!
Yes, this is the Navy lookout
unit at the east port! Over!
All serene! Over!
All serene?!
How can you take this so lightly?!
The pirates are heading there!
Oh no, it's so peaceful out here.
We don't need any more backup! Over!
Over!
You idiot...
Give me your name and Navy Code.
Huh?
Oh, ummm...
Dammit-dara!
The east port has been seized!
Send reinforcements to the east!
Yes, sir!
Go ahead! Straight to the port!
Thank you!
Don't waste my time telling me
about your gratitude!
Debt after debt!
We have too much to repay!
No! Is it a roadblock ahead?
--Go!
--Thanks!
The criminals who were
supposed to be at the Palace
showed up in the ruins of the eastern town!
What?!
Then, is the Palace empty?!
Oh? What the...?!
Come on! Damn! Come on!
My arm got stuck!
--Straw Hat!
--Why's he here?!
My head's spinning!
We're in front of the Palace!
S-Straw Hat is...
Gum-Gum...
...Fireworks!
Rebecca!
Rebecca! Where are you?!
Why is Straw Hat in front
of the Palace-dara?!
--Don't let him get away at any cost!
--Yes, sir!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Pistol!
Wh-What was that?!
Rebecca!
Hey! Rebecca!
Somebody's calling me!
Lucy?!
Lucy! I'm up here!
Lucy!
No, Rebecca-sama!
You cannot talk to a pirate!
There she is!
What?!
Rebecca!!
Lucy!!
Lucy!
Straw Hat! What did you come here for?!
Lucy...
Please get back, Rebecca-sama!
Straw Hat?
Lucy!
Great! I really wanted
to say "Thank you" so...
Shut up!
I'm not here for that!
Are you really okay with things this way?!
What?
About Soldier?!
You'll never see him again!
Lucy... I got a letter from him.
Soldier-san is trying his best
to distance himself from me.
He's trying to make me a stranger.
Oh, please! You're not even my parent!
Why? Because I said terrible things to him?
You have no chance to beat Doflamingo!
Because you're...
...just a one-legged toy!
Do you think he doesn't wanna live with me?!
Am I annoying to him?!
How do I know?! Think for yourself!
I gotta leave this country already!
I only came here to ask
"Are you really okay with things this way?"!
Of course not!
I'm not okay with it!
Then, do you wanna come with me?!
Uh-huh! I do!
--What?!
--Rebecca-sama!
Rebecca! Straw Hat! Wait a minute!
Viola-san!
Can I ask you a favor?!
Let's go!
Hang on tight!
Okay!
He's escaping!
W-We have a problem!
Tell King Riku-sama!
King Riku-sama!
What's wrong?!
Rebecca-sama has been kidnapped by a pirate!
What?!
A pirate from where?! What was he like?!
Is he one of the competitors
from the Colosseum?!
S... Stra... Straw...
Straw Hat Luffy!
Rebecca-sama has been abducted
from the Palace!
--Straw Hat Luffy did it!
--No kidding!
--It's probably for ransom!
--What?!
I can't believe Lucy did it! How audacious!
--Even so,
--Clank.
I still...
...like you!
What are you saying, Gyats?!
See?! This is what happens when you
believe in pirates and let them stay!
Catch Straw Hat as quickly as possible
and rescue Princess Rebecca!
There he is!
Special sniper unit!
Take careful aim and shoot him!
What?
The Navy soldiers suddenly...!
Soldiers collapsed?!
Was it the Color of the Supreme King?!
No, seems like they're conscious...
Whatever it was, they're gonna
escape from the east port-dara!
Send warships, too!
All units, head for Carta in the east-dara!
Yes, sir!
Keep running! We'll be there soon!
Stay with me. The rescue team
will get here any minute.
Y-Yes...
Want some rice crackers?
No thanks...
That's him.
Oh, there he is!
Stop!
Catch Lucy!
I'd like to see you try!
Kyros wishes for his daughter's
happiness as he leaves
for a journey from which
he will never come home.
Meanwhile, Rebecca shakes off
her pursuers with Luffy's help
and rushes to see her father!
Will the father-and-daughter
of fate who overcame
numerous hardships be able
to see each other again?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Bond Between Father and
Daughter! Kyros and Rebecca!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!