Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and brought down the Warlord -
Donquixote Doflamingo.
Now, peace has returned to Dressrosa.
However, the Navy admiral
finally takes action...
...to catch all the pirates on the island
in one fell swoop!
Zoro-senpai!
You and your friends should stand back!
Leave it...
...Up to us!
One day, a Navy soldier died.
He was someone special to me.
I met him when he was a kid
and I thought of him as my son.
He was honest and
had a stronger sense of justice than anyone.
So he was a subordinate
that I could trust as well.
But he lied to me just once in his lifetime.
This is the landing unit.
There is an executive of the Donquixote Family
among the dead.
His code name: Corazon.
Rosinante!
Why were you there on the island?!
But he must've had a reason.
Four things were lost during that incident.
The Barrels Pirates. My subordinate.
The Op-Op Fruit.
And the boy who was with the Donquixote Family
at the time
who was suffering from White Lead Disease!
Yeah, that's me!
"Men's Pride!
Luffy vs. Fujitora, Head-to-Head!"
I thought so.
Rosinante took a half-year break from his mission
because of you?
Yes, he took me to so many hospitals.
Then, he went for the Op-Op Fruit
and he sacrificed himself to save your life?
I wanna know what exactly he died for.
Yeah, you're right.
We were gonna escape together actually.
He gave me back my life and spirit.
I'm forever in his debt!
That's why I've single-mindedly lived
to kill Doflamingo on his behalf!
But...
...I don't know if this is how he wanted me, bearing the name "D."
to live...
"D."?!
Like Straw Hat, I have that secret name, too.
Since you used to be the fleet admiral,
don't you know something
about the meaning of that "D."?
No idea.
Hey! Don't play dumb!
At least,
I know Rosinante had no idea.
So that wasn't the reason he saved you.
Don't try to find a reason...
...for somebody's love!
I love you!
So he is one, too.
The people with the name "D."
always lead a checkered life.
If I were still on active duty,
I would've imprisoned you
to have more time to talk but...
...ironically, you're the only person who I can share
the memory of Rosinante with,
even though you're a pirate.
If you really wanna do something in his memory,
both you and I...
...should always remember him.
That's good enough.
And you live your life as you like.
That's what...
...he would say.
My barrier! Break it if you can!
Oh, is that a barrier?
Looks like this'll be real toughc
What?! What?!
What's going on?!
This must be...
So he's on it now...
--What?! What?!
--Oh, the rubble...
Get away from it!
What in the world is going on?!
The broken buildings are
rising up into the air!
All the rubble in the country is...
...Flying towards the east port!
What in the world is...
...going on here?!
Is it the work of a god?!
Or some mysterious birds?!
There's only one person who's capable of this
on the island now!
Navy Admiral Fujitora's doing this!
Well...
I guess nobody's using all of this.
It's what's left after those
hideous pirates fought!
Don't tell me he's gonna use it as a weapon?!
A barrier that only covers a limited area
won't stand a chance against this!
Is he crazy?!
That's not fair!
What's going on?!
We can't stay surprised forever!
We gotta go help the Usolanders!
Is he going to take down
the pirates like that?!
No one will survive that!
I can't believe this!
Is their escape plan over now?!
Lucy!
Vice Admiral Bastille.
Bastille!
What? Oh, oh, Tsuru-san! I'm sorry!
I couldn't believe my eyes so I...
Do you still need reinforcements?
No!
All Navy units!
We no longer need reinforcements
in the east-dara!
Everybody, retreat from the east port!
Evacuate
while leading the citizens to somewhere safe!
Don't get in the way of Issho-san...
I mean, the Navy admiral!
What the hell is that?!
Hey, guys!
Wherever you are, we're all at risk!
Go to the port and set sail!
Okay! Trafal...
Gagh! Law!
We've been waiting for you and Straw Hat!
Where were you?!
Everybody, run to the ship!
Prepare to sail out!
Yeah!
--Hurry up! Prepare to sail out!
--Run! Run!
I don't mind running to the ship but...
I don't think he'll let us get away!
There! There he is!
Luffy!
Luffy-senpai! Hurry up!
--Straw Hat!
--Everybody's here! Run to the ship!
Luffy-senpai!
Watch out for Fujitora right there!
That guy is...!
You are quite brash. But...
You wanna fight?
What an unpleasant chore this is.
Luffy-senpai! Hurry up!
Dodge him somehow!
Dodge?!
Hey, you old gambler man!
Do you remember me?!
I was expecting you, Straw Hat!
I'm gonna punch you!
Gum-Gum...
What?!
...Elephant Gun!
L-L-L-L-L-L-Luffy-senpai!
He's one of the Navy HQ's greatest military powers -
a Navy admiral!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
Luffy-senpai!
He's a Navy admiral!
What are you doing?!
"Take him down someday" isn't
good enough anymore!
Even if he's a Navy admiral,
why should I run?!
I would've done that until two years ago
but not anymore!
Everyone focus on escaping!
As we are now, we can't beat these guys!
Even a Navy admiral or an Emperor,
I gotta beat them all! Otherwise...
I can't become the King of the Pirates!
Well, that's kind of true.
Okay, Luffy!
Since it has come to this, just fight it out!
What?! Usopp-senpai, even you?!
Are you sure?! He's a Navy admiral!
I'll go all out! Old man!
Fine, I'll do all I can to capture you, too!
Prepare yourself!
I'm gonna punch you!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Bullet!
Why does he have to have a serious fight
at times like this?!
--Are you crazy, Straw Hat?!
--Should we go help?!
I'm gonna tread on you!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Axe!
I'm totally on board with what Luffy said
but why is he fighting in such a strange way?
What are you doing, Luffy?!
I'm gonna punch you so many times!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Gatling!
I'm gonna kick you!
I'm gonna kick and punch you!
What'd'ya do?!
Luffy!
Oh yeah, old man, you're a Devil Fruit eater!
A head-butt!
I'm gonna kick you!
Oh, my mistake! I meant "punch"!
Sorry, old man!
Don't worry.
It didn't even graze my body.
Here I go, old man!
I'm gonna punch you!
I'm gonna kick and punch you!
A lot of...
...punching!
Push you!
Head!
Tread on you!
My body gets lighter and heavier...
What's going on?!
Straw Hat!
I told you! Luffy-senpai, run!
I'm not gonna...
...run anymore!
Right.
Seems like you're strong enough to say so.
I like that spirit but...
I'm gonna punch you!
What exactly have you been doing
all this time?!
Announcing "Kick you" or "Punch you"...
Are you taking pity on me?!
I'm a Navy HQ admiral!
Everyone says I'm like a monster!
I don't want anybody to go easy on me
after all these years!
Does it bother you
that a blind man is on the battlefield?!
If you wanted to make me mad, you succeeded!
I'll chop off your head before you know it!
Shut up!
I just can't attack a blind man like you
without saying a word!
Because I kind of like you!
What's so funny?! You jerk!
I'm gonna kick you!
That sympathy of yours!
What is it good for?!
I'm gonna punch you so many times!
I'm disappointed in you!
This isn't sensible at all!
I'm gonna punch you...
...with all my might!
When men fight,
they should fight in a way
that fits their position.
You can't...
...show pity or say what
you like so honestly!
Shut up!
I don't care at all!
You're such a fool!
I'm fighting as befits my position
even though I don't want to!
Gravity Blade!
Oh no! Get away!
Raging Tiger!
The Straw Hats run desperately to get out of
Dressrosa under the dark sky!
But the enraged Admiral Fujitora doesn't
give up the chase! In a hopeless situation
where they have nowhere to run,
the finishing attack
against Luffy and the others finally rains down!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"No Way Out! Admiral Fujitora's Ruthless Pursuit!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!