Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and brought down the Warlord -
Donquixote Doflamingo.
Now, peace has returned to Dressrosa.
However, the Navy admiral
finally takes action...
...to catch all the pirates on the island
in one fell swoop!
"No Way Out!
Admiral Fujitora's Ruthless Pursuit!"
It's Straw Hat, Hajrudin!
Hey, let go of me, Giant!
Take him to the ship!
Alright, Luffy! It's my turn!
No no! Please stop, Zoro-senpai!
We have our own arrangement!
Arrangement?
Hey, you said you had a ship for us at the port
but there are probably too many ships...
Look carefully!
No one wants to moor their ship in such a dangerous port!
What?!
I-Is that...?!
T-The ships are all lined up!
Look how many there are!
That's right!
The others' ships are in the fog five kilometers ahead!
Take this connecting bridge made by us, the Yontamaria Fleet,
and go across the sea!
Connecting bridge?!
Mm-hm! It's a bridge on the water,
that's...
...connected to our 50 Nitamarias by ropes!
Hey! I'm still fighting!
Let go of me!
Stop it already! I beg you!
Hey, let go of me! I wanna fight!
Maybe, some other time!
We have something to do now!
I know you're trying to
escape but I won't allow it.
It's already too late, Straw Hat.
Wh-What is that?
That admiral is serious!
Here they come! Here they come!
Oh! The rubble started moving!
That's...
It's following after
Straw Hat and the others!
Lucy...
How is that, Straw Hat?
Although I can't see it,
I know it's right before your eyes.
The dark sky is telling you
that you have nowhere to run.
Once you set sail,
this huge rubble cloud will fall on you.
All the ships will sink.
Can't you see?
If by any chance you get away from me,
the Four Emperors will take action.
By taking down Joker,
you'll be targeted for execution.
And your future from now will be hell.
You had pity for my blindness but...
...I asked for this.
I blinded myself
because I have seen so many things
that I wish I hadn't.
Now...
Where should we run?!
I don't wanna get defeated by garbage!
Let me at least guide you to hell!
This is it!
Give us back Rebecca, Lucy!
Weren't you a hero, Lucy?!
Is that...
This country has done a lot of harm to her!
Don't further her misery!
Hold on a second, citizens!
Past this point are only criminals!
Stop right there! I'll put an end to...
Outta our way, Navy!
We don't need your help!
We'll shake off the pirates ourselves!
Oh?
It's not coming down!
Father-sama! The people of the town are...
Hm? What's wrong?
They're running to the port!
There are thousands of them!
What?!
What is it?! It's noisy back there!
It's the people of Dressrosa!
What do they want?!
What the...
Hey, Giant! Let go of me!
Just give it up already.
I'm not gonna fight anymore!
What are they doing?
Prepare yourself, Lucy!
--Don't let him get away!
--We won't forgive you, you damn pirates!
Save Rebecca-sama!
Lucy!
We'll catch you no matter what!
Get ships under way!
Let's chase him out to sea!
Are they...
Lucy!
You can't get away, you jerk!
There is not a trace of
resentment in their voice.
Wait, Lucy! Give us back Rebecca-sama!
Hey, everybody!
I saw Rebecca-sama at the house on the top of the hill...
...with Kyros-sama!
Oh yeah? But everyone knows that.
What?!
If Kyros-sama gives in, they'll stay together
because they're actually father and daughter.
All adults have known that
ever since 16 years ago.
We've known of the family of three,
including Scarlet-sama,
living happily on the top of the hill.
We've known about the true identity of the fairies, too!
We've all been watching them.
I see!
Anyway, we gotta run faster!
We must help the ones who
saved this country escape!
If we follow Lucy,
Fujitora won't be able to drop the rubble from the sky!
Wait, Lucy! Give us back, Rebecca-sama!
Wait, you bastard!
Alright, everybody! Go to the east port!
It's our turn to help the heroes
who saved our country!
Go, go! Keep running!
Now, go! Run and run!
Wow! Can't believe it!
There are a whole bunch of people!
You're foolishly honest Straw Hat Luffy.
I guess everyone wants to help you.
What kind of person are you, really?
What color is your hair?
What is the shape of your eyes?
What do you look like?
I wish I hadn't blinded myself.
I want to see your face.
I bet you look kind.
Now, what should I do
with the weapon that I raised?
It's embarrassing.
All soldiers have retreated!
But citizens are running to the port!
What's Issho-san doing-dara?!
How long will he keep the rubble in the sky?!
Now, look at that!
Oh, it's huge!
Isn't the ship great?!
THE YONTAMARIA
THE FLAGSHIP OF THE YONTAMARIA FLEET
It's not yours!
Okay! Hurry up and get on board!
This is a state of emergency!
I'll show you my ship later!
You'll be surprised!
It's massive!
Straw Hat!
I have four Giant mercenary friends!
I wanna pull together all the Giant tribes with them
eventually
and we'll revive the Giant Pirates
that once terrorized the world!
The Giant Pirates!
Those were the glory days of Master Dorry and Brogy!
Oh yeah? You'll be a tough enemy to fight!
Then, I guess we'll see you
again someday somewhere!
I wanna go to Elbaph!
Our Yontamaria Fleet numbers 56 ships!
I know we can really help you out!
Help us?
Luffyland! We got permission from Chief Tonta!
Let us join, too!
Join?
We won't lose in a fair fight
but we can't say we're champions
without fighting pirates!
So Ideo and I joined hands
and decided to get out to sea!
Hey, we're with you, too!
Don't forget about us, bro!
This fool's gonna let
me be on board his ship.
I'm doing you a favor
so you'd better call me "Captain"!
And you, too!
Don't forget that I'm more experienced than you!
Even if I go along with you,
I'll be the most popular one!
What are you guys talking about?
Do whatever you want!
Well, the fact is we totally hit it off
while we were staying at the Palace for two days!
I'll explain!
For your information, we decided the order by lot.
SULEIMAN A CLASS-A WAR CRIMINAL
FROM THE DIAS NAVAL BATTLE
First, the Beautiful Pirates, 75 members!
WHITE HORSE CAVENDISH - THE PIRATE NOBLE
THE BEAUTIFUL PIRATES
The representative is its
captain, White Horse Cavendish!
MAN-EATING BARTOLOMEO
THE CAPTAIN OF THE BARTO CLUB
Next, the Barto Club, 56 members!
The captain is Man-Eating Bartolomeo!
DON SAI - THE 13TH LEADER
OF THE HAPPOSUI ARMY
The Happosui Army, about 1000 members!
THE HAPPOSUI ARMY
The 13th leader is...
...Don Sai!
--Not bad.
--Honey! You look great!
I just said "Honey"...
BLUE GILLY - A LONGLEG JIAOKUNGDO MARTIAL ARTIST
IDEO - A LONGARM XXX RANK BOXER
The XXX Gym Fighting Alliance, four members!
BLUE GILLY - A LONGLEG JIAOKUNGDO MARTIAL ARTIST
IDEO - A LONGARM XXX RANK BOXER
ABDULLAH AND JEET - FORMER BOUNTY HUNTERS
THE XXX GYM FIGHTING ALLIANCE
The representative is
"Destruction Cannon" Ideo!
LEO - FROM THE DWARF TRIBE (TONTATTAS)
The Tontatta's Tonta Corps, 200 members!
THE TONTA CORPS
The leader is Leo the Warrior!
HAJRUDIN - A PIRATE MERCENARY
Just five members now!
The future Giant Pirates!
THE GIANT PIRATES
The captain is Hajrudin!
And I'm...
ORLUMBUS - THE SURMOUNTER
...the commodore of the Yontamaria
Fleet, 4,300 members!
THE YONTAMARIA FLEET
The "Adventuring Pioneer" - Orlumbus!
H-Hey...
A big troop of 5,600 people in total!
Luffy-senpai!
Will you exchange cups of sake as father and sons...
...with us seven representatives?!
Father and sons?!
That's right! You'll be the boss
and we'll be your followers!
Will you take us under the umbrella of
the Straw Hat Pirates?!
Luffy and the tough Colosseum
warriors now overcame
the deadly battle against
Doflamingo together!
When the seven formidable
and extraordinary men,
all of them troublemakers,
combine their hearts
and raise their sake cups
to their big boss Luffy,
an unbreakable bond that will
go down in history is built!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sons' Cups! Straw Hat Fleet is Formed!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!