Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air, off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal, we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After an unbelievably hard fight,
Luffy and the others defeated
the Warlord - Donquixote Doflamingo
and were about to finally leave
the fateful island, Dressrosa...
Hold on a second, citizens!
Past this point are only criminals!
Prepare yourself, Lucy!
--Don't let him get away!
--We won't forgive you, you damn pirates!
Lucy!
We'll catch you no matter what!
Get ships under way!
Let's chase him out to sea!
If we follow Lucy,
Fujitora won't be able to drop the rubble from the sky!
A big troop of 5,600 people in total!
Luffy-senpai! Will you exchange cups of sake as father and sons...
...with us seven representatives?!
Father and sons?!
That's right! You'll be the boss and we'll be your followers!
Will you take us under the umbrella of
the Straw Hat Pirates?!
"Sons' Cups!
The Straw Hat Fleet is Formed!"
Straw Hat, that bastard!
All our dealings with Doflamingo
came to nothing now!
Don't let him get away from Dressrosa!
If King Riku has returned to the throne,
we want him to pay the price for that, too!
After we wipe out
Straw Hat Luffy and all of his allies...
We'll rampage all over Dressrosa!
All right! From now on,
let's form an allied fleet
built on our mutual hate of Straw Hat!
Cut off his head at any cost!
Now, we'll exchange cups of sake
as a parent and sons!
That's right!
Thanks.
Thank you.
Okay, it's all set on this side.
Now...
BIG BOSS
Alright, we'll exchange father-and-son vows
to inaugurate Luffy-senpai as our boss
and us seven as his followers...
Please, take the cup, Luffy-senpai.
I'm not gonna drink this!
What?!
I thought so.
I don't like this sake much.
No, it's not about the taste!
It's about the vow!
From now on, you'll be targeted by
big names because of the incident on this island!
When that happens,
it doesn't matter how strong you all are,
it's gonna be a tough battle!
But since you saved us,
we can help you at those times!
Yes! Yes!
But if I drink this,
I'll become the grand captain
of this grand fleet, right?
That's right.
If you have 5,600 subordinates in total,
you'll finally be one of the greatest pirates!
You'll become the King of the Pirates eventually!
If you wanna conquer the world,
this won't be enough though.
You'd better stop!
That line of reasoning won't work on him.
Anyway, pour this into a beer mug.
I'll drink it.
Like I said we're not doing this to enjoy the taste!
Why, Straw Hat?!
Why aren't you happy to amass such a great military force?!
Doesn't matter how strong your enemy is -
he can't compete against the force of numbers!
I'm sure you'll need our help someday
like we needed you!
I need my space!
What?! He looks so annoyed!
That aside, aren't they preparing for a banquet in the back?
He's interested in eating at a time like this?!
Screw you, Straw Hat!
I'm a star and more experienced than you
but I'm saying I'll fly under your flag!
Let's force him to drink it!
You don't know how strong we are,
you damn liberator!
You can't talk to him like that
if you're his follower!
--So what?!
--Cut the crap!
Sorry...
Listen! I just wanna become the King of the Pirates!
I don't wanna become someone important!
Hey, what is he talking about?
This is pretty good stuff.
Use a cup! You have bad manners!
Oh! Let me try! Give me some!
Hey!
I'd like to have a little bit, too.
Okay, I'll have some, too!
--You're right! It's good!
--Isn't it?!
Luffy-senpai, what did you mean by that?
Guys!
When we think we're in danger,
we'll shout for you
so come save us!
I don't have to be the boss
or a great pirate, do I?
When you guys are in trouble, call us!
We'll come help you no matter what!
I'll never forget
that we fought together against Mingo!
I'm starting to understand what he's saying
and what it means to be the King of Pirates to him!
He'd rather be free than just important!
What's going on?!
--Somebody's firing at us!
--Is it the Navy?!
It can't be! We've sewn their warships together tightly!
Shoot! Shoot!
Let Columbus take command!
We're still busy here!
--Whoever it is, get rid of them!
--Yes, sir!
I know you have Monkey D. Luffy,
a rookie who's worth over 100 million, on your ship!
Hand him over to us without a fight!
People of Dressrosa! Get back to the land!
It's dangerous!
But if we're not here, Fujitora will attack him!
Fire back!
Shoot! Let them sink!
What?
The rubble's only falling where the enemy ships are!
What's going on?!
This is my farewell gift to you, Straw Hat.
Freedom... Freedom...
That's what Luffy-senpai wants...
In that case, I admire you even more, Luffy-senpai!
So do I!
Hey, Bartolomeo! Make the oath!
He doesn't have to drink out of the parent's cup.
He's right.
You can do whatever you want - so can we.
You can't take away our freedom, either!
Oh yeah?
Luffy-senpai!
Allow me to make a brief oath!
An oath?
Here it goes, Luffy-senpai.
We now become
Straw Hat Luffy-senpai's followers
and we'll be his shield or pike in all weather!
To repay him for what he did this time,
we seven will...
...drink out of these Sons' Cups of our own volition,
devoting our lives and souls!
Sons' Cups?!
What are you guys doing?!
Now we're formally...
Hurry up and prepare for the banquet!
It's all ready!
Celebrate the formation of the Straw Hat Fleet with over 5,600 crew in total!
Yeah!
They just do whatever they like!
Sons' Cups?! What the hell is that?!
Big Boss Straw Hat! Thank you in advance!
What?!
Hey! I didn't drink that, okay?!
Although it's empty for some reason!
Man, that was good!
Yeah, that's okay!
Nothing has changed for you.
We just decided to go ahead
and swear our loyalty to you.
And when something happens to you,
we'll be there risking our lives of our own will.
You'll lose nothing by having us, right?
Now, why don't you remember
our names and faces...
Honey!
Look.
Luffy! The main dish is Fighting Fish Steak!
Looks good!
Hey, that's dirty! Don't climb on food!
Hey, stop crying already.
No, I can't bear to get up...
I'm so moved...
Leo, we're gonna leave the port
and start the banquet.
What are you guys gonna do?
We're gonna attend the banquet!
And we'll get home by Yellow Cubs afterwards.
Don't worry about us!
Are we sailing out?
Okay! An order from the boss!
Hoist the sails!
I'm not your boss and I didn't give you an order!
HAPPO
Vice Admiral Bastille! I have a report!
The rubble's finally raining down, huh?
Have Straw Hat and the others been wiped out?!
No, it's all missing the target!
What do you mean-dara?!
Rubble, then sunny skies.
Quite unusual weather was observed
off the coast of Dressrosa this day.
I actually had no right to chase you all.
I shouldn't say this out loud but...
...thank you very much for
cleaning up the Government's mess!
I heard you!
Alright, guys!
In the battle against the Mingo Family,
we...
...won!
Yeah!
We did it!
Good job, guys!
Fraland!
--Zoroland, thank you!
--No problem!
Crest Head!
Luffy-senpai!
Honey!
--Let's make a toast!
--Okay!
Cheers!
We made it! It's Dressrosa!
Smells good!
I want it! The Flare-Flare Fruit!
Hmmm... It's so mysterious but...
...I like this statue! It's so manly!
You guys are the last people I want,
to have Ace's power!
Even if she's the former king's granddaughter,
it had nothing to do with her!
Franky!
You're free to go all out!
We'll be there as soon as possible!
Don't cry yet!
I won't let the soldier die!
You have to be safe, too!
But instead,
I promise I'll kick Doflamingo's ass for you!
So survive! Okay?!
To kick your ass!
There's no reason for me to accept such a fight!
Doflamingo!!
Tra-guy!!
Fourth...
...Gear!
I promise!
Sabo!
You ate Ace's Fruit, didn't you?
It makes me feel like I'm suffocating!
King Kong...
...Gun!
Seems like they managed to set sail.
I'm glad. Lucy...
Do you think we'll see them again?
Isn't this warmer?
Yes!
It's much warmer!
Oh? You're crying again!
I-I'm not crying! Don't be ridiculous!
Wait!
Hey, come here!
Stop it!
Having enough?
Oh, thanks!
Dammit!
Press and hold for more than three seconds.
Cheers!
Say, Robiland,
we can see you again, can't we?
Of course! Along with everyone else!
Yeah!
--Good for you!
--Oh, when did you get in there?
BIG BOSS
After the hard fight in Dressrosa,
the very unconventional Sons' Cups
were exchanged in secrecy.
By a quirk of fate or by chance,
these seven extraordinary men gathered together
and insisted on becoming Straw Hat Luffy's followers.
They will develop themselves individually hereafter
and will eventually cause a major incident
that will go down in history, but...
...that's a story no one could have known at this time.
Dressrosa has finally won peace.
Meanwhile, while being conveyed to the great prison, Impel Down,
Doflamingo makes a chilly statement!
Who will rule all the seas next?!
Now - the curtain rises on an all new stormy era!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Numerous Rivals Struggle Amongst Themselves!
The Raging Monsters of the New World"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!