kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
Yes, we can! You can!
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
kono shunkan
This moment
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
Yes, we can!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others left Dressrosa
After a hard fight, Luffy and the others
Looks delicious!
and are heading for their
next destination, Zou,
defeated the Warlord - Donquixote Doflamingo
Okay, everybody!
to meet up with the other half of their crew.
You can have as many second
helpings as you like!
and left the fateful island, Dressrosa.
Show us that you can eat as much as they say!
However, they were attacked by
Battle Boats out of the blue
However, they were attacked by Battle Boats
out of the blue
However, they were attacked by
Battle Boats out of the blue
and Luffy was taken to an unknown island,
Silver Mine along with Bartolomeo.
Okay, thanks! It's really really good!
Here it goes, Luffy-senpai.
and Luffy was taken to an unknown island,
Silver Mine along with Bartolomeo.
The members of the Straw Hats are enjoying
our homemade dishes so much...
We now become
Straw Hat Luffy-senpai's followers
Straw Hat, you'll join them.
This is where your voyage ends.
His life was put in danger by Bill who is
the leader of the Silver Pirate Alliance,
and we'll be his shield
or pike in all weather!
I'm so happy to be alive!
There, their lives are put in danger
Oh? I don't like the look of those clouds.
I ate the Smelt-Smelt Fruit
and became a blast-furnace human.
and then, fell into an underground mineshaft
where he learned the truth about Bill.
by Bill who is the leader of
the Silver Pirate Alliance!
To repay him for what he did
this time, we seven will...
My body is an ultra-hot blast furnace.
It's hail!
No way!
He wouldn't do such a thing to his friends!
They're big! Watch out!
...drink out of these Sons'
Cups of our own volition,
What?!
I can smelt ore and produce
all kinds of things.
devoting our lives and souls!
--What?!
--It punched a hole in the deck!
Big Sis!
I know it's hard to believe.
I'll turn you into a nice silver statue
befitting of a man with a bounty of 500 million!
But that's the truth.
Luffy-senpai and everybody! Get inside now!
What're you talking about?! We'll help you!
Hey! Did Bill really tell you to...
Their lives were put in danger by Bill
Which way should we turn?!
...get rid of me as well?!
Who's your navigator?! Give us directions!
who is the leader of the
Silver Pirate Alliance,
Now we're formally...
That's right!
Hurry up and prepare for the banquet!
Oh, we don't have a navigator
since we were a land-based gang originally.
and while fighting one of his underlings,
"An Underground Maze!
Luffy vs. the Tram Human!"
Desire, who was also Bartolomeo's
childhood friend,
I see.
It's all ready!
Gum-Gum...
they fell into an underground mineshaft
where they learned the truth about Bill.
What?! You're in the New World, you know?!
Alright, guys!
Hello, Grandma? It's me, Gambia!
...Jet Bazooka!
Shambles!
In the battle against the Mingo Family,
They defeated Bill's right-hand man, Peseta,
with help from Zoro and the others
The thing is, huge hail
just started falling on us.
we...
and managed to return above ground
only to confront Bill again.
Whenever we're in trouble,
we call Grandma in our hometown.
...won!
Yeah!
AVELON EXPRESS
I see! So she knows about the sea!
What did you say?!
TERMINAL STATION
Luffy-senpai!
Don't tell me you were the one
who sank our boats that day...
Hey, I got it!
I fought in collaboration with Luffy-senpai
for the first time!
We have some chewing gum
stuck to the deck, right?
Don't tell me he fell down below!
That's right!
"The Numerous Rivals Struggle Amongst Themselves!
The Raging Monsters of the New World"
Yeah, and we didn't know what to do!
I can't believe this is happening!
No senpai, no life!
It was me!
Wrap the hailstone in cloth
and cool the gum to peel it off!
I sank them and saved you.
Alright!
If Straw Hat and the others make
it up here, we'll be in trouble!
He left his precious straw hat behind...
It came off surprisingly easily!
Hey! Hey!
Didn't I perform as good as a stage actor?
We don't need that sort of wisdom now!
--Could it be...?!
--Let me out!
But...
See! You got hit!
Then, let's just...
Let's eat more!
And guess what?
Apply sugar to his lump, she says!
--I didn't see that coming!
--I'm glad!
The simple minded idiot that you are
Yeah!
Enough with her wisdom!
...bury them all.
got wrapped up in my dream like a loyal dog.
Oh no! This ship's gonna sink!
Nami, help us!
Ouch...
H-Here you go!
Oh, you're alive, Desire.
Thanks!
We had so many ships to choose from
but we got on board the wrong one!
That's what this is all about.
He doesn't care at all.
"The Sword Technique Heats Up!
Law and Zoro Finally Appear!"
I guess we gotta deal with this ourselves!
My Battle Boat!
If only we had the Sunny's equipment!
Super!
Is this the railroad?
--Thank you!
--Hey!
You bastard...
It's so lively.
Yes, that one goes highest.
They were using it to carry ore out.
I need him... Let me take Straw Hat!
Why aren't you using your barrier?!
What are you talking about?!
That's unforgivable...
What?! Well, Grandma says,
I won't let you!
But we don't know what lies ahead.
And I'm not gonna forgive you...
...for your act of violence not just against me
but also against the Straw Hats!
"You'll regret it if you defy nature!"
How dare you...
So we gotta leave the rest to chance,
right, Luffy-senpai?!
If you're so scared, get back on land!
Are they for real?!
...take advantage of our compassion!
We fell pretty far.
All right, let's go!
How can we get out of here?
I have no choice!
I'll smash all the hailstones up!
Okay!
Hey, what are those rails?
Oh, I'm so thrilled!
Guys! We have the Straw Hats
who don't even fear god
By responding to his commands,
Your tears are pathetic.
We can't see Dressrosa anymore.
and that's like getting help
from a thousand people!
I feel like I'm a member of the Straw Hats!
Our appreciation rains down
like hail and snow pellets!
How have you guys survived until now?!
You achieved your goal by taking
down Doflamingo, didn't you?
"A Desperate Situation!
Luffy Fights a Battle in Extreme Heat!"
Gum-Gum...
What's wrong?! You guys aren't up for it?
Somebody, come in!
...Gatling!
Well, we do wanna get out of here but...
It won't connect!
It's just a short time
until we arrive at Zou,
What are you gonna do next?
If Bill finds us,
we'll be taken back here again.
How can we go back up?
but I get to travel
with that awesome Luffy-senpai...
I don't know this place!
In addition, we'll receive
terrible punishment.
Huh?! I thought this is the
headquarters of your group!
Pathetic! Oh, so pathetic!
What are you guys afraid of?!
I'm too happy and I could be punished for it!
Leave me alone.
Luffy-senpai has the power
of a hundred people!
Boy, pirates are such hopeless people.
The railcar will soon arrive.
I'm so happy!
No, a thousand or 10 thousand or 100 million!
You do something too, you fools!
No, no...
That's enough!
You guys really believe in immature things
like dreams and stuff.
But no matter how strong he is,
he is no match for Bill.
DRESSROSA
Please wait where you are.
You're little better than kids.
THE ROYAL PALACE
I can't find any list they
used for trafficking.
I don't wanna have molten metal poured on me
and be turned into a statue!
But you were very handy!
But it was all clearly stolen by somebody...
The Silver Pirate Alliance!
On top of that, besides Bill,
they have a scary executive called Peseta.
Just by dangling a dream in front of you,
I'm a tram human who ate the Roll-Roll Fruit!
I thought so.
you scum became enthralled
and worked hard for me!
All the weapons and explosives
that were left behind
AVELON EXPRESS
Pffft! Do as you like, then!
Avelon Express is on its way!
Wait!
were stolen after the incident.
What?! Is he one of your allies?!
Without knowing all the treasures
and the people with bounties you brought to me...
There was quite a lot.
I've never heard of him!
I've made up my mind!
CIPHER POL "AIGIS" ZERO
All the passengers who learn about
the underground mineshafts...
It must've been some organization.
I'm gonna get out of here with
Straw Hat to go settle things!
...would be used for me to live
the most luxurious life in the world,
The Navy was panicking about it, too.
...have to be gotten rid of!
Go settle things?
Was it the Revolutionary Army?
Do you guys wanna spend
the rest of your lives here?
you guys were working your butts off all day!
Yeah. Who else would do that?
Come back already.
Interesting!
Even if you stay here,
you can't do anything but wait to be killed!
By the way,
what brought you here now, Desire?
Luffy-senpai, watch out!
Clank.
They're so annoying.
"The Silver Fortress!
Luffy and Barto's Great Adventure!"
You're right, boss!
If so, isn't it better to take your chances
and try to get off of the island?!
You said you wanted to "settle things."
Annoying like you...
You're not thinking you
can defeat me, are you?
Luffy-senpai! Are you alright?!
Show some guts!
Wow! You're way out of line!
What?! I'm so underestimated!
What's with that jerk?!
Why did he try to harm me too?!
If you say you're still a pirate!
All right. Bring it on!
I'm gonna turn the railcar around!
Do you have to pee?
Hey, what's wrong? Huh?! Bring it on!
Where are you going next, Straw Hat?
I'm going!
I'm coming too.
Me too!
Oh, I'm so happy to have a pee
with my hero, Luffy-senpai...
Oh no! It's coming again!
Huh?! I can't hear you!
In that case, I'm gonna
smelt you first as you wish!
Crest Head! Let's get away from here!
This is the land of tragedy.
--Okay! Help me, Desire!
--What?!
Oh, I'm hungry again.
We're gonna go along with him!
What?!
Speeding up! Speeding up!
Oh, do you want me
to fix you a midnight snack?
Dark strings were cast one after another.
Okay! Let's go!
Yeah!
Running near the tracks is dangerous.
Counting the number of tragedies
that fell upon them,
It's meat!
Please do not rush - maintain a walking pace!
they hold back their tears
and play the music...
Oh, you're gonna fall!
No way!
Good job making it this far.
--Is it hailing again?
--I don't know.
Straw Hat!
Oh yeah!
Next stop: Rain of Bombs! Rain of Bombs!
The music of handclapping
that rings out loud.
You're kind of irritating.
--Wait! He's...
--Desire!
Luffy-senpai, neither of us can swim.
Can't you use your barrier?!
Leave it to Luffy-senpai.
Because of this sticky thing,
I can't make the gesture!
We did it, Big Sis!
Olé!
Please be careful!
Yeah, we landed the unwanted one too though.
Luffy-senpai!
What?!
Incredible.
You actually lured Straw Hat with meat!
Such pure eyes...
They make me wanna puke!
Gum-Gum...
Just like you said, Desire!
...Balloon!
I'll chop you up!
Incredible! Incredible!
Incredible!!
What's that?
Ball walking on the rails
is strictly prohibited.
--Luffy!
--Captain!
The curtain was drawn during the long, sad,
There they are!
"Pirate Hunter." "God."
nameless show without any applause
"Cyborg." "Demon Child."
and then the words of truth reach them.
I'm landing on Luffy-senpai's
Gum-Gum Balloon...
I see no track ahead!
Everybody! Let's do this...
Damn!
Oh no!
It's a blissful moment!
...as we planned!
Okay!
The king has returned
and with peace ahead, all is serene.
Why're you sleeping?!
Watch out! The overpass is collapsing!
I have a preposition for you...
--Well done as always!
--He's so strong...
I'm a former leader of the Sweet
Pirates from the East Blue - Desire!
Um, thank you for the introduction.
I'm Chief Tonta, Gancho!
Let me handle it! Barrier!
Yoroshiku (Thanks) !
NIGHT FURNACE SISTER CRIMSON
(YO)      (RO)      (SHI)        (KU)
Cut it out! Give us back Luffy!
You can't bring me down.
Standing next to me is my daughter...
Special Attack: Green Star! Sea Devil!
So this is how strong a person
with a bounty of 500 million is!
I'm Mansherry!
Here comes a plant!
Well done, Crest Head!
He's so persistent!
Formation: Madeleine!
Thanks! I'm honored I could
be of some help to you!
Bill!
--There's a fork ahead!
--What?!
Okay!
So cute!
Is that Desire?!
Which way should we go?!
Why's she with Straw Hat and the other one?!
We don't have time to think! Go right!
Listen to me!
You guys were all fooled by Bill...
You sure?
--What?!
--Let me do it!
Crest Head! Go right!
It's really...
This time, it's a machine gun!
Desire betrayed us!
Oh, I got it!
It's really incredible!
Incredible! Incredible!
Screw you!
Weapon's Left!
She went over to Straw Hat's side
All right!
No!
Peseta! Are these Bill's orders again?!
and is looking to destroy
the Silver Pirate Alliance!
Big Sis!
Do you want us to make this, Leo-kun?
The next stop is hell!
Of course, they are!
She already took down Avelon and Peseta!
--Are you okay?!
--Thank you very much.
That's right! I'm counting on you!
This train is bound for hell!
Are you gonna bury these guys alive as well
after driving them so hard?!
Tsk! I couldn't get them.
What?!
That means we've been attacked
by the Straw Hats because...
What?!
Trying to spare just them is...
What the...?!
The World Conference "Reverie" is this year.
Shoot! Shoot!
Stop, Straw Hat!
Desire masterminded it.
...incredibly troublesome! So I'll just...
You guys have to stop me!
What are you talking about?!
Guys, don't be fooled!
It's coming up soon.
I can't move!
Looks like each country has
already started preparing.
...take care of them along with you guys!
It's no use, Desire.
We can't!
Is this birdlime?!
I saw our friends who were abandoned by Bill,
That makes me angry!
Father-sama!
It's sticky!
Barrier Crush!
Rebecca said she'll come to
cook for us this afternoon!
Do it!
working as slaves under the ground here!
Oh yeah?! What about Kyros?!
What?
They're incredibly pathetic! Do it, do it!
Whoa-whoa! You guys are my friends
He'll come, too, of course.
Good, good. The whole family
will gather together...
and you know I wouldn't
do such a thing to you!
Stop! That's enough.
It sure is a dangerous barrier as they say.
Grandma! What should we
do at a time like this?!
Take down the traitor!
Kill Straw Hat and the other one!
...after all these years!
No!
I'm the leader of this assault!
Let's go back to Silver Mine.
It's not just dangerous!
--How dare he say that without shame...
--Well, I saw that coming.
Visitors to this kingdom will have
something to be amazed about.
Barrier-bility!
Stairs!
Go!
Avelon, how are Straw Hat
and the others doing?
They're so naive.
They fell down to the lowest layer.
Be sure to take them out.
--Can I have a ham?
--Oh, hello!
They'll break before me like my shield...
Roger that.
Rebecca and Mansherry.
This is Silver Mine,
a solitary island near Dressrosa.
Straw Hat! They're just being fooled!
Don't treat them roughly!
"They" are blending in with the town
SILVER MINE
and living side-by-side with humans.
A giant silver fortress dominates
the center of the island
Oh! The stairs made of the barrier!
Bill-sama!
Clank.
Hey, hey. We haven't even
built houses to live in yet.
Go ahead and climb them, Luffy-senpai!
and its sparkle makes even
the surrounding waters shine.
Bill-sama!
Why're you looking the other way?!
No, no, this must be our first priority!
--Big Sis fell...
--Along with Straw Hat and the other!
All right! Crest Head, I'll go first!
Please take care!
The visitors will be amazed
by these adorable Dwarves.
How was it?!
Oh, I mean, I'll come with you!
We got a fine haul again!
Don't worry!
I sent the other unit to search for Desire.
This is awesome! I'm having so much fun!
There you are, Smelt-Smelt!
This is a kingdom of love
and passion and fairies...
If I'm correct, there is
a limit on the size of
What a relief!
No way!
You're right. The statues must come first!
the barrier that you can produce at once.
Please save Big Sis.
They should!
Count on me! Desire is one of my...
Dressrosa.
...dear friends.
Luffy-senpai!
--Now, let's go back to everyone else.
--Okay!
You jerk!
H-He's something else...
When we finish transporting the prisoner,
Are you guys okay?!
I used it up on the staircase!
THE NAVY'S FLEET
I'll go on a journey.
Barely...
A journey?
I thought I was gonna die this time...
If it's for Luffy-senpai, I'll do it!
You're heavy.
Without Straw Hat and Law's heads,
I can't enter any Navy base so...
You said "Go right" so I...
Follow Straw Hat!
You listened to Straw Hat, not me!
Why am I doing this?
Climb all the way up quickly!
Warning - downgrade ahead!
Yeah!
Ouch!
How pathetic of you to be defeated
by a damn pirate.
You're so stubborn...
Keep working! Did you dig up any ore?
Please hold on to the strap!
If you just simply apologize,
Sakazuki can save face.
Peseta-sama! We gotta do something or...
He'll get here soon!
That was the extent of your greed?
Don't panic!
I already have plan B and C ready.
Is Luffy-senpai all right?!
Damn this ball...  I can't break it!
I don't want to.
Why not?
I guess the Monster of the New World will be
quite disappointed in you.
I have face to save, too.
Humph! Bill's creation can't
be broken that easily!
Ouch! Yes, he is, at the moment.
But there's no guarantee he
will be 10 minutes from now!
If he discards you, that'll be it for you.
That's the same guy whose underling tried
to kill you!
At the moment?!
Honestly!
If you do something to him,
I won't forgive you under any circumstances!
He'll never harm his friend!
The Monster of the New World...
Cut it out!
Ouch!
Take a good look at the situation you're in!
Just keep digging!
Fujitora.
We'll burn you up!
A traitor like you has no right to say that!
He's a king of greed...
Wait!
...who once brought my
pirate crew to our knees
He's an idiot, Tsuru-san.
A traitor? What are you talking about?
I'll be back... ouch!
To check... ouch! On you... ouch!!
so easily with the power of money.
We made a promise to aim for the top together
It was his last chance.
If only I could use my barrier...
The face of those giving in to me...
but all of a sudden, you said
you wanted to help Straw Hat
If he had sided with me
and helped me get rid of all those brats,
Anyway, that tramp...
Shambles!
to become the King of the Pirates!
That's entertainment!
What the hell is going on?
Ouch!
it wouldn't have ended up like this.
That's why I went out to sea with my friends!
Excuse me! Foxfire Style!
Luffy-senpai!
Friends?
Fire-Willow Flash!
I was holding the reins.
If he...
Then, what happened to your pirate group?!
Let me out! Let me out! Let me out!
The reins to the monsters of the world.
...discards me...
What?!
That's none of your business!
Kin'emon!
Let me out! Let me out!
Not yet! It's not over for me yet!
How could you say that?!
You shouldn't have taken me down.
There's no fire that I can't cut!
I can't... I'm too hungry and I feel weak...
I'm sure you people will regret this.
It's... gone.
Look at yourself. Just
give up without fighting.
What do you mean?
Don't say such pathetic crap.
You'll be executed by Bill soon.
I once lost...
Take care of the rest.
...everything that I had.
There is no "If."
It's crazy to even think about it.
Bill?
He's our leader.
Where are my friends?!
I don't know. But you can't expect help.
This outcome is the only reality.
Aren't you eating too much?
What? What?
We destroyed that tasteless ship
with our Battle Boats.
Gum-Gum...
You lost.
...Elephant Gun!
We're the ultimate armed group
that makes full use of the weapons Bill forges...
We're lost.
...with his Smelt-Smelt ability.
Oh, what's that?!
Straw Hat Luffy was...
I guess you know what you're doing.
Oh, how can I best you?!
...defeated! And your friends
were sunk into the sea!
Then, let's see what you can do.
The wolf knows what the ill beast thinks.
Zoro and the others won't
get taken down so easily!
I finally made it above ground!
What do you think will happen
to the world of pirates?
But it's the truth.
--You're lying!
--Trust me!
Luffy-senpai's Elephant Gun!
I got to see such a great thing!
--I won't trust you!
--That's enough!
To answer your question
with another question,
--No!
--I said it's the truth!
It's kind of hot!
what do you think the unleashed
monsters who lost the "food"
Why are you just standing?
Let's go already!
I won't trust you!
B-Big Sis...
You're right.
What?!
Oh no, you can't go any farther!
Don't think you won!
I supplied them will do?
Big Sis, relax.
Is there anyone who is at the top
of the ladder in all the seas now?
Still wanna fight?!
I'm hungry...
I-Is this where...
It's you again, Penta?!
What?
I wanted to eat that meat from before.
It's Peseta! Take a look at that!
What's going on?
...I'm gonna... die?
Who's ruling all the seas?
Hey, can I have it?
No way!
Is it one of the Four Emperors of the sea?
Meat! Meat! Meat!
You guys!
Hey!
Big Sis Desire!
Shut up!
Are you alright?! Hey!
Meat!
Or the Seven Warlords who cleverly live out
in the seas?
If you resist, they'll die!
The ground is...!
--Just eat this and forget it!
--Big Sis!
Stay with me!
Now, I need you to come
along without fighting!
Or the brats from the Worst Generation?
It's okay! A piece of chocolate
won't make him full!
There are so many of them!
I'm glad that there are survivors!
How cunning!
He can't break the ball that Bill made.
Peseta! You're really terrible!
No...
There's no end to this!
The Navy, the military forces of justice,
is conquering the seas!
It's good! You're so sweet!
One-Sword Style 360-Pound Phoenix!
Terrible? I don't think so...
D-Don't get me wrong!
I'm not feeling pity or anything!
There are some strong members
who we must keep an eye on,
Zoro! Kin'emon!
I see!
You mean incredible, don't you?!
Where's Straw Hat-ya?!
in the Revolutionary Army,
the ally of the people.
You're the infamous Desire
from the East Blue!
I wish he'd execute you already!
We got to see him but...
"The fastest female pirate racer"!
It's my honor to meet you!
They said they wanted to
settle things themselves.
Ring, ring, ring...
The family of "D." have been hiding
in the shadow of history.
What?
If we stay here, they'll come.
I'm not that person anymore.
What?!
--Okay.
--Clank.
I was betrayed by a guy I trusted and...
How can he be so easygoing?
It's time!
When and where are they
gonna show themselves?!
Bill! Bill! Bill! Bill!
I'm glad that they're fine.
Are you alright?!
...I lost my friends and my bike,
and now I ended up like this.
Y-Yes!
Who's gonna side with who?!
Bill! Bill! Bill!
Zoro!
How silly I was, to dream
of going to the top...
What the...! It's all melting!
Who's gonna betray who?!
Tell the Celestial Dragons
in the Holyland of Mariejois...
Don't give up so easily!
I'm gonna dominate the Pirate Era!
...that they'll be dragged down!
But I need trustworthy friends
to accomplish that!
It's been 25 years since Gold Roger
fully explored the whole Grand Line.
You can have that Battle Boat!
It's not easy to ride but I'm
sure you can make full use of it!
His arch enemy, Whitebeard,
didn't sit on the throne
but just stood in front
of it and took the reins.
If all of us work together,
our dream will come true!
What's with that guy?
Is he even human?
What about now?!
That's Bill.
The number of pirates is ballooning
Would you like to come with me?!
B-Bill?!
I thought he was a blast-furnace human!
and there's one seat that's totally empty!
He's a Paramythia-type
Devil Fruit eater, right?!
My friends of the Silver Pirate Alliance,
You know what I mean, don't you?
I finally met someone who shared my ideals.
But that's more like Logia!
who are aiming for the top
of the Pirate Era with me!
It will start!
All the people at the
fortress trust Bill too.
My friends of the Silver Pirate Alliance!
The biggest struggle for supremacy ever...
There he is!
When his friends have their
back against the wall,
So did you come after Luffy-senpai
to please him?!
he appears at the right moment!
...in the history of pirates!
Zoro-senpai!
Yeah, and you told me
about the Straw Hats repeatedly!
You can't get away!
Luffy, I have to pay him back. Let me do it.
So you've been working hard
for your friends like we do!
Oh yeah? Okay.
Your praise doesn't make me happy!
Bill! Bill! Bill! Bill! Bill!
How could you be so composed,
Pirate Hunter Zoro?
The Bill guy still sounds fishy.
He's way cooler than you or Straw Hat!
You have a bounty of 320 million
but you were pretty
pathetic when we last met!
Okay, let's hear how you did today.
--The mast has caught fire!
--Put it out!
Hey! What are you doing there?
I'll go first! Hey, stand up!
Laugh at him! Just laugh at him, guys!
Who are you guys?!
You got Boblat with a bounty of 68 million.
It's totally like an inferno!
Are we going to Impel Down?
If nothing is done,
the whole island might melt away!
Good job!
I'll go next!
I'm sorry but I need you to
give me a newspaper everyday.
That bastard!
How dare he make fun of Zoro-senpai?!
That's probably what he wants!
You got Tambu with a bounty of 70 million.
He wants to completely smelt everything
along with us!
I'm gonna beat the hell out of him!
I also ripped off the treasure he saved up!
That way, I won't be bored.
What?!
Luffy-senpai?
Oh, well done!
Let's retreat for now!
He said he'll do it.
Bill! Look how well I did today too!
You can't go anywhere!
--Me too!
There are four Navy ships.
Barrier!
There you are, Desire.
But the lineup is so formidable!
Are they gonna go destroy a country?
Bring it on!
You don't know your place!
I'll immobilize you again!
Watch out!
They use so much force just for transport.
Peseta, where's Bartolomeo?
Our retreat is being cut off!
That's how great Doflamingo-sama is!
I'm treating him with respect.
I'm gonna smelt everyone
who I don't have use for!
Will this do?
It's impossible to take back Joker.
Captain Jack, shall we go back?
Yeah! Thanks!
Who is this?
Bill! He's the guy with
a bounty of 500 million
It's flowing in from the side too!
--Why?
--What?
Let's do it!
Straw Hat Luffy, who you've wanted to catch!
You idiot! We're gonna do it!
Ouch! Ouch! Ow! Ow!
What?!
One-Sword Style iai...
--Is that the real Straw Hat Luffy?
--I can't believe it.
Who do you think I am?!
--It's too hot!
--S-Sorry...
Desire, are you alright?!
Whaaat?!
Bill?
It's coming off! One more time!
Desire! Great job!
Luffy-senpai!
That's the wisdom of Grandma back home, huh?
Oh no!
Let go of my hand, Bartolomeo!
No way! My Adhesive Shell should
stick to anything that it touches!
Do you know her?
Let me say thank you to all of you!
Yeah, I do! There's nothing
that Grandma doesn't know!
Aren't you gonna help Straw
Hat who you respect so much
Don't mention it, Bill!
If we hadn't met you,
we would've dropped
become the King of the Pirates?!
It'd be shameful for a swordsman
to even let that disgusting
All right! Look around as you like!
dead somewhere in the Grand Line already!
Cut the crap! I'm not gonna let go!
This must be Bill's work.
thing touch his blade!
That's right!
You're my friend!
--Can you break it?
--No, we can't.
This is the Barto Club's pirate ship
that's filled with love for the Straw Hats!
Only Zoro-dono could've done it!
We all appreciate you for
letting us join your group!
Even if I become rotten,
I'm not gonna cast aside a friend!
Were you guys dropped from up there too?
What happened?
Friend?
Thank you!
Zoro-senpai sliced up all the Adhesive Shells
with just one single slash!
But you did cast me aside!
What do you mean "too"?
Who are you people?
It's called...
It's been a year since we Silver Pirate Alliance
entered the New World!
...the Mister Luffy Go!
What? Did I?
And what's this place?
Now, this is it!
Don't you know anything?
It's far from over yet!
We've taken down more than a
hundred rival pirate groups!
Is this right, guys?!
Silver Mine is a rich mine and...
Right?
It looks like Luffy's on
this ship more than ours!
Hey!
Do you know why we made it this far?!
...we're in its underground mineshafts.
All right!
I'm so happy to hear that!
Tell us, Bill!
It's not a compliment!
We're former members of the
Silver Pirate Alliance.
Bill!
Oh, look!
I'm glad that you noticed it!
Each one of you alone is nothing special.
It was the Straw Hats' first pirate ship
What?
What?!
There! There! There! There!
That was so close!
But when you work together,
you'll become stronger than anyone else!
No matter what, we couldn't please Bill.
Thanks!
Three-Sword Style...
Don't mention it!
and a dear friend - the Going Merry!
Those who can't bring
him treasures or people
I'll back you up with all my
might since my support came late!
Strong enough to capture
a person with a high bounty like him!
...Black Rope Dragon Twister!
I duplicated its bow as a homage!
with bounties will all be tossed down here
Go, go, Luffy-senpai!
and forced to mine ore
from morning till night.
It has evil eyes.
Shut up!
Tell me! What's your dream?!
Crest Head!
How horrible he is to
abandon his own friends!
I want you to take a good look at this curve!
Can you do something about this hot stuff?
I wanna become stronger!
Where did that twister come from?!
Is that all?!
So we're his slaves.
I asked a woodcrafter to
duplicate Luffy-senpai's
I'll handle it for you, of course!
I wanna live happily, as I like!
It's coming this way!
Gum-Gum hands just like the real ones!
Is that it?!
Get rid of it if you can!
I wanna become an unbeatable pirate!
Could it be...
Barrier-bility!
It's terrible!
You can become one!
Yes, Robin-senpai, you have a good eye!
If we unite our hearts,
we can even beat the Four Emperors!
No way! He wouldn't do such
a thing to his friends!
It's terrible!!
Big Hand!
You're right! It's a homage
to Chopper-senpai's horns!
Well done!
I know it's hard to believe.
It doesn't matter if it's Kaido or Big Mom
or Red-Haired or Blackbeard!
Big Sis!
But that's the truth.
Yeah, now is our chance!
Take everybody to the port!
Then, those orange trees are...
Yes! They're a homage to the orange trees that
Nami-senpai
Did we do it?!
We'll leave the island!
If we kick the butts of all our rivals
in the New World and become the best,
Hey, isn't there any way to get out of here?!
No, not yet!
Okay! But what are you gonna do?
took from Bellemere-san's
grove in Coco Village!
The railroad is the only connection
between here and up there.
your dreams will come true!
But if we use it,
Avelon will know immediately.
I'll come after I settle things.
You worthless pirates...
Sometimes oranges are just oranges!
So keep aiming for the very top of this Pirate Era
together with me!
Then, we'll come with you!
I'm sooo moved!
So many people have tried until now
but all of them failed.
I know what none of you know.
Look how nerdy those details are!
Just give up the fight.
--Of course, we will, Bill!
--We'll follow you for the rest of our lives!
Everywhere you look, you feel a sense of fun!
A childish thing...
...like a dream...
It's filled with super love!
It's a problem of my own making.
That's right, Bill! Show us a dream!
...won't help you...
Thank you very much, Franky-senpai!
...survive the New World!
What is this alarm?!
Take us to the top!
Limited Express Avelon will soon arrive!
Let me do it on my own.
A nerd has stirred a pervert's mind...
Aiming for the top?!
And more than anything,
what we're thrilled about now is,
Look over there!
Becoming the King of the Pirates?!
That's how our rivals ended up
after getting defeated by us.
I'm gonna shatter your dreams!
All right. Promise us you'll come back!
Avelon?!
Straw Hat, you'll join them.
This is where your voyage ends.
in the direction this Vivre Card is
pointing towards,
We won't leave until you come back!
I see one ahead of me!
Shut up!
I ate the Smelt-Smelt Fruit
and became a blast-furnace human.
...we have the real Luffy-senpai!
Gum-Gum...
Please mind the bombs again!
Okay!
...Grizzly...
My body is an ultra-hot blast furnace.
All right! Let's go, everyone!
Welcome!
Thank you again for coming on board this ship!
...Magnum!
I can smelt ore and produce
all kinds of things.
Here comes Avelon!
You guys saved our lives!
I gotta remove this sticky thing already!
Thank you!
I'll turn you into a nice silver
statue befitting of a man
Bye!
Hey! Did Bill really tell you to...
Boss! He's so dazzling! I can barely see him!
with a bounty of 500 million!
...get rid of me as well?!
Me, too!
Do you wanna settle things with Bill?
That's right!
Yes!
Luffy-senpai!
--It's none of your business.
--Do you still believe in that jerk?
I can't believe I fought
hand-in-hand with Luffy-senpai!
I see.
Crest Head!
So they're all like that...
No, it's quite the opposite.
My extraordinary dream came true!
Anyway, let me settle something
with you, Straw Hat.
Anyway, it was nice of Sabo
to make a Vivre Card of me.
I'm not gonna let you
even touch Luffy-senpai!
Avelon started running wild!
What?
Rain of Bombs! Rain of Bombs!
I apologize to you for my rudeness till now.
Who is that?
Hey, look!
Here, I made a Vivre Card
of Luffy just in case.
No kidding! Did he climb
all the way up here?!
I'm sorry!
Oh, when did you have time for that?
Never mind! The chocolate
you gave me was delicious!
Why hasn't the situation changed?
Catch him!
I'll take a piece of it.
Oh, that's my great Sabo-senpai!
Yes! It all came off!
Let's go! Usopp and the others
are waiting at the ship.
He's so thoughtful and strong! What a guy!
All the molten metal that Bill produced
is made from real ore!
Now, it's only a matter of time
before enemy boats attack us!
Ow, ow, ow...
Uh-huh!
So it was you as I thought, Desire!
What are you doing here?!
Are you guys okay?!
We must hurry up too!
I'm not gonna become your follower but...
So it won't just go away
even if you took him down!
B-Barely...
Bye!
How about you, Luffy-senpai?!
It's none of your business!
Then, how can we get off of this island?!
I'll take it just in case.
Give us back Straw Hat!
Bellamy!
You tell me!
We're gonna take it, too.
Oh, senpai! Are you all right?!
Hey, that's...
Okay, I'll say goodbye for now!
You can't go anywhere!
I found Straw Hat!
I'll see you soon, boss!
--Hurry up!
--Come on!
With this drill that was
specially made by Bill,
It got cut! No, it's melting!
--Alright, don't rush.
--You're okay now!
Straw Hat Luffy!
stand by for Straw Hat impalement!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ow, ow!
See ya, guys!
Thank you!
It's over.
Oh no!
Hey! Let us get on board too!
If only I could use my barrier...
Oh, I had so much fun at the banquet!
I like them now!
That was close!
Is this it?!
Get on already!
Don't give up!
--We better leave now!
--Big Sis and the others aren't here yet!
Bartolomeo, just hurry up and go to Zou!
Let's go!
What a shame.
The sum total of Straw Hat and Pirate
Hunter's bounties is 820 million
Oh, that's my Luffy-senpai!
We can't wait anymore! Set sail!
Who do you think you're talking to...
I'm counting on you.
Big Sis!
and it was my chance to
capture them both at once.
Okay! Leave it in my hands!
Luffy-senpai!!
Th-Th-Th-That doesn't look good, does it?!
Bill!
Guys! Let's head for Zou at full speed!
You're strong even when you look like that!
Don't we have to go help those two?!
Yeah!
--Luffy!
--We'll back you up!
Anyway,
I wonder if Sanji and the others got to the island safely.
Don't worry!
No, just go ahead!
I'm running out of the energy
from that chocolate...
Nami was with them so I'm
sure navigation was fine
The Vivre Card is moving -
that means he's still okay.
What?!
But...
Take care of Usopp and the others.
but they were chased by Big Mom's ship...
Luffy won't drop dead
from something of this level.
Let's go.
It's off!
What's wrong with them?
I'm worried.
Understood.
Hey, Luffy.
Oh? The island is sinking.
It went through! Why isn't he hurt?!
Chase them!
Seems like our bounties have gone up.
O-Okay!
That's really not good!
Forget about Pirate Hunter.
Where were you aiming at?
What?! Really?!
Luffy-san and our captain
are Devil Fruit eaters!
But I'm not gonna let a man with
a bounty of 500 million get away,
Oh, you didn't know?!
My body's not that big!
Straw Hat.
There they are!
Well, I have the wanted posters
of you all in my room so come on!
Listen, guys!
Here we go, Tram!
Hey!
--Please!
--Alright, I'll go!
It's not easy to get out
of this giant fortress!
I'm switching over to Hyper Special Express!
We're back!
Hey, Trafalgar.
I threw out yours but your bounty
has gone up to 500 million.
Welcome back, you two!
Each team, split up and find Straw
Hat and the other one at any price!
Oh, thanks. But I don't care about the price.
I told you.
Guys! Franky-senpai has taken the trouble to
repair this Mister Luffy Go!
This feels great!
I'll take command! Thanks!
Big Sis!
You guys!
Off we go!
Okay, please take a look at them!
Don't let them damage it any more!
Oh! I'm glad they're okay too!
Th-They're in frames?!
Yeah!
Gum-Gum...
The autographs you gave
me earlier are there, too!
Go! Special Attack: Green Star - Sea Devil!
Take this!
ME
...Hammer!
SWORD
Seems like we shook them somehow.
TO BARTOLOMEO
Yeah, I think so! You saved my life!
That's my Luffy-senpai!
Dodge!
TO MY BROTHER
What?!
Weapon's Left!
NICO ROBIN
I don't deserve such words of praise!
Okay, let's start
with "Straw Hat" Luffy-senpai!
I, unworthy Bartolomeo, will
go through fire and soil for you!
Mil Fleurs...
Second Gear!
...Gigantesco Mano!
Your bounty is 500 million berries!
Gum-Gum...
Oh, moving with this
thing on makes me hungry.
It's 500 million! Yeah!
...Jet Gatling!
"STRAW HAT" LUFFY -
BOUNTY: 500 MILLION BERRIES
They keep coming, one after another!
Next, "Pirate Hunter" Zoro-senpai!
I managed to move for a little while
because of the chocolate
that Lady Crest Head gave me.
320 million berries!
U-Unbelievable! He did it!
Chocolate?
Oh, are you talking about Desire?!
--Isn't Straw Hat-ya here yet?
--I guess he's having trouble.
"PIRATE HUNTER" ZORO -
BOUNTY: 320 MILLION BERRIES
Hey, do you have booze?
That candy lover was my childhood friend.
Luffy...
"Demon Child" Nico Robin-senpai!
What?
Now pulling into the garage!
We came from the same island
130 million berries!
and used to hang out
together doing silly stuff.
"DEMON CHILD" NICO ROBIN -
BOUNTY: 130 MILLION BERRIES
Straw Hat.
Wait!
Oh no. It's gone up.
I'm the one who must settle things with him!
Oh, wait for me! Senpai!
We went out to sea separately but...
"Cyborg" Franky-senpai!
94 million berries!
Hmmm, "settle things"?
...why is she doing this?
Just a little short!
"CYBORG" FRANKY -
BOUNTY: 94 MILLION BERRIES
Now isn't the time to think about that!
My way of settling things is
to collect all the bounties!
On top of that,
the picture is General Franky...
We gotta get out of here as fast as possible!
God Usopp-senpai! 200 million berries!
I'm gonna smelt you along
with this mine for that!
What?!
If you do that, your subordinates will...
GOD USOPP -
BOUNTY: 200 MILLION BERRIES
It's unmasked and
the price is unbelievable!
Stand by for track...
We were really taken care of by you guys.
...change!
I'll be targeted!
What's the problem?
Stop!
Desire!
But I'm happy!
You can't run!
Yeah, you were.
Don't ever get fooled by a bad guy again.
Their bounties are so low
compared to Straw Hat and the others
But the picture is awful!
Found you!
Hey, screw you!
How did your bounty get so high?!
Track change!
but it's better than nothing,
Oh, I'm sorry!
We're the fastest boat
racers in the East Blue!
Yeah, and...
in order to make my dream come true!
What a pain in the butt!
Even my own friend's trying to kill me!
...if you have nowhere to go,
Do you think you can get away from us?!
Luffy-senpai!
Your dream is
to dominate the Pirate Era, isn't it?!
THE GROUP THAT HELPS LUFFY-SENPAI TO BECOME
THE KING OF THE PIRATES - BARTO CLUB
I'm the only one who is less than 100 million!
It's so frustrating!
I can let you join the Barto Club.
Let me take care of him!
Let's hang out together like we used to!
Bartolomeo! For the sake of old friendship,
That's what you told me when
you saved me, isn't it?!
Wait, wait! Take a good look!
Let's hang out!
if you hand over Straw Hat to us,
There are still Nami and the others!
I'll ask Bill to spare your life!
"Black-Foot" Sanji-senpai!
177 million berries!
Bartolomeo...
Changing tracks! Changing tracks!
I'll pass on that one because I'm
not really a fan of Straw Hat.
Don't be ridiculous! Luffy-senpai is...
Changing tracks!
Oh, his poster isn't a drawing anymore!
"BLACK-FOOT" SANJI -
BOUNTY: 177 MILLION BERRIES
No, I can't!
...the most important
person to me in the world!
On top of that, I've had enough
of riding in the back seat.
Tsk! That's boring. The last one was funnier.
Are you still saying that?!
Saved you? Yeah, I did save you.
From now on, we're gonna rise to the
top of the world of the sea on our own!
Then why don't you go to
hell together with him?!
Gum-Gum...
"Cat Burglar" Nami-senpai!
66million berries!
Big Sis...
...Jet Bazooka!
That's our new dream!
Since you had the capability
to lead a girl gang,
"CAT BURGLAR" NAMI -
BOUNTY: 66 MILLION BERRIES
When did she get
her picture taken again?!
That's right!
I thought I could use you...
Don't push your luck!
You have no chance against Luffy-senpai!
--Big Sis! You're shooting too much!
--Desire!
What did you say?!
"Cotton Candy Lover" Chopper-senpai!
What are you doing?! You're gonna hit me!
Don't tell me you were the one
who sank our boats that day...
100 berries!
You won't know until I try!
You'll be sorry for this!
I can't think of any words
to cheer him up...
"COTTON CANDY LOVER" CHOPPER
- BOUNTY: 100 BERRIES
What?!
"Soul King" Brook-senpai!
83 million berries!
It's obvious!
Big Sis!
--He took down Avelon that easily....
--How strong...
"SOUL KING" BROOK -
BOUNTY: 83 MILLION BERRIES
That's like a poster for his concert!
That's right!
You two are really funny!
It was me!
Except for the people who
stood out and showed them
--Now, let's go!
--Okay!
I sank them and saved you.
how dangerous they could
be in the recent incident,
Wait!
Goodbye.
everybody went up by 50 million!
AVELON EXPRESS
--Alright, we gotta get going too!
--Yes, Big Sis!
Didn't I perform as good as a stage actor?
It's kind of noisy out there.
TERMINAL STATION
Ours have gone up by 50 million, too.
See?! I took down Tram!
There was a little accident.
We'll settle it soon.
Take care!
But...
I fought in collaboration with
Luffy-senpai for the first time!
And guess what?
...take a look at that.
For "Black-Foot" Sanji-senpai,
See ya!
Peseta!
The simple minded idiot
that you are got wrapped up
Hey! Let's get out of here now!
It's this month's installment!
Isn't it incredible?!
the price has gone up strangely
high and the text is odd.
in my dream like a loyal dog.
Thank you for contributing tons
of silver to us every month.
Guys! Let's set sail for Zou!
"Only alive"?
That's what this is all about.
Since it's Sanji,
Yeah!
He appreciates it, too.
I bet someone holds a grudge against him
Say hi to the monster
over a woman and wants to
do the honors themselves.
So that's Grantesoro...
of the New World for me.
You're right.
You bastard...
Take care of the people with bounties
that we captured as always.
...where the Monster of the New World...
That's unforgivable...
Ring, ring, ring...
...who has power that equals that
of the Celestial Dragons, lives.
What? Okay, I got it.
How dare you...
Avelon! Hey, Avelon!
Something wrong?
He said Straw Hat and Desire
fell into the abyss.
The ore deposits at Silver Mine
sank along with Bill, Tesoro-sama.
What's wrong?
...take advantage of our compassion!
He's not responding. He must've failed.
Call Avelon.
If Straw Hat and the others make
it up here, we'll be in trouble!
Yeah? Well, that's okay.
Roger that. I'll take
care of them as you say.
Your tears are pathetic.
I've already had quite
a lot of fun with Bill.
Then, let's just...
DEPARTURE
The real entertainment starts from now.
Off we go!
...bury them all.
In front of Luffy and the others who are wandering
around
While Luffy and the others are
heading to the next island, Zou,
In front of Luffy and the others
who are climbing over themselves
Guild Tesoro, the golden
emperor behind the curtain,
Dense fog and a turbulent current keep
to get above ground, the next
assassin, Peseta, appears!
people away from the legendary island, Zou!
they suddenly come across a glittering
solitary island, Silver Mine!
brings out Bill's hidden ability!
maze-like underground mineshafts, Bill's
formidable assassin, Avelon, appears!
Just when the secret weapons
of the Smelt-Smelt Fruit
In a mysterious 1000-year-old country
where the
When Luffy's angry fist clashes with Bill
After being attacked by an
unknown group of pirates,
are
about to burn up everything in the underground mineshafts,
While he attacks them right
and left with explosives,
native inhabitants, the
Mink Tribe, reign supreme,
who rages out of control in blazing fire,
Luffy and Bartolomeo land
on the eerie island!
Zoro and the others finally arrive!
the Special Express Avelon's deadly Silver Drill
and Luffy's furious fists clash!
the curtain rises on Luffy's
exciting new adventure!
the battle in Silver Mine
finally comes to a climax!
Zoro and Peseta's duel, in which
their pride is at stake, begins!
The curtain rises on the first-ever,
great adventure staring just the two!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Curtain-up on a New Adventure!
Arriving at the Phantom Island, Zou!"
"A Desperate Situation! Luffy
Fights a Battle in Extreme Heat!"
"The Sword Technique Heats Up!
Law and Zoro Finally Appear!"
"An Underground Maze!
Luffy vs. the Tram Human!"
"The Silver Fortress! Luffy
and Barto's Great Adventure!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!