Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After a hard fight, Luffy and the others
defeated the Warlord - Donquixote Doflamingo
and left the fateful island, Dressrosa.
Here it goes, Luffy-senpai.
We now become
Straw Hat Luffy-senpai's followers
and we'll be his shield
or pike in all weather!
To repay him for what he did
this time, we seven will...
...drink out of these Sons'
Cups of our own volition,
devoting our lives and souls!
Now we're formally...
Hurry up and prepare for the banquet!
It's all ready!
Alright, guys!
In the battle against the Mingo Family,
we...
...won!
Yeah!
"The Numerous Rivals Struggle Amongst Themselves!
The Raging Monsters of the New World"
Let's eat more!
Yeah!
H-Here you go!
Thanks!
Super!
We can't see Dressrosa anymore.
You achieved your goal by taking
down Doflamingo, didn't you?
What are you gonna do next?
Leave me alone.
DRESSROSA
THE ROYAL PALACE
I can't find any list they
used for trafficking.
But it was all clearly stolen by somebody...
I thought so.
All the weapons and explosives
that were left behind
were stolen after the incident.
There was quite a lot.
CIPHER POL "AIGIS" ZERO
It must've been some organization.
The Navy was panicking about it, too.
Was it the Revolutionary Army?
Yeah. Who else would do that?
Come back already.
Clank.
They're so annoying.
You're right, boss!
Annoying like you...
Wow! You're way out of line!
Where are you going next, Straw Hat?
This is the land of tragedy.
Dark strings were cast one after another.
Counting the number of tragedies
that fell upon them,
they hold back their tears
and play the music...
Oh yeah!
The music of handclapping
that rings out loud.
Olé!
The curtain was drawn during the long, sad,
nameless show without any applause
and then the words of truth reach them.
The king has returned
and with peace ahead, all is serene.
I have a preposition for you...
Um, thank you for the introduction.
I'm Chief Tonta, Gancho!
Standing next to me is my daughter...
I'm Mansherry!
So cute!
Do you want us to make this, Leo-kun?
That's right! I'm counting on you!
The World Conference "Reverie" is this year.
It's coming up soon.
Looks like each country has
already started preparing.
Father-sama!
Rebecca said she'll come to
cook for us this afternoon!
Oh yeah?! What about Kyros?!
He'll come, too, of course.
Good, good. The whole family
will gather together...
...after all these years!
Visitors to this kingdom will have
something to be amazed about.
--Can I have a ham?
--Oh, hello!
Rebecca and Mansherry.
"They" are blending in with the town
and living side-by-side with humans.
Hey, hey. We haven't even
built houses to live in yet.
No, no, this must be our first priority!
The visitors will be amazed
by these adorable Dwarves.
This is a kingdom of love
and passion and fairies...
You're right. The statues must come first!
They should!
Dressrosa.
When we finish transporting the prisoner,
THE NAVY'S FLEET
I'll go on a journey.
A journey?
Without Straw Hat and Law's heads,
I can't enter any Navy base so...
You're so stubborn...
If you just simply apologize,
Sakazuki can save face.
I don't want to.
Why not?
I have face to save, too.
Honestly!
Fujitora.
He's an idiot, Tsuru-san.
It was his last chance.
If he had sided with me
and helped me get rid of all those brats,
it wouldn't have ended up like this.
I was holding the reins.
The reins to the monsters of the world.
You shouldn't have taken me down.
I'm sure you people will regret this.
Don't say such pathetic crap.
There is no "If."
It's crazy to even think about it.
This outcome is the only reality.
You lost.
Oh, how can I best you?!
The wolf knows what the ill beast thinks.
What do you think will happen
to the world of pirates?
To answer your question
with another question,
what do you think the unleashed
monsters who lost the "food"
I supplied them will do?
Is there anyone who is at the top
of the ladder in all the seas now?
Who's ruling all the seas?
Is it one of the Four Emperors of the sea?
Or the Seven Warlords who cleverly live out
in the seas?
Or the brats from the Worst Generation?
No...
The Navy, the military forces of justice,
is conquering the seas!
There are some strong members
who we must keep an eye on,
in the Revolutionary Army,
the ally of the people.
The family of "D." have been hiding
in the shadow of history.
When and where are they
gonna show themselves?!
Who's gonna side with who?!
Who's gonna betray who?!
Tell the Celestial Dragons
in the Holyland of Mariejois...
...that they'll be dragged down!
It's been 25 years since Gold Roger
fully explored the whole Grand Line.
His arch enemy, Whitebeard,
didn't sit on the throne
but just stood in front
of it and took the reins.
What about now?!
The number of pirates is ballooning
and there's one seat that's totally empty!
You know what I mean, don't you?
It will start!
The biggest struggle for supremacy ever...
...in the history of pirates!
--The mast has caught fire!
--Put it out!
Are we going to Impel Down?
I'm sorry but I need you to
give me a newspaper everyday.
That way, I won't be bored.
There are four Navy ships.
But the lineup is so formidable!
Are they gonna go destroy a country?
They use so much force just for transport.
That's how great Doflamingo-sama is!
It's impossible to take back Joker.
Captain Jack, shall we go back?
--Why?
--What?
You idiot! We're gonna do it!
What?!
Who do you think I am?!
Whaaat?!
All right! Look around as you like!
This is the Barto Club's pirate ship
that's filled with love for the Straw Hats!
It's called...
...the Mister Luffy Go!
Is this right, guys?!
It looks like Luffy's on
this ship more than ours!
I'm so happy to hear that!
It's not a compliment!
Oh, look!
I'm glad that you noticed it!
It was the Straw Hats' first pirate ship
and a dear friend - the Going Merry!
I duplicated its bow as a homage!
It has evil eyes.
I want you to take a good look at this curve!
I asked a woodcrafter to
duplicate Luffy-senpai's
Gum-Gum hands just like the real ones!
Could it be...
Yes, Robin-senpai, you have a good eye!
You're right! It's a homage
to Chopper-senpai's horns!
Then, those orange trees are...
Yes! They're a homage to the orange trees that
Nami-senpai
took from Bellemere-san's
grove in Coco Village!
Sometimes oranges are just oranges!
I'm sooo moved!
Look how nerdy those details are!
Everywhere you look, you feel a sense of fun!
It's filled with super love!
Thank you very much, Franky-senpai!
A nerd has stirred a pervert's mind...
And more than anything,
what we're thrilled about now is,
in the direction this Vivre Card is
pointing towards,
...we have the real Luffy-senpai!
Welcome!
Thank you again for coming on board this ship!
Boss! He's so dazzling! I can barely see him!
Me, too!
So they're all like that...
Anyway, it was nice of Sabo
to make a Vivre Card of me.
Here, I made a Vivre Card
of Luffy just in case.
Oh, when did you have time for that?
I'll take a piece of it.
Oh, that's my great Sabo-senpai!
He's so thoughtful and strong! What a guy!
Uh-huh!
I'm not gonna become your follower but...
I'll take it just in case.
Bellamy!
We're gonna take it, too.
Okay, I'll say goodbye for now!
I'll see you soon, boss!
Straw Hat Luffy!
See ya, guys!
Oh, I had so much fun at the banquet!
I like them now!
Bartolomeo, just hurry up and go to Zou!
Who do you think you're talking to...
I'm counting on you.
Okay! Leave it in my hands!
Guys! Let's head for Zou at full speed!
Yeah!
Anyway,
I wonder if Sanji and the others got to the island safely.
Nami was with them so I'm
sure navigation was fine
but they were chased by Big Mom's ship...
I'm worried.
Hey, Luffy.
Seems like our bounties have gone up.
What?! Really?!
Oh, you didn't know?!
Well, I have the wanted posters
of you all in my room so come on!
--Please!
--Alright, I'll go!
Hey, Trafalgar.
I threw out yours but your bounty
has gone up to 500 million.
Oh, thanks. But I don't care about the price.
Okay, please take a look at them!
Th-They're in frames?!
The autographs you gave
me earlier are there, too!
ME
SWORD
TO BARTOLOMEO
TO MY BROTHER
NICO ROBIN
Okay, let's start
with "Straw Hat" Luffy-senpai!
Your bounty is 500 million berries!
It's 500 million! Yeah!
"STRAW HAT" LUFFY -
BOUNTY: 500 MILLION BERRIES
Next, "Pirate Hunter" Zoro-senpai!
320 million berries!
"PIRATE HUNTER" ZORO -
BOUNTY: 320 MILLION BERRIES
Hey, do you have booze?
"Demon Child" Nico Robin-senpai!
130 million berries!
"DEMON CHILD" NICO ROBIN -
BOUNTY: 130 MILLION BERRIES
Oh no. It's gone up.
"Cyborg" Franky-senpai!
94 million berries!
Just a little short!
"CYBORG" FRANKY -
BOUNTY: 94 MILLION BERRIES
On top of that,
the picture is General Franky...
God Usopp-senpai! 200 million berries!
GOD USOPP -
BOUNTY: 200 MILLION BERRIES
It's unmasked and
the price is unbelievable!
I'll be targeted!
But I'm happy!
But the picture is awful!
Hey, screw you!
How did your bounty get so high?!
Even my own friend's trying to kill me!
I'm the only one who is less than 100 million!
It's so frustrating!
Wait, wait! Take a good look!
There are still Nami and the others!
"Black-Foot" Sanji-senpai!
177 million berries!
Oh, his poster isn't a drawing anymore!
"BLACK-FOOT" SANJI -
BOUNTY: 177 MILLION BERRIES
Tsk! That's boring. The last one was funnier.
"Cat Burglar" Nami-senpai!
66million berries!
"CAT BURGLAR" NAMI -
BOUNTY: 66 MILLION BERRIES
When did she get
her picture taken again?!
"Cotton Candy Lover" Chopper-senpai!
100 berries!
I can't think of any words
to cheer him up...
"COTTON CANDY LOVER" CHOPPER
- BOUNTY: 100 BERRIES
"Soul King" Brook-senpai!
83 million berries!
"SOUL KING" BROOK -
BOUNTY: 83 MILLION BERRIES
That's like a poster for his concert!
Except for the people who
stood out and showed them
how dangerous they could
be in the recent incident,
everybody went up by 50 million!
Ours have gone up by 50 million, too.
But...
...take a look at that.
For "Black-Foot" Sanji-senpai,
the price has gone up strangely
high and the text is odd.
"Only alive"?
Since it's Sanji,
I bet someone holds a grudge against him
over a woman and wants to
do the honors themselves.
You're right.
While Luffy and the others are
heading to the next island, Zou,
they suddenly come across a glittering
solitary island, Silver Mine!
After being attacked by an
unknown group of pirates,
Luffy and Bartolomeo land
on the eerie island!
The curtain rises on the first-ever,
great adventure staring just the two!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Silver Fortress! Luffy
and Barto's Great Adventure!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!