kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Looks delicious!
Okay, everybody!
You can have as many second
helpings as you like!
Show us that you can eat as much as they say!
Okay, thanks! It's really really good!
The members of the Straw Hats are enjoying
our homemade dishes so much...
I'm so happy to be alive!
Oh? I don't like the look of those clouds.
It's hail!
They're big! Watch out!
--What?!
--It punched a hole in the deck!
Luffy-senpai and everybody! Get inside now!
What're you talking about?! We'll help you!
Which way should we turn?!
Who's your navigator?! Give us directions!
Oh, we don't have a navigator
since we were a land-based gang originally.
What?! You're in the New World, you know?!
Hello, Grandma? It's me, Gambia!
The thing is, huge hail
just started falling on us.
Whenever we're in trouble,
we call Grandma in our hometown.
I see! So she knows about the sea!
Hey, I got it!
We have some chewing gum
stuck to the deck, right?
Yeah, and we didn't know what to do!
Wrap the hailstone in cloth
and cool the gum to peel it off!
Alright!
It came off surprisingly easily!
We don't need that sort of wisdom now!
But...
See! You got hit!
Apply sugar to his lump, she says!
Enough with her wisdom!
Oh no! This ship's gonna sink!
Nami, help us!
We had so many ships to choose from
but we got on board the wrong one!
I guess we gotta deal with this ourselves!
If only we had the Sunny's equipment!
It's so lively.
Why aren't you using your barrier?!
What?! Well, Grandma says,
"You'll regret it if you defy nature!"
If you're so scared, get back on land!
Are they for real?!
I have no choice!
I'll smash all the hailstones up!
Guys! We have the Straw Hats
who don't even fear god
and that's like getting help
from a thousand people!
Our appreciation rains down
like hail and snow pellets!
How have you guys survived until now?!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
It's just a short time
until we arrive at Zou,
but I get to travel
with that awesome Luffy-senpai...
I'm too happy and I could be punished for it!
I'm so happy!
You do something too, you fools!
"The Silver Fortress!
Luffy and Barto's Great Adventure!"
Do you have to pee?
I'm coming too.
Oh, I'm so happy to have a pee
with my hero, Luffy-senpai...
Oh, I'm hungry again.
What?!
Oh, do you want me
to fix you a midnight snack?
It's meat!
Oh, you're gonna fall!
--Is it hailing again?
--I don't know.
Luffy-senpai, neither of us can swim.
We did it, Big Sis!
Yeah, we landed the unwanted one too though.
Incredible.
You actually lured Straw Hat with meat!
Just like you said, Desire!
Incredible! Incredible!
Incredible!!
What's that?
--Luffy!
--Captain!
There they are!
"Pirate Hunter." "God."
"Cyborg." "Demon Child."
Everybody! Let's do this...
...as we planned!
Okay!
I'm a former leader of the Sweet
Pirates from the East Blue - Desire!
Yoroshiku (Thanks) !
NIGHT FURNACE SISTER CRIMSON
(YO)      (RO)      (SHI)        (KU)
Cut it out! Give us back Luffy!
Special Attack: Green Star! Sea Devil!
Here comes a plant!
Formation: Madeleine!
Okay!
--What?!
--Let me do it!
This time, it's a machine gun!
Weapon's Left!
No!
Big Sis!
--Are you okay?!
--Thank you very much.
Tsk! I couldn't get them.
What the...?!
Shoot! Shoot!
I can't move!
Is this birdlime?!
It's sticky!
Do it!
They're incredibly pathetic! Do it, do it!
Stop! That's enough.
I'm the leader of this assault!
Let's go back to Silver Mine.
This is Silver Mine,
a solitary island near Dressrosa.
SILVER MINE
A giant silver fortress dominates
the center of the island
and its sparkle makes even
the surrounding waters shine.
How was it?!
We got a fine haul again!
If it's for Luffy-senpai, I'll do it!
Why am I doing this?
Ouch!
Keep working! Did you dig up any ore?
Is Luffy-senpai all right?!
Ouch! Yes, he is, at the moment.
But there's no guarantee he
will be 10 minutes from now!
At the moment?!
If you do something to him,
I won't forgive you under any circumstances!
Ouch!
Just keep digging!
Wait!
I'll be back... ouch!
To check... ouch! On you... ouch!!
If only I could use my barrier...
Anyway, that tramp...
What the hell is going on?
Luffy-senpai!
Let me out! Let me out! Let me out!
Let me out! Let me out!
I can't... I'm too hungry and I feel weak...
Look at yourself. Just
give up without fighting.
You'll be executed by Bill soon.
Bill?
He's our leader.
Where are my friends?!
I don't know. But you can't expect help.
We destroyed that tasteless ship
with our Battle Boats.
We're the ultimate armed group
that makes full use of the weapons Bill forges...
...with his Smelt-Smelt ability.
Straw Hat Luffy was...
...defeated! And your friends
were sunk into the sea!
Zoro and the others won't
get taken down so easily!
But it's the truth.
--You're lying!
--Trust me!
--I won't trust you!
--That's enough!
--No!
--I said it's the truth!
I won't trust you!
What?!
Big Sis, relax.
I'm hungry...
What?
I wanted to eat that meat from before.
Hey, can I have it?
No way!
Meat! Meat! Meat!
Shut up!
Meat!
--Just eat this and forget it!
--Big Sis!
It's okay! A piece of chocolate
won't make him full!
He can't break the ball that Bill made.
It's good! You're so sweet!
D-Don't get me wrong!
I'm not feeling pity or anything!
I wish he'd execute you already!
Ring, ring, ring...
What?
--Okay.
--Clank.
It's time!
Bill! Bill! Bill! Bill!
Bill! Bill! Bill!
My friends of the Silver Pirate Alliance,
who are aiming for the top
of the Pirate Era with me!
My friends of the Silver Pirate Alliance!
Bill! Bill! Bill! Bill! Bill!
Okay, let's hear how you did today.
I'll go first! Hey, stand up!
You got Boblat with a bounty of 68 million.
Good job!
I'll go next!
You got Tambu with a bounty of 70 million.
I also ripped off the treasure he saved up!
Oh, well done!
Bill! Look how well I did today too!
--Me too!
There you are, Desire.
Peseta, where's Bartolomeo?
I'm treating him with respect.
Who is this?
Bill! He's the guy with
a bounty of 500 million
Straw Hat Luffy, who you've wanted to catch!
--Is that the real Straw Hat Luffy?
--I can't believe it.
Bill?
Desire! Great job!
Let me say thank you to all of you!
Don't mention it, Bill!
If we hadn't met you,
we would've dropped
dead somewhere in the Grand Line already!
That's right!
We all appreciate you for
letting us join your group!
Thank you!
It's been a year since we Silver Pirate Alliance
entered the New World!
We've taken down more than a
hundred rival pirate groups!
Do you know why we made it this far?!
Tell us, Bill!
Bill!
Each one of you alone is nothing special.
What?!
But when you work together,
you'll become stronger than anyone else!
Strong enough to capture
a person with a high bounty like him!
Tell me! What's your dream?!
I wanna become stronger!
Is that all?!
I wanna live happily, as I like!
Is that it?!
I wanna become an unbeatable pirate!
You can become one!
If we unite our hearts,
we can even beat the Four Emperors!
It doesn't matter if it's Kaido or Big Mom
or Red-Haired or Blackbeard!
If we kick the butts of all our rivals
in the New World and become the best,
your dreams will come true!
So keep aiming for the very top of this Pirate Era
together with me!
--Of course, we will, Bill!
--We'll follow you for the rest of our lives!
That's right, Bill! Show us a dream!
Take us to the top!
Look over there!
That's how our rivals ended up
after getting defeated by us.
Straw Hat, you'll join them.
This is where your voyage ends.
I ate the Smelt-Smelt Fruit
and became a blast-furnace human.
My body is an ultra-hot blast furnace.
I can smelt ore and produce
all kinds of things.
I'll turn you into a nice silver
statue befitting of a man
with a bounty of 500 million!
Luffy-senpai!
Crest Head!
I'm not gonna let you
even touch Luffy-senpai!
Who is that?
No kidding! Did he climb
all the way up here?!
Catch him!
So it was you as I thought, Desire!
What are you doing here?!
It's none of your business!
Give us back Straw Hat!
You can't go anywhere!
It got cut! No, it's melting!
It's over.
If only I could use my barrier...
Is this it?!
Don't give up!
Let's go!
Oh, that's my Luffy-senpai!
You're strong even when you look like that!
I'm running out of the energy
from that chocolate...
What?!
What's wrong with them?
Chase them!
O-Okay!
Listen, guys!
It's not easy to get out
of this giant fortress!
Each team, split up and find Straw
Hat and the other one at any price!
I'll take command! Thanks!
Seems like we shook them somehow.
Yeah, I think so! You saved my life!
What?!
I don't deserve such words of praise!
I, unworthy Bartolomeo, will
go through fire and soil for you!
Oh, moving with this
thing on makes me hungry.
I managed to move for a little while
because of the chocolate
that Lady Crest Head gave me.
Chocolate?
Oh, are you talking about Desire?!
That candy lover was my childhood friend.
What?
We came from the same island
and used to hang out
together doing silly stuff.
We went out to sea separately but...
...why is she doing this?
Now isn't the time to think about that!
We gotta get out of here as fast as possible!
Desire!
Found you!
We're the fastest boat
racers in the East Blue!
Do you think you can get away from us?!
Bartolomeo! For the sake of old friendship,
if you hand over Straw Hat to us,
I'll ask Bill to spare your life!
Don't be ridiculous! Luffy-senpai is...
...the most important
person to me in the world!
Are you still saying that?!
Then why don't you go to
hell together with him?!
Big Sis...
--Big Sis! You're shooting too much!
--Desire!
What are you doing?! You're gonna hit me!
What?!
Big Sis!
It's kind of noisy out there.
There was a little accident.
We'll settle it soon.
Peseta!
It's this month's installment!
Isn't it incredible?!
Thank you for contributing tons
of silver to us every month.
He appreciates it, too.
Say hi to the monster
of the New World for me.
Take care of the people with bounties
that we captured as always.
Ring, ring, ring...
What? Okay, I got it.
Something wrong?
He said Straw Hat and Desire
fell into the abyss.
Call Avelon.
Roger that. I'll take
care of them as you say.
DEPARTURE
Off we go!
In front of Luffy and the others who are wandering
around
maze-like underground mineshafts, Bill's
formidable assassin, Avelon, appears!
While he attacks them right
and left with explosives,
the Special Express Avelon's deadly Silver Drill
and Luffy's furious fists clash!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An Underground Maze!
Luffy vs. the Tram Human!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!