kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others left Dressrosa
and are heading for their
next destination, Zou,
to meet up with the other half of their crew.
However, they were attacked by
Battle Boats out of the blue
and Luffy was taken to an unknown island,
Silver Mine along with Bartolomeo.
There, their lives are put in danger
by Bill who is the leader of
the Silver Pirate Alliance!
What?!
Big Sis!
"An Underground Maze!
Luffy vs. the Tram Human!"
Luffy-senpai!
Don't tell me he fell down below!
I can't believe this is happening!
No senpai, no life!
He left his precious straw hat behind...
Hey! Hey!
--Could it be...?!
--Let me out!
--I didn't see that coming!
--I'm glad!
Ouch...
Oh, you're alive, Desire.
He doesn't care at all.
My Battle Boat!
--Thank you!
--Hey!
I need him... Let me take Straw Hat!
What are you talking about?!
I won't let you!
And I'm not gonna forgive you...
...for your act of violence not just against me
but also against the Straw Hats!
We fell pretty far.
How can we get out of here?
Hey, what are those rails?
Somebody, come in!
It won't connect!
How can we go back up?
I don't know this place!
Huh?! I thought this is the
headquarters of your group!
The railcar will soon arrive.
Please wait where you are.
The Silver Pirate Alliance!
I'm a tram human who ate the Roll-Roll Fruit!
AVELON EXPRESS
Avelon Express is on its way!
What?! Is he one of your allies?!
I've never heard of him!
All the passengers who learn about
the underground mineshafts...
...have to be gotten rid of!
Interesting!
Luffy-senpai, watch out!
Luffy-senpai! Are you alright?!
What's with that jerk?!
Why did he try to harm me too?!
I'm gonna turn the railcar around!
Oh no! It's coming again!
Crest Head! Let's get away from here!
--Okay! Help me, Desire!
--What?!
Speeding up! Speeding up!
Running near the tracks is dangerous.
Please do not rush - maintain a walking pace!
No way!
Next stop: Rain of Bombs! Rain of Bombs!
Can't you use your barrier?!
Because of this sticky thing,
I can't make the gesture!
Please be careful!
What?!
Ball walking on the rails
is strictly prohibited.
I see no track ahead!
Oh no!
He's so persistent!
--There's a fork ahead!
--What?!
Which way should we go?!
We don't have time to think! Go right!
You sure?
Crest Head! Go right!
Oh, I got it!
Screw you!
All right!
The next stop is hell!
This train is bound for hell!
What?!
Stop, Straw Hat!
You guys have to stop me!
We can't!
Grandma! What should we
do at a time like this?!
No!
Avelon, how are Straw Hat
and the others doing?
They fell down to the lowest layer.
Be sure to take them out.
Roger that.
Bill-sama!
Clank.
--Big Sis fell...
--Along with Straw Hat and the other!
Don't worry!
I sent the other unit to search for Desire.
What a relief!
Please save Big Sis.
Count on me! Desire is one of my...
...dear friends.
Are you guys okay?!
Barely...
I thought I was gonna die this time...
You're heavy.
You said "Go right" so I...
You listened to Straw Hat, not me!
Warning - downgrade ahead!
Please hold on to the strap!
He'll get here soon!
Damn this ball...  I can't break it!
Humph! Bill's creation can't
be broken that easily!
That's the same guy whose underling tried
to kill you!
He'll never harm his friend!
Cut it out!
Take a good look at the situation you're in!
A traitor like you has no right to say that!
A traitor? What are you talking about?
We made a promise to aim for the top together
but all of a sudden, you said
you wanted to help Straw Hat
to become the King of the Pirates!
That's why I went out to sea with my friends!
Friends?
Then, what happened to your pirate group?!
That's none of your business!
How could you say that?!
It's... gone.
What do you mean?
I once lost...
...everything that I had.
We're lost.
Oh, what's that?!
B-Big Sis...
I-Is this where...
...I'm gonna... die?
Hey!
Are you alright?! Hey!
Stay with me!
I'm glad that there are survivors!
I see!
You're the infamous Desire
from the East Blue!
"The fastest female pirate racer"!
It's my honor to meet you!
I'm not that person anymore.
I was betrayed by a guy I trusted and...
...I lost my friends and my bike,
and now I ended up like this.
How silly I was, to dream
of going to the top...
Don't give up so easily!
I'm gonna dominate the Pirate Era!
But I need trustworthy friends
to accomplish that!
You can have that Battle Boat!
It's not easy to ride but I'm
sure you can make full use of it!
If all of us work together,
our dream will come true!
Would you like to come with me?!
I finally met someone who shared my ideals.
All the people at the
fortress trust Bill too.
So did you come after Luffy-senpai
to please him?!
Yeah, and you told me
about the Straw Hats repeatedly!
So you've been working hard
for your friends like we do!
Your praise doesn't make me happy!
The Bill guy still sounds fishy.
He's way cooler than you or Straw Hat!
Hey! What are you doing there?
Who are you guys?!
Will this do?
Yeah! Thanks!
Let's do it!
Ouch! Ouch! Ow! Ow!
--It's too hot!
--S-Sorry...
It's coming off! One more time!
That's the wisdom of Grandma back home, huh?
Do you know her?
Yeah, I do! There's nothing
that Grandma doesn't know!
This must be Bill's work.
--Can you break it?
--No, we can't.
Were you guys dropped from up there too?
What do you mean "too"?
Who are you people?
And what's this place?
Don't you know anything?
Silver Mine is a rich mine and...
...we're in its underground mineshafts.
We're former members of the
Silver Pirate Alliance.
What?
No matter what, we couldn't please Bill.
Those who can't bring
him treasures or people
with bounties will all be tossed down here
and forced to mine ore
from morning till night.
How horrible he is to
abandon his own friends!
So we're his slaves.
No way! He wouldn't do such
a thing to his friends!
I know it's hard to believe.
But that's the truth.
Hey, isn't there any way to get out of here?!
The railroad is the only connection
between here and up there.
But if we use it,
Avelon will know immediately.
So many people have tried until now
but all of them failed.
Just give up the fight.
What is this alarm?!
Limited Express Avelon will soon arrive!
Avelon?!
I see one ahead of me!
Please mind the bombs again!
Here comes Avelon!
I gotta remove this sticky thing already!
Hey! Did Bill really tell you to...
...get rid of me as well?!
That's right!
I see.
Avelon started running wild!
Rain of Bombs! Rain of Bombs!
Yes! It all came off!
Ow, ow, ow...
Are you guys okay?!
B-Barely...
How about you, Luffy-senpai?!
Oh, senpai! Are you all right?!
I found Straw Hat!
With this drill that was
specially made by Bill,
stand by for Straw Hat impalement!
Oh no!
Luffy-senpai!!
It's off!
It went through! Why isn't he hurt?!
Where were you aiming at?
My body's not that big!
Here we go, Tram!
I'm switching over to Hyper Special Express!
Off we go!
Gum-Gum...
Take this!
...Hammer!
That's my Luffy-senpai!
Second Gear!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
U-Unbelievable! He did it!
Now pulling into the garage!
Wait!
Oh, wait for me! Senpai!
Stand by for track...
...change!
Stop!
You can't run!
Track change!
What a pain in the butt!
Luffy-senpai!
Let me take care of him!
Changing tracks! Changing tracks!
Changing tracks!
No, I can't!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Bazooka!
--He took down Avelon that easily....
--How strong...
AVELON EXPRESS
TERMINAL STATION
See?! I took down Tram!
I fought in collaboration with
Luffy-senpai for the first time!
Hey! Let's get out of here now!
Avelon! Hey, Avelon!
What's wrong?
He's not responding. He must've failed.
If Straw Hat and the others make
it up here, we'll be in trouble!
Then, let's just...
...bury them all.
In front of Luffy and the others
who are climbing over themselves
to get above ground, the next
assassin, Peseta, appears!
Just when the secret weapons
of the Smelt-Smelt Fruit
are
about to burn up everything in the underground mineshafts,
Zoro and the others finally arrive!
Zoro and Peseta's duel, in which
their pride is at stake, begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Sword Technique Heats Up!
Law and Zoro Finally Appear!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!