I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others left Dressrosa
and are heading for their
next destination, Zou,
to meet up with the other half of their crew.
However, they were attacked by Battle Boats
out of the blue
and Luffy was taken to an unknown island,
Silver Mine along with Bartolomeo.
His life was put in danger by Bill who is
the leader of the Silver Pirate Alliance,
and then, fell into an underground mineshaft
where he learned the truth about Bill.
No way!
He wouldn't do such a thing to his friends!
I know it's hard to believe.
But that's the truth.
Hey! Did Bill really tell you to...
...get rid of me as well?!
That's right!
I see.
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Bazooka!
AVELON EXPRESS
TERMINAL STATION
I fought in collaboration with Luffy-senpai
for the first time!
If Straw Hat and the others make
it up here, we'll be in trouble!
Then, let's just...
...bury them all.
"The Sword Technique Heats Up!
Law and Zoro Finally Appear!"
Is this the railroad?
Yes, that one goes highest.
They were using it to carry ore out.
But we don't know what lies ahead.
So we gotta leave the rest to chance,
right, Luffy-senpai?!
All right, let's go!
Okay!
Oh, I'm so thrilled!
By responding to his commands,
I feel like I'm a member of the Straw Hats!
What's wrong?! You guys aren't up for it?
Well, we do wanna get out of here but...
If Bill finds us,
we'll be taken back here again.
In addition, we'll receive
terrible punishment.
What are you guys afraid of?!
Luffy-senpai has the power
of a hundred people!
No, a thousand or 10 thousand or 100 million!
No, no...
That's enough!
But no matter how strong he is,
he is no match for Bill.
I don't wanna have molten metal poured on me
and be turned into a statue!
On top of that, besides Bill,
they have a scary executive called Peseta.
Pffft! Do as you like, then!
Wait!
I've made up my mind!
I'm gonna get out of here with
Straw Hat to go settle things!
Go settle things?
Do you guys wanna spend
the rest of your lives here?
Even if you stay here,
you can't do anything but wait to be killed!
If so, isn't it better to take your chances
and try to get off of the island?!
Show some guts!
If you say you're still a pirate!
I'm going!
Me too!
Huh?! I can't hear you!
We're gonna go along with him!
Okay! Let's go!
Yeah!
Good job making it this far.
Luffy-senpai!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
I'm landing on Luffy-senpai's
Gum-Gum Balloon...
It's a blissful moment!
Why're you sleeping?!
Watch out! The overpass is collapsing!
Let me handle it! Barrier!
Well done, Crest Head!
Thanks! I'm honored I could
be of some help to you!
It's really...
It's really incredible!
Incredible! Incredible!
Peseta! Are these Bill's orders again?!
Of course, they are!
Are you gonna bury these guys alive as well
after driving them so hard?!
Trying to spare just them is...
...incredibly troublesome! So I'll just...
...take care of them along with you guys!
That makes me angry!
Barrier Crush!
It sure is a dangerous barrier as they say.
It's not just dangerous!
Barrier-bility!
Stairs!
Oh! The stairs made of the barrier!
Go ahead and climb them, Luffy-senpai!
Why're you looking the other way?!
All right! Crest Head, I'll go first!
Please take care!
Oh, I mean, I'll come with you!
This is awesome! I'm having so much fun!
If I'm correct, there is
a limit on the size of
the barrier that you can produce at once.
You jerk!
I used it up on the staircase!
Follow Straw Hat!
Climb all the way up quickly!
Yeah!
Peseta-sama! We gotta do something or...
Don't panic!
I already have plan B and C ready.
We'll burn you up!
Shambles!
Ouch!
Excuse me! Foxfire Style!
Fire-Willow Flash!
What?!
Kin'emon!
There's no fire that I can't cut!
Take care of the rest.
What? What?
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
I finally made it above ground!
Luffy-senpai's Elephant Gun!
I got to see such a great thing!
Why are you just standing?
Let's go already!
Oh no, you can't go any farther!
Don't think you won!
It's you again, Penta?!
It's Peseta! Take a look at that!
You guys!
Big Sis Desire!
If you resist, they'll die!
Now, I need you to come
along without fighting!
How cunning!
Peseta! You're really terrible!
Terrible? I don't think so...
You mean incredible, don't you?!
Are you alright?!
Y-Yes!
Zoro!
There he is!
When his friends have their
back against the wall,
he appears at the right moment!
Zoro-senpai!
Luffy, I have to pay him back. Let me do it.
Oh yeah? Okay.
How could you be so composed,
Pirate Hunter Zoro?
You have a bounty of 320 million
but you were pretty
pathetic when we last met!
Laugh at him! Just laugh at him, guys!
That bastard!
How dare he make fun of Zoro-senpai?!
I'm gonna beat the hell out of him!
Luffy-senpai?
He said he'll do it.
Bring it on!
You don't know your place!
I'll immobilize you again!
One-Sword Style iai...
No way! My Adhesive Shell should
stick to anything that it touches!
It'd be shameful for a swordsman
to even let that disgusting
thing touch his blade!
Only Zoro-dono could've done it!
What happened?
Zoro-senpai sliced up all the Adhesive Shells
with just one single slash!
It's far from over yet!
Right?
Hey!
All right!
There! There! There! There!
Three-Sword Style...
...Black Rope Dragon Twister!
Where did that twister come from?!
It's coming this way!
It's terrible!
It's terrible!!
Well done!
Big Sis!
Yeah, now is our chance!
Take everybody to the port!
We'll leave the island!
Okay! But what are you gonna do?
I'll come after I settle things.
Then, we'll come with you!
It's a problem of my own making.
Let me do it on my own.
All right. Promise us you'll come back!
We won't leave until you come back!
Okay!
All right! Let's go, everyone!
You guys saved our lives!
Thank you!
Bye!
Do you wanna settle things with Bill?
--It's none of your business.
--Do you still believe in that jerk?
No, it's quite the opposite.
Anyway, let me settle something
with you, Straw Hat.
What?
I apologize to you for my rudeness till now.
I'm sorry!
Never mind! The chocolate
you gave me was delicious!
Let's go! Usopp and the others
are waiting at the ship.
Now, it's only a matter of time
before enemy boats attack us!
We must hurry up too!
Bye!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ow, ow!
That was close!
What a shame.
The sum total of Straw Hat and Pirate
Hunter's bounties is 820 million
and it was my chance to
capture them both at once.
Bill!
--Luffy!
--We'll back you up!
No, just go ahead!
But...
Take care of Usopp and the others.
Let's go.
Understood.
Forget about Pirate Hunter.
But I'm not gonna let a man with
a bounty of 500 million get away,
Straw Hat.
Guys! Franky-senpai has taken the trouble to
repair this Mister Luffy Go!
Don't let them damage it any more!
Yeah!
Go! Special Attack: Green Star - Sea Devil!
Dodge!
Weapon's Left!
Mil Fleurs...
...Gigantesco Mano!
They keep coming, one after another!
--Isn't Straw Hat-ya here yet?
--I guess he's having trouble.
Luffy...
Straw Hat.
I'm the one who must settle things with him!
Hmmm, "settle things"?
My way of settling things is
to collect all the bounties!
I'm gonna smelt you along
with this mine for that!
What?!
If you do that, your subordinates will...
What's the problem?
Their bounties are so low
compared to Straw Hat and the others
but it's better than nothing,
in order to make my dream come true!
Your dream is
to dominate the Pirate Era, isn't it?!
That's what you told me when
you saved me, isn't it?!
Saved you? Yeah, I did save you.
Since you had the capability
to lead a girl gang,
I thought I could use you...
What did you say?!
Don't tell me you were the one
who sank our boats that day...
That's right!
It was me!
I sank them and saved you.
Didn't I perform as good as a stage actor?
And guess what?
The simple minded idiot
that you are got wrapped up
in my dream like a loyal dog.
That's what this is all about.
You bastard...
That's unforgivable...
How dare you...
...take advantage of our compassion!
Your tears are pathetic.
Guild Tesoro, the golden
emperor behind the curtain,
brings out Bill's hidden ability!
When Luffy's angry fist clashes with Bill
who rages out of control in blazing fire,
the battle in Silver Mine
finally comes to a climax!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Desperate Situation! Luffy
Fights a Battle in Extreme Heat!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!