I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others left Dressrosa
and are heading for their
next destination, Zou,
to meet up with the other half of their crew.
However, they were attacked by
Battle Boats out of the blue
and Luffy was taken to an unknown island,
Silver Mine along with Bartolomeo.
Straw Hat, you'll join them.
This is where your voyage ends.
I ate the Smelt-Smelt Fruit
and became a blast-furnace human.
My body is an ultra-hot blast furnace.
I can smelt ore and produce
all kinds of things.
I'll turn you into a nice silver statue
befitting of a man with a bounty of 500 million!
Their lives were put in danger by Bill
who is the leader of the
Silver Pirate Alliance,
and while fighting one of his underlings,
Desire, who was also Bartolomeo's
childhood friend,
they fell into an underground mineshaft
where they learned the truth about Bill.
Shambles!
They defeated Bill's right-hand man, Peseta,
with help from Zoro and the others
and managed to return above ground
only to confront Bill again.
What did you say?!
Don't tell me you were the one
who sank our boats that day...
That's right!
It was me!
I sank them and saved you.
Didn't I perform as good as a stage actor?
And guess what?
The simple minded idiot that you are
got wrapped up in my dream like a loyal dog.
That's what this is all about.
You bastard...
That's unforgivable...
How dare you...
...take advantage of our compassion!
Your tears are pathetic.
"A Desperate Situation!
Luffy Fights a Battle in Extreme Heat!"
Pathetic! Oh, so pathetic!
Boy, pirates are such hopeless people.
You guys really believe in immature things
like dreams and stuff.
You're little better than kids.
But you were very handy!
Just by dangling a dream in front of you,
you scum became enthralled
and worked hard for me!
Without knowing all the treasures
and the people with bounties you brought to me...
...would be used for me to live
the most luxurious life in the world,
you guys were working your butts off all day!
By the way,
what brought you here now, Desire?
You said you wanted to "settle things."
You're not thinking you
can defeat me, are you?
What?! I'm so underestimated!
All right. Bring it on!
Hey, what's wrong? Huh?! Bring it on!
In that case, I'm gonna
smelt you first as you wish!
Straw Hat!
You're kind of irritating.
--Wait! He's...
--Desire!
Leave it to Luffy-senpai.
Such pure eyes...
They make me wanna puke!
I'll chop you up!
Damn!
--Well done as always!
--He's so strong...
You can't bring me down.
So this is how strong a person
with a bounty of 500 million is!
Bill!
Is that Desire?!
Why's she with Straw Hat and the other one?!
Listen to me!
You guys were all fooled by Bill...
Desire betrayed us!
She went over to Straw Hat's side
and is looking to destroy
the Silver Pirate Alliance!
She already took down Avelon and Peseta!
What?!
That means we've been attacked
by the Straw Hats because...
Desire masterminded it.
What are you talking about?!
Guys, don't be fooled!
It's no use, Desire.
I saw our friends who were abandoned by Bill,
working as slaves under the ground here!
What?
Whoa-whoa! You guys are my friends
and you know I wouldn't
do such a thing to you!
Take down the traitor!
Kill Straw Hat and the other one!
--How dare he say that without shame...
--Well, I saw that coming.
Go!
They're so naive.
They'll break before me like my shield...
Straw Hat! They're just being fooled!
Don't treat them roughly!
There you are, Smelt-Smelt!
No way!
Luffy-senpai!
--Now, let's go back to everyone else.
--Okay!
H-He's something else...
How pathetic of you to be defeated
by a damn pirate.
That was the extent of your greed?
I guess the Monster of the New World will be
quite disappointed in you.
If he discards you, that'll be it for you.
The Monster of the New World...
He's a king of greed...
...who once brought my
pirate crew to our knees
so easily with the power of money.
The face of those giving in to me...
That's entertainment!
If he...
...discards me...
Not yet! It's not over for me yet!
Aren't you eating too much?
I guess you know what you're doing.
Then, let's see what you can do.
It's kind of hot!
You're right.
Still wanna fight?!
What?
What's going on?
The ground is...!
There are so many of them!
There's no end to this!
One-Sword Style 360-Pound Phoenix!
Zoro! Kin'emon!
Where's Straw Hat-ya?!
We got to see him but...
They said they wanted to
settle things themselves.
If we stay here, they'll come.
What?!
How can he be so easygoing?
I'm glad that they're fine.
What the...! It's all melting!
What's with that guy?
Is he even human?
That's Bill.
B-Bill?!
I thought he was a blast-furnace human!
He's a Paramythia-type
Devil Fruit eater, right?!
But that's more like Logia!
You can't get away!
It's totally like an inferno!
If nothing is done,
the whole island might melt away!
That's probably what he wants!
He wants to completely smelt everything
along with us!
What?!
Let's retreat for now!
You can't go anywhere!
Barrier!
Watch out!
Our retreat is being cut off!
I'm gonna smelt everyone
who I don't have use for!
It's flowing in from the side too!
Desire, are you alright?!
Luffy-senpai!
Oh no!
Let go of my hand, Bartolomeo!
Aren't you gonna help Straw
Hat who you respect so much
become the King of the Pirates?!
Cut the crap! I'm not gonna let go!
You're my friend!
Even if I become rotten,
I'm not gonna cast aside a friend!
Friend?
But you did cast me aside!
What? Did I?
Now, this is it!
That was so close!
Thanks!
Don't mention it!
I'll back you up with all my
might since my support came late!
Go, go, Luffy-senpai!
Shut up!
Crest Head!
Can you do something about this hot stuff?
I'll handle it for you, of course!
Get rid of it if you can!
Barrier-bility!
Big Hand!
Did we do it?!
No, not yet!
You worthless pirates...
I know what none of you know.
A childish thing...
...like a dream...
...won't help you...
...survive the New World!
Aiming for the top?!
Becoming the King of the Pirates?!
I'm gonna shatter your dreams!
Shut up!
Gum-Gum...
...Grizzly...
...Magnum!
Yes!
I can't believe I fought
hand-in-hand with Luffy-senpai!
My extraordinary dream came true!
Hey, look!
Why hasn't the situation changed?
All the molten metal that Bill produced
is made from real ore!
So it won't just go away
even if you took him down!
Then, how can we get off of this island?!
You tell me!
Hey, that's...
--Hurry up!
--Come on!
--Alright, don't rush.
--You're okay now!
Thank you!
Hey! Let us get on board too!
Get on already!
--We better leave now!
--Big Sis and the others aren't here yet!
We can't wait anymore! Set sail!
Big Sis!
Th-Th-Th-That doesn't look good, does it?!
Don't we have to go help those two?!
Don't worry!
The Vivre Card is moving -
that means he's still okay.
Luffy won't drop dead
from something of this level.
Oh? The island is sinking.
That's really not good!
Luffy-san and our captain
are Devil Fruit eaters!
There they are!
Hey!
We're back!
Welcome back, you two!
I told you.
This feels great!
Big Sis!
You guys!
Oh! I'm glad they're okay too!
We were really taken care of by you guys.
Yeah, you were.
Don't ever get fooled by a bad guy again.
Oh, I'm sorry!
Yeah, and...
...if you have nowhere to go,
THE GROUP THAT HELPS LUFFY-SENPAI TO BECOME
THE KING OF THE PIRATES - BARTO CLUB
I can let you join the Barto Club.
Let's hang out together like we used to!
Let's hang out!
Bartolomeo...
I'll pass on that one because I'm
not really a fan of Straw Hat.
On top of that, I've had enough
of riding in the back seat.
From now on, we're gonna rise to the
top of the world of the sea on our own!
That's our new dream!
That's right!
Don't push your luck!
You have no chance against Luffy-senpai!
You won't know until I try!
You'll be sorry for this!
It's obvious!
You two are really funny!
--Now, let's go!
--Okay!
Wait!
Goodbye.
--Alright, we gotta get going too!
--Yes, Big Sis!
Take care!
See ya!
Guys! Let's set sail for Zou!
Yeah!
So that's Grantesoro...
...where the Monster of the New World...
...who has power that equals that
of the Celestial Dragons, lives.
The ore deposits at Silver Mine
sank along with Bill, Tesoro-sama.
Yeah? Well, that's okay.
I've already had quite
a lot of fun with Bill.
The real entertainment starts from now.
Dense fog and a turbulent current keep
people away from the legendary island, Zou!
In a mysterious 1000-year-old country
where the
native inhabitants, the
Mink Tribe, reign supreme,
the curtain rises on Luffy's
exciting new adventure!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Curtain-up on a New Adventure!
Arriving at the Phantom Island, Zou!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!