kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
Help!
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
Shanks!
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Get lost!
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Monkey D. Luffy!
and his friends venture into that sea.
Zoro!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Hey, don't cry! You're a man!
Chopper!
Robin!
After leaving the fateful island, Dressrosa,
Franky!
Brook!
But... Shanks!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
Luffy and the others headed
for the unknown island,
Zou, following Nami and
the others who went ahead.
...are making their way through the vast sea
Your arm!
with their sights set on the One Piece!
Is this the island, Zou?!
It's only an arm. It's no big deal.
No, that's strange!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
I'm just glad you're alright...
No, this is it.
Tra-guy! But this is a zou (elephant)!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
Yeah, Zou is the name of a place
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
that flourishes on the back
of a massive elephant.
You'll never be a pirate!
The enormous island is
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
which is as high as the clouds, is
actually an elephant which has
been alive for a millennium.
I will too!
"The New Warlord!
The Legendary Whitebeard's Son Appears!"
Someday, I'm gonna gather a crew
every bit as good as yours,
as its name suggests, a zou (elephant)
that has been alive for a millennium.
and I'm gonna find the greatest treasure
in the world,
An animal?! A human?!
"A Deadly Elephant Climb!
A Great Adventure on the Back of the Giant Elephant!"
and I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!
I'll show you!
H-Hey, you!
Where did you get that outfit?!
It's awesome!
So this is the back of the elephant!
You're gonna surpass us, huh?
What did you do to Nami?!
We don't have time to
transport you-teia guys!
To meet up with Sanji,
Nami, Chopper, and Brook,
Do as I say!
In that case...
Luffy and the others set foot on Zou
Go through the Rightrump Forest to your right
and turn left at a deep dark swamp!
...I'll leave this hat with you.
and encountered the Mink Tribe
who are known for disliking humans.
It's dear to me.
Wow! It's huge!
And you'll reach the Rightflank Forest!
Take good care of it!
You'll find
the corpse of your-teia friend there!
C-Corpse?!
Come bring it back to me someday!
What the...?!
Wait! Stop, Carrot!
Once you've become a great pirate!
Gum-Gum...
That's our promise, Luffy!
Moo Golova!
The "thing" that Luffy and
the rest are riding is
Here comes something else!
...Bell!
Forget about them-teia!
currently climbing the left
hind leg of the giant elephant.
More importantly, we have an
invader in the Whale Forest!
"Curtain-up on a New Adventure!
Arriving at the Phantom Island, Zou!"
They're the Mink Tribe!
Oh?! I-Isn't that outfit...
Following Nami and the others who they parted with
at Dressrosa,
Luffy and the gang are heading
It's so high - I'm scared!
...Nami's?!
MISTER LUFFY GO
to the next island, Zou.
My arms are exhausted! It's too much!
Hey! Sanji! Nami!
Don't say that, Usopp.
He's giving it all he's got.
Wow! Shanks appears in the story already?!
Chopper! Brook! Momo!
Oh? That's...
This country was ruined by...
That's our Luffy-senpai!
What?! D-D-Don't tell me it's...
Isn't that amazing?! It's so amazing!
Where are you?!
Oh, and the gas guy.
Well, forget about him.
...Jack!
What?! Whoa-whoa!
Jack...
Hey! Somebody, respond!
What are you doing, Boss?!
You look very excited...
What's going on?!
The Sunny!
There'll be a Rain-Ruption!
Scary!
Climb a tree!
I was just telling everyone a series
of legends that I learned by
Usopp, you fool! Don't pull me!
"A Battle Begins!
Luffy vs. the Mink Tribe!"
A Rain-Ruption?!
interviewing Luffy-senpai and the others!
Get on Warney!
I'll take you to the Rightflank!
What?!
You guys can hear it too so just sit down!
Your friends are there!
If we fall into the sea, that'll be it!
Shut up!
Go on already!
So that's...
Dragon, you can do it!
Please, Boss!
"Garchu!
The Straw Hats Reunite!"
That's...
All right!
...the grand ship that carries
the sacred bodies of the Straw Hats!
A decade later,
Luffy-senpai left Windmill Village
and met Roronoa Zoro-senpai, also known as
Okay! Good job!
The Thousand Sunny-senpai!
I feel blessed! I feel blessed!
You showed some guts!
Pirate Hunter, at a Navy base.
A-Attaboy, Dragon...
Hurry up, everybody! Evacuate!
I feel blessed!
"Pirate Hunter"... What a cool name!
No, your name is Ryunosuke from now on!
Our friend, Ryunosuke!
Don't worship it!
Good! So they made it to Zou for sure.
A girl tried to feed him rice balls.
Go, Warney!
All right! So just let go of me!
I guess they got away from Big Mom nicely.
But a Navy soldier stomped on them.
There's no major damage.
It's quite strong!
Hey! Sanji!
So cute...
He scared the crap out of me.
This shaking is no good!
Nami! Chopper! Brook! Momo!
I wish he could fly.
Is this dragon okay?
It was good. Thank you for the food.
And... what was the gas guy's name?
Oh? What's this place?
What are you talking about?
You just saw how he held on, didn't you?
There's no response.
Alright, you can do it, Ryunosuke! Go!
Wow! Cool!
What the hell is that?!
It's huge!
We're back where we started though.
What are you...?!
If I climb on it, I think I can
get a good view of this island!
That doesn't work!
W-Who the hell are you?!
I'm Luffy!
Hey! Sanji! Nami!
The man who's gonna be
the King of the Pirates!
Here comes a Rain-Ruption!
Chopper! Brook! Momo!
--What the...?!
--The elephant's leg is moving!
I'll be your pirate,
if I'm just gonna die here instead!
Where are you?!
But I'll tell you this right now.
I can't see the top yet.
I'm only going to fulfill my ambition!
I wonder how Sanji and
the others climbed this.
What is that weapon?
I felt a shock for a moment!
To be the world's greatest swordsman!
Are they really up there?
Kin'emon, Kanjuro.
That sounds great!
We have an invader in the Whale Forest?!
The King of the Pirates would need
someone like that on his crew!
Come to think of it, why
do you wanna go to Zou?
Yes, we're in trouble!
Oh! It's flying towards us!
Oh yeah.
The Guardians will be mad!
Gum-Gum...
We owe you people a lot
so we must tell you everything eventually.
What?!
An animal?! A human?!
...Pistol!
A big splash of water?!
H-Hey, you!
Where did you get that outfit?!
But first, we need to feel safe.
It'll cause floods!
Get to high ground!
Mm-hm. Zou was always our destination
since leaving the Land of Wano.
Run!
What did you do to Nami?!
Nice!
Are they a cannibal tribe?
But...
We want to see if Momonosuke is okay
Zoro.
It's too late!
Don't say such a scary thing!
My pleasure, Captain.
and if another friend we
were separated from at sea
- Raizo, a ninja, has arrived here safely.
Here it comes!
"Three-Sword Style"
Zoro-senpai who was looking
to become the world's greatest swordsman...
Hang on tight!
--A ninja?!
--Is he a ninja?!
went on a journey with Luffy-senpai.
What the...
A ninja... I wanna meet him!
How awesome is that?!
I wanna see a shuriken.
Will he sit under a waterfall?
I'm a thief who steals from pirates!
The name's Nami!
Can he really use supernatural ninja powers?
What are you? A monster?!
Hey, wanna team up with me?!
Can he disappear in an instant like they say?
Cat Burglar Nami-senpai!
What are you guys...
Yes, indeed!
I'm sorry! Don't eat me!
She was a thief who was stealing
treasure from pirates.
Tell us! What kind of powers does he use?!
Wait!
Look how high she can jump!
Hey! Keep up with it!
Um, for example, being able to see far away.
Do all of them have physical
abilities like that?!
But she had a good reason for it...
Aye, sir, Boss!
Oh?
Barrier-bility: Stairs!
Ninpo - Telescopic Technique!
So these are your true colors, huh?
Cool!
How is it?!
Do you see something, Carrot?!
Surprised? It was all an act.
Hey! Stop talking gibberish!
--Carrot!
--I got it!
I'm a pirate, plain and simple!
And an officer of the Arlong Pirates!
Oh, so it wasn't true.
What?
Luffy! Look up!
Something's falling onto us!
I do! Maybe it's a little too late!
For many years, her home
village was under the control
Straw Hat!
of a Fish-Man named Arlong
On the other side of Kurau City,
there's a disturbance in the Whale Forest!
What is that?!
and she was trying to buy it back
with the money she had
Etetetetete...
I thought so! Let's go, Warney!
risked her own life to collect.
"Ete"?
That's right! Raizo runs
with that kind of rhythm.
Get on, Carrot!
Okay!
I think he has this kind of power.
We don't have time to
transport you-teia guys!
Luffy...
Ninpo - Blindfold Technique!
Guess who!
Do as I say!
Help me...
D-Did it stop?
Go through the Rightrump Forest to your right
I-Is it Kanjuro?
I mean I know you're the only person there.
No, the leg on the other side is
about to move forward now!
and turn left at a deep dark swamp!
Look out! Duck!
Look out!
And you'll reach the Rightflank Forest!
This one will move again soon!
You'll find the corpse of
your-teia friend there!
All of you senpai, hurry up and cross over...
C-Corpse?!
Of course I will!
Hey! Stop the silly ninpo nonsense...
Oh?
Are you okay, Straw Hat?
Where did they go?
Oh! They're already crossing!
You saved me... Thanks!
Oh no! Those two fell!
Wait at the Rightflank Forest!
We'll be there later!
Luffy! Have you seen the others?
Damn! What was that thing that
fell on us out of the blue?!
Seems like they aren't here.
Nami!
Y-You've got to be kidding!
Please tell me you're kidding!
What?!
I don't know. I think it was a bloody person
with knives stuck all over his body...
Meanwhile, Kin'emon and Kanjuro are
climbing the elephant's left leg...
I guess they all made landfall.
You're my friend!
Yeah! Let's catch up to them quickly!
What?!
Or just a small monkey.
Do you think they-teia are gonna be okay?
Finally, it stopped.
What was the shaking all about?
Yeah!
All right, take care, guys!
You're scaring me!
What made you think that?!
--Those were the Straw Hats.
--What?
That was the moment the navigator
Nami-senpai joined the crew.
You're coming with us!
Hey! Are you alright?!
They-teia are gonna be shocked.
I don't know.
Hey! Are you alright?!
F-Friend...
But we're coming to the crucial point.
Hold on, cat! Nekozaemon!
THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY'S GENERAL HEADQUARTERS
BALTIGO, GRAND LINE
It's a shame but there's nothing we can do.
What's done is done.
Dragon-san!
I-I wish I could hear him saying that to me!
Rebel armies are winning
Kin'emon! Kanjuro!
all across the world!
The one who just invaded the Whale Forest
is probably a pirate, Straw Hat Luffy.
MONKEY D. DRAGON
THE GENERAL COMMANDER
OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
The fall of the Donquixote Family
Now hurry up!
The sun is setting, Nekozaemon!
Kin'emon! Kanjuro!
had a huge impact.
Bye, everyone! I'll be back!
He's their-teia captain but I'm sure
the Guardians will show no mercy!
This many countries were involved
--Did they fall into the water?
--Let's go save them!
in the weapon trafficking.
Luffy-dono! We're both okay!
Isn't it too much for a cat
to climb this elephant?
The war situation is looking up.
But tell them not to be too
excited over their win.
Kanjuro!
I am Usopp, leader of the great pirates
who reign over this village!
--That's Kin'emon!
--Good! They're alive!
No, it's not.
Cats are good tree climbers.
Yes, sir!
Go ahead! We'll catch up soon!
The World Government won't
just sit by quietly.
They were killed!
They are!
People praise me - and then praise me more -
as "Captain Usopp"!
Cipher Pol has been
reinforced in recent years.
What is he talking about? No way!
Let's go back down!
She said there's a corpse -
which means they weren't cannibalized.
So tell them to take extra care.
Yes, sir!
Hey, Dragon! Head back down!
Water?!
That's not the problem! Cut it out!
In Syrup Village, they met Usopp-senpai.
What?!
Dragon-san.
He was known as the biggest
talker in the village.
Oh, that's water overflowing from a
Rain-Ruption that poured over the country...
They say they found a
special ore in the weapons
Calm down!
Ryunosuke, head back...
Old "Spiral Eyebrows" is with them.
He won't let anyone be killed.
we brought back from Dressrosa.
Water is no good! It will melt Nekozaemon!
But he's actually a manly man
who'll stand up to his enemy
An ore?
Yeah. They're not gonna
be killed that easily!
Hey, Ryunosuke...
at the risk of his life when the need arises!
Do you know of Drunken Iron Ore?
There is no time to lose...
But again, halfway to the top, we...
This must be a trick to make
us upset and submissive!
It's quite rare
and only a few countries can mine it,
Even if I'm no match for him...
You're right. I can't believe it.
so they might be able to figure out
where the weapons were actually made.
I will protect them!
Oh, that's good news.
How can I calm down?!
I mean, didn't you hear what she said?!
THE WHALE FOREST - LUFFY AND THE OTHERS
How can we tell this poor guy
to go back...
Yes.
I'm a brave warrior of the sea!
You brought back our people who
went missing in Dressrosa too.
She said "corpse," okay?!
Oh, that was a hell of a rain!
You're doing remarkably well.
They must've killed Nami and the others
and ripped off their clothes!
I won't let you lay a finger on the village!
Seems like he wants to finish his job
as soon as possible.
Please! I couldn't do it
without Sabo-kun and Luffy-kun!
Rain-Ruptions aren't actually a type of rain.
Are they the only tribe
living on this island?
He's suffering.
Let's let him keep going.
How was Robin?
Twice a day, Zunesha sprays water on itself.
Why is an outsider like you
butting into this village's business?!
I heard she was caught in Sabaody
but that was completely false.
Are they really a cannibal tribe?
We need to check these things out.
So cute...
I'm sorry but we're gonna go ahead!
See you guys later!
Yes, it was! She was totally full of life!
Why are you so obsessed
with cannibal tribes?!
Because there's a man in this village
I don't wanna let die!
Almost like...
Understood!
Aren't you gonna ask me about Luffy-kun?
We have to find out
if they're our enemies or not.
Hey! I won't allow you to enter the country!
H-Here it comes!
You're right but I'm scared!
Go ahead!
So that was a blast of seawater.
Well, I've had more than enough with that.
That was where they met the
Going Merry-senpai too!
Huh? I think I just heard an unknown voice.
Oh, I bet Sabo-kun told you a lot.
First, we have to collect information.
The water passes through a filtration system
at the center of the city to aqueducts
You guys take care, too!
Let's meet again sometime!
Tra-guy-kun.
Anyway, Koala.
Your friends must be here, right?
Yes.
How come?
and becomes the drinking water
for the whole nation.
Get on already.
We need their help.
Yeah.
We're friends now, aren't we?
--Is there any way to make contact?
--No.
Their?
I didn't even expect to see them again.
Fish fall along with the seawater
so we'd never run out of food.
As a sniper looking to
become a brave warrior of the sea,
Summon all the leaders of the Revolutionary
Army from all over the world!
But now I remember.
Usopp-senpai joined the crew!
I forgot that I had a Vivre Card.
Okay.
Rain-Ruptions provide us with a lot.
What?! Do you really wanna summon
all those big personalities again?!
It belongs to our navigator, Bepo.
Luffy-senpai needed a cook
A SEA SOMEWHERE IN THE NEW WORLD
Hey, Straw Hat!
Oh yeah, you had a talking
polar bear in your crew!
and that's when he met
Sanji-senpai who was working at
Oh, the bear!
Come on, Ryunosuke!
Is he a Mink too?!
I can't leave this forest
a floating restaurant as a sous-chef.
You can do it!
Yeah.
so can you tell our captain about us
and bring him here?!
This is where he came from.
Luffy!
Hey, Luffy!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
How can you sleep
when Ryunosuke is trying so hard?!
Oh, you can't? Okay!
But he didn't remember much
about this island.
Eat it.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
I'm counting on you!
Sorry...
Because he left the island
when he was little.
Bepo was born here
but since he's a pirate,
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Hey, look!
It's pretty damn delicious, isn't it?
This is Lafitte.
It is!
Isn't that the top?!
he's now under the care of
Master Cat Viper, the boss of the forest.
Can we trust him?!
For instance, just for instance, you know,
I found a good cook!
This... urgess.
What?
Oh! It is!
This restaurant is that
damn geezer's treasure!
A little more to go, Ryunosuke!
he might become aware of his nature
as a member of the cannibal tribe!
It's me!
Burgess! It's you!
I... I can't repay the damn geezer
for his kindness...
The top?!
You have a pretty wild imagination too!
"DEMON SHERIFF" LAFITTE
THE CAPTAIN OF THE FIFTH SHIP OF
THE EMPEROR - BLACKBEARD'S PIRATE GROUP
We went to Dressrosa to pick you up
Alright! Ryunosuke! Way to go!
but you weren't there.
KURAU CITY - ZORO AND THE OTHERS
It's flooding!
Yeah, sorry.
...unless I risk my life for him too!
I've known him for a decade.
We can trust him.
Watch out! That was close!
There's a shark! A shark?! Why?!
I couldn't make contact since I was
unconscious almost the whole time.
Dying isn't something you should do
to repay kindness!!
You went way too high!
This is high enough.
If you wanna get reliable information,
let's head straight.
What?
SHIRYU OF THE RAIN
THE CAPTAIN OF THE SECOND SHIP OF
THE EMPEROR - BLACKBEARD'S PIRATE GROUP
Seawater?
No! He fell off!
Oh, that son of a gun was alive.
Say...
Oh, I looked around from up there before!
If we go straight, there'll be a town!
Maybe, that was the giant elephant
spraying water on itself.
--What are you guys doing?!
--Oh my...
do you know the All Blue?
Where've you been?
Luffy! Do something!
No...
We don't know who are there!
Are we gonna be okay?!
Where are you now?
Wait.
Got it!
It's all white...
The cannibal tribe might be there.
It seems like both the town and the forest
are adapted to this water level.
We both have foolish dreams.
It's an island as white as snow.
Yes!
All right!
In order to achieve my goal, the All Blue...
Well, seeing the water amount...
I guess you're right!
It's better than going along
with the unknown animal.
I've been hiding in the bottom of this ship.
Let's follow him.
Hey, Luffy, you idiot! Don't!
That means this happens every day...
Sanji?
Yeah. I'll come along...
D-Don't fall!
Hang on, Ryunosuke!
Tell Captain Teech!
on your journey to become
the "King of the Pirates"!
If we invade here now, we can
get a massive amount of weapons!
I mean I'm gonna fall! Help, Robin!
IN THE WHALE FOREST
What?
I'll be the cook for your ship.
--Good luck.
--What?!
Gum-Gum...
I wouldn't want that tremendous
downpour every day!
It's Commodore Teech.
How many times do I have to tell you?
I'm so scared! Help me!
Moo Golova!
Make sure to bring Doc Q too!
I'm fatally injured!
We must find everybody quickly
and get off of this annoying island!
Is that okay or not?
...Bell!
It's okay!!
Burgess! Tell us already! Where are you?
All right!!
Okay, I'm back!
Owner Zeff!!
I don't know the name of the island.
Shut up!
What are you gonna do about this?!
It's a totally uncharted place.
Ryunosuke! Hang tough!
Hey, there's Luffy!
At the edge of the town!
Follow my Vivre Card and come here!
Don't tell him to hang tough!
It's your fault!
Thank you for all the damn things you've
done for me over all these years!!
He's with the Nami-dog girl
and the jump rabbit from before!
Dragon and the obnoxious Sabo are here too!
Dragon, you can do it!
Ryunosuke! Please!
Why isn't Electro having any effect?!
He's getting fooled
and being taken to their lair...
Give it all you've got! As soon as you can!
Ryunosuke! Show your manliness!
I'll never forget your kindness...
I've found it!
What is it, Usopp?!
Luffy's been eaten a little!
It's the Revolutionary Army's
general headquarters!
...for the rest of my life!!
What?! So they're really...
Sanji-senpai is a first
class chef of the sea!
A cannibal tribe!
I hope I can meet him soon
and see his kicking techniques!
Get fired up, Ryunosuke!
Show some guts, Dragon!
Hey! Hurry up, Ryunosuke!
My legs can't take it any longer!
I told you to stop biting me!
Isn't that... backwards?
Ryunosuke, come on!
To cure Nami-senpai's disease,
they stopped by at a Winter Island.
AN ISLAND SOMEWHERE
Everyone's so dumb and ridiculous!
So cute...
And there, they met
"Cotton Candy Lover" Tonytony Chopper-senpai!
They all say the same thing!
The whole town is soaked in water.
He's a human-reindeer hybrid
because of eating the Human-Human Fruit.
Alright, Ryunosuke! Attaboy!
That the members of the Whitebeard Pirates
are Whitebeard's only sons!
The water will drain away soon.
A little more to go!
We're almost there! Go!
He used to have no friends
because of his outlandish look.
What's wrong with you-gara?!
How can you be unhurt after
getting that attack?!
The top is close at hand!
EDWARD WEEVIL - A WARLORD
SELF-PROCLAIMED "WHITEBEARD JR."
(FORMER BOUNTY: 480 MILLION BERRIES)
Mommy! Mommy!
But he's a good doctor who studied
advanced medical care under his mentors.
I'm Whitebeard's son, right?!
That didn't work
because I'm made of rubber.
My beard's white as well!
Rubber?
That's right, dear!
Ahh!
It's my turn!
Oh! So fast!
The Whitebeard Pirates were
just a make-believe family.
You'd better be prepared if you're gonna
meddle with someone else's skull flag!
Ryunosuke! Make a final sprint!
You're the only biological son of
the world's strongest pirate, Whitebeard!
I know he's here!
Gum-Gum...
Keep going! Ryunosuke!
I told you he's not!
Just a little more to go! Run!
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
And I'm...
You're almost there!
...Bazooka!!
MISS BUCKIN - WEEVIL'S MOTHER
SELF-PROCLAIMED "WHITEBEARD'S LOVER"
...the woman who Whitebeard loved!
You're almost there! You're almost there!
Bring him here or this
country will be destroyed!
You're almost there! You're almost there!
I can't become your friend!
I don't know what you're talking about!
So hold your head up, my treasure!
Yes! I'm starting to see something!
Shut up! Let's go!
Gum-Gum...
You're hurting me, Mommy!
Ryunosuke! Come on! It's right there!
--Look at this!
--What? Is that a mirror?
...Bell!
Luffy-senpai welcomed Chopper-senpai
as the ship's doctor.
I really don't know! What else can I say?!
No, it's a picture of Whitebeard!
Ryunosuke! Ryunosuke! Ryunosuke! Ryunosuke!
Oh, I thought that was a mirror.
He's so great!
You look so much like him - there's
no way you're not his son!
How can you be so silly?!
Ryunosuke! Ryunosuke!
I keep getting moved to tears!
Oh, sorry, Mommy!
You can do it, Ryunosuke!
But I forgive you.
That's...
Because I love you!
Yeah, that's Straw Hat!
Mommy!
Now, let's go!
Say what you've got to do!
That's it! Stop right there!
I know him!
B-B-B-B...
Ummm...
Even if you know him, he's an invader!
Believe it or not,
Robin-senpai and Franky-senpai
were their enemies at first!
I guess we gotta stop you by force!
I forgot.
Find the remnants of the Whitebeard Pirates
like Marco the Phoenix!
Don't get in our way!
Who were you talking about?
What?!
You told me the name of the guy
who attacked this country before.
No! Jean Bart!
And get something back!
His name is Jack.
We made it!
--Damn! This is too much to handle!
--He's too strong!
Your father Newgate must've left
behind a big fortune
To the top!
I saw his obituary in the newspaper
a few days ago.
But Robin-senpai who was also
known as Demon Child,
We finally made it!
and you're the true heir
since you're his biological son!
Keep napping.
Ryunosuke! Good job!
was traveling along with
the crew since Alabasta.
It said, after he overran this country,
Oh, I see, I see.
We're here at Zou!
And Franky-senpai first appeared
as the leader of the Franky Family...
he attacked four Navy ships
that were transporting Doflamingo
I'm gonna knock you down!
Ryunosuke...
...in the City of Water - Water Seven!
and sank two of them but they struck back.
I'm... proud of you.
Robin!
Oh yeah! But what I really
wanna do is get revenge!
What?! Was he there at Dressrosa?!
Come on!
I've come to get you!
He attacked the ships with the Navy admiral
and the former fleet admiral on board.
I wanna have my revenge on
Blackbeard for killing Daddy!
Oh no!
You're turning back to a drawing.
When Roddy gets mad like that,
I'll kill him!
He must have a screw loose.
I won't forgive him at any price!
Just leave the rest to us!
no one can stop him!
Hey, Ryunosuke!
You did it! Well done!
Silly boy! What's the
point in taking revenge?
It said his death wasn't confirmed.
If... I'm allowed to make a small wish...
You can't even earn one berry!
I think he's still alive.
Hey, wait!
We want money!
You must inherit his fortune!
Ryunosuke!
I...
We'll never forgive Jack!
--Ryunosuke!
You're right, Mommy!
Wait a minute!
We haven't really thanked you yet!
I want to live!!
Take me to the seas with you!
Ryunosuke!
What's the matter, Mommy?
Doflamingo was defeated.
Ryunosuke!
Bring it on!
It's him again! Garp's grandson!
We're gonna go back together!
They say Marco and the others tried
to protect him in the Paramount War.
That's enough, Guardians!
Robin!
Then, maybe he knows something about Marco.
Ryunosuke!
A fluttering object!
Should we go beat him up?
Ryunosuke!
A banana!
Oh, the water's gone.
Come on. Get on, Franky.
Thank you!
The ground is soft
because it's the elephant's back, right?
On my ship.
Ryunosuke! Ryunosu...
That's right.
Fine. I suppose I can
take care of it for you.
We have to hurry! Let's take a shortcut!
--This is absurd.
--It's just a bad drawing.
I, Franky, will take on the role of
the shipwright for your crew!
Don't get shaken off!
Hey, hold it right there, you bastards!
Is that how you thank him
for bringing you up here?!
Robin-senpai as an archeologist
who is searching
We're in unknown territory.
We shouldn't look back.
"BUGGY TOWN"
EMPTEE BLUFFS ISLAND, NEW WORLD
for the truth of the 100-Year Void,
You're right but...
and Franky-senpai as the
shipwright for the group -
Yeah! I got a banana!
Usopp! Ryunosuke was a good guy, wasn't he?!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
they both came to travel with the crew.
BUGGY'S DELIVERY - A PIRATE MERCENARY AGENCY
Wow! It's awesome! This wani (alligator)!
RODDY - A BULL MINK
THE WHALE FOREST GUARDIANS
Always pay attention to
what lies ahead. Look.
And in a mysterious area of sea
known as the Florian Triangle,
He's Warney!
BB (BLACKBACK) - A GORILLA MINK
THE WHALE FOREST GUARDIANS
--Hello, hello?
--Do you still have the one from the other day?
Yum! Yum, yum, yum...
they met Brook-senpai who is dead
and whose body is nothing but bones.
--Yes, we do!
--Hi! Thank you for calling Buggy's Delivery!
That must be a gate into the country.
You,
So this is how you handle them.
We need one in a hurry! It's very urgent!
join my crew!
Zou is exciting!
There is certainly civilization
on the elephant's back.
Yeah, okay.
Once I meet up with everyone,
I wanna explore it more!
Oh! Cool!
--Director Buggy!
--What do you want?!
We keep getting orders
and the Snails won't stop ringing!
The name of the friend that we promised
to meet up with at the cape is...
A dog?
There's a watchtower but no guards.
It's not security befitting a country.
WANDA - A DOG MINK
THE BATTLEBEAST TRIBE
You-teia are Straw Hat Luffy, aren't you?
Good, good!
...Laboon!
Since they can't get weapons
from Doflamingo now,
Tsk! They're so cold!
I'm Wanda.
After making such a one-sided promise,
I can't just say "I'm sorry we're dead"...
Honestly! You guys snapped
out of it too quickly!
CARROT - A RABBIT MINK
THE BATTLEBEAST TRIBE
they turned to pirate mercenaries
and we're getting a flood of calls!
She's Carrot.
It's really foggy.
Have we reached the abara (rib)?
We reign supreme over the military market!
And a rabbit.
...from a distant place
where he can't even hear me.
I found a good spot!
We won't do anything to you
so stop resisting.
It's ubara (right flank)!
Will Zoro and the others be there too?
Wait a sec, Luffy!
There are a bunch of strange
creatures in this country.
I think so. I gave them directions
to our hidden fortress.
Did you hear that?!
Because we told him
"We'll be back at any cost" as men!
It's like having a ton of Choppers.
Shambles.
Do you know me?
Hey, guys!
I'm so happy to be alive!
Of course.
Whoever finishes eating,
What's with them?!
It's awesome!
go to battlefields and run
wild, and bring back booty!
I didn't even do anything
but they attacked me!
So this is the back of the elephant!
Of course you are.
Oh, it's you guys!
That's because you-teia invaded the
forest where you mustn't enter.
BUGGY THE GENIUS JESTER - A WARLORD/PIRATE
THE DIRECTOR OF BUGGY'S DELIVERY
Your pirating is legitimate
under the name of...
Hey, Luffy! Where were you bitten?!
Do you still have your limbs?
Can I join the crew?
Oh! Wh-What are you doing?!
...the Warlord - Buggy
the Genius Jester-sama!
It's you-teia guys.
Sure.
The Guardians eject
invaders from this forest.
Since he came back by the power
of the Revive-Revive Fruit,
Hey, you Nami-dog girl right there!
He's our captain!
That's their job.
he had been drifting about the sea all alone.
So I wasn't allowed to enter?
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
No, you weren't.
And that was the moment
he finally got friends!
You wanna eat him, don't you?!
Guardians!
Hey, Usopp! Come up here!
It's amazing!
I won't let you do that, you predatory tramp!
We'll take him out of here!
Please forgive him!
This is how Luffy-senpai
built up a circle of friends
Oh yeah, Director Buggy!
You climbed the watchtower so quickly!
If you don't give us back him
and our friends who came here first,
Wait! I wanna see it too!
I forgot to tell you we got a call from
the S-class mercenary, Hajrudin,
and they became the Straw Hats
as we know it today!
It's awesome!
you'll see these three swords fire up!
So this is the back of the elephant!
and he said he wants to quit.
Oni Girya!
What?
That's it for my interview report.
Well, it's just one Giant - let it go.
We have four others.
For Wanda's sake...
Let's retreat, Roddy!
"Rya"?
I can't believe it.
I think you have the wrong idea.
This is no time to be sentimental!
I mean, all five of them want to.
Let's get Luffy-senpai and
the others safely to Zou!
What?! They're our biggest earners!
BB!
What?!
And we're so busy now!
I wanna know why!
But that's okay. We're here now.
Yeah!
Pedro!
No, you don't wanna hear it...
Everyone, retreat!
What?
Say it!
Look over there in the fog carefully...
What?!
Say it!!
Keep going for Zou!
There are guards and a gate to the fortress.
The A.O. Pirates, formerly of the
NAVY HEADQUARTERS
Was I surrounded?
I didn't sense them at all.
Whitebeard Pirates, have been wiped out.
All you senpai!
Is it that guy again?
We moved all our food to your ship
Yes, it's the Warlord - Edward Weevil.
Just be thankful this wasn't a moonlit night.
so I think you're gonna be okay for a while.
KIZARU (BORSALINO) - THE NAVY HQ ADMIRAL
How many captains who used
to work under Whitebeard...
Is there anything else that you need?
No, we're fine!
Wanda! Who are they-gara?
...have been brought down?
Straw Hat! It's been a while!
Are they the ones who invaded
the Whale Forest?!
Luffy! We're ready.
16 captains, sir.
All right, let's go!
Like the other cases, it
seems like they were blown up
Hey, Straw Hat, don't you remember us?
No kidding!
Is this really the elephant's back?!
They didn't mean any harm!
along with the town after
some kind of argument.
They're on their way.
The Welcoming Bell didn't ring by mistake
The casualties are about 600.
We took care of you after the Paramount War!
I wish I could follow them and
It's so interesting!
and one of them got lost in the Whale Forest!
see all the stars of the Straw Hats
He always causes a lot of collateral damage.
I'm shocked!
There's a massive, millennia-old elephant
from my dreams for even a little while but...
Oh! You're the talking
bear from Tra-guy's crew!
and there's a country on its back!
...I don't wanna get in the way of
the adventures of those gods!
Even though he's the Warlord,
we can't just overlook it.
Open the gate and let everybody know!
Yeah!
Tra-guy?!
What should we do?
No, we work under Trafalgar Law!
Our happiness barometer is
already at full throttle!
That the Straw Hats are here!
BEPO - NAVIGATOR OF THE HEART PIRATES
THE GUARDIANS' HELPER
It has a forest, a river, and a town!
He says he's "Whitebeard" Edward
Newgate's biological son and that
What?! Is that who they-gara are?!
The Heart Pirates!
This sure is awesome!
It's exactly like an island!
Next time we see you,
That's what I said.
makes him special but many
people aren't buying it...
Usopp! That tree's like a whale!
we'll all have abilities that
are worthy of being called
No, you didn't!
Well, we've been reading newspapers!
UNCLEAR JUSTICE
You're right!
Well, it doesn't matter
to us if it's true or not.
The town is bigger than I thought!
There was a whole bunch of surprising news!
subordinates of the Straw Hats.
--We're allied, aren't we?
--Is our captain here too?
But that town is sort of...
So if we can help you at that time,
Whoever his father is, he has one sure value.
INSIDE THE FORTRESS
Yeah, Tra-guy's here!
we want the four other senpai's Divine Drops!
THE DIVINE DROPS (AUTOGRAPHS)
Nami!
You got it wrong again! Who is that?!
As a pirate, he's overwhelmingly strong.
Nami!!
It'll be a sheer pleasure
if we can have them!
Tra-guy is Law.
Oh yeah? I didn't know that.
Luffy and the others are here!
They're finally here!
Luffy jumped down!
Pretty much like Whitebeard
when he was young.
So our captain, he's here! Yeah!
I knew he'd do that.
Do you see old "Eyebrows"?
--Is that an earthworm?
--It's a snake, isn't it?
No.
Captain, I can't wait to see you!
It has legs so it's a lizard.
This place is too high to see anybody.
That's the only thing they have in common.
They're totally ignoring me!
Complete disregard!
Zoro, shouldn't we wait
for Kin'emon and Kanjuro?
Nami! Luffy and the others arrived!
KURAU CITY AT THE CENTER
OF THE ELEPHANT'S BACK
A week after leaving Dressrosa...
It's not as vast as a continent.
Let's just go.
But I'm happy even with that!
They made it safely!
So happy!
Oh, it's too foggy. I can't see ahead.
I guess there's no doubt
that it was attacked.
Wait, wait!
I'm coming with you guys!
They did?! Really, Chopper?!
This city could have as many as
several hundred thousand residents
Okay, it's finished!
He didn't have to jump. The gate's open.
They're at the fortress gate!
You guys are getting seasick too often!
No, I think this is...
How could you call yourselves pirates?!
but not a single person is here.
--What is this?
--I still think it's a snake.
Oh, your friends are here. That's good.
Yeah, it's not actually open...
Chewing gum... Chewing gum...
It's dangerous!
This country's dangerous!
I-Is that a snake?
Chewing gum?
Nami!
Someone destroyed it.
Let's get out!
As soon as we find Sanji and the others!
It'll make it a little better, Grandma said.
I'm sorry.
It's dangerous!
This place is really dangerous!
I'm okay.
Let's go, Chopper!
Oh, that's why there is gum
stuck everywhere on this ship!
Appear, Rising Dragon!
Uh-huh!
You're right.
Dragon?!
They're important guests!
This trail looks strange too.
What a riot!
Prepare to welcome our
great saviors' friends!
It's too wide
to call it an animal trail in a forest.
Boss! I see something at two o'clock!
Hey, this is some pretty serious destruction!
Garchu!
What is it?!
What is this?!
There are signs that people
were just here until recently.
In the dense fog,
And it's still fresh.
Are Sanji and the others gonna be okay?!
there's a mountain or a monster...
It must've just happened.
Garchu!
I hope there's no monster
that can be mistaken for a mountain!
What a mess!
Welcome, Straw Hats!
I couldn't see it from up there
but what's going on here?!
But it looks like it's moving slowly...
Garchu!
Cool!
You're just drunk, you...
Welcome!
Let's proceed with caution!
If it's a mountain that moves, let's go!
What?! We don't really know the residents
here and we have other enemies?!
No, idiot! Anyway, what we gotta do now
is get out of this foggy
maze as soon as possible!
Whoa-whoa, hey!
W-W-W-Wait a minute, guys! Please!
Otherwise, we'll hit a reef and capsize!
What?! What?!
This destruction happened
not so long ago, either.
You don't need to rush like that!
Wait, God.
Oh, it's gonna say something!
Did you call me "God"? I'm flattered!
Oh?! What the...?!
The atmosphere's quite upbeat!
I'm a man of 200 million and I'm flattered!
Dra...
It's hard to walk.
Yeah, it's elephant's skin.
Dragon...
This isn't what we heard about!
Dammit! Bring it on if you want!
But actually, don't!
I'm sure even the Navy admirals
are aware of you now.
Garchu!
We shouldn't be out in the open like this!
D-Dragon...
There are flowers in such strange spots.
The enemies must be around here still!
Look. The Vivre Card is
pointing towards that.
They'll get us! They'll
get us! They'll get us!
Garchu!
Some kind of pathetic creature appeared!
Oh, you're right!
That means your friends are there!
What happened to Bariete?
The Lesser Minks passed through the gate.
What's "Garchu"?
--Why did you...?
--Like they say, an eye for an eye.
I thought the people of
your race hate humans.
Usopp, you look sick.
Do you want chewing gum too?
It's cute...
He might've been taken down!
Is this a device for torture?
Race, huh?
I've been refusing to face the reality...
How interesting!
It's kind of soft so it's hard to run!
That's probably what those who don't know
other Minks think and get scared of.
I heard...
Let's go now, Dragon!
We can't even tell
whether the enemies are humans or not.
Other Minks?
...Zou blocks out invaders
with dense fog and an adverse current.
It's a town!
To us, you-teia guys are
just Monkey Minks who have less hair.
Franky! Don't get too far...
Dragon!
No one's here!
What's wrong with this country?!
There are headwinds too!
Take in the sails! We'll row it forward!
They're all run-down!
What are those scratches?!
You're the same Mink Tribe,
just a different type.
Hey! Sanji! Nami!
There are so many claw marks.
Roger that...
Oh, so we humans are Monkey Minks.
Yeah, what are those?!
Chopper! Brook! Momo!
Hey! That's not how you respond!
It's cute...
That's right.
Hey, come see this.
Well, if we can fly on the dragon,
we can get there quickly.
We judge someone by their character,
not by their race.
Where are you?!
Oh, and the gas guy.
Well, forget about him.
Hey! Somebody, respond!
Garchu!
It's a giant footstep.
Do you think it's an elephant?
Garchu!
Is this the island, Zou?!
This city is dangerous!
We'd better get out...
Garchu!
No, that's strange!
All right, everyone, cling to its back!
It's gonna climb up!
What happened here?
We take pride in
the mink (hair) covering our bodies
This is no good! Let's run! Turn it around!
I smell the faint odor of gunpowder...
and gas, do you?
What the hell is that?!
Isn't it gonna fly?!
but you-teia guys have those beautiful...
Did some monsters and beasts attack
the Minks' country?
No, this is it.
Okay! Let's go!
What's this all about?
..."lesser mink coats"
and quite a lot of us admire it.
Can't we just lie back in a
peaceful country sometimes?!
But looking at those claw marks,
it might be internal discord.
"Lesser mink"?
I'm scared!
One thing is for sure.
That's what we call Minks with fewer hairs.
Scared!
Good! Keep going, Dragon!
--There they are!
--Oh, you're right!
This country was suddenly ruined
only one or two weeks ago.
How many kilometers to go?!
Oh, look! That's Nami and Chopper!
I see no end up there!
What?! What is it?!
Do you see something?!
I'm glad that they're okay!
Are you sure there's a country?!
Don't worry.
The Vivre Card is pointing upwards.
Nami!
Oh, okay. Dragon! You can do it!
Th-Then Sanji and everyone else...
Nami! I'm happy for you! Garchu!
Garchu!
Tra-guy! But this is a zou (elephant)!
were involved in it?!
I got caught! Let me through!
Luffy-senpai! I'll look
forward to seeing you again!
Ruined?
Alright! Garchu! Garchu!
Yeah, Zou is the name of a place
That's why no one's there.
That's great! Garchu!
that flourishes on the back
of a massive elephant.
This centuries-old country's name is
Mokomo Dukedom.
I Bartolomeo will devote myself every day
to becoming a fine pirate!
What?! Is it alive?
I got this.
They're very friendly!
That's so different from what I expected!
It keeps moving so it'll never
be at the same location.
To becoming a fine pirate!
When I trace my memories back
to just a half-month ago,
Did she just...
It's a Phantom Island.
I can see everyone's happy face.
...jump in midair?!
Hey, Luffy! Bartolomeo and the
others are saying something!
It's not actually an island
so Log Poses won't get you here.
Luffy!
Everybody!
Oh, Lome-o, huh?
I forgot to even thank him!
What the...?!
Oh, you guys!
I'm so happy to see you again!
I've never been here before either.
Wait! Stop, Carrot!
Not Lome-o, it's Lomeo!
Nami! Chopper!
It's showing its back to us.
Hey, Lome-o!
That means Black Foot and the others
could've gotten here much earlier.
Bye, Lome-o and everybody!
Thank you for bringing us here!
This country was ruined by...
So we were chasing
an elephant that was walking away.
Everybody!
What?!
Here comes something else!
D-Did he just call my name?!
Usopp!
...Jack!
Yeah. Get ready to make landfall.
Jack...
H-He called my name for the first time!
Can you give us some food?
Forget about them-teia!
Usopp!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Chopper!
For you?!
More importantly, we have an
invader in the Whale Forest!
Oh! What is it?!
Can you give Straw Hat-ya some food?
I'm happy for you, Boss!
So Sanji, Brook, and Momo are all fine too!
Take everything in the food storage!
Y-You too! Thank you very much!
Talking animals?!
What the...?!
So this is Zou!
They're the Mink Tribe!
Please take care on your journey!
There are such unusual
things outside our country!
Oh?! I-Isn't that outfit...
You too! See ya!
What's going on?!
There'll be a Rain-Ruption!
I wonder if Momonosuke is okay.
Climb a tree!
...Nami's?!
Hey! I heard there is a
tribe that hates humans.
A Rain-Ruption?!
One of the Mink Tribe, the residents of Zou,
came to attack suddenly.
Yes, it's the Mink Tribe.
Get on Warney!
I'll take you to the Rightflank!
She stunned Zoro and the others
with her strange ability.
They hold off humans and people say
the history of their country
I'm sorry!
Your friends are there!
Luffy-senpai! Take care!
Are Sanji and everyone else all right?
Great! So Sanji and the others are there!
goes back nearly a thousand years.
A thousand years?!
On the elephant's back?!
And where is Nami?
Thus, the party keeps climbing up to
the top of the Phantom Island, Zou.
Luffy and the gang finally landed on Zou!
What's wrong?!
Does that mean that elephant has
been alive for a thousand years?!
They're all there, aren't they?!
An eventful great adventure in the country
on the elephant's back, now begins!
Sanji-kun is...
Zoro and the others confront
the mysterious Mink Tribe!
With a heavy Rain-Ruption falling from above,
He is the great pirate Whitebeard's son and
Now the detail of Sanji and the others'
deadly voyage to Zou is revealed!
To meet up with Sanji and the
others, Luffy and his group
the last pirate of the Seven
Warlords, Edward Weevil!
Luffy, Wanda, and the others head
desperately for the Rightflank Forest!
head for the massive elephant's
back in the far distance!
Meanwhile, Luffy wanders in a
deep forest of Zou by himself and
While the Emperor, Big Mom's
ship was raining shells on them
After climbing up the steep cliff
When a hidden Mink fortress finally
reveals itself in a thick fog,
when a creepy dark shadow sneaks up on him,
To avenge his father's death,
and overcoming a number of crises
and a heartbreaking goodbye,
and fierce offensive-and-defensive
battles raged,
the strongest son in the world
causes a new big storm
a strike like raging lightning
bears down on him!
Sanji and the rest were driven to the wall
but employed a tactic to recover!
Luffy finally gets to see
Nami and everybody again!
the Phantom Island that's wrapped in a mystery
finally shows itself!
in the sea of the New World!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Battle Begins! Luffy vs. the Mink Tribe!"
"Garchu! The Straw Hats Reunite!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The New Warlord! The Legendary
Whitebeard's Son Appears!"
"Start to Counterattack! Great
Moves by the Twirly Hat Crew!"
"A Deadly Elephant Climb!
A Great Adventure on the Back of the Giant Elephant!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!