kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
Help!
Shanks!
Get lost!
Hey, don't cry! You're a man!
But... Shanks!
Your arm!
It's only an arm. It's no big deal.
I'm just glad you're alright...
You'll never be a pirate!
I will too!
Someday, I'm gonna gather a crew
every bit as good as yours,
and I'm gonna find the greatest treasure
in the world,
and I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!
I'll show you!
You're gonna surpass us, huh?
In that case...
...I'll leave this hat with you.
It's dear to me.
Take good care of it!
Come bring it back to me someday!
Once you've become a great pirate!
That's our promise, Luffy!
"Curtain-up on a New Adventure!
Arriving at the Phantom Island, Zou!"
Following Nami and the others who they parted with
at Dressrosa,
Luffy and the gang are heading
MISTER LUFFY GO
to the next island, Zou.
Wow! Shanks appears in the story already?!
That's our Luffy-senpai!
Isn't that amazing?! It's so amazing!
What are you doing, Boss?!
You look very excited...
I was just telling everyone a series
of legends that I learned by
interviewing Luffy-senpai and the others!
What?!
You guys can hear it too so just sit down!
Go on already!
Please, Boss!
All right!
A decade later,
Luffy-senpai left Windmill Village
and met Roronoa Zoro-senpai, also known as
Pirate Hunter, at a Navy base.
"Pirate Hunter"... What a cool name!
A girl tried to feed him rice balls.
But a Navy soldier stomped on them.
It was good. Thank you for the food.
What are you...?!
That doesn't work!
W-Who the hell are you?!
I'm Luffy!
The man who's gonna be
the King of the Pirates!
I'll be your pirate,
if I'm just gonna die here instead!
But I'll tell you this right now.
I'm only going to fulfill my ambition!
To be the world's greatest swordsman!
That sounds great!
The King of the Pirates would need
someone like that on his crew!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Nice!
Zoro.
My pleasure, Captain.
"Three-Sword Style"
Zoro-senpai who was looking
to become the world's greatest swordsman...
went on a journey with Luffy-senpai.
How awesome is that?!
I'm a thief who steals from pirates!
The name's Nami!
Hey, wanna team up with me?!
Cat Burglar Nami-senpai!
She was a thief who was stealing
treasure from pirates.
But she had a good reason for it...
So these are your true colors, huh?
Surprised? It was all an act.
I'm a pirate, plain and simple!
And an officer of the Arlong Pirates!
For many years, her home
village was under the control
of a Fish-Man named Arlong
and she was trying to buy it back
with the money she had
risked her own life to collect.
Luffy...
Help me...
Of course I will!
Nami!
You're my friend!
Yeah!
That was the moment the navigator
Nami-senpai joined the crew.
F-Friend...
I-I wish I could hear him saying that to me!
Bye, everyone! I'll be back!
I am Usopp, leader of the great pirates
who reign over this village!
People praise me - and then praise me more -
as "Captain Usopp"!
In Syrup Village, they met Usopp-senpai.
He was known as the biggest
talker in the village.
But he's actually a manly man
who'll stand up to his enemy
at the risk of his life when the need arises!
Even if I'm no match for him...
I will protect them!
I'm a brave warrior of the sea!
I won't let you lay a finger on the village!
Why is an outsider like you
butting into this village's business?!
Because there's a man in this village
I don't wanna let die!
H-Here it comes!
That was where they met the
Going Merry-senpai too!
You guys take care, too!
Let's meet again sometime!
How come?
Get on already.
We're friends now, aren't we?
As a sniper looking to
become a brave warrior of the sea,
Usopp-senpai joined the crew!
Luffy-senpai needed a cook
and that's when he met
Sanji-senpai who was working at
a floating restaurant as a sous-chef.
Eat it.
Sorry...
It's pretty damn delicious, isn't it?
It is!
I found a good cook!
This restaurant is that
damn geezer's treasure!
I... I can't repay the damn geezer
for his kindness...
...unless I risk my life for him too!
Dying isn't something you should do
to repay kindness!!
Say...
do you know the All Blue?
No...
Wait.
We both have foolish dreams.
In order to achieve my goal, the All Blue...
Sanji?
Yeah. I'll come along...
on your journey to become
the "King of the Pirates"!
What?
I'll be the cook for your ship.
Is that okay or not?
It's okay!!
All right!!
Owner Zeff!!
Thank you for all the damn things you've
done for me over all these years!!
I'll never forget your kindness...
...for the rest of my life!!
Sanji-senpai is a first
class chef of the sea!
I hope I can meet him soon
and see his kicking techniques!
Isn't that... backwards?
To cure Nami-senpai's disease,
they stopped by at a Winter Island.
And there, they met
"Cotton Candy Lover" Tonytony Chopper-senpai!
He's a human-reindeer hybrid
because of eating the Human-Human Fruit.
He used to have no friends
because of his outlandish look.
But he's a good doctor who studied
advanced medical care under his mentors.
Ahh!
You'd better be prepared if you're gonna
meddle with someone else's skull flag!
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!!
I can't become your friend!
Shut up! Let's go!
Luffy-senpai welcomed Chopper-senpai
as the ship's doctor.
He's so great!
I keep getting moved to tears!
B-B-B-B...
Believe it or not,
Robin-senpai and Franky-senpai
were their enemies at first!
What?!
But Robin-senpai who was also
known as Demon Child,
was traveling along with
the crew since Alabasta.
And Franky-senpai first appeared
as the leader of the Franky Family...
...in the City of Water - Water Seven!
Robin!
I've come to get you!
Just leave the rest to us!
If... I'm allowed to make a small wish...
I...
I want to live!!
Take me to the seas with you!
We're gonna go back together!
Robin!
Come on. Get on, Franky.
On my ship.
Fine. I suppose I can
take care of it for you.
I, Franky, will take on the role of
the shipwright for your crew!
Robin-senpai as an archeologist
who is searching
for the truth of the 100-Year Void,
and Franky-senpai as the
shipwright for the group -
they both came to travel with the crew.
And in a mysterious area of sea
known as the Florian Triangle,
they met Brook-senpai who is dead
and whose body is nothing but bones.
You,
join my crew!
Yeah, okay.
The name of the friend that we promised
to meet up with at the cape is...
...Laboon!
After making such a one-sided promise,
I can't just say "I'm sorry we're dead"...
...from a distant place
where he can't even hear me.
Because we told him
"We'll be back at any cost" as men!
I'm so happy to be alive!
Of course you are.
Can I join the crew?
Sure.
Since he came back by the power
of the Revive-Revive Fruit,
he had been drifting about the sea all alone.
And that was the moment
he finally got friends!
This is how Luffy-senpai
built up a circle of friends
and they became the Straw Hats
as we know it today!
That's it for my interview report.
This is no time to be sentimental!
Let's get Luffy-senpai and
the others safely to Zou!
Yeah!
Keep going for Zou!
The A.O. Pirates, formerly of the
NAVY HEADQUARTERS
Whitebeard Pirates, have been wiped out.
Is it that guy again?
Yes, it's the Warlord - Edward Weevil.
KIZARU (BORSALINO) - THE NAVY HQ ADMIRAL
How many captains who used
to work under Whitebeard...
...have been brought down?
16 captains, sir.
Like the other cases, it
seems like they were blown up
along with the town after
some kind of argument.
The casualties are about 600.
He always causes a lot of collateral damage.
Even though he's the Warlord,
we can't just overlook it.
What should we do?
He says he's "Whitebeard" Edward
Newgate's biological son and that
makes him special but many
people aren't buying it...
UNCLEAR JUSTICE
Well, it doesn't matter
to us if it's true or not.
Whoever his father is, he has one sure value.
As a pirate, he's overwhelmingly strong.
Pretty much like Whitebeard
when he was young.
That's the only thing they have in common.
A week after leaving Dressrosa...
Oh, it's too foggy. I can't see ahead.
You guys are getting seasick too often!
How could you call yourselves pirates?!
Chewing gum... Chewing gum...
Chewing gum?
It'll make it a little better, Grandma said.
Oh, that's why there is gum
stuck everywhere on this ship!
What a riot!
Boss! I see something at two o'clock!
What is it?!
In the dense fog,
there's a mountain or a monster...
I hope there's no monster
that can be mistaken for a mountain!
But it looks like it's moving slowly...
You're just drunk, you...
If it's a mountain that moves, let's go!
No, idiot! Anyway, what we gotta do now
is get out of this foggy
maze as soon as possible!
Otherwise, we'll hit a reef and capsize!
Wait, God.
Did you call me "God"? I'm flattered!
I'm a man of 200 million and I'm flattered!
I'm sure even the Navy admirals
are aware of you now.
Look. The Vivre Card is
pointing towards that.
Oh, you're right!
That means your friends are there!
Usopp, you look sick.
Do you want chewing gum too?
I've been refusing to face the reality...
I heard...
...Zou blocks out invaders
with dense fog and an adverse current.
There are headwinds too!
Take in the sails! We'll row it forward!
Roger that...
Hey! That's not how you respond!
Is this the island, Zou?!
No, that's strange!
This is no good! Let's run! Turn it around!
No, this is it.
Tra-guy! But this is a zou (elephant)!
Yeah, Zou is the name of a place
that flourishes on the back
of a massive elephant.
What?! Is it alive?
It keeps moving so it'll never
be at the same location.
It's a Phantom Island.
It's not actually an island
so Log Poses won't get you here.
I've never been here before either.
It's showing its back to us.
That means Black Foot and the others
could've gotten here much earlier.
So we were chasing
an elephant that was walking away.
Yeah. Get ready to make landfall.
Can you give us some food?
For you?!
Can you give Straw Hat-ya some food?
Take everything in the food storage!
So this is Zou!
There are such unusual
things outside our country!
I wonder if Momonosuke is okay.
Hey! I heard there is a
tribe that hates humans.
Yes, it's the Mink Tribe.
They hold off humans and people say
the history of their country
goes back nearly a thousand years.
A thousand years?!
On the elephant's back?!
Does that mean that elephant has
been alive for a thousand years?!
He is the great pirate Whitebeard's son and
the last pirate of the Seven
Warlords, Edward Weevil!
To avenge his father's death,
the strongest son in the world
causes a new big storm
in the sea of the New World!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The New Warlord! The Legendary
Whitebeard's Son Appears!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!