kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After leaving the fateful island, Dressrosa,
Luffy and the others headed
for the unknown island,
Zou, following Nami and
the others who went ahead.
Is this the island, Zou?!
No, that's strange!
No, this is it.
Tra-guy! But this is a zou (elephant)!
Yeah, Zou is the name of a place
that flourishes on the back
of a massive elephant.
"The New Warlord!
The Legendary Whitebeard's Son Appears!"
Wow! It's huge!
Oh? That's...
What?! D-D-Don't tell me it's...
The Sunny!
Shut up!
So that's...
That's...
...the grand ship that carries
the sacred bodies of the Straw Hats!
The Thousand Sunny-senpai!
I feel blessed! I feel blessed!
I feel blessed!
Don't worship it!
Good! So they made it to Zou for sure.
I guess they got away from Big Mom nicely.
There's no major damage.
Hey! Sanji!
Nami! Chopper! Brook! Momo!
And... what was the gas guy's name?
There's no response.
--What the...?!
--The elephant's leg is moving!
Wait!
Hey! Keep up with it!
Aye, sir, Boss!
Barrier-bility: Stairs!
D-Did it stop?
No, the leg on the other side is
about to move forward now!
This one will move again soon!
All of you senpai, hurry up and cross over...
Oh?
Where did they go?
Oh! They're already crossing!
Luffy! Have you seen the others?
Seems like they aren't here.
What?!
I guess they all made landfall.
Yeah! Let's catch up to them quickly!
All right, take care, guys!
You're coming with us!
THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY'S GENERAL HEADQUARTERS
BALTIGO, GRAND LINE
Dragon-san!
Rebel armies are winning
all across the world!
MONKEY D. DRAGON
THE GENERAL COMMANDER
OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
The fall of the Donquixote Family
had a huge impact.
This many countries were involved
in the weapon trafficking.
The war situation is looking up.
But tell them not to be too
excited over their win.
Yes, sir!
The World Government won't
just sit by quietly.
Cipher Pol has been
reinforced in recent years.
So tell them to take extra care.
Yes, sir!
Dragon-san.
They say they found a
special ore in the weapons
we brought back from Dressrosa.
An ore?
Do you know of Drunken Iron Ore?
It's quite rare
and only a few countries can mine it,
so they might be able to figure out
where the weapons were actually made.
Oh, that's good news.
Yes.
You brought back our people who
went missing in Dressrosa too.
You're doing remarkably well.
Please! I couldn't do it
without Sabo-kun and Luffy-kun!
How was Robin?
I heard she was caught in Sabaody
but that was completely false.
Yes, it was! She was totally full of life!
Almost like...
Aren't you gonna ask me about Luffy-kun?
Well, I've had more than enough with that.
Oh, I bet Sabo-kun told you a lot.
Anyway, Koala.
Yes.
We need their help.
Their?
Summon all the leaders of the Revolutionary
Army from all over the world!
Okay.
What?! Do you really wanna summon
all those big personalities again?!
A SEA SOMEWHERE IN THE NEW WORLD
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
This is Lafitte.
This... urgess.
It's me!
Burgess! It's you!
"DEMON SHERIFF" LAFITTE
THE CAPTAIN OF THE FIFTH SHIP OF
THE EMPEROR - BLACKBEARD'S PIRATE GROUP
We went to Dressrosa to pick you up
but you weren't there.
Yeah, sorry.
I couldn't make contact since I was
unconscious almost the whole time.
SHIRYU OF THE RAIN
THE CAPTAIN OF THE SECOND SHIP OF
THE EMPEROR - BLACKBEARD'S PIRATE GROUP
Oh, that son of a gun was alive.
Where've you been?
Where are you now?
It's all white...
It's an island as white as snow.
I've been hiding in the bottom of this ship.
Tell Captain Teech!
If we invade here now, we can
get a massive amount of weapons!
It's Commodore Teech.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Make sure to bring Doc Q too!
I'm fatally injured!
Burgess! Tell us already! Where are you?
I don't know the name of the island.
It's a totally uncharted place.
Follow my Vivre Card and come here!
Dragon and the obnoxious Sabo are here too!
I've found it!
It's the Revolutionary Army's
general headquarters!
AN ISLAND SOMEWHERE
Everyone's so dumb and ridiculous!
They all say the same thing!
That the members of the Whitebeard Pirates
are Whitebeard's only sons!
EDWARD WEEVIL - A WARLORD
SELF-PROCLAIMED "WHITEBEARD JR."
(FORMER BOUNTY: 480 MILLION BERRIES)
Mommy! Mommy!
I'm Whitebeard's son, right?!
My beard's white as well!
That's right, dear!
The Whitebeard Pirates were
just a make-believe family.
You're the only biological son of
the world's strongest pirate, Whitebeard!
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
And I'm...
MISS BUCKIN - WEEVIL'S MOTHER
SELF-PROCLAIMED "WHITEBEARD'S LOVER"
...the woman who Whitebeard loved!
So hold your head up, my treasure!
You're hurting me, Mommy!
--Look at this!
--What? Is that a mirror?
No, it's a picture of Whitebeard!
Oh, I thought that was a mirror.
You look so much like him - there's
no way you're not his son!
How can you be so silly?!
Oh, sorry, Mommy!
But I forgive you.
Because I love you!
Mommy!
Now, let's go!
Say what you've got to do!
Ummm...
I forgot.
Find the remnants of the Whitebeard Pirates
like Marco the Phoenix!
And get something back!
Your father Newgate must've left
behind a big fortune
and you're the true heir
since you're his biological son!
Oh, I see, I see.
Oh yeah! But what I really
wanna do is get revenge!
I wanna have my revenge on
Blackbeard for killing Daddy!
I'll kill him!
I won't forgive him at any price!
Silly boy! What's the
point in taking revenge?
You can't even earn one berry!
We want money!
You must inherit his fortune!
You're right, Mommy!
What's the matter, Mommy?
Doflamingo was defeated.
It's him again! Garp's grandson!
They say Marco and the others tried
to protect him in the Paramount War.
Then, maybe he knows something about Marco.
Should we go beat him up?
"BUGGY TOWN"
EMPTEE BLUFFS ISLAND, NEW WORLD
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
BUGGY'S DELIVERY - A PIRATE MERCENARY AGENCY
--Hello, hello?
--Do you still have the one from the other day?
--Yes, we do!
--Hi! Thank you for calling Buggy's Delivery!
We need one in a hurry! It's very urgent!
--Director Buggy!
--What do you want?!
We keep getting orders
and the Snails won't stop ringing!
Good, good!
Since they can't get weapons
from Doflamingo now,
they turned to pirate mercenaries
and we're getting a flood of calls!
We reign supreme over the military market!
Did you hear that?!
Hey, guys!
Whoever finishes eating,
go to battlefields and run
wild, and bring back booty!
BUGGY THE GENIUS JESTER - A WARLORD/PIRATE
THE DIRECTOR OF BUGGY'S DELIVERY
Your pirating is legitimate
under the name of...
...the Warlord - Buggy
the Genius Jester-sama!
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Oh yeah, Director Buggy!
I forgot to tell you we got a call from
the S-class mercenary, Hajrudin,
and he said he wants to quit.
What?
Well, it's just one Giant - let it go.
We have four others.
I mean, all five of them want to.
What?! They're our biggest earners!
And we're so busy now!
I wanna know why!
No, you don't wanna hear it...
Say it!
Say it!!
All you senpai!
We moved all our food to your ship
so I think you're gonna be okay for a while.
Is there anything else that you need?
No, we're fine!
Luffy! We're ready.
All right, let's go!
They're on their way.
I wish I could follow them and
see all the stars of the Straw Hats
from my dreams for even a little while but...
...I don't wanna get in the way of
the adventures of those gods!
Our happiness barometer is
already at full throttle!
Next time we see you,
we'll all have abilities that
are worthy of being called
subordinates of the Straw Hats.
So if we can help you at that time,
we want the four other senpai's Divine Drops!
THE DIVINE DROPS (AUTOGRAPHS)
It'll be a sheer pleasure
if we can have them!
--Is that an earthworm?
--It's a snake, isn't it?
It has legs so it's a lizard.
They're totally ignoring me!
Complete disregard!
But I'm happy even with that!
So happy!
Okay, it's finished!
--What is this?
--I still think it's a snake.
I-Is that a snake?
Appear, Rising Dragon!
Dragon?!
What is this?!
Cool!
Oh, it's gonna say something!
Dra...
Dragon...
D-Dragon...
Some kind of pathetic creature appeared!
--Why did you...?
--Like they say, an eye for an eye.
It's cute...
Let's go now, Dragon!
Dragon!
It's cute...
Well, if we can fly on the dragon,
we can get there quickly.
All right, everyone, cling to its back!
It's gonna climb up!
Isn't it gonna fly?!
Okay! Let's go!
Good! Keep going, Dragon!
How many kilometers to go?!
I see no end up there!
Are you sure there's a country?!
Don't worry.
The Vivre Card is pointing upwards.
Oh, okay. Dragon! You can do it!
Luffy-senpai! I'll look
forward to seeing you again!
I Bartolomeo will devote myself every day
to becoming a fine pirate!
To becoming a fine pirate!
Hey, Luffy! Bartolomeo and the
others are saying something!
Oh, Lome-o, huh?
I forgot to even thank him!
Not Lome-o, it's Lomeo!
Hey, Lome-o!
Bye, Lome-o and everybody!
Thank you for bringing us here!
What?!
D-Did he just call my name?!
H-He called my name for the first time!
I'm happy for you, Boss!
Y-You too! Thank you very much!
Please take care on your journey!
You too! See ya!
Luffy-senpai! Take care!
Thus, the party keeps climbing up to
the top of the Phantom Island, Zou.
To meet up with Sanji and the
others, Luffy and his group
head for the massive elephant's
back in the far distance!
After climbing up the steep cliff
and overcoming a number of crises
and a heartbreaking goodbye,
the Phantom Island that's wrapped in a mystery
finally shows itself!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Deadly Elephant Climb!
A Great Adventure on the Back of the Giant Elephant!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!