I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
The enormous island is
actually an elephant which has
been alive for a millennium.
"A Deadly Elephant Climb!
A Great Adventure on the Back of the Giant Elephant!"
The "thing" that Luffy and
the rest are riding is
currently climbing the left
hind leg of the giant elephant.
It's so high - I'm scared!
My arms are exhausted! It's too much!
Don't say that, Usopp.
He's giving it all he's got.
What?! Whoa-whoa!
Scary!
Usopp, you fool! Don't pull me!
If we fall into the sea, that'll be it!
Dragon, you can do it!
Okay! Good job!
You showed some guts!
A-Attaboy, Dragon...
No, your name is Ryunosuke from now on!
Our friend, Ryunosuke!
All right! So just let go of me!
So cute...
He scared the crap out of me.
I wish he could fly.
Is this dragon okay?
What are you talking about?
You just saw how he held on, didn't you?
Alright, you can do it, Ryunosuke! Go!
We're back where we started though.
I can't see the top yet.
I wonder how Sanji and
the others climbed this.
Are they really up there?
Kin'emon, Kanjuro.
Come to think of it, why
do you wanna go to Zou?
Oh yeah.
We owe you people a lot
so we must tell you everything eventually.
But first, we need to feel safe.
Mm-hm. Zou was always our destination
since leaving the Land of Wano.
We want to see if Momonosuke is okay
and if another friend we
were separated from at sea
- Raizo, a ninja, has arrived here safely.
--A ninja?!
--Is he a ninja?!
What the...
A ninja... I wanna meet him!
I wanna see a shuriken.
Will he sit under a waterfall?
Can he really use supernatural ninja powers?
Can he disappear in an instant like they say?
What are you guys...
Yes, indeed!
Tell us! What kind of powers does he use?!
Um, for example, being able to see far away.
Ninpo - Telescopic Technique!
Cool!
Hey! Stop talking gibberish!
Oh, so it wasn't true.
What?
Luffy! Look up!
Something's falling onto us!
What is that?!
Etetetetete...
"Ete"?
That's right! Raizo runs
with that kind of rhythm.
I think he has this kind of power.
Ninpo - Blindfold Technique!
Guess who!
I-Is it Kanjuro?
I mean I know you're the only person there.
Look out! Duck!
Hey! Stop the silly ninpo nonsense...
Oh no! Those two fell!
Damn! What was that thing that
fell on us out of the blue?!
I don't know. I think it was a bloody person
with knives stuck all over his body...
What?!
Or just a small monkey.
You're scaring me!
What made you think that?!
Hey! Are you alright?!
Kin'emon! Kanjuro!
--Did they fall into the water?
--Let's go save them!
Luffy-dono! We're both okay!
--That's Kin'emon!
--Good! They're alive!
Go ahead! We'll catch up soon!
What is he talking about? No way!
Let's go back down!
Hey, Dragon! Head back down!
Ryunosuke, head back...
Hey, Ryunosuke...
How can we tell this poor guy
to go back...
Seems like he wants to finish his job
as soon as possible.
He's suffering.
Let's let him keep going.
So cute...
I'm sorry but we're gonna go ahead!
See you guys later!
Understood!
Hey! I won't allow you to enter the country!
Go ahead!
Huh? I think I just heard an unknown voice.
Come on, Ryunosuke!
You can do it!
Luffy!
Hey, Luffy!
How can you sleep
when Ryunosuke is trying so hard?!
Hey, look!
Isn't that the top?!
What?
Oh! It is!
A little more to go, Ryunosuke!
The top?!
Alright! Ryunosuke! Way to go!
Watch out! That was close!
What?
No! He fell off!
--What are you guys doing?!
--Oh my...
Luffy! Do something!
Got it!
Yes!
All right!
Hey, Luffy, you idiot! Don't!
D-Don't fall!
Hang on, Ryunosuke!
I mean I'm gonna fall! Help, Robin!
--Good luck.
--What?!
I'm so scared! Help me!
Okay, I'm back!
Shut up!
What are you gonna do about this?!
Ryunosuke! Hang tough!
Don't tell him to hang tough!
It's your fault!
Dragon, you can do it!
Ryunosuke! Please!
Give it all you've got! As soon as you can!
Ryunosuke! Show your manliness!
Get fired up, Ryunosuke!
Show some guts, Dragon!
Hey! Hurry up, Ryunosuke!
My legs can't take it any longer!
Ryunosuke, come on!
So cute...
Alright, Ryunosuke! Attaboy!
A little more to go!
We're almost there! Go!
The top is close at hand!
Oh! So fast!
Ryunosuke! Make a final sprint!
Keep going! Ryunosuke!
Just a little more to go! Run!
You're almost there!
You're almost there! You're almost there!
Yes! I'm starting to see something!
Ryunosuke! Come on! It's right there!
Ryunosuke! Ryunosuke! Ryunosuke! Ryunosuke!
Ryunosuke! Ryunosuke!
You can do it, Ryunosuke!
We made it!
To the top!
We finally made it!
Ryunosuke! Good job!
We're here at Zou!
Ryunosuke...
I'm... proud of you.
You're turning back to a drawing.
Hey, Ryunosuke!
You did it! Well done!
Hey, wait!
Ryunosuke!
--Ryunosuke!
Wait a minute!
We haven't really thanked you yet!
Ryunosuke!
Thank you!
Ryunosuke! Ryunosu...
--This is absurd.
--It's just a bad drawing.
Hey, hold it right there, you bastards!
Is that how you thank him
for bringing you up here?!
We're in unknown territory.
We shouldn't look back.
You're right but...
Usopp! Ryunosuke was a good guy, wasn't he?!
Always pay attention to
what lies ahead. Look.
That must be a gate into the country.
There is certainly civilization
on the elephant's back.
Oh! Cool!
There's a watchtower but no guards.
It's not security befitting a country.
Tsk! They're so cold!
Honestly! You guys snapped
out of it too quickly!
I found a good spot!
Wait a sec, Luffy!
It's awesome!
So this is the back of the elephant!
Hey, Usopp! Come up here!
It's amazing!
You climbed the watchtower so quickly!
Wait! I wanna see it too!
It's awesome!
So this is the back of the elephant!
No kidding!
Is this really the elephant's back?!
It's so interesting!
There's a massive, millennia-old elephant
and there's a country on its back!
Yeah!
It has a forest, a river, and a town!
This sure is awesome!
It's exactly like an island!
Usopp! That tree's like a whale!
You're right!
The town is bigger than I thought!
But that town is sort of...
Luffy jumped down!
I knew he'd do that.
Do you see old "Eyebrows"?
No.
This place is too high to see anybody.
Zoro, shouldn't we wait
for Kin'emon and Kanjuro?
It's not as vast as a continent.
Let's just go.
Wait, wait!
I'm coming with you guys!
He didn't have to jump. The gate's open.
No, I think this is...
Yeah, it's not actually open...
Someone destroyed it.
You're right.
This trail looks strange too.
It's too wide
to call it an animal trail in a forest.
Hey, this is some pretty serious destruction!
And it's still fresh.
Are Sanji and the others gonna be okay?!
What a mess!
I couldn't see it from up there
but what's going on here?!
Let's proceed with caution!
What?! We don't really know the residents
here and we have other enemies?!
Whoa-whoa, hey!
W-W-W-Wait a minute, guys! Please!
You don't need to rush like that!
It's hard to walk.
Yeah, it's elephant's skin.
Dammit! Bring it on if you want!
But actually, don't!
There are flowers in such strange spots.
What happened to Bariete?
The Lesser Minks passed through the gate.
He might've been taken down!
How interesting!
It's kind of soft so it's hard to run!
It's a town!
No one's here!
What's wrong with this country?!
They're all run-down!
Hey! Sanji! Nami!
Chopper! Brook! Momo!
Where are you?!
Oh, and the gas guy.
Well, forget about him.
Hey! Somebody, respond!
What happened here?
I smell the faint odor of gunpowder...
and gas, do you?
What's this all about?
Can't we just lie back in a
peaceful country sometimes?!
I'm scared!
Scared!
What?! What is it?!
Do you see something?!
I got this.
Did she just...
...jump in midair?!
What the...?!
Wait! Stop, Carrot!
Here comes something else!
Forget about them-teia!
More importantly, we have an
invader in the Whale Forest!
Talking animals?!
They're the Mink Tribe!
Oh?! I-Isn't that outfit...
...Nami's?!
One of the Mink Tribe, the residents of Zou,
came to attack suddenly.
She stunned Zoro and the others
with her strange ability.
Are Sanji and everyone else all right?
And where is Nami?
Luffy and the gang finally landed on Zou!
An eventful great adventure in the country
on the elephant's back, now begins!
Zoro and the others confront
the mysterious Mink Tribe!
Meanwhile, Luffy wanders in a
deep forest of Zou by himself and
when a creepy dark shadow sneaks up on him,
a strike like raging lightning
bears down on him!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Battle Begins! Luffy vs. the Mink Tribe!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!