I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests, a zou (elephant)
that has been alive for a millennium.
An animal?! A human?!
H-Hey, you!
Where did you get that outfit?!
What did you do to Nami?!
We don't have time to
transport you-teia guys!
Do as I say!
Go through the Rightrump Forest to your right
and turn left at a deep dark swamp!
And you'll reach the Rightflank Forest!
You'll find
the corpse of your-teia friend there!
C-Corpse?!
Gum-Gum...
Moo Golova!
...Bell!
This country was ruined by...
...Jack!
Jack...
What's going on?!
There'll be a Rain-Ruption!
Climb a tree!
A Rain-Ruption?!
Get on Warney!
I'll take you to the Rightflank!
Your friends are there!
"Garchu!
The Straw Hats Reunite!"
Hurry up, everybody! Evacuate!
Go, Warney!
It's quite strong!
This shaking is no good!
Wow! Cool!
What the hell is that?!
Here comes a Rain-Ruption!
Oh! It's flying towards us!
What?!
A big splash of water?!
It'll cause floods!
Get to high ground!
Run!
But...
It's too late!
Here it comes!
Hang on tight!
Oh?
--Carrot!
--I got it!
Straw Hat!
Look out!
Are you okay, Straw Hat?
You saved me... Thanks!
Meanwhile, Kin'emon and Kanjuro are
climbing the elephant's left leg...
Finally, it stopped.
What was the shaking all about?
I don't know.
But we're coming to the crucial point.
Hold on, cat! Nekozaemon!
Now hurry up!
The sun is setting, Nekozaemon!
Isn't it too much for a cat
to climb this elephant?
Kanjuro!
No, it's not.
Cats are good tree climbers.
They are!
Water?!
What?!
Oh, that's water overflowing from a
Rain-Ruption that poured over the country...
Water is no good! It will melt Nekozaemon!
There is no time to lose...
But again, halfway to the top, we...
THE WHALE FOREST - LUFFY AND THE OTHERS
Oh, that was a hell of a rain!
Rain-Ruptions aren't actually a type of rain.
Twice a day, Zunesha sprays water on itself.
So that was a blast of seawater.
The water passes through a filtration system
at the center of the city to aqueducts
and becomes the drinking water
for the whole nation.
Fish fall along with the seawater
so we'd never run out of food.
Rain-Ruptions provide us with a lot.
Hey, Straw Hat!
Oh, the bear!
I can't leave this forest
so can you tell our captain about us
and bring him here?!
Oh, you can't? Okay!
I'm counting on you!
Bepo was born here
but since he's a pirate,
he's now under the care of
Master Cat Viper, the boss of the forest.
KURAU CITY - ZORO AND THE OTHERS
It's flooding!
There's a shark! A shark?! Why?!
You went way too high!
This is high enough.
Seawater?
Maybe, that was the giant elephant
spraying water on itself.
It seems like both the town and the forest
are adapted to this water level.
Well, seeing the water amount...
I guess you're right!
That means this happens every day...
I wouldn't want that tremendous
downpour every day!
We must find everybody quickly
and get off of this annoying island!
Hey, there's Luffy!
At the edge of the town!
He's with the Nami-dog girl
and the jump rabbit from before!
He's getting fooled
and being taken to their lair...
What is it, Usopp?!
Luffy's been eaten a little!
What?! So they're really...
A cannibal tribe!
I told you to stop biting me!
The whole town is soaked in water.
The water will drain away soon.
I know he's here!
I told you he's not!
Bring him here or this
country will be destroyed!
I don't know what you're talking about!
I really don't know! What else can I say?!
Who were you talking about?
You told me the name of the guy
who attacked this country before.
His name is Jack.
I saw his obituary in the newspaper
a few days ago.
It said, after he overran this country,
he attacked four Navy ships
that were transporting Doflamingo
and sank two of them but they struck back.
What?! Was he there at Dressrosa?!
He attacked the ships with the Navy admiral
and the former fleet admiral on board.
He must have a screw loose.
It said his death wasn't confirmed.
I think he's still alive.
We'll never forgive Jack!
Oh, the water's gone.
The ground is soft
because it's the elephant's back, right?
That's right.
We have to hurry! Let's take a shortcut!
Don't get shaken off!
Wow! It's awesome! This wani (alligator)!
He's Warney!
Zou is exciting!
Once I meet up with everyone,
I wanna explore it more!
It's really foggy.
Have we reached the abara (rib)?
It's ubara (right flank)!
Will Zoro and the others be there too?
I think so. I gave them directions
to our hidden fortress.
Shambles.
Oh, it's you guys!
Hey, Luffy! Where were you bitten?!
Do you still have your limbs?
It's you-teia guys.
Hey, you Nami-dog girl right there!
He's our captain!
You wanna eat him, don't you?!
I won't let you do that, you predatory tramp!
If you don't give us back him
and our friends who came here first,
you'll see these three swords fire up!
Oni Girya!
"Rya"?
I can't believe it.
I think you have the wrong idea.
What?!
But that's okay. We're here now.
What?
Look over there in the fog carefully...
There are guards and a gate to the fortress.
Wanda! Who are they-gara?
Are they the ones who invaded
the Whale Forest?!
They didn't mean any harm!
The Welcoming Bell didn't ring by mistake
and one of them got lost in the Whale Forest!
Open the gate and let everybody know!
That the Straw Hats are here!
What?! Is that who they-gara are?!
INSIDE THE FORTRESS
Nami!
Nami!!
Luffy and the others are here!
They're finally here!
Nami! Luffy and the others arrived!
They made it safely!
They did?! Really, Chopper?!
They're at the fortress gate!
Oh, your friends are here. That's good.
Nami!
I'm sorry.
I'm okay.
Let's go, Chopper!
Uh-huh!
They're important guests!
Prepare to welcome our
great saviors' friends!
Garchu!
Welcome, Straw Hats!
Welcome!
What?! What?!
Oh?! What the...?!
The atmosphere's quite upbeat!
This isn't what we heard about!
Garchu!
What's "Garchu"?
I thought the people of
your race hate humans.
Race, huh?
That's probably what those who don't know
other Minks think and get scared of.
Other Minks?
To us, you-teia guys are
just Monkey Minks who have less hair.
You're the same Mink Tribe,
just a different type.
Oh, so we humans are Monkey Minks.
That's right.
We judge someone by their character,
not by their race.
Garchu!
We take pride in
the mink (hair) covering our bodies
but you-teia guys have those beautiful...
..."lesser mink coats"
and quite a lot of us admire it.
"Lesser mink"?
That's what we call Minks with fewer hairs.
--There they are!
--Oh, you're right!
Oh, look! That's Nami and Chopper!
I'm glad that they're okay!
Nami!
Nami! I'm happy for you! Garchu!
Garchu!
I got caught! Let me through!
Alright! Garchu! Garchu!
That's great! Garchu!
They're very friendly!
That's so different from what I expected!
Luffy!
Everybody!
Oh, you guys!
I'm so happy to see you again!
Nami! Chopper!
Everybody!
Usopp!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Chopper!
So Sanji, Brook, and Momo are all fine too!
I'm sorry!
Sanji-kun is...
Now the detail of Sanji and the others'
deadly voyage to Zou is revealed!
While the Emperor, Big Mom's
ship was raining shells on them
and fierce offensive-and-defensive
battles raged,
Sanji and the rest were driven to the wall
but employed a tactic to recover!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Start to Counterattack! Great
Moves by the Twirly Hat Crew!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!