kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new adventure will take place.
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
which is as high as the clouds, is
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests, a zou (elephant)
that has been alive for a millennium.
as its name suggests,
a zou (elephant) that has been alive for a millennium.
as its name suggests, a zou (elephant)
that has been alive for a millennium.
as its name suggests,
a zou (elephant) that has been alive for a millennium.
It's awesome!
Kurau City was peaceful and relaxed.
They met the Mink Tribe who live there
So this is the back of the elephant!
Luffy and the rest met
Wanda and Carrot from the Mink Tribe
People were leading normal lives.
and later, reunited with Nami and the rest.
and were guided to the place
called the Rightflank Fortress.
They were talking with their friends,
loving their families,
The group visited Dogstorm,
King of the Day of
They met the Mink Tribe and
There, they finally reunited
with Nami and the others.
I'm sorry!
and enjoying the blessings of nature.
reunited with Nami and the others
at the Rightflank Fortress.
the Mokomo Dukedom, at his sanatorium.
But it happened half a month ago.
There, they listened to all the details of
the battle between the Minks...
And by 10 days ago,
most of the country had been destroyed.
Sanji-kun is...
Then they were guided to the sanatorium
...and the Beast Pirates led by Jack,
the Emperor Kaido's subordinate,
where Duke Dogstorm, the King of the
Day of the Mokomo Dukedom, rests.
The gate has been broken down! It's pirates!
Kick them out!
But on that day,
Nami and the others arrived here.
"Start to Counterattack!
Great Moves by the Twirly Hat Crew!"
that happened a half month ago.
Duke Dogstorm is the official ruler but...
That can only be described as a miracle!
...Master Cat Viper who guards the
If not for their courage
and Chopper's medical expertise,
The Fool of the Night woke up!
This man right here is...
old sacred Whale Forest
possesses the same right.
Let's retreat, Musketeers!
...the infamous Emperor
Kaido-sama's right-hand man!
every single person in the Mokomo Dukedom
would've been helplessly killed...
Aren't we gonna fight with them?
They really don't like each other.
One of the three henchmen
who are called "Disasters"!
No, the day-and-night shifts are working.
Jack the Drought-sama!
They had too many fights
We can stay on the offensive
without giving them a break.
That was horrible...
and they don't even wanna
face each other now.
I only have one demand!
Jack!
--Are you all right?
--I can't see anything!
Don't think you-gara are
the only unreasonable man here!
Bring Raizo here!
I know it's just happened and it still hurts
So one of them, from six in the morning
to six in the evening with the sun
Get off of me, monkey boy!
It's my country when the moon is up!
so if you don't wanna talk
about it, that's fine but...
Where are we now?
and another from six in the evening
to six in the morning with the moon.
No, I'll tell you everything.
You-teia people have the
right to know everything.
Th-The Thousand Sunny!
How pathetic they are!
I can't believe this! We got carried
all the way back to where we started?!
That's how they split their living hours.
Wanda! Duke Dogstorm said
he'd like to see the saviors!
We have no weaklings in this country!
You came looking for a warrior
from the Land of Wano, didn't you?
The day-and-night shifts
are affecting us too.
All our hard work...
All of us Minks are born
to be gifted fighters!
Okay, I'll be right up!
I wouldn't let any samurai
step onto the island!
You-teia guys, will you come with me?!
The people of the city are active
during the day.
Anyway, we need Nekozaemon
to make one more effort.
If we fight, both of our
troops will get hurt!
If they come in,
I'll be the first to bite them to death!
"A Threat Descends!
The Beast Pirates, Jack!"
And the people of the forest...
If you want to look for someone,
But he got soaking wet...
...are nocturnal...
could you at least have a talk with
the duke of our country?
I'm Cat Viper! The man who waits
for the dawn of the world!
I refuse!
Ink?
We've always lived
with the custom of having two rulers.
Gifters! Come forward!
Okay!
Even during the recent battle.
They didn't listen to us at all
and the fight began.
The peaceful Kurau City was...
You should've withdrawn
while the dog was treating you nicely!
...instantly turned into a battlefield!
By listening to Wanda-san's
story, you know why I said
Master!
"samurai" and "Land of Wano"
are taboo now, don't you?
I-It's a cat monster!
You're right.
So if you use those words,
Dammit, you monster!
you'll anger them and make them hate you.
Captain!
So, anyway...
Excuse my tongue!
You came for us!
The ninja that Kin'emon was talking about isn't here!
What a letdown!
Nekozaemon! Can you still do it?
"The Exterminated Capital!
The Twirly Hat Crew Arrive!"
Captain!
Go for it!
I missed you!
Duke Dogstorm!
Duke-sama!
All the members of the
Heart Pirates are here!
Stop, cat monster! Stop!
Duke-sama came to save us!
What?
Bepo, do you wanna squash him?
"The King of the Day!
Duke Dogstorm Appears!"
You're Jack, aren't you?
Sorry, sorry!
Stop this vandalization and violence now!
Captain, I'm so amazed to know
that you beat Doflamingo!
Nekozaemon can't go on any more.
No, that's Straw Hat-ya's...
But I feel bad and I can't
bring myself to say it to him.
We have a lot to catch up on!
Let's go deeper into the forest!
You must be the ruler of this country!
Okay.
Day and night, without break
the battle went on for five days.
Ninja?
THE RIGHTFLANK FORTRESS
"The King of the Night!
Master Cat Viper Emerges!"
Bone-Bone Chop!
Oh, the sun is setting!
We can't go any farther today!
Going through this passage is the shortest way to
get to Duke-sama's sanatorium.
Mm-hm! Let's go back to the ship
and climb again tomorrow!
Chop! Chop! Chop!
By "ninja," you mean
a warrior from the Land of Wano?
That's curious. Do those fruits emit light?
You-teia, do you know something?
That's right.
They light up the darkness of the night.
We're just teaching him a lesson about minkship!
So never mind!
Oh, that's interesting!
Duke-sama!
Garchu! Garchu!
There are other things
in the fortress that...
So you are...
But I'm sure I heard him
say "ninja" just now.
Indeed. I am the ruler of the Mokomo Dukedom!
--What's wrong?
--One of you is missing.
You-gara! Are you trying to
fend off all my spear attacks?!
Welcome!
No, no, he definitely
didn't say such a thing!
What?!
Boy! Where did Luffy go?!
No one's ever done it,
not even in this country!
Oh, "kanja (patient)"!
He was asking how the patient is doing!
Go to hell, cat monster!
Oh?
What are you doing, Luffy?!
Stop this vandalization and violence now!
I like how you drink!
Here, have another cup!
The patient?
Look at these grapes!
They're growing everywhere!
Oh, I heard him wrong!
You-teia people are kind!
I swear that the person you-gara
people are looking for isn't here!
Go ahead and drink!
I can drink as much as I like!
It's our special "Monkey Wine."
It's made from the abundance of fruits in the forest.
You care about our Duke-sama so much!
Come join me! It's very sweet!
It's no use! This is a senseless fight!
Of course, we do!
Yeah! It tastes good!
Are you gonna drink more?!
I'm already full!
Ni... Ni...
You silly animal!
Come back here now!
How many times do we have to tell you?! Huh?!
Garchu!
Okay!
It doesn't hurt at all...
If you don't want us to destroy your country,
See! I knew that'd happen!
Go away, you fools!
Don't press yourselves against me!
And are we almost there
at the patient's house?
just give us the samurai already!
What?! Let's play!
Yes, I see Duke-sama's sanatorium already.
Oh man, that was good!
Let me give you love bites!
I like this place!
Let us garchu!
Thank you for coming with me.
I'll tell you the rest of the story later.
I'm so happy to hear that.
Let me lick you!
Shut up! Don't be such a baby!
And how many times do we
have to tell you-gara?!
Although, we don't usually use this place.
Whoa-whoa, don't get mad, Zoro!
DUKE DOGSTORM'S SANATORIUM
That person is not here!
The capital of the Mokomo Dukedom was...
Not here! Not here! Not here!!
Look how well they're treating us!
You're so rude!
We're sorry, Shishilian-sama!
...Kurau City which you-teia people saw.
Look all over the country
and bring him here, I said!
Please forgive us!
Let's play!
You're dead!
I can't drink like this!
That's impossible!
Please overlook these cultural differences.
Minkship is a friendly gesture to us.
That's enough!
Vibrant and bustling.
That's what it was like in Kurau City.
We'll kill them all!
Shishilian-sama is raging out of control!
So you call it minkship.
What's going on?
Destroy everything in the country!
Rub-rub, fluff-fluff... It feels good, right?
Understood!
Neigh!
We got some good ones today!
Shishilian-dono! What's the matter?!
In that case, we'll just fight back!
Oh, Wanda!
They-gara kept saying sweet things so...
I ran fast and picked up the ones that...
You don't have to hold back!
Rub yourself against me as much as you want!
...the morning Rain-Ruption provided!
Wait!
I planned on finishing you off quickly
but you're quite tough.
...I just pushed them off the cliff!
It's all fresh today!
FULL-POWER SHISHILIAN (A LION MINK)
THE CAPTAIN OF THE DOGSTORM MUSKETEERS
--Don't touch me!
--Hey, you jerk! Let them have minkship!
Generosity!
Buzz off! I'm not playing with you!
Love! Romance! Babies!
--Oink! Here you go!
--What? That's too many...
What's that? Huh?
Sugar! Honey!
Are you trying to mess with me?!
I'll kill you-gara!
Well, you always shop at our store.
So that's a treat for you.
It's delicious! What kind of meat is this?!
Don't ever talk about sweet stuff
in my presence!
I'd like to see you try.
That's hippo.
And these are lizard, alligator, and frog.
Little guy. Thank you for
shopping with us! Oink!
Or I'll bite out your windpipe!
Uh-huh!
Now, climb up here without help!
We don't eat animals with fur.
It's been a while.
Oh, did you gain some weight?
What'll you do by yourself?!
But why do you welcome us like this?
You got fatter too!
He's so strict but very cool!
Because you-teia guys are
our saviors' friends!
Garchu! I'm so glad that
both of us are doing fine!
Saviors... What happened exactly?
It's already morning!
Alright, stand up.
What? Are you guys gonna switch again?!
He's doing this to us because he loves us.
What?!
N-Nooooo!!
Duke-sama!
Why did you drop your sword?!
Hi! It's a lovely day, isn't it?
I wish I could bite you to death now
but I'll wait until tonight!
I know.
This is his way of trying to train cowards like us.
It is! Drop in for a cup of tea later.
Don't get killed by the dog!
Hey, Bepo! Let's go!
He's so generous!
I'm getting a little bit drowsy...
What did you just say?!
--What? Master, I still wanna...
--Just come with me!
We're not gonna resist!
You can search the country or the island...
Kurau City was peaceful and relaxed.
Master!
You can't get away, you bastard!
...for that samurai, all you want!
What?!
People were leading normal lives.
How could you talk about such sappy stuff
like love or generosity...
So stop the destruction!
They were talking with their friends,
loving their families,
E-Everybody!
...so soon after I told you not to!?
and enjoying the blessings of nature.
Haven't you given up yet, Jack?!
This country has a glorious history!
Brook!
What a relief! I read in the newspaper!
I refuse!
But it happened half a month ago.
Jack-sama, I'll handle him!
But still, he's cool...
--No, I will!
--I'll do it!
I'm glad that you're all okay!
What in the world happened?!
Duke-sama, run!
Duke! Leave the small fry to us!
Luffy-san!
We're sorry!
We'll never say anything sweet again!
By the time we got here,
the city was completely destroyed.
What happened to you?!
--All right then!
--Shishilian-dono.
I'm sorry about Sanji-san!
What?!
I'm too ashamed to face you!
As if a storm had just swept through.
They-teia are the Straw Hats.
Duke-sama!
But I don't have a facial surface anyway.
Oh?! Hey, aren't you with Momo?!
It was 17 days ago to be exact.
Yes, of course,
he's okay but it seems like...
Thank you for saving my country!
Yes, the first time in a month and a half
since Bepo and the others arrived,
That's our Jack-sama!
...he doesn't really like the Minks.
I'll be indebted to you forever!
the visitor's bell rang
all over the Mokomo Dukedom.
What? He doesn't like nice people like them?
You bastard! How dare you kill Duke-sama!
Shishilian-dono puts all
his power into everything.
No. He shuts himself in a room
and never comes out.
But that was...
Calm down, Wanda!
What an annoying lion.
But that's good for us.
Shishilian-dono!
...the seldom-heard Raiding Bell!
Because of you-gara people,
I have to endure that stupid cat's smell!
I don't know what you're
talking about at all.
Who is your-gara captain?!
I am.
I thought so.
Luffy-san, could I have a word with you?
Oh!
So you-gara are Nami and the others' captain!
Great! I couldn't wait to see you!
Come this way.
Garchu!
I thank you, really, from the bottom of my heart!
All of you newcomers to Zou, come here!
You too, Zoro-san!
Ow, ow, ow, ow! It's hot!
The duke is expecting you!
You can go in! Hurry up!
Where is Kin'emon-san now?
Whoa-whoa! What's with that dog?!
He should be arriving soon.
What's wrong with him?!
He withstood Jack-sama's attack!
I see. That's perfect.
We rotated our combatants by day and night
I actually wanna ask you a favor...
That's our Duke Dogstorm!
and continued fighting for two days,
three days, four days, and so on.
I didn't know they had such a strong guy!
Just say it.
Luffy and everybody!
Come closer.
I thought this was a
fairyland of fuzzy animals!
But Jack's reinforcements kept coming from
I want you to try not to use words like
"samurai" or "Land of Wano" in this country.
the sea and we could hardly fend them off.
It was like fighting a
wave of countless zombies!
Don't use them if you can.
Screw you!
However we were steadily
overwhelming the enemy!
If you use those words,
you might offend many people
Our boss, Jack-sama
I gotta warn everybody!
is a great pirate renowned
throughout the New World!
He's huge!
I can say there was only one
that we couldn't bring down and that was...
and anger them or make them hate you.
The bounty on his head is...
Offend?
DUKE DOGSTORM
THE KING OF THE DAY, THE MOKOMO DUKEDOM
Anger? Hate?
...one billion berries!
...Jack!
No! Don't tell me...
Why "samurai"...
Well, this country was actually...
He is, indeed, a monster!
Duke-sama! I'm glad that you're okay!
So just because you're a little strong,
don't think you can push your luck!
I-Is he that strong?
This underling sure is obnoxious.
What's that bell?
That's the Raiding Bell!
He is.
I found you!
--What?!
--Raiding?!
Please!
No wonder a young lady like
you-gara doesn't know.
Hmmm.
It's a false accusation!
We're not hiding the samurai!
The guy who even this old man couldn't
beat was Kaido's subordinate.
Baron Corpse!
It rarely rings.
Here they come!
Let me make it clear!
Unbelievable!
"Corpse"?!
We'll call off our attack as
soon as we get the samurai!
But the enemy was having a hard time too.
The gate has been broken down! It's pirates!
I think Jack got tired of the two rulers
who he couldn't take down
You'll reach the Rightflank Forest!
If you don't have him, it's your own fault!
And you'll find the corpse
of your-teia friend there!
Kick them out!
Wanda. I'm sorry to make you worry.
C-Corpse?!
so he finally brought out a weapon
on the fifth day!
That doesn't make any sense.
--The corpse she was talking about was...
--...Brook!
So you-gara people are the Straw Hats?
It was...
Let me tell you one more thing.
We call him so with affection.
Yeah.
I like destroying stuff.
That's very confusing.
You saved us in every way.
Thank you very much.
To be honest, I was surprised...
...a poison-gas weapon.
I heard my crew saved your people
but I haven't gotten to hear the whole story yet.
This is certainly a disaster!
I didn't know there was such
a tempting race in this world!
--Gas?
--That's right, Luffy.
This country was ruined
by Caesar's poison-gas weapon!
Well, you-gara and the rest saved us too,
Straw Hat Luffy-kun.
Something stinks.
That horrible smell is getting stronger!
Caesar created the weapon
and Doflamingo trafficked it
Stop it! Help!
All we can do is try to take down the
enemy leader and stop the battle now!
--We Dog Minks... h-have a thing for bones!
--Stop chewing on me!
and it made it all the way to Kaido!
Caesar!
Anyway, I bet you're strong!
I mean, really strong!
Kill them all!
--He's quite popular.
--Stop licking...
How stupid...
Let's go!
What?! That's rude!
Duke-sama is the mightiest warrior in the country!
Luffy, what happened to Tra-guy,
by the way?
Cutting up the forest along the way,
the enemy invaded our peaceful city.
Hey, stop.
That's not what you call a loser.
It all happened so quickly.
Oh, he went to the Bear Forest.
You're not a loser!
Bear?
The enemies were surely troublesome
but we had the upper hand!
Feeling such unusual movement,
Zunesha roared!
The deadly gas was filling the whole
country at the speed of a blast wave!
Tra-guy-kun went to see
his friends of the Heart
Pirates including Bepo...
How could anyone escape that?!
...in the Whale Forest.
Hey! More importantly,
what should we do about Sanji-kun?!
Who were they?! What did they want?!
Like I said before, he left a note.
So don't you think it's gonna be alright?
If our vicious enemies want
something that we don't have,
That's horrible!
He's drooling!
Yeah, it's not like he was kidnapped.
I know how you feel! He-teia saved us too!
I'm worried because it didn't look right!
how can we give it to them?
What a delicious-looking savior.
Strong old man...
He must've felt frustrated.
I'm sorry! We couldn't do anything!
You're not fully recovered yet so...
--not now.
--Not now or ever!
You don't need to cry!
Oh, come on! A little won't hurt!
Well, you know what, guys?
Frankly, we're just confused right now.
"A little" could kill me!
The gas filled up
the whole city and half of the forest
You don't know how much I got sucked on and chewed on
the past few days!
We only have a rough idea of what's going on.
and totally paralyzed us.
He's right! The last time we talked,
you guys said you were facing Big Mom's ship!
Except for the people who evacuated
to the back of the fortress,
Well, let's not talk about the loss.
nearly everyone was killed!
You-gara, that straw hat
looks quite good on you.
Now we finally got to Zou and there
I don't even want to remember...
are those talking animals
on the elephant's back
...what happened after that!
and the city's ruined!
I was once...
We thought the Mink Tribe was our enemy
but instead, they welcomed us so warmly!
Oh, I can't remember who it was!
Answer the question!
They even told us we're
their saviors' friends!
That cat...
Where's the warrior from the Land of Wano?
Master Cat Viper.
What a tough guy.
Could you tell us everything in detail, Nami?
He's not here!
I was once traveling across the seas
with that one.
That won't work.
What's happened to your group
since you left Dressrosa 11 days ago?
A mammoth?!
Shanks who is one of the Four Emperors now
was wearing that kind of hat then.
Why's that prehistoric animal here?!
They kept asking questions
they knew the answer to!
Alright, give him to us now!
Yeah, I guess I was a little upset.
What?!
Old man, do you know Shanks?! How?!
Then they brutalized our soldiers
and ruined our country!
I know you have a warrior from the
Land of Wano named Raizo here!
I'm gonna crush you up!
Okay, I'll tell you
everything as it happened.
That's how he broke open
the gate to Kurau City!
We heard people screaming and crying
throughout the country...
I got this hat from him and...
Raizo?
Oh, I give up!
Do whatever you want with me!
Is that what your enemies wanted
and you people didn't have?
I'll take that challenge!
He fell asleep!
What we encountered that day
off the coast of Dressrosa was...
It's already six o'clock.
It's only six! He's not a kid!
Wanda...
Hey, wake up!
Tell me how you know Shanks!
...the Big Mom Pirates'
enormous singing ship!
Hey! Hey!
Are you okay?
Singing?!
Stop it, Luffy! He's still injured!
Ship! Ship!
Like I mentioned earlier,
the Mokomo Dukedom is governed by two rulers all the time.
Yes, I am.
A warrior from the Land of Wano? Raizo?
Its figurehead is singing, isn't it?
We don't know such a person!
Then, they found Master Cat Viper
Ship! Ship!
Duke Dogstorm is the official ruler but...
D-Don't mess with this country! Get out!
and the Guardians who were
paralyzed by the gas...
Their combatants that we could identify
...Master Cat Viper who guards the old sacred Whale Forest
possesses the same right.
were the duo that Luffy met
on the Fish-Man Island.
...and did the same to them.
Mama! I see Caesar! Grr!
So it was real!
The unknown country of the Mink Tribe!
But when they saw
they weren't getting anywhere...
PEKOMS
A COMBATANT OF THE BIG MOM PIRATES
What does it have to do
with him falling asleep?!
You silly animals talk a lot!
our tough ones were crucified and tortured.
They have him with them as we thought-bon!
Identify yourselves!
Who are you-gara people?!
Duke Dogstorm, he's awesome!
BARON TAMAGO
A COMBATANT OF THE BIG MOM PIRATES
I said "Stop"!
He's strong like I thought!
Who do you think
you're asking to identify themselves?!
They really don't like each other.
Where's the warrior from the Land of Wano?!
Let's sink their ship
and recover just Caesar-soir!
I don't know!
This man right here is...
We wouldn't hide anyone like that!
When they come face to face,
they might try to kill one another.
...the infamous Emperor
Kaido-sama's right-hand man!
And another one...
Please stop...
One of the three henchmen
who are called "Disasters"!
But the enemy gave even
the mightiest warrior in
No one in this country
knows anything about that!
JACK THE DROUGHT
A PROMINENT MEMBER OF THE BEAST PIRATES
THE CAPTAIN OF THE MAMMOTH
Jack the Drought-sama!
this country and the Three
Musketeers a hard time...
He's one of the Worst Generation.
Jack the Drought! Sounds super bad.
We're really dying for nothing!
You have no mercy!
The land that he passed through...
...will be destroyed -
ruined as if a drought occurred.
He didn't listen to what
others had to say at all.
Capone "Gang" Bege!
Bege?
What a pain.
Seems like they became
Big Mom's subordinates.
Now, hand over Raizo,
the warrior from the Land of Wano, to us!
He's got a billion-berry bounty.
That's twice Luffy's, you know!
--Kill one another?!
--Why?!
They came for Caesar
but he was more scared of them.
You don't want your quiet life
in which you can hold your kid...
SHEEPSHEAD
THE HEADLINER OF THE GIFTERS,
THE BEAST PIRATES
I don't know why.
How strong this Jack guy is!
I heard they used to be best friends.
...to be threatened!
But, frankly speaking,
we had no chance to get away from them.
I won't let this go even if I die, Jack!
Doesn't matter!
I'll kick his ass someday!
But they're both well-respected kings
so even if they fight, it'll be an equal match.
How can we hand over someone who...
And how did the battle go?
And we knew they'd take us down
if nothing was done!
Or do you wanna fight?! Huh?!
Until the day I curse you-gara
to death with my cat-grudge!
It got more intense from there.
They had too many fights
and they don't even wanna face each other now.
Roger that, Captain!
But how about giving us permission!
We definitely don't want to fight.
Permission?
Yes. Permission to...
So one of them, from six in the morning
to six in the evening with the sun
Mon-ji!
Those tragic events lasted one whole day
and on the sixth day,
However, we need you to listen to us
in order to come to an agreement.
...launch a counterattack
against Big Mom's ship!
and another from six in the evening
to six in the morning with the moon.
maybe because Jack was satisfied
with the destruction
Yeah, you got it.
I already picked a fight with her!
or tired of hearing the same answer,
We can't hand over someone who isn't here.
All right, guys!
We'll be waiting for you at Zou!
he left a few dozen of his men behind
and departed from the island.
Jack-san, we Minks don't lie.
That's how they split their living hours.
All of you, be safe!
That won't work!
Roger that!
They hate each other that much?
--That's too awful!
--There was no salvation.
What was the name of the person?
Alright, guys!
Raizo!
No, that actually saved us too.
Yes, if you want to look for this Raizo,
you can go from door to door...
I didn't realize the
doctors were sleeping too!
Oh, you were up!
Prepare yourselves for the worst!
All of the people in this fortress
should be sleeping now.
I noticed that
when I read Jack's obituary in the newspaper.
Hyena Grip!
S-Shishilian-dono!
He has no mercy
even for women, children, or elderly people!
Leave it to us - the Three Musketeers!
That infernal monster!
He's not going to listen to us!
I'm getting tired. Grr...
JACK DIES!
The PROMINENT MEMBER OF THE BEAST PIRATES
"JACK THE DROUGHT"
Oh, so this is Jack.
Ship! Ship!
Screw the Three Musketeers!
Are we here to talk, Gin-Rummy?
You are...
He sure looks strong!
Shishilian! Always at full power!
We the Gifters Grip Trio will...
Let's get out of here with Coup de Burst!
But I'm relieved if he's really dead.
You don't have to yell! I hear you!
No, Jack-sama.
We're here to capture a samurai.
...Beat you all to bits!
What about Gaon Cannon?!
The day you-gara people took down Doflamingo,
The day-and-night shifts
are affecting us too.
No! We don't have enough Cola!
I have another idea instead!
How dare you do that to our people!
Raizo is not a samurai, you idiot!
He's a ninja!
If it's a three-on-three battle,
we the Three Musketeers will...
Jack left this country.
The people of the city are active
during the day.
Cut it out, Sheepshead-sama!
Okay? Listen carefully!
Win! Win! Win!
He left here to go save Doflamingo.
Samurai is a general term for
all kinds of warriors from the Land of Wano!
And the people of the forest...
Either way is okay!
I guess they had some sort
of a deep connection.
If you have an idea, just do it!
...are nocturnal...
Samurai and ninja aren't the same!
That's our Shishilian-dono!
Help us if you wanna survive!
So the ones who drove that monster
out of here were...
I only have one demand!
He said "three-on-three"
but he took them down single-handedly!
Bring Raizo here!
Brook! Let's fight them at the stern
and let them drop their guard!
So cool!
At full power...
...you-gara people.
Okay!
He fell asleep.
--Nami-san, please take the helm!
--Got it!
They're funny!
He fell asleep again!
I see!
What are you doing?!
Just hit it already-bon!
Given all that,
I'm even more grateful to you all
and feel it was truly a miracle!
We've always lived
with the custom of having two rulers.
Here comes a Rain-Ruption!
--Musketeers, herd the Warneys!
--Yes, sir!
We're alive now,
M-Mammoth?!
really thanks to you-teia guys!
Even during the recent battle.
Soul Parade!
Hey, Usopp! She said it was a mammoth!
Oh no!
The fight between Jack's group and us in Kurau City
was intensifying.
We arrived here
the very next day after Jack left!
What?! Is that what you
find most interesting?!
What the...
Sheepshead-sama! Look at that!
She mentioned the Four Emperors!
Rain? A big splash of water
is falling towards us!
Chopper-san, there they go!
So it was Kaido's subordinates
who attacked this country.
Monster Point!
That's right.
Cho-Cho-Cho-Cho-Cho... Chopperemon?!
We don't know anyone named Raizo!
Catch, Chopper!
Where is the samurai?!
Stop asking for the impossible!
We really don't know!
He is as steady as rock
even with the Rain-Ruption.
How can we tell you
about someone we don't even know?!
Wh-Wh-What are you gonna do to me?!
Grab my hand!
Is that...
Then, search the length and breadth
of the country! Pleasures!
...Zou?!
It's the blessed rain!
We can turn the tables now!
Give us Raizo!
No! Let go of me!
What an unbelievable amount of rainfall!
I warn you!
I don't like the idea of landing here!
I'll get even with you bastard!
How could you use my body like a bag?!
Get out of this country!
My boy!
Silly kid! Show them how merciless we can be!
Don't be intimidated by such rain!
We won't help you
if you don't stop resisting!
Hey.
No!
You bastards!
All yours, Sanji!
Shut up and keep going!
Damn! I'll get even with you buttholes!
Take their alligators!
--That's Caesar! Grr!
--What are they doing-bon?!
Nice pitch, Chopper!
Is that...
Thanks to the Rain-Ruption,
we briefly gained the upper hand,
Ouch!
How can he fly?!
What the...
but once the water drained away,
they came back again.
Find him!
Poele a Frire...
I know Raizo is in this country!
You squirt!
Get him!
Sanji-kun!
...Spectre!
Damn you monster!
The gate is...
Seems like it was broken open
with tremendous force.
There was obviously an invasion!
--Oh no! Grr!
--Turn away-bon!
A-An invasion?!
Are they our enemies too?!
Spit it out! Where is Raizo?!
Brook! Look after Nami-san here.
I'll go check inside.
Find him!
Ship!
No problem.
I-I'll look after Onami too!
The starboard side's been damaged!
Stop!
Don't destroy the city anymore!
Chopper! Caesar! Let's go!
Help!
Why should I go along...
Shut up and get moving!
See you later!
Don't take too long!
Guys! They're getting away from us!
I can't believe there's a forest
on an elephant's back.
Okay! It's my turn!
Climate Baton!
What's the matter?
I have a bad feeling.
Weather...
If nothing is done...
...Egg!
Ouch!
Where's the samurai?!
Yeah?
Come hatch, rain clouds!
I don't know! I really don't know!
That's Master Cat Viper's roar!
Me too.
Then, go to hell.
The Fool of the Night woke up!
What are you guys doing?
Let's retreat, Musketeers!
Here come the Musketeers!
--What?!
--Aren't we gonna fight with them?
Rain Tempo!
This is really elephant's skin!
It's so flabby!
Great! Let them-gara handle it!
Everyone else, just step back!
No, the day-and-night shifts are working.
We can stay on the offensive
without giving them a break.
Minimize damage!
THE MUSKETEERS
It looks abandoned.
You're right!
Ow!
Try to disarm them!
There's no guard or
gatekeeper. What happened?
Jack!
Ship?
Don't think you-gara are
the only unreasonable man here!
--Let's go!
--Okay!
Why did the weather change
in just that area-bon?!
Somebody, help!
Wh-What is it?!
We're gonna lose them! Grr!
What's with them?!
Anywhere you go, you can find a fool!
What?!
How pathetic they are!
Was she the one who talked?!
We have no weaklings in this country!
What's going on?!
Oh, he definitely looks like a villain!
That means she is a victim!
All of us Minks are born
to be gifted fighters!
Good job, Nami-san!
This way!
Even a baby knows how to defend himself!
What's wrong with them-teia?
So creepy!
Wait, you little squirrel!
We just wanna crucify you
and ask some questions!
Only you guys could do that!
PROTECT
Who are you guys?!
That doesn't make me blush, you idiot!
You-gara people, do you think you can
fight all the people in this country?
It's my country when the moon is up!
Brook! Can you handle them?!
Oh, that was a white-knuckler!
Okay.
There are some odd warriors here.
I won't let any invaders get away!
We even have highly-trained Musketeers
whose abilities are beyond words!
That's super!
--Is that a race we don't know?!
--They-teia have strange abilities!
That's great!
THE GUARDIANS
Stop it!
Well, it was a big deal I guess but...
If we fight, both of our
troops will get hurt!
Don't think you can get out of here alive!
And how many days did it take to Zou
from there?
Watch out for those with black horns!
--It's giant!
--A cat monster!
If you want to look for someone,
We arrived here the next day.
could you at least have a talk with
the duke of our country?
Seems like Zou was nearby at that time.
A skeleton?
Yes, it's a skeleton.
--Where is Raizo?!
--We don't have such a person here!
That was 10 days ago.
What are you?!
He's a skeleton!
Can't you see that, Sheepshead-sama?!
As far as I could see,
A talk?
the oldest sign of destruction
in the city at the center of Zou was...
Shut up! Whatever it is,
I'll wipe it out if it gets in my way!
Wolf Grip!
...from a little more than two weeks ago.
Go!
Jack-sama!
His hand turned into a wolf!
Master, the city is...
Go to hell!
That's right.
Never mind! I heard what's going on.
And by 10 days ago,
most of the country had been destroyed.
Wanda!
I refuse!
Soul Parade!
You came looking for a warrior
from the Land of Wano, didn't you?
You-gara, step back!
Gifters! Come forward!
But on that day,
Nami and the others arrived here.
Shishilian-dono!
Okay!
I wouldn't let any samurai
step onto the island!
That can only be described as a miracle!
Ice Burn!
If not for their courage
and Chopper's medical expertise,
If they come in,
I'd be the first to bite them to death!
every single person in the Mokomo Dukedom
would've been helplessly killed...
--Yes!
--Good job, Bonekichi!
What's with their-gara bodies?!
THE THREE DOGSTORM MUSKETEERS
I'm Cat Viper!
The Three Musketeers!
Thank you, Brook!
The man who waits for the dawn of the world!
A talking skeleton and eel!
I'm scared!
All available Musketeers,
lead the citizens to the forest!
Alright! Destroy the country
and find the samurai!
MASTER CAT VIPER
(THE KING OF THE NIGHT)
THE WARDEN OF THE WHALE FOREST
Alright! Let's evacuate to the forest!
Wait! Hey, you!
What's happening on this island?!
We have no choice.
Let's fight, everyone!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Maybe she doesn't like us.
I know it's just happened and it still hurts
--Let's chase her!
--Okay!
Stop!
so if you don't wanna talk
about it, that's fine but...
I'll beat the hell out of them at full power!
No, I'll tell you everything.
You-teia people have the
right to know everything.
They didn't listen to us at all
and the fight began.
Hey!
Sheepshead-sama! You moron!
Everybody!
Damn! Let's chase them!
The peaceful Kurau City was...
Jack-sama!
D-Duke-sama has...
...instantly turned into a battlefield!
So that's why everybody moved to
the Rightflank Fortress here.
Who are they?!
What happened?!
That's right.
Those who could walk
helped those who couldn't
It must be the ancient version
of the Elephant-Elephant Fruit.
Duke-sama has woken up!
and carried them here.
You ate such a rare fruit!
Hey. So in the end,
They've still got this many soldiers.
you don't know why that Jack guy was
looking for the samurai, do you?
That's great!
What's going on here?!
Duke-sama... He's all right now...
It's filled with gas.
Dammit, you monster!
No. We also don't know
how they-teia got to this island
Wanda!
Are those all animals on the ground?!
I'm happy for you, Wanda!
Idiot! They're the Mink Tribe!
Don't you know?!
or what made them think
that the samurai was here.
You fools are about to experience a terror
that you've never known before!
Okay! Let's go examine his condition now!
I bet the mammoth was so big!
You should've withdrawn
while the dog was treating you nicely!
Miyagi! Tristan!
Don't get excited!
Now isn't the time for that!
Oh, wait for me!
Anyway, let's go back to the forest for now!
We'll be killed by the gas!
Master!
Okay, okay!
Let me go at it and learn from you!
Hey, you-gara people...
We have just as many soldiers
as some major countries!
Oh, it's a suspension bridge!
Dr. Miyagi! You're hopping too much!
Hey, Luffy!
What are you doing?! Hey! Stop!
Wanda! Duke Dogstorm said
he'd like to see the saviors!
He's alive!
What?! A talking animal?!
We're gonna fall! We're gonna fall!
So are you.
Tsk! Seems like they're still alive.
Okay, I'll be right up!
You-teia guys, will you come with me?!
Yeah but who's Dogstorm?
You're not their-gara's allies,
are you?
Hey, stop, you idiot!
Get your hands off of it!
Duke Dogstorm!
I'm Pedro! Will you help me?
And then there's us too!
He's the duke of the Mokomo Dukedom.
Oh, that was fun!
Duke-sama!
Which means he's the ruler of the country!
No, it wasn't!
Please!
Duke-sama came to save us!
Bepo!
He'd been in a coma ever
since the city was wiped out.
Duke Dogstorm and Master Cat Viper
need to be treated as soon as possible!
You-gara guys are still under my care!
Let's keep going.
We'll get to Duke-sama's sanatorium soon.
You don't need to fight!
So has the other one.
It's not gonna work that way, Master!
The other one?!
By listening to Wanda-san's story,
Yes! This country has two rulers!
Although I became a pirate,
this is still my home!
you know why I said "samurai" and "Land
of Wano" are taboo now, don't you?
"King of the Day" - Duke Dogstorm!
--To us...
--...It's our friend's home!
Otherwise, they're going to die...
Duke Dogstorm!
You're right.
What bad people!
Don't speak as if you're full-fledged.
"King of the Night" - Master Cat Viper!
So if you use those words,
I'll destroy everything!
you'll anger them and make them hate you.
The country of Zou has been protected
by those two rulers!
You're Jack, aren't you?
We'll fight back!
The world is waiting for them.
So, anyway...
Stop this vandalization and violence now!
Those two men...
We shall never ever...
The ninja that Kin'emon was
talking about isn't here!
...let them die!
What a letdown!
You must be the ruler of this country!
What?
Electro sparks the fire away!
The Rain-Ruption pours down!
There isn't much time left
The Raid Bell suddenly rings
all over the peaceful Mokomo Dukedom!
Jack, Dogstorm, and Cat
Viper put on a display
The Gifters, a creepy group
of Devil Fruit eaters,
for the wounded and downed Minks
as they hover
and the Musketeers, an elite
corps of the Mink Tribes,
When Duke Dogstorm and the
Musketeers are desperately
between life and death,
despairing for their lives!
of animalistic savagery
beyond human understanding!
The earth-rumblings herald Emperor
are thrown into a deadly struggle!
However, Chopper and the others
stand up to save all of them!
Kaido's right hand man,
Jack the Drought!
fighting a defensive war to stop Jack,
However, when it seems like they are helpless
When it seems like the Minks have seized
a slim chance of winning
after their deadly struggle,
before the overwhelmingly strong Jack,
the other raging ruler runs through the forest at dusk,
roaring with anger!
At the critical moment when
the outlook is unclear,
A tragic event that happened
to Wanda and her people,
the mightiest warrior of
the Minks finally shows up!
Jack impatiently executes
a horrifying secret plan!
the Twirly Hat Crew take bold
and compassionate action!
and their fierce fight to protect
the country are now revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The King of the Night! Master Cat Viper Emerges!"
"A Threat Descends! The Beast Pirates, Jack!"
"The Exterminated Capital!
The Twirly Hat Crew Arrive!"
"The Time Limit Closes in!
The Bond Between the Mink Tribe and the Crew!"
"The King of the Day! Duke Dogstorm Appears!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!