kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests,
a zou (elephant) that has been alive for a millennium.
Luffy and the rest met
Wanda and Carrot from the Mink Tribe
and were guided to the place
called the Rightflank Fortress.
I'm sorry!
Sanji-kun is...
"Start to Counterattack!
Great Moves by the Twirly Hat Crew!"
That was horrible...
--Are you all right?
--I can't see anything!
Get off of me, monkey boy!
Where are we now?
Th-The Thousand Sunny!
I can't believe this! We got carried
all the way back to where we started?!
All our hard work...
Anyway, we need Nekozaemon
to make one more effort.
But he got soaking wet...
Ink?
I-It's a cat monster!
Excuse my tongue!
Nekozaemon! Can you still do it?
Go for it!
Stop, cat monster! Stop!
Nekozaemon can't go on any more.
But I feel bad and I can't
bring myself to say it to him.
Oh, the sun is setting!
We can't go any farther today!
Mm-hm! Let's go back to the ship
and climb again tomorrow!
Welcome!
I like how you drink!
Here, have another cup!
Go ahead and drink!
It's our special "Monkey Wine."
It's made from the abundance of fruits in the forest.
Yeah! It tastes good!
Go away, you fools!
Don't press yourselves against me!
What?! Let's play!
Let me give you love bites!
Let us garchu!
Let me lick you!
Shut up! Don't be such a baby!
Whoa-whoa, don't get mad, Zoro!
Look how well they're treating us!
You're so rude!
Let's play!
I can't drink like this!
Please overlook these cultural differences.
Minkship is a friendly gesture to us.
So you call it minkship.
Rub-rub, fluff-fluff... It feels good, right?
You don't have to hold back!
Rub yourself against me as much as you want!
--Don't touch me!
--Hey, you jerk! Let them have minkship!
Buzz off! I'm not playing with you!
It's delicious! What kind of meat is this?!
That's hippo.
And these are lizard, alligator, and frog.
We don't eat animals with fur.
But why do you welcome us like this?
Because you-teia guys are
our saviors' friends!
Saviors... What happened exactly?
N-Nooooo!!
E-Everybody!
Brook!
What a relief! I read in the newspaper!
I'm glad that you're all okay!
Luffy-san!
What happened to you?!
I'm sorry about Sanji-san!
I'm too ashamed to face you!
But I don't have a facial surface anyway.
Oh?! Hey, aren't you with Momo?!
Yes, of course,
he's okay but it seems like...
...he doesn't really like the Minks.
What? He doesn't like nice people like them?
No. He shuts himself in a room
and never comes out.
But that's good for us.
I don't know what you're
talking about at all.
I thought so.
Luffy-san, could I have a word with you?
Come this way.
All of you newcomers to Zou, come here!
You too, Zoro-san!
Where is Kin'emon-san now?
He should be arriving soon.
I see. That's perfect.
I actually wanna ask you a favor...
Just say it.
Come closer.
I want you to try not to use words like
"samurai" or "Land of Wano" in this country.
Don't use them if you can.
If you use those words,
you might offend many people
and anger them or make them hate you.
Offend?
Anger? Hate?
Why "samurai"...
Well, this country was actually...
I found you!
Baron Corpse!
Here they come!
"Corpse"?!
You'll reach the Rightflank Forest!
And you'll find the corpse
of your-teia friend there!
C-Corpse?!
--The corpse she was talking about was...
--...Brook!
We call him so with affection.
That's very confusing.
To be honest, I was surprised...
I didn't know there was such
a tempting race in this world!
Stop it! Help!
--We Dog Minks... h-have a thing for bones!
--Stop chewing on me!
--He's quite popular.
--Stop licking...
How stupid...
Luffy, what happened to Tra-guy,
by the way?
Oh, he went to the Bear Forest.
Bear?
Tra-guy-kun went to see
his friends of the Heart
Pirates including Bepo...
...in the Whale Forest.
Hey! More importantly,
what should we do about Sanji-kun?!
Like I said before, he left a note.
So don't you think it's gonna be alright?
Yeah, it's not like he was kidnapped.
I'm worried because it didn't look right!
I'm sorry! We couldn't do anything!
You don't need to cry!
Well, you know what, guys?
Frankly, we're just confused right now.
We only have a rough idea of what's going on.
He's right! The last time we talked,
you guys said you were facing Big Mom's ship!
Now we finally got to Zou and there
are those talking animals
on the elephant's back
and the city's ruined!
We thought the Mink Tribe was our enemy
but instead, they welcomed us so warmly!
They even told us we're
their saviors' friends!
Could you tell us everything in detail, Nami?
What's happened to your group
since you left Dressrosa 11 days ago?
Yeah, I guess I was a little upset.
Okay, I'll tell you
everything as it happened.
Oh, I give up!
Do whatever you want with me!
What we encountered that day
off the coast of Dressrosa was...
...the Big Mom Pirates'
enormous singing ship!
Singing?!
Ship! Ship!
Its figurehead is singing, isn't it?
Their combatants that we could identify
were the duo that Luffy met
on the Fish-Man Island.
Mama! I see Caesar! Grr!
PEKOMS
A COMBATANT OF THE BIG MOM PIRATES
They have him with them as we thought-bon!
BARON TAMAGO
A COMBATANT OF THE BIG MOM PIRATES
Let's sink their ship
and recover just Caesar-soir!
And another one...
He's one of the Worst Generation.
Capone "Gang" Bege!
Bege?
Seems like they became
Big Mom's subordinates.
They came for Caesar
but he was more scared of them.
But, frankly speaking,
we had no chance to get away from them.
And we knew they'd take us down
if nothing was done!
Roger that, Captain!
But how about giving us permission!
Permission?
Yes. Permission to...
...launch a counterattack
against Big Mom's ship!
Yeah, you got it.
I already picked a fight with her!
All right, guys!
We'll be waiting for you at Zou!
All of you, be safe!
Roger that!
Alright, guys!
Prepare yourselves for the worst!
Ship! Ship!
Let's get out of here with Coup de Burst!
What about Gaon Cannon?!
No! We don't have enough Cola!
I have another idea instead!
Okay? Listen carefully!
If you have an idea, just do it!
Help us if you wanna survive!
Brook! Let's fight them at the stern
and let them drop their guard!
Okay!
--Nami-san, please take the helm!
--Got it!
What are you doing?!
Just hit it already-bon!
Soul Parade!
Chopper-san, there they go!
Monster Point!
Cho-Cho-Cho-Cho-Cho... Chopperemon?!
Catch, Chopper!
Wh-Wh-What are you gonna do to me?!
No! Let go of me!
I'll get even with you bastard!
How could you use my body like a bag?!
We won't help you
if you don't stop resisting!
No!
All yours, Sanji!
--That's Caesar! Grr!
--What are they doing-bon?!
Nice pitch, Chopper!
How can he fly?!
Poele a Frire...
...Spectre!
--Oh no! Grr!
--Turn away-bon!
Ship!
The starboard side's been damaged!
Help!
Guys! They're getting away from us!
Okay! It's my turn!
Climate Baton!
Weather...
...Egg!
Come hatch, rain clouds!
Rain Tempo!
Ship?
Why did the weather change
in just that area-bon?!
We're gonna lose them! Grr!
Good job, Nami-san!
Only you guys could do that!
That doesn't make me blush, you idiot!
Oh, that was a white-knuckler!
That's super!
That's great!
Stop it!
Well, it was a big deal I guess but...
And how many days did it take to Zou
from there?
We arrived here the next day.
Seems like Zou was nearby at that time.
That was 10 days ago.
As far as I could see,
the oldest sign of destruction
in the city at the center of Zou was...
...from a little more than two weeks ago.
That's right.
And by 10 days ago,
most of the country had been destroyed.
But on that day,
Nami and the others arrived here.
That can only be described as a miracle!
If not for their courage
and Chopper's medical expertise,
every single person in the Mokomo Dukedom
would've been helplessly killed...
I know it's just happened and it still hurts
so if you don't wanna talk
about it, that's fine but...
No, I'll tell you everything.
You-teia people have the
right to know everything.
Hey!
Everybody!
D-Duke-sama has...
What happened?!
Duke-sama has woken up!
That's great!
Duke-sama... He's all right now...
Wanda!
I'm happy for you, Wanda!
Okay! Let's go examine his condition now!
Miyagi! Tristan!
Oh, wait for me!
Okay, okay!
Let me go at it and learn from you!
Dr. Miyagi! You're hopping too much!
Wanda! Duke Dogstorm said
he'd like to see the saviors!
Okay, I'll be right up!
You-teia guys, will you come with me?!
Yeah but who's Dogstorm?
He's the duke of the Mokomo Dukedom.
Which means he's the ruler of the country!
He'd been in a coma ever
since the city was wiped out.
So has the other one.
The other one?!
Yes! This country has two rulers!
"King of the Day" - Duke Dogstorm!
"King of the Night" - Master Cat Viper!
The country of Zou has been protected
by those two rulers!
The Raid Bell suddenly rings
all over the peaceful Mokomo Dukedom!
The earth-rumblings herald Emperor
Kaido's right hand man,
Jack the Drought!
A tragic event that happened
to Wanda and her people,
and their fierce fight to protect
the country are now revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Threat Descends! The Beast Pirates, Jack!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!