Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
I only believe in the future --
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
We found an island!
Straight ahead!
What are you talking about?!
We've already been eaten!
That was hot! Couldn't you
have done it a different way?
An island?!
We made it!
Oh! An island! We found an island!
Straight ahead! Straight ahead!
Everyone, come here! This is bad!
Hey, Nami! Good for you!
There's an island! You can get better!
Ah! So that's the second island
in the Grand Line-- Little Garden!
Huh? What is it, Vivi?
Hakoku Sovereignty!
It's Nami-san! She has a terrible fever!
There's an island! An island! Island!
Well, then. Can you tell
which is the real one?
--Island! Island!
--Just go look.
W-What's with this island?!
I have a favor to ask of everyone.
Gum-Gum Stamp!
I know it's not my place to ask
this as a passenger on your ship,
An island!
How... did you know... I was here?
but my homeland is in a terrible
state now, so I'd like to hurry ahead!
Collier Shoot!
All this snow! I'm so happy!
"Nami's Sick?
Beyond the Snow Falling on the Sea!"
We can't waste even a single minute!
So I want this ship to head for
Alabasta at its fastest speed!
That's far enough, pirates!
A hunch.
Of course! That's what we promised!
We're flying out of it!
"Farewell, Giant Island!
Head for Alabasta"
Hey. I found people.
But... they don't seem too friendly...
So let's find an island with
a doctor on it right away!
Attention, pirates! Leave this
place at once! This instant!
Let's cure Nami-san as quickly as
possible and then go to Alabasta!
L-Little Garden?!
Don't look back!
We're going straight ahead!
Whoa! Look behind him!
That's this ship's fastest speed, right?!
W-What's so little...
We came to find a doctor!
A rainbow! There's a rainbow!
We have a sick person onboard!
Yeah! We can't go any faster than that!
...about this island?!
We won't fall for that trick,
you filthy pirates!
Huge! It's so huge!
They cut... the very sea itself...
They really hate our guts.
And we've just met, too...
"A Raid! The Tin Tyrant
and Tin Plate Wapol"
This is the strength of Elbaf warriors!
Don't talk back!
This is an island of ancient times.
Even the way he cries is big!
They're shooting!
You didn't just do that!
It's practically a waterfall!
It's stuck in the age of the dinosaurs!
Incredible!
--Bastard!
--Stop, Sanji-san!
I understand how you feel, Master Broggy!
She needs to see a doctor
as quickly as possible...
The duel has continued for 100 years now.
At this rate, Nami-san will...
I've forgotten the reason for it.
But that doesn't matter, anyway.
Hey!
Then why?!
"An Island Without Doctors?
Adventure in a Nameless Land!"
Friends!
Do you see a doctor?!
Do you expect him to, you idiot?
Pride!
Hey, guys. Do you think...
people can stand on the ocean?
Now go!
Vivi!
Man, he's huge...
Can people stand on the ocean?
Why, you--!
C'mon, Zoro! What kind
of question is that?
Dorry! How are you...
Aim!
Then... what's that?!
It seems I blacked out...
Long ago, there were ruffians on the sea
Huh?
What's what?
known as the Giant Warrior Pirates.
This is Elbaf, the god of war's...
No! Stop!
Mr. 0?
Fighting won't help anything!
The two pirate bosses,
Wasn't Mr. 0 the name of the
enemy boss Vivi-chan talked about?
I'm fine! It only grazed my arm!
Red Ogre Broggy and Blue Ogre Dorry,
were exceptionally strong.
Which means the guy on the other
end of this Transponder Snail...
In that case, we won't land here!
But could we ask for a doctor?
...judgment!
They were left mostly unchecked,
for ordinary people no longer
stood a chance against them.
Our friend is suffering from a grave illness.
Please help! I beg you!
But they say that the one who
put an end to their attacks...
I didn't have his divine protection.
...is one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea?!
Vivi!
You're not fit to be captain, Luffy.
It's been many days since
I issued your orders.
Hi. It sure is chilly today.
Who is it?! Come out!
...was a single little girl.
Not everything can be fixed
by acting recklessly!
What's going on?
Mr. 3... So he's the owner
of this Transponder Snail?
You see what our bosses caught today?!
Yeah! It is chilly today!
You guys spoiled
the old giant guys' duel!
If you start a fight here,
what will happen to Nami-san?
Y-yeah! Chilly, chilly!
Today's very chilly!
Yeah! It's stuck in my mind!
My excitement won't stop!
Ah. I think I got it figured out now.
I'm gonna beat you up!
Really?
This is an enemy hideout,
Each one of 'em bagged an
insanely huge Sea King, after all!
It's no use!
and a guy named Mr. 3 came to
the island to take Vivi-chan's life...
Your friends are going
to become my works of art!
Even though we're Elbaf giants,
Damn... This was no time
for me to be hunting!
nobody can take down those
jumbo-sized beasts except for our bosses!
Increase buoyancy!
Yeah. I'm sorry! I was wrong!
I hope they're all okay!
Yes, sir!
Luffy!
Right, men?!
Please call a doctor!
Why the silent treatment?
--Yeah!
--You got that right!
Please help our friend!
I asked you a question.
Ahh. Such nice tea...
What is that?! A watermelon?!
Have you eliminated Princess
Vivi and the Straw Hats?!
Luffy! What are you doing?!
Why are we shaking?!
Those ones were definitely
the biggest ones...
Hold the rudder! If anything
happens to Nami, I'll gut you all!
Yeah, mission complete!
I got rid of everyone who
found out about your secret.
Yeah! The biggest ones
we've ever caught!
I will show you to the village.
Don't tell me this... is a ship?!
So there's no need to
go after 'em anymore.
So which one was bigger?
Follow me.
I see. Well done.
Such... nice... tea...
As we speak, the Unluckies
are headed your way
--Which...
--...one?
Yeah! Who won the hunting contest?
Luffy!
to confirm your mission is complete
and to deliver a certain package.
See? They understood!
Unluckies? Package?
Yeah! You're amazing!
What are you doing, you idiot?!
Look, Broggy! Mine is slightly bigger!
An Eternal Pose that points
to the Alabasta Kingdom.
You wish! Mine's a whole
3 centimeters bigger!
You and Ms. Golden Week will head
to Alabasta. The time has come.
--Say what?!
--What's your problem?!
It's over for all of you.
Crap! A p-pirate ship!
Bosses! Please stop!
This is my ultimate ability!
We're about to begin our
most important operation.
W-wow!
I must warn you, the only doctor
we have here is a witch.
Special Attack: Exploding Star!
Just when we're in a hurry...
Details will come after you reach
Alabasta. Wait for my orders.
Witch?
You gotta be kidding me.
Nothing here makes sense...
Incidentally, Broggy. There's one
thing I can't seem to remember.
Did our jumbo underwater raid ship,
the Tin Tyrant, surprise you?!
"Time to Fight Back!
Usopp's Quick Thinking and Fire Star!"
What is this place, anyway?
What are these things?!
No, actually, that goes for me, too.
This land still does not have a name.
A nameless land?
Does that really happen?
Vivi-chan! You're in charge here!
Middle Mountain!
Okay!
No matter! Let's just finish this now!
Hey! What's going on?!
Hey. What's going on?
Oh, it's nothing...
A bear!
Yeah! We can think things
through after that!
Everyone! Pretend to be dead!
What an idiot! He missed his
target and hit his own friend!
What the hell?!
A Hiking Bear. They pose no danger.
Where'd his bullets go?!
Don't forget to bow.
It's proper hiking manners.
Breeze Breath Bomb!
Guys! Someday, I will go to Elbaf!
To the village of warriors!
Okay! All better now!
So? What's going on?
See!
The ship's being attacked.
Yeah! Okay!
You tryin' to kill me?!
Bring it on, you damn monkey!
Now I can finally do
some real training!
# Gi-Gi-Giants! Gi-Giants! #
I forgot to mention it,
but my breath explodes.
I was getting sick of
that watered-down training,
# Elbaf-baf! Elbaf-baf! #
Dammit! This is insane!
He had no bullets?!
Well, I had figured as much,
from the looks of things.
and just watching the ship
is boring as hell.
# Everyone's huge!
'Cause they're giants! #
I'm telling you...
Karoo! You alright?!
Maybe I'll go for some cold-weather
swimming to suppress my self.
# They're huge!
They're huge! They're huge! #
Are you really pirates? You're strange.
Hey! You come to your senses?!
...to stop that!
They sure are full of energy...
Y-Yeah...
Is it just you four?
You jumbo-sized chicken!
I'm awake! Thanks!
This is our village, Big Horn.
That attack was meant to burn
his clothes and the trap on it
I find it hard to believe...
that a pirate group
would only have four people.
to undo the mental manipulation!
I'm suddenly exhausted after
everything that's happened.
There are weird animals
walking everywhere...
What was that?! What happened?!
That's snow country for ya!
I've had enough of that paint!
Vivi. Could you watch
this compass for me?
Oh, uhh, no! It ain't--
I mean, it's nothing!
Nami-san! We made it to a village
with people! It's a village!
What is that guy?!
He even ate the knife!
Sure.
That damn Straw Hat was still alive.
I refuse to let anyone else die!
Okay. Thanks for the help, everyone.
It's okay, though. I finished him off.
Just watching hurts!
Now I'm mad!
Those who aren't guards
can return to their work.
No need to worry.
Well, no matter.
I'll start by asking this...
But, will you be alright by yourself,
Dalton-san? They're pirates!
It's definitely weird. Damn weird.
Now you can finally return to Alabasta.
We want to go to the Drum Kingdom.
I believe they pose no threat.
Why hasn't anyone come
back after all this time?
Well, assuming we can make
it there safely, of course...
Do you happen to have an
Eternal Pose or a Log Pose?
Still alive?
That's my hunch of many years
of experience. You can trust it.
Something must've happened to
Nami-san, Vivi-chan, and the rest.
You just said your mission
was complete... Did you not?
What do we do?
Nope. Never even heard of the place.
If that's what Dalton-san says, then...
In which case, this is no time to
be getting ready to cook a lizard!
Yes. I must return!
--And they don't seem dangerous...
--Yeah...
After all, I'm...
Okay, you're done, right?! So leave!
Yes, well...
I thought it was complete...
Alright, Dalton-san!
We leave the rest to you!
...the only way to
save the kingdom, Princess!
Nami-san! Vivi-chan!
We're in a hurry! We don't
have time to mess with you!
Be ever careful, Dalton-san...
The king-- your father-- no longer
has sway with the people now.
But he was much tougher
than you'd believe...
Just call us again if anything happens!
Hey! Say something! I love you!
Don't rush life like that.
In other words... the report
you gave me was a lie.
But if you have neither, then oh well.
Our only hope of
stopping this uprising now
They weren't this land's security forces?
For now, I'll take your
treasure and this ship.
They're ordinary citizens.
is for you to tell the
people the truth directly!
Come to my home for now.
What?!
Umm, well... I suppose so,
when you put it that way...
But first, I'm feeling a bit hungry!
Hey! Look, Luffy! A Hiking Bear!
So, no matter what, you must not die!
What's this?
Again?!
But I've gotten rid of him for sure now.
You must live on, even if it
means losing those near to you
--Oh, Dalton-san!
--Gotta bow.
I heard there were pirates!
Are you okay?
So there's no need to send
any more after 'em. Okay?
or having to betray others!
What is this guy?!
So what if you're mad?
Just look at your friends now!
Yes, everything is okay.
There's nothing to worry about.
It will be painful!
Don't eat our ship!
Very well.
Hold it right there!
Wapol-sama is currently eating!
Princess Vivi!
Are you prepared not to die?
Just head straight to
Alabasta from there now!
So what?! They're still alive!
Oh, Dalton-kun! I look forward
to the election in two days!
Shut up!
Damn that bastard! Fire!
Are they, now?
I will return to Alabasta, alive...
Everyone says they're
going to vote for you!
All they need now is some
of Miss Golden Week's paint
Should've done that
from the very start...
Y-you can't be serious!
I'm nothing but a sinful man!
and they'll be exceptional wax figures!
Oh? We can have at 'em?
It's probably... because of the weapons...
No, wait! We can discuss this!
You're too late, Straw Hat!
Weapons?! Oh, yeah!
There's no need to push
yourself so hard, Vivi-chan.
That's correct!
Not even Elbaf weapons could
keep up with two giants
Use that bed there.
I'll warm the place up.
They started it themselves...
You're not only late, but now you
can experience even more despair!
You have me!
fighting to the death
for 100 years straight!
The fools! They're in a hurry to die!
Today's relaxing sweets.
How about some petit fours?
Gunfire?!
I haven't told you my name yet.
Karoo! Watch Nami-san!
I'll be right back!
For drinks, you have your
choice of coffee or tea...
Talk about crazy...
I'm Dalton, captain of the
security squad of this island.
It's a huge miracle!
Sanji-san...
Please forgive our heavy-handed welcome.
Don't do anything you can't handle!
Hey, Broggy! Don't hold on to me!
That hurts my wounds!
Reception!
Move out!
May I ask you a question?
Yours is in the kitchen!
I'm so glad you're alive, friend of mine!
Eh?
Alright!
I somehow feel like I've seen you before.
I'm first!
Candle...
I-it's probably just your imagination!
Miracle, my ass. It's only natural.
Anyway, please tell us about this witch!
...Champion!
Nami-san's temperature was 42 C
when I checked it just now!
The fact those weapons are
still intact after 100 years
2,603!
of constant bashing and
clanging is even crazier.
2,604!
42?!
As are their owners.
2,605!
What's that?
Her fever's gone up for
three days in a row.
What a wonderful day today is!
I thank you, God of Elbaf!
It's said he once took down a
42 million-Berry bounty with this.
2,606!
She'll die if it goes up any more!
All bark and no bite...
Yes.
Oh, Broggy?
W- Wapol-sama! These guys're--!
If only I could've cut that wax...
It's Mr. 3's ultimate artistic talent.
But we don't even know the cause of
her illness, or how to treat it...
Was chopping me down and
knocking me out that happy for you?
Now, Miss Golden Week!
Perform an artistic paint job on me!
Are you still eating it?!
...I wouldn't have left anyone hanging...
We need a doctor! Anyone will do!
Where is this witch of yours?!
Say, this ship doesn't taste half bad...
You dimwit! That ain't what I'm saying!
Hey, you!
Fool! You're no match for Wapol-sama!
Can I take a break after that?
I'm weak...
The witch, huh. Do you see those
mountains outside the window?
Oww! Don't touch my wounds!
Time to get eaten by the power
of the Munch-Munch Fruit!
Yes, of course! I'd actually
prefer you to stay out of this!
If I'm gonna get stronger...
Yeah, those insanely tall--
Luffy!
Like this, I am invincible!
...I need to be able to cut up
stuff like that from any stance!
W-what is this?!
Hyper Snowman!
Oh, hey, Vivi-chan.
Has something happened to Nami-san?
This armor is as hard as iron,
and wrapped around me like velvet!
Snowzilla, the snow beast!
Eh?
Yeah!
Don't make me kick your asses!
--You want some of this?!
--Yeah! I'll wipe the floor with ya!
"Alabasta Kingdom Sandy Island"
My form now...
What a hard-to-chew person!
Those mountains are known
as the Drum Rockies.
Mr. 2! Bon Clay-sama!
The Swanda is ready to set sail!
...has no flaws!
Why, you--!
Do you see the castle at the top
of the tallest one in the middle?
Cool! Cool! Cool!
Go flying!
Okay, okay! You're so loud, sheesh!
S-So cool!
Castle?!
Why are you guys fighting again?!
--That castle no longer has its king.
--That warms me up...
This is no time to be admiring him! Fight!
Honestly, now! Why do I have to do this?!
...And no further
radio contact from now on.
Yeah, there it is.
What's so important about the castle?
Wapol-sama?
Mr. 3 is nothing but bulky garbage!
You guys go toss him out!
The only doctor in the land,
Dr. Kureha, lives there.
We don't want the Navy
catching whiff of us.
W-We can't!
Alright! Gum-Gum...
All further orders will be
sent via letter, as usual.
We wouldn't stand a chance,
even if we ganged up on him!
People call her a witch.
P-Please! It is the boss' orders!
What?! Of all the places,
why does it have to be so far away?!
That is all. Good luck, Mr. 3.
--Paint job complete!
--Now, then!
Un, deux, trois...
...Pistol!
Then call her here right away!
We have a critical patient!
What's "four" called?
Hey, this is bad!
Wapol-sama was sent flying!
"Bon Clay"
Even if we wanted to,
there's no way to contact her.
Champ Fight! Harvest Field!
This is terrible!
Wapol-sama is unable to swim!
Huh?! And she calls herself a doctor?!
What the hell is she like?!
Zero-chan is so high-maintenance...
Miss All Sunday.
He will surely perish if we
don't rescue him before he sinks!
Gum-Gum...
As a doctor, she's very skilled.
But she's an eccentric old hag.
She's nearly 140 years old now.
Yes?
...Stamp!
Send Mr. 2 to Little Garden.
Vivi... Sorry. I think I'm gonna...
This isn't over, you!
We will make you pay for this!
Eh?!
140?! I think she might need help!
Eliminate Mr. 3 on his direct course
to Alabasta from Little Garden.
It's no use!
Remember us!
And, let's see...
She likes pickled plums.
Not good! The guy's so solid
his attacks don't work!
We'll get you for this!
What happens when people
here get sick or injured?
Please, remember us! Please!
That's quite aggressive,
Mr. 0, Crocodile, sir.
...go lie down...
She comes down from the
mountain when she feels like it.
No problem, Nami-san!
We have enough manpower as it is.
Are you arguing with me?
Damn! The wax haze!
She looks for patients,
treats them, then, as payment,
I'll keep an eye on our course.
You should get some rest.
she takes whatever she wants
from their houses before leaving.
No, I'll do as you wish.
I'll make arrangements at once.
Wax?
Sounds like an unfriendly old hag!
W-what was that just now?
They seemed to call him Wapol, but...
Are you all right?!
Hey! She almost sounds like a pirate!
Everyone, come here! This is bad!
But how does such an old
woman go down that mountain?
Doesn't matter. Don't worry about it.
Huh? What is it, Vivi?
It's an odd rumor...
Nami-san has a terrible fever!
Yeah! Why didn't I realize it?!
He's just a moron.
That's the only possible explanation.
but several people claim to have seen her
Eh?! Nami-san does?!
riding a sleigh through
the sky on moonlit nights...
The fact it turns into
a mist means it can melt!
Well, he's hung up. So let's see...
What were these guys, anyway?!
Luffy! Fire melts this guy's wax!
And that's the reason
she's called a witch...
Have I seen him somewhere before?
No matter how hard it is,
wax is still wax!
Some also saw her with a strange
creature they'd never seen before...
Zoro and all the others
hardened only moments ago!
What do we have here?
We can save them!
I knew it! See? It's a Snow Man!
It's a snowy mountain, after all!
What?! For reals?!
Yeah, for reals.
I knew there'd be one!
Don't admit that to them!
A witch and a Snow Man?!
Oh, please never let us run into them!
But even if you realize that now,
"Several days earlier..."
She is the only doctor, but she's
a hag I'd prefer to stay away from.
you have neither time
nor a chance of winning!
30 more seconds at most!
Is Nami-san gonna die? Is she, Vivi-chan?
After that, their hearts
will completely stop!
All we can do is wait for the next
time she comes down the mountain.
Captain Smoker! Captain Smoker!
As we speak, they're
probably writhing in pain
You can't be serious...
with what little consciousness
they have left
I've just intercepted
an intriguing signal!
Dammit! We can't wait for that!
Even as we speak, Nami-san is--!
as they experience
the terror of dying!
What?
We had completely forgotten
about the bounties on our heads!
Hey! Nami! Nami! Can you hear me?
What an incredible full temper!
It's most likely the climate.
What are you doing?!
We don't need 30 seconds!
I'll save them now!
The Ryo-Wazamono sword, Kashu!
But I was the reason they came to
this island in the first place...
One of the obstacles all sailors
who enter the Grand Line run into
Special Attack: Fire--
Tashigi! Hey! Tashigi!
Breeze Breath Bomb!
Oh! She's awake!
is illness caused by abnormal weather.
Oww!
Only in the Grand Line could
I find a legendary sword so quickly!
Let's have none of that!
Hey, the only way to see a
doctor is to climb a mountain.
There are countless stories
of tough, notorious pirates
Yeah, Vivi! What're you
so down in the dumps for?
Usopp!
We're gonna climb it!
Tashigi! Hey!
Want a rice cracker?
Eh?
Are you deaf, you sword freak?!
Hey! Where did you get those?
Don't be crazy!
What are you doing with Nami?!
Y-yes, sir! What is it,
Captain Smoker?! Is coffee--
suddenly dying from this.
Alright! For now,
let's have a rice cracker party!
Did you not hear him say you
have no chance of winning?
Carelessness makes even
the slightest case deadly.
It's okay! I'll carry her on my back!
Rice crackers aren't very exciting.
That'll only make things even worse!
Really? We can even make
toasts with them!
Nami-san!
What's the problem?
We need to hurry, don't we?
See? Does anyone blame you?
Just get over here and listen with us!
Dammit! There's no time!
That's true, but you can't!
Look at how steep and tall it is!
Is there anyone on this ship with
any medical knowledge at all?
Cheers!
Give it up!
C'mon! Don't do that!
That's a Black Transponder Snail,
a listening device!
I can make it.
Maybe you can make it,
but it'd be too hard on Nami-san!
Geez! You can't just waste food like that!
Listen close. We just picked up
this conversation between two men.
But, look! If we fall,
we'll land in snow!
What're you doing?! Give it here!
Who said you could have mine?!
But eating meat makes
sickness go away! Right, Sanji?
Ready, Sergeant Major? Here we go.
Even a healthy person would die
instantly after a fall from there!
Listen... Take this rope...
--Give it! It's mine!
--Who says?!
Y-yes. Please play it back.
I can make some basic food
meant for sick people,
Seriously! She's 6 C
over normal temperature!
Oh? This looks like fun!
What's wrong?
...me, Mr. 0...
Nothing. Just a bug.
Whatcha planning?
Can I join in, too?
but that's entirely
in "nursing" territory.
...Princess Vivi and the Straw Hat...
Do you even get it?!
Still, waiting a year for the
Log to point to the next island
There's no guarantee
it'd make her better...
Straw Hat? The Straw Hat Pirates!
is pretty serious stuff...
Besides, I normally put
100 times more care
Yeah! It's definitely no laughing matter!
Karoo! Run!
Yeah, mission complete!
into Nami-san and Vivi-chan's
meals than I do with yours...
Run!
I need to get over this fast...
You saved us. We would like
to thank you in some way...
...further orders...
via letter, as usual...
Just run around all the candlesticks!
I serve them fresh meat and
vegetables, for balanced nutrition.
That is all. Good luck...
I need to hurry... for Vivi...
Oh, in that case, you old guys
can do something about our Log!
Everything you try is pointless!
And I give all the
rotting stuff to you guys.
The rest is undecipherable.
It's a faint signal, but there are
four keywords in their conversation.
Pardon me.
Hey, now!
I'm afraid Logs are the only
thing we can't help you with...
It's still good, though!
I'm counting on you, Captain!
Crescendo Stone!
In any case, as long
as I'm this ship's cook,
How many kilograms
can you endure, I wonder...
Princess Vivi. Straw Hat.
Orders via letter. And Mr. 0.
Nami-san! Vivi-chan!
And you other bums!
there'll be no problems whatsoever
in terms of getting a balanced diet.
That's more like it!
Just leave it to me!
Hey! Sanji!
10 kilograms...
Mr. 0? Could that be a codename?!
But there are different kinds
of meals for sick people.
You're okay! Thank goodness!
100 kilograms...
If so, could he be connected to
that suspicious swordsman we caught
What are her symptoms? What does
she need? I can't make that call...
That jerk suddenly shows up
only after we needed help!
200 kilograms...
in Runess the other day?
With him... Mr. 11?
300 kilograms!
Then she can just eat it all!
Yeah.
What in the hell?! Are you Mr. 3?!
A criminal organization that
uses numbers for codenames
She's sick because she doesn't
have the energy for that!
Damn nimble bird!
I can't believe it!
Like captain, like navigator!
and sends orders via letter to
get tasks done. Sound about right?
Hey! How do you know about Mr. 3?
40C?! Her fever's gone up again!
Give it up! Give it up!
Do you know what condition
you're in, Nami-san?!
Nami-san!
Mr. 0? Criminal organization?
Dunno what you're talking about.
There'll be doctors when
we get to Alabasta, right?!
Are you sure you'll be okay?
It'll take hours to get there!
They've become my works of art!
You're so titillating!
Don't give me your guesswork.
Feel like getting slugged?
How much longer will it take, Vivi?
Old guy! Meat! Gimme meat!
Then what was that letter with
orders that we found in your pocket?
Now, now, Nami-san.
You'll catch cold dressed like that.
Meat?
I don't know, but one week
is out of the question...
I don't think so!
Alright! I'm comin' too!
I won't let you have their lives!
I thought I burned that letter!
Here you are.
Listen, Luffy! Don't fall even once,
or you can expect Nami to die!
Is being sick that bad?
Thanks.
T-that was, uhh...
If fire can melt them,
then I'll use this fire!
All that aside, I just finished talking
with Mr. 0 via Transponder Snail.
Dunno. Never been sick...
Oh? But there wasn't
anything in your pocket.
Eh?! Even once?!
Who in the world are you guys?!
Don't pull! Stop!
Wait! Hold still!
I need to tie this right!
Luffy! That small flame
won't do it fast enough!
You talked to the boss?!
Of course it's bad!
40C fevers don't happen every day!
Yeah. I found this weird
hideout in the jungle, you see.
All set.
Light Karoo's rope on fire!
Okay, I'm going to wait here.
I'd only get in the way.
This may be a life-threatening illness...
He seemed to think I was Mr. 3,
so I told him I eliminated everyone.
The bird's rope?!
Princess Vivi...
Same here!
It's a special rope...
That's the name of the princess
of Alabasta, as I recall.
Got it!
--Nami's gonna die?!
--Don't die, Nami-san!
...soaked in oil!
Okay, Nami! Hold on tight!
She's currently missing.
--Okay! Everyone! Wake up!
--Hey! Wait! Stop!
Yeah...
Isn't the Alabasta Kingdom
in the middle of coup, too?
So that means he thinks we're dead?!
Stop that! Be quiet!
It'll be a little hot, but endure it...
If you're really set on going...
I won't stop you.
Let's find a doctor to help Nami!
So we're finally free of people
chasing us, but we can't go anywhere!
Could this mysterious criminal
organization and the Straw Hat Pirates
Stop!
But at least climb up from the other side.
Okay! Just calm down!
be involved in the uproar somehow?
You're going to make
her illness even worse!
There are Lapins on this course.
Can't go anywhere? Do we still
have business on this island?
No.
Don't know. But this is the only
clue to Straw Hat's whereabouts
Fierce, carnivorous rabbits.
Just after I managed
to get ahold of this, too...
If you encounter a pack of them,
you're as good as dead.
No.
that we have right now.
Nami-san?
Does that mean we're going to--?
Rabbits? But we're in a hurry.
Oh! She's all better!
Get real!
Yeah. Contact HQ and
get an Eternal Pose!
We should be fine. Right?
Yeah! I'll kick 'em!
Kick?! You can't be serious!
You'd be walking to your deaths!
Eh? What?
Yes, sir!
In my desk drawer...
there's a newspaper...
It's an Eternal Pose to Alabasta!
Let's pay a visit to Alabasta,
the sand kingdom!
It's okay!
Alright, then! Let's go, Sanji!
Before Nami dies!
--Hurray!
--Now we can set sail!
What?! Don't say things that
could jinx us, you dumbass!
Hurray! Way to go, Sanji-kun!
No change in course...
N-No!
Thank you, Sanji-san!
Will they really be all right?
I was so worried for a moment there!
That can't be!
Well, I'm not worried about those two...
Oww! Hot! Hot!
Hey. What is it?
No, no! It was my pleasure!
I'm glad I could make you so happy!
Is it about Alabasta, Vivi-chan?
But the question is if Nami-san's
strength will last long enough...
What a big fire!
Are they gonna be alright?!
300,000 royal soldiers
defected to the Resistance...
Alright, everyone!
Let's have a rice cracker party!
I hope they make it there safely...
Curse you... Curse you, Straw Hat!
Oh no, Luffy!
We only have three left!
We can't have a rice cracker party!
How dare you destroy
my Candle Service Set?!
It was originally a cold war,
Are you sure she's not just hungry?
What?!
with 600,000 royal soldiers and
400,000 Resistance soldiers...
You know this is no time for that!
You'll pay for this!
If so, she should eat
enough meat for 100 people!
Let's go, Captain! We don't
have time to be lounging around!
But now that's suddenly changed!
What's wrong?
Eating meat makes sickness go away!
Come inside. It's cold out.
Look, you...
I won't let you get away, you jerks!
The uprising in Alabasta is
finally going to get serious now...
Come on! Cheer up! Look! Look!
Oh, yeah! Hey, you.
Oh, that's okay.
I want to stay outside.
You haven't forgotten
our hunting contest, I hope!
Me, too...
That paper's from three days ago...
Damn it! How dare you mock us?!
Nope! But I win!
I caught a rhino this huge!
She isn't laughing... Not one bit...
I'm sorry. We can't change our speed,
Now you've done it!
A rhino? I assume you can eat that?!
I see.
Won't her fever go down
if we dump water on her?
so I didn't want to worry
you by showing you that...
Playtime is over!
Of course!
Understand, Luffy?
You idiot!
Hunting contest?
I'm going to shatter that
neck of yours into pieces!
This isn't good. The sun's about
to set for today, Vivi-chan.
Hunting contest?
Things seem very bad!
Then I will join you.
Those words sound familiar somehow...
Whew, that got through to
you more than I expected...
Yes, you're right.
Let's drop anchor somewhere.
Special Attack:
10,000 Kilogram Guillotine!
But you need to see a doctor!
Yes...
I'm fine... That thermometer
must be broken...
We can't navigate at night
without Nami-san's instructions.
Alright, round old guy and giant old guy!
Nobody gets a temperature of 40C...
Yeah.
This is bad!
We're gonna go now!
It's probably just
sunstroke or something...
Oh, I see. Well, you do
seem to be in a hurry.
We don't need a doctor.
I'll get better on my own...
That's too bad, but we won't stop you.
I hope your homeland is okay.
For now, let's head straight
for Alabasta as planned!
That was hot! Couldn't you
have done it a different way?
We did have some, long ago...
Yes! Thank you!
Thanks for worrying about me.
See ya! Don't die anymore!
Eh?
Doctors. But they're all gone now,
for certain reasons.
Don't be fussy!
Just be thankful you were saved!
Master! I will visit Elbaf someday!
They were all incredibly skilled...
You'll see. Mine's way bigger than yours.
Oh! She's better now?
You're right. Thanks!
We were even known as
an advanced medical nation.
This doesn't seem real... We're alive!
You idiot. She's just acting tough.
You wish!
I'm gonna be a brave warrior of the sea!
So what happened?
The wax melted.
What a pain! We can't afford to
screw up our mission any further!
This country was destroyed
just a few months ago.
Our friends are setting sail.
Mr. 5!
Yes. We can't just sit here.
There's a monster in the western sea.
At the hands of pirates!
At this rate, so much blood will
be shed throughout the kingdom.
--Eh?!
--The entire country?!
Special Attack: Exploding Star!
It'll be an all-out war...
Dorry! How are your wounds?
So that's why you were so nervous about us?
Fool! I've shown several times
that explosives don't work on me!
If I don't stop that,
the Alabasta Kingdom will be done for!
Oh! You want my autograph that badly?!
Yes. The word "pirate" is still
too much for everyone to handle...
These? They won't kill me.
I'm an "explosive man"!
Crocodile will take over!
You took the bait!
I'm sorry about that.
I can't just return safely!
This axe and that sword
are just about done with.
But there were only five
people in that pirate group.
I need to return as quickly as possible!
So sorry! I'm a liar, you see!
The captain called himself "Blackbeard,"
If I don't make it in time,
Whew, it's cold...
Do you have regrets?
That wasn't an Exploding Star!
It was a Special Tabasco Star!
I do. This axe fought alongside
me for over 100 years.
and he destroyed our country
in the blink of an eye
a million citizens will
kill themselves pointlessly!
with his devastating power...
There's a million people?!
Spicy!
But, if it's for them, it's worth it!
What an immense burden
you're carrying, Vivi-chan...
Almost a full moon...
Only five pirates?!
You can't be serious!
Then it's decided...
Blackbeard?!
But there are some who say it was
actually good for the country.
I already proved its
effectiveness the hard way!
There's nothing good about
a country being destroyed!
Damn you pirates!
Yeah! That's the stupidest
thing I've ever heard!
How dare you make a mockery of me?!
See?! Mine's far huger than yours!
Thank you.
Urgh! What were you
watching all this time?!
Look closer! My lizard's bigger!
Time to blow up in a full-body explosion!
But people say that because the
monarchy that existed here until then
Whadya talking about?
The ship's been going straight.
Are you blind or something?!
My rhino's way bigger!
There won't even be bone fragments left!
was appalling in the eyes of the citizens.
Yeah, straight at a right angle!
Look at the compass!
No! Stop!
The country's former name
was the Drum Kingdom!
It doesn't really matter!
They both look yummy!
Usopp!
Brr! Oh, crap, I fell asleep!
I don't need to.
I was watching that big cloud there.
No! I'm sorry! I won't do it anymore!
--You shut up!
--Huh?
The king's name was Wapol!
--Look! Mine's bigger!
--No, mine is!
You're up early, Usopp!
Clouds move and change shape!
He was the worst king possible!
I can't just sit around doing nothing!
Oh, geez, my head's killing me...
We gotta get out of this
jam as quick as possible!
How long are you gonna keep at that?
So just leave this to me and go to bed!
We don't need all of it, so cut up
what we do need so we can set sail!
Flaming Oni...
Yes! That man! I remember him!
I'm here because
I can't leave this to you!
Yeah. Good point.
Wapol?!
Yes, Nami-san!
...Giri!
Hey, Usopp!
I'm clearly the winner, right?!
The air's changed...
Blehhh!
The air? It's been nice
weather this whole time.
C'mon, Nami! Look!
I don't really care.
Never mind! Just get the others!
Can't you call it a tie?
This is weird. She won't smile!
C'mon, smile, Nami!
It's gotten a little colder.
The wind's picking up.
There are no ties in a challenge!
Hey! Get out here, you guys!
Got work to do!
Hurry it up!
What's goin' on, Luffy?
So why aren't you wearing shoes?!
Just seeing that is painful!
What?
"Meat"
Right!
Huh? Hard to feel motivated
when you're giving the orders.
This is my police!
Quit that! You're creepin' me out!
Police?! You mean "policy"!
Really? Thanks!
Just shut up and move!
Set sail!
Yeah!
Take the seat and
catch the portside wind!
Flaming swords aren't too shabby.
Anyway, did you know?
People in snowy countries never sleep!
What's going on, Nami-san?
The waves are quiet,
and the weather's nice...
They said going straight will take us
to the western end of the island.
Say, doesn't this area
seem kind of calm and cold?
Huh? Why's that?
Zoro!
'Cause they'll die if they go to sleep!
Wind...
Hey. Couldn't you have gotten
any more meat on board?
Don't be stupid!
There's nobody like that!
Wind?
Yeah, sudden, strange calms...
Yeah, right! Don't be stupid!
We can't preserve any more than that.
An immense wind...
is coming directly this way...
It's the truth!
Someone told me a long time ago!
I guess that's another thing that
happens in the erratic Grand Line.
Do you want to sink the ship?!
I think.
What?
Usopp, I bet.
Hot!
That's not necessarily so.
No! I heard it in a pub in my village!
You're hot! Yeah, you stay inside
the ship! Let's go to a doctor!
Yo. Good to see you're alive.
It's probably proof
that an island is nearby.
Mind your own business!
This is my normal temperature!
Then why did that Dalton guy have a bed?
Look, it's the old guys!
They came to see us off!
Yeah.
Sanji-san! Could you look
carefully out at the horizon?
Now quit being stupid and pull the ropes!
Vivi-chan?
That's a good point.
Nami-san. I know you're
saying that for Vivi-chan,
A winter island is nearby.
I'm certain of it.
Maybe it's for when he dies, then?
Ahead is a great obstacle...
but if you push too hard...
--Winter island?
--Oww!
Climatically, there are four basic
types of islands in the Grand Line.
Yeah, right!
...that prevents people who come to
this island from reaching the next...
I told you, I'm fine!
Master...
Okay, did you know this?
Summer islands, spring islands,
autumn islands, winter islands...
Women in snowy lands
all have silky-smooth skin!
Hey, Nami. I think you really should--
You fought desperately
to protect our pride.
That leaves two foes left.
How come?
And each one generally has
four seasons of its own.
Just hurry and move the ship!
Isn't it obvious?
As such, no matter what manner
of enemy there may be...
Whenever you're cold,
you rub your skin for warmth.
"Summery Summer ----------- Wintery Winter"
"Summer Is. Spring Is. Autumn Is. Winter Is."
In short, when on the Grand Line,
there are at least 16 seasonal levels
So you get smooth skin.
Bird!
So women in snowy places have
such silky-smooth, white skin!
...we will not let them
destroy your pride, friends!
Don't let them get away with this!
you must conquer, from summer island
summer to winter island winter.
Sheesh...
Real men don't spoil people's fights!
What could it be?
Have faith in us,
and continue straight ahead!
How come it's white?
It seems a little different than a storm...
Of course, there are many
exceptions and unknown climates.
Because the color of the
constantly-falling snow dyes their skin!
Straight ahead, no matter what happens!
Got it!
I get it.
Huh?! You're so dumb!
What's this about?
The Grand Line has all these
different islands one after the other,
Like you're really anyone to talk!
What do you got?
How good of you to come!
Welcome to my Wax-Wax Manor!
and that's why the seas between
them have such unstable weather.
And...
We'll go straight ahead, no matter what!
...quit being so damn annoying!
That's right. Which is why stable
weather means an island is nearby.
What was with that guy?
What is this?!
Well, then. Can you tell where I am?
Hang in there, Nami-san!
We're gonna get you to a doctor!
Yeah... I see it!
This is goodbye!
It would appear you picked a
fight with the wrong people!
The snow's really deep around here...
Let's meet again someday.
Without fail.
Hey, Luffy!
We found an island!
Look! Up ahead!
Run more smoothly!
You're gonna make Nami-san worse!
We're the most intellectual
team in all of Baroque Works!
An island?!
I need to hurry back to Alabasta...
Oh! An island! We found an island!
A brute-force buffoon like you who
acts on instinct cannot catch us!
Hey, Nami! Good for you!
There's an island! You can get better!
W-what are these?
I have a favor to ask, everyone!
There's an island! An island! Island!
They're white and big,
so they're polar bears! I'm sure of it!
Island! Island! Island! Island!
I am Mr. 3. I carry out all
assignments given to me flawlessly.
I know it's not my place to ask
this as a passenger on your ship,
There you are, Island-Eater!
Wait! You know Wapol?!
You will open the path,
in the name of Elbaf!
but my homeland is in a terrible state now,
We don't just know him!
He's the pirate who attacked our ship!
Just go look. I got her covered.
Now, then! Step forward!
so I'd like to hurry ahead!
We can't waste even a single minute!
I got rid of him, though.
So I want this ship to head for
Alabasta at its fastest speed!
An island!
But I do recall him saying
something about the Drum Kingdom...
White! It's so white! It must
be snow! A snow island, huh?!
The moment your back is
turned to me, I'll stab you...
Yes.
There's no question about it!
I remember clearly now!
Hey, Luffy! Just so you know,
we're not here to have an adventure!
I met him once at a monarch
meeting my father took me to
Of course! That's what we promised!
We're dropping by to find a doctor!
We're leaving once
we get Nami-san looked at!
when I was very young!
...right through the heart.
Hey! Hey, Luffy!
Monarch meeting?!
Snow is so nice and white!
--Wha...
--Something's appeared!
So let's find an island with
a doctor on it right away!
Just who are you?
No, uhh, you see...
It's no use. He doesn't hear me...
What's this guy? A goldfish?
Let's cure Nami-san as quickly as
possible and then go to Alabasta!
In any case, we met Wapol!
Yesterday, on our way here!
H-h-hold on! Is this a good idea?!
A g-giant goldfish?!
W-Why does that sound familiar?!
If there's snow, couldn't
there be snow monsters too?!
That's this ship's fastest speed, right?!
Besides, we're not even sure
if people live there or not!
Yesterday?! Are you sure?!
Work the rudder! Hurry!
We're gonna get eaten!
Yeah! We can't go any faster than that!
Oh, no! My chronic
Can't-Go-to-the-Island disease!
But what's going on, then?!
He called himself a pirate, not a king!
Hurry, Usopp!
Are you sure?
I-I can't!
Snow! I love snow! It's white!
As their princess, you should be
worried about those million citizens.
Gum-Gum...
Go straight ahead! R-Right, Luffy?!
...Stamp!
He must be calling himself
that as camouflage.
Guess I'll get us ready to land.
Yeah! Of course!
That's right! So we need to hurry
and cure Nami-san's illness!
Wapol is merely wandering the sea,
trying to return to this island.
How... did you know...
Well said, Vivi-chan!
I've fallen for you all over again!
So the people on that ship were
kicked out because they were no match
Don't be stupid! This won't be
like what happened with Laboon!
You got guts.
...I was here?
for the Blackbeard Pirates
when they attacked this country?
Thanks...
I know. Calm down. Here, I'll let
you have the last rice cracker.
No match? It's not like that!
Don't overexert yourself, Nami-san!
Eh?
I don't want it! If we don't
turn the ship, we're gonna be--
When it happened, Wapol's army
didn't even try to fight!
Sorry, Vivi... I think...
I am kind of... in trouble...
A hunch.
In fact, the moment he learned
how strong the pirates were,
Just give it up, Nami.
Nami-san! Hang in there!
What is that?!
Wapol abandoned the country and was
the very first to flee out to sea!
All this snow! I'm so happy!
It's a cyclone!
Luffy! We can trust those guys, I hope?!
It's huge!
W-Wait! That's the direction--
That threw the entire nation into despair.
This is really somethin'.
What's with those mountains?
Yeah!
Are you crazy?! Are we really
going straight into that beast?!
That's the direction our
ship was just headed in!
Say, Luffy. Aren't you cold,
dressed like that?
Is this what the king--
No! We're too late now!
It would've been a direct hit
had we kept going straight!
Is that what the king of
an entire country does?!
It's -10 C right now!
That's when bears get ready to hibernate!
That's appalling!
A king abandoning his people!
Huh? Oh.
Vivi...
You're exactly right.
You've grown a lot, Island-Eater!
You filthy monster goldfish!
So cold!
Yikes! We just barely made it through!
But at least Wapol's
tyranny is finally over.
Took you long enough!
His size isn't his only surprise.
Incredible!
The remaining people on this
island have come together
Grand Line cyclones are said
to be impossible to predict!
to try to create a new country.
There's also the size and
length of the dung he produces
It's a waterfall of melted snow.
We may be able to stop around here.
Yet, she--
after devouring any islands nearby.
Afternoons are definitely
best with Earl Grey.
So what we most fear right
now is Wapol's return...
She doesn't predict weather
based on standard theory...
I recall a giant piece of dung
named Nothing At All Island...
So, who's going doctor-hunting?
It's almost as if she's detecting
the weather with her body!
The return of his monarchy.
Hold on, now!
No, I guess people-hunting comes first...
We must avoid that at all costs,
while people are still feeling unsure!
This is no time for me to be
drinking tea all fancy-like!
I've never seen such a navigator before!
--I'm going!
--Me too!
And that we landed on it long ago,
thinking it was actual land!
Okay! Have fun!
If we're to create a new,
peaceful nation on this island!
Alright! Let's hurry, then!
That's far enough, pirates!
Nami-san and the others might
be waiting for me to help them!
This is a nostalgic day of adventure!
Let's go find us a doctor!
As I look at them,
I'm reminded of the old days!
Yeah!
Still, though. What's such a
relaxing place doing in the jungle?
It jumped!
The only thing we can't penetrate
is the bloodstained snake!
You gotta be kidding me!
How can it move like that?!
Hey. I found people.
Observe, the most powerful Giant spear,
as passed down in Elbaf!
--What is it, a gorilla?!
--No! A polar bear!
But... they don't seem too friendly...
It's a bunny!
You're the one who just
called it a gorilla...
What's that?
These must be the Lapins that
Dalton was talking about!
What do we do, Vivi-chan?!
Nami-san's fever won't go down!
Straight ahead! Straight ahead!
Sanji-san! Karoo!
I asked you to stop freaking out!
This many of them?!
Attention, pirates! Leave this
place at once! This instant!
What are you talking about?!
We've already been eaten!
Oh...
Oh!
Straight ahead! Straight ahead!
It's a Transponder Snail.
Oh! Wapol-sama!
We came to find a doctor!
What is it, Chess?
Did you find Straw Hat's ship?!
We have a sick person onboard!
Heya. You've called the Damn Restaurant.
We won't fall for that trick,
you filthy pirates!
See any doctors?!
Do you expect him to, you idiot?
No, Wapol-sama!
We've finally returned home!
This is our island!
We won't let any pirates land here!
You want reservations?
What?!
How many months have passed
as we've wandered the sea?
Raise anchor and leave now!
Or else we'll blow your whole ship up!
Hey, guys. Do you think
people can stand on the ocean?
Quit fooling around, dumbass.
It's our homeland! The Drum Kingdom!
Can people stand on the ocean?
They really hate our guts.
And we've just met, too...
C'mon, Zoro. What kind of question is that?
Truly?!
Aren't you a bit late with your report?
Then... what's that?
Don't talk back!
They're shooting!
Oh? Report?
You didn't just do that!
Huh?
--Stop, Sanji-san!
--Bastard!
What's what?
And who might I be talking to?
Hakoku Sovereignty!
It's me.
Mr. 0.
Vivi!
Huh?!
The world is awfully big
so even if there is treasure somewhere,
the odds are astronomical
So relying on dumb luck
won't get you anywhere
So even...
So even,
...if someone stops me or
laughs at me from the shadows
if someone stops me or
the ship will continue forward
Bon voyage!
Forget about them!
I know I'm a fool, but I gotta go
I know I'm a fool,
but I gotta go
The crazier the dream,
the cooler the ambition
I know I'm a fool, but I'm gonna fight
I know I'm a fool,
but I'm gonna fight
The farther the sea,
the more heavenly it surely is
Do everything you can, and you'll
get a little nearer to any horizon
Do everything you can,
and you'll get a little nearer to any horizon
Oh, Nami-san!
Listen, Luffy!
Don't you dare fight these guys!
--I'm tired for some reason...
--Eh? Are you all right?
--I got my hands on this...
--An Eternal Pose to Alabasta!
Okay! We're going up that mountain!
To see the witch!
Forgive me for not being
able to lower your fever!
Don't be crazy! That'd be fine
for you, but not for Nami!
Everyone come here!
Nami-san has a terrible fever!
Why not?
Nami-san will feel
the whole impact and die!
--Yes!
--Now we can set sail!
You need to cool your head off!
Look around!
Is Nami-san gonna die?
We should treat her soon, right?
Alright, everyone!
Let's have a rice cracker party!
Okay! I won't fight!
But, what do I do?!
The ship's being attacked right now.
Let's find an island
with a doctor right away!
But look at how steep and high up it is!
Oh, no! We only have three left!
We can't have a rice cracker party!
What do we do?! What do we do?!
Don't we need to hurry to Alabasta?
Just dodge! Dodge and run!
But don't retreat!
--We can make it!
--I'm counting on you, Captain...
Oh, that's it? Nothing's worse
than Nami-san being sick!
Curing Nami-san's illness comes first!
You know this is no time for that!
Okay! Let's go! Before Nami dies!
Well said, Vivi-chan!
That's hard!
Let's go, Captain! We don't
have time to be lounging around!
Don't say things that could jinx us!
Whoa! He's eating our ship!
What?! The witch is
in the next town over?!
--What's that?!
--Do you see a doctor?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An Island Without Doctors?
Adventure in a Nameless Land!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Farewell, Giant Island!
Head for Alabasta"
"A Raid! Tin Tyrant
and Tin Plate Wapol"
"Nami's Sick?
Beyond the Snow Falling on the Sea!"
"Are You Happy?
The Doctor Called Witch!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!