I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is
as its name suggests, a zou (elephant)
that has been alive for a millennium.
They met the Mink Tribe who live there
and later, reunited with Nami and the rest.
The group visited Dogstorm,
King of the Day of
the Mokomo Dukedom, at his sanatorium.
There, they listened to all the details of
the battle between the Minks...
...and the Beast Pirates led by Jack,
the Emperor Kaido's subordinate,
that happened a half month ago.
The Fool of the Night woke up!
Let's retreat, Musketeers!
Aren't we gonna fight with them?
No, the day-and-night shifts are working.
We can stay on the offensive
without giving them a break.
Jack!
Don't think you-gara are
the only unreasonable man here!
It's my country when the moon is up!
You came looking for a warrior
from the Land of Wano, didn't you?
I wouldn't let any samurai
step onto the island!
If they come in,
I'll be the first to bite them to death!
I'm Cat Viper! The man who waits
for the dawn of the world!
You should've withdrawn
while the dog was treating you nicely!
Master!
"The Exterminated Capital!
The Twirly Hat Crew Arrive!"
Day and night, without break
the battle went on for five days.
You-gara! Are you trying to
fend off all my spear attacks?!
No one's ever done it,
not even in this country!
Go to hell, cat monster!
You're dead!
I planned on finishing you off quickly
but you're quite tough.
What's that? Huh?
Are you trying to mess with me?!
I'll kill you-gara!
I'd like to see you try.
It's already morning!
What? Are you guys gonna switch again?!
I wish I could bite you to death now
but I'll wait until tonight!
Don't get killed by the dog!
Hey, Bepo! Let's go!
--What? Master, I still wanna...
--Just come with me!
Master!
You can't get away, you bastard!
Haven't you given up yet, Jack?!
Jack-sama, I'll handle him!
--No, I will!
--I'll do it!
Duke! Leave the small fry to us!
Because of you-gara people,
I have to endure that stupid cat's smell!
We rotated our combatants by day and night
and continued fighting for two days,
three days, four days, and so on.
But Jack's reinforcements kept coming from
the sea and we could hardly fend them off.
It was like fighting a
wave of countless zombies!
However we were steadily
overwhelming the enemy!
I can say there was only one
that we couldn't bring down and that was...
...Jack!
He is, indeed, a monster!
I-Is he that strong?
He is.
Hmmm.
The guy who even this old man couldn't
beat was Kaido's subordinate.
Unbelievable!
But the enemy was having a hard time too.
I think Jack got tired of the two rulers
who he couldn't take down
so he finally brought out a weapon
on the fifth day!
It was...
...a poison-gas weapon.
--Gas?
--That's right, Luffy.
This country was ruined
by Caesar's poison-gas weapon!
Caesar created the weapon
and Doflamingo trafficked it
and it made it all the way to Kaido!
Caesar!
It all happened so quickly.
The deadly gas was filling the whole
country at the speed of a blast wave!
How could anyone escape that?!
That's horrible!
Strong old man...
He must've felt frustrated.
The gas filled up
the whole city and half of the forest
and totally paralyzed us.
Except for the people who evacuated
to the back of the fortress,
nearly everyone was killed!
I don't even want to remember...
...what happened after that!
Answer the question!
Where's the warrior from the Land of Wano?
He's not here!
They kept asking questions
they knew the answer to!
Then they brutalized our soldiers
and ruined our country!
We heard people screaming and crying
throughout the country...
Wanda...
Are you okay?
Yes, I am.
Then, they found Master Cat Viper
and the Guardians who were
paralyzed by the gas...
...and did the same to them.
But when they saw
they weren't getting anywhere...
our tough ones were crucified and tortured.
Where's the warrior from the Land of Wano?!
I don't know!
We wouldn't hide anyone like that!
Please stop...
No one in this country
knows anything about that!
We're really dying for nothing!
You have no mercy!
I won't let this go even if I die, Jack!
Until the day I curse you-gara
to death with my cat-grudge!
Those tragic events lasted one whole day
and on the sixth day,
maybe because Jack was satisfied
with the destruction
or tired of hearing the same answer,
he left a few dozen of his men behind
and departed from the island.
--That's too awful!
--There was no salvation.
No, that actually saved us too.
Oh, you were up!
I noticed that
when I read Jack's obituary in the newspaper.
JACK DIES!
The PROMINENT MEMBER OF THE BEAST PIRATES
"JACK THE DROUGHT"
Oh, so this is Jack.
He sure looks strong!
But I'm relieved if he's really dead.
The day you-gara people took down Doflamingo,
Jack left this country.
He left here to go save Doflamingo.
I guess they had some sort
of a deep connection.
So the ones who drove that monster
out of here were...
...you-gara people.
He fell asleep again!
I see!
Given all that,
I'm even more grateful to you all
and feel it was truly a miracle!
We're alive now,
really thanks to you-teia guys!
Oh no!
We arrived here
the very next day after Jack left!
Is that...
...Zou?!
I warn you!
I don't like the idea of landing here!
Hey.
You bastards!
Shut up and keep going!
Damn! I'll get even with you buttholes!
Is that...
Sanji-kun!
The gate is...
Seems like it was broken open
with tremendous force.
There was obviously an invasion!
A-An invasion?!
Are they our enemies too?!
Brook! Look after Nami-san here.
I'll go check inside.
No problem.
I-I'll look after Onami too!
Chopper! Caesar! Let's go!
Why should I go along...
Shut up and get moving!
See you later!
Don't take too long!
I can't believe there's a forest
on an elephant's back.
What's the matter?
I have a bad feeling.
Yeah?
Me too.
This is really elephant's skin!
It's so flabby!
It looks abandoned.
There's no guard or
gatekeeper. What happened?
Somebody, help!
Wh-What is it?!
What?!
Was she the one who talked?!
What's going on?!
Oh, he definitely looks like a villain!
That means she is a victim!
This way!
Wait, you little squirrel!
We just wanna crucify you
and ask some questions!
Who are you guys?!
Brook! Can you handle them?!
Okay.
A skeleton?
Yes, it's a skeleton.
What are you?!
He's a skeleton!
Can't you see that, Sheepshead-sama?!
Shut up! Whatever it is,
I'll wipe it out if it gets in my way!
Go!
Soul Parade!
Ice Burn!
--Yes!
--Good job, Bonekichi!
Thank you, Brook!
A talking skeleton and eel!
I'm scared!
Wait! Hey, you!
What's happening on this island?!
Maybe she doesn't like us.
--Let's chase her!
--Okay!
Stop!
Sheepshead-sama! You moron!
Damn! Let's chase them!
What's going on here?!
It's filled with gas.
Are those all animals on the ground?!
Idiot! They're the Mink Tribe!
Don't you know?!
Anyway, let's go back to the forest for now!
We'll be killed by the gas!
Hey, you-gara people...
He's alive!
What?! A talking animal?!
So are you.
Tsk! Seems like they're still alive.
You're not their-gara's allies,
are you?
I'm Pedro! Will you help me?
Please!
Duke Dogstorm and Master Cat Viper
need to be treated as soon as possible!
Otherwise, they're going to die...
The world is waiting for them.
Those two men...
We shall never ever...
...let them die!
There isn't much time left
for the wounded and downed Minks
as they hover
between life and death,
despairing for their lives!
However, Chopper and the others
stand up to save all of them!
At the critical moment when
the outlook is unclear,
the Twirly Hat Crew take bold
and compassionate action!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Time Limit Closes in!
The Bond Between the Mink Tribe and the Crew!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!