I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a journey with you, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
Despite the fact that everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
Both the rain and our tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
I've never seen the end of the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
That's why we've got to go, Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
Who says it's impossible? Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani? mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
...except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new adventure will take place.
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests,
a zou (elephant) that has been alive for a millennium.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests,
a zou (elephant) that has been alive for a millennium.
a zou (elephant) that has
been alive for a millennium.
as its name suggests,
a zou (elephant) that has been alive
They met the Mink Tribe and while heading
Luffy met the Mink Tribe who live there.
They met the Mink Tribe who live there.
They met the Mink Tribe who live there
and later, reunited with Nami and the rest.
for a millennium.
towards the Whale Forest
where Master Cat Viper is,
But Sanji went off on his own.
There they listened to all the details of
the battle between the Minks and...
The group visited Dogstorm,
King of the Day of
they listen what happened to Sanji.
the Mokomo Dukedom, at his sanatorium.
The group visited Dogstorm, King of the Day of
...the Beast Pirates led by Jack, Emperor Kaido's subordinate,
that happened a half month ago.
There they listened to all the details of
Don't move, you bastards!
the battle between the Minks and...
You fools can't kill me either, can you?!
By Mama's order, we have business
other than capturing Caesar.
There they listened to all the details of
the battle between the Minks and...
...the Beast Pirates led by Jack,
Emperor Kaido's subordinate,
And while heading towards
the Whale Forest to meet Master Cat Viper,
Hearing about this marriage
solves a mystery for me.
that happened a half month ago.
...the Beast Pirates led by Jack,
It could spell doom for your pirate group.
Emperor Kaido's subordinate,
that happened a half month ago.
they hear what happened to Sanji two days ago.
On the fifth day of the battle,
My wanted poster says "Only alive"!
Doom?
Jack finally brought out a poison-gas weapon.
Sanji and the rest arrived at Zou
the very next day after Jack left.
So let's forget it!
You gotta catch me alive!
The groom is the third son of the Vinsmoke Family,
The mission is failed!
Just give us Caesar!
The gas quickly filled the country
making the Minks fall one after another.
If you kill me, you'd piss somebody off,
wouldn't you?!
They found the Mink Tribe poisoned by gas
and took action to save their lives.
I'll just tell Mama
that we let the Straw Hats get away!
GROOM - THIRD SON OF THE VINSMOKE FAMILY - SANJI
Sanji!
Have you been told to treat me civilly
without even cuffs?!
The bride is the 35th daughter of the Charlotte Family, Pudding.
Pekoms! Are you losing your mind?!
Put your feelings aside!
Roko!
BRIDE - 35TH DAUGHTER OF THE CHARLOTTE FAMILY - PUDDING
The person who made them write
that phrase on the poster
Even if I don't rough you up,
you won't get away from Mama's tea party.
Shut up, newbie! I'll take the punishment!
and the one who arranged my marriage
must be the same person!
Pedro!
What's going on here?!
Wanda.
They-gara have nothing to do with Jack.
They saved my family members and friends.
That's common knowledge
throughout the New World.
Don't worry! I'll come with you.
To sort things out with that person!
The poison gas has just cleared away
from the city...
I can't do anything to them...
Anyway, let's go back to the forest for now!
We'll be killed by the gas!
That's right. Mama hates bitter sweets
...because of their-gara magic.
So don't do anything to my friends!
and empty seats at tea parties-rero.
It's night now so I'll go examine
Cat Viper, the King of the Night,
"The Time Limit Closes in!
The Bond Between the Mink Tribe and the Crew!"
All right!
We don't know what's on his mind
so let's go ask him!
and the Guardians of the Whale Forest!
You coward!
When you get an invitation to a tea party
from Big Mom-rero,
Okay! Let's go see Master Cat Viper!
It was a terrible sight.
What?!
that's basically an undeclinable summons!
We wanted to do something right away,
Hey! Forget it, Luffy!
"The Delinquent Comes Home!
Emperor Big Mom's Assassins!"
Don't tell me we're gonna head for Big Mom!
but the gas was still there
and it could've put our lives in jeopardy too.
Even the devil himself comes from hell
to attend Mama's tea party, they say!
We have no choice.
Did you forget that you picked a fight with her?!
That's why we left the city temporarily.
You bastard!
She's an Emperor.
I see.
Luffy! Don't forget.
She's on a totally different level than any of our past enemies.
It's a full moon tonight
but I'm glad that it's covered by the clouds.
Of course, you have a choice not to go-rorero.
But if you refuse...
Then, we'll go quietly.
How do we find them?!
Listen to me-rorero.
--Be careful!
--Okay!
Well, there is a way to go after them but...
ZOU, 10 DAYS AGO
Boy! I can't believe it!
"The Truth Behind the Disappearance!
Sanji Gets a Startling Invitation!"
Thank you, Carrot, for giving us a ride.
The whole country has been
ravaged by the poison gas!
That's okay. I'm a Kingsbird too.
Chopper, can't we do anything?
He's right.
Sanji-san has gone because of the Big Mom Pirates
Anyway, Wanda, so far in your story...
Considering the smell of the gas,
Yeah, both Twirly Eyebrows
and Gassy hadn't left yet.
it definitely has a nerve
agent as an ingredient.
but they left something big behind instead.
He shot his ally in the back!
There are other odors that I don't recognize.
How could he do that?!
If that person is awake now,
there should be something he can tell us.
Well...
"To My Buds!
Sanji's Farewell Note!"
Let me tell you what happened to them.
I got the chills seeing its power!
What did I just see?
What's so funny?!
The thing is we didn't tell that many
people in this country about this.
That person?
He may not look like it
but he's quite a well-known pirate.
The name of the gas is Koro!
It's a weapon of mass
destruction that I invented!
However, when he chose to act
on his pathetic feelings,
What did you just say?
We didn't want to make the people
"Let's Go and Meet Master Cat Viper!"
I said that gas was made by me...
he turned into such a coward.
who had their country ruined worry more.
There's no longer any use for him.
What?! Why should I take the blame?!
I'll do it myself!
How did you find that out?
This was a big event that happened
secretly just two days ago.
I'm not the one who used it!
Alright, guys! Come on out!
That's a silly question.
This guy is the worst.
Please be prepared
for what you're going to hear.
Who do you think our master is?
If you hadn't made it,
no one would've fallen victim to it!
That person,
Pekoms-san feels indebted to us
because we saved his people, the Minks.
Sanji-san might not...
The Four Emperors are the most powerful pirates there are,
reigning supreme over the New World,
I'm sure you can neutralize
it with your ability!
...come back to us.
Do it now!
Then, make an antidote!
It's not too late yet!
What?!
one of them being Big Mom herself.
Whoa-whoa.
That's why he tried to go
against Big Mom's order
Go!
Why, Brook?!
The gas works quite slowly, doesn't it?!
It says "I'll be back" in his note!
She has countless islands under her control
and let us get away.
I told you it's actually more complicated!
I made it that way on purpose
by my own calculations.
and the power that she possesses is
beyond your wildest imagination.
What?!
He will be back! I believe in Sanji!
But that only brought tragedy upon him.
How long will it take for them to die
after exposure?!
Nothing is impossible for her.
48 hours, maybe?
It was a mistake to show them this first.
She has it all.
48 hours?!
Without that annoying crappy cook,
I feel better so I don't mind at all.
Considering how much it cleared away,
more than a day has passed already!
If she tells someone she'll kill him,
he'll die.
What?! Humans?!
No! Sanji is our friend!
She doesn't bluff.
But now,
to find out where Sanji-san has gone,
Not again!
Hey! Don't think the
underdogs are always good!
Okay, okay, please relax, Luffy-san.
Stake your life on every word you say.
the only thing we can do is ask him
since he is a member of the Big Mom Pirates.
I'll tell you what happened
from the beginning.
What?
The Mink Tribe is known for disliking humans
and their great fighting strength!
If you wish to stay alive
without becoming anybody's subordinate,
Uh-huh!
What the hell?!
This island of Zou that we're on
is the Phantom Island.
do as she says, at least for now.
Okay!
Because the island itself is a living thing,
you can't get here even with a Log Pose
Leave them alone for your own good!
I'll get Sanji's whereabouts out of Lion Viper!
They'll bite us to death
as soon as we save them!
We won't get any answers unless
we talk to Sanji himself!
Give up! You're outnumbered!
or find it in a normal way but...
Bite us to death?
That gas guy's annoying!
Chopper.
...we made a blunder and had a blind spot.
This guy, Pekoms,
will he be well enough to talk?
And he's fascinated by its success.
Did the humans come out of his stomach?!
Sanji-san! Are you okay?
The way the gas works really
reflects his character.
First, at that time...
What kind of ability is that?!
What did he say to you earlier?
I hope he's come around.
You go ahead and sail for Zou!
I thought I saw humans in his hand
but, that wasn't an illusion!
Taking two days to kill people little
by little sounds really awful!
What's the matter, Sanji?!
We'll fight even against an Emperor!
...we allowed the enemy ship that we'd
shaken off to know our destination.
What happened then?
I ate the Castle-Castle Fruit
and became a castle human.
Well...
Be quiet!
I'm regarded in the same
generation as your captain,
Second, someone from the Phantom
Island was on their ship.
We should've waited on the ship quietly!
That's quite a lot.
You're pretty stupid to be
rushing ahead like this!
so you know me, don't you?
Carrot!
Shut up and do what he says!
Are you gonna do it?!
So the ones who showed up in front of us
two days ago were...
Okay!
Capone "Gang" Bege!
What is that?!
Or do you just want your
heart to be crushed?!
CAPONE "GANG" BEGE
BOUNTY: 300 MILLION BERRIES
THE CAPTAIN OF THE FIRETANK PIRATES
When Luffy punched the
Celestial Dragon at Sabaody,
...Emperor Big Mom's pirate group!
A swarm of bugs?!
Give me some paper and a pen.
--Those are Sutchies.
--Sutchies?!
you were there, weren't you?!
--Bring them to him.
--Yes, sir.
Giant insects that suck blood!
Yeah, we were forced to waste so
much energy because of you guys.
Fine! But I won't forget this!
You-teia Lesser Minks have less hair
so they can suck all your blood and kill you in an instant!
Are you gonna leave a note for Straw Hat?
It was the right call to come ashore!
Clank.
We arrived.
We can still save them! We need your help!
We could've blown you guys up too
in a big show with cannons.
Yeah, no problem. Count on us, Mama.
--Really?!
--Look up! Look!
The two of us can finish this.
In that case, why don't you
treat me more nicely...
We're not gonna make a scene here.
We don't want that, either.
We'll be drained dry!
Zou is where I came from! Grr!
Did you say something?!
Stop taunting me with that!
Special Attack: Exploding Star!
Hurry up, Caesar!
If they die because of you,
I'll make you pay for it!
If the Minks come,
they'll definitely take your side.
Sutchies are vicious.
They even suck Zunesha's blood and weaken it.
I know how well they can fight.
We need your help!
Hand this to Luffy and everybody.
What?
What?!
Can they even weaken the elephant?!
We're not looking for their
help in the first place!
Sanji-kun...
What?
That's why, in this country,
we exterminate all we find.
Nami-san.
Chopper.
--What the...?
--What's going on?
I'll accept anyone's challenge!
Brook.
Y-You've got to be kidding...
Sanji-san!
Believe this if nothing else.
When it comes to this,
we gotta stop them here!
I didn't mean to hide anything from my friends.
I agree! Pekoms-san was trying
to settle this peacefully,
What the hell... Hey!
Stop, Carrot! Luffy and the others' Warney
has been brought down!
Where is everybody?!
but he shot him like that! In the back!
Vinsmoke.
So this is the Phantom Island, Zou.
That's something from the past
that I thought I'd never have to deal with again.
I can't forgive him, either!
I'm losing my power...
What happened?! Grr!
Who did this to Zou?!
It's salty! It's seawater!
I really need to go and sort things out!
I knew that's what you would do.
Get up, Warney!
They'll get you if you keep still!
Hey! Anybody?! Is anybody here?!
Chopper!
Vito!
Everybody! Where did you go?!
No!
Wait a minute, Sanji-san.
Do you mean "by yourself"?
Gust Sword!
Let go of me!
--Nami-san!
--Chopper-san!
I'll attract the bugs!
I feel a powerful presence outside.
It's probably one of the Minks.
Franky...
Sanji, thank you.
I-I'm sorry!
We couldn't help worrying so...
...Nipple Light!
Did the Straw Hats do this?!
Are you ready?
I'm sorry! I thought there
were only two enemies!
How does that even work?!
Couldn't you save me a little more gently?!
Ready for what?
Good luck!
What did they do to my home?!
Oh, your-teia light is drawing the Sutchies!
Stop complaining after I saved you!
Oh...
What? Is it working?
Black-Foot!
Caesar! Why don't you come out, too?!
I'm gonna exterminate the Sutchies!
That's Nami-san's voice!
Okay, Caesar?!
I'll back you up!
Get the poison gas you created
out of the city before I come back!
I have no blood to be sucked!
We'll fire shotguns containing Sea Prism Stone
towards the sky in two seconds!
What about me?!
What?!
Otherwise,
I'll crush your heart here in my fist and...
--That fool!
--He freed his allies!
Two!
That bastard!
Alright! You devil!
One!
You idiot!
Sanji, leave him in my hands.
Chase them!
They're weak but don't lower your guard!
Wait a sec! I'm here! Don't shoot!
Yeah, thanks!
Okay! If I do this,
they can't sting or get away!
Hold him down!
Okay, it's ready.
Don't point them at me!
There she is!
Take it.
Brook!
Tell them to stand down!
--Keep stalling him like that!
--What?!
Looks delicious!
Come to think of it, we don't have any bullets
containing Sea Prism Stone.
I made you two your own batch.
Diable! Mouton...
Really?! Yes!
What?!
...Mallet!
Here! Come to me!
But we have a spear that works like that!
I-I feel so weak...
I'm gonna fight too! Kung Fu Point!
Damn! You little jerk!
Sheepshead-sama!
Wait-rero! You can't shoot him!
Now...
Everyone's here now.
Let's go greet everyone!
Guys! Retreat!
Sheepshead-sama has been taken down!
Rather than standing around here talking,
get into my castle.
Garchu!
What?!
Special Attack: Green Star - Skull-Blast Glass!
But we haven't found the samurai yet!
Don't move, you bastards!
Although we cornered them this far,
he didn't show himself!
Why...?
Sanji's cooking is really good!
That's an order!
Okay, listen carefully!
The samurai's not here! Tell him so!
It brings the Chill of the Dead!
This genius scientist is important to you
and I bet you don't want me to blow his brains out!
Damn! He's completely in control.
Its nutritional balance is perfect
so make sure to eat it all.
Yes, ma'am!
Soul Solid!
--Can I have more?!
--I want more!
I'll get even with you, Black-Foot!
All right. Now let me see your arm.
Cien Fleurs!
Hey, what did he mean by his "castle"?
Okay.
Weren't you listening?!
Three-Sword Style Dragon Twister!
I thought so.
Dr. Chopper made this injectable drug.
You'll get better soon.
You fools can't kill me either, can you?!
Bege is a castle human who ate
the Castle-Castle Fruit. Okay?
Thanks.
Hearing about this marriage
solves a mystery for me.
Do it! Neutralize the gas!
So you guys got into his body.
Tongue, tongue, bleah!
But I don't have a tongue!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
How annoying. All right.
I'll do it! Are you happy now?!
--Yes.
--Really?! How?!
My wanted poster says "Only alive"!
By slicing through his stomach, maybe?
Gum-Gum...
Okay, it's done! Good boy!
...Gatling!
You gotta catch me alive!
Stop it, Robin!
Koro-neutralizing gas!
Super disgusting...
If you kill me, you'd piss somebody off,
wouldn't you?!
This is so against my will!
That's not it!
Thank you, Dr. Chopper!
Have you been told to treat me civilly
without even cuffs?!
An entrance appeared around his chest.
Seems like we got rid of them!
Roko!
The person who made them
write that phrase on the poster
We were in chains
and the one who arranged my marriage
must be the same person!
Alright. My next patient is...!
so we had no choice but to obey.
Ouch!
Thanks to you all, we cleared the Sutchies.
You-teia guys have been helping us a lot.
Dr. Miyagi! You're hopping too much!
Damn! Let's get out and chase them!
This is a residential quarter
where our ancestors used to live.
I said "Don't move"!
Don't mention it.
Please don't move!
Thank you.
You know someone's got my back now, don't you?!
Anyway, Cat Viper's place, are we there yet?
Zunesha has carried the whole history of
the Mink Tribe without change.
Just a bit more.
We'll get to the Guardians' Dwelling soon so...
Don't worry! I'll come with you.
To sort things out with that person!
One of the Mink Tribe's tradition
that goes far back in that history is...
--Master Cat Viper, huh?
--I wonder what kind of person he is.
...exchanging clothes with foreigners,
as a sign of friendship!
So don't do anything to my friends!
He is heavily injured.
I hope he is resting in bed quietly.
Oh, this is beautiful!
It's like a dress for somebody great.
All of you, stay where you are!
--What?!
--Father!
Yes. And that accessory
is a national treasure.
Master Cat Viper.
He's a wonderful person!
What?! Are you giving it to me?!
Of course. Everyone agreed we should.
I like him so much so I wrote a song about him.
There is a... monster... outside now!
Garchu! Garchu-chu!
Mademoiselle, garchu.
Let's go and meet Master Cat Viper
Garchu.
Master Cat Viper...
How are you?! Garchu.
You're up!
Garchu.
Let's go and meet Master Cat Viper
Tristan-chan!
Thank you for waiting.
Garchu!
Is that a cat monster?!
I didn't know there was such a terrible thing here!
Okay, it's good!
Garchu!
Would you guys like to eat something?
Hey! Guys!
Sanji-san, you like to greet everyone.
Hey!
No thanks.
Let's go and meet Master Cat Viper
Get over here now!
You-gara, who are you?
You don't have to be humble.
Maybe a glass of wine?
That's Chopperemon!
From the forest down below!
What is "garchu"?
I saw Pekoms lying down back there bleeding.
We don't want anything!
Get down to business already!
Let's go now! There's no time to lose!
Is it a miraculous magic word or something?
Let's go and meet Master Cat Viper
He'll kill us! He'll kill us! He'll kill us!
Sanji! It's from us to you,
our great savior; Garchu!
Th-This is awful!
You should cut yourself some slack sometimes.
Were they all killed by Caesar's weapon?!
Shut up! I don't want it from guys!
Did you-gara do that?
Oh, Sanji-san. Garchu!
Yeah. Most of the people have been wiped out.
Garchu! Garchu!
Let's go and meet Master Cat Viper
We exchanged gunfire at sea
a week ago but the situation
That's not fair.
No, you got it wrong! I'm his crewmate!
It must've been done by
those fools from earlier.
The Lesser Minks are only nice to girls.
You mean those people who just attacked us?
Crewmate?
has changed since then.
Oh, boy! Viva minkship!
Yes, we belong to the same pirate group!
Seems like Caesar neutralized
the gas successfully
I was asked to hand you this invitation.
We've actually been attacked by
the remnants of Jack's crew!
Let's go and meet Master Cat Viper
Is that a goddess?!
but they've done so much damage.
No...
Invitation?
It's an invitation to Mama's tea party.
So there is a chance
That's not true!
Nami-san!
that a lot of them are
still hiding somewhere on the island.
Don't be fooled! He shot Pekoms!
Cut the crap.
Garchu!
Are you sure?!
Why would I wanna go to Big Mom's tea party?
Is that it?
Why would I shoot my ally?!
There is a chance, I said.
You were just repeating the same phrase
over and over.
The highlight of the party
will be a wedding ceremony.
According to the gas idiot,
the Mink Tribe is a savage race.
Sanji-kun, come on out!
Why do you wanna stay?!
Where is Momo?
Screw it.
Yes, because this song is called
"Let's Go and Meet Master Cat Viper."
He's still locked in his room.
He feels more comfortable that way.
Tell us what's really going on, Sanji!
The groom is the third son
of the Vinsmoke Family,
We might end up regretting that we saved them
but...
What do you mean you need to go?!
Why can't we all go together?!
--No kidding!
--Is it just repeating the same line throughout the song?
Plus, he shouldn't let
them see his human form.
GROOM - THIRD SON OF THE
VINSMOKE FAMILY - SANJI
Sanji!
Are you-teia guys Jack's allies too?!
You're right.
What?!
No, it'll get a little more complex from here.
We'd better not mention the word "samurai"
while we're in this country.
Let's wait for Luffy-san and everybody,
Sanji-san!
What?!
What?!!
S-Stay away!
Nami-san!
Cat Viper, Cat Viper
The bride is the 35th daughter
of the Charlotte Family,
Come on out already!
Just give that annoying brat to the Minks
and let's leave this crappy island already!
Onami!
BRIDE - 35TH DAUGHTER OF THE
CHARLOTTE FAMILY - PUDDING
Pudding.
Marriage?!
Wait! It's okay!
Shut up!
Hey, Caesar, did you make the drugs?
Cat Viper, let's go and meet the Master
She's weaken by the poison!
This is my problem.
I met my quota because I'm a genius.
--Make more! Don't stop!
--There are still so many injured people!
I'll be back.
Master Cat Viper gets lonely easily
Keep working!
Why should I do such a thing...
Tell them "Hi" for me.
Dr. Caesar, I came to pick up the drugs.
Nami-san! She has an explosive!
When I think of him like that
it makes my heart twinge
Hey, don't make a mistake!
I'm Cedar the pharmacist!
What?!
Here.
Damn! Why am I making drugs to save people?!
I'll never forgive you-teia people! Never!
Castle Tank!
When he is bathed in the moonlight
his face looks innocent
Thank you, Dr. Caesar!
What did we do to you?!
What do you gain from killing us?!
It's Cedar!
Man! This work disgraces my name,
Caesar the genius mad scientist!
The person you-teia are looking
for isn't here!
Sanji!
He gazes up at it with his sparkling eyes
--Oh yeah...
--It's Cedar!
TEA PARTY
This country has a millennium-long history!
Sanji-kun!
Baron Corpse,
your fans are waiting for you outside.
D-During a tea party...
How much do you have to destroy
to get your fill?!
Erk!
They'll hold Sanji's wedding?!
Where's Baron Corpse?!
--Let me garchu!
--Gimmie them bones to chew!
GROOM - THIRD SON OF THE
VINSMOKE FAMILY - SANJI
BRIDE - 35TH DAUGHTER OF THE
CHARLOTTE FAMILY - PUDDING
But he tries to act tough under the sun
I don't need popularity among dogs...
Take it.
--Somebody's coming.
--Are they the remnants of the Beast Pirates?
He does his best and lives his life on his own
TEA PARTY
I like that song.
GROOM - THIRD SON OF THE
VINSMOKE FAMILY - SANJI
Is Master Cat Viper really like that?
Wait! It's me! Grr!
Not at all.
You-gara are...
Why, after all these years?!
Pekoms!
Hey! You're wounded!
What happened to you? Grr!
THE VINSMOKE FAMILY
He's not?!
I don't know the deal with your family!
It's just a song inspired by him.
Well, it's...
--Was it the Straw Hats?!
--What?!
Memorize it.
Wanda-san!
Where are they?!
I'll avenge you against them!
Those-teia people saved me!
You bastard! Are you trying to set fire to my castle?!
Hey, what are you talkin...
Tristan!
All of Jack's subordinates have just
left the island!
Hey, Sanji-kun, what is this all about?!
Those bastards! I won't forgive them!
Are you gonna get married?!
What? Left?
The Straw Hats!
Who made the decision without asking?!
Did they-teia?
Okay, we're here.
Your family, of course!
Being a son of the Vinsmoke Family means...
Pedro!
Wanda. They-gara have
nothing to do with Jack.
Nami! Chopper! Should I just chase him?!
...you're quite ill-bred.
No, it's no use, Wanda-san!
Baron Corpse!
V-V-Vinsmoke is Sanji-san's surname?!
It's the Guardians' Dwelling.
The poison gas has just cleared away
from the city...
Even if we can catch up to him,
he has...
The name gives me chills down my spine.
It's inexcusable!
Where're the Straw Hats?!
...no intentions of coming back now!
...because of their-gara magic.
But no, that's not possible.
--Hey, bring me a glass of wine!
--Yes, sir!
Come to think of it, the gas is gone.
They'll pay for this! Where are they?!
Sanji-kun's family... Oh!
You-teia people...
Tell me!
--W-Wait a minute!
--Calm down, Pekoms!
Who are you?
Remember when we found the
What are you guys doing?!
"To my buds,"
picture book called "Noland the Liar" at Mont Blanc's place!
Shut up! Let go of me!
Chopper!
Wait! All of our friends are okay!
They're in the fortress!
More than a day has passed
since the gas was released!
"I've gotta go see a woman.
I'll be back."
NOLAND THE LIAR
A picture book...
It's titled "Noland the Liar"...
To counteract this gas, we
have to give the poisoned ones
The Straw Hats saved us!
the antidote within 48 hours
or it'll be too late for them!
TO MY BUDS, I'VE GOTTA GO SEE A WOMAN. I'LL BE BACK.
SANJI
That's a cool title! Nice idea for a book!
What?!
What's that?
I'm gonna make the antidote now!
"Noland the Liar"?
You know it, Sanji-kun?
What?
What did you say?
To save everybody in the country,
we can't even waste a second!
But it says it was published in the North Blue.
This place has been totally wrecked.
Yeah. I was born in the North Blue.
Where is there a hospital?!
I need more instruments and medicine!
Bring everybody who can help here!
Haven't I told you guys?
THE GUARDIANS' DWELLING, THE WHALE FOREST
--Pekoms!
--It's you, Pekoms!
That's news. I thought you were from the East, too.
I'm a doctor! Do as I say!
--You're home!
--Pekoms!
I'm a nurse! Let me help you!
I grew up there. Well, who cares.
Okay! Thanks!
So you guys are all okay!
I remember feeling strange at that time.
Are you going to... save us?
Dad! Mom!
All my relatives and friends!
We met him in the East Blue
but he said he was born in the North Blue.
The Whale Tree...
Nami. I don't see Sanji or Cedar.
...looks even bigger up close!
--Welcome home!
--How long has it been?!
What?! Are you sure, Nami-san?!
This brings back memories!
If that's true, it's a big deal!
Don't tell me they were taken away...
I thought we were going to die... All of us!
Yeah! You're looking good and I'm so happy!
Garchu!
No, he went willingly.
Hey, guys!
It's the Straw Hats!
We won't give up on anybody!
What?
You idiot! You're covered with cuts and bruises!
Don't tell me you're happy!
Chopper is here!
The sea of the world is divided by the Red Line,
What do you mean?
Garchu!
the massive red soil continent which is taller than the clouds.
You need to help us.
Garchu!
When I saw the city,
I thought my heart would stop!
Tsk. All right.
Garchu!
Wanda! Carrot!
The Grand Line, the sea route that goes round the world...
--Garchu!
--Hey, you're hurting me!
It was a race against time from there.
They-gara want you to forget about it.
You must understand.
--The Minks are recovering fast, aren't they?
--You're right.
...which is perpendicular to the Red Line,
dividing it into four.
It's all thanks to the Straw Hats!
Straw Hat Luffy! It's us!
If it weren't for their desperate rescue,
We'll take care of Pekoms too.
The seas that are divided into
the north, south, east and west are called;
Sorry for what we did in the forest.
I don't know what would've
happened to us by now.
Don't give the daytime people
unnecessary anxiety.
East Blue, West Blue,
Doesn't matter who it is,
we can't let any invader get by!
Really, thank you for staying alive!
Are you telling me to make it with these?!
South Blue and North Blue.
Yes, I understand, sire.
Oh, it's you guys!
I apologize.
Well, never mind!
Yes, make the antidote!
I'm sorry.
In order to move to the East Blue from the North Blue,
--Where are the doctors?
--They're taking shelter in the fortress.
Um, where's Cat Viper?
No, please.
I'm sorry for making you feel that way after you saved us.
you have to surmount the Red Line!
Whoa-whoa, stop crying.
Fortress?
Most of the citizens are taking shelter
at the Rightflank Fortress in the forest.
--That's right!
--Is it difficult?
I'm glad to see you!
Thank you, Master.
Our saviors and their friends!
What's going on?
You-gara guys show concern for
our broken-hearted citizens.
Yes, it's not just one family moving to another place!
Those jerks!
Bring everyone here now!
Let me say it once again.
Thank you!
Hey, look!
It's a great voyage!
We should thank you.
Damn! I can't forgive Jack
of the Beast Pirates!
I need their help with
carrying the injured to the open space here!
Who is this?!
Sanji-san, what kind of
childhood did he have?
TREETOP PEDRO (A JAGUAR MINK)
CAPTAIN, THE GUARDIANS OF THE WHALE FOREST
Sorry for my subordinates' action in the forest.
Tristan, I'm alright.
The gas is flowing into the forest too.
How dare he do that to my home!
And, you know,
Charlotte is Big Mom's surname!
They were too wary of invaders.
Were you there?
What?!
We need everyone's help!
Yes, I was up in a tree.
But, at any rate,
I'm glad that you're all okay!
That fool! Is he gonna marry Big Mom's daughter?!
Okay! I'll go and get them!
It won't take long!
Bepo and the others are waiting for you-gara guys
back there.
There's silver vine!
Will he join an Emperor's family?!
When the antidote is made,
we'll administer it to everyone!
If your fellow crewmember becomes her son-in-law,
We can see them later.
Look! Those guys from the Big Mom Pirates!
They made it this far!
Okay!
you guys will practically be her subordinates!
Let's do it.
We wanna see Cat Viper
and Lion Viper the lion first.
We'll start treating those we can!
That's Pekoms! He came home.
What?!
Don't jump to conclusions!
Garchu!
Then, "gotta go see a woman" means...
Yeah, thanks! Now, let's do it!
He used to be an infamous delinquent.
If you're talking about Pekoms, he's up now.
He's in the building at the back.
I'm under no obligation to
go to such a tea party!
...he's gonna get married?
Oh, so he's a Mink.
We kept the whole incident secret
from everybody.
How ridiculous!
That's not necessarily the case but...
My wedding ceremony?
Sanji is a nice guy.
They must've heard this
is where we were heading!
...it seemed like he was determined.
Marrying a woman I don't even know?!
I hope we can help you in some way.
This way! Hurry up!
They want me!
You've got to be kidding me!
--Oh, maybe he'll return with his wife.
--What?!
Hey, please!
Don't hand me over to them.
Luffy! I'm worried about Cat Viper -
not just about his condition though, so I'll go see him first!
In that case, we'll get a new member!
Wh-What the...
You were our trump card against Doflamingo.
I don't want the Straw Hats
to become your subordinates either!
You're so optimistic.
Okay!
Now that Luffy and the others took him down,
Then, let me lead the way, Dr. Chopper.
Th-This is... awful...
Luffy-san.
The bride is the Emperor's daughter.
we don't care what happens to you.
Our captain isn't the type of guy
who works under someone!
Don't say such a thing! We're friends!
That means
we'll become Big Mom's subordinates.
Luffy will...
When did we become friends?!
What?!
...become the King of the Pirates!
You were whining about
something at Dressrosa too.
No!
Of course, Sanji-san doesn't want that either.
What did you do to Big Mom?
Oh, that's it! Hear me out!
Done!
Hey, Chopper! Why are you frozen?
He refused it firmly right there.
That's some big talk.
Hey! The antidote will be ready soon!
Please! We need your help!
I got an offer to research something
which I haven't succeeded at yet,
But that troubles me.
I-I-I'm not frozen.
Are we done here? You can have Caesar.
and I lied to her
and ripped her off pretty badly!
Considering who he is dealing with this time,
if he couldn't avoid the marriage,
You're acting strange.
What?!
I had Doflamingo at my back
so I pushed my luck!
Let us go!
It's this way.
O-Okay!
Screw you!
what do you think he would do?
Master Cat Viper is taking a bath now.
So you asked for it.
I think you have the wrong idea.
The invitation was only for you to see.
Well, he would...
I hope all they want is Caesar...
What?!
Yeah, he's the kind of guy
who'll try not to cause us any trouble
I wasn't looking for your answer.
A bath?!
Monkey D. Luffy.
I know your name now.
SAKE
You're in my body!
Will this work?!
so he'd try to separate himself from us!
PROTECT
Come to the New World!
I made that! Of course, it'll work!
Lasagna-meow!
You mean Sanji will quit this group?!
Sure, wait for me there.
You guys have already been captured!
I'll take you all to Mama!
Okay, we need enough for
all the fallen people!
It's good-meow! Yeah!
That's even more unacceptable!
There's some business
I want to settle with you, too.
Make more!
When he tossed us out,
For all of them?!
Hey, Cat Viper!
I can't leave it in your hands -
that's too dangerous!
What?!
he could've gotten away too.
You shouldn't take a bath!
Your wound's gonna reopen!
And you should eat light meals!
Okay! You're alright now.
It'll take effect soon.
I'll kick your ass all over the New World...
When he wrote the note,
I think he'd already made up his mind to go by himself.
I'm sure you don't feel any motion
Why are you using your left hand?!
Thank you.
...and make the Fish-Man Island my territory!
but I'm already on the move.
Is it really moving?!
Now we know everything.
You've been through a lot.
Are you listening to me?!
Luffy picked a fight with Big Mom
at the Fish-Man Island.
Oh, Chopper!
She'll kill me! Let me out!
No problem. No problem.
We broke their ship too.
Big Mom's daughter, huh?
He got a pretty troublesome offer of marriage.
You...
I'm a freedom-loving man!
A life being targeted by an Emperor...
We're better off dead.
Don't worry. They are okay!
You have to listen to your doctor!
If you wanna fight, I'll fight you.
He's larger than I expected.
And did you say Vinsmoke?
I guess that family is the key.
Well, I'm already dead though.
I'm sorry but even if it's a doctor's instruction...
Oops.
What the...!
It could be Sanji's father or mother or brother...
I don't care!
What should we do, Sanji-kun?!
I still can't get used to not having a left hand!
Sanji-kun!
There! You're okay now!
They once lived in the North Blue and then moved
Yes!
to the East Blue and now,
they're in the New World.
I can't even clap my hands like this!
Hey, Black-Foot.
Let me help you too!
Do you wanna work together
with me and take them out?
Unbelievable!
Is it okay for you to move now?
You should rest more.
Vinsmoke...
Think about it!
--Do you know of them?
--I think I've heard of them before...
So you-gara people are the Straw Hats!
They're from the Big Mom Pirates
but only the two of them are here!
No, I'm much better.
I'm sorry. I can't remember.
If it's just them,
you and I can handle them together!
And this is our country!
You saved me!
I have full command
over the interior of the castle!
Thank you!
Let's use my poison gas again and...
I'll repay my debt to you someday!
We're sorry.
I may not look it but
I have a strong sense of obligation and compassion!
I wish we could've stopped him
at least until you guys arrived...
You have to pull yourself together!
Everything is under my control!
Sanji wouldn't let you stop him.
It's not your fault, guys.
Oh, a ball.
--Help!
--Oh! Nami's sinking!
But, Robin,
what if we never get to see him again?!
Nami-san!
Yeah! A ball!
Nothing wrong with that.
Nami!
--Nami-san, stay with the rest here.
--Uh-huh.
Huh?! What are you saying, Zoro?!
Okay, everybody!
I made something for you!
--I won't forgive you!
--Bring her back up already!
--Brook, come with me.
--Okay.
I mean, if he was leaving for good,
Eat up! It'll give you strength!
Stop!
I told you to rest!
Hey, Black-Foot!
What about my cool idea to assassinate them?!
he should've said
"Thank you for everything."
Shut up you unthinking idiot.
See! The wound reopened!
And "I'm sorry for causing so much trouble."
No!
No, that's not the point!
I said "Stop"!
That is the point.
It's damn good, isn't it?
Think about it.
We're on an unstoppable train now.
Yeah, thank you.
Listen, I...
It's warming up my entire body.
I got into bed because I wanted to.
Remember what Caesar said?
Are you alright?
So the members of the Big Mom Pirates
were here in Zou too!
Do you want some more?
--Uh-huh.
--What a relief!
The biggest customer of SMILEs,
the artificial Devil Fruits, is Kaido.
No, I had enough.
Let everyone else have more.
Uh-huh, uh-huh, okay.
Even if I don't rough you up,
you won't get away from Mama's tea party.
Before that, it was Kaido's Beast Pirates.
They're both Emperors.
Whatever the case, just stay still!
Well, I can keep making more!
Eat as much as you can!
I'm gonna give you a shot.
Did Sanji get into a fight
with that Peko-something?!
Alright, everybody!
I'll play you some soothing music.
I'm sure he won, didn't he?!
We pissed Doflamingo off
by destroying the lab on Punk Hazard,
That's common knowledge
throughout the New World.
Don't set him up for a fight with an Emperor!
No problem!
I already picked a fight with her!
Hey, you-gara!
we destroyed the SMILE factory in Dressrosa,
Show me that foxtail right there.
Sanji-san is truly kind.
and the man who's gonna go nuts next is...
That's right. Mama hates bitter sweets
Like this?
He took the two out of the Rightflank
Fortress to a distant forest.
...Emperor Kaido!
He's not some distant threat anymore.
and empty seats at tea parties-rero.
Chopper!
Hurry up while I'm distracted and enjoying myself!
We've already had a fight with his subordinates,
the Beast Pirates.
When someone refuses her
because he's ignorant-rero,
I said "Stay still"!
Jack who ruined this country, and others will
come after us in a matter of time!
Are you afraid of shots?!
Even looking like that?!
he'll cry in regret later and I
can't bear to see that-rorero!
You didn't even know who we were!
"PHANTOM GUN" VITO
AN ADVISOR OF THE FIRETANK PIRATES
What do you Big Mom Pirates want?
But you saved us without giving up.
We're allying with Tra-guy
for upcoming battles.
Don't cause trouble.
When you get an invitation to a tea party from Big Mom-rero,
The people in this country are hurt
inside and out now.
We'll never forget what you did for us!
I don't know why but it seems like
Kin'emon and the others are targeted by Kaido too.
that's basically an undeclinable summons!
If you need to talk, talk to me first.
We'll pay our debt to you someday!
It's completely cured now.
We'll face Emperor Kaido very soon!
No, no! You don't have to do that!
If that's not enough,
I'm afraid we gotta take it out of the country.
There's no wonder drug like that
so keep quiet!
Even the devil himself comes from hell
to attend Mama's tea party, they say!
Don't hit an injured person.
How stupid can he be to get involved with
We're not gonna run or hide.
You guys did such a nice thing!
I'm so proud of you!
another Emperor, Big Mom, now?!
That twirly-eyebrowed fool!
Boy, he's so funny!
Of course, you have a choice not to go-rorero.
I can't believe it was that serious...
I love him!
All I can say is thank you! Grr!
Now I understand why
we were so welcomed.
But if you refuse...
Don't say it like that!
You boorish son of a gun!
Those things are unrelated!
I can't believe you survived!
Listen to me-rorero.
I blocked about half of the attack
with my ability! Grr!
Anyway, that Jack guy makes me mad!
H-Hey...
N-Nami-san...
I'll kick his butt as
well as Kaido's someday!
Bege, that bastard!
First of all, how could he get wrapped up in
such a thing as marriage?! It's such a small deal!
I didn't expect to see my home country
devastated like this...
But he said there was an obituary...
I'm sorry.
They must've taken Black-Foot with them.
Oh yeah!
Damn! I can't kick his butt!
What did you say?!
He can't get away from the wedding now!
Both of you! Don't get so heated up!
But you guys saved the people, didn't you?!
Well, it's hard to believe
if you had seen him with your own eyes.
Yeah, about that, Lion Viper,
It is a big deal!
You can't say someone else's problem is big or small!
I owe you!
who arranged the marriage?
How can I thank you...
Do you think he's alive?
Well, of course, our Mama and
the father of the Vinsmoke Family!
What?!
I don't know.
All right!
We don't know what's on his mind
so let's go ask him!
Guys, will you stay here and talk?
Sanji-kun's father?!
What kind of person is he?!
Are you gonna go somewhere, Chopper?
What?!
It's night now so I'll go examine
Cat Viper, the King of the Night,
He's quite infamous in the underworld.
Hey! Forget it, Luffy!
and the Guardians of the Whale Forest!
Don't tell me we're gonna head for Big Mom!
By Mama's order, we have business
other than capturing Caesar.
Have you ever heard the name, Germa 66?
Oh, I'll take you there with my Warney.
We have no choice.
Come to think of it, Wanda,
isn't it time for you to sleep too?
Did you forget that you picked a fight with her?!
Also known as the Warmongers.
It could spell doom for your pirate group.
What are you talking about?!
That's a mythical evil army!
Without a strategy or reinforcements,
we'll just get beaten and that'll be it!
I work as a Kingsbird.
Doom?
So let's forget it! The mission is failed!
Just give us Caesar!
A Kingsbird?
How ridiculous!
She's an Emperor.
Yes - an aide to the kings
and the only office that is
Luffy! Don't forget.
She's on a totally different level than any of our past enemies.
No, it's an actual organization.
I'll just tell Mom
that we let the Straw Hats get away!
allowed to go back and forth between them
Vito. Relax.
Then, we'll go quietly.
regardless of whether it's day or night.
The Vinsmoke Family is at the top of it!
How do we find them?!
Wow, that's an important job!
Pekoms! Are you losing your mind?!
Put your feelings aside!
And their boss is Black-Foot's father!
Well, there is a way to go after them but...
I have to tell him
that Duke Dogstorm is okay.
Shut up, newbie! I'll take the punishment!
He'd probably say it's unnecessary.
Believe this if nothing else.
Okay! See you guys!
He's right.
I didn't mean to hide anything from my friends.
They saved my family members and friends.
I'll come with you!
I wanna see Cat Viper!
Sanji-san has gone because of the Big Mom Pirates
How did you find that out?
I can't do anything to them...
Master Cat Viper! I like him so much!
I'll come with you!
That's a silly question.
but they left something big behind instead.
The Vinsmoke Family is, well, to put it simply,
We'll come too!
I'm curious about this King of the Night!
If that person is awake now,
there should be something he can tell us.
You coward!
a family of assassins!
Chopper said he's heavily injured...
Well, he has amazing recuperative powers.
That person?
And he's big like Dogstorm!
Is it really okay for us to come?
Let's just keep going.
Yes, you're welcome.
I'm sure Master Cat Viper will be happy
to see our saviors.
Well, if you're sure it's all right...
Okay! Let's go see Master Cat Viper!
Sanji and the rest who
saved the Minks that were
Pekoms tells
how formidable the great pirate Emperor is!
Making their way through
the dangerous night-time forest,
The unimaginable horror of Emperor Big Mom drives Sanji into a corner!
Gang Bege, one of the rookies,
holds the key to the disappearance of Sanji!
Luffy and the rest head for the Whale Forest.
in trouble face another crisis!
Along the way, Brook sings his new song soulfully!
When the Twirly Hat Crew fall
Big Mom forced Sanji to make an ultimate choice
on that fateful day,
Pekoms, burning with anger at
seeing his hometown destroyed
To save his captive friends from Bege
into an impossible-to-escape situation
and Bege who devotes himself solely
towards fulfilling his duty!
and to settle things from the past,
due to Gang Bege's formidable
Castle-Castle Fruit power,
but when the terrible details are revealed,
the angry Luffy makes a new decision to take back Sanji!
Surrounded by steam and a singing voice,
It's an explosive situation!
Sanji gets a surprising
letter from Emperor Big Mom!
Sanji takes determined action all by himself!
An intense face-off against
the Big Mom Pirates begins!
the King of the Night - Cat Viper finally
shows up in front of Luffy and the others!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To My Buds! Sanji's Farewell Note!"
"Luffy's Decision! Sanji on the Brink of Quitting!"
"The Delinquent Comes Home!
Emperor Big Mom's Assassins!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Let's Go and Meet Master Cat Viper!"
"The Truth Behind the Disappearance!
Sanji Gets a Startling Invitation!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!