I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests,
a zou (elephant) that has been alive
for a millennium.
The group visited Dogstorm,
King of the Day of
the Mokomo Dukedom, at his sanatorium.
There they listened to all the details of
the battle between the Minks and...
...the Beast Pirates led by Jack,
Emperor Kaido's subordinate,
that happened a half month ago.
On the fifth day of the battle,
Jack finally brought out a poison-gas weapon.
The gas quickly filled the country
making the Minks fall one after another.
What's going on here?!
Anyway, let's go back to the forest for now!
We'll be killed by the gas!
"The Time Limit Closes in!
The Bond Between the Mink Tribe and the Crew!"
It was a terrible sight.
We wanted to do something right away,
but the gas was still there
and it could've put our lives in jeopardy too.
That's why we left the city temporarily.
I see.
ZOU, 10 DAYS AGO
Boy! I can't believe it!
The whole country has been
ravaged by the poison gas!
Chopper, can't we do anything?
Considering the smell of the gas,
it definitely has a nerve
agent as an ingredient.
There are other odors that I don't recognize.
I got the chills seeing its power!
What's so funny?!
The name of the gas is Koro!
It's a weapon of mass
destruction that I invented!
What did you just say?
I said that gas was made by me...
What?! Why should I take the blame?!
I'm not the one who used it!
This guy is the worst.
If you hadn't made it,
no one would've fallen victim to it!
I'm sure you can neutralize
it with your ability!
Do it now!
Then, make an antidote!
It's not too late yet!
The gas works quite slowly, doesn't it?!
I made it that way on purpose
by my own calculations.
How long will it take for them to die
after exposure?!
48 hours, maybe?
48 hours?!
Considering how much it cleared away,
more than a day has passed already!
Not again!
Hey! Don't think the
underdogs are always good!
What?
The Mink Tribe is known for disliking humans
and their great fighting strength!
Leave them alone for your own good!
They'll bite us to death
as soon as we save them!
Bite us to death?
That gas guy's annoying!
And he's fascinated by its success.
The way the gas works really
reflects his character.
Taking two days to kill people little
by little sounds really awful!
What happened then?
Well...
We should've waited on the ship quietly!
You're pretty stupid to be
rushing ahead like this!
Shut up and do what he says!
Are you gonna do it?!
Or do you just want your
heart to be crushed?!
Fine! But I won't forget this!
It was the right call to come ashore!
We can still save them! We need your help!
In that case, why don't you
treat me more nicely...
Did you say something?!
Stop taunting me with that!
Hurry up, Caesar!
If they die because of you,
I'll make you pay for it!
We need your help!
What?
--What the...?
--What's going on?
I'm losing my power...
It's salty! It's seawater!
Chopper!
Sanji, thank you.
Couldn't you save me a little more gently?!
Stop complaining after I saved you!
That's Nami-san's voice!
Okay, Caesar?!
Get the poison gas you created
out of the city before I come back!
What?!
Otherwise,
I'll crush your heart here in my fist and...
Alright! You devil!
Sanji, leave him in my hands.
Yeah, thanks!
There she is!
Brook!
--Keep stalling him like that!
--What?!
Diable! Mouton...
...Mallet!
Sheepshead-sama!
Guys! Retreat!
Sheepshead-sama has been taken down!
What?!
But we haven't found the samurai yet!
Although we cornered them this far,
he didn't show himself!
The samurai's not here! Tell him so!
Yes, ma'am!
Do it! Neutralize the gas!
How annoying. All right.
I'll do it! Are you happy now?!
Koro-neutralizing gas!
This is so against my will!
Roko!
Okay, it's good!
Hey! Guys!
Get over here now!
That's Chopperemon!
From the forest down below!
Let's go now! There's no time to lose!
Th-This is awful!
Were they all killed by Caesar's weapon?!
Yeah. Most of the people have been wiped out.
It must've been done by
those fools from earlier.
You mean those people who just attacked us?
Seems like Caesar neutralized
the gas successfully
but they've done so much damage.
So there is a chance
that a lot of them are
still hiding somewhere on the island.
Are you sure?!
There is a chance, I said.
According to the gas idiot,
the Mink Tribe is a savage race.
We might end up regretting that we saved them
but...
Are you-teia guys Jack's allies too?!
Nami-san!
Onami!
Wait! It's okay!
She's weaken by the poison!
Nami-san! She has an explosive!
What?!
I'll never forgive you-teia people! Never!
What did we do to you?!
What do you gain from killing us?!
The person you-teia are looking
for isn't here!
This country has a millennium-long history!
How much do you have to destroy
to get your fill?!
Wanda-san!
Those-teia people saved me!
Tristan!
All of Jack's subordinates have just
left the island!
What? Left?
Did they-teia?
Pedro!
Wanda. They-gara have
nothing to do with Jack.
The poison gas has just cleared away
from the city...
...because of their-gara magic.
Come to think of it, the gas is gone.
You-teia people...
Who are you?
What are you guys doing?!
Chopper!
More than a day has passed
since the gas was released!
To counteract this gas, we
have to give the poisoned ones
the antidote within 48 hours
or it'll be too late for them!
What's that?
I'm gonna make the antidote now!
What?
To save everybody in the country,
we can't even waste a second!
Where is there a hospital?!
I need more instruments and medicine!
Bring everybody who can help here!
I'm a doctor! Do as I say!
I'm a nurse! Let me help you!
Okay! Thanks!
Are you going to... save us?
I thought we were going to die... All of us!
We won't give up on anybody!
You need to help us.
Tsk. All right.
It was a race against time from there.
Are you telling me to make it with these?!
Yes, make the antidote!
--Where are the doctors?
--They're taking shelter in the fortress.
Fortress?
Most of the citizens are taking shelter
at the Rightflank Fortress in the forest.
Bring everyone here now!
I need their help with
carrying the injured to the open space here!
Tristan, I'm alright.
The gas is flowing into the forest too.
We need everyone's help!
Okay! I'll go and get them!
It won't take long!
When the antidote is made,
we'll administer it to everyone!
Okay!
Let's do it.
We'll start treating those we can!
Yeah, thanks! Now, let's do it!
This way! Hurry up!
Wh-What the...
Th-This is... awful...
Done!
Hey! The antidote will be ready soon!
Please! We need your help!
Will this work?!
I made that! Of course, it'll work!
Okay, we need enough for
all the fallen people!
Make more!
For all of them?!
Okay! You're alright now.
It'll take effect soon.
Thank you.
Don't worry. They are okay!
There! You're okay now!
Yes!
Let me help you too!
Is it okay for you to move now?
You should rest more.
No, I'm much better.
And this is our country!
You have to pull yourself together!
Okay, everybody!
I made something for you!
Eat up! It'll give you strength!
It's damn good, isn't it?
Yeah, thank you.
It's warming up my entire body.
Do you want some more?
No, I had enough.
Let everyone else have more.
Well, I can keep making more!
Eat as much as you can!
Alright, everybody!
I'll play you some soothing music.
You didn't even know who we were!
But you saved us without giving up.
We'll never forget what you did for us!
We'll pay our debt to you someday!
No, no! You don't have to do that!
You guys did such a nice thing!
I'm so proud of you!
I can't believe it was that serious...
Now I understand why
we were so welcomed.
Anyway, that Jack guy makes me mad!
I'll kick his butt as
well as Kaido's someday!
But he said there was an obituary...
Oh yeah!
Damn! I can't kick his butt!
Well, it's hard to believe
if you had seen him with your own eyes.
Do you think he's alive?
I don't know.
Guys, will you stay here and talk?
Are you gonna go somewhere, Chopper?
It's night now so I'll go examine
Cat Viper, the King of the Night,
and the Guardians of the Whale Forest!
Oh, I'll take you there with my Warney.
Come to think of it, Wanda,
isn't it time for you to sleep too?
I work as a Kingsbird.
A Kingsbird?
Yes - an aide to the kings
and the only office that is
allowed to go back and forth between them
regardless of whether it's day or night.
Wow, that's an important job!
I have to tell him
that Duke Dogstorm is okay.
He'd probably say it's unnecessary.
Okay! See you guys!
I'll come with you!
I wanna see Cat Viper!
Master Cat Viper! I like him so much!
I'll come with you!
We'll come too!
I'm curious about this King of the Night!
Chopper said he's heavily injured...
Well, he has amazing recuperative powers.
And he's big like Dogstorm!
Is it really okay for us to come?
Yes, you're welcome.
I'm sure Master Cat Viper will be happy
to see our saviors.
Well, if you're sure it's all right...
Okay! Let's go see Master Cat Viper!
Sanji and the rest who
saved the Minks that were
in trouble face another crisis!
Pekoms, burning with anger at
seeing his hometown destroyed
and Bege who devotes himself solely
towards fulfilling his duty!
It's an explosive situation!
An intense face-off against
the Big Mom Pirates begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Delinquent Comes Home!
Emperor Big Mom's Assassins!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!