I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests,
a zou (elephant) that has been alive for a millennium.
They met the Mink Tribe who live there
and later, reunited with Nami and the rest.
The group visited Dogstorm, King of the Day of
the Mokomo Dukedom, at his sanatorium.
There they listened to all the details of
the battle between the Minks and...
...the Beast Pirates led by Jack,
Emperor Kaido's subordinate,
that happened a half month ago.
Sanji and the rest arrived at Zou
the very next day after Jack left.
They found the Mink Tribe poisoned by gas
and took action to save their lives.
Roko!
Pedro!
Wanda.
They-gara have nothing to do with Jack.
The poison gas has just cleared away
from the city...
...because of their-gara magic.
It's night now so I'll go examine
Cat Viper, the King of the Night,
and the Guardians of the Whale Forest!
Okay! Let's go see Master Cat Viper!
"The Delinquent Comes Home!
Emperor Big Mom's Assassins!"
It's a full moon tonight
but I'm glad that it's covered by the clouds.
--Be careful!
--Okay!
Thank you, Carrot, for giving us a ride.
That's okay. I'm a Kingsbird too.
Anyway, Wanda, so far in your story...
Yeah, both Twirly Eyebrows
and Gassy hadn't left yet.
Well...
Let me tell you what happened to them.
The thing is we didn't tell that many
people in this country about this.
We didn't want to make the people
who had their country ruined worry more.
This was a big event that happened
secretly just two days ago.
Please be prepared
for what you're going to hear.
Sanji-san might not...
...come back to us.
What?!
Whoa-whoa.
Why, Brook?!
It says "I'll be back" in his note!
I told you it's actually more complicated!
He will be back! I believe in Sanji!
It was a mistake to show them this first.
Without that annoying crappy cook,
I feel better so I don't mind at all.
No! Sanji is our friend!
Okay, okay, please relax, Luffy-san.
I'll tell you what happened
from the beginning.
Uh-huh!
This island of Zou that we're on
is the Phantom Island.
Because the island itself is a living thing,
you can't get here even with a Log Pose
or find it in a normal way but...
...we made a blunder and had a blind spot.
First, at that time...
You go ahead and sail for Zou!
...we allowed the enemy ship that we'd
shaken off to know our destination.
Second, someone from the Phantom
Island was on their ship.
So the ones who showed up in front of us
two days ago were...
...Emperor Big Mom's pirate group!
Clank.
We arrived.
Yeah, no problem. Count on us, Mama.
The two of us can finish this.
Zou is where I came from! Grr!
What?
Y-You've got to be kidding...
What the hell... Hey!
Where is everybody?!
So this is the Phantom Island, Zou.
What happened?! Grr!
Who did this to Zou?!
Hey! Anybody?! Is anybody here?!
Everybody! Where did you go?!
Did the Straw Hats do this?!
What did they do to my home?!
Okay, it's ready.
Take it.
Looks delicious!
I made you two your own batch.
Really?! Yes!
Now...
Let's go greet everyone!
Garchu!
Sanji's cooking is really good!
Its nutritional balance is perfect
so make sure to eat it all.
--Can I have more?!
--I want more!
All right. Now let me see your arm.
Okay.
Dr. Chopper made this injectable drug.
You'll get better soon.
Thanks.
Tongue, tongue, bleah!
But I don't have a tongue!
Okay, it's done! Good boy!
Thank you, Dr. Chopper!
Alright. My next patient is...!
Dr. Miyagi! You're hopping too much!
This is a residential quarter
where our ancestors used to live.
Zunesha has carried the whole history of
the Mink Tribe without change.
One of the Mink Tribe's tradition
that goes far back in that history is...
...exchanging clothes with foreigners,
as a sign of friendship!
Oh, this is beautiful!
It's like a dress for somebody great.
Yes. And that accessory
is a national treasure.
What?! Are you giving it to me?!
Of course. Everyone agreed we should.
Garchu! Garchu-chu!
Mademoiselle, garchu.
Garchu.
How are you?! Garchu.
Tristan-chan!
Garchu!
Sanji-san, you like to greet everyone.
What is "garchu"?
Is it a miraculous magic word or something?
Sanji! It's from us to you,
our great savior; Garchu!
Shut up! I don't want it from guys!
Oh, Sanji-san. Garchu!
Garchu! Garchu!
That's not fair.
The Lesser Minks are only nice to girls.
Oh, boy! Viva minkship!
Is that a goddess?!
No...
Nami-san!
Garchu!
Where is Momo?
He's still locked in his room.
He feels more comfortable that way.
Plus, he shouldn't let
them see his human form.
You're right.
We'd better not mention the word "samurai"
while we're in this country.
Just give that annoying brat to the Minks
and let's leave this crappy island already!
Shut up!
Hey, Caesar, did you make the drugs?
I met my quota because I'm a genius.
--Make more! Don't stop!
--There are still so many injured people!
Keep working!
Why should I do such a thing...
Dr. Caesar, I came to pick up the drugs.
Hey, don't make a mistake!
I'm Cedar the pharmacist!
Here.
Damn! Why am I making drugs to save people?!
Thank you, Dr. Caesar!
It's Cedar!
Man! This work disgraces my name,
Caesar the genius mad scientist!
--Oh yeah...
--It's Cedar!
Baron Corpse,
your fans are waiting for you outside.
Erk!
Where's Baron Corpse?!
--Let me garchu!
--Gimmie them bones to chew!
I don't need popularity among dogs...
--Somebody's coming.
--Are they the remnants of the Beast Pirates?
Wait! It's me! Grr!
You-gara are...
Pekoms!
Hey! You're wounded!
What happened to you? Grr!
Well, it's...
--Was it the Straw Hats?!
--What?!
Where are they?!
I'll avenge you against them!
Hey, what are you talkin...
Those bastards! I won't forgive them!
The Straw Hats!
It's inexcusable!
Where're the Straw Hats?!
They'll pay for this! Where are they?!
Tell me!
--W-Wait a minute!
--Calm down, Pekoms!
Shut up! Let go of me!
Wait! All of our friends are okay!
They're in the fortress!
The Straw Hats saved us!
What?!
What did you say?
--Pekoms!
--It's you, Pekoms!
--You're home!
--Pekoms!
So you guys are all okay!
Dad! Mom!
All my relatives and friends!
--Welcome home!
--How long has it been?!
This brings back memories!
Yeah! You're looking good and I'm so happy!
Garchu!
You idiot! You're covered with cuts and bruises!
Don't tell me you're happy!
When I saw the city,
I thought my heart would stop!
--Garchu!
--Hey, you're hurting me!
It's all thanks to the Straw Hats!
If it weren't for their desperate rescue,
I don't know what would've
happened to us by now.
Really, thank you for staying alive!
Whoa-whoa, stop crying.
What's going on?
Those jerks!
Hey, look!
Damn! I can't forgive Jack
of the Beast Pirates!
How dare he do that to my home!
But, at any rate,
I'm glad that you're all okay!
Look! Those guys from the Big Mom Pirates!
They made it this far!
That's Pekoms! He came home.
He used to be an infamous delinquent.
Oh, so he's a Mink.
They must've heard this
is where we were heading!
They want me!
Hey, please!
Don't hand me over to them.
You were our trump card against Doflamingo.
Now that Luffy and the others took him down,
we don't care what happens to you.
Don't say such a thing! We're friends!
When did we become friends?!
You were whining about
something at Dressrosa too.
What did you do to Big Mom?
Oh, that's it! Hear me out!
I got an offer to research something
which I haven't succeeded at yet,
and I lied to her
and ripped her off pretty badly!
I had Doflamingo at my back
so I pushed my luck!
So you asked for it.
I hope all they want is Caesar...
What?!
Monkey D. Luffy.
I know your name now.
Come to the New World!
Sure, wait for me there.
There's some business
I want to settle with you, too.
I can't leave it in your hands -
that's too dangerous!
I'll kick your ass all over the New World...
...and make the Fish-Man Island my territory!
Luffy picked a fight with Big Mom
at the Fish-Man Island.
We broke their ship too.
A life being targeted by an Emperor...
We're better off dead.
Well, I'm already dead though.
What should we do, Sanji-kun?!
Hey, Black-Foot.
Do you wanna work together
with me and take them out?
Think about it!
They're from the Big Mom Pirates
but only the two of them are here!
If it's just them,
you and I can handle them together!
Let's use my poison gas again and...
--Nami-san, stay with the rest here.
--Uh-huh.
--Brook, come with me.
--Okay.
Hey, Black-Foot!
What about my cool idea to assassinate them?!
Shut up you unthinking idiot.
So the members of the Big Mom Pirates
were here in Zou too!
Before that, it was Kaido's Beast Pirates.
They're both Emperors.
Did Sanji get into a fight
with that Peko-something?!
I'm sure he won, didn't he?!
Don't set him up for a fight with an Emperor!
No problem!
I already picked a fight with her!
Sanji-san is truly kind.
He took the two out of the Rightflank
Fortress to a distant forest.
What do you Big Mom Pirates want?
Don't cause trouble.
The people in this country are hurt
inside and out now.
If you need to talk, talk to me first.
If that's not enough,
I'm afraid we gotta take it out of the country.
We're not gonna run or hide.
All I can say is thank you! Grr!
H-Hey...
I didn't expect to see my home country
devastated like this...
But you guys saved the people, didn't you?!
I owe you!
How can I thank you...
By Mama's order, we have business
other than capturing Caesar.
It could spell doom for your pirate group.
Doom?
So let's forget it! The mission is failed!
Just give us Caesar!
I'll just tell Mom
that we let the Straw Hats get away!
Pekoms! Are you losing your mind?!
Put your feelings aside!
Shut up, newbie! I'll take the punishment!
They saved my family members and friends.
I can't do anything to them...
You coward!
Gang Bege, one of the rookies,
holds the key to the disappearance of Sanji!
When the Twirly Hat Crew fall
into an impossible-to-escape situation
due to Gang Bege's formidable
Castle-Castle Fruit power,
Sanji gets a surprising
letter from Emperor Big Mom!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Truth Behind the Disappearance!
Sanji Gets a Startling Invitation!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!