I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests,
a zou (elephant) that has
been alive for a millennium.
They met the Mink Tribe and while heading
towards the Whale Forest
where Master Cat Viper is,
they listen what happened to Sanji.
By Mama's order, we have business
other than capturing Caesar.
It could spell doom for your pirate group.
Doom?
So let's forget it!
The mission is failed!
Just give us Caesar!
I'll just tell Mama
that we let the Straw Hats get away!
Pekoms! Are you losing your mind?!
Put your feelings aside!
Shut up, newbie! I'll take the punishment!
They saved my family members and friends.
I can't do anything to them...
You coward!
You bastard!
"The Truth Behind the Disappearance!
Sanji Gets a Startling Invitation!"
He shot his ally in the back!
How could he do that?!
What did I just see?
He may not look like it
but he's quite a well-known pirate.
However, when he chose to act
on his pathetic feelings,
he turned into such a coward.
There's no longer any use for him.
I'll do it myself!
Alright, guys! Come on out!
Go!
What?!
What?! Humans?!
What the hell?!
Give up! You're outnumbered!
Did the humans come out of his stomach?!
What kind of ability is that?!
I thought I saw humans in his hand
but, that wasn't an illusion!
I ate the Castle-Castle Fruit
and became a castle human.
I'm regarded in the same
generation as your captain,
so you know me, don't you?
Capone "Gang" Bege!
CAPONE "GANG" BEGE
BOUNTY: 300 MILLION BERRIES
THE CAPTAIN OF THE FIRETANK PIRATES
When Luffy punched the
Celestial Dragon at Sabaody,
you were there, weren't you?!
Yeah, we were forced to waste so
much energy because of you guys.
We could've blown you guys up too
in a big show with cannons.
We're not gonna make a scene here.
We don't want that, either.
If the Minks come,
they'll definitely take your side.
I know how well they can fight.
We're not looking for their
help in the first place!
I'll accept anyone's challenge!
Sanji-san!
When it comes to this,
we gotta stop them here!
I agree! Pekoms-san was trying
to settle this peacefully,
but he shot him like that! In the back!
I can't forgive him, either!
I knew that's what you would do.
Vito!
No!
Let go of me!
--Nami-san!
--Chopper-san!
I-I'm sorry!
We couldn't help worrying so...
I'm sorry! I thought there
were only two enemies!
Oh...
Caesar! Why don't you come out, too?!
We'll fire shotguns containing Sea Prism Stone
towards the sky in two seconds!
Two!
One!
Wait a sec! I'm here! Don't shoot!
Don't point them at me!
Tell them to stand down!
Come to think of it, we don't have any bullets
containing Sea Prism Stone.
What?!
But we have a spear that works like that!
I-I feel so weak...
Everyone's here now.
Rather than standing around here talking,
get into my castle.
That's an order!
Damn! He's completely in control.
Hey, what did he mean by his "castle"?
Weren't you listening?!
Bege is a castle human who ate
the Castle-Castle Fruit. Okay?
So you guys got into his body.
--Yes.
--Really?! How?!
By slicing through his stomach, maybe?
Stop it, Robin!
Super disgusting...
That's not it!
An entrance appeared around his chest.
We were in chains
so we had no choice but to obey.
Thank you for waiting.
Would you guys like to eat something?
No thanks.
You don't have to be humble.
Maybe a glass of wine?
We don't want anything!
Get down to business already!
He'll kill us! He'll kill us! He'll kill us!
You should cut yourself some slack sometimes.
We exchanged gunfire at sea
a week ago but the situation
has changed since then.
I was asked to hand you this invitation.
Invitation?
It's an invitation to Mama's tea party.
Cut the crap.
Why would I wanna go to Big Mom's tea party?
The highlight of the party
will be a wedding ceremony.
Screw it.
The groom is the third son
of the Vinsmoke Family,
GROOM - THIRD SON OF THE
VINSMOKE FAMILY - SANJI
Sanji!
What?!
What?!!
The bride is the 35th daughter
of the Charlotte Family,
BRIDE - 35TH DAUGHTER OF THE
CHARLOTTE FAMILY - PUDDING
Pudding.
Marriage?!
TEA PARTY
D-During a tea party...
They'll hold Sanji's wedding?!
GROOM - THIRD SON OF THE
VINSMOKE FAMILY - SANJI
BRIDE - 35TH DAUGHTER OF THE
CHARLOTTE FAMILY - PUDDING
Take it.
TEA PARTY
GROOM - THIRD SON OF THE
VINSMOKE FAMILY - SANJI
Why, after all these years?!
THE VINSMOKE FAMILY
I don't know the deal with your family!
You bastard! Are you trying to set fire to my castle?!
Hey, Sanji-kun, what is this all about?!
Are you gonna get married?!
Who made the decision without asking?!
Your family, of course!
Being a son of the Vinsmoke Family means...
...you're quite ill-bred.
V-V-Vinsmoke is Sanji-san's surname?!
The name gives me chills down my spine.
But no, that's not possible.
--Hey, bring me a glass of wine!
--Yes, sir!
Sanji-kun's family... Oh!
Remember when we found the
picture book called "Noland the Liar" at Mont Blanc's place!
NOLAND THE LIAR
A picture book...
It's titled "Noland the Liar"...
That's a cool title! Nice idea for a book!
"Noland the Liar"?
You know it, Sanji-kun?
But it says it was published in the North Blue.
Yeah. I was born in the North Blue.
Haven't I told you guys?
That's news. I thought you were from the East, too.
I grew up there. Well, who cares.
I remember feeling strange at that time.
We met him in the East Blue
but he said he was born in the North Blue.
What?! Are you sure, Nami-san?!
If that's true, it's a big deal!
The sea of the world is divided by the Red Line,
the massive red soil continent which is taller than the clouds.
The Grand Line, the sea route that goes round the world...
...which is perpendicular to the Red Line,
dividing it into four.
The seas that are divided into
the north, south, east and west are called;
East Blue, West Blue,
South Blue and North Blue.
In order to move to the East Blue from the North Blue,
you have to surmount the Red Line!
--That's right!
--Is it difficult?
Yes, it's not just one family moving to another place!
It's a great voyage!
Sanji-san, what kind of
childhood did he have?
And, you know,
Charlotte is Big Mom's surname!
What?!
That fool! Is he gonna marry Big Mom's daughter?!
Will he join an Emperor's family?!
If your fellow crewmember becomes her son-in-law,
you guys will practically be her subordinates!
What?!
Don't jump to conclusions!
I'm under no obligation to
go to such a tea party!
How ridiculous!
My wedding ceremony?
Marrying a woman I don't even know?!
You've got to be kidding me!
I don't want the Straw Hats
to become your subordinates either!
Our captain isn't the type of guy
who works under someone!
Luffy will...
...become the King of the Pirates!
That's some big talk.
Are we done here? You can have Caesar.
What?!
Let us go!
Screw you!
I think you have the wrong idea.
The invitation was only for you to see.
I wasn't looking for your answer.
You're in my body!
You guys have already been captured!
I'll take you all to Mama!
What?!
I'm sure you don't feel any motion
but I'm already on the move.
Is it really moving?!
She'll kill me! Let me out!
You...
If you wanna fight, I'll fight you.
What the...!
Sanji-kun!
I have full command
over the interior of the castle!
Everything is under my control!
--Help!
--Oh! Nami's sinking!
Nami-san!
Nami!
--I won't forgive you!
--Bring her back up already!
Stop!
No!
I said "Stop"!
Are you alright?
--Uh-huh.
--What a relief!
Even if I don't rough you up,
you won't get away from Mama's tea party.
That's common knowledge
throughout the New World.
That's right. Mama hates bitter sweets
and empty seats at tea parties-rero.
When someone refuses her
because he's ignorant-rero,
he'll cry in regret later and I
can't bear to see that-rorero!
"PHANTOM GUN" VITO
AN ADVISOR OF THE FIRETANK PIRATES
When you get an invitation to a tea party from Big Mom-rero,
that's basically an undeclinable summons!
Even the devil himself comes from hell
to attend Mama's tea party, they say!
Of course, you have a choice not to go-rorero.
But if you refuse...
Listen to me-rorero.
Vito. Relax.
How did you find that out?
That's a silly question.
The unimaginable horror of Emperor Big Mom drives Sanji into a corner!
To save his captive friends from Bege
and to settle things from the past,
Sanji takes determined action all by himself!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To My Buds! Sanji's Farewell Note!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!