I've never seen the end of the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go, Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible? Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani? mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests,
a zou (elephant) that has been alive for a millennium.
They met the Mink Tribe who live there.
There they listened to all the details of
the battle between the Minks and...
...the Beast Pirates led by Jack, Emperor Kaido's subordinate,
that happened a half month ago.
And while heading towards
the Whale Forest to meet Master Cat Viper,
they hear what happened to Sanji two days ago.
The groom is the third son of the Vinsmoke Family,
GROOM - THIRD SON OF THE VINSMOKE FAMILY - SANJI
Sanji!
The bride is the 35th daughter of the Charlotte Family, Pudding.
BRIDE - 35TH DAUGHTER OF THE CHARLOTTE FAMILY - PUDDING
Even if I don't rough you up,
you won't get away from Mama's tea party.
That's common knowledge
throughout the New World.
That's right. Mama hates bitter sweets
and empty seats at tea parties-rero.
When you get an invitation to a tea party
from Big Mom-rero,
that's basically an undeclinable summons!
Even the devil himself comes from hell
to attend Mama's tea party, they say!
Of course, you have a choice not to go-rorero.
But if you refuse...
Listen to me-rorero.
"To My Buds!
Sanji's Farewell Note!"
How did you find that out?
That's a silly question.
Who do you think our master is?
The Four Emperors are the most powerful pirates there are,
reigning supreme over the New World,
one of them being Big Mom herself.
She has countless islands under her control
and the power that she possesses is
beyond your wildest imagination.
Nothing is impossible for her.
She has it all.
If she tells someone she'll kill him,
he'll die.
She doesn't bluff.
Stake your life on every word you say.
If you wish to stay alive
without becoming anybody's subordinate,
do as she says, at least for now.
Sanji-san! Are you okay?
What did he say to you earlier?
What's the matter, Sanji?!
We'll fight even against an Emperor!
Be quiet!
Give me some paper and a pen.
--Bring them to him.
--Yes, sir.
Are you gonna leave a note for Straw Hat?
Hand this to Luffy and everybody.
Sanji-kun...
Nami-san.
Chopper.
Brook.
Believe this if nothing else.
I didn't mean to hide anything from my friends.
Vinsmoke.
That's something from the past
that I thought I'd never have to deal with again.
I really need to go and sort things out!
Wait a minute, Sanji-san.
Do you mean "by yourself"?
I feel a powerful presence outside.
It's probably one of the Minks.
Are you ready?
Ready for what?
Good luck!
Black-Foot!
What about me?!
--That fool!
--He freed his allies!
That bastard!
Chase them!
Hold him down!
Damn! You little jerk!
Wait-rero! You can't shoot him!
Don't move, you bastards!
Why...?
Okay, listen carefully!
This genius scientist is important to you
and I bet you don't want me to blow his brains out!
I'll get even with you, Black-Foot!
I thought so.
You fools can't kill me either, can you?!
Hearing about this marriage
solves a mystery for me.
My wanted poster says "Only alive"!
You gotta catch me alive!
If you kill me, you'd piss somebody off,
wouldn't you?!
Have you been told to treat me civilly
without even cuffs?!
The person who made them
write that phrase on the poster
and the one who arranged my marriage
must be the same person!
Damn! Let's get out and chase them!
I said "Don't move"!
Please don't move!
You know someone's got my back now, don't you?!
Don't worry! I'll come with you.
To sort things out with that person!
So don't do anything to my friends!
All of you, stay where you are!
--What?!
--Father!
There is a... monster... outside now!
Master Cat Viper...
You're up!
Is that a cat monster?!
I didn't know there was such a terrible thing here!
Hey!
You-gara, who are you?
I saw Pekoms lying down back there bleeding.
Did you-gara do that?
No, you got it wrong! I'm his crewmate!
Crewmate?
Yes, we belong to the same pirate group!
We've actually been attacked by
the remnants of Jack's crew!
That's not true!
Don't be fooled! He shot Pekoms!
Why would I shoot my ally?!
Sanji-kun, come on out!
Why do you wanna stay?!
Tell us what's really going on, Sanji!
What do you mean you need to go?!
Why can't we all go together?!
Let's wait for Luffy-san and everybody,
Sanji-san!
S-Stay away!
Come on out already!
This is my problem.
I'll be back.
Tell them "Hi" for me.
Castle Tank!
Sanji!
Sanji-kun!
Nami! Chopper! Should I just chase him?!
No, it's no use, Wanda-san!
Baron Corpse!
Even if we can catch up to him,
he has...
...no intentions of coming back now!
"To my buds,"
"I've gotta go see a woman.
I'll be back."
TO MY BUDS, I'VE GOTTA GO SEE A WOMAN. I'LL BE BACK.
SANJI
Nami. I don't see Sanji or Cedar.
Don't tell me they were taken away...
No, he went willingly.
What?
What do you mean?
Wanda! Carrot!
They-gara want you to forget about it.
You must understand.
We'll take care of Pekoms too.
Don't give the daytime people
unnecessary anxiety.
Yes, I understand, sire.
I apologize.
I'm sorry.
No, please.
I'm sorry for making you feel that way after you saved us.
Thank you, Master.
You-gara guys show concern for
our broken-hearted citizens.
We should thank you.
There's silver vine!
Then, "gotta go see a woman" means...
...he's gonna get married?
That's not necessarily the case but...
...it seemed like he was determined.
--Oh, maybe he'll return with his wife.
--What?!
In that case, we'll get a new member!
You're so optimistic.
Luffy-san.
The bride is the Emperor's daughter.
That means
we'll become Big Mom's subordinates.
What?!
No!
Of course, Sanji-san doesn't want that either.
He refused it firmly right there.
But that troubles me.
Considering who he is dealing with this time,
if he couldn't avoid the marriage,
what do you think he would do?
Well, he would...
Yeah, he's the kind of guy
who'll try not to cause us any trouble
so he'd try to separate himself from us!
You mean Sanji will quit this group?!
That's even more unacceptable!
When he tossed us out,
he could've gotten away too.
When he wrote the note,
I think he'd already made up his mind to go by himself.
Now we know everything.
You've been through a lot.
Big Mom's daughter, huh?
He got a pretty troublesome offer of marriage.
And did you say Vinsmoke?
I guess that family is the key.
It could be Sanji's father or mother or brother...
They once lived in the North Blue and then moved
to the East Blue and now,
they're in the New World.
Unbelievable!
Vinsmoke...
--Do you know of them?
--I think I've heard of them before...
I'm sorry. I can't remember.
We're sorry.
I wish we could've stopped him
at least until you guys arrived...
Sanji wouldn't let you stop him.
It's not your fault, guys.
But, Robin,
what if we never get to see him again?!
Nothing wrong with that.
Huh?! What are you saying, Zoro?!
I mean, if he was leaving for good,
he should've said
"Thank you for everything."
And "I'm sorry for causing so much trouble."
No, that's not the point!
That is the point.
Think about it.
We're on an unstoppable train now.
Remember what Caesar said?
The biggest customer of SMILEs,
the artificial Devil Fruits, is Kaido.
We pissed Doflamingo off
by destroying the lab on Punk Hazard,
we destroyed the SMILE factory in Dressrosa,
and the man who's gonna go nuts next is...
...Emperor Kaido!
He's not some distant threat anymore.
We've already had a fight with his subordinates,
the Beast Pirates.
Jack who ruined this country, and others will
come after us in a matter of time!
We're allying with Tra-guy
for upcoming battles.
I don't know why but it seems like
Kin'emon and the others are targeted by Kaido too.
We'll face Emperor Kaido very soon!
How stupid can he be to get involved with
another Emperor, Big Mom, now?!
That twirly-eyebrowed fool!
Don't say it like that!
You boorish son of a gun!
Those things are unrelated!
N-Nami-san...
First of all, how could he get wrapped up in
such a thing as marriage?! It's such a small deal!
What did you say?!
Both of you! Don't get so heated up!
It is a big deal!
You can't say someone else's problem is big or small!
What?!
All right!
We don't know what's on his mind
so let's go ask him!
What?!
Hey! Forget it, Luffy!
Don't tell me we're gonna head for Big Mom!
We have no choice.
Did you forget that you picked a fight with her?!
Without a strategy or reinforcements,
we'll just get beaten and that'll be it!
She's an Emperor.
Luffy! Don't forget.
She's on a totally different level than any of our past enemies.
Then, we'll go quietly.
How do we find them?!
Well, there is a way to go after them but...
He's right.
Sanji-san has gone because of the Big Mom Pirates
but they left something big behind instead.
If that person is awake now,
there should be something he can tell us.
That person?
Let's just keep going.
Making their way through
the dangerous night-time forest,
Luffy and the rest head for the Whale Forest.
Along the way, Brook sings his new song soulfully!
Surrounded by steam and a singing voice,
the King of the Night - Cat Viper finally
shows up in front of Luffy and the others!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Let's Go and Meet Master Cat Viper!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!