I've never seen the end of the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go, Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible? Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani? mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests,
a zou (elephant) that has been alive for a millennium.
Luffy met the Mink Tribe who live there.
But Sanji went off on his own.
Don't move, you bastards!
You fools can't kill me either, can you?!
Hearing about this marriage
solves a mystery for me.
My wanted poster says "Only alive"!
You gotta catch me alive!
If you kill me, you'd piss somebody off,
wouldn't you?!
Have you been told to treat me civilly
without even cuffs?!
The person who made them write
that phrase on the poster
and the one who arranged my marriage
must be the same person!
Don't worry! I'll come with you.
To sort things out with that person!
So don't do anything to my friends!
All right!
We don't know what's on his mind
so let's go ask him!
What?!
Hey! Forget it, Luffy!
Don't tell me we're gonna head for Big Mom!
We have no choice.
Did you forget that you picked a fight with her?!
She's an Emperor.
Luffy! Don't forget.
She's on a totally different level than any of our past enemies.
Then, we'll go quietly.
How do we find them?!
Well, there is a way to go after them but...
He's right.
Sanji-san has gone because of the Big Mom Pirates
but they left something big behind instead.
If that person is awake now,
there should be something he can tell us.
That person?
"Let's Go and Meet Master Cat Viper!"
That person,
Pekoms-san feels indebted to us
because we saved his people, the Minks.
That's why he tried to go
against Big Mom's order
and let us get away.
But that only brought tragedy upon him.
But now,
to find out where Sanji-san has gone,
the only thing we can do is ask him
since he is a member of the Big Mom Pirates.
Okay!
I'll get Sanji's whereabouts out of Lion Viper!
We won't get any answers unless
we talk to Sanji himself!
Chopper.
This guy, Pekoms,
will he be well enough to talk?
I hope he's come around.
That's quite a lot.
Carrot!
Okay!
What is that?!
A swarm of bugs?!
--Those are Sutchies.
--Sutchies?!
Giant insects that suck blood!
You-teia Lesser Minks have less hair
so they can suck all your blood and kill you in an instant!
--Really?!
--Look up! Look!
We'll be drained dry!
Special Attack: Exploding Star!
Sutchies are vicious.
They even suck Zunesha's blood and weaken it.
What?!
Can they even weaken the elephant?!
That's why, in this country,
we exterminate all we find.
Stop, Carrot! Luffy and the others' Warney
has been brought down!
Get up, Warney!
They'll get you if you keep still!
Gust Sword!
I'll attract the bugs!
Franky...
...Nipple Light!
How does that even work?!
Oh, your-teia light is drawing the Sutchies!
What? Is it working?
I'm gonna exterminate the Sutchies!
I'll back you up!
I have no blood to be sucked!
You idiot!
They're weak but don't lower your guard!
Okay! If I do this,
they can't sting or get away!
Here! Come to me!
I'm gonna fight too! Kung Fu Point!
Special Attack: Green Star - Skull-Blast Glass!
It brings the Chill of the Dead!
Soul Solid!
Cien Fleurs!
Three-Sword Style Dragon Twister!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Seems like we got rid of them!
Ouch!
Thanks to you all, we cleared the Sutchies.
You-teia guys have been helping us a lot.
Don't mention it.
Thank you.
Anyway, Cat Viper's place, are we there yet?
Just a bit more.
We'll get to the Guardians' Dwelling soon so...
--Master Cat Viper, huh?
--I wonder what kind of person he is.
He is heavily injured.
I hope he is resting in bed quietly.
Master Cat Viper.
He's a wonderful person!
I like him so much so I wrote a song about him.
Let's go and meet Master Cat Viper
Is that it?
You were just repeating the same phrase
over and over.
Yes, because this song is called
"Let's Go and Meet Master Cat Viper."
--No kidding!
--Is it just repeating the same line throughout the song?
No, it'll get a little more complex from here.
Cat Viper, Cat Viper
Cat Viper, let's go and meet the Master
Master Cat Viper gets lonely easily
When I think of him like that
it makes my heart twinge
When he is bathed in the moonlight
his face looks innocent
He gazes up at it with his sparkling eyes
But he tries to act tough under the sun
He does his best and lives his life on his own
I like that song.
Is Master Cat Viper really like that?
Not at all.
He's not?!
It's just a song inspired by him.
Memorize it.
Okay, we're here.
It's the Guardians' Dwelling.
This place has been totally wrecked.
THE GUARDIANS' DWELLING, THE WHALE FOREST
The Whale Tree...
...looks even bigger up close!
Hey, guys!
It's the Straw Hats!
Chopper is here!
Garchu!
--The Minks are recovering fast, aren't they?
--You're right.
Straw Hat Luffy! It's us!
Sorry for what we did in the forest.
Doesn't matter who it is,
we can't let any invader get by!
Oh, it's you guys!
Well, never mind!
Um, where's Cat Viper?
I'm glad to see you!
Our saviors and their friends!
Let me say it once again.
Thank you!
Who is this?!
TREETOP PEDRO (A JAGUAR MINK)
CAPTAIN, THE GUARDIANS OF THE WHALE FOREST
Sorry for my subordinates' action in the forest.
They were too wary of invaders.
Were you there?
Yes, I was up in a tree.
Bepo and the others are waiting for you-gara guys
back there.
We can see them later.
We wanna see Cat Viper
and Lion Viper the lion first.
Garchu!
If you're talking about Pekoms, he's up now.
He's in the building at the back.
We kept the whole incident secret
from everybody.
Sanji is a nice guy.
I hope we can help you in some way.
Luffy! I'm worried about Cat Viper -
not just about his condition though, so I'll go see him first!
Okay!
Then, let me lead the way, Dr. Chopper.
Hey, Chopper! Why are you frozen?
I-I-I'm not frozen.
You're acting strange.
It's this way.
O-Okay!
Master Cat Viper is taking a bath now.
A bath?!
SAKE
PROTECT
Lasagna-meow!
It's good-meow! Yeah!
Hey, Cat Viper!
You shouldn't take a bath!
Your wound's gonna reopen!
And you should eat light meals!
Why are you using your left hand?!
Are you listening to me?!
Oh, Chopper!
No problem. No problem.
I'm a freedom-loving man!
You have to listen to your doctor!
He's larger than I expected.
I'm sorry but even if it's a doctor's instruction...
Oops.
I don't care!
I still can't get used to not having a left hand!
I can't even clap my hands like this!
So you-gara people are the Straw Hats!
You saved me!
Thank you!
I'll repay my debt to you someday!
I may not look it but
I have a strong sense of obligation and compassion!
Oh, a ball.
Yeah! A ball!
I told you to rest!
See! The wound reopened!
Listen, I...
I got into bed because I wanted to.
Uh-huh, uh-huh, okay.
Whatever the case, just stay still!
I'm gonna give you a shot.
Hey, you-gara!
Show me that foxtail right there.
Like this?
Chopper!
Hurry up while I'm distracted and enjoying myself!
I said "Stay still"!
Are you afraid of shots?!
Even looking like that?!
It's completely cured now.
There's no wonder drug like that
so keep quiet!
Don't hit an injured person.
Boy, he's so funny!
I love him!
I can't believe you survived!
I blocked about half of the attack
with my ability! Grr!
Bege, that bastard!
I'm sorry.
They must've taken Black-Foot with them.
He can't get away from the wedding now!
Yeah, about that, Lion Viper,
who arranged the marriage?
Well, of course, our Mama and
the father of the Vinsmoke Family!
Sanji-kun's father?!
What kind of person is he?!
He's quite infamous in the underworld.
Have you ever heard the name, Germa 66?
Also known as the Warmongers.
What are you talking about?!
That's a mythical evil army!
How ridiculous!
No, it's an actual organization.
The Vinsmoke Family is at the top of it!
And their boss is Black-Foot's father!
Believe this if nothing else.
I didn't mean to hide anything from my friends.
The Vinsmoke Family is, well, to put it simply,
a family of assassins!
Pekoms tells
how formidable the great pirate Emperor is!
Big Mom forced Sanji to make an ultimate choice
on that fateful day,
but when the terrible details are revealed,
the angry Luffy makes a new decision to take back Sanji!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy's Decision! Sanji on the Brink of Quitting!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!