in all these centuries!
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
That red stone is called a Road Ponegliff!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new adventure will take place.
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
There are four of those red stones
- the Road Ponegliffs in the world!
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests, a zou (elephant)
that has been alive for a millennium.
as its name suggests,
a zou (elephant) that has been
That stone must indicate the location of
some unknown spot but it's not Raftel.
alive for a millennium.
They met the Mink Tribe who live there
Oh no-saru! Samurai are here-saru!
The group listened to all the details of the battle
between the Minks and...
and listened to all the
details of the battle between
They met the Mink Tribe who live there
I gotta let them know as soon as possible!
The other three Road Ponegliffs all indicate
different locations in the same manner.
...the Beast Pirates led
by Jack, Emperor Kaido's
and listened to all the details of the battle
between the Minks and
the Minks and
the Beast Pirates led by Jack, Emperor Kaido's subordinate,
Samurai are here-saru!
subordinate, that happened a half month ago.
the Beast Pirates led by Jack,
that happened a half month ago,
When you learn where those locations are
and connect those four points on a map,
and they also learned Sanji
was taken to a wedding
Then, they learned Sanji was taken by
them two days ago, to a tea party...
Emperor Kaido's subordinate,
that happened a half month ago.
"A Volatile Situation!
The Dog and the Cat and the Samurai!"
of himself and Emperor Big Mom's daughter.
They also learned Sanji was taken to
those lines will cross at the center!
...where his wedding with Emperor
Big Mom's daughter will take place.
Then...
a wedding of himself and
Emperor Big Mom's daughter.
Stop fighting!
This is my problem.
That's where the last island is.
Hey, you idiot! What are you doing?!
Only the King of the Pirates
and his crew have reached it
People from the country of Zou!
No! I fell asleep!
I'll be back.
I'm a retainer of the Kozuki Clan from
the Land of Wano, named Kin'emon!
Is that...
Hey, both of you, wake up!
That's Raizo's voice.
Tell them "Hi" for me.
What?! The ninja?!
Wake up!
Ninja!
The Vinsmoke Family is,
well, to put it simply,
I'm here to look for my comrade named Raizo
who is a warrior from the same country!
And that's Raftel!
We have a problem!
Kin'emon and Kanjuro must've arrived already!
What?!
Has he been here?!
The last island - Raftel!
a family of assassins!
Well, this country was destroyed
because he wasn't here!
Is it morning already?!
--Ya-hoo! Where's the ninja?!
--Ninja! Ninja!
--Look.
--That drawing is...
Raizo-dono is...
"Luffy's Decision!
Sanji on the Brink of Quitting!"
Here we are.
He-gara is the ninja, Raizo.
Ryunosuke.
...safe!
"The Secret of the Land of Wano!
The Kozuki Family and the Ponegliffs!"
No! The one next to it!
Y-Y-Y...
It's a new drawing by Kanjuro!
You all almost died!
There you are, Cat Viper!
Sanji-kun is from a family of assassins?!
--When did it appear?!
--While we were sleeping!
Raftel...
You! Why didn't you just
hand me over to them?!
What kind of a pathetic animal is this?
The Land of Wano's Kozuki Clan
and we have been like a family since way back.
Finally!
I don't know what you're talking
about and I don't care!
I wonder if it's there!
Everyone that brought me food here...
I don't know for sure but
I think it's a tiger.
Or not!
Grr! I'm sure you don't!
No matter what will be ruined,
we'd never sell out our friends!
...was injured!
The One Piece!
What we wanna know is
whether he'll come back or not!
A tiger?!
They told me the country is okay,
but is it true?!
Who cares?!
So we can get ahold of the One Piece!
He can get married if he wants!
If it's a lie, I, Raizo, will hate you!
If they meet the Minks and say
they're looking for Raizo,
"The Third One!
Raizo of the Mist, the Ninja, Appears!"
But we don't wanna become Big
Mom's subordinates because of it!
It's finally in sight!
Conquering the Grand Line!
it's gonna be messy!
Right! Because of some samurai
named Raizo who isn't even here,
So if they get married,
you guys become my subordinates!
I'm getting fired up! Super!
the Mokomo Dukedom was destroyed!
Anyway, we have to stop those two!
Ouch!
What?!
I can't wait!
--Yeah!
--Let's go!
He's nothing like we expected!
JACK DIES!
THE PROMINENT MEMBER OF THE BEAST PIRATES
"Emperor Kaido's right-hand
man, Jack the Drought,"
"suspected of trading fire with
the Navy that was transporting
Doflamingo and presumed dead"?
Pekoms, are you okay?
The Ponegliffs.
That's bullshit!
--Luffy, you're funny!
--Understood, Lion Viper?!
Fabled indestructible stones
that are scattered across the world.
"A Red Stone!
A Guide to the One Piece!"
--Hey!
--Yes, sir!
Hurry up-saru! Hurry up-saru!
Tell Big Mom so!
What do you think? Am I dead?
They have an ancient
language carved on them -
N-No! Definitely not!
This is serious-saru! This is serious-saru!
Watch what you say, you brat!
Or I'll destroy you!
You're alive, Jack-sama!
the deciphering of which has
proved a difficult task.
Samurai-saru!
Grr!
Samurai are here-saru!
Hey! What in the world has happened,
Cat Viper?!
I owe you guys but don't push your luck!
Too slow...
Mama is one of the Four Emperors of the sea!
Why's this ship this slow?!
Go faster!
Forgive me, Raizo.
OHARA
We had no choice.
Bariete's ringing the bell!
Uh-huh.
Yes, sir!
However, Robin who grew up in Ohara
where people were studying the Ponegliffs,
Samurai-saru!
Samurai are here-saru!
This is bad for my wound.
can read the language.
You have pretty eyes.
That's a disappointment.
There are two kinds of Ponegliffs;
the ones that hold information
Shut up!
--His face is huge!
--Doesn't seem like a fast runner!
and the other ones that point to them.
--Is that Raizo?
--I can't accept a ninja like that!
Move! Get out of my way!
Out of my way!
And if some of those Ponegliffs
that hold information are connected,
Well, either way,
he can't escape the marriage.
I don't think you guys are from this country!
Who are you?!
they will become one text
that holds the secret of...
Why?!
Shishilian.
Just like Black-Foot has gone to attend it,
Let's go to the city!
Tell everyone who is capable to follow me!
Raizo!
the 100-Year Void in History
that has eluded the records of history.
no one can turn down an invitation
to Mama's tea party on any account.
Kin'emon! Kanjuro! Momonosuke-sama!
Yes, sir!
Duke-sama! Your Warney is ready!
The currently non-existent text
that will be completed by...
--I'm glad that you're okay!
--We're glad you're okay too!
If anybody turns it down,
he'll get himself...
THE REAL PONEGLIFF
...connecting those passages is
what they call the Real Ponegliff.
Raizo!
...quite a shocking present.
Because he put Mama to shame.
The King of the Pirates - Gol D. Roger
A present?
Sorry to keep you waiting, Raizo!
I'll unchain you now!
managed to take those passages
to the goal; Raftel.
It's not the kind of present you want.
Thanks!
Listen, everyone!
Do as you've been told!
Shishilian-dono, what have we been told?!
We haven't been told anything!
He'll receive the decapitated head of a person
who was close to him!
All able-bodied people in the fortress,
go into action!
"I made it here.
I will guide this text to the ends of the earth."
Follow Duke-sama along with me, Shishilian!
What's your problem, you bastards?
"Pirate Gol D. Roger"
A head?!
Of course, at full speed!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Look at this place.
It could be a head of someone
from the Straw Hats...
I'm deeply grateful to you all!
Okay! Let's go search!
Where are you going?! It's a big world!
...or someone from the restaurant
in the East Blue.
That's...
I'll get back Sanji quickly!
Listen to me!
It's not a big deal! Don't mention it!
Oh, it could be someone
from the Kamabakka Kingdom.
The crest of the Kozuki Family!
You-gara, if you're gonna go to
Whole Cake Island along with Pekoms,
Thank you!
No...
And now, as proof, I offer you this!
it wouldn't be such a bad idea.
The same as Kin'emon's!
Hey!
How do you guys know about all those things?!
That crest has existed for centuries.
Of the four Road Ponegliffs,
we are missing the whereabouts of only one.
That's what power can do, Straw Hat!
We have one here.
And that stone is...
Yes, that's certainly the
same Kozuki Clan crest
And the other two are
under the control of some pirates.
I've never seen it in such a color.
Deep red...
that Duke-sama, Master and Raizo-san have!
What he was told at that
time must have been...
Pirates?
Who are those pirates?
Yeah, it's a Ponegliff.
When someone as powerful as that makes
a threat, it's definitely not idle.
--Master!
--Pedro!
Emperor Big Mom!
And another Emperor -
Kaido, King of the Beasts!
We know you-gara, Nico Robin.
Kozuki...
Who can fight it?
I can't believe they know each other!
This is an extremely serious matter!
Don't fall behind!
That's how powerful the Four Emperors are!
I heard the Ohara people
can read those letters.
What?!
Yeah!
I was really prepared for a
clash against the Minks! Jeez!
There's really nothing you can do about it!
I see!
So you two know about Ohara.
So we should just rob them!
We were trying to keep the samurai a secret.
That's why Sanji-kun had no choice but to go!
Whoever it is, I'll just cut them.
We were just beating our
bones against the wall.
Samurai! Two samurai appeared!
I mean, heads.
Oh, I suddenly see nothing but darkness
before my eyes...
There's one other thing.
Let me ease your worry, my saviors.
It couldn't be helped.
They couldn't have told the whole story even to us.
Follow Master!
Me too!
You guys will not become
her subordinates. Grr!
Luffy, wake up!
But I don't have eyes.
You're right.
She just said the doggy and the kitty
have the same crest.
Wake up!
Why?! We gotta kick their butts anyway
so let's just do it!
It's a political marriage.
Yeah, I can eat more!
Maybe, their bond is far
stronger than we realize.
Don't say it like it's nothing!
Mama always forms a connection with
those who'll become her subordinates.
I didn't care much because I thought
we wouldn't fight them anytime soon
Hey, Luffy!
You're still half sleep! Just wake up!
But Dogstorm, Cat Viper...
So this marriage is a ritual to form a
but the thought of it makes me wet myself!
connection between the Vinsmoke
Family and the Charlotte Family.
Yeah! We'll wet our pants!
Don't mess with us!
It is surprising to see you two
alive and well here!
But you don't need to rob the Ponegliffs.
Death would've been a relief to us.
It's got nothing to do with you guys.
But we thought if we trust the words
from that day and wait here...
By the way, that bell is very noisy.
It's been ringing constantly.
Here, this proves that you're
a scholar. Take this, Robin.
Do you want me to break it down for you more?
Yeah, then we would get
to see you-gara guys one day!
We don't?
Isn't it a bell to tell
everyone they have a visitor?
Usually, people can copy their text
like making a rubbing.
I'm happy for you, Robin.
From the moment they get married,
Hey, cat monster!
Congratulations!
They must be welcoming us!
What do you want, dog?!
Black-Foot Sanji will no longer
be part of your crew!
No one goes around carrying around
such massive stones.
I was talking to Kin'emon!
Listen, Robin. You must understand well
what it means to be an archaeologist.
That's certainly possible!
I've got an idea!
Don't interrupt as you please!
That's totally unacceptable!
Sanji's my friend!
In that case, we'll sneak into
Big Mom and Kaido's headquarters
Yes, Professor Clover!
I was just thinking Kin'emon must be
sick of talking to you-gara
But he's Vinsmoke's son first!
and get the copies!
But Law-dono was saying that...
so I tactfully took over!
Don't get mad at me! Grr!
...the inhabitants of Zou who don't like humans
are actually the Mink Tribe.
What did you say?!
Then, we'll reach Raftel before anyone knows!
Yes, is that what people are saying?
I can't understand why.
Oh, here we go again!
And you'll become the King of the Pirates!
I know Sanji will refuse such a marriage!
I thought they were cooled down.
Well, when they're both present,
it's not gonna be peaceful.
In the face of Mama
and the vicious Vinsmoke Family?
If that's what people
are saying these days...
What's your problem, you dummy?!
Why do they hate each other so much?!
Well, I wonder if he can manage
to stay alive after he refuses.
Why is that Ponegliff red?
Who is it?!
That's not manly at all!
Whoever it is, we can just kick their butts!
--You-gara served your purpose! Get lost!
--You get lost!
What do you mean?!
Easy, easy, easy!
None of the Ponegliffs I've ever seen
were that color.
Please stop, both of you!
Our long-awaited guests have just arrived!
Hey, Lion Viper!
What are you gonna do now?!
Stop!
Father! Kanjuro!
Cut it out!
I'll go back to Mama after I get well.
Stop running!
It has a different purpose.
No, I won't!
Momonosuke!
He thinks he killed me,
that son of a gun - Bege!
Kanjuro! So you're all right!
But he can't get away with it!
Can you read it?
Then, take me with you!
Yes, may I?
Ah, I'm sorry to make you worry.
Of course, you may.
Luffy!
Can't we figure it out
with just three of them?
I'm relieved!
--Nami, I'm gonna go by myself.
--What?
Stop fighting! Dogstorm! Cat Viper!
Like Robin and the others said,
The location of Raftel.
if we go together, it'd
seem like we want a war.
Now, why are you here alone?
Where are Luffy-dono and everybody?
No, we can't. We can't identify
the location with just three.
We don't have time for that.
You two used to be such good friends!
Why have you been fighting like
you wanna kill each other?!
I thought so.
I'll go by myself!
Actually, I haven't been at ease
since we came to this country
What's wrong with you guys?
Why are you staring hard at me like that?
I think we'll have to look for
the fourth Ponegliff eventually.
If I go with him, maybe I can sneak into the tea party
and ruin the wedding.
Because...
I forbid you to ever fight again!
so I've been sleeping in a room by myself.
Of course! There's no short route
to become the King of the Pirates!
It's even more inexcusable
if it's because of my father!
Are you really a ninja?
Screw you!
Are you asking me to harbor an enemy?!
How insolent! Who are you?!
--Oh no!
--You poor thing.
It would make my father sad
to see you two like this...
Shut up!
What's wrong with taking a short route?!
Oh, sounds like fun!
We haven't introduced them to you yet.
And when I woke up, nobody was there
so I came looking for someone.
What did you say?!
Raizo, they're the Straw Hats.
They're pirates.
Carrot, this is serious!
Oden-sama...
They're full of life.
I see. Then come with us.
Okay, it's a deal!
Pirates?
H-Hey!
If you're a real ninja, throw a shuriken!
They-gara are a lot of fun.
I guess they're assembling to welcome us!
Ouch!
I'll get Chopper! Get well already!
Meditate under a waterfall!
Momo?
There's no mistake!
You're not at liberty to decide that!
Did you say it'd make your father sad?
But I'm more worried about
you-gara, Nico Robin.
Say "Nin" and use ninja powers!
Why?! Why?! Why?!
Why should I be running this early in the morning?!
But Kin'emon's right here.
Ow, ow... Hey!
I wanna see the Earth Escape Technique!
I want the fire version!
I told you! Kin'emon and...
What was his name?!
Don't tell me...
Wait, Straw Hat!
No, the water version!
Those-gara who are interested
in the 100-Year Void
Zoro, you're here!
Did you hear all that?!
I'm sorry!
Such rapid-fire requests!
Kanjuro!
Yes! Those two arrived!
Momonosuke-sama! I'm ashamed of myself!
You're absolutely right!
Show us your ninja powers already!
are now collecting the
copies across the world
Just barely.
They say two samurai appeared
and the whole country is in a great uproar!
Why do you pirates want to see it so badly?!
You're worried about Sanji, aren't you?
but no one can read them.
--What?!
--Duke-sama!
It's not because we're pirates.
Master Cat Viper headed for the city
leading the Guardians!
I'll kick you, fool!
I told you to forget about that idiot!
I can't believe Master's bowing his head!
Big names all around the world will...
Another welcome banquet?!
I wouldn't mind having one for two consecutive days!
Super!
Hey!
Luffy! Zoro! How's Pekoms doing?!
All boys like ninjas!
No, they've got a score to settle!
...surely target you-gara for kidnap
when they're ready to read them.
Oh, Chopper!
Of course, they do!
He's crying from pain and banging
his head against a wall and yelling!
They were wrongly accused of hiding a samurai
and almost died!
K...
Cure him now!
Kidnap Robin?!
Would that child be...
Those are crazy symptoms!
I'll check him right away!
What?!
Well, he can move around which
means he's fine, I guess.
That makes me blush.
You're right.
Hey, have you ever gone out
with a female ninja?!
Garchu! Baron Corpse!
Are you insane?!
Train your jumping ability
by jumping over a bamboo shoot every day!
Don't think that you'll be able to survive
after making the entire world your enemy!
What? Hey!
--Garchu! Garchu!
--Hey!
Bring it on!
Show me the Shadow Clone Technique.
Hide in the ceiling and
get stabbed by a spear.
Momonosuke-sama is right!
Hey, stop! No! Hey!
Sama?
Fly in the sky with a cloth parachute!
Garchu!
Hey, did you just use "sama"
when you mentioned Momonosuke?
Summon a giant frog!
You look so delicious, Baron Corpse!
We're gonna go back together!
Hold a scroll in your
mouth and say "Nin-nin"!
Seems like it wasn't just
the Minks who had a secret.
Help me! I'm in a bigger state
of emergency than anyone else!
Robin!
Raizo!
Hurry up!
No, don't just watch and laugh!
Please forgive me for lying to you all, too!
Just do it.
Show us ninja powers!
Listen carefully, Robin!
To tell you the truth,
Momonosuke-sama and I are...
Where are they?!
Oh! You-gara are Straw Hat Luffy, aren't you?!
I couldn't wait to meet you!
You're alone now,
...not father and son!
We'll find them right away!
Oh, shut up!
but you'll meet friends someday for sure!
People across the country
keep rolling into the city...
Stop imposing your damn dreams on me!
What?!
What?! Why did you follow us?! Get rest!
We ninja don't say things like "Nin-nin"!
The ninja in your heads are all fantasies!
I just got better!
It's no problem.
No, you didn't!
He's huge! Is that Cat Viper?!
He's a cat monster!
Pedro! Can you see them?!
What?!
This man right here is the heir to...
...Kozuki Oden-sama, great daimyo
of Kuri in the Land of Wano!
Th-They don't say that?!
KOZUKI MOMONOSUKE
THE HEIR TO THE DAIMYO OF KURI IN THE LAND OF WANO
What's wrong?!
I have strong friends who will protect me.
Then, what makes you a ninja?!
It can't be your physique!
His name is Kozuki Momonosuke-sama!
This is no good.
A Garchu of thanks!
That's right. With this physique,
I can't even attract female ninjas...
Whoa-whoa, did you say "Strong"?
That makes me blush!
That means for all of us including
Dogstorm and Cat Viper,
Can't you find the samurai yet?!
I'll kick anyone's butt for you!
Hey, shut up!
We're on the hunt now!
he's our lord!
--Find them as soon as possible!
--Yes, sir!
You shouldn't count on me like that...
Listen! It takes a quiet and
tough mind to be a master ninja!
Master, please pull back!
I'll protect Robin-san no matter what!
--Pull back?!
--Hurry up!
What?! Usopp!
What in the world is going on?!
We're supposed to be living in the shadows.
We can't show off our techniques.
Cat Viper's spouting blood!
Humph! What are you talking about?!
I'll do anything for Robin too!
What lord?! I don't understand!
Hey, what are you doing, cat monster!?
Ninjutsu is not entertainment...
Super!
The dog, the cat, Kin'emon
and Kanjuro are retainers
I won't let anyone touch Robin!
What?! Duke Dogstorm!
and Momo must be their master but...
Stay with me! Cat Viper!
If they do, I'll take their lives and money!
I'll pretend I didn't see him.
I don't understand either!
So he's the heir of the Kozuki Family
and Oden-dono's son!
They-gara are very dependable!
How could I miss that?!
You have good friends.
Please. Just keep going.
Is Momo someone important?
If they're heading the list of his retainers,
he could be quite a powerful lord.
Along the way, if his true identity was revealed,
we could've attracted more enemies
He's really big! And so fluffy, too!
The cat monster!
Ninpo - Smoke Escape Technique!
There are four Navy ships.
But the lineup is so formidable!
Are they gonna go destroy a country?
so we pretended as if we were father and son.
Get off of him, Luffy!
He may not look it but he's heavily injured!
H...
He disappeared!
What's going on?
Although we trusted you all,
we never had a good chance to tell you.
They use so much force just for transport.
What?
I'm out of blood!
Bring me some blood quick!
That's how great Doflamingo-sama is!
Where did he go?!
Sorry.
Okay, Dr. Chopper.
It's impossible to take back Joker.
Captain Jack, shall we go back?
I didn't disappear!
Th-Th-Th-Thank...
Oh...
So you're not father and son.
What's wrong, Chopper?!
Oh no! The two ran into each other!
Cat monster, stand up! I'll cut you up!
But they're alike. They're both perverts.
--Why?
--What?
I'm here.
You idiot! We're gonna do it!
Whoa-whoa, he's injured.
Wh-What?!
You-gara...
Who cares!
I'll run him through all nine of his lives!
What?!
Who do you think I am?!
No, don't!
And here too!
Oh, Tra-guy!
Prepare to fire!
Here too!
Oh! Are they your friends?!
Hurry up!
What?! He's got doubles?!
Yeah, I came to introduce them to you.
They're my crew - 20 in total!
Could it be...?!
I'm sorry that I was lying!
I'm actually an important figure!
Ninpo - Shadow Clone Technique!
Yes, and a pervert.
Cool!
No, I'm not!
How's this? Can you catch me?
Whatever!
Oh, shoot!
What do you mean by that?!
Bow down, Luffy!
It's nice to make your
acquaintance! Straw Hat!
That's the Beast Pirates!
They're such a formidable enemy to face!
THE HEART PIRATES
What?!
No way! Why do we have to change our behavior
Yeah!
We need to talk.
--Master!
--Duke-sama!
just because you're an
important person?! Idiot!
They only have one ship.
I got you!
What?! Is that it?!
Please don't do it, Master!
M-Momonosuke-sama!
Slighted! Slighted!
How's this?!
Slighted! Slighted! Slighted!
Oh, boy...
You're afraid of heights
and you have no guts!
Duke-sama! Please calm down!
We feel slighted, Captain!
Ninpo - Body Replacement Technique!
We samurai aren't afraid of anything!
How rude!
We're pirate allies, aren't we?!
Introduce us to the Straw Hats properly!
--You coward!
--What an insolent fellow!
Starboard!
Here we go again.
He saved our lives but...
He's right, Captain!
He's unexpectedly agile!
You can't ask a pirate to be humble.
Fire!
Did you doubt I was really a ninja?
Momonosuke-sama's getting
distracted so that's good.
We're just allies.
We don't necessarily have to get friendly.
Fire!
Flower Shuriken!
Is it a fight?
Stay with me, Cat Viper!
SHINOBI
So frustrating, Onami!
Luffy is a terrible guy!
That's...
Help me...
Oh, there, there.
Never popular with girls
but still an invincible ninja!
What?! Black-Foot-ya went to see Big Mom?!
Stay away from her, Momonosuke-sama!
You damn brat!
Hurry up! We're getting raided!
Uh-huh.
Raizo of the Mist is now...
How in the world could that happen?!
Hey!
Don't worry!
I'm gonna go take him back!
Pull up to them!
Say, Momo-chan,
...here before your eyes!
So could you wait to fight
Kaido a little bit?!
if your father is a lord, there must be
treasure in his castle, isn't that right?
That's not my call!
Cut it out!
It's only a matter of time
before Kaido comes after us!
You're really a bad person!
The ninja's so cool!
That's...
Raizo!
I thought we could hide ourselves
here in Zou for a while
It's only been a few months since...
Nin! Nin!
but they know where it is.
What are you doing?!
Man! That was...
Their-gara cheeriness must be helping him.
...Really close!
Even if their target is us
next, what do you think
will happen to this country
if it's attacked again?!
You three, take my advice
and go back to the Sunny now!
How kind of you!
Oh, they're fighting!
Boy! If you go out there now,
it'd be like pouring gasoline on a fire!
Jack-sama, Sheepshead-sama is back.
Since when were they there?!
Garchu!
How many years has it been, cat monster?
You've become even more monstrous.
You-gara guys, are you really pirates?!
Nin-nin! You're unbelievable!
Thank you for caring about us
on top of saving us!
What about you-gara?
You've lost one of your legs.
Nin-nin! Being a ninja isn't about how you look
but about your mind! Nin-nin!
Thank you! Garchu!
Garchu, Baron Corpse!
Can I become a ninja
if I train myself a lot?! Nin-nin!
--What should we do?!
--Somebody, please stop them!
I can't take it anymore...
Where is Raizo?!
Oh, Pekoms, are you hurt?
Nin-nin!
I wanna see more ninjutsu! Nin-nin!
Give us Raizo!
--Yeah...
--Well, who cares!
I know Raizo is in this country!
Momonosuke won!
Cut the Nin-nin crap!
By the way, how do you guys know
so much about the Ponegliffs?
We don't have such a person here!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
Oh, you came around!
Stay quiet this time!
Search through the country as you please!
We don't have a samurai...
It all started with our master -
Okay, let's have a banquet!
You got me, Momo!
You already saw my ninjutsu accidentally.
Kozuki Oden-sama who used to
have an interest in the stones.
Bring drinks and food!
Yeah, because I'm a samurai!
Why, Cat Viper?!
Accidentally?
I'm in!
I know you did them for us!
I wonder if you'll say goodbye to this leg first,
or tell us where the samurai is.
No!
These fools...
Because...
Is it okay to tell them, dog?
Let's try it, "Dog King."
Go ahead. You don't have
to hide anything from them.
Banquet!
You can tell them anything.
We're gonna have the greatest
night of our lives!
Did you say "Go ahead"?
What's that bossy attitude?!
Then, there is no way
for me to save this leg.
Cheers!
I am their boss! You insolent dork!
Let's make a truce, cat.
If we keep dwelling in the past,
we'll make Momonosuke-sama suffer.
How can you be ceremonious all of a sudden?!
Yummy!
Cut it out! Luffy!
Oh yeah?!
Now, what's with that person - Kozuki Oden?
Grill more! Our saviors are hungry!
Okay, for the sake of our lord!
You-gara got your hand chopped off.
You can't fight anymore.
I'll communicate with you-gara
but won't connect with you-gara!
--Let's keep grilling!
--Yeah!
The most you can do is eat lasagna.
Cheers!
The Kozuki Family of the
Land of Wano was, in fact,
That's a deal!
Say it! Where's the samurai?!
a clan of stonemasons that has quarried stones
and processed them for generations.
How can I tell you the whereabouts
of someone who isn't here?!
A person from the Land of
Wano has no business here!
They are still highly skilled.
Are you guys crying?
Oh! Look at that!
Then, we have no choice but...
Those two are... No way!
Stonemasons?
...to kill these guys one by one.
Don't be silly!
Yes. It goes way back, 800 years ago...
Master!
All you can do is use poison gas
and attack the weakened men!
Here is the main dish!
Men from the Land of Wano don't cry!
You cowards!
Lasagna-meow!
Oh no! This guy's trying to break the chains!
Wow! Yum-yum!
It's just...
Don't be shy!
The Kozuki Clan invented an indestructible
book with their sophisticated skills.
Is the gas really working?!
Immobilize his arms!
You-gara guys, enjoy the
Whale Forest's Special
It's a miracle!
Our two kings made up!
Yeah, you'd better do that!
...it wasn't like this when I arrived here!
Lasagna as much as you like!
The King of the Day and the King of the Night
finally...
That's what the Ponegliffs are!
Yeah! I'll have some!
If you have time to harm my people,
point your spear at me!
How amazing the Kozuki Family's power is!
What?!
Yummy!
No... Master!
I'll take all of those crappy spears myself!
You're right! This is quite good!
The city and the river were both beautiful!
Yeah? Let me have it!
The Kozuki Family?!
It makes me cry!
Dr. Miyagi! You're hopping too much!
Master!
Were they the ones who made all
those Ponegliffs in the world?!
The streets were bustling
and people were living their lives!
You made the stones that
Robin is looking for?!
This is, indeed, another miracle!
It's a shame that
you-gara have only lost one of your legs!
And the whole country...
Not me! It was my ancestors from way back!
...was full of energy!
What happened to them suddenly?
I wouldn't mind if you were dead.
Then, do you guys know
what's written on them?!
--They're getting excited over something.
--Yeah.
One king is enough for the country!
Oh?
That hasn't been passed down fully
through the generations.
It feels like I'm forgetting
something important...
Please stop, both of you!
You can find it out by reading the stones.
Then let's send one of us to kingdom come!
Well, never mind!
The only thing that has been passed down
was how to read and write the ancient text.
You-gara must die!
However...
A dog and a cat?!
Hey!
Unfortunately, that's...
Before it was passed down to Momonosuke-sama,
it was cut off at his father -
Kozuki Oden-sama's generation!
I heard about it before
but they're really strong!
It's beautiful.
It's a rainbow!
Hey, wait!
By "cut off," you mean
Momonosuke-san's father is...
Stop fighting!
Hey, you idiot! What are you doing?!
Yes, Oden-sama is...
That's...
...a samurai!
Wano...
See?! They found you!
Seems like Luffy-san and the others are
completely forgetting about it.
Run, Kin'emon! They're gonna kill you!
Wa...
--Momo-chan!
--Hey, let go of me! Please!
Wa...
What are you gonna do?!
But we mature adults must
get our act together.
Damn those Minks!
Momo, stay away!
Let's climb the whale.
Kanjuro! Why did you guys come out?!
What they did was so rash!
That's right.
This country doesn't want them.
If you learn which vines to take,
you can reach the top.
Run! Now!
Yeah! Under no circumstances
should a samurai enter!
I will work as hard as I can to avenge you!
So Raizo's here?!
After all, Raizo-san, the
person Kin'emon-san and
--Yeah.
--Ya-hoo!
Kanjuro-san are looking for,
isn't here so there's no point.
Cat Viper! Dogstorm! Wait a minute!
So forgive me!
Forgive me!
In addition, because of that,
They really mean no harm!
Oden wouldn't be "oden"
if it wasn't boiled!
the millennium-old city was ruined!
People from the country of Zou!
--Nin-nin!
I'm a retainer of the Kozuki Clan from
the Land of Wano, named Kin'emon!
Bring Raizo here!
--Nin-nin!
Where's the warrior from the Land of Wano?
I'm here to look for my comrade
named Raizo who is a warrior
from the same country!
Can't wait to see the ninja! Nin-nin!
They call us saviors and thank us.
Has he been here?!
I get to see a ninja! Nin-nin!
Well, this country was destroyed
because he wasn't here!
So we absolutely can't tell them
that we actually have some samurai friends.
The Watery Escape Technique! Nin-nin!
Luffy!
Yeah!
Hey, you-gara guys!
I still don't feel well, Kin'emon.
--It's not looking good.
--Shoot! Should we fight?!
Seems like the deciphering of the stone is done!
Come back into the whale!
You can wait at the bottom if you want,
Momonosuke-sama.
If they find out that
Kin'emon and the others were
Hey! It's okay if you
don't wanna talk about it!
going to use this island
as their rendezvous point,
As we get closer to the whale,
the voice I hear is getting louder.
What do you think, Nami?
Oden-sama was...
Is this what's written on the Ponegliff?
even the cheerful Minks would be pissed off.
...executed!
Yeah, I can draw a nautical
chart based on this!
You have a similar ability to Oden-sama.
By the shogun of the Land of Wano
and the pirate Kaido!
We can pinpoint the location of something,
Robin!
There was another man
who used to say something like that.
What?!
That red stone is called a Road Ponegliff!
I don't wanna fight them
after we got to know each other!
To save all of us retainers,
I was just thinking about the same thing.
Let's keep guard all night long
to prevent Kin'emon and Kanjuro from entering.
All the tough guys of the sea are
searching for the end of the Grand Line,
he met his fate!
By Kaido?!
We'll be in trouble if we
get tired and fall asleep.
and that stone is a guide to get there!
Kaido...
Let's take turns. I'll go first.
No, I'll go first.
No, I'll keep guard!
We've been expecting you.
Oh, I can't believe there's an entrance here!
The Whale Forest is considered sacred
because of it
And...
--Let's do it together then.
--Okay.
I don't know Raizo! I swear to god!
...Emperor Kaido's Beast Pirates are...
so it needs to be protected by us Guardians!
On the tail of the Whale Tree?!
No one would notice!
And it's a hidden door
so it's impossible to find.
The end of the Grand Line...
...still in the Land of Wano!
Let's go.
You mean, a guide to the
last island - Raftel?!
If the man you're talking about is here,
you can take my life!
THE NEXT MORNING
That's right!
What?!
This place is cool!
However...
Me first!
Raftel?!
Raizo-dono is...
In the Land of Wano?
Hey! Don't go too fast!
That's the goal!
To become King of the Pirates!
...safe!
Bye!
Wait!
Finally, we can get there!
The last island - Raftel!
If you don't wanna talk about it,
that's okay but...
It's a long flight of stairs so be careful.
...why was your master executed?
Well... Well, well, well,
it's still dark so it's before dawn.
You guys have been captured and targeted
because of that, haven't you?
That's the island the flower pops mentioned!
We made it!
That's right! We finally made it!
Does it say where Raftel is?!
Wait, wait, don't jump to conclusions!
Hear me out. You see...
Oh boy, it was a disaster
but all's well that ends well.
There are four of those red stones - the Road Ponegliffs
in the world!
Momo-chan...
Yes, you're right.
You could say it's a cardinal sin.
What?! Does it mean there are four Raftels?!
Is that...
No, there aren't! Let him finish first!
That's Raizo's voice.
I'm sure Luffy-dono and everybody
are worried about us.
What?! The ninja?!
Oh, he's safe! I'm relieved!
Ninja!
I feel bad.
That stone must indicate the location of
some unknown spot but it's not Raftel.
Yes, they must've been waiting for us!
Ninja!
Kaido is trying to pull information from us!
Well done, Torasaburo.
Tora (tiger)?!
Oh, I didn't know this animal was a tiger!
Ninja! Ninja! Ninja!
Whoa, wait a minute!
The other three Road Ponegliffs all indicate
different locations in the same manner.
Hey, was Raizo here all this time?!
Ninja! Ninja! Ninja!
The previous daimyo - Kozuki Oden-sama...
That's right! Nekozaemon should be happy
that his efforts weren't for nothing.
Did you all know?!
When you learn where those locations are
and connect those four points on a map,
Ninja!
...traveled to the last island Raftel
with the King of the Pirates - Gol D. Roger
Alright, that's enough.
Revert to a painting!
--Ya-hoo! Where's the ninja?!
--Ninja! Ninja!
those lines will cross at the center!
and witnessed the secret of the world!
Here we are.
But monkey fellow,
you didn't tell us anything after all.
He-gara is the ninja, Raizo.
Y-Y-Y...
You all almost died!
Ninja! Nin...
I just wanna know
if a warrior named Raizo is...
The millennium-old city was ruined!
I-I don't know anything-saru!
There you are, Cat Viper!
That's where the last island is.
What's the matter? You look pale...
Only the King of the Pirates and his crew
have reached it in all these centuries!
You! Why didn't you just
hand me over to them?!
What?!
RAIZO OF THE MIST - A NINJA
FROM THE LAND OF WANO
Oh, hey, wait! Where are you going?!
Everyone that brought me food here...
We can't look for Raizo on our own!
Roger?
...was injured!
And that's Raftel!
Wait, monkey fellow!
We need you to take us around!
They told me the country is okay,
but is it true?!
I'm sorry that we kept it a secret
from you-gara guys too.
If it's a lie, I, Raizo, will hate you!
The Land of Wano's Kozuki Clan
and we have been like a family since way back.
Hey!
Wait!
Momonosuke's father...
Monkey fellow!
No matter what will be ruined,
we'd never sell out our friends!
Oh no-saru! Samurai are here-saru!
...went to Raftel with Gold Roger?!
What?!
The last island - Raftel!
He's nothing like we expected!
I gotta let them know as soon as possible!
Samurai are here-saru!
A mysterious shadow in the dark night,
which runs with a rhythm!
The emergency bell rings
all over Zou once again!
The mystery of the Ponegliffs
that Robin is searching for comes to light!
Momonosuke remembers the pain
from when he last saw his father Oden!
The King of the Pirates - Gold Roger,
the man who once attained everything
this world has to offer,
Cat Viper and Dogstorm rush
towards Kin'emon and Kanjuro!
He sneakily throws an 8-pointed shuriken,
When the conflict among the Four Emperors
who are trying to get to Raftel
When the earnest wish of the samurais
left behind the legendary
treasure of One Piece.
and his mutable short
sword will cut down evil!
who left their home, the Land of Wano,
for a long rough journey is revealed,
and the deep connection between the
The Mink Tribe who are badly bruised
after getting their country ruined
When Luffy finds a new Ponegliff,
Kozuki Clan,
including Momonosuke, and the Ponegliffs are revealed,
because of some unknown samurai,
With these dreams of being a
ninja which all boys share,
Luffy makes a stunning decision
that shocks everybody!
the road to becoming the King
of the Pirates will be revealed!
vent their unbridled emotions
against the two samurai!
Luffy will learn the samurais' great sorrow!
Raizo the ninja finally shows himself!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Red Stone! A Guide to the One Piece!"
"A Volatile Situation! The Dog
and the Cat and the Samurai!"
"A Vow Between Two Men! Luffy
and Kozuki Momonosuke!"
The Secret of the Land of Wano!
The Kozuki Family and the Ponegliffs!
"The Third One! Raizo of the
Mist, the Ninja, Appears!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!