kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests,
a zou (elephant) that has been
alive for a millennium.
They met the Mink Tribe who live there
and listened to all the details of the battle
between the Minks and
the Beast Pirates led by Jack,
Emperor Kaido's subordinate,
that happened a half month ago.
They also learned Sanji was taken to
a wedding of himself and
Emperor Big Mom's daughter.
Is that...
That's Raizo's voice.
What?! The ninja?!
Ninja!
--Ya-hoo! Where's the ninja?!
--Ninja! Ninja!
Here we are.
He-gara is the ninja, Raizo.
There you are, Cat Viper!
You! Why didn't you just
hand me over to them?!
Everyone that brought me food here...
...was injured!
They told me the country is okay,
but is it true?!
If it's a lie, I, Raizo, will hate you!
What?!
He's nothing like we expected!
"A Red Stone!
A Guide to the One Piece!"
Hey! What in the world has happened,
Cat Viper?!
Forgive me, Raizo.
We had no choice.
That's a disappointment.
--His face is huge!
--Doesn't seem like a fast runner!
--Is that Raizo?
--I can't accept a ninja like that!
I don't think you guys are from this country!
Who are you?!
Raizo!
Kin'emon! Kanjuro! Momonosuke-sama!
--I'm glad that you're okay!
--We're glad you're okay too!
Raizo!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Raizo!
I'll unchain you now!
Thanks!
What's your problem, you bastards?
Look at this place.
That's...
The crest of the Kozuki Family!
The same as Kin'emon's!
That crest has existed for centuries.
And that stone is...
I've never seen it in such a color.
Deep red...
Yeah, it's a Ponegliff.
We know you-gara, Nico Robin.
I heard the Ohara people
can read those letters.
So you two know about Ohara.
Here, this proves that you're
a scholar. Take this, Robin.
I'm happy for you, Robin.
Congratulations!
Listen, Robin. You must understand well
what it means to be an archaeologist.
Yes, Professor Clover!
Why is that Ponegliff red?
None of the Ponegliffs I've ever seen
were that color.
It has a different purpose.
Can you read it?
Yes, may I?
Of course, you may.
What's wrong with you guys?
Why are you staring hard at me like that?
Are you really a ninja?
How insolent! Who are you?!
We haven't introduced them to you yet.
Raizo, they're the Straw Hats.
They're pirates.
Pirates?
If you're a real ninja, throw a shuriken!
Meditate under a waterfall!
Say "Nin" and use ninja powers!
I wanna see the Earth Escape Technique!
I want the fire version!
No, the water version!
Such rapid-fire requests!
Show us your ninja powers already!
Why do you pirates want to see it so badly?!
It's not because we're pirates.
Super!
All boys like ninjas!
That makes me blush.
Hey, have you ever gone out
with a female ninja?!
Train your jumping ability
by jumping over a bamboo shoot every day!
Show me the Shadow Clone Technique.
Hide in the ceiling and
get stabbed by a spear.
Fly in the sky with a cloth parachute!
Summon a giant frog!
Hold a scroll in your
mouth and say "Nin-nin"!
Raizo!
Hurry up!
Just do it.
Show us ninja powers!
Oh, shut up!
Stop imposing your damn dreams on me!
We ninja don't say things like "Nin-nin"!
The ninja in your heads are all fantasies!
What?!
Th-They don't say that?!
Then, what makes you a ninja?!
It can't be your physique!
That's right. With this physique,
I can't even attract female ninjas...
Hey, shut up!
Listen! It takes a quiet and
tough mind to be a master ninja!
We're supposed to be living in the shadows.
We can't show off our techniques.
Ninjutsu is not entertainment...
Ninpo - Smoke Escape Technique!
H...
He disappeared!
What?
Where did he go?!
I didn't disappear!
I'm here.
Wh-What?!
And here too!
Here too!
What?! He's got doubles?!
Could it be...?!
Ninpo - Shadow Clone Technique!
Cool!
How's this? Can you catch me?
What?!
I got you!
How's this?!
Ninpo - Body Replacement Technique!
He's unexpectedly agile!
Did you doubt I was really a ninja?
Flower Shuriken!
SHINOBI
Never popular with girls
but still an invincible ninja!
Raizo of the Mist is now...
...here before your eyes!
The ninja's so cool!
Raizo!
Nin! Nin!
Nin-nin! You're unbelievable!
Nin-nin! Being a ninja isn't about how you look
but about your mind! Nin-nin!
Can I become a ninja
if I train myself a lot?! Nin-nin!
Nin-nin!
I wanna see more ninjutsu! Nin-nin!
Cut the Nin-nin crap!
You already saw my ninjutsu accidentally.
Accidentally?
I know you did them for us!
These fools...
Are you guys crying?
Don't be silly!
Men from the Land of Wano don't cry!
It's just...
...it wasn't like this when I arrived here!
The city and the river were both beautiful!
The streets were bustling
and people were living their lives!
And the whole country...
...was full of energy!
Damn those Minks!
What they did was so rash!
I will work as hard as I can to avenge you!
So forgive me!
Forgive me!
Hey, you-gara guys!
Seems like the deciphering of the stone is done!
Come back into the whale!
What do you think, Nami?
Is this what's written on the Ponegliff?
Yeah, I can draw a nautical
chart based on this!
We can pinpoint the location of something,
Robin!
That red stone is called a Road Ponegliff!
All the tough guys of the sea are
searching for the end of the Grand Line,
and that stone is a guide to get there!
The Whale Forest is considered sacred
because of it
so it needs to be protected by us Guardians!
The end of the Grand Line...
You mean, a guide to the
last island - Raftel?!
That's right!
What?!
However...
Raftel?!
That's the goal!
To become King of the Pirates!
Finally, we can get there!
The last island - Raftel!
That's the island the flower pops mentioned!
Does it say where Raftel is?!
Wait, wait, don't jump to conclusions!
Hear me out. You see...
There are four of those red stones - the Road Ponegliffs
in the world!
What?! Does it mean there are four Raftels?!
No, there aren't! Let him finish first!
That stone must indicate the location of
some unknown spot but it's not Raftel.
The other three Road Ponegliffs all indicate
different locations in the same manner.
When you learn where those locations are
and connect those four points on a map,
those lines will cross at the center!
That's where the last island is.
Only the King of the Pirates and his crew
have reached it in all these centuries!
And that's Raftel!
The last island - Raftel!
The mystery of the Ponegliffs
that Robin is searching for comes to light!
When the conflict among the Four Emperors
who are trying to get to Raftel
and the deep connection between the
Kozuki Clan,
including Momonosuke, and the Ponegliffs are revealed,
Luffy will learn the samurais' great sorrow!
On the next episode of One Piece!
“The Secret of the Land of Wano!
The Kozuki Family and the Ponegliffs!”
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!