Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
That was hot! Couldn't you
have done it a different way?
Well, then. Can you tell
which is the real one?
Gum-Gum Stamp!
How... did you know... I was here?
A hunch.
"Farewell, Giant Island!
Head for Alabasta"
Whoa! Look behind him!
A rainbow! There's a rainbow!
Even the way he cries is big!
It's practically a waterfall!
I understand how you feel, Master Broggy!
Dorry! How are you...
It seems I blacked out...
Mr. 0?
Wasn't Mr. 0 the name of the
enemy boss Vivi-chan talked about?
Which means the guy on the other
end of this Transponder Snail...
...is one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea?!
It's been many days since
I issued your orders.
What's going on?
Mr. 3... So he's the owner
of this Transponder Snail?
Ah. I think I got it figured out now.
This is an enemy hideout,
and a guy named Mr. 3 came to
the island to take Vivi-chan's life...
Damn... This was no time
for me to be hunting!
I hope they're all okay!
Why the silent treatment?
I asked you a question.
Have you eliminated Princess
Vivi and the Straw Hats?!
Yeah, mission complete!
I got rid of everyone who
found out about your secret.
So there's no need to
go after 'em anymore.
I see. Well done.
As we speak, the Unluckies
are headed your way
to confirm your mission is complete
and to deliver a certain package.
Unluckies? Package?
An Eternal Pose that points
to the Alabasta Kingdom.
You and Ms. Golden Week will head
to Alabasta. The time has come.
We're about to begin our
most important operation.
Details will come after you reach
Alabasta. Wait for my orders.
What are these things?!
Hey. What's going on?
Oh, it's nothing...
What the hell?!
You tryin' to kill me?!
Bring it on, you damn monkey!
I'm telling you...
...to stop that!
You jumbo-sized chicken!
What was that?! What happened?!
Oh, uhh, no! It ain't--
I mean, it's nothing!
That damn Straw Hat was still alive.
It's okay, though. I finished him off.
No need to worry.
Still alive?
You just said your mission
was complete... Did you not?
Yes, well...
I thought it was complete...
But he was much tougher
than you'd believe...
In other words... the report
you gave me was a lie.
Umm, well... I suppose so,
when you put it that way...
But I've gotten rid of him for sure now.
So there's no need to send
any more after 'em. Okay?
Very well.
Just head straight to
Alabasta from there now!
It's probably... because of the weapons...
Weapons?! Oh, yeah!
Not even Elbaf weapons could
keep up with two giants
fighting to the death
for 100 years straight!
Talk about crazy...
It's a huge miracle!
Hey, Broggy! Don't hold on to me!
That hurts my wounds!
I'm so glad you're alive, friend of mine!
Miracle, my ass. It's only natural.
The fact those weapons are
still intact after 100 years
of constant bashing and
clanging is even crazier.
As are their owners.
What a wonderful day today is!
I thank you, God of Elbaf!
Oh, Broggy?
Was chopping me down and
knocking me out that happy for you?
You dimwit! That ain't what I'm saying!
Oww! Don't touch my wounds!
--You want some of this?!
--Yeah! I'll wipe the floor with ya!
Cool! Cool! Cool!
Why are you guys fighting again?!
...And no further
radio contact from now on.
We don't want the Navy
catching whiff of us.
All further orders will be
sent via letter, as usual.
That is all. Good luck, Mr. 3.
Miss All Sunday.
Yes?
Send Mr. 2 to Little Garden.
Eliminate Mr. 3 on his direct course
to Alabasta from Little Garden.
That's quite aggressive,
Mr. 0, Crocodile, sir.
We have enough manpower as it is.
Are you arguing with me?
No, I'll do as you wish.
I'll make arrangements at once.
Well, he's hung up. So let's see...
What were these guys, anyway?!
What do we have here?
We had completely forgotten
about the bounties on our heads!
But I was the reason they came to
this island in the first place...
Oww!
Let's have none of that!
Yeah, Vivi! What're you
so down in the dumps for?
Want a rice cracker?
Hey! Where did you get those?
Alright! For now,
let's have a rice cracker party!
Rice crackers aren't very exciting.
Really? We can even make
toasts with them!
See? Does anyone blame you?
Cheers!
C'mon! Don't do that!
Geez! You can't just waste food like that!
What're you doing?! Give it here!
Who said you could have mine?!
--Give it! It's mine!
--Who says?!
What's wrong?
Nothing. Just a bug.
Still, waiting a year for the
Log to point to the next island
is pretty serious stuff...
Yeah! It's definitely no laughing matter!
You saved us. We would like
to thank you in some way...
Oh, in that case, you old guys
can do something about our Log!
I'm afraid Logs are the only
thing we can't help you with...
Nami-san! Vivi-chan!
And you other bums!
Hey! Sanji!
You're okay! Thank goodness!
That jerk suddenly shows up
only after we needed help!
What in the hell?! Are you Mr. 3?!
Hey! How do you know about Mr. 3?
Nami-san!
You're so titillating!
Feel like getting slugged?
Now, now, Nami-san.
You'll catch cold dressed like that.
Here you are.
Thanks.
All that aside, I just finished talking
with Mr. 0 via Transponder Snail.
You talked to the boss?!
Yeah. I found this weird
hideout in the jungle, you see.
He seemed to think I was Mr. 3,
so I told him I eliminated everyone.
So that means he thinks we're dead?!
So we're finally free of people
chasing us, but we can't go anywhere!
Can't go anywhere? Do we still
have business on this island?
Just after I managed
to get ahold of this, too...
Eh? What?
It's an Eternal Pose to Alabasta!
--Hurray!
--Now we can set sail!
Hurray! Way to go, Sanji-kun!
Thank you, Sanji-san!
I was so worried for a moment there!
No, no! It was my pleasure!
I'm glad I could make you so happy!
Alright, everyone!
Let's have a rice cracker party!
Oh no, Luffy!
We only have three left!
We can't have a rice cracker party!
What?!
You know this is no time for that!
Let's go, Captain! We don't
have time to be lounging around!
Oh, yeah! Hey, you.
You haven't forgotten
our hunting contest, I hope!
Nope! But I win!
I caught a rhino this huge!
A rhino? I assume you can eat that?!
Of course!
Hunting contest?
Those words sound familiar somehow...
Yes...
Alright, round old guy and giant old guy!
We're gonna go now!
Oh, I see. Well, you do
seem to be in a hurry.
That's too bad, but we won't stop you.
I hope your homeland is okay.
Yes! Thank you!
See ya! Don't die anymore!
Master! I will visit Elbaf someday!
You'll see. Mine's way bigger than yours.
You wish!
I'm gonna be a brave warrior of the sea!
Our friends are setting sail.
Yes. We can't just sit here.
There's a monster in the western sea.
Dorry! How are your wounds?
These? They won't kill me.
This axe and that sword
are just about done with.
Do you have regrets?
I do. This axe fought alongside
me for over 100 years.
But, if it's for them, it's worth it!
Then it's decided...
See?! Mine's far huger than yours!
Look closer! My lizard's bigger!
Are you blind or something?!
My rhino's way bigger!
It doesn't really matter!
They both look yummy!
--You shut up!
--Huh?
--Look! Mine's bigger!
--No, mine is!
How long are you gonna keep at that?
We don't need all of it, so cut up
what we do need so we can set sail!
Yes, Nami-san!
Hey, Usopp!
I'm clearly the winner, right?!
I don't really care.
Can't you call it a tie?
There are no ties in a challenge!
Hurry it up!
Right!
Set sail!
They said going straight will take us
to the western end of the island.
Hey. Couldn't you have gotten
any more meat on board?
Yeah, right! Don't be stupid!
We can't preserve any more than that.
Do you want to sink the ship?!
Look, it's the old guys!
They came to see us off!
Ahead is a great obstacle...
...that prevents people who come to
this island from reaching the next...
You fought desperately
to protect our pride.
As such, no matter what manner
of enemy there may be...
...we will not let them
destroy your pride, friends!
Have faith in us,
and continue straight ahead!
Straight ahead, no matter what happens!
Got it!
What's this about?
What do you got?
We'll go straight ahead, no matter what!
This is goodbye!
Let's meet again someday.
Without fail.
Look! Up ahead!
There you are, Island-Eater!
You will open the path,
in the name of Elbaf!
--Wha...
--Something's appeared!
What's this guy? A goldfish?
A g-giant goldfish?!
W-Why does that sound familiar?!
Work the rudder! Hurry!
We're gonna get eaten!
Hurry, Usopp!
I-I can't!
Go straight ahead! R-Right, Luffy?!
Yeah! Of course!
Don't be stupid! This won't be
like what happened with Laboon!
I know. Calm down. Here, I'll let
you have the last rice cracker.
I don't want it! If we don't
turn the ship, we're gonna be--
Just give it up, Nami.
Luffy! We can trust those guys, I hope?!
Yeah!
Are you crazy?! Are we really
going straight into that beast?!
No! We're too late now!
You've grown a lot, Island-Eater!
You filthy monster goldfish!
His size isn't his only surprise.
There's also the size and
length of the dung he produces
after devouring any islands nearby.
I recall a giant piece of dung
named Nothing At All Island...
And that we landed on it long ago,
thinking it was actual land!
This is a nostalgic day of adventure!
As I look at them,
I'm reminded of the old days!
The only thing we can't penetrate
is the bloodstained snake!
Observe, the most powerful Giant spear,
as passed down in Elbaf!
Straight ahead! Straight ahead!
What are you talking about?!
We've already been eaten!
Straight ahead! Straight ahead!
Hakoku Sovereignty!
The world is awfully big
so even if there is treasure somewhere,
the odds are astronomical
So relying on dumb luck
won't get you anywhere
So even...
...if someone stops me or
laughs at me from the shadows
the ship will continue forward
Bon voyage!
Forget about them!
I know I'm a fool, but I gotta go
The crazier the dream,
the cooler the ambition
I know I'm a fool, but I'm gonna fight
The farther the sea,
the more heavenly it surely is
Do everything you can, and you'll
get a little nearer to any horizon
--I'm tired for some reason...
--Eh? Are you all right?
Everyone come here!
Nami-san has a terrible fever!
Is Nami-san gonna die?
Let's find an island
with a doctor right away!
Don't we need to hurry to Alabasta?
Curing Nami-san's illness comes first!
Well said, Vivi-chan!
--What's that?!
--Do you see a doctor?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Nami's Sick?
Beyond the Snow Falling on the Sea!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!