in all these centuries!
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
That red stone is called a Road Ponegliff!
There are four of those red stones
- the Road Ponegliffs in the world!
That stone must indicate the location of
some unknown spot but it's not Raftel.
The other three Road Ponegliffs all indicate
different locations in the same manner.
When you learn where those locations are
and connect those four points on a map,
those lines will cross at the center!
That's where the last island is.
Only the King of the Pirates
and his crew have reached it
And that's Raftel!
The last island - Raftel!
"The Secret of the Land of Wano!
The Kozuki Family and the Ponegliffs!"
Raftel...
Finally!
I wonder if it's there!
Or not!
The One Piece!
So we can get ahold of the One Piece!
It's finally in sight!
Conquering the Grand Line!
I'm getting fired up! Super!
I can't wait!
The Ponegliffs.
Fabled indestructible stones
that are scattered across the world.
They have an ancient
language carved on them -
the deciphering of which has
proved a difficult task.
OHARA
However, Robin who grew up in Ohara
where people were studying the Ponegliffs,
can read the language.
There are two kinds of Ponegliffs;
the ones that hold information
and the other ones that point to them.
And if some of those Ponegliffs
that hold information are connected,
they will become one text
that holds the secret of...
the 100-Year Void in History
that has eluded the records of history.
The currently non-existent text
that will be completed by...
THE REAL PONEGLIFF
...connecting those passages is
what they call the Real Ponegliff.
The King of the Pirates - Gol D. Roger
managed to take those passages
to the goal; Raftel.
"I made it here.
I will guide this text to the ends of the earth."
"Pirate Gol D. Roger"
Okay! Let's go search!
Where are you going?! It's a big world!
I'll get back Sanji quickly!
Listen to me!
You-gara, if you're gonna go to
Whole Cake Island along with Pekoms,
it wouldn't be such a bad idea.
Of the four Road Ponegliffs,
we are missing the whereabouts of only one.
We have one here.
And the other two are
under the control of some pirates.
Pirates?
Who are those pirates?
Emperor Big Mom!
And another Emperor -
Kaido, King of the Beasts!
What?!
I see!
So we should just rob them!
Whoever it is, I'll just cut them.
Oh, I suddenly see nothing but darkness
before my eyes...
Me too!
But I don't have eyes.
Why?! We gotta kick their butts anyway
so let's just do it!
Don't say it like it's nothing!
I didn't care much because I thought
we wouldn't fight them anytime soon
but the thought of it makes me wet myself!
Yeah! We'll wet our pants!
Don't mess with us!
But you don't need to rob the Ponegliffs.
We don't?
Usually, people can copy their text
like making a rubbing.
No one goes around carrying around
such massive stones.
I've got an idea!
In that case, we'll sneak into
Big Mom and Kaido's headquarters
and get the copies!
Then, we'll reach Raftel before anyone knows!
And you'll become the King of the Pirates!
What's your problem, you dummy?!
That's not manly at all!
Whoever it is, we can just kick their butts!
Easy, easy, easy!
Stop!
Cut it out!
Stop running!
No, I won't!
Can't we figure it out
with just three of them?
The location of Raftel.
No, we can't. We can't identify
the location with just three.
I thought so.
I think we'll have to look for
the fourth Ponegliff eventually.
Of course! There's no short route
to become the King of the Pirates!
Shut up!
What's wrong with taking a short route?!
What did you say?!
They're full of life.
They-gara are a lot of fun.
But I'm more worried about
you-gara, Nico Robin.
Those-gara who are interested
in the 100-Year Void
are now collecting the
copies across the world
but no one can read them.
Big names all around the world will...
...surely target you-gara for kidnap
when they're ready to read them.
K...
Kidnap Robin?!
What?!
Are you insane?!
Don't think that you'll be able to survive
after making the entire world your enemy!
Bring it on!
We're gonna go back together!
Robin!
Listen carefully, Robin!
You're alone now,
but you'll meet friends someday for sure!
It's no problem.
I have strong friends who will protect me.
Whoa-whoa, did you say "Strong"?
That makes me blush!
I'll kick anyone's butt for you!
You shouldn't count on me like that...
I'll protect Robin-san no matter what!
I'll do anything for Robin too!
Super!
I won't let anyone touch Robin!
If they do, I'll take their lives and money!
They-gara are very dependable!
You have good friends.
There are four Navy ships.
But the lineup is so formidable!
Are they gonna go destroy a country?
They use so much force just for transport.
That's how great Doflamingo-sama is!
It's impossible to take back Joker.
Captain Jack, shall we go back?
--Why?
--What?
You idiot! We're gonna do it!
What?!
Who do you think I am?!
Prepare to fire!
Hurry up!
That's the Beast Pirates!
They're such a formidable enemy to face!
They only have one ship.
Oh, boy...
Starboard!
Fire!
Hurry up! We're getting raided!
Pull up to them!
Jack-sama, Sheepshead-sama is back.
By the way, how do you guys know
so much about the Ponegliffs?
It all started with our master -
Kozuki Oden-sama who used to
have an interest in the stones.
Because...
Is it okay to tell them, dog?
Go ahead. You don't have
to hide anything from them.
You can tell them anything.
Did you say "Go ahead"?
What's that bossy attitude?!
I am their boss! You insolent dork!
How can you be ceremonious all of a sudden?!
Cut it out! Luffy!
Now, what's with that person - Kozuki Oden?
The Kozuki Family of the
Land of Wano was, in fact,
a clan of stonemasons that has quarried stones
and processed them for generations.
They are still highly skilled.
Stonemasons?
Yes. It goes way back, 800 years ago...
The Kozuki Clan invented an indestructible
book with their sophisticated skills.
That's what the Ponegliffs are!
What?!
The Kozuki Family?!
Were they the ones who made all
those Ponegliffs in the world?!
You made the stones that
Robin is looking for?!
Not me! It was my ancestors from way back!
Then, do you guys know
what's written on them?!
That hasn't been passed down fully
through the generations.
You can find it out by reading the stones.
The only thing that has been passed down
was how to read and write the ancient text.
However...
Unfortunately, that's...
Before it was passed down to Momonosuke-sama,
it was cut off at his father -
Kozuki Oden-sama's generation!
By "cut off," you mean
Momonosuke-san's father is...
Yes, Oden-sama is...
Wano...
Wa...
Oden wouldn't be "oden"
if it wasn't boiled!
Hey! It's okay if you
don't wanna talk about it!
Oden-sama was...
...executed!
By the shogun of the Land of Wano
and the pirate Kaido!
What?!
To save all of us retainers,
he met his fate!
By Kaido?!
Kaido...
And...
...Emperor Kaido's Beast Pirates are...
...still in the Land of Wano!
In the Land of Wano?
If you don't wanna talk about it,
that's okay but...
...why was your master executed?
You guys have been captured and targeted
because of that, haven't you?
Momo-chan...
Yes, you're right.
You could say it's a cardinal sin.
Kaido is trying to pull information from us!
The previous daimyo - Kozuki Oden-sama...
...traveled to the last island Raftel
with the King of the Pirates - Gol D. Roger
and witnessed the secret of the world!
What?!
Roger?
Momonosuke's father...
...went to Raftel with Gold Roger?!
Momonosuke remembers the pain
from when he last saw his father Oden!
When the earnest wish of the samurais
who left their home, the Land of Wano,
for a long rough journey is revealed,
Luffy makes a stunning decision
that shocks everybody!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Vow Between Two Men! Luffy
and Kozuki Momonosuke!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!