an island where their new
adventure will take place.
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new adventure will take place.
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests, a zou (elephant)
that has been alive for a millennium.
as its name suggests,
a zou (elephant) that has been alive for a millennium.
as its name suggests, a zou (elephant)
that has been alive for a millennium.
In the tall Whale Tree on
the back of the elephant...
What was hidden in the
giant Whale Tree was...
Now, we're gonna go
so can we have lots of food?!
...lay one of the Road Ponegliffs
that hint at the location of the hidden Raftel.
That red stone is called a Road Ponegliff!
Who is it?! Whose voice is that?!
The Kozuki Clan from the Land of Wano,
who created all the Ponegliffs...
The Straw Hats discovered that the Kozuki Clan
The Kozuki Family?!
If you're there...
Were they the ones who made all
those Ponegliffs in the world?!
...were Momonosuke's ancestors.
Hurry up!
However, knowledge of how
Who the hell are you?!
to read and write the ancient
text written on those stones...
Oden-sama was...
Give me an order!
...was cut off at Momonosuke's
father, Kozuki Oden's generation
...executed!
Give you an order to do what?!
before it was passed down to Momonosuke.
By the shogun of the Land of Wano
and the pirate Kaido!
Answer me! Who are you?!
That's... really bad!
Oden-sama was...
Let's join hands!
I gotta let everyone know!
...executed!
The words he left behind
were just one phrase!
"A Battle to Defend Zou!
Luffy and Zunesha!"
We're allies!
By the shogun of the Land of Wano
and the pirate Kaido!
Taking down Kaido and opening
up the Land of Wano.
"Open up the Land of Wano!"
To achieve the same goal,
By Kaido?!
"Save Zunesha!
The Straw Hat's Rescue Operation!"
they formed the Ninja-Pirate-Mink-Samurai
Alliance.
Are you just a figurehead, Momo?!
Why was your master executed?
You say it!
You guys have been captured and targeted
because of that, haven't you?
We met Tra-guy-kun and came to Zou
following the Vivre Card by chance
Yeah, yeah! You can take
as much food as you want!
I thought you were an important person!
You're a leader of these great men,
aren't you?!
Yes, you're right.
You could say it's a cardinal sin.
Come on!
Answer me! Who are you?!
and found the Road Ponegliff
which points the location of Raftel by accident.
Carrot. Show him the way to the food storage.
Hey, Luffy!
Who are you talking to?!
I want to bring down Kaido!
Okay!
The previous daimyo - Kozuki Oden-sama...
We can't hear anything!
Thanks!
But according to Crocus-san
at the Twin Capes,
I can only hear his voice!
We have a problem!
Let's join hands!
if you track logs,
every route will come to one in the end.
He's not listening to me
and I have no idea who it is!
...traveled to the last island Raftel
with the King of the Pirates - Gol D. Roger
We're allies!
Let me have Kaido's head though!
What's wrong, Musatobi?!
Don't tell me Jack is back again!
I'd always imagined that's Raftel.
and witnessed the secret of the world!
--What do you mean?!
--What the hell is going on?!
N-No! It's not about Jack!
One of Zunesha's forelegs is...
Thank you!
Yes, I understand.
Gol D. Roger...
Momonosuke's father...
If you're interested where logs will lead you,
go see it yourself.
All right!
It looks really terrible...
The wound is so large and deep...
Our objective is...
And Oden-sama as well.
I heard they experienced the same thing.
...went to Raftel with Gold Roger?!
...to kick Emperor Kaido's butt!
There is definitely a route on
which all of those three needles
They heard a loud voice
but they couldn't get it to respond.
It's miraculous that
he's still on his feet...
point in the same direction
- towards one specific place.
We're the Ninja-Pirate-Mink-Samurai Alliance!
What?
"A Vow Between Two Men!
Luffy and Kozuki Momonosuke!"
Gold Roger?
However, you-gara people have
already left on a journey
which lies beyond that point.
"The Legendary Journey!
The Dog and the Cat and the Pirate King!"
What? What do you mean?
You're supposed to find out about
something for the first time
Was your father one of
the Pirate King's crew?!
at the end of the route.
Momo's father was?!
Find out the truth about
the Ponegliffs and the ancient script.
Today is really a miraculous day!
Are we safe now?
Yeah! It is a great day!
Find out about the civilization
Momonosuke-sama...
Just run!
Those two even split the day in half
because they didn't want to see each other
Thank you!
that created those and the existence
of the hidden last island Raftel!
I'm sorry!
--I'm asking you, Momo!
--Luffy!
Everyone! Gather together in one spot!
Get away from buildings!
No, that's okay.
So this is what Jack left us with.
but now they're reconciled!
That is right!
He witnessed the secret of the world?
Probably, with Rayleigh-san too.
We must do something as soon as possible!
When Roger got there,
he had to do everything all over again.
Yeah, it's hard to believe
that such a day has come.
Say, Luffy...
Can we delay our departure a bit?
Yes. We know.
We learned the entirety of history.
Don't worry! You're on the right track.
They say Duke Dogstorm and Master Cat Viper
were once closest friends.
Do you wanna treat the elephant?
Just keep going!
Flower Shuriken!
Uh-huh!
However when they came back
from a long journey barely alive,
But for now, we have so many things
to do before fighting Kaido!
The entirety of history...
Even the 100-Year Void.
All right! Treat him quickly!
they were already deep in a feud.
Uh-huh!
We need to prepare.
No, that's so nice of you but...
Every time they came face-to-face,
they'd try to kill each other.
Like I told you before,
we're trying to recruit
--Wow! That's our ninja!
--That's our ninja!
Stop it!
I wonder what happened...
samurai who will fight with
us in the Land of Wano now!
What is it?! What's happening?!
We're the Ninja-Pirate-Mink-Samurai Alliance!
The 100-Year Void.
That was before I was born, right?
In the meantime, we've got
someone we need to see!
It's a century-long gap in
the history of the world.
Alliance?
Yes. Even Pedro and I
were small at that time.
But...
With this many people, it won't take long.
It's always good to have more reinforcements.
What's going on?
After that mysteriously dark period,
Yup! Count on us!
Since Straw Hat and the others came,
things are starting to go well in this country.
Who is it?
--That's right!
--Yes, yes!
He is the former 1st division commander of
the Whitebeard Pirates...
they say the World Government
was established.
I knew this is what we'd do.
Let's have a banquet to celebrate
the reconciliation of our kings today!
Since then, they have been ruling
the world for eight centuries.
Okay, let's do it!
Marco the Phoenix!
--Right, Chopper?
--Uh-huh!
First, we need tons of medicinal
herbs! That, I can get!
We can wake up and go to bed anytime we like!
The World Government strictly prohibits...
But the problem is the bandage.
"The Nightmare Returns!
The Invincible Jack's Fierce Attack!"
Cat.
...searching for the truth about
the 100-Year Void.
A bandage, huh?
How can we wrap his massive leg?
Yeah, I guess something is happening
to Zunesha.
I mean is there a bandage for an elephant
in the first place?
What happened in that century...
Momonosuke-sama!
We have to get away from here!
Our enemy is Kaido!
...is said to be revealed
by reading the Ponegliffs.
Dogstorm, Cat Viper!
Marco?
I think I can get a bandage.
Yeah.
Momo, Kin'emon, Kanjuro and the ninja!
Momonosuke-sama! What's wrong?!
--You sure?!
--Yes! Leave it to me!
In the past, in Ohara, the holy land
of archaeology where Robin is from,
Really?
And Tra-guy too!
We all join our hands to take down Kaido!
That's what we allied for!
--Momonosuke-sama!
--Are you okay?! Momonosuke-sama!
Thanks, Robin!
--I didn't expect to hear that name here.
--Marco... Marco...
Now, let's talk about how
we apply the bandage.
Professor Clover was studying the Ponegliffs
Momonosuke-sama! Momonosuke-sama!
Oh! So you guys are friendly with him!
That's good to know!
Hey, when you found out Jack was alive,
you said "Send out the ships," didn't you?
Guys! Don't ever bow your heads!
Nor get down on your knees!
to unearth the secret of the 100-Year Void.
Momonosuke-sama!
If he can back us up,
that's going to be a tremendous help!
I did.
An alliance means...
How do you launch them?
...friendship!
But he was wiped off the face of the earth
along with all the Ohara people.
Don't tell me you simply throw them down,
do you?
No but wait a minute.
In the event a year ago, they...
Not necessarily!
We're already allies
but there's one condition.
It's so high. They would break.
Well, don't expect too much.
Well, isn't that something you should've told us
before we agreed to join forces?!
Let me show you!
Even if we can find him,
there's only a little hope.
Everything that relates to the 100-Year Void
including that incident has been...
What is this?
Marco... Marco...
I'm sure I know him...
What is the condition?
One of our crew isn't with us now.
This place was affected by Jack's attack, too!
It's a mess!
...smothered by the World Government.
You must've met him
in the Paramount War at Marineford!
My head! My head... h-hurts!
Oh, it's about Sanji, isn't it?
Why do they want to keep a tight lid
on the history of the 100-Year Void?
Oh, Franky, look!
Sanji?
Marco... Who was it?
Well, a lot has happened...
I see. They move the ships
up and down with these.
Don't you remember?
Even those who know about the secret
keep their mouths closed.
He was Whitebeard's right hand!
This is...!
They say he ate a very
rare type of Devil Fruit!
Unlike other stuff, they look fine.
All right!
It's Jack!
Zoro! Brook! Kin'emon!
Fell some trees from the forest!
What? Rare?
What?! Big Mom?!
I haven't heard about this!
He looks like a pineapple.
I see!
Got it!
It happened while you were sleeping.
In order to get the secret of
the world out of you retainers,
Jack?!
Did you hear that, you all?!
I see.
That's why we didn't see Sanji-dono.
Oh, that guy!
Did he say Jack?!
Devote all of your strength
and save Zunesha with the Straw Hats!
Doflamingo and Caesar
who were tied to Kaido...
Fire!
...were trying to catch you guys.
I'll go and get him back
so don't go off to fight until then!
Yeah!
1st division commander - Marco!
We're really getting so much
help from you-teia guys.
That's right!
Thanks! You saved me!
Is that the condition?
If so, sure, we'll wait.
So do you guys know the secret of the world?!
How can we thank you for going this far...
Fire! Keep firing!
Don't mention it!
No, no! Don't mention it!
Yeah, he was really strong!
We'll definitely repay you for this somehow.
Thanks! In return, Sanji will be a big help!
Oh? Then why is there only a little hope?
Well... Actually we don't know it!
Oh no, please...
Go! Shoot it to death!
It's like getting help
from a thousand people!
Oh yeah! Say Wanda, do you have a sea chart
that shows the way to Big Mom's island?
--That's because there was this war.
--A war?
I'm worth two thousand people!
Oden-sama didn't want to
burden us with the secret.
Yeah, it was a major clash between the
Okay, okay.
A sea chart?
Jack is...
Jack is attacking the elephant!
I see. Sounds like he's pretty dependable
but will you be alright?
Yes. If you have one,
I wanna do my homework before the voyage.
remnants of the Whitebeard
Pirates led by Marco
We don't know anything!
and the Blackbeard Pirates!
I'd rather not have any trouble navigating.
Yes, but even if we knew it,
we wouldn't tell anybody.
You're talking about Emperor Big Mom!
There are five powerful-looking
ships at nine o'clock!
I'm not gonna fight her so I'll be fine.
I'll go with Lion Viper!
It's been a year since
the so-called Grudge War,
A sea chart...
I think we have one.
Whether we know or not,
we'll keep being hunted!
but we haven't heard about what happened to
the commanders yet.
--Zunesha is under attack?!
--As I thought, Jack wasn't dead.
Lion... Viper?
If so, the only option we have is to fight!
Momo! How do you know that?!
Lion Viper!
If he's alive,
I think I know where he would be.
I don't know... I just saw it!
Everyone!
Collect this herb! As much as you can!
You saw?
Understood! Dr. Chopper!
That's right!
It... It came to my mind...
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
Did they fight against Blackbeard?!
Although we are defeated soldiers,
we accept our disgrace
Oh! You can use it as medicine?
I didn't know that.
They did.
I'm scared!
and survive to this day for one reason!
Both sides had reinforcements.
It was quite a large-scale battle.
Momo...
The leaf part is for hemostasis
and the stem part is for sterilization.
Zunesha's cry and this quake...
Yes, it makes sense.
Just because of Oden-sama's words
that are etched in our minds!
Both parts work very well
but since it's a rare herb,
Those words are the reason we live!
Damn Jack!
How dare he attack Zunesha!
you don't often see it in encyclopedias.
I see! That's why...
But if he's alive, that's good for us!
Let's fight back!
The same here.
There are so many here so that's great!
Uh-huh.
Guardians!
Dr. Chopper, is there
anything you don't know?
Wh-What are those words?
--Musketeers!
--Yes, sir!
The words he left behind
were just one phrase!
Send out the ships!
Return fire against Jack on the water!
And Marco and the others
suffered a crushing defeat.
Okay!
Get to the ships! At full speed!
It's going well!
Blackbeard came to be recognized
as one of the Four Emperors after the war.
One, two!
"Open up the Land of Wano!"
Let's defeat Jack this time!
Here we go!
There!
I didn't know that.
Damn, Blackbeard!
Are you ready?
--Yes!
--We are!
That was a major incident!
What do they mean by "open up"?
Mil Fleurs!
Target confirmed, Jack-sama!
The Land of Wano is closed off to the world.
You really have no idea about
what had happened
Yeah, I see it. You don't have to tell me.
Which means no one's allowed
to leave the country
while you were under training.
Hands came out!
Needlewoman!
Damn. I can't believe I came back here.
Jimbei told me.
or enter from the outside,
Momonosuke-sama!
In the Paramount War,
but if they open up, that means
they'll interact with other countries.
--Hang on! Don't move!
--Watch out for buildings!
after I passed out,
the Whitebeard Pirates saved my life.
Sheepshead.
The sheets have been sewn together!
"Raizo wasn't there."
It's a pity that, although we
I didn't expect you to come back saying that.
There are so many hands! Cool!
should have been shields
for our master Oden-sama,
We'll repeat this over and over
to make it one big bandage.
we were saved by him instead
and we brought shame to ourselves!
I... I am so sorry, sir...
--Now, lay them side by side again.
--Okay!
I'm not gonna let you kill him!
This is painful!
The Minks have a strong vital force.
Okay! It's going well here too!
Move out of my way!
What if those who escaped the gas
were able to treat the others who passed out?
What we have to do now is
If I collapse,
Alright, let's begin.
to put our lives on the
line and avenge our master!
The war is not over yet!
it would put all of you in danger!
We need to kill the shogun
who stole the Land of Wano
Keep your mouth shut, Sheepshead-sama!
Okay, I've chopped them.
and open the closed country to the world!
If he finds out that not
only are the Minks alive
Take Ace's brother with you, Jimbei!
but also that we were kicked
off the island by someone...
That's our wish!
All right!
--Wow! When did he do that?!
--That was awesome, Baron Corpse!
When you start killing someone,
don't stop until he dies!
Straw Hat's life is how
Ace's life will live on!
The Land of Wano is almost
entirely under the control
Mercy will only cause
the messy business of revenge!
of the shogun and Kaido who've joined forces.
Not again!
We will protect him at any cost
on behalf of Ace!
Garchu, Baron Corpse!
Our friends are trying to
muster dissidents there now
You don't need to worry!
Hey, please...
If we let him die,
The Minks are weakening anyway.
If we make a raid, they'll just...
Never mind.
Just do whatever you want.
but they're still vastly outnumbered by
the enemy's great army!
it's a dishonor to the Whitebeard Pirates!
Okay, it's my turn!
That's not necessary.
The one behind the voice is...
That's cool too, Kin'emon!
There's no chance to win!
...this...
So that's what's happening there.
I wanna see him again and thank him.
But don't set the wood on fire!
...elephant!
So just like Kin'emon,
we need time to prepare too.
I-Is that ninpo?
Momo-chan...
Oh no! It's not.
We'll kill the giant elephant!
Okay, got it!
Then, let's split up for now!
Kill the elephant? But it's massive!
We will round up allies
and plot a strategy in the Land of Wano.
But we have to win!
How do we do that?!
Thus, to look for someone
who will fight with us,
Are you gonna be okay there?
I thought you guys are being
targeted by the shogun.
Hey! Take those to Franky now...
we set out to the sea!
We're fully aware of the risk.
The one behind the voice is...
First, we were heading for Zou!
...this...
But we're worried about our comrades there.
...elephant!
Where did they all go?!
Because to fight against the Beast Pirates,
The Land of Wano is occupied by Kaido now,
right?
we surely needed the help of
Minks, our closest allies.
You mean Zunesha?!
It's the other way around.
Momonosuke-sama! What's going on?!
Your chances of encountering the
Beast Pirates are high and isn't it
You walked off on your own, Zoro-ya.
Momo-chan?
hard to even enter the country?
Yes, the Kozuki Clan and the Minks...
Are you that ridiculously terrible
with directions?
Can't you do something with your ninjutsu?
...have a special bond from way back,
which means whatever happens,
Again!
It'd be hard to use it against everyone.
we'll share the same fate!
It's Shanks!
Boo! Boo! You stray swordsman!
I see.
Don't tell me you know him, Cat Viper.
A long time ago, I...
More than anything, the dog and I are
Oden-sama's direct retainers.
If you come on our submarine,
you'll be safe while traveling.
Yes, I know him!
"Red-Haired" Shanks, right?
Shut up! I can carry them on my own!
Then you'll have no problem, will you?!
Ever since the day Raizo arrived here,
all of our warriors were prepared!
Oh, are you sure, Law-dono?!
I see!
No wonder that straw hat looks familiar!
A long time ago,
the elephant committed a crime...
--We'd like that!
--Please take us!
That's a waste of time.
We don't want you to get lost again.
And...
But when we actually fought,
Damn you! How could you say...
Oh, does it?!
And now... all he is
allowed... to do is... walk.
Shambles!
Dogstorm said that too!
Do you all know Shanks?!
...if you know a place to hide
on the island, you'll be alright.
What? What?!
it turned out like this against Jack's unit
which was just a part of Kaido's army!
Did he disappear?!
Yes because both the cat and I were once
traveling on Roger's ship.
I'll go look for Marco with my subordinates.
He has been... obeying that order.
Our final targets are the shogun and Kaido.
How disappointing.
If Kin'emon and the others
are headed there first,
That bastard...
What?!
Thus...
Were you guys the Pirate King's crewmembers?!
What a shame.
we'd better meet up in the Land of Wano.
Hey! But that's because they
used that dirty weapon!
It's a little old. Does it help?
What's going on?
Let's make Kin'emon's Vivre Card.
Yeah, it's good enough.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
Crewmembers...
Well, you can put it that way too but...
Okay! It's a deal!
No one could've expected
they'd use the poison gas!
Uh-huh, understood.
Big Mom's headquarters is down this way.
Don't get lost, guys.
...we boarded many ships
as Oden-sama's attendants.
If there were a judge to call foul and we'd win,
maybe that would work, but...
Shoot it up! Blow it away!
Look who's talking.
Unfortunately, we don't
have a map of the island.
There he is! Raizo-dono!
Even when we were traveling
on Whitebeard's Moby Dick.
I see. If we travel at normal speed,
it'll take more than a week.
No matter how dirty they play,
this is our country!
Good to see you again!
Thus, give me permission for once!
What?
Maybe.
We should've won!
And when Oden-sama was recruited by Roger,
we were always by his side...
I'm glad that you're okay!
We gotta get going!
We have to make it in time for the tea party!
But we won't let it happen again!
We won't repeat the same failure!
Finish it off! Kill the elephant!
Raizo-san!
Whoa, wait, wait! Whitebeard?!
To return the favor...
We have an ace up our sleeve too.
Y-You guys...?
To help them-gara make it
to Big Mom's island safely...
If we fight again, we'll show them
the true power of the Mink Tribe!
--Let's have a celebratory banquet.
--It's ready!
Yes. We were still young...
We have no choice but to travel with them!
The true power?
...just like the apprentices
such as Shanks and Buggy.
Yes! We're not gonna just back down!
A celebratory banquet?
What are we celebrating?!
That worked! It's gonna collapse!
Hell yeah!
Oh, there's a small isolated island here.
You're right. It's as tiny as a rice grain!
Not even an ant could live on such an island!
Hey, wait! Stop! Stop!
Raizo-san's safety and...
Then, take your injury more seriously!
I'm completely lost! Um...
Otherwise, you won't be able
to exercise that true power!
The reconciliation of the two kings and...
No, no! It looks that way
because this is a sea chart.
But the two of us didn't
go to Raftel with them.
It'd be nice if they have a restaurant there!
I know.
The Kozuki Clan for reuniting safely!
No drinking until you're fully recovered!
I don't know about that!
I said "Wait a minute"!
That's boring...
Oh my!
I mean when did you guys get here?!
Order me!
No baths either!
Um, first, on Whitebeard's ship,
To fight!
Alright! Everything's going well!
there was Oden, the dog and the cat.
Boy...
ODEN
Wh-What are you talking about?!
Grab on to something! Anything is fine!
And then Oden was recruited by Roger
and you three switched to Roger's ship.
You damn Minks!
Now, we have a favor to ask, Luffy-dono!
Yeah, I remember!
We were having so much fun at that time!
Sorry for locking you up!
And you too, Law-dono!
We wanted to save you-gara
from Jack and the others!
Is that...?!
For once!
I know it's presumptuous of me to ask
you a favor after you saved my life
Raizo-san!
We tied up your hands - did we hurt you?
but I've been impressed by
how strong you guys are!
Give me permission!
Raizo-san!
Don't ask me about my hands!
Since we are fated to share the same purpose,
Oh, the species, geographical features, and climates
that I'd never seen!
You guys are way more wounded than I am!
will you help us fight to kill
the shogun of the Land of Wano
The elephant is... asking for permission!
The sea of clouds in the sky!
He needs someone to... order him to fight!
and Emperor Kaido?!
How annoying!
Oh, they're finally here!
The island that floats undersea!
The sunlight!
Zunesha does?!
Please! I'm begging you, Luffy-dono!
Every day, I was very excited!
I'm begging you too!
One, two!
Kin'emon! Kanjuro!
What am I supposed to do?!
Those good old adventurous days!
Ninpo!
Alright, let's do it!
I-love-you Technique!
Oh! Yes! Who can ask for more?!
Momo!
You tell him!
I have a feeling that your voice will reach him!
You two were trying to kill each other earlier,
weren't you?
Those samurai and the Minks!
They'll be a big help for us too!
Raizo-dono!
Then, Kin'emon, were you guys traveling
on Whitebeard's ship too?
But...
Raizo-dono!
Swoosh!
If they bring down the elephant,
we'll all end up in the sea!
We were gonna fight Kaido sooner or later!
We gotta jump at this chance!
Nin! Nin! Nin! Nin!
Oh, how cool is that?!
No, we stayed in the Land of Wano
the whole time.
But how loud should I be...
It's beautifully done! They look brand-new!
They even have a ninja, Luffy!
Instead, we were trying
desperately to stop Oden-sama
Just shout it out!
Or the elephant's gonna die!
It barely looks like the work of a human!
from getting on board a pirate ship!
What? You were?
Uh-huh, as we mentioned earlier,
That's because I'm a super cyborg shipwright
who's beyond human understanding!
the Land of Wano is closed off
from the world and interacting
Hey, Franky! The medicine is prepared!
with other countries is prohibited.
Please help us!
In the closed-off nation,
even leaving the country is a crime.
A little more to go!
The bandages are completed too!
On the other hand, Oden-sama was a heretic
Where's Robin?
She's making extra bandages to change later.
All right! Let's have a banquet!
who had doubts about the law of the country.
I refuse!
How thoughtful! That's our Robin!
Hurry up, Momo!
The elephant's really gonna die!
We became acquainted with
Whitebeard, Roger and the
Do it now!
Laying the tracks is completed too!
others when they landed on the Land of Wano.
They were loyal to others
and we didn't think they were particularly bad people.
Banquet! Banquet! Banquet! Banquet! Banquet!
But I'd never heard of a daimyo
getting aboard a pirate ship so as his retainer...
All right, guys!
Bind the gondolas to the ropes
and get on board!
Wh-What?!
Wh-What did you just say?!
Yeah!
So anyway, you all know Shanks!
And Rayleigh as well?!
I refuse!
Why?! We've been traveling together!
Yes, of course!
I thought so!
Luffy-dono!
What's wrong, Nami?
I refuse!
Wait, Luffy!
Don't!
I see!
It's a Silent Supercell!
We've already had a banquet!
Tell me you're kidding!
What's that?
Let's get going!
It's gonna be too late to save Sanji-kun!
Why can't you get it?!
Can I ask something?
It's a massive thundercloud that appears suddenly
without warning.
Think about it!
We have to join hands!
If you got on board Roger's ship,
Elephant!!
What?! Are you coming?!
It'll cause a severe storm.
Even if it breezes by, it'll wreak enormous havoc!
it must've been the Oro Jackson which was
built by my shipwright teacher Tom-san!
Are you out of your mind?!
Of course, I'm coming with you!
I feel responsible.
Just a moment! Forget about what he said!
We'll teach him a lesson!
What?!
Besides, do you think you can travel the sea
Luffy! Tell them to stop the elephant's treatment!
We gotta evacuate everybody!
What?!
Are you the shipwright Tom's pupil?!
Don't give up, elephant!
You can't fall down!
of the New World without a navigator?
Stop!
Wind it up!
Luffy, think again!
About assisting that Roger guy...
This will make you less of a man!
Make Jack...
I'm coming too! Pekoms is heavily injured!
Down! Down!
I'm resolutely proud of it!
Wait!
Make Jack go away!!
Okay, stop!
He needs a doctor!
Yeah, I'm Tom-san's pupil!
I think Luffy has a point there.
Plus,
Super!
who is going to play music
when you guys feel down?
Nami?!
Um, can I go next?
Then, I bet you know Crocus the ship doctor...
I'm gonna go...
Let's go and meet Master Cat Viper
...negotiate!
Wait, Brook.
That's not it! No!
Sorry to interrupt you.
I gotta check something with them.
Boy, it's a terrible wound!
It is.
Who needs that?
Hey! Don't exclude me!
I'm sure it's unbearably painful,
but he's staying calm and letting us treat him.
Are you just a figurehead, Momo?!
We both allowed them take Sanji-san!
Understood!
Cut it out! He's only a child!
Okay, okay, you're doing great!
It won't be long!
Kin'emon, do you mind if I take them with me?
You said the four Road Ponegliffs will
show us the way to Raftel, right?
You say it!
I thought you were an important person!
You don't need my permission!
They're your crew!
I bet Zunesha senses Dr. Chopper's
passion to cure him like we do.
You're a leader of these
great men, aren't you?!
I'm starting to worry about the route.
And no one can stop someone
who is trying to save his friend!
What's going on?!
Look.
It'd be so nice if I could
study medical care under him.
I wish I could come along!
Are you gonna just cry?!
The needles on the Log Pose!
I'm in debt to Sanji-dono!
Normally, we choose our next destination
looking at where these three needles point
It's done here! Apply the bandage!
I'm sorry!
What happened?
Now it's getting hard to sneak in.
Got it! Hey!
Move the gondola down slowly!
but we're not tracking them now.
Is it okay?!
Get out of there as soon as
you screw up the wedding!
Roger!
Wind it up!
We're gonna go along with Kin'emon
so you take care of Sanji!
--Uh-huh!
--Count on us!
Oh, Luffy.
How could you make him cry like that?!
Don't be harsh to an eight-year old!
Robin, are you gonna go with them?!
In case you find a Ponegliff,
can you take a rubbing for me?
Luffy-san. Generally, heirs
don't necessarily stand
Look.
--Okay!
--So light-hearted!
on their feet until they're fully grown.
The needles on the Log Pose!
We're not tracking them now. Is it okay?!
--What the hell?!
--The elephant moved suddenly!
I'll do research on the Ponegliff that Kaido has
in the Land of Wano too.
--Oh no! We can't make it in time like this!
--I'll go first!
If adults assist them properly...
Great!
H-Hey, Nami?
Alright! Is that all for now?
Oh, Momonosuke-san?
--Carrot! Go assist Luffy!
--Okay!
We met Tra-guy-kun
and came to Zou following the Vivre Card by chance
Momonosuke-sama...
and found the Road Ponegliff
which points the location of Raftel by accident.
--Hang on tight!
--Don't get shaken off!
Let's have a banquet!
But according to Crocus-san
at the Twin Capes,
Yes, come here, Momo-chan.
if you track logs,
every route will come to one in the end.
I'm sorry for what our stupid
captain said to you...
The wind is so strong!
If nothing is done, the gondolas will...
I'd always imagined that's Raftel.
It's not looking good. With this much
wind, the tracks and the ropes will...
Hm? What's wrong?
Father...
What is it?!
Pull us up now!
I...
Oh, Crocus!
I haven't seen him for a long time!
What is this force?
Is that...
I'm gonna be blown off!
Father!
How is he doing?!
What?! What?!
He was fine!
But that was two years ago!
Luffy! This way!
You mean the old man who was with Laboon,
right?
What is it gonna do?!
There!
Crocus the ship doctor! He-gara was looking for
some pirate group back in those days.
You can't see it all!
And that's how the world is, Momonosuke!
Oh, that was my group -
the whole crew is dead!
Green Star - Cushion Vine!
Trunk!
What?!
Hey! Listen!
I'm talking about something important!
Usopp!
Yes, I understand.
Father, I...
If you're interested where logs will lead you,
go see it yourself.
We're surrounded!
There is definitely a route on which
all of those three needles point
Mother!
--Again!
--It's going the other way now.
in the same direction -
towards one specific place.
Ready the flaming arrows!
--This is it...
--Hang on!
Run! There must be a way out!
However, you-gara people have
already left on a journey
Everyone! Run!
Father...
which lies beyond that point.
Grab on!
What? What do you mean?
Jack-sama, our ship has
been thrown into the air!
Luffy!
You're supposed to find out about something
for the first time at the end of the route.
That was close!
You're okay now! Move slowly!
The whole island is shaking!
It's out of control!
Find out the truth about
the Ponegliffs and the ancient script.
Zunesha is crying out!
What's going on?!
Luffy! I...
Who's Zunesha?!
Find out about the civilization
Huh? You're standing on it!
that created those and the existence
of the hidden last island Raftel!
Oh! It's the elephant's name!
It's a big quake!
It's never happened before!
Your father is...
When Roger got there,
he had to do everything all over again.
...a foolish lord!
It stopped.
Who is it?! Whose voice is that?!
Crocus was also part of the Pirate King's crew.
He is one of those who know everything.
Luffy!
I'm relieved! Way to go, Luffy!
He wouldn't tell a lie
unless he doesn't like you-gara guys.
But he can't hold out forever!
We gotta lift everyone up now!
I want to bring down Kaido!
And the name of the island at the end of
the route is... Raftel.
Cien Fleurs - Spider Net!
He was an enemy to my parents!
It's the last point on the Grand Line.
Oh no!
He killed my mother too!
The only one in history who confirmed
that island is the King of the Pirates.
Room!
Shambles!
I wish to grow up
and become strong quickly
It's a legendary island.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Now, everyone, climb up!
Captain!
Beyond the end of the route...
Run! It's gonna collapse!
and avenge my father and mother!
--We're okay now!
--Robin!
Strong Right!
I want to protect all my retainers too!
Get away from the building!
C-Climb now!
We're already on a journey beyond the end?
Momonosuke-sama!
What a relief!
Oh...
--Hold onto the tree!
--Okay!
Oh no-saru!
It's enough to know that you feel that way!
Oh, that was a hell of a storm.
You-gara got older and weepy.
This way!
Shut up!
But because my body's still small,
I can't do that!
Let's get to work!
Hurry up now!
Thank you!
Yeah!
Who is it?! Who's talking?!
That's why I want you to fight with me!
Here we are!
Great! It hasn't collapsed!
Food!
I'm begging you!
--There are tons of it!
--But it's so messy...
Please...
My bone's gonna break, break, break!
It doesn't matter if it's messy.
It's still food!
My bones go crack, crack, crack, crack!
I got it!
--You guys are awesome, Luffy!
--Yeah?
I got it!
Momonosuke-sama! Are you hurt?!
Yes! You have Dr. Chopper
who can cure anything,
I didn't need to worry.
We weren't wandering off of the route.
and you have Nami the navigator
who can predict weather like a prophet!
Let's join hands!
What's happening to Zunesha?!
I was just confused by the glimpses of the truth
we hadn't yet discovered.
It quieted down.
Baron Corpse is a famous musician,
isn't he?
What happened?!
We're allies!
I don't know. I don't see anything
or hear the voice now.
Yeah.
Let me have Kaido's head though!
And you have...
...God Usopp who has 8,000 followers,
As Crocus-san said,
the logs are leading us to Raftel for sure!
You too, Luffy?
and Robot Franky
who is like a jack in the box!
If you're there...
Yeah, come to think of it,
I don't hear anything now.
You have the great-but-tends-to-stray
swordsman Zoro
Leading us to the way to Raftel
which lies beyond the end of the route!
Wh-Who is it?!
and a good sewer Robin who
can sprout many hands!
Momonosuke-sama, are you okay?!
--I hear the voice again!
--Momonosuke-sama!
Thank you! Thank you!
Robin is an archaeologist!
She's very smart!
I'm not surprised.
It'd been so intense all this time.
Luffy, what's wrong?!
Oh, is she?!
"What's wrong"?!
You hear it too, right?!
You're doing it wrong!
You gotta grab tight! Like this!
And Sanji. He saved the whole country
and made delicious soup for us!
This is serious-saru!
Huh?! Hear what?!
Can't you hear it?!
This is serious-saru!
I have... I have a report-saru!
Thank you!
--No way!
--Can he-gara hear it too?!
He's such a good cook!
With more energy!
The logs weren't lying!
Hurry up!
And the awesome captain who brings together
those awesome members - Luffy!
--But I am grabbing your hand...
--No, do this!
Are you a navigator?
You're very dependable.
Who the hell are you?!
It's the loudest ever!
He's right. This is how it
should be.
Don't worry! You're on the right track.
Oh, crap! The backpack is already full!
I should've brought a bigger one!
Fire!
Our leaders are bonded! This is great!
Just keep going!
Oh, really?!
So Zunesha used his own trunk?
Say, Luffy,
can I come along with you guys...
Uh-huh!
Hey, hey! I don't know what
you guys are talking about
Straw Hat-ya.
That's right-saru! With a single blow!
I forgot!
Didn't you have to ask me first?
but don't you think our navigator's amazing?!
This elephant is strong.
What is it?
--It's cool, right?
--Yeah, but...
It's starting to work!
Am I dependable? Yes, I'm sure I am!
Lion Viper!
I'm so relieved!
I can't believe it.
I'd never thought Zunesha has a mind of his own.
Lion...
No wonder.
Whew, I almost left without him!
Yeah! The navigator of the next Pirate King!
We have to reflect on what we were doing.
Normal elephants are panicked
by just one bee.
Sorry to ask you this but
could you take this to the gate for me?
Furthermore, we can even
communicate with him.
How cool is that!
We were treating him as a child
but he is the head of the Kozuki Clan.
Take a good look at its body.
Don't hit me! That hurts!
Did Oden-sama know
about Momonosuke-sama's ability?
That's where our ship is!
I'll go pick him up and be there soon too!
If it's really been living for a millennium,
its skin must've gotten weak!
We were forgetting about that
and thinking we have to protect him.
But...
Luffy...
Thanks! See ya!
It seems you-gara guys have been having fun
all this time.
Hey, Jack is a Devil Fruit eater, right?
If he fell into the water, he must be...
Gee...
Even though that was too harsh
on an eight-year old,
no one treats Momonosuke-sama
as a whole man...
Yeah, that means he's dead!
One, two!
Is it a living legend?
No! It's just an old animal!
Alright! That's good!
...like Luffy-dono!
Hey!
A little more to go! You can do it!
Uh-huh! You're right!
What's wrong?
You guys still look serious.
Concentrate fire on its left foreleg!
Now I know why you guys admire him so much.
We're stunned at this sudden occurrence.
Now I think we can finish this.
Anyway, you guys are tied
to so many legends and
More volleys!
First, we gotta find out
how Jack was able to get here.
I was worried at one point.
I feel dizzy like when I met Rayleigh.
Thank you very much, you-gara all!
Otherwise, this place will no longer be safe.
All right! Guys! Gather up!
I met Roger and the others too
Thank you, Robin!
Thank you!
I see. Well, good luck with that.
It'd be cool if this elephant becomes our ally.
but I don't remember clearly
because I was so young.
That's not enough! Get out of my way!
Oh, so you don't remember clearly...
You brave ones who saved our country
not only once but twice!
That's easy for you to say.
Our objective is...
I mean, no way! Roger died
more than two decades ago!
Now, we're gonna go
so can we have lots of food?!
Keep shooting!
Who are you talking about?!
Thank you, thank you,
thank you very much!
If we can make it bend its knees
and it brings its face closer,
...to kick Emperor Kaido's butt!
So much had happened on Oden-sama's journey.
we can finish it off as we like!
I'll tell you all about it sometime.
That's too much.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
We're the Ninja-Pirate-Mink-Samurai Alliance!
But for now, we have so many things to do
before fighting Kaido!
I'd like to gouge its eyes out
and cut out its tongue!
Ring, ring, ring...
We need to prepare.
Maybe we can cut its stomach up from within!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Like I told you before, we're
trying to recruit samurai
The sea is beautiful.
I wanna sail out to sea even just once.
who will fight with us
in the Land of Wano now!
Clank.
Hurry!
What do you want?
In the meantime, we've got
someone we need to see!
Give me an order!
That's too long!
They say that communication with Jack
has been lost suddenly!
It's always good to have more reinforcements.
Yeah, I guess I have no choice!
Is "Ninja" necessary?
If you are there!
Of course, it is!
Who is it?
Kaido-san!
Give you an order to do what?!
Okay, okay.
This is for you, Bariete.
He is the former 1st division commander of
the Whitebeard Pirates...
Answer me! Who are you?!
Hey!
Lion Viper!
Marco the Phoenix!
Hey!
A big incident involving Blackbeard and
The giant elephant and
the ultra-giant elephant!
In preparation for taking down Kaido,
In their early days, Dogstorm and Cat Viper
Dr. Chopper takes action to save Zunesha!
Zoro and the others first
head for the Land of Wano!
Jack and Zunesha's greatest-ever
battle is now on!
set out to sea, led by Kozuki Oden!
Marco the Phoenix that shook
the world is now revealed!
Meanwhile, Luffy sets out
for the Whole Cake Island
Using Zoro and Brook's sword skills,
Robin's Flower-Flower Fruit ability,
When their historic ties to
the legendary men
When Luffy and the others are about to
When Luffy and Momonosuke hear
the mysterious voice again
where Big Mom resides to take back Sanji!
take to sea in order
to round up allies,
who created an era come to light,
and Usopp and Franky's techniques,
in the country of Zou, submerged in chaos,
They finally set sail on the sea where
Jack's unsinkable fleet comes to attack!
the road to the Great Treasure of
an unprecedented major
treatment project begins!
an earth-shattering blow
with a howl strikes the sea of the New World!
the Four Emperors reign! A dramatic
new adventure now begins!
One Piece will be
shown to the Straw Hats!
Luffy and his friends are in trouble!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Save Zunesha! The Straw
Hat's Rescue Operation!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Legendary Journey!
The Dog and the Cat and the Pirate King!"
"The Nightmare Returns! The
Invincible Jack's Fierce Attack!"
"Saying Goodbye and Descending from the
Elephant! Setting Out to Take Back Sanji!"
"A Battle to Defend Zou! Luffy and Zunesha!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!