I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new
adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests, a zou (elephant)
that has been alive for a millennium.
What was hidden in the
giant Whale Tree was...
That red stone is called a Road Ponegliff!
The Kozuki Family?!
Were they the ones who made all
those Ponegliffs in the world?!
Oden-sama was...
...executed!
By the shogun of the Land of Wano
and the pirate Kaido!
By Kaido?!
Why was your master executed?
You guys have been captured and targeted
because of that, haven't you?
Yes, you're right.
You could say it's a cardinal sin.
The previous daimyo - Kozuki Oden-sama...
...traveled to the last island Raftel
with the King of the Pirates - Gol D. Roger
and witnessed the secret of the world!
Momonosuke's father...
...went to Raftel with Gold Roger?!
"A Vow Between Two Men!
Luffy and Kozuki Momonosuke!"
Was your father one of
the Pirate King's crew?!
Momo's father was?!
Momonosuke-sama...
--I'm asking you, Momo!
--Luffy!
That is right!
He witnessed the secret of the world?
Probably, with Rayleigh-san too.
Yes. We know.
We learned the entirety of history.
The entirety of history...
Even the 100-Year Void.
The 100-Year Void.
It's a century-long gap in
the history of the world.
After that mysteriously dark period,
they say the World Government
was established.
Since then, they have been ruling
the world for eight centuries.
The World Government strictly prohibits...
...searching for the truth about
the 100-Year Void.
What happened in that century...
...is said to be revealed
by reading the Ponegliffs.
In the past, in Ohara, the holy land
of archaeology where Robin is from,
Professor Clover was studying the Ponegliffs
to unearth the secret of the 100-Year Void.
But he was wiped off the face of the earth
along with all the Ohara people.
Everything that relates to the 100-Year Void
including that incident has been...
...smothered by the World Government.
Why do they want to keep a tight lid
on the history of the 100-Year Void?
Even those who know about the secret
keep their mouths closed.
I see!
In order to get the secret of
the world out of you retainers,
Doflamingo and Caesar
who were tied to Kaido...
...were trying to catch you guys.
That's right!
So do you guys know the secret of the world?!
Well... Actually we don't know it!
Oden-sama didn't want to
burden us with the secret.
We don't know anything!
Yes, but even if we knew it,
we wouldn't tell anybody.
Whether we know or not,
we'll keep being hunted!
If so, the only option we have is to fight!
That's right!
Although we are defeated soldiers,
we accept our disgrace
and survive to this day for one reason!
Just because of Oden-sama's words
that are etched in our minds!
Those words are the reason we live!
The same here.
Uh-huh.
Wh-What are those words?
The words he left behind
were just one phrase!
"Open up the Land of Wano!"
What do they mean by "open up"?
The Land of Wano is closed off to the world.
Which means no one's allowed
to leave the country
or enter from the outside,
but if they open up, that means
they'll interact with other countries.
It's a pity that, although we
should have been shields
for our master Oden-sama,
we were saved by him instead
and we brought shame to ourselves!
What we have to do now is
to put our lives on the
line and avenge our master!
We need to kill the shogun
who stole the Land of Wano
and open the closed country to the world!
That's our wish!
The Land of Wano is almost
entirely under the control
of the shogun and Kaido who've joined forces.
Our friends are trying to
muster dissidents there now
but they're still vastly outnumbered by
the enemy's great army!
There's no chance to win!
So that's what's happening there.
Momo-chan...
But we have to win!
Thus, to look for someone
who will fight with us,
we set out to the sea!
First, we were heading for Zou!
Because to fight against the Beast Pirates,
we surely needed the help of
Minks, our closest allies.
Yes, the Kozuki Clan and the Minks...
...have a special bond from way back,
which means whatever happens,
we'll share the same fate!
More than anything, the dog and I are
Oden-sama's direct retainers.
Ever since the day Raizo arrived here,
all of our warriors were prepared!
But when we actually fought,
it turned out like this against Jack's unit
which was just a part of Kaido's army!
How disappointing.
What a shame.
Hey! But that's because they
used that dirty weapon!
No one could've expected
they'd use the poison gas!
If there were a judge to call foul and we'd win,
maybe that would work, but...
No matter how dirty they play,
this is our country!
We should've won!
But we won't let it happen again!
We won't repeat the same failure!
We have an ace up our sleeve too.
If we fight again, we'll show them
the true power of the Mink Tribe!
The true power?
Yes! We're not gonna just back down!
Then, take your injury more seriously!
Otherwise, you won't be able
to exercise that true power!
I know.
No drinking until you're fully recovered!
That's boring...
No baths either!
Now, we have a favor to ask, Luffy-dono!
And you too, Law-dono!
I know it's presumptuous of me to ask
you a favor after you saved my life
but I've been impressed by
how strong you guys are!
Since we are fated to share the same purpose,
will you help us fight to kill
the shogun of the Land of Wano
and Emperor Kaido?!
Please! I'm begging you, Luffy-dono!
I'm begging you too!
Oh! Yes! Who can ask for more?!
Those samurai and the Minks!
They'll be a big help for us too!
We were gonna fight Kaido sooner or later!
We gotta jump at this chance!
They even have a ninja, Luffy!
Please help us!
I refuse!
Wh-What?!
Wh-What did you just say?!
I refuse!
Why?! We've been traveling together!
Luffy-dono!
I refuse!
Don't!
Tell me you're kidding!
Why can't you get it?!
Think about it!
We have to join hands!
Are you out of your mind?!
Just a moment! Forget about what he said!
We'll teach him a lesson!
Stop!
Luffy, think again!
This will make you less of a man!
Wait!
I think Luffy has a point there.
Nami?!
I'm gonna go...
...negotiate!
That's not it! No!
Are you just a figurehead, Momo?!
Cut it out! He's only a child!
You say it!
I thought you were an important person!
You're a leader of these
great men, aren't you?!
Are you gonna just cry?!
How could you make him cry like that?!
Don't be harsh to an eight-year old!
Luffy-san. Generally, heirs
don't necessarily stand
on their feet until they're fully grown.
If adults assist them properly...
Oh, Momonosuke-san?
Momonosuke-sama...
Yes, come here, Momo-chan.
I'm sorry for what our stupid
captain said to you...
Father...
I...
Father!
You can't see it all!
And that's how the world is, Momonosuke!
Father, I...
We're surrounded!
Mother!
Ready the flaming arrows!
Run! There must be a way out!
Everyone! Run!
Father...
Luffy! I...
Your father is...
...a foolish lord!
I want to bring down Kaido!
He was an enemy to my parents!
He killed my mother too!
I wish to grow up
and become strong quickly
and avenge my father and mother!
I want to protect all my retainers too!
Momonosuke-sama!
It's enough to know that you feel that way!
You-gara got older and weepy.
Shut up!
But because my body's still small,
I can't do that!
That's why I want you to fight with me!
I'm begging you!
Please...
I got it!
Let's join hands!
We're allies!
Let me have Kaido's head though!
Thank you! Thank you!
You're doing it wrong!
You gotta grab tight! Like this!
Thank you!
With more energy!
--But I am grabbing your hand...
--No, do this!
He's right. This is how it
should be.
Our leaders are bonded! This is great!
Straw Hat-ya.
Didn't you have to ask me first?
--It's cool, right?
--Yeah, but...
I'm so relieved!
We have to reflect on what we were doing.
We were treating him as a child
but he is the head of the Kozuki Clan.
We were forgetting about that
and thinking we have to protect him.
Even though that was too harsh
on an eight-year old,
no one treats Momonosuke-sama
as a whole man...
...like Luffy-dono!
Uh-huh! You're right!
Now I know why you guys admire him so much.
All right! Guys! Gather up!
Our objective is...
...to kick Emperor Kaido's butt!
We're the Ninja-Pirate-Mink-Samurai Alliance!
That's too long!
Is "Ninja" necessary?
Of course, it is!
Okay, okay.
In their early days, Dogstorm and Cat Viper
set out to sea, led by Kozuki Oden!
When their historic ties to
the legendary men
who created an era come to light,
the road to the Great Treasure of
One Piece will be
shown to the Straw Hats!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Legendary Journey!
The Dog and the Cat and the Pirate King!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!