I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests,
a zou (elephant) that has been alive for a millennium.
In the tall Whale Tree on
the back of the elephant...
...lay one of the Road Ponegliffs
that hint at the location of the hidden Raftel.
The Straw Hats discovered that the Kozuki Clan
who created all the Ponegliffs...
...were Momonosuke's ancestors.
Oden-sama was...
...executed!
By the shogun of the Land of Wano
and the pirate Kaido!
The words he left behind
were just one phrase!
"Open up the Land of Wano!"
Are you just a figurehead, Momo?!
You say it!
I thought you were an important person!
You're a leader of these great men,
aren't you?!
I want to bring down Kaido!
Let's join hands!
We're allies!
Let me have Kaido's head though!
Thank you!
All right!
Our objective is...
...to kick Emperor Kaido's butt!
We're the Ninja-Pirate-Mink-Samurai Alliance!
"The Legendary Journey!
The Dog and the Cat and the Pirate King!"
Today is really a miraculous day!
Yeah! It is a great day!
Those two even split the day in half
because they didn't want to see each other
but now they're reconciled!
Yeah, it's hard to believe
that such a day has come.
They say Duke Dogstorm and Master Cat Viper
were once closest friends.
However when they came back
from a long journey barely alive,
they were already deep in a feud.
Every time they came face-to-face,
they'd try to kill each other.
I wonder what happened...
That was before I was born, right?
Yes. Even Pedro and I
were small at that time.
Since Straw Hat and the others came,
things are starting to go well in this country.
Let's have a banquet to celebrate
the reconciliation of our kings today!
We can wake up and go to bed anytime we like!
Our enemy is Kaido!
Dogstorm, Cat Viper!
Momo, Kin'emon, Kanjuro and the ninja!
And Tra-guy too!
We all join our hands to take down Kaido!
That's what we allied for!
Guys! Don't ever bow your heads!
Nor get down on your knees!
An alliance means...
...friendship!
Not necessarily!
We're already allies
but there's one condition.
Well, isn't that something you should've told us
before we agreed to join forces?!
What is the condition?
One of our crew isn't with us now.
Oh, it's about Sanji, isn't it?
Sanji?
Well, a lot has happened...
What?! Big Mom?!
I haven't heard about this!
It happened while you were sleeping.
I see.
That's why we didn't see Sanji-dono.
I'll go and get him back
so don't go off to fight until then!
Is that the condition?
If so, sure, we'll wait.
Thanks! In return, Sanji will be a big help!
It's like getting help
from a thousand people!
I'm worth two thousand people!
Okay, okay.
I see. Sounds like he's pretty dependable
but will you be alright?
You're talking about Emperor Big Mom!
I'm not gonna fight her so I'll be fine.
I'll go with Lion Viper!
Lion... Viper?
Lion Viper!
Target confirmed, Jack-sama!
Yeah, I see it. You don't have to tell me.
Damn. I can't believe I came back here.
Sheepshead.
"Raizo wasn't there."
I didn't expect you to come back saying that.
I... I am so sorry, sir...
The Minks have a strong vital force.
What if those who escaped the gas
were able to treat the others who passed out?
Keep your mouth shut, Sheepshead-sama!
If he finds out that not
only are the Minks alive
but also that we were kicked
off the island by someone...
When you start killing someone,
don't stop until he dies!
Mercy will only cause
the messy business of revenge!
You don't need to worry!
The Minks are weakening anyway.
If we make a raid, they'll just...
That's not necessary.
We'll kill the giant elephant!
Kill the elephant? But it's massive!
How do we do that?!
It's Shanks!
Don't tell me you know him, Cat Viper.
Yes, I know him!
"Red-Haired" Shanks, right?
I see!
No wonder that straw hat looks familiar!
Oh, does it?!
Dogstorm said that too!
Do you all know Shanks?!
Yes because both the cat and I were once
traveling on Roger's ship.
What?!
Were you guys the Pirate King's crewmembers?!
What's going on?
Crewmembers...
Well, you can put it that way too but...
...we boarded many ships
as Oden-sama's attendants.
Even when we were traveling
on Whitebeard's Moby Dick.
And when Oden-sama was recruited by Roger,
we were always by his side...
Whoa, wait, wait! Whitebeard?!
Yes. We were still young...
...just like the apprentices
such as Shanks and Buggy.
Hey, wait! Stop! Stop!
I'm completely lost! Um...
But the two of us didn't
go to Raftel with them.
I said "Wait a minute"!
Um, first, on Whitebeard's ship,
there was Oden, the dog and the cat.
ODEN
And then Oden was recruited by Roger
and you three switched to Roger's ship.
Yeah, I remember!
We were having so much fun at that time!
Oh, the species, geographical features, and climates
that I'd never seen!
The sea of clouds in the sky!
The island that floats undersea!
The sunlight!
Every day, I was very excited!
Those good old adventurous days!
You two were trying to kill each other earlier,
weren't you?
Then, Kin'emon, were you guys traveling
on Whitebeard's ship too?
No, we stayed in the Land of Wano
the whole time.
Instead, we were trying
desperately to stop Oden-sama
from getting on board a pirate ship!
What? You were?
Uh-huh, as we mentioned earlier,
the Land of Wano is closed off
from the world and interacting
with other countries is prohibited.
In the closed-off nation,
even leaving the country is a crime.
On the other hand, Oden-sama was a heretic
who had doubts about the law of the country.
We became acquainted with
Whitebeard, Roger and the
others when they landed on the Land of Wano.
They were loyal to others
and we didn't think they were particularly bad people.
But I'd never heard of a daimyo
getting aboard a pirate ship so as his retainer...
So anyway, you all know Shanks!
And Rayleigh as well?!
Yes, of course!
I see!
Can I ask something?
If you got on board Roger's ship,
it must've been the Oro Jackson which was
built by my shipwright teacher Tom-san!
What?!
Are you the shipwright Tom's pupil?!
About assisting that Roger guy...
I'm resolutely proud of it!
Yeah, I'm Tom-san's pupil!
Super!
Um, can I go next?
Then, I bet you know Crocus the ship doctor...
Wait, Brook.
Sorry to interrupt you.
I gotta check something with them.
You said the four Road Ponegliffs will
show us the way to Raftel, right?
I'm starting to worry about the route.
Look.
The needles on the Log Pose!
Normally, we choose our next destination
looking at where these three needles point
but we're not tracking them now.
Is it okay?!
Look.
The needles on the Log Pose!
We're not tracking them now. Is it okay?!
H-Hey, Nami?
We met Tra-guy-kun
and came to Zou following the Vivre Card by chance
and found the Road Ponegliff
which points the location of Raftel by accident.
But according to Crocus-san
at the Twin Capes,
if you track logs,
every route will come to one in the end.
I'd always imagined that's Raftel.
Oh, Crocus!
I haven't seen him for a long time!
How is he doing?!
He was fine!
But that was two years ago!
You mean the old man who was with Laboon,
right?
Crocus the ship doctor! He-gara was looking for
some pirate group back in those days.
Oh, that was my group -
the whole crew is dead!
What?!
Hey! Listen!
I'm talking about something important!
Yes, I understand.
If you're interested where logs will lead you,
go see it yourself.
There is definitely a route on which
all of those three needles point
in the same direction -
towards one specific place.
However, you-gara people have
already left on a journey
which lies beyond that point.
What? What do you mean?
You're supposed to find out about something
for the first time at the end of the route.
Find out the truth about
the Ponegliffs and the ancient script.
Find out about the civilization
that created those and the existence
of the hidden last island Raftel!
When Roger got there,
he had to do everything all over again.
Crocus was also part of the Pirate King's crew.
He is one of those who know everything.
He wouldn't tell a lie
unless he doesn't like you-gara guys.
And the name of the island at the end of
the route is... Raftel.
It's the last point on the Grand Line.
The only one in history who confirmed
that island is the King of the Pirates.
It's a legendary island.
Beyond the end of the route...
We're already on a journey beyond the end?
I got it!
I didn't need to worry.
We weren't wandering off of the route.
I was just confused by the glimpses of the truth
we hadn't yet discovered.
As Crocus-san said,
the logs are leading us to Raftel for sure!
Leading us to the way to Raftel
which lies beyond the end of the route!
The logs weren't lying!
Are you a navigator?
You're very dependable.
Don't worry! You're on the right track.
Just keep going!
Uh-huh!
Hey, hey! I don't know what
you guys are talking about
but don't you think our navigator's amazing?!
Am I dependable? Yes, I'm sure I am!
Yeah! The navigator of the next Pirate King!
How cool is that!
Don't hit me! That hurts!
Luffy...
It seems you-gara guys have been having fun
all this time.
Anyway, you guys are tied
to so many legends and
I feel dizzy like when I met Rayleigh.
I met Roger and the others too
but I don't remember clearly
because I was so young.
Oh, so you don't remember clearly...
I mean, no way! Roger died
more than two decades ago!
Who are you talking about?!
So much had happened on Oden-sama's journey.
I'll tell you all about it sometime.
But for now, we have so many things to do
before fighting Kaido!
We need to prepare.
Like I told you before, we're
trying to recruit samurai
who will fight with us
in the Land of Wano now!
In the meantime, we've got
someone we need to see!
It's always good to have more reinforcements.
Who is it?
He is the former 1st division commander of
the Whitebeard Pirates...
Marco the Phoenix!
A big incident involving Blackbeard and
Marco the Phoenix that shook
the world is now revealed!
When Luffy and the others are about to
take to sea in order
to round up allies,
Jack's unsinkable fleet comes to attack!
Luffy and his friends are in trouble!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Nightmare Returns! The
Invincible Jack's Fierce Attack!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!