kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new adventure will take place.
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
as its name suggests, a zou (elephant)
that has been alive for a millennium.
Now, we're gonna go
so can we have lots of food?!
That's... really bad!
I gotta let everyone know!
"Save Zunesha!
The Straw Hat's Rescue Operation!"
Yeah, yeah! You can take
as much food as you want!
Carrot. Show him the way to the food storage.
Okay!
Thanks!
We have a problem!
What's wrong, Musatobi?!
Don't tell me Jack is back again!
N-No! It's not about Jack!
One of Zunesha's forelegs is...
It looks really terrible...
The wound is so large and deep...
It's miraculous that
he's still on his feet...
Are we safe now?
I'm sorry!
No, that's okay.
So this is what Jack left us with.
We must do something as soon as possible!
Say, Luffy...
Can we delay our departure a bit?
Do you wanna treat the elephant?
Uh-huh!
All right! Treat him quickly!
No, that's so nice of you but...
Stop it!
We're the Ninja-Pirate-Mink-Samurai Alliance!
Alliance?
But...
With this many people, it won't take long.
Yup! Count on us!
--That's right!
--Yes, yes!
I knew this is what we'd do.
Okay, let's do it!
--Right, Chopper?
--Uh-huh!
First, we need tons of medicinal
herbs! That, I can get!
But the problem is the bandage.
A bandage, huh?
How can we wrap his massive leg?
I mean is there a bandage for an elephant
in the first place?
I think I can get a bandage.
--You sure?!
--Yes! Leave it to me!
Thanks, Robin!
Now, let's talk about how
we apply the bandage.
Hey, when you found out Jack was alive,
you said "Send out the ships," didn't you?
I did.
How do you launch them?
Don't tell me you simply throw them down,
do you?
It's so high. They would break.
Let me show you!
This place was affected by Jack's attack, too!
It's a mess!
Oh, Franky, look!
I see. They move the ships
up and down with these.
Unlike other stuff, they look fine.
All right!
Zoro! Brook! Kin'emon!
Fell some trees from the forest!
Got it!
Did you hear that, you all?!
Devote all of your strength
and save Zunesha with the Straw Hats!
Yeah!
We're really getting so much
help from you-teia guys.
How can we thank you for going this far...
No, no! Don't mention it!
We'll definitely repay you for this somehow.
Oh no, please...
Oh yeah! Say Wanda, do you have a sea chart
that shows the way to Big Mom's island?
A sea chart?
Yes. If you have one,
I wanna do my homework before the voyage.
I'd rather not have any trouble navigating.
A sea chart...
I think we have one.
Everyone!
Collect this herb! As much as you can!
Understood! Dr. Chopper!
Oh! You can use it as medicine?
I didn't know that.
The leaf part is for hemostasis
and the stem part is for sterilization.
Both parts work very well
but since it's a rare herb,
you don't often see it in encyclopedias.
I see! That's why...
There are so many here so that's great!
Dr. Chopper, is there
anything you don't know?
It's going well!
One, two!
Here we go!
There!
Are you ready?
--Yes!
--We are!
Mil Fleurs!
Hands came out!
Needlewoman!
The sheets have been sewn together!
There are so many hands! Cool!
We'll repeat this over and over
to make it one big bandage.
--Now, lay them side by side again.
--Okay!
Okay! It's going well here too!
Alright, let's begin.
Okay, I've chopped them.
--Wow! When did he do that?!
--That was awesome, Baron Corpse!
Not again!
Garchu, Baron Corpse!
Hey, please...
Never mind.
Just do whatever you want.
Okay, it's my turn!
That's cool too, Kin'emon!
But don't set the wood on fire!
I-Is that ninpo?
Oh no! It's not.
Hey! Take those to Franky now...
Where did they all go?!
It's the other way around.
You walked off on your own, Zoro-ya.
Are you that ridiculously terrible
with directions?
Boo! Boo! You stray swordsman!
Shut up! I can carry them on my own!
Then you'll have no problem, will you?!
That's a waste of time.
We don't want you to get lost again.
Damn you! How could you say...
Shambles!
What? What?!
Did he disappear?!
That bastard...
It's a little old. Does it help?
Yeah, it's good enough.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
Big Mom's headquarters is down this way.
Unfortunately, we don't
have a map of the island.
I see. If we travel at normal speed,
it'll take more than a week.
Maybe.
We gotta get going!
We have to make it in time for the tea party!
To return the favor...
To help them-gara make it
to Big Mom's island safely...
We have no choice but to travel with them!
Oh, there's a small isolated island here.
You're right. It's as tiny as a rice grain!
Not even an ant could live on such an island!
No, no! It looks that way
because this is a sea chart.
It'd be nice if they have a restaurant there!
I don't know about that!
I mean when did you guys get here?!
Alright! Everything's going well!
Boy...
Is that...?!
Oh, they're finally here!
One, two!
Alright, let's do it!
Swoosh!
Oh, how cool is that?!
It's beautifully done! They look brand-new!
It barely looks like the work of a human!
That's because I'm a super cyborg shipwright
who's beyond human understanding!
Hey, Franky! The medicine is prepared!
The bandages are completed too!
Where's Robin?
She's making extra bandages to change later.
How thoughtful! That's our Robin!
Laying the tracks is completed too!
All right, guys!
Bind the gondolas to the ropes
and get on board!
Yeah!
I thought so!
What's wrong, Nami?
It's a Silent Supercell!
What's that?
It's a massive thundercloud that appears suddenly
without warning.
It'll cause a severe storm.
Even if it breezes by, it'll wreak enormous havoc!
What?!
Luffy! Tell them to stop the elephant's treatment!
We gotta evacuate everybody!
Wind it up!
Down! Down!
Okay, stop!
Boy, it's a terrible wound!
It is.
I'm sure it's unbearably painful,
but he's staying calm and letting us treat him.
Okay, okay, you're doing great!
It won't be long!
I bet Zunesha senses Dr. Chopper's
passion to cure him like we do.
It'd be so nice if I could
study medical care under him.
It's done here! Apply the bandage!
Got it! Hey!
Move the gondola down slowly!
Roger!
Wind it up!
--Oh no! We can't make it in time like this!
--I'll go first!
--Carrot! Go assist Luffy!
--Okay!
--Hang on tight!
--Don't get shaken off!
The wind is so strong!
If nothing is done, the gondolas will...
It's not looking good. With this much
wind, the tracks and the ropes will...
Pull us up now!
I'm gonna be blown off!
Luffy! This way!
There!
Green Star - Cushion Vine!
Usopp!
--This is it...
--Hang on!
Grab on!
Luffy!
That was close!
You're okay now! Move slowly!
It stopped.
Luffy!
I'm relieved! Way to go, Luffy!
But he can't hold out forever!
We gotta lift everyone up now!
Cien Fleurs - Spider Net!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Now, everyone, climb up!
--We're okay now!
--Robin!
C-Climb now!
What a relief!
Oh, that was a hell of a storm.
Let's get to work!
Yeah!
Here we are!
Great! It hasn't collapsed!
Food!
--There are tons of it!
--But it's so messy...
It doesn't matter if it's messy.
It's still food!
--You guys are awesome, Luffy!
--Yeah?
Yes! You have Dr. Chopper
who can cure anything,
and you have Nami the navigator
who can predict weather like a prophet!
Baron Corpse is a famous musician,
isn't he?
Yeah.
And you have...
...God Usopp who has 8,000 followers,
and Robot Franky
who is like a jack in the box!
You have the great-but-tends-to-stray
swordsman Zoro
and a good sewer Robin who
can sprout many hands!
Robin is an archaeologist!
She's very smart!
Oh, is she?!
And Sanji. He saved the whole country
and made delicious soup for us!
He's such a good cook!
And the awesome captain who brings together
those awesome members - Luffy!
Oh, crap! The backpack is already full!
I should've brought a bigger one!
Say, Luffy,
can I come along with you guys...
I forgot!
What is it?
Lion Viper!
Lion...
Whew, I almost left without him!
Sorry to ask you this but
could you take this to the gate for me?
That's where our ship is!
I'll go pick him up and be there soon too!
But...
Thanks! See ya!
Gee...
One, two!
Alright! That's good!
A little more to go! You can do it!
Now I think we can finish this.
I was worried at one point.
Thank you very much, you-gara all!
Thank you, Robin!
Thank you!
That's not enough! Get out of my way!
You brave ones who saved our country
not only once but twice!
Thank you, thank you,
thank you very much!
That's too much.
The sea is beautiful.
I wanna sail out to sea even just once.
Yeah, I guess I have no choice!
This is for you, Bariete.
Hey!
Lion Viper!
In preparation for taking down Kaido,
Zoro and the others first
head for the Land of Wano!
Meanwhile, Luffy sets out
for the Whole Cake Island
where Big Mom resides to take back Sanji!
They finally set sail on the sea where
the Four Emperors reign! A dramatic
new adventure now begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Saying Goodbye and Descending from the
Elephant! Setting Out to Take Back Sanji!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!