I've never seen the end of the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante kono me de mita wake janai
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
Both the rain and our tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
That's why we've got to go, Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
Who says it's impossible? Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani? mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji, Luffy
and the others set out
Luffy and the others split into four teams,
each on different missions.
Luffy and the others arrived at Zou,
an island where their new adventure will take place.
To take back Sanji, Luffy
and the others set out for
To take back Sanji from Big Mom,
Luffy and the others...
for the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom waits,
This enormous island,
which is as high as the clouds, is,
...parted from Zoro and the rest who have started
preparing for a battle with Emperor Kaido.
The Sanji retrieval team led by Luffy set out for
the Whole Cake Island
the Whole Cake Island where
Emperor Big Mom waits.
while people in different countries
started preparing for the Reverie...
as its name suggests,
a zou (elephant) that has been alive for a millennium.
Don't get caught by Big Mom!
She's the emperor of the sea!
They headed for the Whole Cake Island
but now face a serious food shortage...
where Emperor Big Mom waits.
...that takes place in the Holyland of Mariejois
every four years.
See you in the Land of Wano!
We have a problem!
Yeah! See you!
--Okay!
--Don't get caught by Big Mom!
Wow! I'm really right on the sea!
She's the emperor of the sea!
Ya-hoo!
What's wrong, Musatobi?!
Don't tell me Jack is back again!
This ship looks so heavy
but it's floating and moving forward!
Yeah! See you!
Meanwhile, people in different countries
started preparing for the Reverie,
N-No! It's not about Jack!
One of Zunesha's forelegs is...
Wh-Why are you here?!
Ya-hoo!
Hey! Cut it out!
the World Conference
that takes place every four years.
It looks really terrible...
The wound is so large and deep...
"To the Reverie!
Rebecca and the Sakura Kingdom!"
Princess Vivi and Princess Shirahoshi!"
All right!
I'll do it so watch the sea, okay?
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
In order to treat the elephant who was shot by Jack's clan,
Luffy and the rest took action.
Luffy-san, you can't eat him!
Carrot?!
--Yes, sir!
--Yay!
--Luffy! It's me! It's me!
--Let go of him! No! He's gonna eat you!
Carrot, why are you here?!
THE KINGDOM OF SAND - ALABASTA KINGDOM
I'm sure it's unbearably painful
but he's staying calm and letting us treat him.
Each of you must pay me 5,000 berries.
That's enough!
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
I came along with you!
Your Majesty!
Garchu!
All of our allowance will be gone!
--I can't do this anymore...
--Nami-san!
What should we do then?
Nami!
I'll make something!
MUNCH!
Munch!
--Hang on tight!
--Don't get shaken off!
What?!
Chopper!
We're in dire straits without any food...
All aboard!
CHOMP!
Chomp!
Baron Corpse!
I'm gonna be blown off!
Will we be able to see Sanji-kun?
This is quite a large headline.
CRUNCH!
Crunch!
Too hard!
I'm sorry but can we go back?
"The island, for decades
veiled in mystery..."
Is that...
Luffy!
What?!
Don't do that! Wanda will be mad at me!
That's Vivi-sama!
"...was finally revealed."
Hey! You-gara guys!
Vivi-sama!
Cien Fleurs - Spider Net!
Are you trying to cause trouble to
those who saved us, Carrot?!
There's an island!
"The Revolutionary Army's
general headquarters - Baltigo..."
NEFELTARI VIVI - THE PRINCESS
OF ALABASTA KINGDOM
An island?
THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY'S HQ FOUND
Oh, could it be...
I just wanted to go on an adventure
"...has already been laid to waste?!"
Have a nice trip!
at sea along with Luffy and
the others even if only once!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Now, everyone, climb up!
...the island on the chart?!
--Vivi-sama!
--Your Majesty!
Yes!
We're going to sneak into the Emperor's headquarters!
We're not playing!
--We're okay now!
--Robin!
The gods saved me!
It must be a reward for being so good all the time!
"Kaido Returns!
An Imminent Threat to the Worst Generation!"
Everyone! See you!
Please! I'll do anything - take me with you!
I didn't wanna cause you trouble so I brought...
Hey!
Food!
Lion Viper!
Look!
Okay! Guys!
Lunch!
Hey, Koza.
Juice!
Let's go to the food island!
A snack!
Vivi-chan looked very excited.
"Saying Goodbye and Descending from the Elephant!
Setting Out to Take Back Sanji!"
An extra shirt!
Yeah!
Unlike everything else,
the shirt is not a carrot, is it?
Wait!
I guess her pirate spirit is back.
Don't go to that island.
No, no. But there's one on it!
Just when I was thinking
she had become more like a princess.
Good, good!
Everything is nice and fresh!
Why?!
Do you know something?
That's nice!
How long will they last?
Pirates shouldn't go there.
Alright then, let's do it!
Like a half day! The sea is vast, isn't it?!
Oh, how exactly do you cook?
That island is...
Yes, this is Hina. We just left Alabasta.
What?!
It'll take several days to get to Big Mom's island?!
...a Navy base!
Clip it right there and we're done.
We'll get the Nefeltari
Family to Mariejois safely.
A Navy base?
"BLACK CAGE" HINA - A NAVY HQ REAR ADMIRAL
We're done too!
Even if we go straight?!
I can't believe it's so big and wide!
I have no idea!
"A Hungry Front!
Luffy and the Navy Rookies!"
Hina-sama, accept these flowers!
Who cares!
Let's just chop everything up!
The sea is like a wonderland!
I picked them for you!
The medical knowledge of the now-named Sakura Kingdom
and the pharmaceutical knowledge of the Birdie Kingdom.
Oops!
I don't want them.
This will be my first sleepover!
Django! Fullbody!
Go to your positions now!
A wonderland? It's not even an island.
It's really incredible!
Yes, ma'am!
The bleeding has stopped.
Please look out for the Sunny!
Oh, well.
You're here now and it can't be helped.
Pekoms, are you okay?
Thank you.
I'm fatally injured but it's nothing. Grr.
You did great!
Vivi-sama! Vivi-sama!
--Yeah, leave it to us!
--You really going?
Can you protect yourself?
I prepared more than enough medicine
so you'll be okay!
Don't worry! We'll steal their food
and be back soon!
Yes! Thank you! I'll be alright...
It's dangerous, Vivi-sama!
Luffy does nothing but crazy things.
Only Dr. Chopper could've done it!
Even though you're with Straw Hat,
don't lower your guard!
Why are you eating my carrot?!
It's really amazing!
He's the worst.
I've never seen anybody jump off Zou. Grr.
Please come down from there right now!
Vivi-sama!
S-Such compliments...
They have notorious hotheads from
various Navy units on that island.
...don't make me happy,
you fools!
Pat her head, Luffy!
What a nice sea breeze...
That's an annoying frontline base
where they observe the Whole Cake Island.
Like you taught us,
we'll try to remove the bandages on a regular basis
to see how the wound is.
Pedro?
Where's Luffy?
If you underestimate them, you'll get hurt.
That was close! You almost killed me!
You're strong!
What? Oh, I think he's in the kitchen.
Is anything wrong?
Good.
But even just changing the bandages is painstaking.
I wonder if I can see them again...
Okay, you can have the carrot.
Go get him. It's serious.
We'll be careful.
Luffy was almost defeated!
What?
Yeah! Leave it to us!
What?!
THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY'S HQ FOUND
All right!
At any rate, no matter what happens,
Well, she is quite a fighter.
We'll protect Zunesha!
The Revolutionary Army got defeated?!
Okay, guys!
Let's execute our plan right away!
Yeah!
this thing on our left arm is
the sign of our friendship!
I thought you-gara were
the son of the revolutionary - Dragon...
Pedro-san, when did you get up there?
You really like heights.
Yeah!
You're all so dependable!
Sabo!
That's my brother!
Zunesha is our millennium-old land!
I'm hungry. Let's eat.
Sabo-san?! The other brother that
you said you met at Dressrosa?
Somebody, make something!
We might've gotten too comfortable and forgotten about it
because it's always been there since we were born.
I wanna kick Crocodile's ass!
Is he the Chief of Staff?!
That makes him No.2 of the Revolutionary Army!
You hope nobody dies in this fight.
What an unusual group of
three brothers you guys are!
Today, we were reminded.
Wow! I can't believe it!
None of the citizens, and none of us!
All right!
I'll do it so watch the sea, okay?
We were reminded that we're always kept alive
by this great lifeform.
So this Dragon guy beside him is...
Yes, that's him!
Your grandpa told you two years ago.
Even when a million people are going wild.
--Yes, sir!
--Yay!
Vice Admiral Prodi.
The reserves will arrive soon.
Come to think of it, Luffy...
I heard that you saw your old man.
Don't you think that's too soft-hearted?
Each of you must pay me 5,000 berries.
Mm-hm.
And what's wrong with thinking that?
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
And it will come to an end one day.
What?! My dad?
What's wrong with not wanting people to die?!
What do you mean by my dad?
I have a dad?
All of our allowance will be gone!
What should we do then?
If Zunesha, our land, has free will,
People die.
Brook, either you or I should make something.
Oh... Then he didn't tell you who he was?
What's going on?!
Stop talking like that!
I want to ask him this now.
You're right.
If we leave it to Luffy-san,
we don't know what he'll make for us!
Say that again and I'll make you pay!
I heard that he saw you off at Rogue Town.
The people of this kingdom
haven't done anything wrong!
Luffy's old man was in that town?!
I'll make something!
So why do people have to die...
What?!
JUSTICE
"You have been walking for a thousand years.
Where are you heading?"
Count on me!
I'll cook you a lot of delicious dishes!
Wh-What's my dad like?
...when it's all Crocodile's fault?!
I'm curious... about Luffy's father!
Oh, no...
Oh, please don't... Hey, wait!
Then why are you putting
your life on the line?!
Your father's name is...
Food! Food! Food!
...Monkey D. Dragon.
He's a revolutionary!
Wait! Don't do it!
Luffy! Can you even cook?!
They're all useless.
KURAU CITY, MOKOMO DUKEDOM
The leader of the Revolutionary Army - Dragon.
That's your father!
You want to stay? Here in Zou?
Cowardly weaklings!
Just one look at this kingdom
and even I can tell...
Meanwhile, another country starts preparing
for the Reverie...
Uh-huh.
I'll beat you all up!
What are you going to do here?
Tell what?!
...what most needs to be done!
I actually don't know what to do but...
What?! Is this my dad?!
What?!
Get him, everyone!
As if putting your single
life on the line is enough!
THE SAKURA KINGDOM, GRAND LINE
What did you say, Dr.
Kureha? Are you serious?
--After all these years?!
--I've never seen him before!
Then what should I be putting on the line?!
DALTON - THE KING OF THE SAKURA KINGDOM
Why are you looking so displeased?!
For once!
What?! Luffy's father is
the boss of the Revolutionary Army?!
Dalton, you will attend
Give me permission!
Oh my! Oh my! Garchu!
the Reverie as the first king
of the Sakura Kingdom, right?
DR. KUREHA
Make Jack go away!!
I don't have anything else
that I can put on the line...
Didn't you look into it at all
over the last couple of years?!
Y-Yes.
In that case, I'll be your
ship's doctor, I said!
At least try putting all of our lives
on the line together!
Normally people would care
if their father is such a famous figure!
Aren't we friends?!
Are you happy?
And he took care of Robin for quite a while.
Understood!
Well, I'm amazed how you
reconstructed this Winter Island
I see! I've never seen him before!
He doesn't really look like me.
That's enough, new boy!
If it's possible,
I want to talk with him once again!
and built a kingdom that is good
enough to attend the Reverie.
Anyway, I'm worried about Sabo!
You're Vice Admiral Prodi.
With Zunesha!
Jeez...
Thanks to them.
Let me tell you something...
Well, you can't really
empathize with a picture.
You mean those pirates
who took away my stupid son?
Just who I was looking for.
With the one who has been living for a millennium!
Send these dumb-asses
back to their old units.
You can't save this country.
Yes, the Straw Hats.
And... Dr. Hiriluk.
Why could he hear my voice?
"The location of their general headquarters was found
by an anonymous tip."
You twit!
Goodbye, Princess...
"However, when the Navy and
Cipher Pol arrived there,"
Maybe he knows something about the Kozuki Clan!
"the Blackbeard Pirates had already
destroyed the headquarters."
That quack...
--What?
--Momonosuke-sama!
My name is Dr. Hiriluk!
Blackbeard?! Those bastards!
I understand but there are people waiting for us
in the Land of Wano...
Thank you for
your better-than-expected reaction!
I'm a doctor!
But why did Emperor Blackbeard want to
attack the Revolutionary Army?
Skull...
Okay, everyone!
Come out and get changed!
This is a symbol of the belief that
nothing is impossible!
That's all right, Kin'emon.
Isn't it strange?
Back in Dressrosa, Sabo fought...
Dogstorm!
I will save this country as a doctor!
--...against the champion. Is that why?
--Hey, Luffy!
By raising this,
I'll fight just like pirates do!
I've been thinking I still have to
protect this country from the threat of Kaido.
I'm so excited to sneak into the base
disguised as a Navy soldier!
Crocodile!!
We don't know yet how Jack could make it here twice
so we mustn't let down our guard.
Emperor Blackbeard fled
after butting heads with Cipher Pol, it seems.
Are you happy, young man?
--I don't wanna wear this.
--Wear it if you wanna get food!
The doctor hunt has come to the final stage.
Okay.
Hey, Luffy!
I hear that you and I are
the only doctors left in this country.
Luffy-san!
There is no report on casualties.
Luffy! I smell something good!
We can't all get into the Land of Wano
at once anyway.
Wapol is trying desperately to catch us.
Hey!
If your-gara father or brother
had been caught or killed,
I think it stopped.
I think I'll stay here for a while.
If we'd arrived here a little later,
we would've run into that Navy ship.
Even if that wasn't the case,
you're already an outcast in this country...
Just in time.
I'll bring Momonosuke-sama with me later.
That was close.
that would've made headlines.
Hey, Luffy!
...since you're the worst of the quacks.
So I guess they're okay for now.
Nami-san,
I'm going back to the Submerge.
My voice... no longer reaches anyone...
I won't get caught by some doctor hunt.
Yeah! You're right!
Understood. Thank you.
Thanks! Please keep guard!
Hey, Luffy!
Nami! Look at the tower!
I'll save this country
using medical science one day.
Cat Viper made my Vivre Card earlier.
What do you want?!
Thank you for cooking for us
but is that normal?!
At this rate, the country will...
The soldiers are carrying food in there!
Give this to everyone.
I'm gonna... die...
Don't worry.
That must be their food storage!
What?
But their headquarters is close to it
so we'd better watch out!
Now, let's split up into four groups.
Yeah, you will...
Your voice is heard by us.
Fire?!
Yeah, let's grab the food carefully
without causing any trouble!
What... happened to you?
What?!
First, the group that will search for Marco the Phoenix,
the former 1st division commander of the Whitebeard Pirates.
Why?! Why is it on fire?!
Yes...!
Uh-huh!
No!
Mushroom...
Okay, Luffy, let's go...
Medicine...
He's gone!
CAT VIPER TEAM - THE SEARCH FOR MARCO
That's an Amiudake mushroom!
Oh, no! I left the stove on!
Carrot too!
Cat Viper's group!
I won't... lose again!
Food...
Doctor also said he got better!
What?!
Not that way!
Second, the group that will stay here on Zou
and join us later.
There's no way he'll die!
You're a liar!
Oh! There's an explosion!
Put out the fire!
Please... stop fighting!
Did you plan it, Garp?!
DOGSTORM TEAM - ZOU
He was happy about your thoughts.
Dogstorm's group!
Please... stop fighting!
He destroyed one whole ship!
The skull in the book indicates poison.
Wait a minute! A storm is coming!
Please... stop fighting!
Third, the group that will head for the Whole Cake Island
to take back Sanji-dono.
That's not good.
What?!
That's a lie!
That's not a lie! Remember it!
You think it's not your problem?!
Aren't you his instructor?!
What is that?! Electro?!
There's no medicine
that can work for all diseases in this world.
LUFFY TEAM - THE WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Grount requested the transfer!
Take good care of him!
Luffy's group!
Gum-Gum...
Furl the sail now! The
wind is gonna rip it up!
That's why doctors exist!
...Storm!
Clank.
Vice Admiral Garp.
And the rest of us will go back to the Land of Wano,
round up allies, and plot a strategy while waiting for everyone.
That's not true...!
What about the fire?!
Listen.
You can't save people just by being kind!
--Grount was transferred to Vice Admiral Prodi?
--Yeah.
There'll be heavy rain! It'll put it out!
--So lucky!
--Cut it out!
If you want to save them,
then learn medical knowledge and skills!
KIN'EMON TEAM - THE LAND OF WANO
Why did he want to go to such an remote place?
What is he thinking?
Yeah! It's raining!
Without skill, you can't save anyone!
We're the Ninja-Pirate-Mink-Samurai Alliance!
It's putting out the fire! Phew!
Damn, that old bastard!
Our objective is to subdue Emperor Kaido
and the shogun of the Land of Wano!
You guys can't kill me.
Yeah! Pour more!
Hey, why did you want
to be transferred here?!
Huh?
Ya-hoo!
Big Mom is somewhere near here, right?
Hey...
You can get there by following the Vivre Card,
When do you think a person dies?
I'll bring her down!
Oh, he's quick!
You're so naive!
but the problem is how we communicate.
Chopper, are you okay?!
All-Hunt Grount. You're just 17 years
old but you're a naval captain?!
When a bullet from a
pistol pierces his heart?
I need a hand! There!
In other countries, they use a snail to...
Okay!
No...
When he's attacked by an incurable disease?
Here I go!
What are the people at the HQ thinking?!
I mean, it's this big and if you speak into it,
someone at a distance will...
Plus, you used to be in Kuzan's unit.
No...!
When he eats a deadly poisonous mushroom soup?
--Oh, you mean the Transponder Snail.
--Oh, that.
Brook! Get cola ready to fill
up at a moment's notice!
We have two soldiers with the same
background here. Do you know them?
But in this country,
we're not accustomed to using them.
No!
I got it!
A man dies when people forget him...
I see...
Maybe.
Then all we have to do...
is beat up that Crocodile, right?
How could Kuzan leave
such a good-for-nothing brat behind?!
Even if I disappear,
my dream will come true.
If you want a Transponder Snail,
I saw a wild one in the forest.
Well, he's worthless too since he left the Navy
after losing in the power struggle!
The citizens' sickness of the heart
will be cured as well...
Luffy-san...
If you want one, I can set it up for you.
It's easy.
He won!!
Why're you crying... Dalton?
We only hear bad rumors about him these days!
--What?
--E-Easy?
Don't talk bad about Aokiji-san!
I wonder... if it's the same for a country...
THE WHALE FOREST
Hey!
You'd better be careful
not to become like him.
When our enemy's already gone...
Hey!
THE OUTSKIRTS OF THE GUARDIANS' DWELLING
Yeah, if there's someone to pass it on to...
You do something, too!
Hey! I'll assign him to duty soon!
Let him rest a while!
Don't shed... any more blood...
I had... such a good life!
I'm fatally injured!
Hey!
Goodbye, quack...
Please stop fighting!
Yes, sir!
Lion Viper's house is collapsed!
Thank you, Chopper!
Aren't we there yet?
Hey, Lion Viper!
We're getting closer!
It's from that building!
Are you okay?! Answer me!
ZOU
Lion Viper! Where are you?!
Please don't fight... any more...!!
Oh, Luffy and Carrot!
I'm here! Grr!
Then Carrot is out at sea now?!
Of all places,
they're going into the headquarters!
Where are you?!
Look down!
We gotta catch them first! Let's go!
--Okay!
--Honestly!
Vivi's voice has reached everyone...
Why didn't you tell me sooner, Bariete?
Ac
Please... teach me to be a doctor!
I'll become the all-purpose medicine!
I'm sorry-saru, Wanda!
I told Carrot that she had to tell everyone
that she was going-saru.
A turtle?!
Since our nightmares are... all over...
Step back!
I'll become a doctor who can cure anything!
I'll cure even a country!
But she said...
Oh, this is great!
The rain falling right now...
will fall again as it used to...
No way! If I tell anybody,
they'll try to stop me!
Because... Because...
there's no disease in this world that can't be cured!
Boy! What was the quake all about?!
--Rest here until you get assigned to a task.
--Be nice to your "friends"!
Keep it to yourself just for a while!
How can I get a good rest?! Grr!
N-No! I can't keep it to myself-saru...
Hey.
So you're Turtle Viper!
Okay, so not only do you not remember my name,
but you also forgot that I'm a lion! Grr!
--Are you guys pirates?
--Yes...
R-Real ones?
Real ones.
You really can't-saru?
How did you survive?!
The room is all destroyed!
You have a flag with a skull?
Hey, newbie!
It's attached to our ship.
Why did you wreak havoc earlier?
THE EASTERN HARBOR - TAMARISK
Of course, I could survive!
I ate the Turtle-Turtle Fruit!
Let's go. It's past noon.
Are you interested in pirates?
If you don't care about
your colleagues, go away!
No! You idiot! No!
Yeah, go away!
There's no way that she didn't come!
And my shell is as hard as a diamond!
Hey, we're talking to you!
I see! She bribed you-teia, didn't she?
Let's get out and look for
her! She's definitely here!
You idiot!
Why aren't you listening?!
Hey, this is bad!
The Navy is after us again!
Shock!
What an insolent twit!
Okay, okay. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
N-N-No! Wh-Wh-What are
you talking about-saru?!
Chopper said he'll take responsibility
for treating you.
Don't push your luck, newbie!
Give up, Luffy.
Her case is different from ours.
But... Then... wanna come, too?
I see! You're not gonna
respond to the diamond part? Grr!
These bananas are...
I-I mean, they sure look delicious but...
Who said anything about bananas?
Everyone!
Ow, ow, ow!
To the sea!
Why don't you come with us...?
--Ouch!
--You okay?!
But I appreciate his care.
That bastard!
Dodge it! Watch out!
You caught me-saru...
I owe you guys a lot.
You can't break this flag!
But Carrot didn't wanna
go behind your back...
What?
He must've been blown away! Such an idiot!
Vivi!
What?!
That's okay.
I'm glad to know where she is.
Karoo!
What?!!
Vivi-chan!
Let's go back! Better hurry!
So let's go see Big Mom!
I was just worried that she was missing.
The Navy is right there, too!
If she's with Luffy and the others,
she'll be fine.
What?!
See? It didn't break...
Wait, you bastard!
Do you still wanna fight?
I came to say goodbye!
Don't you get it? I'm fatally injured now!
You'd better be prepared if you're gonna
meddle with someone else's skull flag!
What did she just...?
Gum-Gum...
I'd like to go on more adventures,
Hey! I'm injured! You've got to stop...
Hold on a sec!
I'll give you status and a medal!
but there's no ignoring...
that I love this country!
Duke-sama, please get some rest.
I'll post extra guards if you want.
Bring it on!
Okay.
Doctor...
So I can't go!
The kingdom is...
But before that...!
It's insane! I can't believe this!
The Drum Kingdom is...
I see!
You're the worst person to have debts to!
Oh, I missed you, Grount!
I...
The enemy was probably using a Vivre Card.
Then... I'll make you vice-king...!
Shut up!
That's annoying!
Let go of me, Bonham!
...about to fall!
I wonder how they got it.
Calm down or I'll break your bones!
...Bazooka!!
I...
This will do!
I hope the card was lost
along with the fleet that Zunesha sank...
I will remain here...
Hey! Zappa's here too, right?
Where is he?
It's a sign of our friendship!
He's... there!
Do you think they'll return?
But if we ever meet again someday...
While I'm away,
work together and protect Zunesha, you-gara guys!
Thank you. Drum will definitely...
We'd better be on the lookout.
will you call me your friend again?!
As soon as he got here,
he started proposing to every single woman but...
Okay.
...be reborn...
Count on us, Master!
...he finally got turned down
by the very last one.
I'm sorry, Doctor!
But I wanna see the world!
Master.
Hey, it's been a while since we last met!
We have a lot of catching-up to do!
You'll forever be our...
Pedro.
Sanji saved this country.
Idiot!
Don't reply! The Navy has noticed Vivi.
What do you think someone like you
can do at sea?!
And he was kidnapped in this country.
We three will have a good
time together again!
If we prove she's connected with us,
she'll become a criminal.
Are you gonna live in a fantasy
just like that quack did?!
As long as you stay out of my way...
I mean, let go of me!
Even though the team has to be small,
we will fail in our duty...
You're wrong! It wasn't a fantasy!
Here you go!
Doctor's research had
actually been completed!
Let's part without saying anything.
...if no one from the Mink Tribe other than Pekoms
accompanies them.
Eat it up!
Yum-yum!
Put a lot of carrots on mine!
You-gara, do you want to go along with Luffy?
Was it okay to bid farewell like that?
I do!
Don't try to get the jump on the rest, Pedro!
Hey, are you okay?!
That is a role that...
A pet I was taking care of is being taken in
by someone else. That's all.
What's wrong?!
Report this to the headquarters A.S.A.P.!
...we the Three Dogstorm Musketeers are
prepared to take on!
I don't like... tears...
Back off, Shishilian!
A noisy guy like you is the least suitable for the job!
Are you ready, young men?!
Come on!
I'm not noisy!
Let me go!
I was with the Straw Hats the whole time!
FINE-
TUNED
JUSTICE
Pull me up already!
Let me go too as an assistant to Dr. Chopper!
FINE-TUNED JUSTICE
I will make cherry blossoms bloom.
Wanda! Tristan!
No matter what happens, this thing on our left arm
is the sign of our friendship!
Once my invention is completed,
this country will be saved!
We befriended Luffy after we fought him,
Pedro-san!
A ghost?!
BB! Roddy!
Doctor...! Dr. Kureha...!
Yes, they're saying that it appeared in front of them
out of the blue and attacked them.
Nami likes to sleep on my stomach!
Yeah?
That won't do them any good, Pastor Yomo!
I see. So you're saying a ghost
tied them up and took their uniforms?
Some strange bird might come and kidnap you.
What would you do then?!
I wanna chew on Baron Corpse's bones forever!
What if a sniper's targeting you from somewhere
or a meteor falls out of the sky?!
--Me too!
Yes... No... I mean...
That's just your own goal! Shut up, dogs!
You worry too much.
--I wanna go!
Don't be ridiculous!
Maybe I can help them in some way!
Vivi-sama was once a pirate.
Listen! Enforce the search inside the facilities
and along the shoreline!
I wanna go too!
A CERTAIN COUNTRY
--Me too!
--Let me go!
Are you out of your mind, Pell?!
We have the Navy next to us!
Go find their invasion route!
Kaido-sama!
--I'll go!
--I wanna go too!
Now, have a safe trip, my stupid son...
Kaido-sama!
--Now, go!
--Y-Yes, sir!
All right!
Don't push yourself, Your Majesty.
Hey! What's going on with the
Video Transponder Snails?
If you don't feel well,
we'll head back right away.
I understand how you all feel!
I was able to confirm!
We were right!
All of them are running, sir.
I wonder where he is and what he's doing now...
My stupid son...
No, I'm fine.
--Let's go to the monitoring room!
--Yes, sir!
But you have to...
Ever since I met Nico Robin,
...let Pedro handle it!
As we thought,
Jack-sama failed to rescue Joker!
I'm sure he's having a good time
sailing some sea with the Straw Hats.
NEFELTARI COBRA - THE
KING OF ALABASTA KINGDOM
I've wanted to ask the World
Government about something.
It's hot!
Why, Master?!
This spicy flavor is addicting!
About the Ponegliffs?
Mm-hm. I'm going to attend the upcoming Reverie
no matter what!
Because Pekoms will be there.
That means the man-made Devil Fruit
SMILE trade is practically at an end...
You're still a kid, huh?
Screw you!
Only Pedro can get him-gara under control!
If I have a chance, I want to know...
What's so funny?!
...what some king of the Nefeltari Family did to the world
many years ago.
He's getting as hot as curry.
I wish I could go!
So good!
Look, Luffy!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
A seagull-shaped carrot! How cute!
THE EVIL BLACK DRUM KINGDOM
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh...
Something is going on over there.
Can I have yours?
The Evil Black Drum Kingdom!
He's a weepy drunk today.
Yes, you can.
I called the last one "perfect" but...
The first king Wapol-sama
is leaving for the Reverie!
Thanks!
That means we can't have more Gifters!
...the new one surpasses that easily!
I can't believe it.
They're totally exposed and no one's noticing.
I incorporated
the growth capability of Pop Green
Hey! That's enough, Vivi-sama!
I'm hungry...
WAPOL - THE KING OF THE
EVIL BLACK DRUM KINGDOM
and got Franky's help
for the surface treatment.
I remember how I came back...
...as a king who'd even be
allowed to attend the Reverie
It's not too much to say
that it's the greatest invention of the century...
Father-sama, how are you?
after getting kicked out of the Drum Kingdom.
Nami!
My life has been full of ups and downs!
You don't look familiar.
Not very good.
Maybe I only have a very short time to live.
You listening, Nami?!
If I squeeze here...
I wish my daughter to
take a husband already...
I got blown away by Straw Hat
and woke up in an unknown place.
That's unacceptable!
A new soldier like you has to eat a lot
and gain weight or you can't keep up!
I ate trees and rocks.
I was okay with being all by myself.
That's not fair!
You're taking advantage of your illness again!
Eat up and hang in there!
Joker! Oh, Joker!
Huge man right there,
you can have some too!
We've got tons of pictures
of potential suitors!
How come you got beaten?!
Great! Thank you!
I ate lamps. I ate benches.
Throw them away!
That was close!
Don't mention it. Just eat it!
Hey! What are you...
You said we'd form the strongest pirate group
made of all Devil Fruit eaters!
ROGUE TOWN, EAST BLUE
The whole town was a snack to me.
Okay!
This is so good!
Of course, it was because I was a king.
Congratulations on your enthronement, sir.
What's the situation?
It's a little too long, Usopp!
Our hotel was built exclusively for royal families
who go to the Reverie every four years.
We still haven't found out who invaded
or their route in.
But the Navy arrested me.
Listen to my instruction! You extended it too far!
You need some practice!
Where are they hiding?
I shook them off and fled in tears!
And yet...
We hope you like it.
That's a new Climate Baton which you can extend
as you like with slight variations in handling!
I got clear but that made me realize
that I was no longer a king.
I won't let them get away at any cost!
Would you like to buy a box of matches?
You've been taken down by... those upstart brats
before we fulfilled that dream?
Nami and Chopper!
It isn't not-not-so-bad.
I was selling matches
and living under a bridge.
SALLY ISNTOINETTE - THE QUEEN OF GOA KINGDOM
Nami! Chopper! We're here!
Using the Munch-Munch Factory,
I was playing with refuse.
Right, honey?
Well, it's nothing special.
But those toys that I created
won the hearts of children!
He means it isn't not-not-so-special.
--Hey!
--Come here, guys!
Poor Joker! Even though it's primarily
your own fault for being weak!
Nami!
I see!
All it offers is a view of the scaffold
where Gold Roger was executed.
WAPOL'S TOY STORE
I earned some money by selling those toys,
I incorporated all the gadgets from Weatheria
that I got from you in Sabaody.
But everyone's talking about Straw Hat these days.
If you underestimate him...
I heard someone said "Nami"!
and opened Wapol's Toy Store!
H-Have a nice rest
after the fatigue of your journey.
Where is she?!
The business thrived instantly!
Let's eat together! Come on!
King Stelly.
But just one thing...
Yeah, you guys are eyesores to me.
Go away, trash.
A local scientist uncovered
the secret of my toys:
a new alloy, Wapometal!
You said to me in Sabaody...
Y-Y-Yes, sir!
The number of customers, increased!
A-Am I seeing her in a vision?!
The store, expanded!
Toyshop Wapol was booming!
It's like a magic wand!
Business was prosperous! Profits were rising!
Why is she here?
I didn't understand what it meant.
The Munch-Munch Factory was flourishing!
The reason that countries
are buzzing a little...
This is the chance of a lifetime!
I won't blow it!
It fits to my hand! It's easy to twirl!
I rose from the quagmire
and became the CEO of the Wapol Konzern!
...is because of the Reverie
that takes place in the
--So it's up to you to decide.
--This is great, Usopp!
What's the matter, Zappa?
Holyland of Mariejois, the center
of the world, every four years.
Wh-Wh-Wh...
What an advanced ninjutsu that is!
I married Miss Universe and
my life has been filled with happiness!
If I underestimate him...
It's nice!
Wapol's insignia has
spread all over the world
At this paramount meeting,
leaders of 50 nations gather together...
Then what?!
This sure is the culmination of
Weatheria's science of weather!
and I came back into power as an evil ruler!
The Sorcerer's Climate Baton that I wanted!
...to discuss matters of concern
from around the world,
Wh-What?!
Oh yeah?!
No matter how many times I talk about it,
it still feels good!
Thanks, Usopp!
You're Ms. Nami of the Straw Hats,
aren't you?
and establish future guidelines.
Don't mention it!
Oh, yeah! Let's publish it as
"Wapol-sama's Great Memoir"!
I just thought, for the future, you might need a weapon
that'll make you feel safe if only a little!
However, since they are all judicious
and sly leaders of nations,
No, I'm new here. My name is Mina...
Wapol-sama! I have a report!
things never go smoothly.
You can't fool me.
Now, about the cost...
The Drum Kingdom that you once ruled
became a new country - the Sakura Kingdom,
Mirage Tempo!
Oh, no! He knows who I am!
Don't try to run!
and Dalton will attend the Reverie as a king,
they say!
The leader of the Happosui
Army - Don Chin Jao...
THE MAIN GATE OF ZOU
I've been gazing at...
What?! The Sakura Kingdom?!
Damn Dalton...
KANO KINGDOM, WEST BLUE
I mean, the new leader Sai
is not back yet, is he?
...your wanted poster night and day!
Since Straw Hat and the others took down
the Donquixote Family,
How can I drag him down at the Reverie?!
Urgh! What's wrong with him?!
our enemy can't buy weapons from them.
Who do you think I am?!
In the end, it's the six of us.
And now, you're in front of me!
Thanks to that, the war is over.
It's nice to have you, Peropero!
He became a quarrelsome drunk!
DRESSROSA - A KINGDOM OF PASSION
Looks like we can make it to the Reverie.
It's Pedro. I won't bother you.
Oh, my beautiful amore!
Luffyland! This way!
Wh-Why's Big Bro Pedro coming, Grr?
There are tons of things that we want to say!
Forget that we're a Navy soldier and a pirate,
and marry me, amore?!
I'll come along as someone who's known you-gara well
for a long time.
THE RYUGU KINGDOM
THE SEA FLOOR UNDER THE RED LINE
What do you mean by that?! Grr!
Lucy...
Marry?!
No, no, no!
I've never thought about marrying!
Garchu!
It was really nice meeting you-teia guys!
K-Kaido-sama... Please calm down!
Again, I can't do it.
You always try to strangle everything
within your hands
Let me loosen up your closed heart
with my lonely heart!
I'm scared.
You too! Garchu!
Nami! Take care!
and try to manipulate everybody!
Luffy-sama promised me.
Accept my love! Baciami!
Thanks! You too, Wanda!
It makes me feel like I'm suffocating!
When I see him again someday,
he'll take me to a real forest above ground!
PRINCESS SHIRAHOSHI
THE PRINCESS OF THE RYUGU KINGDOM
Stay away! You make me sick!
We still wanna come with you, Baron Corpse!
Of course, Luffy-kun will take you farther.
What?! Can I come too?!
I-I'm very flattered but no thanks,
dog ladies and gentlemen!
Straw Hat Luffy! Trafalgar Law!
Of course, you can!
Would you like to come as my lady-in-waiting?
Oh, it's spicy!
But on this occasion,
you only have to go straight up to Mariejois.
I'd love to! Thank you, Viola-san!
Thank you very much for everything.
You must be excited, Rebecca!
Dr. Chopper. Please take care.
Are you in your right mind?
I am!
Your brothers and the Neptune Army
will come with you, Princess Shirahoshi!
Uh-huh!
But what am I supposed
to wear to the Reverie?
Ms. Nami...
Take care, Dr. Chopper.
I know!
They're from the generation, right?!
She ran away.
You can wear one of my gowns.
But...
Oh, boy...
--What do you think?
--They're all nice!
Very beautiful!
Those brats think they're something
just because they brought down a Warlord!
Listen. We know him.
You can take whatever you like.
Shirahoshi...
He could be dancing around like that
being happy about his marriage.
Father, could we go without
her this time-mi-re-do?
Oh, but...
They must realize they messed up my business!
RYUBOSHI - THE PRINCE OF THE RYUGU KINGDOM
...maybe I'll take my mother's dress!
No way!
What's wrong with that creepy soldier?!
Yeah! We got tons of signatures
on the petition...
But I can't deny it!
MANBOSHI - THE PRINCE OF THE RYUGU KINGDOM
Well, it's gonna be okay!
Are you okay?
...that asks to relocate the Fish-Man Island!
Yes! That sounds good!
Alright, Luffy-dono!
We'll be waiting for you in the Land of Wano!
Ooh mambo!
THE PRODENCE KINGDOM
That is like saying that we
don't trust humans-jamon.
Oh, it's heavy!
Good luck, Luffy!
NEPTUNE - THE KING OF THE RYUGU KINGDOM
King Riku! I turned down the Navy escort!
They serve delicious curry here, huh?
One, two!
Screw them!
ELIZABELLO II - THE KING
OF THE PRODENCE KINGDOM
Take care!
Would you like to go to the Holyland with me?
Hey, what are you doing?!
What should we do?
Let us know if something happens.
Shirahoshi, what did you
learn from the Straw Hats?
Why does everyone think of it
as a vacation or something?
RIKU DOLDO III - THE KING OF DRESSROSA
FUKABOSHI - THE PRINCE OF THE RYUGU KINGDOM
I'll make a weapon to destroy Kaido!
Hey, you!
Tell those idiots from your generation!
What's wrong with that?
Where the hell are they?!
I'll round up the samurai in the Land of Wano!
The Reverie is like a festival!
Oh? Is that a fight?
If I can see you again someday,
Now, I'll help you descend from the elephant.
Meanwhile, Luffy's group...
"You'd better run! What we were doing
was just playing at being pirates!"
What's going on here?!
That's okay, Kanjuro!
Now, what should I make?!
I promise I won't be a crybaby!
Is this...?
Hey! Zoom in to this guy!
Oh! There is tons of food!
Yes, sir!
It's a nice kitchen!
Take me out for a fun stroll again!
Bye!
Yes, Sanji-san usually cooks
and we all eat here, talking and laughing.
Ya-hoo!
D-Don't tell me he's...
A stroll?
Do you wanna go to your mother's grave again?
Eustass "Captain" Kid!
Oh, yeah.
Let me give you the tour of our ship.
Garp's grandson?!
No.
I want to go somewhere farther next time!
What?
Garchu! Baron Corpse!
CRUNCH!
Crunch!
Oh, it's cold!
Again, you're too hard!
I want to go to a real forest above ground!
To all soldiers across the island!
--We covered up the roof!
--Okay, thank you.
This is the aquarium bar.
We found the invader!
All right! The storm passed!
And we covered up the roof that was blown off!
Okay, fine!
There are so many beautiful fish!
He's devouring curry in the cafeteria!
Will you promise?
Well, it's just a place to store fish we caught
to keep them fresh to eat later.
I saved the food I made so eat up!
Leave Sanji in our hands!
We promise!
What?!
Yeah! We get to eat! We're hungry!
He is none other than Straw Hat Luffy!
What?!
This meeting is what our mother Otohime
was looking forward to.
Are you listening?
See you in the Land of Wano!
Straw Hat Luffy?!
Oh, do you like it?!
--Okay!
--Don't get caught by Big Mom!
This is a room where Nami-san figures out
Come with us!
She's the emperor of the sea!
My original curry!
where we are using the sea
chart or keeps the ship's log.
Is that him?!
--Chopper, let's run!
--To where?!
Yeah! See you!
Meanwhile, Luffy and the
others who left Zou...
Luffy, we can't eat uncooked rice!
To the food storage outside, of course!
I'm not gonna leave empty-handed!
There are a lot of books!
--What's that bitter purplish thing?
--It's full of fish bones.
Hey, starboard...
Ya-hoo!
Okay...
Help me...
--So much jam!
--Something's slimy and light blue...
They must have hid their ship somewhere!
Look everywhere along the coast!
How's that?
Oh, a little more...
This is a big bathtub!
What did we do to deserve this?
It hasn't been filled with warm water yet.
You can take a hot shower too.
Hey, hey, hey!
Yeah!
How could you guys be so rude
after I've taken the trouble to cook this!
Pull yourselves together! Or we'll sink!
I wonder if
Luffy-san and the others are okay...
Let's see.
Shut up! Because you jumped off
the elephant all of a sudden,
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ow! Ow! Ow!
For the pride of the Navy,
catch them at any price!
Yuck!
we're all worn out! Idiot!
--See?!
--How can I eat this?!
Thank you.
I'm savoring the joy of living now.
I didn't know you could feel heat too!
Don't let them escape from this island!
Don't knock it over!
Of course, I do!
Thus, the Sanji retrieval team led by Luffy...
How dare you waste food!
Sanji-san would be mad if he heard about this!
These are Nami-san's tangerine trees,
But... I'll make you pay for it!
Oh, no!
...sets out for the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom, who Luffy picked a fight with, waits.
Robin-san's flower garden
and the Usopp Garden.
It made my blood freeze in my veins...
Luffy! We're in trouble!
Oh! I can grow carrots here!
Let's plant some now!
Oh, all I have is bones though.
We had tons of food and it's all gone!
What's going on?
Meanwhile, at the desert kingdom Alabasta
in the Grand Line...
Yeah, I messed up several times
so I used it all!
Okay, I won't say anything.
Damn! What did I do to deserve this?
He's the man of 500 million?!
Oh, I can't believe I get to travel on such a lovely ship...
It's so wonderful!
Ms. Nami's captain?!
What?! That was a week's
worth of food for all of us!
Father-sama, hurry up!
No... We swerved from the course again.
Wait, Vivi.
Why are you in such a good mood?
He looks dumb. Straw Hat Luffy...
I thought you were hungry!
Port...
It's not funny!
What are we gonna do now?!
Okay! Leave it to me!
This is quite a large headline.
Look! She's full of energy...
Luffy...
Hey, I'm starving...
Wow! I'm really right on the sea!
"The island, for decades
veiled in mystery..."
Sanji-san! Help us!
Because it's been a while
since I went out to sea!
I will...
This ship looks so heavy but it's
floating and moving forward!
CARROT - A MEMBER OF THE MINK MUSKETEERS
"...was finally revealed."
Thus, Luffy's group faces a lack of provisions
on the very first day of their voyage.
...kick your ass!
Wh-Why are you here?!
"The Revolutionary Army's
general headquarters - Baltigo..."
THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY'S HQ FOUND
Whaaat?!
"...has already been laid to waste?!"
It's a no-where-to-run solitary
island far off in the sea!
Luffy's arch-nemesis Blackbeard
seems to be behind
Luffy's hungry group launches a
high-stakes mission to acquire food!
The princess of the desert kingdom who once traveled and
cried together with the Straw Hats!
Chopper's foster mother Dr. Kureha
Luffy and the others are
besieged by the Navy!
the destruction of the Revolutionary Army!
and Rebecca who helped Luffy
take down Warlord Doflamingo
Meanwhile, Kaido, the strongest
man in the world, is burning with
They head for a Navy frontline base
where many tough soldiers are stationed!
And the Mermaid Princess who holds
a promise with Luffy in her mind!
Grount, Bonham and Zappa raise
their fighting spirit against
start to move for the Reverie!
the man worth 500 million - Luffy,
Young officers who are
responsible for the Navy's
rage against Luffy and Law!
It is time for them to set sail, each with their own dreams, for
the Reverie where kings from all around the world get together!
Meanwhile, Luffy's team,
welcoming a new member Carrot,
As the Four Emperors start making a move
and their ultimate fighting techniques
next generation and the Straw Hats
get caught in a fierce battle!
blast leads them to a battle
royal against the Straw Hats!
in an eerie way, the Straw
Hats face another crisis!
gets news about another incident
that shakes up the world!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Hungry Front! Luffy and the Navy Rookies!"
"To the Reverie! Princess Vivi and Princess Shirahoshi!"
"The Implacable Three! A Big
Chase After the Straw Hats!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To the Reverie! Rebecca and the Sakura Kingdom!"
"Kaido Returns! An Imminent
Threat to the Worst Generation!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!