Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Straight ahead!
What are you talking about?!
We've already been eaten!
Straight ahead! Straight ahead!
Hakoku Sovereignty!
"Nami's Sick?
Beyond the Snow Falling on the Sea!"
We're flying out of it!
Don't look back!
We're going straight ahead!
Huge! It's so huge!
They cut... the very sea itself...
This is the strength of Elbaf warriors!
Incredible!
Friends!
Now go!
Long ago, there were ruffians on the sea
known as the Giant Warrior Pirates.
The two pirate bosses,
Red Ogre Broggy and Blue Ogre Dorry,
were exceptionally strong.
They were left mostly unchecked,
for ordinary people no longer
stood a chance against them.
But they say that the one who
put an end to their attacks...
...was a single little girl.
You see what our bosses caught today?!
Yeah! It's stuck in my mind!
My excitement won't stop!
Each one of 'em bagged an
insanely huge Sea King, after all!
Even though we're Elbaf giants,
nobody can take down those
jumbo-sized beasts except for our bosses!
Right, men?!
--Yeah!
--You got that right!
Those ones were definitely
the biggest ones...
Yeah! The biggest ones
we've ever caught!
So which one was bigger?
--Which...
--...one?
Yeah! Who won the hunting contest?
Look, Broggy! Mine is slightly bigger!
You wish! Mine's a whole
3 centimeters bigger!
--Say what?!
--What's your problem?!
Bosses! Please stop!
Incidentally, Broggy. There's one
thing I can't seem to remember.
No, actually, that goes for me, too.
Middle Mountain!
No matter! Let's just finish this now!
Yeah! We can think things
through after that!
Guys! Someday, I will go to Elbaf!
To the village of warriors!
Yeah! Okay!
# Gi-Gi-Giants! Gi-Giants! #
# Elbaf-baf! Elbaf-baf! #
# Everyone's huge!
'Cause they're giants! #
# They're huge!
They're huge! They're huge! #
They sure are full of energy...
I'm suddenly exhausted after
everything that's happened.
Vivi. Could you watch
this compass for me?
Sure.
Now you can finally return to Alabasta.
Well, assuming we can make
it there safely, of course...
Yes. I must return!
After all, I'm...
...the only way to
save the kingdom, Princess!
The king-- your father-- no longer
has sway with the people now.
Our only hope of
stopping this uprising now
is for you to tell the
people the truth directly!
So, no matter what, you must not die!
You must live on, even if it
means losing those near to you
or having to betray others!
It will be painful!
Princess Vivi!
Are you prepared not to die?
I will return to Alabasta, alive...
There's no need to push
yourself so hard, Vivi-chan.
You have me!
Today's relaxing sweets.
How about some petit fours?
For drinks, you have your
choice of coffee or tea...
Sanji-san...
Yours is in the kitchen!
Alright!
I'm first!
2,603!
2,604!
2,605!
2,606!
If only I could've cut that wax...
...I wouldn't have left anyone hanging...
I'm weak...
If I'm gonna get stronger...
...I need to be able to cut up
stuff like that from any stance!
"Alabasta Kingdom Sandy Island"
Mr. 2! Bon Clay-sama!
The Swanda is ready to set sail!
Okay, okay! You're so loud, sheesh!
Honestly, now! Why do I have to do this?!
Mr. 3 is nothing but bulky garbage!
You guys go toss him out!
W-We can't!
We wouldn't stand a chance,
even if we ganged up on him!
P-Please! It is the boss' orders!
Un, deux, trois...
What's "four" called?
"Bon Clay"
Zero-chan is so high-maintenance...
Vivi... Sorry. I think I'm gonna...
...go lie down...
No problem, Nami-san!
I'll keep an eye on our course.
You should get some rest.
Are you all right?!
Everyone, come here! This is bad!
Huh? What is it, Vivi?
Nami-san has a terrible fever!
Eh?! Nami-san does?!
Is Nami-san gonna die? Is she, Vivi-chan?
It's most likely the climate.
One of the obstacles all sailors
who enter the Grand Line run into
is illness caused by abnormal weather.
There are countless stories
of tough, notorious pirates
suddenly dying from this.
Carelessness makes even
the slightest case deadly.
Nami-san!
Is there anyone on this ship with
any medical knowledge at all?
But eating meat makes
sickness go away! Right, Sanji?
I can make some basic food
meant for sick people,
but that's entirely
in "nursing" territory.
There's no guarantee
it'd make her better...
Besides, I normally put
100 times more care
into Nami-san and Vivi-chan's
meals than I do with yours...
I serve them fresh meat and
vegetables, for balanced nutrition.
And I give all the
rotting stuff to you guys.
Hey, now!
It's still good, though!
In any case, as long
as I'm this ship's cook,
there'll be no problems whatsoever
in terms of getting a balanced diet.
But there are different kinds
of meals for sick people.
What are her symptoms? What does
she need? I can't make that call...
Then she can just eat it all!
She's sick because she doesn't
have the energy for that!
40°C?! Her fever's gone up again!
There'll be doctors when
we get to Alabasta, right?!
How much longer will it take, Vivi?
I don't know, but one week
is out of the question...
Is being sick that bad?
Dunno. Never been sick...
Who in the world are you guys?!
Of course it's bad!
40°C fevers don't happen every day!
This may be a life-threatening illness...
--Nami's gonna die?!
--Don't die, Nami-san!
Stop that! Be quiet!
Let's find a doctor to help Nami!
Okay! Just calm down!
You're going to make
her illness even worse!
No.
Nami-san?
Oh! She's all better!
Get real!
In my desk drawer...
there's a newspaper...
No change in course...
N-No!
That can't be!
Hey. What is it?
Is it about Alabasta, Vivi-chan?
300,000 royal soldiers
defected to the Resistance...
It was originally a cold war,
with 600,000 royal soldiers and
400,000 Resistance soldiers...
But now that's suddenly changed!
The uprising in Alabasta is
finally going to get serious now...
That paper's from three days ago...
I'm sorry. We can't change our speed,
so I didn't want to worry
you by showing you that...
Understand, Luffy?
Things seem very bad!
Whew, that got through to
you more than I expected...
But you need to see a doctor!
I'm fine... That thermometer
must be broken...
Nobody gets a temperature of 40°C...
It's probably just
sunstroke or something...
We don't need a doctor.
I'll get better on my own...
For now, let's head straight
for Alabasta as planned!
Thanks for worrying about me.
Oh! She's better now?
You idiot. She's just acting tough.
At this rate, so much blood will
be shed throughout the kingdom.
It'll be an all-out war...
If I don't stop that,
the Alabasta Kingdom will be done for!
Crocodile will take over!
I can't just return safely!
I need to return as quickly as possible!
If I don't make it in time,
a million citizens will
kill themselves pointlessly!
There's a million people?!
What an immense burden
you're carrying, Vivi-chan...
Urgh! What were you
watching all this time?!
Whadya talking about?
The ship's been going straight.
Yeah, straight at a right angle!
Look at the compass!
I don't need to.
I was watching that big cloud there.
Clouds move and change shape!
Oh, geez, my head's killing me...
So just leave this to me and go to bed!
I'm here because
I can't leave this to you!
The air's changed...
The air? It's been nice
weather this whole time.
Never mind! Just get the others!
Hey! Get out here, you guys!
Got work to do!
What?
Huh? Hard to feel motivated
when you're giving the orders.
Just shut up and move!
Take the seat and
catch the portside wind!
What's going on, Nami-san?
The waves are quiet,
and the weather's nice...
Wind...
Wind?
An immense wind...
is coming directly this way...
I think.
What?
Hot!
You're hot! Yeah, you stay inside
the ship! Let's go to a doctor!
Mind your own business!
This is my normal temperature!
Now quit being stupid and pull the ropes!
Nami-san. I know you're
saying that for Vivi-chan,
but if you push too hard...
I told you, I'm fine!
Hey, Nami. I think you really should--
Just hurry and move the ship!
Sheesh...
What could it be?
It seems a little different than a storm...
I need to hurry back to Alabasta...
I have a favor to ask, everyone!
I know it's not my place to ask
this as a passenger on your ship,
but my homeland is in a terrible state now,
so I'd like to hurry ahead!
We can't waste even a single minute!
So I want this ship to head for
Alabasta at its fastest speed!
Of course! That's what we promised!
So let's find an island with
a doctor on it right away!
Let's cure Nami-san as quickly as
possible and then go to Alabasta!
That's this ship's fastest speed, right?!
Yeah! We can't go any faster than that!
Are you sure?
As their princess, you should be
worried about those million citizens.
That's right! So we need to hurry
and cure Nami-san's illness!
Well said, Vivi-chan!
I've fallen for you all over again!
You got guts.
Thanks...
Don't overexert yourself, Nami-san!
Sorry, Vivi... I think...
I am kind of... in trouble...
Nami-san! Hang in there!
What is that?!
It's a cyclone!
It's huge!
W-Wait! That's the direction--
That's the direction our
ship was just headed in!
It would've been a direct hit
had we kept going straight!
Yikes! We just barely made it through!
Incredible!
Grand Line cyclones are said
to be impossible to predict!
Yet, she--
She doesn't predict weather
based on standard theory...
It's almost as if she's detecting
the weather with her body!
I've never seen such a navigator before!
Alright! Let's hurry, then!
Let's go find us a doctor!
Yeah!
What do we do, Vivi-chan?!
Nami-san's fever won't go down!
Sanji-san! Karoo!
I asked you to stop freaking out!
See any doctors?!
Do you expect him to, you idiot?
Hey, guys. Do you think
people can stand on the ocean?
Can people stand on the ocean?
C'mon, Zoro. What kind of question is that?
Then... what's that?
Huh?
What's what?
Huh?!
The world is awfully big
so even if there is treasure somewhere,
the odds are astronomical
So relying on dumb luck
won't get you anywhere
So even...
...if someone stops me or
laughs at me from the shadows
the ship will continue forward
Bon voyage!
Forget about them!
I know I'm a fool, but I gotta go
The crazier the dream,
the cooler the ambition
I know I'm a fool, but I'm gonna fight
The farther the sea,
the more heavenly it surely is
Do everything you can, and you'll
get a little nearer to any horizon
Oh, Nami-san!
Forgive me for not being
able to lower your fever!
You need to cool your head off!
Look around!
The ship's being attacked right now.
What do we do?! What do we do?!
Oh, that's it? Nothing's worse
than Nami-san being sick!
Whoa! He's eating our ship!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Raid! Tin Tyrant
and Tin Plate Wapol"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!