kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Sanji, the cook of the Straw Hats,
suddenly left his friends behind.
To take back Sanji from Emperor Big Mom,
Sanji, the cook of the Straw Hats,
suddenly left his friends behind.
Luffy and the others had reached
the Phantom Island, Zou.
To take back Sanji from Emperor Big Mom,
Luffy and the others were heading
for the Whole Cake Island.
They met its residents, the Mink Tribe,
and reunited with Nami and the rest.
He was being pressed into marrying
Emperor Big Mom's daughter.
But now they're facing a
serious food shortage...
TEA PARTY
However, Sanji was pressed into marrying
Emperor Big Mom's daughter
They snuck into a Navy base
which they stumbled upon
Split up temporarily from
Zoro and the others,
Luffy snuck into a Navy base which they stumbled upon
to steal food,
Split up temporarily from
Zoro and the others,
and managed to steal some food.
Luffy's team is heading for the Whole Cake Island
where Big Mom waits to take back Sanji!
and suddenly left his friends behind.
Luffy's team is heading for the
But there are young soldiers
who are willing to take down Luffy.
but he was surrounded by soldiers.
Whole Cake Island where Big
Mom waits to take back Sanji.
TO MY BUDS, I'VE GOTTA GO SEE A WOMAN.
I'LL BE BACK. SANJI
Among them are three Navy rookies
who are looking to subdue pirates.
Meanwhile, Sanji is...
On top of that, Luffy and company learned
that
But Luffy is currently on the verge of
You pests!
I can't let you pass through here.
Kin'emon and the others'
home, the Land of Wano,
life and death
after eating a giant highly-venomous fish.
She thinks highly of you for once being a chef
at the Sea Restaurant in the East Blue-bon.
I'll take your lives!
is currently under Emperor Kaido's reign.
Where the hell are they?!
Therefore, to take down Kaido,
they formed an alliance
Well, of course I look like him.
Oh? Is that a fight?
with the samurai from the
Land of Wano and the Minks.
You can get even better treatment
depending on how well you cook-jour.
My name is Yonji!
"The Devil's Fist!
A Show Down! Luffy vs. Grount!"
What's going on here?!
Screw that!
Luffy-san!
Split up temporarily from Zoro and the others
who started preparing to fight Kaido,
Listen!
These hands are only meant to cook for my friends!
Hey, please!
I bet you have antidotes!
Is this...?
Hey! Zoom in to this guy!
I won't let you get away, Straw Hat Luffy!
We used all we got but he still needs more!
Luffy's team is heading for the Whole Cake Island
where Big Mom waits to take back Sanji!
Yes, sir!
This is your fiance.
I don't really care if you take
that small amount of food. But...
I'm sorry.
I have no interest in saving people.
The 35th daughter of the Charlotte Family.
Charlotte Pudding-sama!
D-Don't tell me he's...
Or do you wanna try and
rob the medicine from us?
...since this island is
the frontline base against Big Mom,
(I'm gonna be dried up...)
Garp's grandson?!
if the HQ finds out that we were
messed with by you pirates,
"Sanji's Homecoming!
Into Big Mom's Territory!"
Like pirates?
Oh, no!
(Sanji, food! Ice cream!)
especially one from the Worst Generation...
Luffy! We're in trouble!
Stop being so stingy!
I'll be reassigned with
my retirement at hand!
What's going on?
If I get demoted,
my pension will be cut significantly!
He's the man of 500 million?!
Luffy! You got a bite!
My well-funded retirement
plan will be ruined!
Ms. Nami's captain?!
Who are you?!
He looks dumb. Straw Hat Luffy...
What?!
He can't stop speaking frankly!
Anyway, the Submerge is right there!
If we can get to it, we win!
Hello. I'm sorry.
--Pull it up, Luffy!
--Luffy-san, go...
I will...
...kick your ass!
I'm hungry... Do something...
My young brother is a cold-blooded jackass.
You can do it, Luffy!
Me too... Oh, I feel so weak...
And mission accomplished!
"The Implacable Three!
A Big Chase After the Straw Hats!"
Food...
Nutrition...
We're losing weight...
Luffy!
"A Deadly Poison Crisis!
Luffy and Reiju!"
I don't have any flesh to lose though.
Pull!
Luffy-san...
What is he gonna do?! Don't tell me...
The ship's gonna turn over!
Furl the sail!
That's right!
I can't!
Straw Hat Luffy... I will kick your ass!
Can we really get to
the Whole Cake Island like this?
No, let me take care of him.
Young brother?
Are you his sister?
I'm starving...
The captain of the Straw Hats...
Huh? What did you say?
--Brook!
--Blown up with the Submerge?!
Food!
If I can kill him,
VINSMOKE REIJU
GERMA 66 (POISON PINK)
I used to fight your
grandfather with this often.
Ms. Nami will be mine!
"Zero and Four!
Encountering Germa 66!"
Hunger can't beat me!
My grandpa?
Her eyebrows are twirly too!
That's right! When we were young,
it was evenly matched against his fists!
Luffy, what should we do?!
She's gorgeous!
We'll rescue you at any cost, Sanji!
They know who we are
and we're surrounded!
I fought Garp with this Haki-filled ammo!
Reiju!
Is he flying?!
"What should we do"?
We have no choice!
You moron!
How could you humiliate me?!
Do you want a taste of it?!
It...
It's pulling me!
We're gonna run!
Shut up!
You should be ashamed of yourself!
That's right! We're gonna eat more!
Hey! You pulled it all the way up!
What?!
Luffy-san!
What? Is he hovering in the air?
Ship! Ship! Ship! Ship!
Is he a Devil Fruit eater?
Carrot! Let's eat more!
I won't let it get away!
If so, he should've been weakened
by falling into the water!
I'll have some too!
Ship! Ship!
But it looks different from
Sanji-kun or CP9 members' special skills, too.
It's so powerful! This is gonna be a tough haul!
Until it gets weak!
Hey! That's enough!
That's not a skill he
acquired through training.
Food!
--Let's take the whole pot!
--Good idea! We got food!
That was sudden and close!
--He's going crazy!
--Luffy, stay cool!
It's science!
Nothing'll be left for us to eat!
What?!
Don't rush!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Germa 66 is a group of fighters
who have honed themselves with science.
I love pretty girls who know what they want!
Food! Food! Food!
Food! Food! Food! Food! Food!
I thought it was snow but...
That fool is worth 500 million?
He's a big nothing.
Gum-Gum...
They are a scientific
fighting squad, if you will.
It's Cotton Candy Flurry-soir!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
...Hook, Line and Sinker!
It's not working!
Why's that?!
And Mama is...
I'll take him down!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Your Transponder Snail won't stop ringing.
...looking to get that technology!
What's going on?!
Sweat!
What?! He's using mechanical power to hover?!
Ow, ow...
It's receiving Warning Signals-bon.
I'm eating here! Don't bother me!
It's been a few hours
since you invaded the base!
That means
we're in Mama's territory already-souffl.
We don't have curry here
for you damn pirates to eat!
Cool!
Sanji-kun's family is unbelievable.
I did it!
That was enough time for us
to come up with a countermeasure!
Will those Warning Signals
reach over there too?
Nice! Nice!
Germa 66...
The Vinsmoke Family that leads it...
We're gonna be alright now.
All we did was put rubber on shields,
You catch on quickly! That's TARTE 28.
But this fish...
but doesn't it work well?!
It's an outpost where a platoon from the Big
Mom Pirates is standing ready-millefeuille!
Its color doesn't seem right.
Pekoms-san, if I'm correct,
Vinsmoke was...
Is it okay to eat?
If this weren't one of Mama's ships,
they'd attack us like "Boom."
It's pretty doubtful...
...the name of a royal family, wasn't it?
Everyone knows they're there now.
Are they gonna be okay?
What are you saying?!
There's no such thing as an inedible fish!
Shields can't stop me!
If I remember right, it was a family that
Don't worry.
He's not gonna get caught by the likes of them.
Now, have you made up your mind?
Don't be so stubborn.
Luffy! Wait a sec!
I'll go check real quick!
Nice try.
What?
conquered the North Blue
by force of arms long ago!
Thunder isn't my only weapon!
More importantly, what we gotta do now is
steal food!
Just swear allegiance to us, Big Mom Pirates,
along with Germa 66-bon.
Don't underestimate me!
Mirage Tempo!
By "royal family,"
you mean like Vivi and Neptune?!
Sanji. I'm sorry but I
have to open your locker.
What? Are they such a prominent family?
What?!
That's what your father wants-amour.
That's right. They were synonymous
with "evil" in a past age.
Ouch!
Gust Sword!
Wh-What the hell?
Don't talk about him!
It makes me sick to my stomach!
That's why they were used as
models for the comic strip.
Our relationship has already been broken off!
Where's the encyclopedia of fish?!
Skeleton-san,
you have so much historical knowledge.
Gum-Gum Hawk Whip!
Sanji's bookshelf is full of nudity!
No good. I can't open it.
I've lived a long time...
Found it!
It's locked.
Straw Hat!
I'm dead now though.
Alright.
But it's not just a story from the past.
We're still a royal family.
Leave it to me.
This is my chance to show my skill as a cat burglar!
No, this is not it.
I only came to bring this to a close!
Neither's this one...
Here it is!
Hm? Sanji's cooking note?
Let's see.
Germa is a country without soil.
We have no land to govern
but we're given the right to attend the Reverie.
Don't try to act strong.
What?!
They're having a big fight!
Mama is in a more welcoming
mood than you think.
Luffy! Watch out for its skin!
The skin of that fish is extremely poisonous!
Grount! Wake up and get up on
your feet already! Let's go!
Oh, I beg your pardon.
Of course, she knows you're
that foolish Straw Hat's crewmember-il vous plat.
Look! I found Sanji's note!
If that is so, may I see your panties?
I'm not going.
The skin tastes good!
But she thinks highly of you
for once being a chef at
What's wrong?
Damn!
Luffy! Wait! I'll grill it for you!
Ms. Nami is waiting for me.
How pathetic, Grount. Let me fight!
Stop it!
Here, try it, Carrot.
the Sea Restaurant in the East Blue-bon.
I'm useless.
Broken bones...
The skin's so slimy...
Breath Qigong - the first step!
Too weak!
Luffy!
You can get even better treatment
depending on how well you cook-jour.
Reinforcing!
Extremely poisonous?
Okay, now, can I have it?
Screw that!
What?
I'm too weak!
Adios!
Whaaat...
Listen! These hands are only
meant to cook for my friends!
No!
Can you have... what?
Grount...
Finger Pistol!
Oops, I ate it.
What about you guys?!
Looks like he ate an Armored-Stone Fish
from the Boiling Sea, didn't he?
No one else has eaten any.
You fool...!
--That's good.
--No, it's not.
You can move quickly!
What? How did you know?
Finger Pistol Yellow Lotus!
For that purpose,
I even trained myself in hell!
Are you okay?
How this venom works is unique.
Yeah, I'm good as new.
Is it really highly poisonous?
What's wrong with you?!
Flying Finger Pistol Sting!
He must be greedy.
It could even kill a Giant instantly.
That's what Sanji's note says.
It's no mistake.
I thought you were better than this!
No matter who you were up against,
you always took a stand!
I can picture them missing my cooking
and crying by now!
Then what should we do about this fish?
What?! Oh, no!
Then, there's no way to save Luffy...
I'm a master of the Six Powers!
If we can't eat it, we should just dump it.
Have you lost the guts?! Well?!
Tempest Kick!
What?!
I've gone through so much trouble to catch it!
That's absurd!
I shouldn't be a ship doctor anymore!
You people don't even care that
one of your friends was killed.
Well, Sanji's note says
if you peel the skin off, you can eat it.
But this boy is lucky.
It's no use.
All this moving is making me hungry.
He even put down a recipe.
Let's go!
I have no dish to cook for such assholes!
Yay! Okay, I'll cook it!
Because this venom is...
Are you okay, Luffy?
Oh, you're talking about Pekoms, huh?
Bonham has got the Breath Qigong.
I've got these swords.
Where are Nami and Chopper?
...one of my favorite things!
--What?!
--Do you wanna start a fire again?!
He let his personal feelings interfere with his work.
Bege did the right thing.
Running is all you can do?!
You've got your left arm.
I don't ever wanna eat
your Kitchen Sink Curry again!
Gum-Gum...
Wh-What are you gonna do?
Have you forgotten what
the admiral taught us?
Iron Body!
Luffy, you wait here! I'll do it!
...Jet Pistol!
Baron Tamago.
Let's have it!
Tsk!
--Let's look for more food!
--Okay!
Vito!
Luffy, are you really all right?
We got a picture of Pudding-sama
from the Whole Cake Island-rero!
--Why?
--Because of the poison?!
What?
I'm totally fine!
Oh, carrots!
So you can prepare yourself.
Smooch!!
O-Okay...
What the admiral taught us...?
A present for you.
They understand that it's
hard to marry someone
What? Are you gonna give me those carrots?
who you meet for the first
time. It was so kind of them.
Wh-What are you doing?!
You pretty and cute young lady...
Gum-Gum...
So daring...
It doesn't make any difference, idiot!
I'm not gonna get married!
...Eagle Bazooka!
Wh-Wh-What's your name?
What?! Whoa-whoa-whoa!
If you suck up venom like that, you're gonna die!
At least, take a look at it.
I'm Carrot!
Shut up! Stay away or I'll kick you to death!
Yes!
Vice Admiral Prodi!
Well, come on.
Oh! I'm jealous! Smooch!
Ms. Carrot!
Cut it out...
Let's see... What do I do next?
What a lovely name!
I wish I could change places with him!
Even though my lips...
Here!
Salt.
Yay!
...are gone!
I'm so happy! Thank you! Garchu!
Pepper.
Munch!
Coriander.
Some grated garlic and ginger...
Those guys...
Smells good!
This is what I'd expect from Sanji-kun's recipe.
This is your fiance.
G-G-G-Garchu!
The 35th daughter of the Charlotte Family.
Charlotte Pudding-sama!
Carrot, let's go see Nami and Chopper!
Okay!
Okay! Here you go!
The rash is transferring to her body!
Ship, ship, ship! Ship!
He took my Ms. Carrot!
If I can chop his head off,
both Ms. Nami and Ms. Carrot will be mine!
Ship, ship, ship! Ship!
Wow! Can I eat it?!
Straw Hat!
--Of course, you can! Eat as much as you like!
--Thanks!
It's a return match!
--Shall we eat too?
--Yes!
It's delicious! It's so delicious, Nami!
Ms. Nami! Ms. Carrot!
You're such a pain in the neck!
I just wanna eat more!
--Yes, it even makes me cry!
--I'm so happy to be alive! Grr!
It's so good!
I just cooked it like it
said in Sanji-kun's note.
Admiral...
I'm sorry for doing this
after you gave me carrots.
Chopper, you need energy too, first.
Eat it.
Ms. Carrot...
Aokiji-san...
Thank you, Carrot!
What did you think of the bride?
She's cute, isn't she-rorero?
Luffy's gonna... d-die!
Luffy-san!
I-It's cold...
You were glad to see her, weren't you-rero?
Rero?
Oh, did I surprise you?
What?!
I'm sorry.
By the way, can I see your panties?
Are you ignoring me? Well, that's okay.
Crying isn't gonna help!
The rash on Luffy's body is all gone!
Brook, where are Nami and Chopper?
Here! To take care of Luffy,
you have to gain energy, Chopper!
By the way, have you ever read the WEJ?
Oh, um,
they're at a food storage facility outside.
You've sucked it all out?! Are you alright?!
Now, eat!
The WEJ-rero, you know? The
World Economic Journal!
Yes, of course. I'm Poison Pink.
Okay!
Food?! Okay, let's go, Carrot!
You know it, don't you-rero?
But even if I wanna treat him,
we're short of antidotal herbs!
Uh-huh!
Poison...
What the hell...
This way!
There was this comic strip in the WEJ!
Pink?
Food! Food!
Let's stop by for a bit...
A giant dreamlike robot featured in it!
Sora, Warrior of the Sea!
Carrots! Carrots!
--That bastard!
--Outta my way, Grount! I'll beat him!
I've been constantly reading it-rero!
It was delicious!
Ms. Carrot!
Yum!
Sora, a hero who can walk on water,
I'll do it! Stay out of it, Bonham!
We gotta find an island, Nami!
accompanied by a transforming
robot and a sea gull-rorero,
--What did you just say?!
--Ms. Carrot! Electrify me more!
fights the evil armies of Germa 66.
It's a story of a marine hero!
We're lacking herbs!
Please! Please!
What?! What happened?!
Yum!
There they are!
Luffy!
Gum-Gum Jet Gatling!
Food...
Luffy!
--I'm so relieved!
--Are you all right?!
Hurry up!
But it's not that easy to find an island...
What a relief!
We'll stop you!
Sanji-kun's encyclopedia says
it's extremely poisonous
Luffy!
Oh, so...
I guess you did this, didn't you, boy?
Get out of my way!
Oh? Did I fall asleep while eating fish?
and kills you instantly if
you eat the skin, right?
Yeah.
Yum!
The skin was so good! Is there any left?
But he's still alive!
Doesn't that mean he has strong antibodies?
Well, you can't undo what you did...
--No! Don't you remember?!
--Nope.
He has one of the best vital powers
of all humankind!
This is fun!
You were on the verge of life and death!
But he's in very bad shape!
It's down this way!
Oh, no...
You gave us a lot of trouble!
Ow, ow, ow... It's a dead end.
Yum!
Oh, did I?
Oh, I'm sorry!
Luffy, are you okay?
I forgot you can't run through a wall
if you're flesh and blood.
Sanji!
She's a woman!
The river is... beautiful...
Oh, right. Who is this?
Stop!
I'm just bones - rather boneheaded actually!
He's seeing the River Styx!
Luffy-san, she saved your life!
I don't want this arm! Cut it off!
What? Luffy-san?!
Stop!
What? Thank you for... what again?
What a fool!
You're literally a cornered rat!
Cut it off!
Yum!
Is he dying?
Even if you're feared as one
of the Worst Generation,
Cut it off!
Luffy!!
you act dumb when it counts.
So that's Straw Hat Luffy...
Yum!
Grount, he's just like you!
Oh! You're Sanji's sister!
Unfortunately for Straw Hat,
we can't look for herbs now.
What?!
Are you saying that I'm a dumb-ass?!
Yes.
I didn't say that!
But I won't deny it either.
Sanji is one of us, the Vinsmoke Family.
We're about to reach Mama's territory.
Oh, my dear Ms. Carrot!
Give me the "garchu" once more!
Our father parted from Sanji
when he was a little kid
and has been looking for him.
Luffy, what should we do?
There are some islands in the area
around the Whole Cake Island.
When Sanji's wanted poster was circulated
two years ago,
--It's down this way, right?
--Yes.
NAVY
our father immediately asked the Navy HQ
to pursue him.
I'd say Black-Foot and the others
have passed through those islands
SORA, WARRIOR OF THE SEA
Ms. Carrot!
and reached the Whole Cake Island by now.
But they found the wrong man -
someone named Duval.
Admiral! Wait a minute!
Oh, wait!
It has fans all over the world!
Why should I be on stand-by
again?! I can fight!
Duval!
Damn!
I heard it's based on true
stories of naval heroes.
--I smell food from that way!
--Luffy, you have a good nose!
I've been working harder than anyone else
to become a full-fledged soldier!
He's the guy from the Flying Fish Riders
who we met before Sabaody...
Don't lower your guard, guys...
Let's chase them!
Well, um... What can I say?
You're still a fledgling and not ready yet.
--Luffy-san, I'll leave the rest to you!
--Yeah!
NAVY
So it's sort of educational
material to brainwash children!
Why... Why do I have to be chased by
the Navy Headquarters?!
I'll stand guard!
I'm gonna go back to the ship then!
To teach them "The Navy is
always right and strong"!
I was gonna stop by at the first island.
Let's get an antidote there.
I can even control this arm now!
So...
Why do I have to be nearly killed by
some ill-regarded bounty hunters?!
But that's not what I like about it!
Okay.
It's Germa! Germa 66!
Oh, I remember!
Sanji-san was mad about it too.
Damn!
Well, that's what I'm talking about.
What? This time, it's snow?
They're evil armies that always corner Sora
by all possible means!
I don't want it to go out of
control in the middle of a battle.
You're finally here, Luffy.
It was only recently
that the Government called us saying...
It's beautiful!
--Yummy!
--This is nice, isn't it, Luffy?
It's not snow! Are those Sugar Clouds?!
They're evil heroes!
Once you set out to sea in the future,
you'll face relentless outlaws.
...that they finally captured an image
of Black-Foot Sanji amid the chaos
That's right.
And it's Cotton Candy Flurry that's falling.
Why are you guys so relaxed and eating?!
evoked by the Straw Hats' comeback.
She's right. Hurry up, Luffy.
You can't eat too much here!
Let me ask you.
What?! Cotton candy?!
Our father raised the bounty right away
If you encounter nemeses
like that, what will you do?
You too?!
and made them change "DEAD OR ALIVE"...
Nice! Nice!
Come on!
Let's take food and get out of here!
...to "ONLY ALIVE."
Anyway, there's no need to rush.
You'll see someday.
Sweet...
Why? I haven't had enough!
Here we are finally
That's why only Sanji-kun's poster was
changed a little bit.
Well, good luck.
Straw Hat Luffy!
I recognize your large appetite
and how fast you can run away!
Where is Sanji now?
--Hey, listen-rero!
--Shut up!
I don't know.
Yes, they get defeated for the
sake of the story every time
Maybe he's with Big Mom or with our father.
I see... So this is what
Aokiji-san was talking about.
but I'd always supported them
with a white-knuckled intensity!
Ring, ring, ring...
Fight me!
I supported you guys!
We came to greet him
but I think we missed each other.
--Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
--Oh? Who is it?
Don't include me!
I have nothing to do with them!
Your Transponder Snail is receiving
Warning Signals.
That means we're in Big
Mom's territory for sure.
Don't say such a thing!
I'm kind of happy to see you in person actually!
Well, if he can attend the tea party,
that's all that matters.
Why don't you tell that to them?
And I got to see you guys too.
We're finally here.
Cotton candy!
Guys! Hide or disguise yourself!
Thank you for looking after my brother
all this time.
So sweet!
Fight me!
Hey, open!
Are you listening?!
Straw Hat Luffy.
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
Door!
Sanji's sister!
I see something, Pekoms!
Thank you for saving my life.
It's a ship! A ship is coming towards us!
We don't have food for pirates here!
But...
Listen...
What?! Are they here already?!
I still want Sanji back! He's my friend!
Stop following me!
I thought this was my room!
Luffy! Are you okay?
What do you mean?!
This room belongs to me, too!
Let me out! Dammit!
--That's probably a TARTE, one of our scout ships.
--What?!
--I'm okay! What about the food?!
--We got it!
Why are you treating me so differently?!
I'm a genius scientist!
But Brook...
Kung Fu Point!
--I can't see it clearly because of the fog.
--What should we do?
Everybody!
I'll fight you!
Iron Body!
Glad to finally see you again!
What a relief!
--I'll handle it somehow so all of you, go hide!
--Got it!
Haven't you given up yet?!
Brook!
We were only told to capture you, Caesar!
--Oh, no! Luffy is looking really sick!
--What?!
Gee, we were worried about you!
So you can transform yourself too.
Yeah, he fired at me all of a sudden
and I was scared half to death!
But he is a precious groom who will
The poison must've spread
into his system even more!
What?
It's dangerous! We gotta treat him A.S.A.P.!
connect the Vinsmoke Family
and us - the Charlotte Family!
I'm already dead though!
Don't they have an antidote
on that scout ship?!
Of course, the Submerge is safe too!
You two are different in value.
--I'll ask them for you! Hurry up and hide!
--Okay!
Oh, that was really terrible!
I thought I was a goner!
Breath Qigong - the second step.
Reducing.
I'm not gonna get married.
Just get out.
Gracias!
Chopper-san, hurry up!
--I guess I am already gone though!
--We can finally go back to the ship!
"Get out"?!
Nobody can stop me!
He's just been mean to Vito!
Straw Hat!
"HITMAN" GOTTI
THE FIRE TANK PIRATES
So quick!
I can't stand it! Apologize to him!
Gotti! Whoa, wait! Wait!
He hasn't been that mean to me!
You're the guy from earlier!
I'm okay. Thanks. We were
just messing around-rorero.
I'm not gonna let you get away!
I wasn't.
Huh! You can't see me, can you?!
Gotti. I want both you and Vito out!
What?!
I don't need to see.
Oh, you said it again!
You're a dead man!
I'm gonna take back Sanji at any cost!
Guard Point!
Grount, you finally came!
No, Gotti!
You can say whatever you like to me!
Bonham! Zappa!
Leave the rest to me!
But I can't tolerate anyone
who insults my friends!
No, that's not a TARTE!
See? She saved our enemy's life.
I said "Wait"! Please don't do it-rero!
Straw Hat! Fight me!
Those crappy attacks won't work
against Guard Point!
You don't have to tolerate me.
Hey, you!
You're Pekoms from the Big Mom Pirates, right?
I will take you down with my left arm!
It's not like I wanna be your friend.
If so, I'll just break it by force!
Why are you with the Straw Hats?
Son of a...
Gotti!
Ten Finger Pistol!
I have my own reason!
Why do I have to explain it to you guys?! Grr!
The Six Powers will take you down!
What are you doing?!
I have to thank you, Straw Hat.
You woke me up!
There's no bond between us yet!
Heavy Point!
Luffy...
Ma'am!
You're right!
I'm a monster!
Heavy Gong!
Straw Hat!
Iron Body Strength!
I'll pretend that I didn't
see anything for now.
I'm going to...
...best you!
Yeah, we don't wanna cause trouble and
break off our brother's marriage.
I'm second to none in transformation!
Gotti!
We'd best all tread lightly.
Love Slashing!
That'd be smart! Grr!
Do you know that he's Vinsmoke's son?!
Unanchor the ship. Let's go back.
If you lay so much as a finger on him,
Straw Hat, I can't let you go that easily.
Is that a Transponder Snail?
your Father's head will roll!
Can't you get it?! Huh?!
It's huge!
Well, good luck.
Nor Ms. Nami's heart either!
There is a number.
No! This guy again!
Sixty-six?
Do you want me to chop your head off first,
you dummy?!
Carrot! Thanks!
--Grount!
--He finally did it!
Ouch! I'm sorry! Ma'am! I'm sorry!
This is Germa.
Is that the Straw Hats' ship?
Hey, you...
That's Germa 66's ship!
I love both the beautiful Ms. Nami
and the brave Ms. Carrot!
I'm sorry. You're our important guest.
Germa 66...
The organization led by Sanji-kun's father...
Reiju-san... I wanted to see her panties.
Forget about this idiot
and make yourself comfortable.
Ms. Nami! Ms. Carrot!
Will you be my wives?
Guys.
Ow, ow, ow!
Also known as the Warmongers!
I'm sorry! Ma'am! I'm sorry!
I have no energy to even smack you.
Go ahead.
No food for you today as punishment!
Okay, we should get going too.
Even if you say no, I know you love me!
Why are you here, Straw Hats?!
--Yeah!
--Uh-huh!
Okay! Let's go!
No, please, ma'am!
You're fickle.
--Uh-huh!
--Brook!
I don't think you understand what girls want.
We're gonna collide!
Guys, furl the sail!
Sorry to bother you.
Let me hear about Germa some other time...
Cool down and think about it!
Luffy, I'll be back.
Nope.
Weather Egg!
What's your name?
Come on and hatch, thunderclouds!
I'm Grount!
They didn't get into a fight with Germa,
it seems.
What? Th-Thunder?!
Thunderbreed Tempo!
Yes, I'm sure that's their ship.
Straw Hat Luffy is on board too.
Well...
An awakening of love!
It's like heaven!
What do you wanna do?
She resembles her...
Jimbei.
--That was cool, Nami!
--Now, let's go!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Wait, Straw Hat!
Damn! How dare they mess with me!
--Shut up!
--I'm still examining you. Don't move.
Wow! He's tough.
Here we go!
I wanna go on an adventure
along with beautiful ladies!
It's not gonna stop by picking up.
It's a Warning Signal.
I'm gonna be killed! Big Mom will kill me!
We managed to avoid the crash...
Seems like there's nothing wrong.
That's such an impure reason
to go on an adventure!
Gum-Gum Jet Pistol!
Sanji!
Yep!
How resilient you are.
Or maybe it's Reiju's strange power that's amazing.
By taking down Straw Hat,
Sanji!
I'll be the captain of
Ms. Nami and Ms. Carrot!
Oh, that twirly eyebrow! It's Sanji-san!
You're so lucky.
Probably both.
Burning Blow!
Even when you see Big Mom,
they'll treat you well and protect your life.
What? Sanji? Is that Sanji?!
Good for you, Luffy! Munch!
Sanji!
Just because you have Vinsmoke's
blood in your veins!
Armament Hardening!
Sanji-kun!
I'm kind of hungry again!
Should I fish again?
Great!
I didn't expect to see you this soon!
Gear Three!
No!
That's what I'm supposed to say,
How lucky we are...
but we're still in a food crisis.
You're right.
Don't worry. We'll see an island soon.
Oh, no!
Hey, Sanji! We have a problem!
Luffy got poisoned by eating fish and is dying!
A FEW DAYS LATER
You mean an island in Big Mom's territory?
Is there any antidote on that ship?!
I can't take it anymore... I'm gonna die...
Yeah, let me give you some extra information
while I can.
Sanji!
It's hot... I'm gonna die...
Are you listening, Sanji?!
There are a total of 34 islands
around the Whole Cake Island.
Stop calling me "Sanji"!
(I'm gonna be dried up...)
You got the wrong person!
That many?!
There are 34 ministers, one for each island,
to run the place.
(Sanji, food! Ice cream!)
Oh, I'm hungry again!
Well, of course I look like him.
Straw Hat!
Straw Hat! Is that all you got?!
They call this vast marine area...
Huh? You're so persistent!
My name is Yonji!
My name is All-Hunt Grount!
You'd better remember it!
I can't stand the heat...
I wish I could take off this fur skin...
VINSMOKE YONJI
GERMA 66 (WINCH GREEN)
...Totto Land!
We're like you...
We Minks have low tolerance for heat.
But your journey ends here.
Yonji?!
Totto Land...
Gratin, you're quite strong!
Not "San(three)-ji" but "Yon(four)-ji"?!
All right!
Because I've never lost to anyone!
It's really hot.
I'm gonna become a mummy...
He resembles him
and has twirly eyebrows but he's not him?!
Ring, ring, ring...
We're already in the area
so why don't you disguise yourself?!
My relationship with your friend Sanji
is a secret of secrets.
A mummy...
A mummy?
It's absolutely confidential!
A mummy!
Nami-san, if I become a mummy,
What's the matter?!
Gum-Gum...
He's definitely his younger brother...
It's coming!
--it'd be a little bit of a resurrection for me, isn't it?
--I don't care.
Damn!
Cut the "Gum-Gum" crap!
There's another incoming ship!
In that case, may I see your panties?
So he also had a younger brother...
H-His punch is heavier than before.
Maybe Reiju-san's clan is coming back!
What?! How can you tell
that's his younger brother?!
I have no energy even to smack you.
...Thor Elephant...
Who is that?
That's because I hadn't eaten anything.
Because his name is Yonji!
Nami, I'm so hungry and it's hot...
...Gun!
I need nutrition...
We're out of food and we couldn't fish
because it'd been stormy for days
Cutie!! Cute, so cute...
No, this time, it's surely one of our TARTEs!
Our scout ship!
Are you really not Sanji?!
and finally it's clear.
No! My retirement plan!
Yonji-sama.
Catch some fish somehow
before the weather changes!
I told you to be ready!
You guys, hide in the cabin!
I don't think they are transporting
Sanji-sama on that ship.
Damn!
We're all gonna starve to death
before we get there!
Why?!
If they find you, it's gonna be trouble!
So I guess we missed each other.
Food...
Pekoms-san, are you going to be okay?
You're right. Let's go back.
It was a wasted trip.
We wanna do so but Nami...
If Germa didn't alert them, it's gonna be okay.
Hurry up!
Wait, Sanji!
Grount!
I'm Yonji!
We're counting on you!
The water is boiling because it's too hot!
Oh, Luffy...
What?!
There won't be any fish around then.
A rash is breaking out all over his body!
He's losing his resistance!
What should we do?!
Now...
I've got to become stronger and stronger!
This poison is so severe!
Luffy may have strong antibodies but it's...
Emergency food...
Don't look at me!
Luffy, stay with us!
Pirates...
Hey, it's just fish poison!
I thought you were gonna be the King of the Pirates!
Mm-hm, mm-hm, mm-hm, I see. I'm sorry.
And the Four Emperors...
I'll bring them all down!
Luffy! Don't die!
Luffy-san!
I thought it was an enemy ship.
Hey, please!
I bet you have antidotes!
Luffy! You got a bite!
Yeah, I hijacked the ship from a pirate group.
I'll present it to Mama myself.
We used all we got but he still needs more!
No, I'm the one who brings
the Four Emperors down!
Oh!
Do you have something sweet in that ship?
There's a fish! It's huge!
Hey!
If you're Sanji-san's brother,
please save Luffy-san!
--Of course.
--Mama will be happy then!
It's a surprise.
Don't report to her about that ship.
I'm sorry.
I have no interest in saving people.
Oh, that's wonderful!
Grount!
Understood! Pekoms-sama, that's very cool!
Or do you wanna try and
rob the medicine from us?
Hey, Grount!
--Are you okay?!
--Grount!
--Pull it up, Luffy!
--Luffy-san, go...
Like pirates?
Okay, let's run!
Oh, he's waking up!
What a jerk!
Grount!
He's totally different from Sanji-kun!
Even though he likes girls too!
You can do it, Luffy!
Food...
He's not kind at all!
I think it's gonna work out.
Nutrition...
You guys...
Luffy!
Just say the word if you want me to kill him!
Hey!
Pull!
Where's Straw Hat?!
Luffy-san...
Before we knew it, he was gone.
--I wanna see!
--Just a little more patience.
Yonji.
--Where is the Submerge?
--That way!
Stop being so stingy!
Where are Luffy and Chopper?
Damn!
Yonji-sama!
What's going on?!
As I thought, the man worth 500
million was something else!
You pests!
I can't let you pass through here.
I don't see them.
Don't tell me they set foot
on the island already!
He was.
That's how Ms. Nami's captain should be.
Have you ever imagined
how many people are living in fear and tears...
That's not fair!
Luffy!
Food!
Jeez... They're so troublesome...
Oh, Reiju-sama!
He did it!
...from your barbarous acts?!
We'll catch Straw Hat next time for sure!
Luffy!
It's very big!
All for your selfish dreams,
Let's eat!
despite the misery you cause,
you guys call it an adventure!
Of course!
Luffy!
Hurry up, Chopper!
Wait for me, Luffy!
And as Navy soldiers, we can't let you off!
--Luffy-san!
--No!
What are you guys doing?!
Come on, Chopper!
It can't be helped. I was starving...
--Let's go!
--Yeah!
Sorry! I ate too much!
That was good!
An invader!
You already ate at the base!
Otherwise...
Who are you?!
I'll be demoted!
I can't believe it didn't
even last 10 minutes...
So you're doing it for your own benefit?!
Look at that!
Luffy! What are we gonna do?!
--Divert course to the west.
--Yes, sir.
Well, we'll be fine!
Bricks and houses and everything...
They're all...
That's how fine-tuned justice works!
Oh yeah?! Then...
Aren't we going back?
Hey, listen to me!
And now, I'll take your lives!
It's about time he got here.
Let's go welcome him.
Hello. I'm sorry.
...made of chocolate!
Oh, I see.
A chocolate town!
Straw Hat Luffy!
A man worth 500 million!
It's like a dream!
My young brother is a cold-blooded jackass.
I can't wait.
Yeah.
Unforeseen trouble puts
Luffy's life in jeopardy!
The Straw Hats get overwhelmed
by Germa 66's formidable abilities!
On the sweet, sweet chocolate island,
Grount recalls former Navy Admiral Aokiji!
Sanji is separated from his friends,
being transported in the snow
Luffy meets a lovely pastry chef, Pudding!
Then, a giant ship appears out
of nowhere and, surprisingly,
As the moribund Luffy lies writhing
in agony from the intense poison
to the Whole Cake Island
where his arch-nemesis
Luffy struggles against the
Navy's desperate resistance
Meanwhile, as the clock is ticking
down to the hellish tea party,
Germa 66 and Emperor Big
Mom are waiting for him.
with death approaching moment by moment,
standing on the deck is a
man with twirly eyebrows!
and when Grount stands in his way again,
blood is shed among screams in the New World!
Sanji's sister Reiju's bewitching lips
suddenly close in on him!
The mysterious man and Luffy's team
get ready for an unavoidable battle!
a decisive battle between a
pirate and a Navy soldier,
Singing and dancing to a song of madness,
And to rescue Sanji,
Luffy and the others get into a new battle!
each with their pride at stake, begins!
the last one of the Four
Emperors shows herself!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Zero and Four! Encountering Germa 66!"
"Sanji's Homecoming! Into Big Mom's Territory!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Totto Land! Emperor Big Mom Appears!"
"A Deadly Poison Crisis! Luffy and Reiju!"
"The Devil's Fist! A Show
Down! Luffy vs. Grount!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!