kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji from Emperor Big Mom,
Luffy and the others were heading
for the Whole Cake Island.
But now they're facing a
serious food shortage...
They snuck into a Navy base
which they stumbled upon
and managed to steal some food.
But there are young soldiers
who are willing to take down Luffy.
You pests!
I can't let you pass through here.
I'll take your lives!
"The Devil's Fist!
A Show Down! Luffy vs. Grount!"
I won't let you get away, Straw Hat Luffy!
I don't really care if you take
that small amount of food. But...
...since this island is
the frontline base against Big Mom,
if the HQ finds out that we were
messed with by you pirates,
especially one from the Worst Generation...
I'll be reassigned with
my retirement at hand!
If I get demoted,
my pension will be cut significantly!
My well-funded retirement
plan will be ruined!
What?!
He can't stop speaking frankly!
Anyway, the Submerge is right there!
If we can get to it, we win!
And mission accomplished!
What is he gonna do?! Don't tell me...
That's right!
--Brook!
--Blown up with the Submerge?!
I used to fight your
grandfather with this often.
My grandpa?
That's right! When we were young,
it was evenly matched against his fists!
I fought Garp with this Haki-filled ammo!
Do you want a taste of it?!
That was sudden and close!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
It's not working!
Why's that?!
What's going on?!
It's been a few hours
since you invaded the base!
That was enough time for us
to come up with a countermeasure!
All we did was put rubber on shields,
but doesn't it work well?!
Shields can't stop me!
Nice try.
Thunder isn't my only weapon!
Don't underestimate me!
Mirage Tempo!
What?!
Gust Sword!
Gum-Gum Hawk Whip!
Straw Hat!
They're having a big fight!
Grount! Wake up and get up on
your feet already! Let's go!
I'm not going.
What's wrong?
Ms. Nami is waiting for me.
I'm useless.
Too weak!
I'm too weak!
Grount...
You fool...!
What's wrong with you?!
I thought you were better than this!
No matter who you were up against,
you always took a stand!
Have you lost the guts?! Well?!
It's no use.
Let's go!
Bonham has got the Breath Qigong.
I've got these swords.
You've got your left arm.
Have you forgotten what
the admiral taught us?
What the admiral taught us...?
Gum-Gum...
...Eagle Bazooka!
Yes!
Vice Admiral Prodi!
Those guys...
Straw Hat!
It's a return match!
Admiral...
Aokiji-san...
What the hell...
Let's stop by for a bit...
Oh, so...
I guess you did this, didn't you, boy?
Well, you can't undo what you did...
Oh, no...
Stop!
I don't want this arm! Cut it off!
Cut it off!
NAVY
Admiral! Wait a minute!
Why should I be on stand-by
again?! I can fight!
I've been working harder than anyone else
to become a full-fledged soldier!
Well, um... What can I say?
You're still a fledgling and not ready yet.
I can even control this arm now!
So...
Damn!
Well, that's what I'm talking about.
I don't want it to go out of
control in the middle of a battle.
Once you set out to sea in the future,
you'll face relentless outlaws.
Let me ask you.
If you encounter nemeses
like that, what will you do?
Anyway, there's no need to rush.
You'll see someday.
Well, good luck.
I see... So this is what
Aokiji-san was talking about.
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
Luffy! Are you okay?
--I'm okay! What about the food?!
--We got it!
But Brook...
Everybody!
Glad to finally see you again!
What a relief!
Brook!
Gee, we were worried about you!
Yeah, he fired at me all of a sudden
and I was scared half to death!
I'm already dead though!
Of course, the Submerge is safe too!
Oh, that was really terrible!
I thought I was a goner!
--I guess I am already gone though!
--We can finally go back to the ship!
Straw Hat!
You're the guy from earlier!
I'm not gonna let you get away!
Grount, you finally came!
Bonham! Zappa!
Leave the rest to me!
Straw Hat! Fight me!
I will take you down with my left arm!
I have to thank you, Straw Hat.
You woke me up!
Straw Hat!
I'm going to...
...best you!
--Grount!
--He finally did it!
Guys.
Go ahead.
Okay! Let's go!
--Uh-huh!
--Brook!
What's your name?
I'm Grount!
Here we go!
Gum-Gum Jet Pistol!
Gear Three!
Straw Hat! Is that all you got?!
Gratin, you're quite strong!
All right!
Gum-Gum...
Cut the "Gum-Gum" crap!
...Thor Elephant...
...Gun!
No! My retirement plan!
I've got to become stronger and stronger!
Grount!
Hey, Grount!
Oh, he's waking up!
Grount!
You guys...
Where's Straw Hat?!
Before we knew it, he was gone.
Damn!
As I thought, the man worth 500
million was something else!
He was.
That's how Ms. Nami's captain should be.
We'll catch Straw Hat next time for sure!
Of course!
What are you guys doing?!
It can't be helped. I was starving...
Sorry! I ate too much!
That was good!
You already ate at the base!
I can't believe it didn't
even last 10 minutes...
Luffy! What are we gonna do?!
Well, we'll be fine!
Oh yeah?! Then...
Hey, listen to me!
Straw Hat Luffy!
A man worth 500 million!
Sanji is separated from his friends,
being transported in the snow
to the Whole Cake Island
where his arch-nemesis
Germa 66 and Emperor Big
Mom are waiting for him.
And to rescue Sanji,
Luffy and the others get into a new battle!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sanji's Homecoming! Into Big Mom's Territory!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!