I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Luffy and the others had reached
the Phantom Island, Zou.
They met its residents, the Mink Tribe,
and reunited with Nami and the rest.
TEA PARTY
However, Sanji was pressed into marrying
Emperor Big Mom's daughter
and suddenly left his friends behind.
TO MY BUDS, I'VE GOTTA GO SEE A WOMAN.
I'LL BE BACK. SANJI
On top of that, Luffy and company learned
that
Kin'emon and the others'
home, the Land of Wano,
is currently under Emperor Kaido's reign.
Therefore, to take down Kaido,
they formed an alliance
with the samurai from the
Land of Wano and the Minks.
Split up temporarily from Zoro and the others
who started preparing to fight Kaido,
Luffy's team is heading for the Whole Cake Island
where Big Mom waits to take back Sanji!
"Sanji's Homecoming!
Into Big Mom's Territory!"
I'm hungry... Do something...
Me too... Oh, I feel so weak...
We're losing weight...
I don't have any flesh to lose though.
The ship's gonna turn over!
Furl the sail!
I can't!
Can we really get to
the Whole Cake Island like this?
I'm starving...
Hunger can't beat me!
We'll rescue you at any cost, Sanji!
Ship! Ship! Ship! Ship!
Ship! Ship!
I thought it was snow but...
It's Cotton Candy Flurry-soir!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Your Transponder Snail won't stop ringing.
Sweat!
It's receiving Warning Signals-bon.
That means
we're in Mama's territory already-soufflé.
Will those Warning Signals
reach over there too?
You catch on quickly! That's TARTE 28.
It's an outpost where a platoon from the Big
Mom Pirates is standing ready-millefeuille!
If this weren't one of Mama's ships,
they'd attack us like "Boom."
Now, have you made up your mind?
Don't be so stubborn.
Just swear allegiance to us, Big Mom Pirates,
along with Germa 66-bon.
That's what your father wants-amour.
Don't talk about him!
It makes me sick to my stomach!
Our relationship has already been broken off!
I only came to bring this to a close!
Don't try to act strong.
Mama is in a more welcoming
mood than you think.
Of course, she knows you're
that foolish Straw Hat's crewmember-il vous plaît.
But she thinks highly of you
for once being a chef at
the Sea Restaurant in the East Blue-bon.
You can get even better treatment
depending on how well you cook-jour.
Screw that!
Listen! These hands are only
meant to cook for my friends!
For that purpose,
I even trained myself in hell!
I can picture them missing my cooking
and crying by now!
That's absurd!
You people don't even care that
one of your friends was killed.
I have no dish to cook for such assholes!
Oh, you're talking about Pekoms, huh?
He let his personal feelings interfere with his work.
Bege did the right thing.
Baron Tamago.
Vito!
We got a picture of Pudding-sama
from the Whole Cake Island-rero!
So you can prepare yourself.
They understand that it's
hard to marry someone
who you meet for the first
time. It was so kind of them.
It doesn't make any difference, idiot!
I'm not gonna get married!
At least, take a look at it.
Shut up! Stay away or I'll kick you to death!
Well, come on.
Cut it out...
This is your fiancée.
The 35th daughter of the Charlotte Family.
Charlotte Pudding-sama!
Ship, ship, ship! Ship!
What did you think of the bride?
She's cute, isn't she-rorero?
You were glad to see her, weren't you-rero?
Rero?
Are you ignoring me? Well, that's okay.
By the way, have you ever read the WEJ?
The WEJ-rero, you know? The
World Economic Journal!
You know it, don't you-rero?
There was this comic strip in the WEJ!
A giant dreamlike robot featured in it!
Sora, Warrior of the Sea!
I've been constantly reading it-rero!
Sora, a hero who can walk on water,
accompanied by a transforming
robot and a sea gull-rorero,
fights the evil armies of Germa 66.
It's a story of a marine hero!
SORA, WARRIOR OF THE SEA
It has fans all over the world!
I heard it's based on true
stories of naval heroes.
NAVY
So it's sort of educational
material to brainwash children!
To teach them "The Navy is
always right and strong"!
But that's not what I like about it!
It's Germa! Germa 66!
They're evil armies that always corner Sora
by all possible means!
They're evil heroes!
--Hey, listen-rero!
--Shut up!
Yes, they get defeated for the
sake of the story every time
but I'd always supported them
with a white-knuckled intensity!
I supported you guys!
Don't include me!
I have nothing to do with them!
Don't say such a thing!
I'm kind of happy to see you in person actually!
Why don't you tell that to them?
Hey, open!
Door!
Listen...
Stop following me!
I thought this was my room!
This room belongs to me, too!
Let me out! Dammit!
Why are you treating me so differently?!
I'm a genius scientist!
Haven't you given up yet?!
We were only told to capture you, Caesar!
But he is a precious groom who will
connect the Vinsmoke Family
and us - the Charlotte Family!
You two are different in value.
I'm not gonna get married.
Just get out.
"Get out"?!
He's just been mean to Vito!
"HITMAN" GOTTI
THE FIRE TANK PIRATES
I can't stand it! Apologize to him!
Gotti! Whoa, wait! Wait!
He hasn't been that mean to me!
I'm okay. Thanks. We were
just messing around-rorero.
I wasn't.
Gotti. I want both you and Vito out!
Oh, you said it again!
You're a dead man!
No, Gotti!
You can say whatever you like to me!
But I can't tolerate anyone
who insults my friends!
I said "Wait"! Please don't do it-rero!
You don't have to tolerate me.
It's not like I wanna be your friend.
Son of a...
Gotti!
What are you doing?!
Ma'am!
Gotti!
Do you know that he's Vinsmoke's son?!
If you lay so much as a finger on him,
your Father's head will roll!
Can't you get it?! Huh?!
Do you want me to chop your head off first,
you dummy?!
Ouch! I'm sorry! Ma'am! I'm sorry!
Hey, you...
I'm sorry. You're our important guest.
Forget about this idiot
and make yourself comfortable.
Ow, ow, ow!
I'm sorry! Ma'am! I'm sorry!
No food for you today as punishment!
No, please, ma'am!
Sorry to bother you.
Let me hear about Germa some other time...
Nope.
Well...
She resembles her...
Damn! How dare they mess with me!
I'm gonna be killed! Big Mom will kill me!
You're so lucky.
Even when you see Big Mom,
they'll treat you well and protect your life.
Just because you have Vinsmoke's
blood in your veins!
A FEW DAYS LATER
I can't take it anymore... I'm gonna die...
It's hot... I'm gonna die...
(I'm gonna be dried up...)
(Sanji, food! Ice cream!)
I can't stand the heat...
I wish I could take off this fur skin...
We're like you...
We Minks have low tolerance for heat.
It's really hot.
I'm gonna become a mummy...
A mummy...
A mummy?
A mummy!
Nami-san, if I become a mummy,
--it'd be a little bit of a resurrection for me, isn't it?
--I don't care.
In that case, may I see your panties?
I have no energy even to smack you.
Nami, I'm so hungry and it's hot...
I need nutrition...
We're out of food and we couldn't fish
because it'd been stormy for days
and finally it's clear.
Catch some fish somehow
before the weather changes!
We're all gonna starve to death
before we get there!
Food...
We wanna do so but Nami...
The water is boiling because it's too hot!
What?!
There won't be any fish around then.
What should we do?!
Emergency food...
Don't look at me!
Luffy! You got a bite!
There's a fish! It's huge!
--Pull it up, Luffy!
--Luffy-san, go...
You can do it, Luffy!
Food...
Nutrition...
Luffy!
Pull!
Luffy-san...
Food!
He did it!
Luffy!
It's very big!
Let's eat!
--Divert course to the west.
--Yes, sir.
Aren't we going back?
It's about time he got here.
Let's go welcome him.
Oh, I see.
I can't wait.
Yeah.
Unforeseen trouble puts
Luffy's life in jeopardy!
Then, a giant ship appears out
of nowhere and, surprisingly,
standing on the deck is a
man with twirly eyebrows!
The mysterious man and Luffy's team
get ready for an unavoidable battle!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Zero and Four! Encountering Germa 66!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!