I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Sanji, the cook of the Straw Hats,
suddenly left his friends behind.
He was being pressed into marrying
Emperor Big Mom's daughter.
Split up temporarily from
Zoro and the others,
Luffy's team is heading for the Whole Cake Island
where Big Mom waits to take back Sanji!
Meanwhile, Sanji is...
She thinks highly of you for once being a chef
at the Sea Restaurant in the East Blue-bon.
You can get even better treatment
depending on how well you cook-jour.
Screw that!
Listen!
These hands are only meant to cook for my friends!
This is your fiancée.
The 35th daughter of the Charlotte Family.
Charlotte Pudding-sama!
(I'm gonna be dried up...)
(Sanji, food! Ice cream!)
Luffy! You got a bite!
--Pull it up, Luffy!
--Luffy-san, go...
You can do it, Luffy!
Food...
Nutrition...
Luffy!
Pull!
Luffy-san...
Food!
"Zero and Four!
Encountering Germa 66!"
It...
It's pulling me!
Hey! You pulled it all the way up!
Luffy-san!
I won't let it get away!
It's so powerful! This is gonna be a tough haul!
Until it gets weak!
Food!
--He's going crazy!
--Luffy, stay cool!
Don't rush!
Food! Food! Food!
Food! Food! Food! Food! Food!
Gum-Gum...
...Hook, Line and Sinker!
Ow, ow...
I did it!
Nice! Nice!
We're gonna be alright now.
But this fish...
Its color doesn't seem right.
Is it okay to eat?
It's pretty doubtful...
What are you saying?!
There's no such thing as an inedible fish!
Luffy! Wait a sec!
I'll go check real quick!
What?
Sanji. I'm sorry but I
have to open your locker.
Ouch!
Wh-What the hell?
Where's the encyclopedia of fish?!
Sanji's bookshelf is full of nudity!
Found it!
Alright.
No, this is not it.
Neither's this one...
Here it is!
Hm? Sanji's cooking note?
Let's see.
What?!
Luffy! Watch out for its skin!
The skin of that fish is extremely poisonous!
Look! I found Sanji's note!
The skin tastes good!
Luffy! Wait! I'll grill it for you!
Here, try it, Carrot.
The skin's so slimy...
Luffy!
Extremely poisonous?
What?
Whaaat...
No!
Oops, I ate it.
What about you guys?!
No one else has eaten any.
--That's good.
--No, it's not.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm good as new.
Is it really highly poisonous?
That's what Sanji's note says.
It's no mistake.
Then what should we do about this fish?
If we can't eat it, we should just dump it.
What?!
I've gone through so much trouble to catch it!
Well, Sanji's note says
if you peel the skin off, you can eat it.
He even put down a recipe.
Yay! Okay, I'll cook it!
--What?!
--Do you wanna start a fire again?!
I don't ever wanna eat
your Kitchen Sink Curry again!
Luffy, you wait here! I'll do it!
Tsk!
Luffy, are you really all right?
--Why?
--Because of the poison?!
I'm totally fine!
O-Okay...
Let's see... What do I do next?
Salt.
Pepper.
Coriander.
Some grated garlic and ginger...
Smells good!
This is what I'd expect from Sanji-kun's recipe.
Okay! Here you go!
Wow! Can I eat it?!
--Of course, you can! Eat as much as you like!
--Thanks!
--Shall we eat too?
--Yes!
It's delicious! It's so delicious, Nami!
--Yes, it even makes me cry!
--I'm so happy to be alive! Grr!
It's so good!
I just cooked it like it
said in Sanji-kun's note.
Chopper, you need energy too, first.
Eat it.
Luffy's gonna... d-die!
I-It's cold...
Crying isn't gonna help!
Here! To take care of Luffy,
you have to gain energy, Chopper!
Now, eat!
Okay!
But even if I wanna treat him,
we're short of antidotal herbs!
Yum!
We gotta find an island, Nami!
We're lacking herbs!
Yum!
Food...
But it's not that easy to find an island...
Sanji-kun's encyclopedia says
it's extremely poisonous
and kills you instantly if
you eat the skin, right?
Yeah.
Yum!
But he's still alive!
Doesn't that mean he has strong antibodies?
He has one of the best vital powers
of all humankind!
But he's in very bad shape!
Yum!
Luffy, are you okay?
The river is... beautiful...
He's seeing the River Styx!
What? Luffy-san?!
Yum!
Is he dying?
Luffy!!
Yum!
Unfortunately for Straw Hat,
we can't look for herbs now.
We're about to reach Mama's territory.
There are some islands in the area
around the Whole Cake Island.
I'd say Black-Foot and the others
have passed through those islands
and reached the Whole Cake Island by now.
Don't lower your guard, guys...
I'll stand guard!
I was gonna stop by at the first island.
Let's get an antidote there.
Okay.
What? This time, it's snow?
It's beautiful!
It's not snow! Are those Sugar Clouds?!
That's right.
And it's Cotton Candy Flurry that's falling.
What?! Cotton candy?!
Nice! Nice!
Sweet...
Here we are finally…
Ring, ring, ring...
--Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
--Oh? Who is it?
Your Transponder Snail is receiving
Warning Signals.
That means we're in Big
Mom's territory for sure.
We're finally here.
Cotton candy!
Guys! Hide or disguise yourself!
So sweet!
Are you listening?!
I see something, Pekoms!
It's a ship! A ship is coming towards us!
What?! Are they here already?!
What do you mean?!
--That's probably a TARTE, one of our scout ships.
--What?!
--I can't see it clearly because of the fog.
--What should we do?
--I'll handle it somehow so all of you, go hide!
--Got it!
--Oh, no! Luffy is looking really sick!
--What?!
The poison must've spread
into his system even more!
It's dangerous! We gotta treat him A.S.A.P.!
Don't they have an antidote
on that scout ship?!
--I'll ask them for you! Hurry up and hide!
--Okay!
Chopper-san, hurry up!
What?!
No, that's not a TARTE!
Luffy...
Is that a Transponder Snail?
It's huge!
There is a number.
Sixty-six?
This is Germa.
Is that the Straw Hats' ship?
That's Germa 66's ship!
Germa 66...
The organization led by Sanji-kun's father...
Also known as the Warmongers!
Why are you here, Straw Hats?!
We're gonna collide!
Guys, furl the sail!
Luffy, I'll be back.
We managed to avoid the crash...
Sanji!
Oh, that twirly eyebrow! It's Sanji-san!
What? Sanji? Is that Sanji?!
Sanji!
Sanji-kun!
Great!
I didn't expect to see you this soon!
How lucky we are...
Hey, Sanji! We have a problem!
Luffy got poisoned by eating fish and is dying!
Is there any antidote on that ship?!
Sanji!
Are you listening, Sanji?!
Stop calling me "Sanji"!
You got the wrong person!
Well, of course I look like him.
My name is Yonji!
VINSMOKE YONJI
GERMA 66 (WINCH GREEN)
Yonji?!
Not "San(three)-ji" but "Yon(four)-ji"?!
He resembles him
and has twirly eyebrows but he's not him?!
My relationship with your friend Sanji
is a secret of secrets.
It's absolutely confidential!
He's definitely his younger brother...
So he also had a younger brother...
What?! How can you tell
that's his younger brother?!
Because his name is Yonji!
Cutie!! Cute, so cute...
Are you really not Sanji?!
Yonji-sama.
I don't think they are transporting
Sanji-sama on that ship.
So I guess we missed each other.
You're right. Let's go back.
It was a wasted trip.
Wait, Sanji!
I'm Yonji!
Oh, Luffy...
A rash is breaking out all over his body!
He's losing his resistance!
This poison is so severe!
Luffy may have strong antibodies but it's...
Luffy, stay with us!
Hey, it's just fish poison!
I thought you were gonna be the King of the Pirates!
Luffy! Don't die!
Luffy-san!
Hey, please!
I bet you have antidotes!
We used all we got but he still needs more!
Hey!
If you're Sanji-san's brother,
please save Luffy-san!
I'm sorry.
I have no interest in saving people.
Or do you wanna try and
rob the medicine from us?
Like pirates?
What a jerk!
He's totally different from Sanji-kun!
Even though he likes girls too!
He's not kind at all!
Just say the word if you want me to kill him!
Yonji.
Stop being so stingy!
Yonji-sama!
What's going on?!
Luffy!
Oh, Reiju-sama!
--Luffy-san!
--No!
An invader!
Who are you?!
Hello. I'm sorry.
My young brother is a cold-blooded jackass.
The Straw Hats get overwhelmed
by Germa 66's formidable abilities!
As the moribund Luffy lies writhing
in agony from the intense poison
with death approaching moment by moment,
Sanji's sister Reiju's bewitching lips
suddenly close in on him!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Deadly Poison Crisis! Luffy and Reiju!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!