kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Sanji, the cook of the Straw Hats,
suddenly left his friends behind.
He was being pressed into marrying
Emperor Big Mom's daughter.
Split up temporarily from
Zoro and the others,
Luffy's team is heading for the
Whole Cake Island where Big
Mom waits to take back Sanji.
But Luffy is currently on the verge of
life and death
after eating a giant highly-venomous fish.
Well, of course I look like him.
My name is Yonji!
Luffy-san!
Hey, please!
I bet you have antidotes!
We used all we got but he still needs more!
I'm sorry.
I have no interest in saving people.
Or do you wanna try and
rob the medicine from us?
Like pirates?
Stop being so stingy!
Who are you?!
Hello. I'm sorry.
My young brother is a cold-blooded jackass.
"A Deadly Poison Crisis!
Luffy and Reiju!"
Young brother?
Are you his sister?
VINSMOKE REIJU
GERMA 66 (POISON PINK)
Her eyebrows are twirly too!
She's gorgeous!
Reiju!
Is he flying?!
You moron!
How could you humiliate me?!
Shut up!
You should be ashamed of yourself!
What? Is he hovering in the air?
Is he a Devil Fruit eater?
If so, he should've been weakened
by falling into the water!
But it looks different from
Sanji-kun or CP9 members' special skills, too.
That's not a skill he
acquired through training.
It's science!
What?!
Germa 66 is a group of fighters
who have honed themselves with science.
They are a scientific
fighting squad, if you will.
And Mama is...
...looking to get that technology!
What?! He's using mechanical power to hover?!
Cool!
Sanji-kun's family is unbelievable.
Germa 66...
The Vinsmoke Family that leads it...
Pekoms-san, if I'm correct,
Vinsmoke was...
...the name of a royal family, wasn't it?
If I remember right, it was a family that
conquered the North Blue
by force of arms long ago!
By "royal family,"
you mean like Vivi and Neptune?!
What? Are they such a prominent family?
That's right. They were synonymous
with "evil" in a past age.
That's why they were used as
models for the comic strip.
Skeleton-san,
you have so much historical knowledge.
I've lived a long time...
I'm dead now though.
But it's not just a story from the past.
We're still a royal family.
Germa is a country without soil.
We have no land to govern
but we're given the right to attend the Reverie.
Oh, I beg your pardon.
If that is so, may I see your panties?
Stop it!
Broken bones...
Okay, now, can I have it?
Can you have... what?
Looks like he ate an Armored-Stone Fish
from the Boiling Sea, didn't he?
What? How did you know?
How this venom works is unique.
He must be greedy.
It could even kill a Giant instantly.
What?! Oh, no!
Then, there's no way to save Luffy...
I shouldn't be a ship doctor anymore!
But this boy is lucky.
Because this venom is...
...one of my favorite things!
Wh-What are you gonna do?
Let's have it!
Smooch!!
Wh-What are you doing?!
So daring...
What?! Whoa-whoa-whoa!
If you suck up venom like that, you're gonna die!
Oh! I'm jealous! Smooch!
I wish I could change places with him!
Even though my lips...
...are gone!
The rash is transferring to her body!
What?!
The rash on Luffy's body is all gone!
You've sucked it all out?! Are you alright?!
Yes, of course. I'm Poison Pink.
Poison...
Pink?
It was delicious!
What?! What happened?!
Luffy!
--I'm so relieved!
--Are you all right?!
What a relief!
Luffy!
Oh? Did I fall asleep while eating fish?
The skin was so good! Is there any left?
--No! Don't you remember?!
--Nope.
You were on the verge of life and death!
You gave us a lot of trouble!
Oh, did I?
Sanji!
She's a woman!
Oh, right. Who is this?
Luffy-san, she saved your life!
What? Thank you for... what again?
So that's Straw Hat Luffy...
Oh! You're Sanji's sister!
Yes.
Sanji is one of us, the Vinsmoke Family.
Our father parted from Sanji
when he was a little kid
and has been looking for him.
When Sanji's wanted poster was circulated
two years ago,
our father immediately asked the Navy HQ
to pursue him.
But they found the wrong man -
someone named Duval.
Duval!
He's the guy from the Flying Fish Riders
who we met before Sabaody...
Why... Why do I have to be chased by
the Navy Headquarters?!
Why do I have to be nearly killed by
some ill-regarded bounty hunters?!
Oh, I remember!
Sanji-san was mad about it too.
It was only recently
that the Government called us saying...
...that they finally captured an image
of Black-Foot Sanji amid the chaos
evoked by the Straw Hats' comeback.
Our father raised the bounty right away
and made them change "DEAD OR ALIVE"...
...to "ONLY ALIVE."
That's why only Sanji-kun's poster was
changed a little bit.
Where is Sanji now?
I don't know.
Maybe he's with Big Mom or with our father.
We came to greet him
but I think we missed each other.
Well, if he can attend the tea party,
that's all that matters.
And I got to see you guys too.
Thank you for looking after my brother
all this time.
Sanji's sister!
Thank you for saving my life.
But...
I still want Sanji back! He's my friend!
I'm gonna take back Sanji at any cost!
See? She saved our enemy's life.
Hey, you!
You're Pekoms from the Big Mom Pirates, right?
Why are you with the Straw Hats?
I have my own reason!
Why do I have to explain it to you guys?! Grr!
There's no bond between us yet!
You're right!
I'll pretend that I didn't
see anything for now.
Yeah, we don't wanna cause trouble and
break off our brother's marriage.
We'd best all tread lightly.
That'd be smart! Grr!
Unanchor the ship. Let's go back.
Well, good luck.
Reiju-san... I wanted to see her panties.
I have no energy to even smack you.
Okay, we should get going too.
--Yeah!
--Uh-huh!
They didn't get into a fight with Germa,
it seems.
Yes, I'm sure that's their ship.
Straw Hat Luffy is on board too.
What do you wanna do?
Jimbei.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
--Shut up!
--I'm still examining you. Don't move.
It's not gonna stop by picking up.
It's a Warning Signal.
Seems like there's nothing wrong.
Yep!
How resilient you are.
Or maybe it's Reiju's strange power that's amazing.
Probably both.
Good for you, Luffy! Munch!
I'm kind of hungry again!
Should I fish again?
No!
That's what I'm supposed to say,
but we're still in a food crisis.
You're right.
Don't worry. We'll see an island soon.
You mean an island in Big Mom's territory?
Yeah, let me give you some extra information
while I can.
There are a total of 34 islands
around the Whole Cake Island.
That many?!
There are 34 ministers, one for each island,
to run the place.
They call this vast marine area...
...Totto Land!
Totto Land...
Ring, ring, ring...
We're already in the area
so why don't you disguise yourself?!
What's the matter?!
It's coming!
There's another incoming ship!
Maybe Reiju-san's clan is coming back!
Who is that?
No, this time, it's surely one of our TARTEs!
Our scout ship!
I told you to be ready!
You guys, hide in the cabin!
Why?!
If they find you, it's gonna be trouble!
Pekoms-san, are you going to be okay?
If Germa didn't alert them, it's gonna be okay.
Hurry up!
We're counting on you!
Now...
Mm-hm, mm-hm, mm-hm, I see. I'm sorry.
I thought it was an enemy ship.
Yeah, I hijacked the ship from a pirate group.
I'll present it to Mama myself.
Oh!
Do you have something sweet in that ship?
--Of course.
--Mama will be happy then!
It's a surprise.
Don't report to her about that ship.
Oh, that's wonderful!
Understood! Pekoms-sama, that's very cool!
I think it's gonna work out.
Hey!
--I wanna see!
--Just a little more patience.
Where are Luffy and Chopper?
I don't see them.
Don't tell me they set foot
on the island already!
That's not fair!
Jeez... They're so troublesome...
Hurry up, Chopper!
Wait for me, Luffy!
Come on, Chopper!
--Let's go!
--Yeah!
Look at that!
Bricks and houses and everything...
They're all...
...made of chocolate!
A chocolate town!
It's like a dream!
On the sweet, sweet chocolate island,
Luffy meets a lovely pastry chef, Pudding!
Meanwhile, as the clock is ticking
down to the hellish tea party,
blood is shed among screams in the New World!
Singing and dancing to a song of madness,
the last one of the Four
Emperors shows herself!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Totto Land! Emperor Big Mom Appears!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!