I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Sanji, the cook of the Straw Hats,
suddenly left his friends behind.
He was being pressed into marrying
Emperor Big Mom's daughter.
Split up temporarily from
Zoro and the others,
Luffy's team is heading for the
Luffy's team is heading for the Whole Cake Island
where Big Mom waits to take back Sanji.
Luffy's team is heading for the
Whole Cake Island where Big
Mom waits to take back Sanji.
Mom waits to take back Sanji!
Meanwhile, on the Whole Cake Island...
On the way there, they secretly
stopped by at Chocolat Town,
They came across Germa 66's ship
Croquembouche!
The girl who they met at
Chocolat Town on Cacao Island was...
Croquembouche!
none of the outermost towns of
Totto Land, for food supplies
and met Sanji's siblings, Yonji and Reiju.
Big Mom was having a Hunger Pangs attack
and destroying everything.
Are you the Big Mom's daughter
who's gonna get married to Sanji, Pudding?!
but they got in trouble by eating a
She wouldn't stop rampaging
until she got a bite of what she was craving,
Croquembouche!
whole cafe and were saved by
the owner of the cafe, Pudding.
Mm-hm.
Oh no! It's Mama's illness!
I won't tell Mama about
Straw Hat-san and the rest of you!
and the Whole Cake Island
sustained great damage.
So your name is Pudding.
Thank you for helping us!
Hurry up-bon!
What does she want this time-soir?!
The rash on Luffy's body is all gone!
The one who handled the situation was
the former Warlord - Jimbei.
I am scared of Mama but I've made up my mind!
No, no! I'm the one who
should be thanking you!
She wants...
It was delicious!
...croquembouche!
Sanji's sister!
Why?
Issue an evacuation order in Sweet City!
Because you said...
If you all came to take back Sanji-san,
I'll help you!
It's delicious!
Thank you for saving my life.
Only a croquembouche can stop Mama now!
"It was too delicious"!
I'm here to...
But...
I haven't asked your name, have I?
Mama! Mama! Not in this city!
Take this route.
I still want Sanji back! He's my friend!
...tell you something important today.
I'm Luffy.
This is the only way you can get there
without Mama's seeing,
--She'll destroy her own castle!
--It's no good. She can't hear us.
The future Pirate King...
Hey!
What?
which only we children know of.
Is that where Sanji is?
Luffy?
If you go along this route,
you can get to the Whole Cake Island.
Croquembouche!
Look at that!
But Mama won't let go of Sanji-san.
"The Emperor's Daughter!
Sanji's fiancée - Pudding!"
Bricks and houses and everything...
They're all...
...made of chocolate!
"The Capital City Falls?!
Big Mom and Jimbei!"
So let's meet up at the southwest coast of
the Whole Cake Island tomorrow.
You're not gonna leave my crew, are you?
A chocolate town!
CHOCOLAT TOWN, CACAO ISLAND
I'll bring Sanji-san there at any price.
THE WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
"Totto Land!
Emperor Big Mom Appears!"
Luffy is...
I'll cooperate with you!
"The Emperor's Castle!
Arriving at the Whole Cake Island!"
There is a message in the bathroom!
TURN BACK
Oh, no!
"Turn back"?
This isn't it!
--Did Pekoms write this?
--Who else would do that?
Now that I look closer, you look familiar!
Straw Hat Luffy!
L-Look up!
Did somebody invade?
SWEET CITY
THE CAPITAL OF THE WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Has Pekoms been abducted?
That's right! I'm gonna be
the King of the Pirates!
Maybe they've found out about us.
Wow! There are so many kinds
of people and animals!
In any event, this is serious.
We're totally screwed.
What the...! What the...!
What's with this town?!
Where is it?! Croquembouche?!
"Turn back" means if we don't do so,
something's gonna happen.
Are you people really
the Straw Hats, the pirates?!
There are tons of chocolate and candies!
Yeah.
Yes, we are!
Okay, everyone,
keep that in mind!
What should I try first?!
What should I do?!
Moscato-sama!
Sanji-san's comrades?! You're kidding!
Let's go on!
Moscato-sama is dead!
Pine! Pine! Pine! Pine!
Chopper!
It's getting exciting!
I'm not kidding! Sanji is our buddy!
Look! Chocolate is pouring out!
Don't die, Moscato-sama!
Pine!
What? Do you know Sanji?
Moscato-sama!
Oh, I knew you wanted to start
with the fountain of chocolate!
"A Massive Attack!
Mom's Hunger Pangs!"
Help me!
The chocolate spout!
Wait a minute.
I can't stop thinking that I've heard
the name Pudding somewhere before...
This isn't it!
They're finally here.
BROCK COLLIE ISLAND, NEW WORLD
Yes, me too.
Help!
Uh-huh, you're right. Where was it?
Pudding... Pudding... Pudding...
So sweet!
--Hurry up and take him away.
--Yes, ma'am.
This isn't it either!
What's with this chocolate?
It's unbelievably good!
Step back.
Run!
Pudding?! Ah!
I can't stop!
Croquembouche...
The highlight of the party
will be a wedding ceremony.
CHOCOLATE BATHHOUSE
Where is it?!
"Chocolate Bathhouse"?!
The groom is the third son
of the Vinsmoke Family,
A chocolate bath?!
Listen, guys.
Can you really get cleaned
up? But I wanna try!
Every last second. Okay?
GROOM - THIRD SON OF THE
VINSMOKE FAMILY - SANJI
Sanji!
What?!
--Chocolate clothes?!
--Can you eat them?!
What?!!
The bride is the 35th daughter
of the Charlotte Family,
This isn't the taste!
BRIDE - 35TH DAUGHTER OF THE
CHARLOTTE FAMILY - PUDDING
Pudding.
He's eating it!
You losers aren't it either!
Marriage?!
Chocolate instruments?!
It's all wrong!
Moscato-sama...
Chocolate clocks?!
Damn!
Pudding-san, would you by
any chance happen to be
Chocolate fireworks?!
Say, do you think Boss Jimbei will
be killed too, Montd'Or-sama?!
a member of the Charlotte Family?
You set off chocolate?!
I am.
--So interesting!
--It's a paradise!
How do I know?!
I-It's no mistake.
When someone makes Mama angry,
this is surely what happens,
--All done?
--Yes, sir.
You should know this, Luffy!
Okay, let's go.
What is it, Chopper?
even if it's her own son!
I can't believe this!
I smell something really delicious!
If she keeps rampaging,
the capital city will fall apart-bon!
How dare you kill my wife?
What?!
What?! Let's go!
How dare you kill my children?
Isn't the croquembouche ready yet?!
How dare you destroy my country?
How is it, chef?! How's it going?!
Are you the Big Mom's daughter
who's gonna get married to Sanji, Pudding?!
I managed to cover for us
but we should not stay long. Grr!
You're Germa, aren't you?!
You guys are not human!
I'm still working on the
special cream filling
that gives you that smooth
feeling on your tongue!
Wall.
Mm-hm.
Whatever! Just hurry up!
We gotta do what we have to do and just go...
Sanji's fiancée...
Mama is coming closer
to the Whole Cake Chateau-soir!
I'm jealous! She'll be such a beautiful wife!
Here I am, everyone of the Sun Pirates!
We must stop her from destroying
this castle at any price!
Are you done?
W-Wife?!
What should we do?!
I heard Moscato-sama is heading there now!
A FEW HOURS AGO
Oh! But why?!
You people aren't even Mama's allies!
How did you pass the TARTE security?
Wow! This is cute!
Croquembouche!
Straw Hat Luffy will
change the world someday!
Oh, Nami, you look great!
Why did you come?!
Y-You're gonna be killed!
Thanks!
I can't believe it took four hours.
I know he is still young but
I don't think any one of the
Hey, look! My costume looks
quite nice too, right?
--Run somewhere far!
--Thank you!
You're already in Mama's territory
and she's a very scary pirate!
I have to attend my brother's wedding.
current Four Emperors will
become the king of the sea!
Oh, it's Moscato-sama!
Yeah, that's really gorgeous!
I think Straw Hat Luffy will be the one!
But I know you people are scary pirates too!
The 16th son of the Charlotte Family
and the Minister of Gelato!
I have no interest in your family.
He's a member of Mama's family!
I'm sure he can stop her!
How's this?
Do I look like a pirate, Broo...
No!
I...
This is Moscato! How's the croquembouche?!
Wait! Calm down!
We won't get rough with you!
CHARLOTTE MOSCATO
THE 16TH SON OF THE CHARLOTTE FAMILY
THE MINISTER OF GELATO
Nor your war for that matter.
...want to be of help to him!
What?
I heard it'll take half an hour or so
to be ready-bon!
Luffy, what should we do with her-gara?
It'll be too late by then!
We can't let her destroy the castle!
Don't get rough, Pedro!
Do you want more?
I'm too...
It's finished.
How could a war between such
weak countries last two years?
...weak!!
It's gonna take one more day to
get to the Whole Cake Island where Sanji is.
Let her go, Pedro.
I... I want to get on board his ship...
We came to take back Sanji.
--The commission?
--I got it.
This isn't it!
Go food shopping.
What?
Mama! Stop it!
...and dedicate my life to him!
Okay! Yay!
So you came for Sanji-san...
I believe that journey will bring true freedom
to the Fish-Men in the end!
I can't wait!
I wonder what kind of place it is!
Who is that?!
Pedro, do you have binoculars?!
To take him back.
Mama! It's me! Moscato!
Thanks! Let's see...
ALADDIN (A BROTULA MERMAN)
THE FIRST MATE OF THE SUN PIRATES
I knew he didn't consent
since Mama is so self-centered.
--Thank you!
For the last two years, you
told us a lot about Luffy-kun.
Wow! It's so diverse here, Pekoms!
--Thank you!
Where is my croquembouche?
She even uses her children's marriage
to strengthen her pirate group.
Our country has been saved.
Did we ask demons for help?
I see Minks, too!
It's like a wonderland!
I've been thinking you should go join him
if you like him so much.
Croquembouche...
We're giving up on marrying someone
freely out of love.
Yes, that's exactly what
Mama's dream is about.
Croquembouche!
No, we didn't! They're angels!
D-Did I really?!
Give us 30 minutes! The chefs are trying
to make it as quickly as they can!
Humans, Minks, Fish-men,
Longarms, Longlegs, Dwarves...
Did I talk about him so much?!
We only have two choices; give up or run.
Drop your weapons!
The war is over! It's over!
No, Big Bro Mos!
It's impossible to stop her!
One of my older sisters that I loved very dearly
went out to the sea looking for love.
A country where all races in the world
can live together without discrimination.
I can't let her ruin the capital!
Thank you, Germa!
Go, Jimbei!
Move out of my way!
No, I mean everything in the world!
Germa 66! Hurray!
To seek a match.
Germa! Germa! Germa! Germa!
Are you sure?
Everything in the world?
Just out of curiosity,
Yes, that's Mama's ideal world, Totto Land!
Can't you recognize me, Mama?!
No one here has the right to object, Captain!
it said you're the 35th daughter
of the Charlotte Family.
Yeah! You were a soldier of the Neptune Army
but you became a pirate...
TOTTO LAND
Does Big Mom have 35 daughters?
Realize you're already deep
into a great territory!
The wedding is in three days.
Well, she has 39 daughters and 46 sons.
This island is Cacao Island
run by the Minister of Chocolate.
Two days is enough
to get to the Whole Cake Island.
...to fight with us - the former slaves
who fled from Mariejois!
The name of the town is Chocolat Town!
What about Sanji?
We're 85 brothers and sisters.
You became a Warlord
to help advance the social status of us Fish-Men!
Life...
He's already here.
Chocolat Town?! What a wonderful name!
Oh, my!
...or...
Oh, great. I can't wait to see him.
Wow! That's so many brothers and sisters!
...treat!
Everything in this town is made of chocolate.
And you allied with the Big Mom Pirates
Yeah, right!
What?! I love chocolate!
Am I allowed to eat it?!
We have different fathers.
Mama has 43 husbands so we're a family of 129.
See you in two days.
to protect us and our home Ryugu Kingdom
under Big Mom's name.
Clank.
Grr! In this town,
you can eat chocolate all you like!
Life or treat...
What... 129?!
Yes!
Lifespan or snack!
You've always made choices
for the sake of others!
But be careful!
Some of my older brothers and sisters
already have children
You gotta be kidding, Mama!
He's your own son!
After their guide Pekoms disappeared,
Luffy's team left Cacao Island
It's against the law to eat
the roof-tile chocolates.
Because they won't be able
to keep off rain or snow.
so if you count them in, there are more.
Mama, don't do it!
and is following Pudding's directions
to the Whole Cake Island
Window glass is the Minister
of Candy's jurisdiction
W-We have whipped cream here-fa!
No dough yet but Mama, don't!
The Big Mom Pirates consist
mainly of her blood relatives.
and construction posts are
the Minister of Biscuit's.
where Emperor Big Mom is.
You did enough, Jimbei.
And everything else other than chocolate is
private or public property.
Th-The treat is not here yet!
I'm worried about Pekoms.
We gotta look for him!
I'll take the treat...
Yeah! Be free, Jimbei-san!
She's true to her name - Big Mom!
Looks delicious...
Hey! Were you listening?!
Thank you but that won't be easy.
He's a tough man so he'll be okay.
Don't get in my way!
--Go, Jimbei!
--Yeah, Captain Jimbei!
I couldn't understand at all.
Have you met Sanji?
Say, are their panties
also made of chocolate?
We'll be fine without you.
Don't underestimate us!
Yeah but...
I'm getting nervous.
Y-Y-Yes... just once.
Of course, they are.
Because we are going deeper into
the Emperor's territory.
Live for yourself from now on!
I can't wait to see chocolate panties!
Although his eyebrows are twirly,
he is very kind and gentlemanly!
We should just trust this map and go on.
We're not here to take a break.
At any rate, we need to get
to the whole Cake Island
Come back as soon as you
finish food shopping. Grr!
Mama!
Flower! Flower!
Moscato, stay cool!
without being seen by the enemy.
Even though he's got heart eyes,
Okay!
Hey, where are we now?
he knows so much about making
sweets and taught me a lot!
Brook, you gotta get changed already.
No-fa! Any sign of fear and your
lifespan will be taken away!
Okay...
Flower! Flower!
I'll stay in the ship since they know my face
but I love chocolate.
We haven't gone far from Cacao Island yet.
We like the same stuff and he's so manly!
You guys... Thank you!
I heard his feet are black
but he's tough and dependable!
Get me some!
It's still a long way to go
to the Whole Cake Island.
Okay!
Okay.
He is, isn't he?!
Have mercy, Mama!
I won't stop you anymore!
There's no need to rush, Luffy-san.
Pudding-san promised us...
That's not what "Black-Foot" means.
Just please! Don't kill me!
Hey, Straw Hat!
If you're gonna go,
stop wasting your time and put on your disguise...
You really got him! He's a great guy!
...that she'll bring Sanji-san
to the southwest coast of the
Luffy and Chopper have
already gone to the town.
Whole Cake Island at any cost.
What?!
Hey, what do you think will
happen if they find out
D-Don't tell me you're in love with...
I smell something good!
Having said that, I don't think Big
Mom will let Captain go so easily...
I brought you guys here?!
Act cautiously!
Yeah, it's not the smell of the sea!
Are you in love with Sanji-kun?!
Don't worry!
We'll know where they are soon.
It's sweet!
If she gets mad at us too,
all we can do is run!
L-L-Love?! Well, I mean...
What kind of snack will
the next town be made of?
Give me 40 years.
Oh, it's fun out here on the sea!
Somebody ate a cafe!
But what about Aladdin-san?
Mama's decision can't be overturned.
There they are!
Screw you!
He got married to Madam Praline
and became a member of Big Mom's family.
And if I marry someone, I prefer, um...
Hey, I see an island!
Big Bro!
Oh?
Yay! What kind of snack will be there?!
I like Sanji very much too!
We're the same!
Moscato-sama!
Are you guys worried about me?
She killed...
I can tell from the smell!
It must be something sweet!
No, I can't say such a thing!
Oh, Madam!
...her own son!!
The next one is probably a town made of jam.
SHOCK!!
Shock!
CHARLOTTE PRALINE
(HALF-HUMAN, HALF-HAMMERHEAD SHARK MERMAID)
THE 29TH DAUGHTER OF THE CHARLOTTE FAMILY
Jam?!
This is totally unexpected!
I can't believe such a lovely girl is the bride!
We're not gonna stop there though.
Are you talking behind my back?
If it were just the chocolate
walls they could be put back later
What?!
Moscato-sama has been killed!
Here, look.
Did you hear what we said?!
What?!
but the whole cafe is gone!
When we see Jam Island,
No wonder Sanji-san's got heart eyes!
Hey, are you trying to
hide something from me?!
Croquembouche!
we turn in the direction of the
Log Pose 2 instead of approach.
We should tie her up!
But it's sweet! Nami!
Aladdin! Don't tell me you were gonna
leave me behind if Mama gets angry!
Run! No one can stop her now!
We're not gonna go there
even though it's sweet?!
You guys messed with candies,
marshmallows, almonds and jelly beans!
Let's see...
No, of course, I'd ask you...
That way.
You don't need to ask!
Okay!
That's a crime of Snackalism!
I need to question you!
She'll tell them that we're here.
I'll definitely choose you over Mama!
If anything happens, take me with you!
Luffy, starboard! In the direction
of sanji (three o'clock)!
If they find us while we're on
one of the outermost islands,
Come to the station with me!
That's right! Chopper! Carrot!
We're going in the direction of Sanji!
But, old man,
there is a good reason for this.
we'll never be able to get to Sanji!
Oh, so passionate!
How could you say that, Pedro?
But it's sweet!
Yeah? Out with it!
Sorry, Wadatsumi.
We're gonna go pick up Sanji!
Hard a starboard!
How else can we silence her?
--Mama is about to reach the castle!
--Oh, boy!
It was too delicious!
I just brought you here but
as you heard, I've got to go.
Okay, well said, idiots!
Come with me!
Don't forget she's Big Mom's daughter.
Oh, no! It's too late!
That's too much!
That's okay! I'm so happy
to be with these guys.
You're bad at this, Luffy-san!
Yeah but she's scared of her mother too!
You too, Brook!
Oh, no! They're gonna get arrested!
But it's sweet...
Don't make a scene, Pedro-san!
That's why she'll tell her!
By turning towards the next island
before getting too close to another one,
Now, Praline, do you think Mama
won't forgive me... I mean, us?
How would you know?!
Wait, Chocopolice-san!
That's terrible.
You stay out of this!
we can avoid their surveillance network,
she said.
Well, there were precedents,
but those who wished to leave her crew...
Oh, so that's how you read the map.
Excuse me.
Nami! This way!
Wait!
Somebody's coming from the river of juice!
--Can you do it?
--Count on me.
They're in trouble! What should we do?!
Luffy-san, I'll take it from here.
--That's...
--That man is...
...are all dead.
No doubt!
Okay.
Everyone, move!
Alright, guys, I'll cook something for you!
JIMBEI - THE FORMER WARLORD
THE CAPTAIN OF THE SUN PIRATES
I won't tell Mama about
Straw Hat-san and the rest of you!
It's Boss Jimbei!
What?!
I gotta cook!
Help!
Please!
Luffy, wait a sec!
We'll be eaten!
I guess you're leaving, Jimbei.
What was that?
What do you want, Nami? I'll cook.
He has a croquembouche on his side!
No!
Is that...
I'm not gonna mess up this time!
A carpet?
He caught those tourist cream puffs for us!
Carpet! Carpet!
I'll do it! Don't you ever set
foot in the kitchen again!
They are coated with candy!
Did the Minister of Candy do it?!
The carpet is flying...
I'm Big Mom's daughter
so I know it's hard to believe me but...
I'm not paying you one dime!
Carpet! Carpet!
--I don't need your money!
--What?!
--Why, Boss?!
--Don't leave, Boss! Why do you have to leave?!
Don't say that.
Oh, you're the... owner!
Shut up!
I am scared of Mama but I've made up my mind!
Can I look, Pedro?
I wanna help!
Oh, more trouble!
The owner of the cafe came!
Look over here!
Okay.
Don't get in my way!
If you all came to take back Sanji-san,
I'll help you!
Don't ask someone why they're leaving!
That's pathetic!
Look what they've done to your cafe!
Let's see...
Catch this!
Oh, no!
Who cares?!
How commendable of her...
Hey! The water is grape-colored!
You sure?
Yes because Mama and I
are two different people.
Grape?
If you're a pirate,
of course you want to live as you like.
I can't believe this!
--She's right!
--Yeah, it is!
Let me garchu one more time!
There is an island that
spills juice around here.
Am I delicious? Tell me, am I...
It's no harm to us.
What?! Is that juice?!
Having said that,
This place is such a paradise!
having a pledge of loyalty reneged
brings shame to a lord.
How can you help us?
Pedro, how do you know
so much about this area?
Jimbei, you know this means
I'm going to lose a powerful asset - you.
Remember? You also saw someone
you know in Chocolat Town.
Yes but...
THE OWNER OF CAFE "CARAMEL"
No "but"! You should lose something too!
NITRO THE JELLY
I think I can still let go of my feelings...
Yeah, I've been here once before.
You have to pay a price!
It's delicious!
RABIAN THE CARPET
What?
...towards Sanji-san!
How could you leave this much?
This isn't what we agreed to! Gee!
--Yeah!
--Mama has cooled down!
Hey, Brook! What are you doing?!
--Bring me the roulette!
--What?
You have to finish it properly!
It's not me!
This is it!
If it's delicious,
that's all that matters...
Thank you, Boss Jimbei!
What was that?!
Hey, do you know her?
No, I don't. Who is it?
Let the chefs know! The crisis is over!
And what's that thing on her shoulder?
I see something in the water!
Summon all the ministers!
I thought the combination of jam and biscuits
and chocolate here was delicious!
What?!
Restore the capital as
rapidly as possible-bon!
What's that?
Oh, flying carpet! Wait!
A map?
Now, spin it.
People in Totto Land...
Oh?
Oh, no. I can't get up.
I can't wait to see what you're gonna lose!
What are you doing?
give their blessings to my marriage.
Oh my loyal knight of the sea, Jimbei!
So do the members of the Vinsmoke Family.
Good job bringing me the
Ponegliff the other day.
Mama looks forward to the wedding cake.
Here! Try this!
CHARLOTTE LINLIN - ONE OF THE FOUR EMPERORS
THE QUEEN OF TOTTO LAND
THE CAPTAIN OF THE BIG MOM PIRATES
I can't read it though.
None of us can disobey Mama's order
so I knew I couldn't marry for love,
How is it?
but I've been dreaming
ever since I was a child.
It's good!
What do you want today?
Why are we out here?
Meanwhile, Luffy and the others are
on the water in Big Mom's territory.
Chocopolice-san, I'm sorry.
Wondering what my husband would be like.
Oh? The city is looking better than ever.
The cafe will be expired soon
so I asked them to eat the whole building!
And then, Sanji-san came along.
Did you do this?
It's hardly melting.
Oh, pardon me! I didn't know
they were a demolition crew!
No, I just arrived
and I have no clue what happened, ma'am.
Damn! There! There! There! There! There!
Come on, guys!
Luffy! That doesn't work.
You have to take your time.
Oh...
You should've had a sign out
when you were working.
I'm here...
What? That's a pain in the butt.
There were still some customers, too.
What is that?!
Well then, if you'll excuse me.
Oh, no! It's kind of snake-like!
...to tell you something important today.
So sweet!
Yes, thank you!
And I'm sorry to disturb you, everyone!
Anyway, it's not moving a bit.
It's gone.
Carrot-san, do you see anything?!
No...
So it was nothing serious.
I was surprised
because he was such a wonderful man.
Well, let's just stay here and sleep!
Oh, we were so worried.
Let's see... Oh, look! It's coming again!
No! What if those ants attack us again?!
Oh, yeah!
But he actually said to me in the end,
Congratulations on getting married,
Pudding-sama!
When the sun rises,
it'll begin to flow again.
Your wedding day is approaching
and you're checking in on your cafe?
But during night-time,
it gets cold and solidifies.
There it is!
"I want to marry you but I can't do it."
Don't work too much.
You're not gonna leave my crew, are you?
Share those things beforehand!
We all wish for your happiness!
It's gigantic!
Wow! It's big!
Thank you!
We've gotta melt it and get out
of this area of starch syrup!
"I want to go back to my friends."
She saved Luffy and Chopper.
It's a Giant Sea Centipede.
They reside in this area.
What?! Sanji rejected a girl?!
Yeah!
She's so kind. I wonder who it is.
Pull it!
We just put the army of ants to sleep!
They are monsters that eat anything -
people, ships, etc.
They're so lucky!
But... it's good to know...
I knew he wanted to continue the adventure!
This is how fortune favors
the Pirate King to-be.
--It's gonna be trouble when they wake up.
--That's right.
No! Giant Sea Centipede, go away!
Oh?
Captain Pedro?!
We'll be eaten!
It wasn't just him who wanted to be back
Luffy, this is your job!
You're Captain Pedro, aren't you?!
I thought so! It's been a while!
Nami, where are we now?
All right!
because you all actually came here
to take him back at the risk of your lives.
Those Sea Ants once ate my ship.
Let's see.
Why are you here?
Oh my!
I'll do what little I can too!
We're passing by Cheese Island
and heading towards Biscuit Island.
Once? What did you come here for?
I'm here for sightseeing. Don't tell anyone.
Even if this is Mama's decision,
O-Okay. It's a pleasure to see you.
it'd be hard for me to stay with someone
who didn't want to get married.
Pedro used to be a pirate
along with Pekoms.
You know people in this town, Pedro?
Here it comes!
Luffy!
Gum-Gum...
What?! Really?!
And most of all, I know you all
care about Sanji-san so much
--There's something wrong with the sea!
--What?!
I'll tell you later.
...Gatling!
Pedro?
Luffy-san, the helm!
A pirate?
and I can't take him away from you.
The water's turning red!
He said he wanted to go
back to his friends too.
I was so naive.
It's a sea of watermelon juice!
I thought of myself as an explorer
but I became a wanted person.
What?!
Then all I can do for him
is help him with that.
It was grape before
and now it's watermelon?!
The wall chocolate is good!
I only accompanied Pekoms halfway.
This place is such a paradise!
I want it! I want it!
Right?
Not just red!
I trust you-gara people so I can tell you.
Pudding-san!
Orange-colored water from the right
and pink-colored water from the left!
Oh, is that it?
Hey, guys, how much can you eat?
I was looking for Ponegliffs
because I wanted to help Master Cat Viper.
Take this route.
Who wants more?!
What is this place?
This is where three kinds of juice mix up.
It's the Mixed Juice Current.
This is the only way you can get there
What?! I wanted to fight too!
without Mama's seeing, which
only we children know of.
Mixed Juice Current?!
I'm in a candy house. This is like a dream!
Sorry, sorry!
But when I trespassed in Big Mom's territory,
it became my last voyage.
Is that where Sanji is?
So is it mixed juice?!
Sounds delicious!
If you go along this route,
you can get to the Whole Cake Island.
What?! What?! What?!
What is it this time?!
I'm so happy.
I wanna drink!
But Mama won't let go of Sanji-san.
Where did the food in your stomach
from earlier go?
I...
Nice! Nice, nice!
...got defeated here once.
Luffy! This wall is delicious too!
Don't get carried away!
So let's meet up at the southwest coast of
the Whole Cake Island tomorrow.
There are dangerous creatures
in this mixed current!
When did you get there?!
Okay!
Oh, look!
I'll bring Sanji-san there at any price.
I've seldom told anyone about this.
Wow, look at that!
This one is bigger than the last one!
I'll cooperate with you!
It's so good!
Every part of it is good!
There's a giant watermelon!
I didn't know that.
Is it okay?
Won't you get punished by Big Mom?
An orange on this side!
Brook, you gotta try this too! It's good!
I'm her biological daughter.
Don't worry.
It's twice as big as the last one!
A peach on this side!
You too, Nami!
It's almost as big as the Neptunians!
You're in enemy territory.
Worry about yourself.
Is it really okay to eat this much?
Pudding...
You have bad memories,
yet came back?
Yes!
Let's eat!
If my experience helps you even a little bit
to take back Sanji, I'll be happy.
Gum-Gum...
Um... Can I see your panties...
No, those are...
But is it really okay?
The sea of the New World is unbelievable!
...Watermelon!
Don't push your luck!
Sanji-san and you all care about each other.
Why are you so happy?!
On top of that,
Okay, I'll just have this then.
maybe it wasn't so bad that I came along.
This one is enormous.
This one may give us some trouble!
Jeez.
Pudding-san, you're so...
Whaaat?!
I heard our kings showed you-gara people
the Road Ponegliff at the Whale Tree.
It's a bit of a shame
but my next husband to-be...
I won't let you eat my ship!
Yum-yum!
It's delicious!
Gum-Gum...
That-gara is a Fruit Footballfish!
They did.
So your name is Pudding.
Thank you for helping us!
...Gatling!
I was surprised.
...could be someone nicer!
Even though you may have saved us,
H-How wonderful this girl is!
Is she really the Emperor's daughter?!
No, no! I'm the one who
should be thanking you!
they haven't shown it to anybody
other than the Kozuki Clan...
Why?
...for 26 years...
Luffy's been eaten!
Because you said...
...since they showed it to
Gol D. Roger's pirate group.
"It was too delicious"!
Thank you, Pudding!
You're welcome!
The Pirate King?!
That chocolate at the cafe is a
new blend that I came up with!
Later, Roger reached Raftel
and was called the Pirate King.
Did you like how it melted in your mouth?
Pudding-sama, we're here to pick you up.
Gum-Gum...
I added milk to cocoa butter
and highly-pure beet sugar
...Watermelon Splitting!
Its shell is too hard so
it doesn't feel anything!
One moment!
You-gara people remind
Duke Dogstorm and Master Cat Viper of them.
and kneaded it for three days
straight at 29 degrees Celsius!
I'm working now so wait a second.
Plus, it's massive!
Okay, aim at its belly!
Let's attack all at once!
I don't know what you're talking about
but it was so good!
Whew! Yes! I got something to eat!
It was!
They're expecting you to become
somebody who'll need the Road Ponegliffs.
You said it was delicious
and it really makes me want to cry!
Gear Two!
Get out through here.
And go in the direction of the cafe.
Thank you! I'm so happy to hear it!
Gum-Gum...
Got it!
Wh... What a nice girl!
...Jet Stamp!
What are you gonna do after you defeat Kaido?
Say, Pudding-san, before I leave,
I can't believe they are all footballfish.
That's too far ahead!
I haven't thought about it...
Do you like making chocolate?
may I see your panties...
Let's eat!
Next, you'll need the Road Ponegliff
that Big Mom has!
I love sweets!
Hurry up!
This town smells like chocolate
and it's like heaven!
Pudding-sama!
It's good! This fish tastes like watermelon!
Yes!
If so, this would be our biggest chance!
Even the table is chocolate!
You need to stop working until the wedding,
Pudding-sama.
It's nice to know that!
Since we came this deep into her territory,
We really want to stay
and thank you, Pudding,
We'll eat too!
But I have customers...
we'd better steal Big Mom's Road Ponegliff
in addition to taking back Sanji!
but we need to go...
This one tastes like peach!
You have to prepare for the wedding too.
Yeah? That's too bad.
This one tastes like orange!
Before you go, would you like a cup of tea?
It's so good!
What? But that's...
It's so sweet and good!
I guess you have a sweet taste in your mouth.
It's so sour and delicious!
Tea sounds good!
That's impressive.
Not just Sanji but also a Road Ponegliff?
Okay. I'll be right back.
I'm exhausted from being scared...
Is it okay to eat those?
Oh, what a nice girl!
She's really a nice girl!
The worst is yet to come.
It's fine. It's not poisonous.
Well, Robin asked me to get it too,
but I wanna rescue Sanji first...
Are there more of those?!
Let's try...
I haven't asked your name, have I?
He said we'll attack all at once!
But again I didn't get a chance to show off!
Oh? Nami-san, aren't you gonna have any?
I know.
I'm Luffy.
No, I'll pass on that.
I'll get the Road Ponegliff.
You-gara guys go for Sanji.
The future Pirate King...
Hey!
It's delicious, Nami! This monster!
What?
Do you think it was edible?
My heroes, the evil army - Germa 66!
What?
No! Don't eat it!
I'm not hungry anymore...
When we reach the island,
could I have a little time?
Hey, Luffy-san! Don't eat it all by yourself!
I haven't had any yet!
Meanwhile, on the Whole Cake Island...
It gives me a thrill-rero.
Luffy?
This time, I'll get it!
THE WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
No but if you're doing it for us,
we'll come with you!
Croquembouche!
SOME ISLAND WHERE YOU CAN GET EGGS
No, you make sure to protect Sanji.
Mama! Stop! Mama!
Even after you get him
back, things will be tough.
The Emperor is on the move!
There'll be a tea party!
Okay. Then I'll leave it to you!
A tea party sounds like fun!
Croquembouche!
Don't be silly!
Great!
Don't decide so easily...
What are they gonna make this time?!
Follow me.
No idea! But so many people will die again!
BROCK COLLIE ISLAND, NEW WORLD
I wonder if Luffy-san was born to be lucky...
Mama... Mama, please stop!
Move!
Croquembouche!
What is it, Brook?
Just one person?
Nothing. I am lucky too.
Oh no! It's Mama's illness!
What are you talking about? You're weird.
Tighten security at the entrance!
AN ISLAND WHERE YOU CAN GET FLOUR
Hurry up-bon!
What does she want this time-soir?!
Dammit! Big Mom!
She wants...
...croquembouche!
Croquembouche?!
Is that the decorated dessert that
is composed of cream puffs piled up?
Charge!
AN ISLAND WHERE YOU CAN GET FRUIT
This will be a challenge.
This is how it should be.
Oh, the ants are up!
Oh! No, wait!
Ever since I met Straw Hat Luffy that day,
No!
I think there is a tourist group of
Ant! Ant! Ant! Ant!
cream puffs staying at a
hotel in the city-je-t'aime!
Here they come!
this is what I was destined for.
Gum-Gum...
They already checked out this morning.
This country is doomed!
...Whip!
Should we just make one?
What does the chef say?
How dare she do this?!
Do me a once-in-a-lifetime favor!
I want to make the dough special.
Could you get me almonds?
How could she do this for a
stupid thing like a tea party?!
No!
Ant!
Take me with you!
I can help you for sure!
It's Germa!
THE WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Ant!
I'll tell the Minister of Nuts!
It's Germa 66's ship!
Croquembouche! Croquembouche!
--Can you fight, Luffy?
--Of course!
Hey, Luffy-kun,
you should not fight anymore!
Thank you for coming, Germa-sama!
Ace's Vivre Card!
Cut it out.
Let me explain the situation.
They're not decreasing at all! Ouch!
Don't need that either.
Mama is heading towards Sweet City now!
What?!
I can't stand it! I really can't stand!
--Do you have the money ready?
--O-Of course.
She's coming this way?!
This is the capital! Mama's castle is here!
No!
You have to live strong!
Nami!
--Then, we have no business with you.
--Just stay here and watch.
We can't talk her out of it!
She's losing her mind from the attack!
Save the Sunny!
Screw that "King of the Pirates" crap!
How long do we have until the tea party?
Can't you see things clearly now?!
Three days, Mama
The death toll is still rising!
Flower! Flower!
Issue an evacuation order in Sweet City!
You believed that you
could overcome anything!
I see
What about Germa's son?
Only a croquembouche can stop Mama now!
And you've never doubted your strength!
Oh, it's you! The groceries
that you ordered are ready.
He's here, Mama
Oh, ow, ow, ow! Damn ants!
They bit me everywhere!
But all those formidable enemies
took away your confidence!
This way! Hurry up and evacuate!
Hurry up!
Furniture! Furniture! Furniture! Furniture!
They're there so just take them.
Oh, there they are!
Hey! Isn't the croquembouche ready yet?!
Oh, my back tingles!
Can you carry them?
And your brother was your guide on the sea!
I know that you have lost a lot!
Thanks. We'll be fine!
There will be a wedding
Croquembouche!
Oh?
This is why!
How is the cake?
Chocolate burger?!
I know that it's painful now, Luffy,
but you have to bottle up those feelings!
Don't look at other stuff!
Let's go! Pekoms is waiting for us!
The wedding cake
Mama! I hope she's not
gonna eat the capital up!
The wedding cake
Hey, guys!
Don't just think about the ones you've lost!
I want the chocolate burger, Nami!
--The design?
--Okay!
Wake up!
--The budget?
--Don't be stingy!
You can't get back what you've lost!
Ingredients must be carefully selected
--Chocolate pasta.
--Chocolate fried chicken.
Mama, please stop!
What is it that you still have?!
Kill the people and rob them
Huh? What is it?
We have enough food! Come on!
Mama, let's not do this!
Bring me croquembouche!
I still have...
I still have my friends!
Eggs!
Oh? Pekoms?
I cannot stop Luffy-sama's bleeding!
Look! Look!
I got them.
Pekoms?
Flour!
Hey please!
If nothing is done, Luffy is gonna...
Mama entered Sweet City!
She entered Sweet City!
Pekoms-san?
I got it!
Fruit!
Luffy is gonna die!
Oh, she's finally here...
Pekoms?
Take my blood.
Mama's Hunger Pangs are
very troublesome-bon!
I got it.
Aren't you here?
We'll make it taste good!
It's F.
Here we are finally!
You don't know when the attack will strike.
You can have as much as you need.
Pekoms!
Let's eat a delicious cake!
It's worse than any kind of disaster.
Hey, Jimbei.
Did you find him?
Sweet dealings!
No!
Is the chef still making it?!
This is strange.
Wow, it's gigantic!
The tea party from hell!
Doing number two, maybe?
What about the bathroom?
The kitchen is busy as hell!
All we can do is wait-main.
Hey!
So this is where the Emperor lives!
--Is this strawberry jam?
--Or somebody's blood?
There is a message in the bathroom!
The destruction continues
until she gets a bite of what she craves.
There's a cake!
Join...
I don't care either way
...my crew!
That tallest whole cake is a castle
where Big Mom lives.
If you're invited, be there at any cost!
Anyway, evacuate all the residents!
As I said, I can't join you right now!
A sweet moment
Run! Hurry up!
"Turn back"?
Sacrifices to the Devil
A castle?!
I know it'd be fun
to sail the sea with you all.
--Did Pekoms write this?
--Who else would do that?
Big Mom's having a tantrum!
Nami-san, we'll continue
on straight like this?
--Stop!
--Not in this city!
This is a dream land for everyone
Yes, that cape is
the only place without security.
Did somebody invaded?
But I still have things that need to be done.
Has Pekoms been abducted?
All kinds of races come together
I see.
Maybe they've found out about us.
I have my current responsibilities
which I'm just taking a break from right now.
That's the place Pudding-san mentioned.
Mama! Mama! Not in this city!
Totto Land!
Yeah, we have to really thank her.
In any event, this is serious.
--She'll destroy her own castle!
--It's no good. She can't hear us.
TURN BACK
If it weren't for her,
I don't know if we could've make it this far.
When I fulfill my duties
and am free from them,
"Turn back" means if we don't do so,
something's gonna happen.
You're right.
I promise I will come to see you all again.
Yeah.
Hey, somebody's there!
Okay, everyone, keep that in mind!
Mmm, I can't wait!
I heard he is here
Yes, he is here
Croquembouche!
The time to fulfill my promise...
Sanji?
Let's go on!
Is that Sanji?! Hey!
...has finally come!
Straw Hat!
It's getting exciting!
Sanji!
Croquembouche!
Consulting the map that Pudding drew,
The lovely girl Pudding
who saved Luffy reveals
They finally arrived at
the Whole Cake Island!
Losing herself, Big Mom eats up everything
in town and terrorizes Sweet City!
The determined Jimbei and Big Mom start
a tense negotiation!
Luffy and the others head
for the Whole Cake Island!
the surprising truth of the Big Mom Pirates
Chasing Sanji, Luffy and the others enter
Meanwhile, Pedro reveals his hidden past
as the Straw Hats sail along the sea!
However, on that island,
Emperor Big Mom is running amok!
and her budding love for Sanji.
a forest of candies filled with sweets!
When even the Big Mom
Pirates run out of options,
Is she an enemy or an ally?
However, someone is waiting for
the happily advancing clan.
When Luffy and the others
renew their resolve,
Trees and buildings have been destroyed
that man who used to be one of the
As the gang takes precautions against her,
she makes an unexpected move!
and no one can stop her insane rampage!
the island where Sanji is
being kept finally appears!
Seven Warlords cuts through the rough
sea and shows up to end the crisis!
And surprisingly, that
someone is another Luffy!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Massive Attack! Mom's Hunger Pangs!"
"The Capital City Falls?! Big Mom and Jimbei!"
"The Emperor's Castle! Arriving
at the Whole Cake Island!"
"A Mysterious Forest Full of
Candies! Luffy vs. Luffy?!"
"The Emperor's Daughter!
Sanji's fiancée - Pudding!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!