I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Sanji, the cook of the Straw Hats,
suddenly left his friends behind.
He was being pressed into marrying
Emperor Big Mom's daughter.
Split up temporarily from
Zoro and the others,
Luffy's team is heading for the Whole Cake Island
where Big Mom waits to take back Sanji.
Meanwhile, on the Whole Cake Island...
Croquembouche!
Oh no! It's Mama's illness!
Hurry up-bon!
What does she want this time-soir?!
She wants...
...croquembouche!
Issue an evacuation order in Sweet City!
Only a croquembouche can stop Mama now!
Mama! Mama! Not in this city!
--She'll destroy her own castle!
--It's no good. She can't hear us.
Croquembouche!
"The Capital City Falls?!
Big Mom and Jimbei!"
THE WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
This isn't it!
L-Look up!
Where is it?! Croquembouche?!
Pine! Pine! Pine! Pine!
Pine!
Help me!
This isn't it!
Help!
This isn't it either!
Run!
Croquembouche...
Where is it?!
This isn't the taste!
You losers aren't it either!
It's all wrong!
I can't believe this!
If she keeps rampaging,
the capital city will fall apart-bon!
Isn't the croquembouche ready yet?!
How is it, chef?! How's it going?!
I'm still working on the
special cream filling
that gives you that smooth
feeling on your tongue!
Whatever! Just hurry up!
Mama is coming closer
to the Whole Cake Chateau-soir!
We must stop her from destroying
this castle at any price!
What should we do?!
I heard Moscato-sama is heading there now!
Croquembouche!
--Run somewhere far!
--Thank you!
Oh, it's Moscato-sama!
The 16th son of the Charlotte Family
and the Minister of Gelato!
He's a member of Mama's family!
I'm sure he can stop her!
This is Moscato! How's the croquembouche?!
CHARLOTTE MOSCATO
THE 16TH SON OF THE CHARLOTTE FAMILY
THE MINISTER OF GELATO
I heard it'll take half an hour or so
to be ready-bon!
It'll be too late by then!
We can't let her destroy the castle!
This isn't it!
Mama! Stop it!
Who is that?!
Mama! It's me! Moscato!
Where is my croquembouche?
Croquembouche...
Croquembouche!
Give us 30 minutes! The chefs are trying
to make it as quickly as they can!
No, Big Bro Mos!
It's impossible to stop her!
I can't let her ruin the capital!
Move out of my way!
Can't you recognize me, Mama?!
Life...
...or...
...treat!
Life or treat...
Lifespan or snack!
You gotta be kidding, Mama!
He's your own son!
Mama, don't do it!
W-We have whipped cream here-fa!
No dough yet but Mama, don't!
Th-The treat is not here yet!
I'll take the treat...
Don't get in my way!
Mama!
Moscato, stay cool!
No-fa! Any sign of fear and your
lifespan will be taken away!
Have mercy, Mama!
I won't stop you anymore!
Just please! Don't kill me!
Give me 40 years.
Big Bro!
Moscato-sama!
She killed...
...her own son!!
Moscato-sama has been killed!
What?!
Croquembouche!
Run! No one can stop her now!
--Mama is about to reach the castle!
--Oh, boy!
Oh, no! It's too late!
That's terrible.
Somebody's coming from the river of juice!
--That's...
--That man is...
No doubt!
Everyone, move!
JIMBEI - THE FORMER WARLORD
THE CAPTAIN OF THE SUN PIRATES
It's Boss Jimbei!
Help!
We'll be eaten!
He has a croquembouche on his side!
He caught those tourist cream puffs for us!
They are coated with candy!
Did the Minister of Candy do it?!
Look over here!
Don't get in my way!
Catch this!
It's delicious!
--Yeah!
--Mama has cooled down!
This is it!
If it's delicious,
that's all that matters...
Thank you, Boss Jimbei!
Let the chefs know! The crisis is over!
Summon all the ministers!
Restore the capital as
rapidly as possible-bon!
Oh?
Oh my loyal knight of the sea, Jimbei!
Good job bringing me the
Ponegliff the other day.
CHARLOTTE LINLIN - ONE OF THE FOUR EMPERORS
THE QUEEN OF TOTTO LAND
THE CAPTAIN OF THE BIG MOM PIRATES
I can't read it though.
What do you want today?
Why are we out here?
Oh? The city is looking better than ever.
Did you do this?
No, I just arrived
and I have no clue what happened, ma'am.
Oh...
I'm here...
...to tell you something important today.
You're not gonna leave my crew, are you?
Nami, where are we now?
Let's see.
We're passing by Cheese Island
and heading towards Biscuit Island.
Luffy!
--There's something wrong with the sea!
--What?!
Luffy-san, the helm!
The water's turning red!
It's a sea of watermelon juice!
What?!
It was grape before
and now it's watermelon?!
This place is such a paradise!
Not just red!
Orange-colored water from the right
and pink-colored water from the left!
What is this place?
This is where three kinds of juice mix up.
It's the Mixed Juice Current.
Mixed Juice Current?!
So is it mixed juice?!
Sounds delicious!
I wanna drink!
Nice! Nice, nice!
Don't get carried away!
There are dangerous creatures
in this mixed current!
Oh, look!
There's a giant watermelon!
An orange on this side!
A peach on this side!
Let's eat!
Gum-Gum...
No, those are...
...Watermelon!
Whaaat?!
Yum-yum!
That-gara is a Fruit Footballfish!
Luffy's been eaten!
Gum-Gum...
...Watermelon Splitting!
Whew! Yes! I got something to eat!
I can't believe they are all footballfish.
Let's eat!
It's good! This fish tastes like watermelon!
We'll eat too!
This one tastes like peach!
This one tastes like orange!
It's so good!
It's so sweet and good!
It's so sour and delicious!
Is it okay to eat those?
It's fine. It's not poisonous.
Let's try...
Oh? Nami-san, aren't you gonna have any?
No, I'll pass on that.
It's delicious, Nami! This monster!
I'm not hungry anymore...
Hey, Luffy-san! Don't eat it all by yourself!
I haven't had any yet!
Follow me.
This is how it should be.
Ever since I met Straw Hat Luffy that day,
this is what I was destined for.
Do me a once-in-a-lifetime favor!
Take me with you!
I can help you for sure!
--Can you fight, Luffy?
--Of course!
Hey, Luffy-kun,
you should not fight anymore!
Ace's Vivre Card!
You have to live strong!
Screw that "King of the Pirates" crap!
Can't you see things clearly now?!
You believed that you
could overcome anything!
And you've never doubted your strength!
But all those formidable enemies
took away your confidence!
And your brother was your guide on the sea!
I know that you have lost a lot!
I know that it's painful now, Luffy,
but you have to bottle up those feelings!
Don't just think about the ones you've lost!
You can't get back what you've lost!
What is it that you still have?!
I still have...
I still have my friends!
I cannot stop Luffy-sama's bleeding!
Hey please!
If nothing is done, Luffy is gonna...
Luffy is gonna die!
Take my blood.
It's F.
You can have as much as you need.
Hey, Jimbei.
Join...
...my crew!
As I said, I can't join you right now!
I know it'd be fun
to sail the sea with you all.
But I still have things that need to be done.
I have my current responsibilities
which I'm just taking a break from right now.
When I fulfill my duties
and am free from them,
I promise I will come to see you all again.
The time to fulfill my promise...
...has finally come!
The determined Jimbei and Big Mom start
a tense negotiation!
Meanwhile, Pedro reveals his hidden past
as the Straw Hats sail along the sea!
When Luffy and the others
renew their resolve,
the island where Sanji is
being kept finally appears!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Emperor's Castle! Arriving
at the Whole Cake Island!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!