I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Sanji, the cook of the Straw Hats,
suddenly left his friends behind.
He was being pressed into marrying
Emperor Big Mom's daughter.
Split up temporarily from
Zoro and the others,
Luffy's team is heading for the
Whole Cake Island where Big
Mom waits to take back Sanji.
Croquembouche!
Big Mom was having a Hunger Pangs attack
and destroying everything.
She wouldn't stop rampaging
until she got a bite of what she was craving,
and the Whole Cake Island
sustained great damage.
The one who handled the situation was
the former Warlord - Jimbei.
It's delicious!
I'm here to...
...tell you something important today.
You're not gonna leave my crew, are you?
"The Emperor's Castle!
Arriving at the Whole Cake Island!"
SWEET CITY
THE CAPITAL OF THE WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Moscato-sama!
Moscato-sama is dead!
Don't die, Moscato-sama!
Moscato-sama!
They're finally here.
--Hurry up and take him away.
--Yes, ma'am.
Step back.
Listen, guys.
Every last second. Okay?
Moscato-sama...
Say, do you think Boss Jimbei will
be killed too, Montd'Or-sama?!
How do I know?!
When someone makes Mama angry,
this is surely what happens,
even if it's her own son!
Here I am, everyone of the Sun Pirates!
A FEW HOURS AGO
Straw Hat Luffy will
change the world someday!
I know he is still young but
I don't think any one of the
current Four Emperors will
become the king of the sea!
I think Straw Hat Luffy will be the one!
I...
...want to be of help to him!
I'm too...
...weak!!
I... I want to get on board his ship...
...and dedicate my life to him!
I believe that journey will bring true freedom
to the Fish-Men in the end!
ALADDIN (A BROTULA MERMAN)
THE FIRST MATE OF THE SUN PIRATES
For the last two years, you
told us a lot about Luffy-kun.
I've been thinking you should go join him
if you like him so much.
D-Did I really?!
Did I talk about him so much?!
Go, Jimbei!
Are you sure?
No one here has the right to object, Captain!
Yeah! You were a soldier of the Neptune Army
but you became a pirate...
...to fight with us - the former slaves
who fled from Mariejois!
You became a Warlord
to help advance the social status of us Fish-Men!
And you allied with the Big Mom Pirates
to protect us and our home Ryugu Kingdom
under Big Mom's name.
You've always made choices
for the sake of others!
You did enough, Jimbei.
Yeah! Be free, Jimbei-san!
--Go, Jimbei!
--Yeah, Captain Jimbei!
We'll be fine without you.
Don't underestimate us!
Live for yourself from now on!
You guys... Thank you!
Having said that, I don't think Big
Mom will let Captain go so easily...
If she gets mad at us too,
all we can do is run!
But what about Aladdin-san?
He got married to Madam Praline
and became a member of Big Mom's family.
Oh?
Are you guys worried about me?
Oh, Madam!
CHARLOTTE PRALINE
(HALF-HUMAN, HALF-HAMMERHEAD SHARK MERMAID)
THE 29TH DAUGHTER OF THE CHARLOTTE FAMILY
Are you talking behind my back?
Did you hear what we said?!
Hey, are you trying to
hide something from me?!
Aladdin! Don't tell me you were gonna
leave me behind if Mama gets angry!
No, of course, I'd ask you...
You don't need to ask!
I'll definitely choose you over Mama!
If anything happens, take me with you!
Oh, so passionate!
Sorry, Wadatsumi.
I just brought you here but
as you heard, I've got to go.
That's okay! I'm so happy
to be with these guys.
Now, Praline, do you think Mama
won't forgive me... I mean, us?
Well, there were precedents,
but those who wished to leave her crew...
...are all dead.
I guess you're leaving, Jimbei.
--Why, Boss?!
--Don't leave, Boss! Why do you have to leave?!
Shut up!
Don't ask someone why they're leaving!
That's pathetic!
Who cares?!
If you're a pirate,
of course you want to live as you like.
Am I delicious? Tell me, am I...
Having said that,
having a pledge of loyalty reneged
brings shame to a lord.
Jimbei, you know this means
I'm going to lose a powerful asset - you.
Yes but...
No "but"! You should lose something too!
You have to pay a price!
--Bring me the roulette!
--What?
Now, spin it.
I can't wait to see what you're gonna lose!
Meanwhile, Luffy and the others are
on the water in Big Mom's territory.
It's hardly melting.
Damn! There! There! There! There! There!
Luffy! That doesn't work.
You have to take your time.
What? That's a pain in the butt.
So sweet!
Anyway, it's not moving a bit.
No...
Well, let's just stay here and sleep!
No! What if those ants attack us again?!
When the sun rises,
it'll begin to flow again.
But during night-time,
it gets cold and solidifies.
Share those things beforehand!
We've gotta melt it and get out
of this area of starch syrup!
Yeah!
Pull it!
We just put the army of ants to sleep!
--It's gonna be trouble when they wake up.
--That's right.
Those Sea Ants once ate my ship.
Oh my!
Once? What did you come here for?
Pedro used to be a pirate
along with Pekoms.
What?! Really?!
A pirate?
I was so naive.
I thought of myself as an explorer
but I became a wanted person.
I only accompanied Pekoms halfway.
I trust you-gara people so I can tell you.
I was looking for Ponegliffs
because I wanted to help Master Cat Viper.
But when I trespassed in Big Mom's territory,
it became my last voyage.
I...
...got defeated here once.
I've seldom told anyone about this.
I didn't know that.
You have bad memories,
yet came back?
If my experience helps you even a little bit
to take back Sanji, I'll be happy.
On top of that,
maybe it wasn't so bad that I came along.
I heard our kings showed you-gara people
the Road Ponegliff at the Whale Tree.
They did.
I was surprised.
Even though you may have saved us,
they haven't shown it to anybody
other than the Kozuki Clan...
...for 26 years...
...since they showed it to
Gol D. Roger's pirate group.
The Pirate King?!
Later, Roger reached Raftel
and was called the Pirate King.
You-gara people remind
Duke Dogstorm and Master Cat Viper of them.
They're expecting you to become
somebody who'll need the Road Ponegliffs.
What are you gonna do after you defeat Kaido?
That's too far ahead!
I haven't thought about it...
Next, you'll need the Road Ponegliff
that Big Mom has!
If so, this would be our biggest chance!
Since we came this deep into her territory,
we'd better steal Big Mom's Road Ponegliff
in addition to taking back Sanji!
What? But that's...
Not just Sanji but also a Road Ponegliff?
Well, Robin asked me to get it too,
but I wanna rescue Sanji first...
I know.
I'll get the Road Ponegliff.
You-gara guys go for Sanji.
What?
When we reach the island,
could I have a little time?
This time, I'll get it!
No but if you're doing it for us,
we'll come with you!
No, you make sure to protect Sanji.
Even after you get him
back, things will be tough.
Okay. Then I'll leave it to you!
Great!
Don't decide so easily...
I wonder if Luffy-san was born to be lucky...
What is it, Brook?
Nothing. I am lucky too.
What are you talking about? You're weird.
Oh, the ants are up!
No!
Ant! Ant! Ant! Ant!
Here they come!
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
No!
Ant!
They're not decreasing at all! Ouch!
I can't stand it! I really can't stand!
No!
Nami!
Save the Sunny!
Oh, ow, ow, ow! Damn ants!
They bit me everywhere!
Oh, my back tingles!
Oh?
This is why!
Hey, guys!
Wake up!
Huh? What is it?
Look! Look!
Here we are finally!
Wow, it's gigantic!
So this is where the Emperor lives!
There's a cake!
That tallest whole cake is a castle
where Big Mom lives.
A castle?!
Nami-san, we'll continue
on straight like this?
Yes, that cape is
the only place without security.
I see.
That's the place Pudding-san mentioned.
Yeah, we have to really thank her.
If it weren't for her,
I don't know if we could've make it this far.
You're right.
Hey, somebody's there!
Sanji?
Is that Sanji?! Hey!
Sanji!
They finally arrived at
the Whole Cake Island!
Chasing Sanji, Luffy and the others enter
a forest of candies filled with sweets!
However, someone is waiting for
the happily advancing clan.
And surprisingly, that
someone is another Luffy!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Mysterious Forest Full of
Candies! Luffy vs. Luffy?!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!