I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
To take back Sanji who was being
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
Sanji, the cook of the Straw Hats,
suddenly left his friends behind.
who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
pressed into a marriage and
left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole
Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy and the others infiltrated the
He was being pressed into marrying
Emperor Big Mom's daughter.
Whole Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy has separated from Nami, Chopper and Carrot
in the Seducing Woods.
Then, in a mysterious forest,
they finally found Sanji. However...
Chasing Sanji,
they stepped into a mysterious forest,
Looking for Sanji,
they wandered in the Seducing Woods,
Split up temporarily from
Zoro and the others,
Luffy's team is heading for the
and got involved in a series of
strange phenomena.
Meanwhile, Sanji got into a
fight with Vinsmoke Judge,
and got separated by Brulee's trap.
Whole Cake Island where Big
Mom waits to take back Sanji.
Hey!
There he is!
This forest has a bunch of creepy traps!
Let's go back to the Sunny!
his father and Germa 66's generalissimo.
Meanwhile, Sanji was in the
seafaring Germa Kingdom,
Sanji!
I guess you're leaving, Jimbei.
You are a sacrifice, Sanji.
He disappeared for some reason.
Okay!
a land-less kingdom anchored
at the Whole Cake Island.
They tried to get out of the forest
but somehow, they ended up going in circles.
In addition, a Luffy double who moves and talks
exactly the same as him appeared.
But,
I haven't changed.
There, he reunited with his siblings
and his father who is the absolute ruler.
having a pledge of loyalty reneged
brings shame to a lord.
I don't think of you as my son even one bit!
Then, they finally found out
the truth about the forest.
What's the matter?
I thought I taught you how to use a sword.
Who are you?!
And then, they found Sanji again.
However...
Jimbei, you know this means
I'm going to lose a powerful asset - you.
Who am I?
If you try to get off of this island,
your hands will be blown off!
Sanji-kun, what are you doing up there?!
Yes but...
We were together the whole time!
I refuse!
At the same time,
Brook and Pedro were secretly on the move...
No "but"!
You should lose something too!
I'm not gonna use my hands for such crap.
Oh, he's running again! Sanji!
No matter how many times you try,
you'll never get out of this forest!
...to get Big Mom's Road Ponegliff
which is one of the keys to the One Piece.
You bastard! Outta my way!
You have to pay a price!
Never...
Not until you die!
"A Giant Ambition!
Big Mom and Caesar!"
It's good to finally see you!
Damn! You guys, go ahead!
Chase him!
My hands...
I was surprised to know
that weak old Sanji is still alive
O-Okay!
...are for cooking only.
I'm coming too!
SOMEWHERE AROUND THE CAPITAL - SWEET CITY
Extra! Extra!
and is a pirate now.
Now, spin it.
Don't get separated!
Chopper! Carrot!
Go away.
Boss Jimbei betrayed?!
This forest is strange!
Something's gonna happen again!
This happened between him and Mama yesterday?
I cut ties with my family.
I have nothing to say to you guys.
"A Battle Between Father and Son!
Judge vs. Sanji!"
I know! But if we lose Sanji again...
I can't wait to see what you're gonna lose!
Well, we have something to say!
Boss Jimbei was sure cool
when he stopped Mama's tantrum.
Sanji!
I heard you're refusing to marry
the daughter of the Charlotte Family.
What are you gonna do after you defeat Kaido?
Sanji! Please stop!
He blustered that he
wanted to leave her crew,
You're a good-for-nothing fool.
You have no choice.
That's too far ahead!
I haven't thought about it...
but he got scared of paying
the price and backed down!
Next, you'll need the Road Ponegliff
that Big Mom has!
Yeah? That's pathetic!
If so, this would be our biggest chance!
"A Seafaring Kingdom!
Germa's King Judge!"
What a loser!
Didn't he know how much he benefitted
from being one of Emperor Big Mom's subordinates?
Since we came this deep into her territory,
Gum-Gum...
we'd better steal Big Mom's Road Ponegliff
in addition to taking back Sanji!
He's known as the "First Son of the Sea" for nothing.
I lost respect for him.
...Gatling!
Big Mom's castle - the Whole Cake Chateau.
So he was a coward as well as a traitor.
The lake behind it is called Lake Aprico.
When we reach the island,
could I have a little time?
This time, I'll get it!
Jimbei-san,
I didn't know you were working under Big Mom.
And Luffy and the others arrived at their
destination by following Pudding's map.
Who the hell are you?!
That's why the Fish-Man Island
was protected by Big Mom.
This is Germa's ship!
Requesting permission to enter the port!
Oh, that weak little Sanji
became this strong...
Hey, somebody's there!
"Mom's Assassin!
Luffy and the Seducing Woods!"
Go ahead!
Cooking? That's absurd!
Jimbei is a former Warlord, isn't he?
I can't believe someone of his stature is her subordinate.
Unless you're food,
Big Mom's subordinate pirates and those
Sanji?
who will be soon are permitted
to enter the port.
I'm not gonna use blades or hands on you.
Brook, do you know this man?
Is that Sanji?! Hey!
Leg attacks are my specialty.
Yes, he's a very important person to us.
Sanji!
Keep it coming! Keep it coming!
Do you still cook for rats?
Royalty mustn't offer services!
Hey, Jimbei.
"A Mysterious Forest Full of Candies!
Luffy vs. Luffy?!"
How embarrassing!
That's ridiculous.
Join...
...my crew!
When I fulfill my duties
and am free from them,
--Did you see him?
--Are you sure, Luffy?!
Keep it coming! Keep it coming!
What problem do you have with this marriage?!
I promise I will come to see you all again.
All right. Stop right there!
Where? Where?
Brace for the impact!
Where is he?
And if you haven't changed your mind,
What?!
Oh?
Where did he go? Sanji!
can I take you up on your offer then?
Sanji!
Generalissimo's hand-to-hand combat!
Yikes!
Germa is...
The fighting style of the man
who is known as the Garuda!
THE WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
...the name of the one and only seafaring kingdom
that has no land of its own.
It's a rare sight to behold!
I guess he turned down the offer to join our crew
that day
An aerial attack?
Ironically, it's my forte.
We are go!
because he wanted to fulfill
his duty to Big Mom.
Several dozen of their ships
usually travel independently
--I never get tired of looking at it!
--Me neither!
Th-There's a gigantic half-buried man!
Diable Jambe!
but occasionally come together
to form the shape of the kingdom.
Channel 3!
Now, this article...
It doesn't sound like something he'd do.
Collier...
It's a Giant!
--You scared me!
--We should be saying that!
...Coup!
Here it comes!
Won't he come see us again?
Shark Submerge 3!
Hey, Brook!
Are you okay?!
Who did this to you?!
What?
The country is ruled by the
Vinsmoke Family that once
Your body is half-buried!
Please! I have to go somewhere!
conquered the North Blue by force.
War advances science!
Nothing is more important to you now
than choosing a dress!
I'll take Pedro-san then.
My body?
I'm just asking you "Did someone bury you?"
This is the Germa Kingdom.
I'm sorry, Luffy!
Stop being such a baby-s'il vous plat,
Pudding-sama!
Their army, Germa 66
is still viewed as a threat in the world.
Electromagnetic Crack!
I said I'll go on my own
but I'm relying on Brook.
But...
Pudding-sama!
What's the matter?
Blaster!
Most of its citizens are men and soldiers.
Don't mention it!
How about this dress?
I'm half-buried because I wanted to be.
Wow, it looks good on you!
I think I can help you, Pedro-san!
Infiltration is my specialty!
How about this one? I knew it, Pudding-sama!
It looks wonderful!
What?! Is he stupid?!
I shouldn't have been worried!
Everything looks good on you!
I'll get a copy of the Ponegliff at any cost!
The thing is...
Which one do you like, Pudding-sama?
I wanna have some juice.
I don't care!
Yeah, I'll be counting on you!
Brook! Pedro!
Um...
Pudding-sama,
do you know what the groom likes?
Stop it!
Chopper, don't take him seriously!
He'll drive you crazy!
What?!
No! I've only met him once so...
I'm sorry that I always scare you!
The Germa that you once knew
is a thing of the past now!
After we meet up with Sanji and Pudding,
we'll be waiting for you around here.
Wait, wait, you guys.
Whaaat?!
Wait a minute, Pudding-san,
what is she doing here?!
We all have to be really careful!
Don't forget Pekoms' message!
He's saying something.
Ignore him!
I guess she got caught by her attendants.
I like apple juice very much.
TURN BACK
I assumed she'd already led Sanji-san out
Yeah, we decided to go on!
We just gotta do it!
--So what?!
--Don't listen to him.
to meet with Luffy-san and the others by now.
If you go left,
there are waterfalls of apple juice.
Looking at this, I bet
Sanji doesn't even know that we're here.
--We're counting on you!
--See you!
Good luck!
I like them very much.
Then, who did Luffy-san see at the shore?
See you later!
Remember what Luffy told us?
We should be looking for Sanji-kun.
Okay, let's go!
I don't know.
Maybe he just saw someone else.
Am I dreaming?
That's... If I'm not mistaken,
he was on Big Mom's ship...
You're looking for someone, aren't you?
He came this way.
There is not a day that
they don't train themselves.
Shark Submerge 3.
Commence dive.
What?! Did he?!
Yeah, I know him very well.
I said "Don't take him seriously"!
Hey, young Sanji.
Can I ask you something?
Baron Tamago!
If you get me some apple juice,
I'll tell you.
Baron Tamago, may I speak to you?
Okay, okay.
Do you think being a biological parent
entitles someone to respect?
You don't...
Watch out! Nami! Chopper!
What is it-soir?
Why don't you go away already?
The Straw Hat's ship that stopped by
at Chocolat Town yesterday...
...even have a single good
memory of him, do you?
How could you say that...
They already know!
...to your sister that you haven't seen
for 13 years?
When they left, Mr. Pekoms who was guiding them
was already gone, they say.
Depth: 15 meters. Visibility: good.
You...
How many times do I have to tell you?
They know everything!
Father! Let me out!
I cut ties with you guys
under no uncertain terms!
A rabbit?!
And the four Straw Hats
who wandered into the Seducing Woods today.
Oxygen: good enough. Cola: full.
...suffered so much.
You guys must be crazy
to put up a tasteless picture like this!
No! Let's run!
They're already cornered!
They're as good as captured!
All quiet.
Luffy-san and the others got caught?!
It's going well!
But we still can't find the remaining two.
Father! It's too dark!
Let's go up the river,
straight to Big Mom's castle!
These two.
That's us!
I hope the river is deep.
Poele a Frire...
It's leaked out completely!
They knew everything from the start!
Thank you for this!
You only have animosity... towards him.
Where were they watching us from?!
The big incident where four kings in the North Blue
were put down.
A PANTHER MINK
That mink is not a panther-soir.
There are talking trees and crocodiles,
and the rabbit was trying to kill us!
The Conquest of Four Nations.
Wall.
He's a jaguar Mink. His name is Pedro.
SOUTHWEST COAST
This place is weird.
Let's go back to see Luffy!
Ya-hoo!
Do you know him?
Hey, you guys, move!
We still know the way!
Just a little bit from the past.
Okay, I landed!
We've arrived at Big Mom's island!
But what about Sanji?!
We don't know
if he was real or not anymore!
I know what he would do-feuille.
We finally saw each other
but he didn't even get up!
Have mercy!
Please! Don't kill me!
He didn't say anything!
That's huge!
The whole island is made of cakes!
--Anyway, I want you guys to look for Pekoms.
--Yes, sir.
Yeah...
And if that's the real Sanji-kun,
do you think he'd just stand by
and watch us going through this?!
Pekoms. Since he was alive-bon,
--I smell an adventure!
--I don't want one!
N-No, maybe not...
for the sake of our
long-standing partnership,
E.M. Shaft!
Yeah, he said nothing and disappeared
when we first found him.
As soon as we find Sanji-kun,
we'll go back!
I was going to ask for
Mama's pardon with him.
Hey! Sanji! Pudding!
He gives me a lot of trouble-marron.
All right. Let's go back.
We're here as promised!
We are in big trouble!
Don't shout! The enemy will notice!
The needles are...
Hey, did you really see them, Luffy?
Look! The clock is like that too!
THE NORTHEAST COAST OF THE WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Our father's dream is to bring the North Blue
under Germa's control again.
Hey, cut it out, junior!
I did! I'm sure!
But when we looked,
they were already gone!
You fool!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
What's wrong with that?
Everything about this forest is strange!
It's natural for men to be
hung up on power and fame.
Just be...
Yummy! Nami, try and eat the soil!
It's hard whipped cream!
Why don't you enjoy being a
member of privileged royalty
...quiet!
rather than stay in a
silly little pirate group?
Yummy!
Oh, he's laughing! That's good!
CHARLOTTE CHIFFON - BEGE'S WIFE
THE 22ND DAUGHTER OF THE CHARLOTTE FAMILY
Screw you.
You're right! It's meringue.
Is this island full of candies like the others?
Look. These 10 waiting maids
will do whatever you ask them to.
CAPONE "GANG" PEZ - BEGE'S SON
What?! I wanna live here!
Hey! Nami!
THE SEDUCING WOODS
Good, good, good, good! You're a good boy!
CAPONE "GANG" BEGE
THE CAPTAIN OF THE FIRETANK PIRATES
Don't hesitate to ask, Prince-sama.
Chopper! Carrot!
Around here!
Nice, nice!
Hey, junior.
I hope you'll become a great boss like me one day.
That's because you're of royal blood.
I'm sure I saw Sanji and Pudding here
but when I looked away, they were gone!
If we keep sending our troops to countries in war,
we'll never run out of money.
This is certainly the southwest coast.
I can't stand watching that! Grr!
You don't have to fight yourself.
And I know you don't lie,
but I don't know why they left.
He's dazzling, isn't he?
Don't you like the sound of that?
He was just born.
We Vinsmoke Family have always gained
wealth through our force of arms.
I wanna see Sanji already.
And you're going to die.
This is weird. Where did they go?!
Don't you think it's an exquisite contrast?
It's like a painting.
Did you hear that?
You have that blood in your veins.
Oh?
Yes, I did
Like I care.
Move over
This is what you chose.
I'm not gonna marry her!
Tree, tree, tree, tree
Pudding is a nice girl, isn't she?
I like her.
Pekoms. I gave you a chance.
Close up their way out
It didn't look like a chance to me. Grr!
Generalissimo, where are you going?
Flower! Flower! Flower!
I'm gonna go see Sanji.
Remember what happened to you in Zou.
Don't bother me.
Hey!
What the hell?!
There he is!
Let's play
They saved my family members and friends.
Let's play a murder game!
--Sanji!
--What?
I can't do anything to them...
What's wrong with this forest?!
Why are they moving?!
You coward!
--Chopper, can't you go faster?!
--This is the fastest I can go!
Father-sama, why are you here?
Sanji!
Human empathy is useless shit.
--What happened?
--Hey!
Let's play! Let's play!
Is he coming?
Yeah, he's coming after us!
What's going on?
Let's play a murder game!
Sanji was there just now!
Why is he hiding?
You're not cut out for this business.
We gotta get out of this
forest as soon as possible!
Let's play! Let's play!
VINSMOKE JUDGE - THE KING OF THE GERMA KINGDOM
THE GENERALISSIMO OF GERMA 66
Yeah!
Let's play a murder game!
That rabbit is formidable!
Really?
Flower!
This is the perfect place
for getting rid of someone.
Are you still whining?
--You can't escape now!
--Not anymore!
But he's not a Mink!
You bastard...
You sure?!
You can't get out of here alive!
Is he a Devil Fruit eater?
--Give up!
--Prepare yourself!
They've noticed
Oh, my son.
Go to hell!
Any last words?
The Straw Hats have noticed
Don't call me that.
Stop resisting! You're already...
Even if I call someone "Father,"
it wouldn't be you!
About us
--No, they haven't.
--There's something wrong
They've noticed
Oh?
--Brulee-sama is...
--...Playing with them
What did you do to Yonji?
He must be quite strong.
Sanji?
What? Where did he go?
Who will make prey of them?
It's just that I'm stronger than him!
It will be delicious if we
make smoothies out of them
I'm looking for my friends!
Don't get in my way!
Even if you guys can talk,
why don't you be quiet for a while?!
We lost him!
But this place looks delicious!
Tree!
Step outside!
--Shut up!
--Straw Hat!
It's a forest of candies!
--You'll regret this!
--We won't let you walk away alive!
Men should talk with their fists.
Smells sweet!
You underestimate Mama too much!
If all three of them saw him,
it can't be wrong.
Attack him all at once!
THE SEDUCING WOODS
But why did he have to disappear?
Sanji-kun...
Damn! Where did they go?!
What was that fake me from earlier?
Believe this if nothing else.
I didn't mean to hide
anything from my friends.
See! He can't use Electro!
Maybe he feels embarrassed...
Take this!
--Carrot! Stay with us!
--Okay!
Hey! Sanji! Come on out!
--He'll never be able to...
--...Get out of here!
Hey!
THE SOUTHWEST COAST - THE SEDUCING WOODS
I'm sorry, Bird-san!
We're here to pick you up!
C...
Crane!
We won't let him escape!
Brook and Pedro are on a different mission
from Luffy and the others.
Hey, wait!
Sanji!
RANDOLPH - THE CRANE RIDER
THE BIG MOM PIRATES
Sanji!
They are trying to sneak into Sweet City,
the capital of the Whole Cake Island.
Nami! Chopper!
What?! Sanji! What are you doing?!
Okay, let's split up and search!
--The weapon is...
--...Coming towards us!
Should we do it ourselves?
I'm going this way!
Where you see a bunch of cakes!
Let's do it ourselves!
Damn! Hey, wait!
Carrot!
The river is getting much shallower.
I'm going straight!
Where the sweet caramel-like
smell comes from!
Pudding!
Yes, we're almost there.
Then, I'll go this way!
Look at those jelly beans! They're cute!
What?!
Isn't this the right way?
I see it.
Wait! I don't want a secondary disaster!
Hey!
Can we beat him?
Wh-What's wrong with you guys?!
--He looks strong.
--How about a surprise attack?
What?! We just lost him
so all we can do is chase a hunch!
That's Sweet City.
I like that idea!
Hey, stop running!
Let's go ashore in an out-of-sight place.
So... shall we?
That's how people who get lost would think.
Gum-Gum...
We'll head to Big Mom's
castle on foot from there.
Plus, aren't you guys driven by
some other cravings?!
...Finger Net!
Okay. Ahead slowly.
Some other?
Cravings?
You can't run anymore!
No, we aren't.
There's a duel!
Don't lie!
All right! I'll search with you guys!
All three of you, stay with me! Okay?
Who's gonna fight who?
Generalissimo will fight
the fabled Sanji-sama!
Cut it out, Sanji!
That's enough!
Sanji-sama?
I heard he defeated Yonji-sama!
It's a very lively city.
Everyone's waiting for you.
Let's go back.
Mm-hm. Got it!
What kind of guy is he?!
Yes, this place is a melting pot.
We got permission! Let's eat!
We know a bit about how he looks at least!
--Yay!
--I love sweet things!
Extra, extra!
The Totto Land News! Breaking news!
Are we gonna be okay like this?
YONJI'S CASTLE, THE GERMA KINGDOM
Look! There are lollipops!
Breaking news? What is it about?
Oh yeah! Let's go!
I heard he was still refusing to marry
Stay here.
Damn Sanji! How dare he hide
in such a delicious place!
That bastard!
so I tried to teach him a
lesson on Father's behalf.
There are two Sanjis?!
Just like the old days.
I said "Stay with me"! Hey!
And this is what happened!
He'll pay for this! Sanji, that asshole!
Extra, extra!
No, Yonji-sama, a hammer won't do.
The Totto Land News! Breaking news!
Strawberry-flavored!
Does it bring back memories?
Strawberry?! I want that too!
It's good to finally see you!
THE WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
I was surprised to know
that weak old Sanji is still alive
I'm gonna press it. Stay still.
and is a pirate now.
--This flower is a candy!
--Really?!
THE QUEEN'S CHAMBER
This is where the caramel smell comes from!
It's fixed.
Say something.
I think I invested enough money,
Caesar Clown.
Damn!
That bastard! He's just a failure...
Go away.
What was that all about?
Y-Y-Y-Y-Yes!
And of course, I didn't stop researching!
It's so sweet! It sticks my teeth!
I cut ties with my family.
I have nothing to say to you guys.
Now that I beat so many of them,
they quieted down.
I'm so happy!
So that's Sanji-sama!
Well, we have something to say!
Is that so?
Who cares? Hey!
I heard you're refusing to
marry the daughter of the Charlotte Family.
Nami! Chopper!
Hey, guys! Do you remember?
We're here to pick up Sanji-kun!
You're a good-for-nothing fool.
--There you are again!
--Here you come again!
You have no choice.
You guys are too distracted by the candy!
My dream! My dream is...
Man, this forest is so annoying!
I thought we were gonna look for Sanji-kun!
I know!
Are you ready?
Something's stuck in my head.
But there are sweets everywhere!
Anytime.
All right!
Don't you think that's strange?!
We're in the enemy's territory!
I can't stand the pain
so I want you to pull it out for me.
Here I come!
Didn't you hear me?
I'm busy right now!
We'll search to some extent
and if we can't find him, we'll go back.
I said "Go away."
It hurts and I can't stop thinking about it!
Yeah? Then, why don't you
make me go away yourself?!
...for all races in the
world to become family
What?!
Why?!
and sit around a dining table
at the same eye level.
Oh, boy! Alright, alright!
Diable Jambe!
This green river! It's melon juice!
They'll drink what I drink,
You're a nice person.
Really?! Let me try!
Is this it?
Flambage Shot!
and eat what I eat!
--So sweet!
--Isn't it?!
There you go.
If you take a close look at this bridge,
it's a doughnut!
Oh, now I feel better so I want some juice.
I don't care!
Hey! That's enough!
I'm looking for my friends!
Isn't that a wonderful dream?!
Have you seen them?
There are waterfalls of
apple juice on my left.
And you're gonna make it come true for me,
Caesar!
What speed!
I'm asking you a question!
That's just what you'd expect
from a wanted pirate!
I want you to make my family members gigantic
with the power of science.
Cross the bridge!
There you are! Chopper!
You kept telling me...
Nami!
...that you were almost done
but you needed a little more research money.
You're tough as nails. I'm surprised.
I was excited and
spent quite a lot of money.
I can't believe you're
that weak little Sanji.
Chopper! Carrot! Dodge!
Okay!
So how're the results?
This is getting ridiculous.
Well, thanks to you, they're quite good!
I wanna attend the tea party
and get out of here already.
What's going on back there...
How dare you kick your real father!
Then I'm gonna be free from
the curse of Big Mom's invitation.
No!
Cut it out! You started this!
The gigantification of the human body.
Yes, I was doing experiments.
What?!
I thought you might've changed a little
but you actually got worse!
He can serve as a landmark!
And you'd better stop saying
that you're my father!
The whole world is
looking for a technology like that.
Oh, you guys from earlier!
Get out of this room, old man!
You're a stranger to me!
But I was performing experiments
to turn kids into giants. It was deadly.
You're my son who came back! Sanji!
Don't say that while you're attacking me!
He's strong!
The field of lollipops!
He doesn't even have a Raid Suit on!
A little more to go until we reach Luffy!
It's a crocodile!
Do you wanna take it down, Luffy?!
I'll go back to the pirate ship
as soon as the tea party ends.
I'm a genius scientist.
I knew the results from the beginning.
You bastard! Outta my way!
No, you have my blood in your veins.
I'll just pretend to marry her!
It's impossible to make a drug
that'll magically make people
You still saying that?!
Don't get me wrong.
All Germa soldiers are...
No.
Gear Three!
You just want the bond between
you guys and Big Mom, don't you?
gigantic like this old bag wants.
Gum-Gum...
...followers who are willing to die for
the Vinsmoke Family at a moment's notice!
That's why I just screwed her out of her money
and...
Then, it doesn't matter where I end up!
...Giant...
Oh, just humans...
...Pistol!
You can't do that!
They're Germa's biggest military force!
It would be seen as the
Vinsmoke Family's betrayal!
...called girls' ships over to the island
every night,
You think Big Mom would allow that?!
and spent all the money on alcohol and women!
I don't care what would happen to you guys.
Then, why don't you make your
stupid dream come true using them?
What did you think we were?!
I just came to save my friends' lives!
That's not important!
Conquering the North Blue? Great!
That's perfect for an evil organization.
Those were the good old days!
I was going nuts behind Joker's back!
The crocodile is wearing clothes and a hat
and he talked!
Are you gonna abandon your family?!
Just as I thought,
this forest is dangerous and strange!
You're quick on the uptake.
That's right.
You guys are not my family!
DOFLAMINGO FALLS!!
I didn't expect Joker to be defeated...
If that surprises you, take a look at us.
By joining hands with Big Mom,
--He's still fighting!
--Luffy!
it'll become an objective
I can achieve for sure!
Let's go back to the coast!
Well, I know what you mean but...
An objective I can achieve for sure!
Oh? Why're you guys here?!
I guess this is good enough.
...and my life to become this miserable!
Hurry up! I'll tell you later!
If you can understand that,
I have nothing left to say.
This forest has a bunch of creepy traps!
Let's go back to the Sunny!
Dammit! All was smooth sailing before!
I wanted to settle this with you peacefully
somehow but...
Okay!
This is all because of that...
Somebody's after us!
Are you giving a facial performance?
Let's get out of the
forest as fast as we can!
I think we'd better trust Pudding
and wait by the sea!
I need Big Mom's help
but the condition is establishing blood ties.
No!
This! And that! And everything!
They're all Straw Hat Luffy's fault!
I'm sure she'll bring Sanji-kun!
And look!
Our road back is already problematic!
--Where did he go?
--Oh, I know...
It's just a marriage,
Big Mom! I was doing the research
without taking time for sleep!
but I can't let any of my precious sons
marry someone from that crazy old bag's family!
That's the river where
we saw the talking crocodile!
We'll be fine. If we jump over
the river, we can always go back.
The same old place.
If I remember right, as soon as we
cross the river, we can get out!
It was almost completed when...
Then I remembered having another son...
You're right but I don't think we should stay in this forest
any longer...
Let's jump over it like this!
...Straw Hat and Trafalgar Law appeared!
Here we go!
...who was a failure.
What?! I wanna stay here
and eat more candies!
Done!
Wait, guys! That's not the real me...
You are a sacrifice, Sanji.
Why don't you have a lollipop too?
Did you say something, Luffy?!
If it weren't for them,
the Gigantism Drug would've been completed!
I haven't changed.
No, I didn't.
Hey!
I don't think of you as my son even one bit!
Give it back!
Because I'm a genius!
Guys! Let's keep running
without slowing down!
It's a shame that the lab
built by the World Government
He was in the kitchen as I thought.
Okay!
He was making food for rats again!
with such a high level of
technology was destroyed!
Hey, what are these?
What happened to Sanji?!
He ran away from us
and didn't come back!
I could only achieve the results
in that perfectly controlled environment!
You said your hands are important to you.
What?
That's great.
Royalty mustn't cook.
Something's wrong with him,
even though he sure looks like Sanji!
Do you know the shackle collars
that the slaves to the Celestial Dragons wear?
The vast amount of money you invested
and that lab!
Shut up! Give it back!
Let's talk after we get out, Nami!
If they try to escape from their masters,
they'll explode along with their heads.
Yeah! I'm glad that we still know the way!
Ouch...
I lost them so I can't create
the Gigantism Drug now!
What?!
There's another Luffy?!
We'll reach the coast soon!
Those work the same way.
You idiot!
Yeah!
What?!
Don't touch me!
If you try to get off of this island,
your hands will be blown off!
I can't!
Who are you?!
He's so weak and pathetic!
--Oh?!
--What?!
Screw you! Take them off!
We were all born on the same day!
Big Mom had the foresight to lent them to me.
Why are you such a failure while we're not?!
"Who are you"?! I'm Luffy!
Stop mocking me!
She has the key.
What?!
What?! Why?!
What do you want?!
How did you do this?!
I built the exact same lab
as the one on Punk Hazard.
Oh, it's you guys again!
Don't do that.
What?!
I had the blueprint long before that.
Hey, could you pull out the thing
that's stuck to my...
You failure!
You can't try to rip them off.
Our Minister of Candy
can make anything out of candy.
We just went straight back the way we came!
How about this?!
Using the key is the only way
to take them off, of course.
Why are you here?!
You can spend as much money as you want
for the research.
Don't yell. It scares me.
You can't escape.
What?!
A-A-A-A... A-Are you sure?!
Well, first of all,
Oh, Father!
Did you ask why I am here?
I was here the whole time!
I said "Stop mocking me"!
Or I'll beat you up!
I mean, I appreciate it!
we Germa won't let you get away!
What?! What's going on?!
Which one is the real Luffy?!
So?
Are you beating up Sanji again?
You were here the whole time?
"So?"
They move and talk exactly the same!
It's you guys that left and came back.
You have to marry!
No, they're a bit different!
Help me!
When will it be ready?
--Chopper, let's try again!
--Uh-huh!
In a week? Or two weeks?
Hey! Pull out the thing
that's stuck in my head!
Like a mirror-image, his scar and accessories
and everything are inverted.
Chopper! Where have you been?
Help me! Father!
Where are Nami and Carrot?
I can't wait!
It really looks like there's a mirror!
Who is that?!
Running through the field of lollipops...
Don't be ridiculous!
Mankind has been doing the research for centuries,
Who are you?!
Chopper?
She's asking who you are!
Answer her, you idiot!
Why?
but no one's ever succeeded!
Hey, wait! Chopper!
"Why?"
Chopper!
I don't think you're gonna be a good soldier
in the future.
Jumping over the crocodile's river...
What's the matter?!
Lick! Lick!
There he is! I found Sanji!
Do you like that, Caesar-kun?
I have no obligation to help you
and you're not worth raising.
There! Up in the tree!
Let's get to the coast this time!
Oh?
What?
It seems to be quite authentic, doesn't it?
Hey! Sanji!
I said "Wait"!
You scared me!
CHARLOTTE PEROSPERO - THE MINISTER OF CANDY
THE ELDEST SON OF THE CHARLOTTE FAMILY
A CANDY HUMAN WHO ATE THE LICK-LICK FRUIT
Father!
The inside is exactly like
the way it was too. Lick!
Oh, Nami!
Why do you guys keep coming back here?
You're a disgrace to our family!
Get out of my way, you fool!
Again?! Even without the Log Pose working,
What are you hiding...
Sanji!
What?! How did you get there?!
Sanji-kun, what are you doing up there?!
That's...
we don't need to know the directions
because it's one simple path!
Carrot?!
Oh, he's running again! Sanji!
No! Don't do that!
This is fun.
You bastard! Outta my way!
Going straight back this way...
Stand up! I'll train you!
Slowly... Slowly...
What's wrong with you guys?!
A disgrace to the Vinsmokes!
Dammit!
Go ahead and make a charge at him, Yonji.
Damn! You guys, go ahead!
Chase him!
Oops.
Are you screwing with me?!
Flower?!
Okay!
I'll catch you!
We've arrived at the Whole Cake Island.
O-Okay!
What?! The trees and flowers are moving!
I'm coming too!
Okay, let's go-rero.
One, two! One, two!
Don't get separated!
Chopper! Carrot!
The soil is moving and talking!
This forest is strange!
Something's gonna happen again!
Wait! Hey, Black-Foot!
What's going on?
I know! But if we lose Sanji again...
What are those things?
What's with this forest?!
Give me back my heart before you go!
Sanji!
--They found out!
--They did!
Oh, okay.
Nami, go with them!
Cake!
I'll catch up with you after I beat him up!
Yeah, okay!
Flower! Flower!
Brulee-sama is playing with him!
What is that look?!
Why are you doing this, Sanji-kun?
There was no path from the beginning!
Dammit!
Lead him astray and confine him.
This is the Seducing Woods
where people get lost.
You finally became aware...
You only have two weeks to
produce the Gigantism Drug!
Did you remember something?!
...of the terror of this forest!
You'll never be able to get out!
Hey, Luffy, what are you doing?!
If it takes longer than that,
I'll turn you into a "candy man" and lick you!
He blocked the blade with his leg!
This is the Seducing Woods!
Wander about until you die!
Wander about even after you die!
Nami! That's not Luffy!
Sanji!
A candy man?
I can't believe that weak
Sanji uses Haki now.
Damn! Wait!
It seems like he's taken some damage though.
I'll be killed! I'll be killed in two weeks!
I gotta do something!
Who are you?!
--Give me a sword!
--Y-Yes, sir!
Who am I?
We were together the whole time!
I have seen you like dozens of times now.
Take it.
No matter how many times you try,
you'll never get out of this forest!
Gum-Gum...
Now, let me see your hands.
--It's you again.
--I found another one.
...Rocket!
What's the matter?
I thought I taught you how to use a sword.
Never...
They're covered in bruises.
Not until you die!
There are so many of them!
Let go of me!
Sanji! Please stop!
Calm down, young girl.
I refuse!
Look at the scar on my face.
CHARLOTTE BRULEE
THE 8TH DAUGHTER OF THE CHARLOTTE FAMILY
Little brat!
I'm not gonna use my hands for such crap.
Ouch!
Isn't it terrible?
Who are you-teia?! A tree?
I'm not a damn tree! I'm Brulee!
Anyway...
What's your problem, you damn old geezer?!
Brulee?
Gum-Gum...
Are your hands for fighting?!
A cute rabbit and a pretty girl...
...Gatling!
My hands...
How nice...
When I see those beautiful faces...
...are for cooking only.
it makes me want to scratch them up!
Who the hell are you?!
Dammit!
How did you guys multiply?!
Big Mom's extraordinary ability allows her
Chasing after Sanji and the others,
Luffy continues fighting a fierce battle
against the other Luffy!
The Kingdom of Germa once ruled
Holding a grudge from the past,
a father and a son clash!
Luffy is falling into the death
trap of the Seducing Woods!
over the North Blue with their
massive military forces!
to create a world of dreams and madness!
Meanwhile, in front of Nami and the others
who are headed deeper into the forest,
Judge, also known as the Garuda,
uses his scientific powers and aerial attacks on Sanji!
Meanwhile, Big Mom tells Caesar
her dreadful ambition and dream!
The singing flowers, the romping snacks,
and the
Its king is Sanji's father,
namely Vinsmoke Judge!
a mysterious big man
and a rabbit knight suddenly appear!
trees that attack Luffy and
the others in the woods...
The true purpose of the
nefarious human experiment
Those mysterious creatures of Totto Land have
As a result of the battle in which neither yields,
Sanji falls into a desperate situation!
When Sanji sees him again,
In the forest where everything
starts moving and going
which once took place on Punk
Hazard will be revealed!
a stunning secret in their lives
and now it comes to light!
it brings back memories
from his rough and painful childhood!
out of control, the Straw Hats
get caught in a deadly trap!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Land of Souls! Mom's Fatal Ability!"
"A Giant Ambition! Big Mom and Caesar!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Seafaring Kingdom! Germa's King Judge!"
"A Battle Between Father
and Son! Judge vs. Sanji!"
"Mom's Assassin! Luffy
and the Seducing Woods!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!