kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole
Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Chasing Sanji,
they stepped into a mysterious forest,
and got involved in a series of
strange phenomena.
This forest has a bunch of creepy traps!
Let's go back to the Sunny!
Okay!
They tried to get out of the forest
but somehow, they ended up going in circles.
Then, they finally found out
the truth about the forest.
Who are you?!
Who am I?
We were together the whole time!
No matter how many times you try,
you'll never get out of this forest!
Never...
Not until you die!
It's good to finally see you!
I was surprised to know
that weak old Sanji is still alive
and is a pirate now.
Go away.
I cut ties with my family.
I have nothing to say to you guys.
Well, we have something to say!
I heard you're refusing to marry
the daughter of the Charlotte Family.
You're a good-for-nothing fool.
You have no choice.
"A Seafaring Kingdom!
Germa's King Judge!"
Big Mom's castle - the Whole Cake Chateau.
The lake behind it is called Lake Aprico.
This is Germa's ship!
Requesting permission to enter the port!
Go ahead!
Big Mom's subordinate pirates and those
who will be soon are permitted
to enter the port.
Keep it coming! Keep it coming!
All right. Stop right there!
Brace for the impact!
Germa is...
...the name of the one and only seafaring kingdom
that has no land of its own.
Several dozen of their ships
usually travel independently
but occasionally come together
to form the shape of the kingdom.
The country is ruled by the
Vinsmoke Family that once
conquered the North Blue by force.
This is the Germa Kingdom.
Their army, Germa 66
is still viewed as a threat in the world.
Most of its citizens are men and soldiers.
There is not a day that
they don't train themselves.
Why don't you go away already?
How could you say that...
...to your sister that you haven't seen
for 13 years?
How many times do I have to tell you?
I cut ties with you guys
under no uncertain terms!
You guys must be crazy
to put up a tasteless picture like this!
The big incident where four kings in the North Blue
were put down.
The Conquest of Four Nations.
Have mercy!
Please! Don't kill me!
Our father's dream is to bring the North Blue
under Germa's control again.
What's wrong with that?
It's natural for men to be
hung up on power and fame.
Why don't you enjoy being a
member of privileged royalty
rather than stay in a
silly little pirate group?
Screw you.
Look. These 10 waiting maids
will do whatever you ask them to.
Don't hesitate to ask, Prince-sama.
Nice, nice!
That's because you're of royal blood.
If we keep sending our troops to countries in war,
we'll never run out of money.
You don't have to fight yourself.
Don't you like the sound of that?
We Vinsmoke Family have always gained
wealth through our force of arms.
You have that blood in your veins.
Like I care.
I'm not gonna marry her!
Pudding is a nice girl, isn't she?
I like her.
Generalissimo, where are you going?
I'm gonna go see Sanji.
Don't bother me.
Father-sama, why are you here?
VINSMOKE JUDGE - THE KING OF THE GERMA KINGDOM
THE GENERALISSIMO OF GERMA 66
Are you still whining?
You bastard...
Oh, my son.
Don't call me that.
Even if I call someone "Father,"
it wouldn't be you!
What did you do to Yonji?
He must be quite strong.
It's just that I'm stronger than him!
Step outside!
Men should talk with their fists.
THE SEDUCING WOODS
Damn! Where did they go?!
What was that fake me from earlier?
--He'll never be able to...
--...Get out of here!
We won't let him escape!
Nami! Chopper!
Should we do it ourselves?
Let's do it ourselves!
Carrot!
Isn't this the right way?
Can we beat him?
--He looks strong.
--How about a surprise attack?
I like that idea!
So... shall we?
There's a duel!
Who's gonna fight who?
Generalissimo will fight
the fabled Sanji-sama!
Sanji-sama?
I heard he defeated Yonji-sama!
What kind of guy is he?!
We know a bit about how he looks at least!
YONJI'S CASTLE, THE GERMA KINGDOM
I heard he was still refusing to marry
so I tried to teach him a
lesson on Father's behalf.
Just like the old days.
And this is what happened!
He'll pay for this! Sanji, that asshole!
No, Yonji-sama, a hammer won't do.
I'm gonna press it. Stay still.
It's fixed.
Damn!
That bastard! He's just a failure...
So that's Sanji-sama!
Are you ready?
Anytime.
All right!
Here I come!
What speed!
That's just what you'd expect
from a wanted pirate!
How dare you kick your real father!
Cut it out! You started this!
And you'd better stop saying
that you're my father!
You're my son who came back! Sanji!
Don't say that while you're attacking me!
He's strong!
He doesn't even have a Raid Suit on!
I'll go back to the pirate ship
as soon as the tea party ends.
I'll just pretend to marry her!
You still saying that?!
You just want the bond between
you guys and Big Mom, don't you?
Then, it doesn't matter where I end up!
You can't do that!
It would be seen as the
Vinsmoke Family's betrayal!
You think Big Mom would allow that?!
I don't care what would happen to you guys.
I just came to save my friends' lives!
Are you gonna abandon your family?!
You guys are not my family!
I guess this is good enough.
--Where did he go?
--Oh, I know...
The same old place.
Done!
Hey!
Give it back!
He was in the kitchen as I thought.
He was making food for rats again!
Royalty mustn't cook.
Shut up! Give it back!
Ouch...
You idiot!
Don't touch me!
He's so weak and pathetic!
We were all born on the same day!
Why are you such a failure while we're not?!
You failure!
Oh, Father!
Are you beating up Sanji again?
Help me!
Help me! Father!
Why?
"Why?"
I don't think you're gonna be a good soldier
in the future.
I have no obligation to help you
and you're not worth raising.
Father!
You're a disgrace to our family!
Stand up! I'll train you!
A disgrace to the Vinsmokes!
Go ahead and make a charge at him, Yonji.
Okay!
What is that look?!
Did you remember something?!
He blocked the blade with his leg!
I can't believe that weak
Sanji uses Haki now.
It seems like he's taken some damage though.
--Give me a sword!
--Y-Yes, sir!
Take it.
What's the matter?
I thought I taught you how to use a sword.
I refuse!
I'm not gonna use my hands for such crap.
My hands...
...are for cooking only.
Holding a grudge from the past,
a father and a son clash!
Judge, also known as the Garuda,
uses his scientific powers and aerial attacks on Sanji!
As a result of the battle in which neither yields,
Sanji falls into a desperate situation!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Battle Between Father
and Son! Judge vs. Sanji!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!