kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji who was being
pressed into a marriage and
left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the
Whole Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Looking for Sanji,
they wandered in the Seducing Woods,
and got separated by Brulee's trap.
Meanwhile, Sanji was in the
seafaring Germa Kingdom,
a land-less kingdom anchored
at the Whole Cake Island.
There, he reunited with his siblings
and his father who is the absolute ruler.
What's the matter?
I thought I taught you how to use a sword.
I refuse!
I'm not gonna use my hands for such crap.
My hands...
...are for cooking only.
"A Battle Between Father and Son!
Judge vs. Sanji!"
Oh, that weak little Sanji
became this strong...
Cooking? That's absurd!
Unless you're food,
I'm not gonna use blades or hands on you.
Leg attacks are my specialty.
Do you still cook for rats?
Royalty mustn't offer services!
How embarrassing!
That's ridiculous.
What problem do you have with this marriage?!
Generalissimo's hand-to-hand combat!
The fighting style of the man
who is known as the Garuda!
It's a rare sight to behold!
An aerial attack?
Ironically, it's my forte.
Diable Jambe!
Collier...
...Coup!
War advances science!
Electromagnetic Crack!
Blaster!
The Germa that you once knew
is a thing of the past now!
Hey, young Sanji.
Can I ask you something?
Do you think being a biological parent
entitles someone to respect?
You don't...
...even have a single good
memory of him, do you?
You...
Father! Let me out!
...suffered so much.
Father! It's too dark!
Poele a Frire...
You only have animosity... towards him.
Wall.
Hey, you guys, move!
E.M. Shaft!
Hey! Nami!
THE SEDUCING WOODS
Chopper! Carrot!
This is weird. Where did they go?!
What the hell?!
What's wrong with this forest?!
Why are they moving?!
Let's play! Let's play!
Let's play a murder game!
Flower!
--You can't escape now!
--Not anymore!
You can't get out of here alive!
--Give up!
--Prepare yourself!
Go to hell!
Stop resisting! You're already...
I'm looking for my friends!
Don't get in my way!
Even if you guys can talk,
why don't you be quiet for a while?!
Tree!
--Shut up!
--Straw Hat!
--You'll regret this!
--We won't let you walk away alive!
Attack him all at once!
Brook and Pedro are on a different mission
from Luffy and the others.
They are trying to sneak into Sweet City,
the capital of the Whole Cake Island.
The river is getting much shallower.
Yes, we're almost there.
I see it.
That's Sweet City.
Let's go ashore in an out-of-sight place.
We'll head to Big Mom's
castle on foot from there.
Okay. Ahead slowly.
It's a very lively city.
Yes, this place is a melting pot.
Extra, extra!
The Totto Land News! Breaking news!
Breaking news? What is it about?
Stay here.
Extra, extra!
The Totto Land News! Breaking news!
What was that all about?
Now that I beat so many of them,
they quieted down.
Who cares? Hey!
Nami! Chopper!
--There you are again!
--Here you come again!
Man, this forest is so annoying!
Something's stuck in my head.
I can't stand the pain
so I want you to pull it out for me.
I'm busy right now!
It hurts and I can't stop thinking about it!
Oh, boy! Alright, alright!
You're a nice person.
Is this it?
There you go.
Oh, now I feel better so I want some juice.
I don't care!
I'm looking for my friends!
Have you seen them?
There are waterfalls of
apple juice on my left.
I'm asking you a question!
There you are! Chopper!
You're tough as nails. I'm surprised.
I can't believe you're
that weak little Sanji.
This is getting ridiculous.
I wanna attend the tea party
and get out of here already.
Then I'm gonna be free from
the curse of Big Mom's invitation.
I thought you might've changed a little
but you actually got worse!
Get out of this room, old man!
You're a stranger to me!
No, you have my blood in your veins.
Don't get me wrong.
All Germa soldiers are...
...followers who are willing to die for
the Vinsmoke Family at a moment's notice!
They're Germa's biggest military force!
Then, why don't you make your
stupid dream come true using them?
Conquering the North Blue? Great!
That's perfect for an evil organization.
You're quick on the uptake.
That's right.
By joining hands with Big Mom,
it'll become an objective
I can achieve for sure!
An objective I can achieve for sure!
If you can understand that,
I have nothing left to say.
I wanted to settle this with you peacefully
somehow but...
I need Big Mom's help
but the condition is establishing blood ties.
It's just a marriage,
but I can't let any of my precious sons
marry someone from that crazy old bag's family!
Then I remembered having another son...
...who was a failure.
You are a sacrifice, Sanji.
I haven't changed.
I don't think of you as my son even one bit!
Hey, what are these?
You said your hands are important to you.
That's great.
Do you know the shackle collars
that the slaves to the Celestial Dragons wear?
If they try to escape from their masters,
they'll explode along with their heads.
Those work the same way.
If you try to get off of this island,
your hands will be blown off!
Screw you! Take them off!
Big Mom had the foresight to lent them to me.
She has the key.
What?!
Don't do that.
You can't try to rip them off.
Using the key is the only way
to take them off, of course.
You can't escape.
Well, first of all,
we Germa won't let you get away!
You have to marry!
Chopper! Where have you been?
Where are Nami and Carrot?
Chopper?
Hey, wait! Chopper!
Chopper!
What's the matter?!
Oh?
What?
I said "Wait"!
Oh, Nami!
What are you hiding...
What?! How did you get there?!
Carrot?!
What's wrong with you guys?!
Are you screwing with me?!
I'll catch you!
Brulee-sama is playing with him!
Lead him astray and confine him.
This is the Seducing Woods
where people get lost.
You'll never be able to get out!
Wander about until you die!
Wander about even after you die!
Damn! Wait!
Now, let me see your hands.
They're covered in bruises.
Little brat!
Ouch!
What's your problem, you damn old geezer?!
Are your hands for fighting?!
Dammit!
Chasing after Sanji and the others,
Luffy is falling into the death
trap of the Seducing Woods!
Meanwhile, Big Mom tells Caesar
her dreadful ambition and dream!
The true purpose of the
nefarious human experiment
which once took place on Punk
Hazard will be revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Giant Ambition! Big Mom and Caesar!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!