I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy has separated from Nami, Chopper and Carrot
in the Seducing Woods.
Meanwhile, Sanji got into a
fight with Vinsmoke Judge,
his father and Germa 66's generalissimo.
You are a sacrifice, Sanji.
I haven't changed.
I don't think of you as my son even one bit!
If you try to get off of this island,
your hands will be blown off!
At the same time,
Brook and Pedro were secretly on the move...
...to get Big Mom's Road Ponegliff
which is one of the keys to the One Piece.
"A Giant Ambition!
Big Mom and Caesar!"
SOMEWHERE AROUND THE CAPITAL - SWEET CITY
Extra! Extra!
Boss Jimbei betrayed?!
This happened between him and Mama yesterday?
Boss Jimbei was sure cool
when he stopped Mama's tantrum.
He blustered that he
wanted to leave her crew,
but he got scared of paying
the price and backed down!
Yeah? That's pathetic!
What a loser!
Didn't he know how much he benefitted
from being one of Emperor Big Mom's subordinates?
He's known as the "First Son of the Sea" for nothing.
I lost respect for him.
So he was a coward as well as a traitor.
Jimbei-san,
I didn't know you were working under Big Mom.
That's why the Fish-Man Island
was protected by Big Mom.
Jimbei is a former Warlord, isn't he?
I can't believe someone of his stature is her subordinate.
Brook, do you know this man?
Yes, he's a very important person to us.
Hey, Jimbei.
Join...
...my crew!
When I fulfill my duties
and am free from them,
I promise I will come to see you all again.
And if you haven't changed your mind,
can I take you up on your offer then?
I guess he turned down the offer to join our crew
that day
because he wanted to fulfill
his duty to Big Mom.
Now, this article...
It doesn't sound like something he'd do.
Won't he come see us again?
Hey, Brook!
What?
Please! I have to go somewhere!
Nothing is more important to you now
than choosing a dress!
Stop being such a baby-s'il vous plaît,
Pudding-sama!
But...
How about this dress?
Wow, it looks good on you!
How about this one? I knew it, Pudding-sama!
It looks wonderful!
Everything looks good on you!
Which one do you like, Pudding-sama?
Um...
Pudding-sama,
do you know what the groom likes?
What?!
No! I've only met him once so...
Whaaat?!
Wait a minute, Pudding-san,
what is she doing here?!
I guess she got caught by her attendants.
I assumed she'd already led Sanji-san out
to meet with Luffy-san and the others by now.
Looking at this, I bet
Sanji doesn't even know that we're here.
Then, who did Luffy-san see at the shore?
I don't know.
Maybe he just saw someone else.
That's... If I'm not mistaken,
he was on Big Mom's ship...
Yeah, I know him very well.
Baron Tamago!
Baron Tamago, may I speak to you?
What is it-soir?
The Straw Hat's ship that stopped by
at Chocolat Town yesterday...
They already know!
When they left, Mr. Pekoms who was guiding them
was already gone, they say.
They know everything!
And the four Straw Hats
who wandered into the Seducing Woods today.
They're already cornered!
They're as good as captured!
Luffy-san and the others got caught?!
But we still can't find the remaining two.
These two.
That's us!
It's leaked out completely!
They knew everything from the start!
Where were they watching us from?!
A PANTHER MINK
That mink is not a panther-soir.
He's a jaguar Mink. His name is Pedro.
Do you know him?
Just a little bit from the past.
I know what he would do-feuille.
--Anyway, I want you guys to look for Pekoms.
--Yes, sir.
Pekoms. Since he was alive-bon,
for the sake of our
long-standing partnership,
I was going to ask for
Mama's pardon with him.
He gives me a lot of trouble-marron.
We are in big trouble!
THE NORTHEAST COAST OF THE WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Hey, cut it out, junior!
You fool!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
Just be...
...quiet!
Oh, he's laughing! That's good!
CHARLOTTE CHIFFON - BEGE'S WIFE
THE 22ND DAUGHTER OF THE CHARLOTTE FAMILY
CAPONE "GANG" PEZ - BEGE'S SON
Good, good, good, good! You're a good boy!
CAPONE "GANG" BEGE
THE CAPTAIN OF THE FIRETANK PIRATES
Hey, junior.
I hope you'll become a great boss like me one day.
I can't stand watching that! Grr!
He's dazzling, isn't he?
He was just born.
And you're going to die.
Don't you think it's an exquisite contrast?
It's like a painting.
This is what you chose.
Pekoms. I gave you a chance.
It didn't look like a chance to me. Grr!
Remember what happened to you in Zou.
They saved my family members and friends.
I can't do anything to them...
You coward!
Human empathy is useless shit.
You're not cut out for this business.
This is the perfect place
for getting rid of someone.
Any last words?
You underestimate Mama too much!
Hey!
THE SOUTHWEST COAST - THE SEDUCING WOODS
Hey, wait!
Sanji!
What?! Sanji! What are you doing?!
Damn! Hey, wait!
Pudding!
What?!
Hey!
Wh-What's wrong with you guys?!
Hey, stop running!
Gum-Gum...
...Finger Net!
You can't run anymore!
Cut it out, Sanji!
That's enough!
Everyone's waiting for you.
Let's go back.
There are two Sanjis?!
THE WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
THE QUEEN'S CHAMBER
I think I invested enough money,
Caesar Clown.
Y-Y-Y-Y-Yes!
And of course, I didn't stop researching!
Is that so?
My dream! My dream is...
...for all races in the
world to become family
and sit around a dining table
at the same eye level.
They'll drink what I drink,
and eat what I eat!
Isn't that a wonderful dream?!
And you're gonna make it come true for me,
Caesar!
I want you to make my family members gigantic
with the power of science.
You kept telling me...
...that you were almost done
but you needed a little more research money.
I was excited and
spent quite a lot of money.
So how're the results?
Well, thanks to you, they're quite good!
The gigantification of the human body.
Yes, I was doing experiments.
The whole world is
looking for a technology like that.
But I was performing experiments
to turn kids into giants. It was deadly.
I'm a genius scientist.
I knew the results from the beginning.
It's impossible to make a drug
that'll magically make people
gigantic like this old bag wants.
That's why I just screwed her out of her money
and...
...called girls' ships over to the island
every night,
and spent all the money on alcohol and women!
Those were the good old days!
I was going nuts behind Joker's back!
DOFLAMINGO FALLS!!
I didn't expect Joker to be defeated...
...and my life to become this miserable!
Dammit! All was smooth sailing before!
This is all because of that...
Are you giving a facial performance?
No!
This! And that! And everything!
They're all Straw Hat Luffy's fault!
Big Mom! I was doing the research
without taking time for sleep!
It was almost completed when...
...Straw Hat and Trafalgar Law appeared!
If it weren't for them,
the Gigantism Drug would've been completed!
Because I'm a genius!
It's a shame that the lab
built by the World Government
with such a high level of
technology was destroyed!
I could only achieve the results
in that perfectly controlled environment!
The vast amount of money you invested
and that lab!
I lost them so I can't create
the Gigantism Drug now!
I can't!
I built the exact same lab
as the one on Punk Hazard.
What?!
I had the blueprint long before that.
Our Minister of Candy
can make anything out of candy.
You can spend as much money as you want
for the research.
What?!
A-A-A-A... A-Are you sure?!
I mean, I appreciate it!
So?
"So?"
When will it be ready?
In a week? Or two weeks?
I can't wait!
Don't be ridiculous!
Mankind has been doing the research for centuries,
but no one's ever succeeded!
Lick! Lick!
Do you like that, Caesar-kun?
It seems to be quite authentic, doesn't it?
CHARLOTTE PEROSPERO - THE MINISTER OF CANDY
THE ELDEST SON OF THE CHARLOTTE FAMILY
A CANDY HUMAN WHO ATE THE LICK-LICK FRUIT
The inside is exactly like
the way it was too. Lick!
That's...
No! Don't do that!
This is fun.
Dammit!
We've arrived at the Whole Cake Island.
Okay, let's go-rero.
Wait! Hey, Black-Foot!
Give me back my heart before you go!
Oh, okay.
Dammit!
You only have two weeks to
produce the Gigantism Drug!
If it takes longer than that,
I'll turn you into a "candy man" and lick you!
A candy man?
I'll be killed! I'll be killed in two weeks!
I gotta do something!
I have seen you like dozens of times now.
--It's you again.
--I found another one.
There are so many of them!
Anyway...
How did you guys multiply?!
Big Mom's extraordinary ability allows her
to create a world of dreams and madness!
The singing flowers, the romping snacks,
and the
trees that attack Luffy and
the others in the woods...
Those mysterious creatures of Totto Land have
a stunning secret in their lives
and now it comes to light!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Land of Souls! Mom's Fatal Ability!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!