I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a journey with you, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that everyone laughs and says
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our tears will eventually stop
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go, Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible? Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani? mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
...except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
a marriage and left his friends behind,
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy and the others infiltrated the
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole
Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Whole Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Separated from Nami and the others in
the Seducing Woods, Luffy caught...
Luffy was wandering in the Seducing Woods,
the forest with no escape, and reunited with Nami.
The Seducing Woods is the forest with no escape.
Chopper and Carrot have been
trapped in a world of mirrors.
They entered the Seducing Woods
and started to fight against Cracker,
one of the Sweet 3 Generals.
As Luffy and Nami discovered that
Pound was Big Mom's husband,
Brook and Pedro have snuck into Sweet City.
I see! I'm glad that you found me!
Pretzel Roll!
How did you guys multiply?!
Cracker, one of the Sweet 3 Generals,
showed up.
As everyone acts separately,
nearby in the Seducing Woods,
All right!
the fierce duel between Luffy and
Sweet General Cracker enters a new phase.
Cracker-kun, let go of me!
I just want to see Lola and Chiffon...
Let's go save Chopper and Carrot now!
Where are they?
Here.
It all happened right here.
Meanwhile, Pound who was watching Nami
being attacked and cornered...
It multiplies as I clap my hands!
That's how my dreamlike biscuit works.
I just want to see my daughters!
But now, they're all gone.
That's why I'm asking him!
Let go of her, Brulee!
Wh-What are you gonna do to me?!
So I have a limitless force at my disposal!
You were watching the whole time!
Where's Chopper? And Carrot?!
Mama told me
what she wants me to do with you.
Nami finally drove Brulee off.
The one that you broke with your life
was just one of my Biscuit Warriors...
What? Did she?
That woman, Brulee, and the forest monsters
didn't even touch you!
Thunderbolt...
She said I can kill you.
...Tempo!
What?!
...that I can generate endlessly.
That means you're one of them!
Do you understand why you'll never see
Vinsmoke Sanji again?
One of them?
Well, I'm certainly not their enemy.
Th-Think about it!
I'm your stepfather, Cracker-kun!
In addition, Nami became
confirmed that the Vivre Card
I'll be back.
Years and years ago,
I was Big Mom's... I mean, the pirate Charlotte Linlin's...
You used to be! Not now!
that Lola gave her was Big Mom's.
Mama considers her 43 ex-husbands as
strangers unrelated to us by blood.
I see. It's no mistake!
I'm gonna see Sanji!
Leave or Life?
Lola's mother is Big Mom.
Linlin's...
How dare you!
But I'm definitely related to my daughters by blood!
Life.
The fact that those trees in the forest
are afraid of this Vivre Card is the proof.
"The First and the Second Join!
The Vinsmoke Family!"
Linlin's husband!
Enough!
I just want to give my blessing to my daughters!
I'll make the most of it, Lola!
What?!
Meanwhile, a shadow of another enemy
was closing in on Luffy and Nami...
Cracker was about to give Pound a death blow
since he revealed Big Mom's secret to Luffy and Nami.
Leave or Life?
Learning that there are people you can't beat
no matter how hard you try...
Life.
"An All-out Duel!
Gear Four vs. the Bis-Bis Ability!"
Wh-Why is one of the Sweet 3 Generals here?!
...is the mark of true progress, brat!
Leave or Life?
Life.
"A Top Officer!
The Sweet 3 General Cracker Appears!"
Life.
I'll teach you a lesson!
Can't you sleep?
Was that out of sympathy?
S-Sir, what brings you here?
I've run in to him dozens of times!
Of course I became attached to him!
What do you want?
Am I not allowed to be here?
You're as cold as ever.
Leave or Life?
Don't you think it's natural for a big sister
to worry about her sweet little brother?
No! Of course, you're welcomed!
"An Enemy Worth 800 million!
Luffy vs. Thousand Armed Cracker!"
Flower! Flower!
Stop it. That creeps me out.
Ichiji and Niji will be here by tomorrow.
Evacuate! We'll get hurt too!
"The Land of Souls!
Mom's Fatal Ability!"
What's wrong?
You've got no energy left to break them?
Gum-Gum...
...Rhino Schneider!
Run!
For the first time in 13 years,
the whole family will gather together.
What's going on?!
They have multiplied and
are barking like animals!
Gum-Gum...
Tomorrow's gonna be very busy.
...Leo Bazooka!
What happened to you guys?!
We'll meet Big Mom at the Whole Cake Chateau.
Big Mom's...
Aren't any of you real?!
...Ex-husband?!
Damn!
Hey, Sanji!
And we'll have an engagement ceremony
for you and Pudding.
Uh-huh.
As soon as two daughters were born,
she dumped me.
You'd better get some rest.
Pudding! Chopper!
Gum-Gum...
Carrot!
Nami!
...Culverin!
Untie me!
It's not that they're avoiding attacking me.
She talks like a human!
They just don't care about me.
Interesting techniques.
I'm the real Nami!
Gear Two!
He's so persistent.
Listen! I was looking for you!
What is it?!
Gum-Gum...
How dare you tie me up all of a sudden!
...Red Hawk!
I... I'm really sorry...
But it sure is surprising.
What's going on?
He destroyed all of them.
Hey... What's coming now?!
She certainly looks like me.
If all the real ones are among them,
that'd make it easy.
I'm not done!
Straw Hat!
I thought you guys multiplied.
Wh-What?!
What?! What the...
No, we didn't!
I mean, we kinda did but...
--We can't do it!
--We have no chance!
Cut it out! Hey, you!
Who is this?!
What?! He's got another arm!
What?!
Run!
You know something, don't you?
How is that possible?!
You were here the whole time even
when we were attacked by that woman!
Hey!
Here I go!
I didn't see anything!
THE SEDUCING WOODS
Don't lie!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Hey, what happened?
Gum-Gum...
What?!
I was attacked by you, Luffy!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
What?! He's got another one!
...Giant Axe!
By me?!
To be exact, that was a fake you who I
thought was you and tried to escape with!
--His body's coming out!
--Get back, Nami!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
What do you mean?
Stop this useless resistance, Straw Hat!
Don't... Don't... Don't do that!
That "Luffy" suddenly turned into
a giant woman and attacked us...
Gum-Gum...
No!
...Grizzly Magnum!
No matter how many of them you beat,
it doesn't make any difference.
I thought he was a Giant!
Let go of me!
Who are you-teia?!
I'm Brulee!
Brulee?
A cute rabbit and a pretty girl...
How nice...
Is this really Big Mom's Vivre Card?!
Double Pretzel...
Y-You are...!
When I see those beautiful faces...
I guess we'll be safe here.
Are you crazy? How could you spill information
to our enemy like that, you fool!
...Roll!
We're no match for him!
it makes me want to scratch them up!
Oh? Hey, look!
W-Wait, Cracker-kun!
Nami!
That girl is gone!
I want to see my daughter, Chiffon,
even just for a moment!
No!
I'm here.
Stop resisting, young lady.
I heard she got married!
I want to give her my blessing!
Luffy! No!
Wh-Where's Luffy?!
You okay?!
Well, I don't know.
I guess he's wandering in the forest.
So let me talk to Linlin!
When did she get there?!
I heard Lola ran away!
C-Cracker-kun!
Climate Baton!
If you close your mouth,
you'll be sealing your doom.
They're both my precious daughters!
He has extra arms!
Damn!
Lola?
That bastard!
Ran away?
I'm the Biscuit Knight - Cracker,
one of the Sweet 3 Generals.
One of my older sisters that I loved very dearly
went out to the sea looking for love.
I told you to take Cracker down!
It's really impossible!
Nami, are you okay?!
Yeah! That was close!
Also known as...
Cracker-sama and Straw Hat are
so intimidating we can't go near!
To seek a match.
...Thousand Armed Cracker.
Thank you, Usopp!
So what?
Lola who ran away from home?
If I tap once, it becomes two.
No matter how many of you get withered,
my heart won't ache in the slightest!
How insolent!
Who is it?
Oh, no! We'll get involved!
Cracker-kun, let go of me!
I just want to see Lola and Chiffon...
If I tap it again,
What?!
it becomes three.
Carrot!
You're a horrible person.
I just want to see my daughters!
Leave it to me!
What?!
They'll keep multiplying.
You have a pretty face
but a lot of nerve as well!
Sweet General Cracker
and his mother Emperor Big Mom.
Lola... Don't tell me that Lola is...
Which of them scares you more?
Hey! Don't spread out too much
and neglect our duty as the Seducing Woods!
His legs have multiplied too.
You're scarier than both!
Eleclaw!
Wait a minute!
I'm... I'm actually a guy!
We shouldn't let anyone out of here!
Don't even dream of beating me.
THOUSAND ARMED CRACKER - ONE OF THE SWEET 3 GENERALS
EMPEROR BIG MOM PIRATES
BOUNTY: 860 MILLION BERRIES
I won't let you screw up Mama's tea party!
BRULEE'S MIRRO-WORLD
What is this?
What?!
You've got extra limbs. So what?!
Gear Two!
The inside of someone's house?
A-Are you?!
O-Okay!
I think so.
It's my turn!
Y-Yes, I am! I like dressing like a girl!
I'm not kidding!
Block his way!
What about this one?
Gum-Gum...
Reflection!
I don't see anything.
On top of that,
...Jet...
I think you and that animal man
will make a great couple and I wanted to help!
...Bullet!
Carrot!
Gum-Gum...
What?! Really?!
Is it a bathroom somewhere?
...Hawk Whip!
Maybe...
Are you okay?!
No one's ever supported my feelings for him.
Gum-Gum...
Carrot's punch came out of the mirror!
You're the first person ever
to say such a nice thing to me.
What did you do?!
...Hawk Gatling!
Luffy! No! Don't get into an all-out fight!
That's not our objective!
I see! I get the picture!
Listen, Carrot!
Hard Biscuit!
I'm a mirror!
Raise your head, my friend.
I ate the Mirror-Mirror Fruit
and became a mirror human!
We gotta get out of here
and get Sanji-kun back!
I have a great idea
so please call me Big Bro Chopper from now on!
This is what friendship is!
I only know how to fight...
My name is Namizo. You can call me Nami.
Just like a mirror reflects light,
if you throw a punch at my mirror,
Uh-huh, okay.
...all-out!
Good!
Friendship...
And what is your idea, Chobro?!
Nami!
it'll reflect it back too!
Chobro?!
Thank you for coming to save me!
Damn! It's hard!
This guy's Color of Arms!
That's right!
Short for Big Bro Chopper, Chobro!
Of course I came, Namizo...
Humph! What an insolent brat!
Look at this sword! Isn't it something?
I'm your friend...
Well, okay.
It seems like this world of mirrors
Be careful, Carrot!
It's called Pretzel!
It's a one and only sword in the world!
But I lied to you at that time
because I was scared of you.
I'll destroy your stupid mirror!
is connected to all the mirrors
across the Whole Cake Island!
What a silly rabbit.
I'll teach you a lesson
about the roughness of the New World!
I'm sorry. I'm actually a woman.
Yes, I think so.
Instead of escaping from here,
we should take advantage of Brulee's ability!
Mirro-world!
What?! A one and only sword?!
But you've got six!
You silly girl... I knew all along.
How?
We can look for Sanji through these mirrors!
Lola.
H-Hey!
Now, come on in!
You're right! That's my Chobro!
Carrot!
If you think of Vinsmoke Sanji as your friend,
why don't you leave him alone?
Let's run for now, Luffy!
Why did I say that? Who's Namizo?
Your compliment doesn't make me happy,
you fool!
No way!
Come to think of it, it's strange.
For some reason, I feel like I knew you before.
Gear Three!
Gum-Gum...
He's a prince of a mighty kingdom.
He's in a totally different class from you.
Are you... Lola?!
Alright, let's go!
She disappeared...
Okay, Chobro!
...Elephant Gun!
I am. Did I say my name?
What did you do to her?!
SWEET CITY, CAPITAL OF THE WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Oh, I can't believe it, Lola!
I'm so happy to see you again!
By taking a noble wife, he can live here...
...in great comfort.
One down!
I can't get out! Let me out!
Lola, you guys went to the New World?
What did you do?! Give her back to us!
We didn't go there. We're from there.
You fools have got nowhere to run!
You can't even wish your friend happiness
Stay away, Nami!
My mama is a pirate and... Oh...
I can't do that.
and you're just being selfish
saying you're gonna take him back.
Secret Song Whirlwind Slash.
Here's something for you.
Seeing such an annoying captain,
Nami!
My mama's Vivre Card. You can have it.
Damn!
Chopper!
the virtuous prince would be disgusted
and probably say:
Paper?
Wow! You're lucky!
Captain Lola's mother is an amazing pirate!
Help me!
Don't lose it!
I'm sure it'll come in handy one day!
"Get packing, you pathetic low-class pirate!"
--That went well.
--Mm-hm.
Everything's coming together now!
Pretzel Roll!
Mama already knew that you guys were here!
After patrol, the Biscuit Warriors
will be put away in the chateau.
In that case, could Lola's mother be...
What?!
Did you think that no one noticed?
How idiotic!
He surely is pathetic!
Let's make a move then.
Big Mom?!
You low-class pirate! Get packing!
And this man is...
--...Lola's father?!
--What?
We are all coming after you guys
by Mama's order!
Good work.
Muscle Balloon!
That one...
These ones...
Those fools...
Crane!
You wanna destroy more, don't you?
And him!
All of us have been commanded by Mama!
Keep going.
"Leave the Straw Hats at large for now."
That's my brother!
Crane!
Here are more!
Luffy...
"But don't let them see Sanji."
They came back!
The rabbit and the crane!
"Make them regret standing against me!"
It's fun to have someone
who breaks them like you!
It could fly?!
Gear Four!
It's makes it worth making them.
Bounce-Man!
Stop! Randolph!
Muscle Balloon is a good name.
But however much you fight,
you have no chance to win.
Oh, no!
But what can a balloon do?
They are members of the Emperor's clan!
We should've been more careful!
Let me say it one more time!
Even Luffy's having a hard time
with her subordinate!
Get packing, you pathetic low-class pirate!
Mama knows everything!
Luffy! Run!
Was that Haki?! Maybe not!
What was it then?!
Wh-What the...
Gum-Gum Kong...
Hard Biscuit!
Stop there! I'll fight you two!
I'll beat you up and go see Sanji!
...Gun!
They screamed...
Me too-ju!
...and withered out of fear?!
Alright, Homies! Don't let them escape!
Cracker-sama!
Oh, no! We'll be surrounded!
You can't get away!
Don't underestimate Sanji!
Even if he's happy
and doesn't want to come back,
Gum-Gum...
No!
he'd never talk to us like that!
...Kong...
I know how you feel.
You got scared suddenly, right?
Chopper!
...Organ Gun!
The Worst Generation?
What's so "worst" about it?!
After being puffed up
in the first half of the Grand Line,
Advance!
lots of underlings came here saying "Our captain
will become the Pirate King" - only to be disappointed.
Nami, run!
There are too many enemies!
If all three of us get caught, we'll be dead!
I've seen tons of those cases!
They are members of the Emperor's clan!
We should've been more careful!
Even in the last two years, a number of those pirates
came wandering in Mama's territory.
Crane...
Go look for Luffy!
I'll do the best I can here!
"Captain" Kid.
SWEET CITY
Okay! I'll be back!
"Roar of the Sea" Apoo.
"Gang" Bege.
Honey Pretzel!
"Mad Monk" Urouge.
How could you get in my way like that?
When did you become so important?
Rumble!
So that's the Whole Cake Chateau
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Except for Bege who found his bearings instantly
and became our ally,
Monster Point!
--Yeah.
--How's security?
Randolph!
The chateau is heavily guarded
by Biscuit Warriors.
everyone got driven away
without even seeing Mama or hearing her voice!
I'm sorry. That was his idea.
That's amazing! He's already a funny animal
but he also has such a special skill!
Biscuit Warriors?
Don't lie! It was yours!
The only one who held on was...
They spoke!
Mama will be happy!
..."Mad Monk" Urouge!
--That was his idea.
--Hey!
All the races of the world aren't enough
because she's an unrivalled exotic animal collector!
He was impudent enough to defeat
one of the Sweet Generals!
It's morning, it's morning
We are very sorry.
Good morning!
They were the Sweet 4 Generals
until not so long ago.
Today, we'll have the Vinsmokes
over to get acquainted,
Good morning
Is he someone in a high position?
Now, catch them!
THE WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
and we'll have an engagement ceremony, Mama.
He's certainly strong.
What about the wedding cake?
Mama always makes a pre-emptive move.
Stop, you brat!
That comes tomorrow.
Since Straw Hat Luffy beat Doflamingo,
Go away!
One night has passed.
she bet Brulee would have a hard time
so she sent me.
How are those mold fungi holding up?
That's it!
I can't let you just say that, Big Bro!
This is their last chance
to meet their friend.
I guess I can't see an Emperor's face that easily.
Oh, please! How could you say that
after you sent Cracker-sama?
She can't get away!
It's true that once Black-Foot enters the castle,
they'll have no chance to see him!
Pedro-san, how can we get through
such tight security?
What is it this time?!
Both the tea party and the wedding
will be held in the castle.
Don't worry. I have an idea.
Are they more bark than
bite like all the others?
Let's use that one-gara.
Luffy! Where are you?!
What?
Some of Vinsmoke's sons
aren't here yet, right?
Whoa! A tree monster!
THE GERMA KINGDOM
Well, I've just had a call
saying that they've arrived.
Then, I kept running around
Oh, that woman!
You've roughed me up so much.
and was looking for you until it got dark!
If I'm asked to kill them, I'll do it right away!
What is this place?
Good. They're here.
I think it's a world in Brulee's mirror.
KINGBAUM - THE MASTER OF THE SEDUCING WOODS
I see! I'm glad that you found me!
That's right-ju!
Retribution!
My dearest sons!
We, the Seducing Woods Team,
All right!
I can't wait to see them facing Sanji.
have never let even a single target
walk away alive-ju!
I wonder how far it goes.
Let's go save Chopper and Carrot now!
Where are they?
Oh! Not only Cracker-sama and Brulee-sama
but also Kingbaum-sama is here!
Here.
It all happened right here.
I see no end.
I can't believe that those three are all here at once.
But now, they're all gone.
That's why I'm asking him!
But I see mirrors everywhere.
What?!
That's great but we have no time to waste now.
Is that all you've got, "Mad Monk" Urouge?
--Let's look into one.
--Yeah.
You were watching the whole time!
Where's Chopper? And Carrot?!
Pretzel Roll!
By tomorrow noon, all brothers and sisters of the Vinsmokes
will get together and enter the Whole Cake Chateau.
My ankles hurt!
THE WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
How are the Straw Hats doing?
Hang on, Carrot!
Forming a family connection with the Vinsmokes is
something that Mama has wanted for a long time.
They're being tormented
in the Seducing Woods!
This isn't that hard so stop whining!
By Brulee-sama!
But that was it.
And by the Homies!
All right!
He made Mama mad
and got beaten badly by Brother Cracker!
You'll never get out of the forest!
Welcome back!
How much more can they stand?!
We can share Germa 66's formidable military
and science technology.
He has nowhere to run!
I bet he's dead in a ditch somewhere by now!
VINSMOKE ICHIJI - SPARKING RED
ELDEST SON OF THE VINSMOKE FAMILY
I know!
I see. That's good.
She disappeared!
VINSMOKE NIJI - ELECTRIC BLUE
SECOND SON OF THE VINSMOKE FAMILY
They've turned into animals!
What do you mean by making
the most of Linlin's...
--Ichiji-sama! Niji-sama!
--Nice to see you back from your long trip!
And how can that branch talk?
I mean, Big Mom's Vivre Card?
There you are, Cracker.
Listen!
I couldn't believe that you ended that
interminable war on Brock Collie!
I'm not a branch!
You've reached a dead end in the New World!
What do you want, Mama?
Didn't you hear what that
arrogant tree said earlier?
Look at this, Straw Hat!
Go teach Straw Hat and his clan a lesson.
Oh, Luffy!
You mean Kingbaum?
Straw Hat?
Luffy! Nami! Help!
He said "We Homies can't
fight against her-ju!"
They're in the Seducing Woods.
Give them a taste...
What?!
Fighting an Emperor?
That's just a dream!
Chopper got caught too?!
What happened, you guys?!
How did you get in there?!
Stop!
...of pain and terror
which will make them welcome death!
You can't even see Mama!
Are you guys trying to escape?
She trapped us in the mirror!
She has an ability involving mirrors! Be careful!
Sneaking into the tea party?
Messing up the wedding?!
I'm sorry. It was his idea.
Why isn't he coming out to greet us?
Don't lie! It was yours!
Stop, Niji.
And taking your friend back?!
That's not gonna happen!
Listen. You guys are gonna be my loyal servants
from now on.
Okay.
You see what I did, Brother Cracker?!
Mama.
You guys will die in this forest
without even seeing Mama!
I'm grabbing these fools...
Stop talking nonsense, you brat!
Say something already!
...by the scruff of their neck!
Yeah! Who do you think you are?!
Father, we are back.
That woman, Brulee, and the forest monsters
didn't even touch you!
Thank you for your work, Ichiji, Niji.
What? Are you gonna resist?
M-My baton...
Am I talking nonsense?
That means you're one of them!
Where is he?
He's here.
Now, come to the Mirro-world!
One of them?
Well, I'm certainly not their enemy.
N-No, you aren't-ju...
Rabbit-kun, what do you think?
Where are those two?!
--I'm sorry. It was his fault.
--Hey!
Hey, Chopper! Carrot! Are you okay?!
Let go of me!
Sanji! Wow!
Listen, you guys must back Luffy up now!
Oh! If you want me to tell you,
bring me some apple juice from over on my left...
You're really alive!
Come on! Come on! Come to me!
We're fine!
I'll cut up your face and body slowly
in the other dimension!
We're not hurt at all!
We have no time for that!
A-Are you telling us
to fight against Cracker-sama?!
It's just the mirror that broke.
We're safe in this dimension!
If you really tell us something good,
sure, I'll bring it to you!
Congratulations on your engagement, Sanji.
That's impossible-ju!
No!
Hey, say something.
You mean it?!
Oh, yeah?
--So you're okay!
--I don't know what you're talking about but that's good.
Yeah, since you insist on it,
I wanna drink it too!
Let go of me!
Uh-huh!
Luffy! Listen...
By the way,
You get to wear such nice
things on your wrists!
you look quite strong but...
Let go of me!
Get your hands off of me!
That's our father! He knows everything!
...are you strong too?
These things fit you the best.
Come on, go help Luffy now!
Take Cracker down!
Y-Yes, I am strong! So what?
Forget it.
Let's start with this loose-tongued fool.
Lessons like these.
I see. You don't look strong.
Don't!
Wh-What are you gonna do to me?!
We can't fight Mama's Life Paper -
Vivre Card-ju!
That reindeer guy was surprisingly strong,
Mama told me
what she wants me to do with you.
but the trees of the forest attacked him
without hesitation.
What? Did she?
Ichiji, Niji, relax from your journey.
What did she say?
Once they're ordered,
they're not gonna stop...
First, eat something.
She said I can kill you.
Pound-chan!
What?!
You little...
...until they fulfill their mission!
Just give up!
The battlefront Brock Collie is another victim of
the fall of the Doflamingo regime, you could say.
Yeah? Then, why did they stop attacking me?
Let go of her, Brulee!
Th-Think about it!
I'm gonna go see Sanji!
I'm your stepfather, Cracker-kun!
Gum-Gum...
When I beat tons of them,
they quieted down too!
Their army could no longer source weapons
from Doflamingo
Don't push your luck!
You used to be! Not now!
Hey, how can they even move?
so they turned to us for help.
Pretzel...
Mama considers her 43 ex-husbands as
strangers unrelated to us by blood.
Every six months,
the citizens of Totto Land...
...Kong Gun!
...Roll!
Thank you!
They gave up on the idea of
merely suppressing their rivals...
Stepfather Pound!
...must pay one-month worth of their "souls"
I mean, Pound!
What you just did was treason against Mama!
It's a good example of how irresponsible do-gooding
only increases the bloodshed in the end.
How dare you!
But I'm definitely related to my daughters by blood!
to the country in exchange for their safety.
Treason?!
"Soul"?
Screw the reasons.
Yes, in other words, their lifespans.
You're a dead man! No one will save you!
Enough!
We just make whoever pays
us win and that's it.
I just want to give my blessing to my daughters!
So the people lose two months
of their lifespans in a year
If we crush both sides,
we can earn more money!
and one year of their lifespans out of every six.
That's what pirates would do.
Cracker-sama!
What do you mean?
We're still a member nation
of the World Government.
Linlin, I mean Big Mom
ate the Soul-Soul Fruit.
Thunderbolt...
...Tempo!
Speaking of which, Father,
the Reverie will take place soon.
What's that?
She can manipulate people's souls.
Yes.
However, they'll likely strip us of our right
to participate in the Reverie starting from this one.
With that power,
she's claiming part of the citizens' lifespans.
All of you, be prepared for it!
At that moment, they have to choose to stay
in Totto Land or leave.
What?!
The power that we'll get in exchange
is tremendous!
Germa will change!
You did a good job breaking...
Leave or Life?
...my armor!
Things that make Father this happy
rarely happen.
Was that out of sympathy?
Life.
And by spreading the collected souls
all over the country,
I've run in to him dozens of times!
Of course I became attached to him!
I can't believe you came in handy after all.
Who are you?!
all kinds of things come to life
and are anthropomorphized.
Who am I?
Sanji!
We were surprised the day
that you disappeared.
I think I already told you
that I'm Sweet General Cracker.
We call those who came to life the Homies.
Thank you!
Really.
Thank you!!
THOUSAND ARMED CRACKER
We used to talk about you from time to time.
Collecting and scattering the souls...
...are done by incarnations made of
Linlin, I mean Big Mom's own soul.
We wondered about where the funniest
place for you to die would be and how.
It's so powerful! My Climate Baton!
That was my favorite armor...
Armor?
No way! He coughed up blood!
Brulee will come back.
That's the truth of Totto Land.
--That was jam!
--Jam?!
She can show up any place that has a mirror.
In the town of chocolate where we stopped by first,
a variety of things were alive too!
Since I'm a true artisan,
I even make sure that it tastes good too.
You still have food on your plate, Niji.
Eat everything.
Is that why the crocodile talked
and the rabbit acted like a human?!
I'm sorry. You did it to help me!
I ate the Bis-Bis Fruit
and became a biscuit human.
I was targeted to be killed anyway.
That's correct.
Animals can be anthropomorphized too.
This?
I'll just leave it. I don't wanna eat.
There is a sense of menace!
I can generate an infinite amount of biscuits
and manipulate them!
What a power!
Cracker-sama is gonna start a fight here!
What about them?
By my ex-wife.
I ate tons of chocolate earlier
They're different.
Oh, they started on their own!
and this sauce that's poured on it
doesn't look good.
They're merely animals who have been turned into
human forms by Brulee's power.
By the way, are you Lola's friend?
It's gooey and disgusting.
Oh, well!
Homies!
Catch those two and let's be done with this!
This should be thrown away.
To shape them into anything...
Uh-huh.
Eat it!
Oh, by the way, souls can't be infused into
other people and corpses.
Crushed Biscuit!
You don't know how valuable food is
It's not safe here! Let's run!
or how much work goes into
cooking, you stupid prince!
Why didn't you say something?!
You've been watching the whole time!
Hurry up!
Stupid?!
I don't wanna get involved in anything!
We'll take care of them!
You're a weakling Sanji!
And if I craft it carefully...
I see. It's no mistake!
Don't let them get away!
Why are you buried here
if you don't wanna get involved?!
You have no right to insult
me and tell me what to do!
Lola's mother is Big Mom.
There you go! The face of a tough warrior!
Why?! Who are you?!
Call the head chef!
Where are you, Cosette?!
Hey, what's your name?!
The fact that those trees in the forest
are afraid of this Vivre Card is the proof.
Say it! I'll give you the juice!
HEAD CHEF COSETTE
I'm Pound.
Throughout history, biscuits changed
O-Okay! I'll say it so get off of me!
Stop!
their shapes with the times
and on their bakers' whims.
Because you served this disgusting stuff,
my brother has offended me!
I'll make the most of it, Lola!
Did you mention Lola before?
Not that many people have ever found out
what I truly look like.
I did. Hold on.
Yes, sir! I'm sorry!
Um...
I shouldn't serve anything
unpalatable to you...
In fact, the picture on my wanted poster
that's issued by the Government...
Okay.
...is not me. It's my armor.
They're gonna catch up to us!
Stay right there, Cosette.
I hate pain. I hate shots too!
Say it already!
Here it is!
That's why I wear armor or manipulate it
to fight.
Years and years ago, I was Big Mom's...
I mean, the pirate Charlotte Linlin's...
Pretzel Roll!
It multiplies as I clap my hands!
That's how my dreamlike biscuit works.
What's that?
This is my friend Lola's mom's Vivre Card!
So I have a limitless force at my disposal!
Gum-Gum...
Linlin's...
What?!
But I don't know if that's Big Mom or not...
...Jet Stamp Gatling!
The one that you broke with your life
was just one of my Biscuit Warriors...
Linlin's husband!
What are you doing?!
What's wrong, guys?!
...that I can generate endlessly.
What?!
It's no use, Straw Hat!
Your techniques won't work against me!
What, Kingbaum?!
Even you're stopping?!
We can't do it-ju, Brulee!
Do you understand why you'll never see
Vinsmoke Sanji again?
Damn!
You bastard...
How much of an asshole can you be?
We Homies can't fight against her-ju!
Wh-Why is the one of the
Sweet 3 Generals here?!
Get away!
Are you trying
to leave a scar on a woman's face?!
Why not?!
Don't get involved in their fight!
I'll be back.
I feel Mama's strong soul-ju!
CHARLOTTE CRACKER - THE 10TH SON
ONE OF THE SWEET 3 GENERALS, THE MINISTER OF BISCUIT
THE BIG MOM PIRATES
Straw Hat!
What?
Give up, Straw Hat!
I'm going to...
Shut up! I'm gonna go see Sanji!
...put an end...
I'm gonna see Sanji!
...to your lives!
Cracker's extraordinary strength leaves
Luffy completely helpless!
Sanji's father figure in the East Blue and
the man who raised him - Owner Zeff.
The man with a bounty of 860 million berries, Cracker!
The Sweet 3 Generals are the Big
Mom Pirates' greatest warriors!
The Biscuit Warriors keep
multiplying without end!
The back and forth battle between them
and Luffy's Gear Four attacks intensifies!
One of them, Cracker comes to attack!
His phantasmagoric evil arms that multiply one after another
roar and strike out at Luffy!
He gets blown about and crushed but when he hears
his enemy making fun of Sanji, he finally erupts in rage!
The irreplaceable bond between them now
forces Sanji
to make the biggest decision in his life!
When a tremendous wave of his anger turns
the Seducing Woods into hell,
Meanwhile, Sanji meets
his two older brothers!
With the wedding close at hand,
Luffy's deadly blow using Gear Four
and Cracker's hidden power clash!
Facing someone who could be the strongest enemy he's
ever fought, a whole-hearted Luffy throws an all-out punch!
Their outrageous behaviors enflame
Sanji's chivalrous spirit!
the reason
that Sanji left the Straw Hats behind is finally revealed!
a fierce deadly battle
between Cracker and Luffy begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An Enemy Worth 800 million! Luffy vs. Thousand Armed Cracker!"
"An All-out Duel! Gear Four vs. the Bis-Bis Ability!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Benefactor's Life! Sanji and Owner Zeff!"
"A Top Officer! The Sweet 3 General Cracker Appears!"
"The First and the Second
Join! The Vinsmoke Family!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!