I've never seen the end of the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go, Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible? Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani? mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy was wandering in the Seducing Woods,
the forest with no escape, and reunited with Nami.
I see! I'm glad that you found me!
All right!
Let's go save Chopper and Carrot now!
Where are they?
Here.
It all happened right here.
But now, they're all gone.
That's why I'm asking him!
You were watching the whole time!
Where's Chopper? And Carrot?!
That woman, Brulee, and the forest monsters
didn't even touch you!
That means you're one of them!
One of them?
Well, I'm certainly not their enemy.
Years and years ago,
I was Big Mom's... I mean, the pirate Charlotte Linlin's...
Linlin's...
Linlin's husband!
What?!
Meanwhile, a shadow of another enemy
was closing in on Luffy and Nami...
Wh-Why is one of the Sweet 3 Generals here?!
"A Top Officer!
The Sweet 3 General Cracker Appears!"
S-Sir, what brings you here?
Am I not allowed to be here?
No! Of course, you're welcomed!
Flower! Flower!
Big Mom's...
...Ex-husband?!
Uh-huh.
As soon as two daughters were born,
she dumped me.
It's not that they're avoiding attacking me.
They just don't care about me.
What is it?!
Hey... What's coming now?!
Wh-What?!
Who is this?!
Hey!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
What?!
--His body's coming out!
--Get back, Nami!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Don't... Don't... Don't do that!
No!
I thought he was a Giant!
Y-You are...!
Are you crazy? How could you spill information
to our enemy like that, you fool!
W-Wait, Cracker-kun!
I want to see my daughter, Chiffon,
even just for a moment!
I heard she got married!
I want to give her my blessing!
So let me talk to Linlin!
I heard Lola ran away!
They're both my precious daughters!
Lola?
Ran away?
One of my older sisters that I loved very dearly
went out to the sea looking for love.
To seek a match.
Lola who ran away from home?
Who is it?
Cracker-kun, let go of me!
I just want to see Lola and Chiffon...
I just want to see my daughters!
Lola... Don't tell me that Lola is...
Wait a minute!
I'm... I'm actually a guy!
What?!
A-Are you?!
Y-Yes, I am! I like dressing like a girl!
I'm not kidding!
On top of that,
I think you and that animal man
will make a great couple and I wanted to help!
What?! Really?!
No one's ever supported my feelings for him.
You're the first person ever
to say such a nice thing to me.
Raise your head, my friend.
This is what friendship is!
My name is Namizo. You can call me Nami.
Friendship...
Nami!
Thank you for coming to save me!
Of course I came, Namizo...
I'm your friend...
But I lied to you at that time
because I was scared of you.
I'm sorry. I'm actually a woman.
You silly girl... I knew all along.
Lola.
Why did I say that? Who's Namizo?
Come to think of it, it's strange.
For some reason, I feel like I knew you before.
Are you... Lola?!
I am. Did I say my name?
Oh, I can't believe it, Lola!
I'm so happy to see you again!
Lola, you guys went to the New World?
We didn't go there. We're from there.
My mama is a pirate and... Oh...
Here's something for you.
My mama's Vivre Card. You can have it.
Paper?
Wow! You're lucky!
Captain Lola's mother is an amazing pirate!
Don't lose it!
I'm sure it'll come in handy one day!
Everything's coming together now!
In that case, could Lola's mother be...
Big Mom?!
And this man is...
--...Lola's father?!
--What?
Crane!
They came back!
The rabbit and the crane!
It could fly?!
Stop! Randolph!
Was that Haki?! Maybe not!
What was it then?!
They screamed...
...and withered out of fear?!
Crane...
How could you get in my way like that?
When did you become so important?
Randolph!
I'm sorry. That was his idea.
Don't lie! It was yours!
They spoke!
--That was his idea.
--Hey!
We are very sorry.
Is he someone in a high position?
He's certainly strong.
Mama always makes a pre-emptive move.
Since Straw Hat Luffy beat Doflamingo,
she bet Brulee would have a hard time
so she sent me.
I can't let you just say that, Big Bro!
What is it this time?!
Whoa! A tree monster!
Oh, that woman!
If I'm asked to kill them, I'll do it right away!
KINGBAUM - THE MASTER OF THE SEDUCING WOODS
That's right-ju!
We, the Seducing Woods Team,
have never let even a single target
walk away alive-ju!
Oh! Not only Cracker-sama and Brulee-sama
but also Kingbaum-sama is here!
I can't believe that those three are all here at once.
That's great but we have no time to waste now.
By tomorrow noon, all brothers and sisters of the Vinsmokes
will get together and enter the Whole Cake Chateau.
Forming a family connection with the Vinsmokes is
something that Mama has wanted for a long time.
We can share Germa 66's formidable military
and science technology.
I know!
They've turned into animals!
And how can that branch talk?
I'm not a branch!
Look at this, Straw Hat!
Oh, Luffy!
Luffy! Nami! Help!
What?!
Chopper got caught too?!
What happened, you guys?!
How did you get in there?!
She trapped us in the mirror!
She has an ability involving mirrors! Be careful!
You see what I did, Brother Cracker?!
I'm grabbing these fools...
...by the scruff of their neck!
Hey, Chopper! Carrot! Are you okay?!
We're fine!
We're not hurt at all!
It's just the mirror that broke.
We're safe in this dimension!
--So you're okay!
--I don't know what you're talking about but that's good.
Luffy! Listen...
Forget it.
Let's start with this loose-tongued fool.
Wh-What are you gonna do to me?!
Mama told me
what she wants me to do with you.
What? Did she?
What did she say?
She said I can kill you.
What?!
Th-Think about it!
I'm your stepfather, Cracker-kun!
You used to be! Not now!
Mama considers her 43 ex-husbands as
strangers unrelated to us by blood.
How dare you!
But I'm definitely related to my daughters by blood!
Enough!
I just want to give my blessing to my daughters!
Was that out of sympathy?
I've run in to him dozens of times!
Of course I became attached to him!
Thank you!
Thank you!!
There is a sense of menace!
Cracker-sama is gonna start a fight here!
Oh, they started on their own!
Oh, well!
Homies!
Catch those two and let's be done with this!
It's not safe here! Let's run!
Hurry up!
We'll take care of them!
Don't let them get away!
Hey, what's your name?!
I'm Pound.
Did you mention Lola before?
I did. Hold on.
Um...
They're gonna catch up to us!
Here it is!
What's that?
This is my friend Lola's mom's Vivre Card!
What?!
But I don't know if that's Big Mom or not...
What are you doing?!
What's wrong, guys?!
What, Kingbaum?!
Even you're stopping?!
We can't do it-ju, Brulee!
We Homies can't fight against her-ju!
Why not?!
I feel Mama's strong soul-ju!
What?
The man with a bounty of 860 million berries, Cracker!
His phantasmagoric evil arms that multiply one after another
roar and strike out at Luffy!
Facing someone who could be the strongest enemy he's
ever fought, a whole-hearted Luffy throws an all-out punch!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An Enemy Worth 800 million! Luffy vs. Thousand Armed Cracker!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!