I've never seen the end of the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Take the helm, now, win a victory
kajitore saa kachitore
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
It makes me long to see someone
dareka ni aitakunarun da
There are tons of unimaginable truth
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
Don't turn a blind eye
miteminufuri suruna yo
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
I've never seen the end of the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante kono me de mita wake janai
That's why we've got to go, Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
Who says it's impossible? Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani? mada nani mo hajimatte nai
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
kono shunkan
We can! I can!
This great feeling
kono kaikan
Now, now, yes, we can!
ima ima, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
The Seducing Woods is the forest with no escape.
As Luffy and Nami discovered that
Pound was Big Mom's husband,
Cracker, one of the Sweet 3 Generals,
showed up.
Cracker-kun, let go of me!
I just want to see Lola and Chiffon...
I just want to see my daughters!
Wh-What are you gonna do to me?!
Mama told me
what she wants me to do with you.
What? Did she?
She said I can kill you.
What?!
Th-Think about it!
I'm your stepfather, Cracker-kun!
You used to be! Not now!
Mama considers her 43 ex-husbands as
strangers unrelated to us by blood.
How dare you!
But I'm definitely related to my daughters by blood!
Enough!
I just want to give my blessing to my daughters!
Cracker was about to give Pound a death blow
since he revealed Big Mom's secret to Luffy and Nami.
Was that out of sympathy?
I've run in to him dozens of times!
Of course I became attached to him!
"An Enemy Worth 800 million!
Luffy vs. Thousand Armed Cracker!"
Evacuate! We'll get hurt too!
Run!
Gear Two!
Gum-Gum...
...Red Hawk!
I'm not done!
Straw Hat!
What?! What the...
What?! He's got another arm!
How is that possible?!
Here I go!
What?! He's got another one!
Stop this useless resistance, Straw Hat!
Is this really Big Mom's Vivre Card?!
Luffy! No!
You okay?!
C-Cracker-kun!
He has extra arms!
Damn!
That bastard!
I'm the Biscuit Knight - Cracker,
one of the Sweet 3 Generals.
Also known as...
...Thousand Armed Cracker.
If I tap once, it becomes two.
If I tap it again,
it becomes three.
What?!
They'll keep multiplying.
His legs have multiplied too.
Don't even dream of beating me.
THOUSAND ARMED CRACKER - ONE OF THE SWEET 3 GENERALS
EMPEROR BIG MOM PIRATES
BOUNTY: 860 MILLION BERRIES
I won't let you screw up Mama's tea party!
You've got extra limbs. So what?!
Gear Two!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
...Bullet!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Whip!
Luffy! No! Don't get into an all-out fight!
That's not our objective!
We gotta get out of here
and get Sanji-kun back!
I only know how to fight...
...all-out!
Humph! What an insolent brat!
Look at this sword! Isn't it something?
It's called Pretzel!
It's a one and only sword in the world!
I'll teach you a lesson
about the roughness of the New World!
What?! A one and only sword?!
But you've got six!
H-Hey!
Let's run for now, Luffy!
No way!
Gear Three!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
You fools have got nowhere to run!
Damn!
Pretzel Roll!
That's my brother!
Luffy...
Oh, no!
They are members of the Emperor's clan!
We should've been more careful!
Even Luffy's having a hard time
with her subordinate!
Luffy! Run!
Wh-What the...
Stop there! I'll fight you two!
Me too-ju!
I know how you feel.
You got scared suddenly, right?
The Worst Generation?
What's so "worst" about it?!
After being puffed up
in the first half of the Grand Line,
lots of underlings came here saying "Our captain
will become the Pirate King" - only to be disappointed.
I've seen tons of those cases!
Even in the last two years, a number of those pirates
came wandering in Mama's territory.
"Captain" Kid.
"Roar of the Sea" Apoo.
"Gang" Bege.
"Mad Monk" Urouge.
Except for Bege who found his bearings instantly
and became our ally,
everyone got driven away
without even seeing Mama or hearing her voice!
The only one who held on was...
..."Mad Monk" Urouge!
He was impudent enough to defeat
one of the Sweet Generals!
They were the Sweet 4 Generals
until not so long ago.
That's it!
I guess I can't see an Emperor's face that easily.
You've roughed me up so much.
Retribution!
What?!
Is that all you've got, "Mad Monk" Urouge?
Pretzel Roll!
But that was it.
He made Mama mad
and got beaten badly by Brother Cracker!
He has nowhere to run!
I bet he's dead in a ditch somewhere by now!
She disappeared!
Listen!
You've reached a dead end in the New World!
Fighting an Emperor?
That's just a dream!
You can't even see Mama!
Sneaking into the tea party?
Messing up the wedding?!
And taking your friend back?!
That's not gonna happen!
You guys will die in this forest
without even seeing Mama!
M-My baton...
Now, come to the Mirro-world!
Let go of me!
Come on! Come on! Come to me!
I'll cut up your face and body slowly
in the other dimension!
No!
Let go of me!
Get your hands off of me!
Don't!
Pound-chan!
Just give up!
Let go of her, Brulee!
Thank you!
Stepfather Pound!
I mean, Pound!
What you just did was treason against Mama!
Treason?!
You're a dead man! No one will save you!
Thunderbolt...
...Tempo!
It's so powerful! My Climate Baton!
Brulee will come back.
She can show up any place that has a mirror.
I'm sorry. You did it to help me!
I was targeted to be killed anyway.
By my ex-wife.
By the way, are you Lola's friend?
Uh-huh.
I see. It's no mistake!
Lola's mother is Big Mom.
The fact that those trees in the forest
are afraid of this Vivre Card is the proof.
I'll make the most of it, Lola!
Pretzel Roll!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Stamp Gatling!
It's no use, Straw Hat!
Your techniques won't work against me!
Damn!
Get away!
Don't get involved in their fight!
Give up, Straw Hat!
Shut up! I'm gonna go see Sanji!
Cracker's extraordinary strength leaves
Luffy completely helpless!
He gets blown about and crushed but when he hears
his enemy making fun of Sanji, he finally erupts in rage!
Luffy's deadly blow using Gear Four
and Cracker's hidden power clash!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An All-out Duel! Gear Four vs. the Bis-Bis Ability!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!