Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
We found an island!
An island?!
Oh! An island! We found an island!
Hey, Nami! Good for you!
There's an island! You can get better!
There's an island! An island! Island!
--Island! Island!
--Just go look.
An island!
All this snow! I'm so happy!
That's far enough, pirates!
Hey. I found people.
But... they don't seem too friendly...
Attention, pirates! Leave this
place at once! This instant!
We came to find a doctor!
We have a sick person onboard!
We won't fall for that trick,
you filthy pirates!
They really hate our guts.
And we've just met, too...
Don't talk back!
They're shooting!
You didn't just do that!
--Bastard!
--Stop, Sanji-san!
"An Island Without Doctors?
Adventure in a Nameless Land!"
Vivi!
Why, you--!
Aim!
No! Stop!
Fighting won't help anything!
I'm fine! It only grazed my arm!
In that case, we won't land here!
But could we ask for a doctor?
Our friend is suffering from a grave illness.
Please help! I beg you!
Vivi!
You're not fit to be captain, Luffy.
Not everything can be fixed
by acting recklessly!
If you start a fight here,
what will happen to Nami-san?
Yeah. I'm sorry! I was wrong!
Please call a doctor!
Please help our friend!
I will show you to the village.
Follow me.
See? They understood!
Yeah! You're amazing!
I must warn you, the only doctor
we have here is a witch.
Witch?
You gotta be kidding me.
Nothing here makes sense...
What is this place, anyway?
This land still does not have a name.
A nameless land?
Does that really happen?
A bear!
Everyone! Pretend to be dead!
A Hiking Bear. They pose no danger.
Don't forget to bow.
It's proper hiking manners.
Okay! All better now!
See!
Now I can finally do
some real training!
I was getting sick of
that watered-down training,
and just watching the ship
is boring as hell.
Maybe I'll go for some cold-weather
swimming to suppress my self.
This is our village, Big Horn.
There are weird animals
walking everywhere...
That's snow country for ya!
Nami-san! We made it to a village
with people! It's a village!
Okay. Thanks for the help, everyone.
Those who aren't guards
can return to their work.
But, will you be alright by yourself,
Dalton-san? They're pirates!
I believe they pose no threat.
That's my hunch of many years
of experience. You can trust it.
What do we do?
If that's what Dalton-san says, then...
--And they don't seem dangerous...
--Yeah...
Alright, Dalton-san!
We leave the rest to you!
Be ever careful, Dalton-san...
Just call us again if anything happens!
They weren't this land's security forces?
They're ordinary citizens.
Come to my home for now.
Hey! Look, Luffy! A Hiking Bear!
Again?!
--Oh, Dalton-san!
--Gotta bow.
I heard there were pirates!
Are you okay?
Yes, everything is okay.
There's nothing to worry about.
Oh, Dalton-kun! I look forward
to the election in two days!
Everyone says they're
going to vote for you!
Y-you can't be serious!
I'm nothing but a sinful man!
Use that bed there.
I'll warm the place up.
I haven't told you my name yet.
I'm Dalton, captain of the
security squad of this island.
Please forgive our heavy-handed welcome.
May I ask you a question?
Eh?
I somehow feel like I've seen you before.
I-it's probably just your imagination!
Anyway, please tell us about this witch!
Nami-san's temperature was 42° C
when I checked it just now!
42°?!
Her fever's gone up for
three days in a row.
She'll die if it goes up any more!
Yes.
But we don't even know the cause of
her illness, or how to treat it...
We need a doctor! Anyone will do!
Where is this witch of yours?!
The witch, huh. Do you see those
mountains outside the window?
Yeah, those insanely tall--
Hyper Snowman!
Snowzilla, the snow beast!
Yeah!
Don't make me kick your asses!
Those mountains are known
as the Drum Rockies.
Do you see the castle at the top
of the tallest one in the middle?
Castle?!
--That castle no longer has its king.
--That warms me up...
Yeah, there it is.
What's so important about the castle?
The only doctor in the land,
Dr. Kureha, lives there.
People call her a witch.
What?! Of all the places,
why does it have to be so far away?!
Then call her here right away!
We have a critical patient!
Even if we wanted to,
there's no way to contact her.
Huh?! And she calls herself a doctor?!
What the hell is she like?!
As a doctor, she's very skilled.
But she's an eccentric old hag.
She's nearly 140 years old now.
Eh?!
140?! I think she might need help!
And, let's see...
She likes pickled plums.
What happens when people
here get sick or injured?
She comes down from the
mountain when she feels like it.
She looks for patients,
treats them, then, as payment,
she takes whatever she wants
from their houses before leaving.
Sounds like an unfriendly old hag!
Hey! She almost sounds like a pirate!
But how does such an old
woman go down that mountain?
It's an odd rumor...
but several people claim to have seen her
riding a sleigh through
the sky on moonlit nights...
And that's the reason
she's called a witch...
Some also saw her with a strange
creature they'd never seen before...
I knew it! See? It's a Snow Man!
It's a snowy mountain, after all!
I knew there'd be one!
A witch and a Snow Man?!
Oh, please never let us run into them!
She is the only doctor, but she's
a hag I'd prefer to stay away from.
All we can do is wait for the next
time she comes down the mountain.
You can't be serious...
Dammit! We can't wait for that!
Even as we speak, Nami-san is--!
Hey! Nami! Nami! Can you hear me?
What are you doing?!
Oh! She's awake!
Hey, the only way to see a
doctor is to climb a mountain.
We're gonna climb it!
Eh?
Don't be crazy!
What are you doing with Nami?!
It's okay! I'll carry her on my back!
That'll only make things even worse!
What's the problem?
We need to hurry, don't we?
That's true, but you can't!
Look at how steep and tall it is!
I can make it.
Maybe you can make it,
but it'd be too hard on Nami-san!
But, look! If we fall,
we'll land in snow!
Even a healthy person would die
instantly after a fall from there!
Seriously! She's 6° C
over normal temperature!
Do you even get it?!
I need to get over this fast...
I need to hurry... for Vivi...
I'm counting on you, Captain!
That's more like it!
Just leave it to me!
I can't believe it!
Like captain, like navigator!
Do you know what condition
you're in, Nami-san?!
Are you sure you'll be okay?
It'll take hours to get there!
Old guy! Meat! Gimme meat!
Meat?
Alright! I'm comin' too!
Listen, Luffy! Don't fall even once,
or you can expect Nami to die!
Eh?! Even once?!
Wait! Hold still!
I need to tie this right!
All set.
Okay, I'm going to wait here.
I'd only get in the way.
Same here!
Got it!
Okay, Nami! Hold on tight!
Yeah...
If you're really set on going...
I won't stop you.
But at least climb up from the other side.
There are Lapins on this course.
Fierce, carnivorous rabbits.
If you encounter a pack of them,
you're as good as dead.
Rabbits? But we're in a hurry.
We should be fine. Right?
Yeah! I'll kick 'em!
Kick?! You can't be serious!
You'd be walking to your deaths!
It's okay!
Alright, then! Let's go, Sanji!
Before Nami dies!
What?! Don't say things that
could jinx us, you dumbass!
Will they really be all right?
Well, I'm not worried about those two...
But the question is if Nami-san's
strength will last long enough...
I hope they make it there safely...
What's wrong?
Come inside. It's cold out.
Oh, that's okay.
I want to stay outside.
Me, too...
I see.
Then I will join you.
We did have some, long ago...
Eh?
Doctors. But they're all gone now,
for certain reasons.
They were all incredibly skilled...
We were even known as
an advanced medical nation.
So what happened?
This country was destroyed
just a few months ago.
At the hands of pirates!
--Eh?!
--The entire country?!
So that's why you were so nervous about us?
Yes. The word "pirate" is still
too much for everyone to handle...
I'm sorry about that.
But there were only five
people in that pirate group.
The captain called himself "Blackbeard,"
and he destroyed our country
in the blink of an eye
with his devastating power...
Only five pirates?!
You can't be serious!
Blackbeard?!
But there are some who say it was
actually good for the country.
There's nothing good about
a country being destroyed!
Yeah! That's the stupidest
thing I've ever heard!
Thank you.
But people say that because the
monarchy that existed here until then
was appalling in the eyes of the citizens.
The country's former name
was the Drum Kingdom!
The king's name was Wapol!
He was the worst king possible!
Yes! That man! I remember him!
Wapol?!
It's gotten a little colder.
The wind's picking up.
So why aren't you wearing shoes?!
Just seeing that is painful!
This is my police!
Police?! You mean "policy"!
Yeah!
Anyway, did you know?
People in snowy countries never sleep!
Huh? Why's that?
'Cause they'll die if they go to sleep!
Don't be stupid!
There's nobody like that!
It's the truth!
Someone told me a long time ago!
Usopp, I bet.
No! I heard it in a pub in my village!
Then why did that Dalton guy have a bed?
That's a good point.
Maybe it's for when he dies, then?
Yeah, right!
Okay, did you know this?
Women in snowy lands
all have silky-smooth skin!
How come?
Isn't it obvious?
Whenever you're cold,
you rub your skin for warmth.
So you get smooth skin.
So women in snowy places have
such silky-smooth, white skin!
How come it's white?
Because the color of the
constantly-falling snow dyes their skin!
Huh?! You're so dumb!
Like you're really anyone to talk!
And...
...quit being so damn annoying!
What was with that guy?
Hang in there, Nami-san!
We're gonna get you to a doctor!
The snow's really deep around here...
Hey, Luffy!
Run more smoothly!
You're gonna make Nami-san worse!
W-what are these?
They're white and big,
so they're polar bears! I'm sure of it!
Wait! You know Wapol?!
We don't just know him!
He's the pirate who attacked our ship!
I got rid of him, though.
But I do recall him saying
something about the Drum Kingdom...
Yes.
There's no question about it!
I remember clearly now!
I met him once at a monarch
meeting my father took me to
when I was very young!
Monarch meeting?!
Just who are you?
No, uhh, you see...
In any case, we met Wapol!
Yesterday, on our way here!
Yesterday?! Are you sure?!
But what's going on, then?!
He called himself a pirate, not a king!
He must be calling himself
that as camouflage.
Wapol is merely wandering the sea,
trying to return to this island.
So the people on that ship were
kicked out because they were no match
for the Blackbeard Pirates
when they attacked this country?
No match? It's not like that!
Eh?
When it happened, Wapol's army
didn't even try to fight!
In fact, the moment he learned
how strong the pirates were,
Wapol abandoned the country and was
the very first to flee out to sea!
That threw the entire nation into despair.
Is this what the king--
Is that what the king of
an entire country does?!
That's appalling!
A king abandoning his people!
Vivi...
You're exactly right.
But at least Wapol's
tyranny is finally over.
The remaining people on this
island have come together
to try to create a new country.
So what we most fear right
now is Wapol's return...
The return of his monarchy.
We must avoid that at all costs,
while people are still feeling unsure!
If we're to create a new,
peaceful nation on this island!
It jumped!
You gotta be kidding me!
How can it move like that?!
--What is it, a gorilla?!
--No! A polar bear!
It's a bunny!
You're the one who just
called it a gorilla...
These must be the Lapins that
Dalton was talking about!
This many of them?!
Oh!
Oh! Wapol-sama!
What is it, Chess?
Did you find Straw Hat's ship?!
No, Wapol-sama!
We've finally returned home!
What?!
How many months have passed
as we've wandered the sea?
It's our homeland! The Drum Kingdom!
Truly?!
The world is awfully big
so even if there is treasure somewhere,
the odds are astronomical
So relying on dumb luck
won't get you anywhere
So even,
if someone stops me or
laughs at me from the shadows
the ship will continue forward
Bon voyage!
Forget about them!
I know I'm a fool,
but I gotta go
The crazier the dream,
the cooler the ambition
I know I'm a fool,
but I'm gonna fight
The farther the sea,
the more heavenly it surely is
Do everything you can,
and you'll get a little nearer to any horizon
Listen, Luffy!
Don't you dare fight these guys!
Why not?
Nami-san will feel
the whole impact and die!
Okay! I won't fight!
But, what do I do?!
Just dodge! Dodge and run!
But don't retreat!
That's hard!
What?! The witch is
in the next town over?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Are You Happy?
The Doctor Called Witch!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!