I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
In search of the one-piece treasure
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
that it's just a fantasy
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
A rush of excitement is our only compass
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
Just keep pretending you know everything
shittakaburi shitero yo
Textbooks are just guidebooks
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into
a marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole
Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Chopper and Carrot have been
trapped in a world of mirrors.
Brook and Pedro have snuck into Sweet City.
As everyone acts separately,
nearby in the Seducing Woods,
the fierce duel between Luffy and
Sweet General Cracker enters a new phase.
It multiplies as I clap my hands!
That's how my dreamlike biscuit works.
So I have a limitless force at my disposal!
The one that you broke with your life
was just one of my Biscuit Warriors...
...that I can generate endlessly.
Do you understand why you'll never see
Vinsmoke Sanji again?
I'll be back.
I'm gonna see Sanji!
"The First and the Second Join!
The Vinsmoke Family!"
Learning that there are people you can't beat
no matter how hard you try...
...is the mark of true progress, brat!
I'll teach you a lesson!
What's wrong?
You've got no energy left to break them?
Gum-Gum...
...Rhino Schneider!
...Leo Bazooka!
Damn!
Gum-Gum...
...Culverin!
Interesting techniques.
He's so persistent.
He destroyed all of them.
--We can't do it!
--We have no chance!
Run!
No matter how many of them you beat,
it doesn't make any difference.
I guess we'll be safe here.
We're no match for him!
Oh? Hey, look!
That girl is gone!
I'm here.
When did she get there?!
If you close your mouth,
you'll be sealing your doom.
I told you to take Cracker down!
It's really impossible!
Cracker-sama and Straw Hat are
so intimidating we can't go near!
So what?
No matter how many of you get withered,
my heart won't ache in the slightest!
What?!
You're a horrible person.
Sweet General Cracker
and his mother Emperor Big Mom.
Which of them scares you more?
You're scarier than both!
BRULEE'S MIRRO-WORLD
What is this?
The inside of someone's house?
I think so.
What about this one?
I don't see anything.
Is it a bathroom somewhere?
Maybe...
I see! I get the picture!
Listen, Carrot!
I have a great idea
so please call me Big Bro Chopper from now on!
Uh-huh, okay.
Good!
And what is your idea, Chobro?!
Chobro?!
That's right!
Short for Big Bro Chopper, Chobro!
Well, okay.
It seems like this world of mirrors
is connected to all the mirrors
across the Whole Cake Island!
Yes, I think so.
Instead of escaping from here,
we should take advantage of Brulee's ability!
How?
We can look for Sanji through these mirrors!
You're right! That's my Chobro!
Your compliment doesn't make me happy,
you fool!
Alright, let's go!
Okay, Chobro!
SWEET CITY, CAPITAL OF THE WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Secret Song Whirlwind Slash.
--That went well.
--Mm-hm.
After patrol, the Biscuit Warriors
will be put away in the chateau.
Let's make a move then.
Good work.
You wanna destroy more, don't you?
Keep going.
Here are more!
It's fun to have someone
who breaks them like you!
It's makes it worth making them.
But however much you fight,
you have no chance to win.
I'll beat you up and go see Sanji!
Gum-Gum...
...Kong...
...Organ Gun!
Advance!
Honey Pretzel!
It's morning, it's morning
Good morning!
Today, we'll have the Vinsmokes
over to get acquainted,
Good morning
THE WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
and we'll have an engagement ceremony, Mama.
What about the wedding cake?
That comes tomorrow.
One night has passed.
How are those mold fungi holding up?
This is their last chance
to meet their friend.
Oh, please! How could you say that
after you sent Cracker-sama?
It's true that once Black-Foot enters the castle,
they'll have no chance to see him!
Both the tea party and the wedding
will be held in the castle.
Are they more bark than
bite like all the others?
Some of Vinsmoke's sons
aren't here yet, right?
THE GERMA KINGDOM
Well, I've just had a call
saying that they've arrived.
Good. They're here.
My dearest sons!
I can't wait to see them facing Sanji.
Welcome back!
VINSMOKE ICHIJI - SPARKING RED
ELDEST SON OF THE VINSMOKE FAMILY
VINSMOKE NIJI - ELECTRIC BLUE
SECOND SON OF THE VINSMOKE FAMILY
--Ichiji-sama! Niji-sama!
--Nice to see you back from your long trip!
I couldn't believe that you ended that
interminable war on Brock Collie!
Why isn't he coming out to greet us?
Stop, Niji.
Father, we are back.
Thank you for your work, Ichiji, Niji.
Where is he?
He's here.
Sanji! Wow!
You're really alive!
Congratulations on your engagement, Sanji.
Hey, say something.
You get to wear such nice
things on your wrists!
That's our father! He knows everything!
These things fit you the best.
Lessons like these.
Ichiji, Niji, relax from your journey.
First, eat something.
The battlefront Brock Collie is another victim of
the fall of the Doflamingo regime, you could say.
Their army could no longer source weapons
from Doflamingo
so they turned to us for help.
They gave up on the idea of
merely suppressing their rivals...
It's a good example of how irresponsible do-gooding
only increases the bloodshed in the end.
Screw the reasons.
We just make whoever pays
us win and that's it.
If we crush both sides,
we can earn more money!
That's what pirates would do.
We're still a member nation
of the World Government.
Speaking of which, Father,
the Reverie will take place soon.
Yes.
However, they'll likely strip us of our right
to participate in the Reverie starting from this one.
All of you, be prepared for it!
The power that we'll get in exchange
is tremendous!
Germa will change!
Things that make Father this happy
rarely happen.
I can't believe you came in handy after all.
Sanji!
We were surprised the day
that you disappeared.
Really.
We used to talk about you from time to time.
We wondered about where the funniest
place for you to die would be and how.
You still have food on your plate, Niji.
Eat everything.
This?
I'll just leave it. I don't wanna eat.
I ate tons of chocolate earlier
and this sauce that's poured on it
doesn't look good.
It's gooey and disgusting.
This should be thrown away.
Eat it!
You don't know how valuable food is
or how much work goes into
cooking, you stupid prince!
Stupid?!
You're a weakling Sanji!
You have no right to insult
me and tell me what to do!
Call the head chef!
Where are you, Cosette?!
HEAD CHEF COSETTE
Because you served this disgusting stuff,
my brother has offended me!
Yes, sir! I'm sorry!
I shouldn't serve anything
unpalatable to you...
Okay.
Stay right there, Cosette.
You bastard...
How much of an asshole can you be?
Are you trying
to leave a scar on a woman's face?!
Sanji's father figure in the East Blue and
the man who raised him - Owner Zeff.
The irreplaceable bond between them now
forces Sanji
to make the biggest decision in his life!
With the wedding close at hand,
the reason
that Sanji left the Straw Hats behind is finally revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Benefactor's Life! Sanji and Owner Zeff!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!