kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
The goal is the last island - Raftel
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
Luffy and the others infiltrated
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
the Whole Cake Island
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
Nami fought Sweet General Cracker
to protect the exhausted Luffy,
In the Seducing Woods,
Luffy and Nami have been
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
fighting a deadly battle
against Sweet General Cracker.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
but got cornered by Cracker's fierce attack.
Meanwhile, Sanji recalls
his painful past at home,
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
However, that's when...
the Germa Kingdom, which has been
concealed deep in his heart.
Don't touch...
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
You are... a failure.
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
...my friend!
Monkey D. Luffy!
Meanwhile, Sanji was beaten by
Ichiji and the rest of his brothers
Zoro!
Nami!
and was branded a failure.
Usopp!
Sanji!
Wait! I don't wanna stay here!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Let me out!
Brook!
"A Battle of Limits!
Luffy and the Infinite Biscuits!"
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
"To the East Blue!
Sanji's Resolute Departure!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
What a pain! Bring it on all at once!
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy and the others infiltrated the
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole
Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Whole Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy is fighting a fierce battle against
Cracker who revealed
Sanji found out that the Germa Kingdom
Sanji was having a meal with
his father and the others
was manufacturing Clone Soldiers underground.
at the castle in the Germa
Kingdom, his home country,
himself in the Seducing Woods.
Sanji-sama!
Stop it! That's enough!
but he got into an argument
with his arrogant brothers.
Oh, no. Is he conscious?
However, he was forced to back down
because his foster parent Zeff was taken hostage.
This makes me sick!
Meanwhile, Sanji faced his
older brothers Ichiji and Niji
for the first time in
years at Germa's castle.
Then, he turned his fury on Niji
who beat Cosette.
Well, only in the worst-case scenario
where you become uncontrollable,
Get out of my way.
Oh, Reiju-sama, we'll treat him right away.
Niji!
I'll use it as a threat like
"We'll chop this guy's head off."
Meanwhile, in the middle of the battle against
Sweet General Cracker,
I said "Get out of my way"!
You bastard...
How much of an asshole can you be?
I'm sorry!
Luffy found himself in trouble
after time ran out for Gear Four.
They're developing very fast!
Your children are real superhumans!
Let's have a peaceful wedding tomorrow.
Are you trying
to leave a scar on a woman's face?!
Meanwhile, Luffy was fighting a
Boy...
fierce battle against Sweet General
Cracker in the Seducing Woods.
Are you going to see your fiance
with that face?
"The Benefactor's Life!
Sanji and Owner Zeff!"
Easy win!
Cracker-sama,
I didn't wanna do such a thing-ju!
Kids!
What the?!
If you'd given up on the owner of the restaurant
that you were working at,
Well done!
She ordered me and I had no choice...
you could've avoided this.
Gum-Gum...
Good job, Kingbaum!
--Father!
--Father-sama!
Oh, no!
...Kong Gun!
Why did you come back?
But as time ran out for Gear Four Bounce-man,
he collapsed in the woods.
Kingbaum and the Homies led by Nami
saved him.
I thought this was the place
that you didn't even want to remember.
I'm proud of you all!
But they are now besieged by
Cracker's group again.
Sanji.
There is a good reason for it...
My dearest children!
I gotta go see Sanji!
THE SEDUCING WOODS
Damn! I see no end!
No excuse.
That's right. There is no end.
"An Angry Sanji!
The Secret of Germa 66!"
I'm gonna kill you all!
SIXTH MONTHS INTO SANJI'S IMPRISONMENT
My biscuits are endless!
I'll destroy them faster
than you can make them!
You damn brat.
Finding out which of us is faster?
Sounds like fun!
But I guess you didn't pick a fight
with Mama for nothing.
Where do they take that luxurious food
every mealtime?
"The Past that He Let Go of!
Vinsmoke Sanji!"
Gum-Gum...
...Double Culverin!
I don't know. We don't have any guests.
Luffy...
Don't be nosy! It's King-sama's order!
We'll just cook it as we're told!
Don't underestimate my ability!
Nami!
Get in there!
Cracker-sama,
I didn't wanna do such a thing-ju!
Yeah, okay!
She ordered me and I had no choice...
Good job, Kingbaum!
Dammit...
Nami!
Kingbaum!
Damn. This is no good!
I don't have time!
Luffy! Are you okay?
I'm hungry...
I can't-ju! I can't-ju!
Go, Biscuit Warriors!
You're gonna tell me to fight Cracker-sama,
aren't you?!
Damn you! Don't think you can survive
after challenging Cracker-sama!
Are you giving up?
Or are you running out of energy?
I'm gonna fight him!
Oh? How could you say that?
What?!
I want you guys to protect Luffy
with all your might!
I'm gonna destroy them all at once!
You really think you're in
a position to mouth off?
Y-You're gonna fight him?!
Cracker-sama is unusually strong-ju!
Stop it-ju! Damn...
Straw Hat... I'm gonna take my time to torture you
and then kill you.
Sanji!
A girl like you is no match for him-ju!
Royalty mustn't serve anyone!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
Nami...
Bounce-man's time is up.
Whatever!
You just make sure to protect Luffy!
You too, traitor, and your friends!
Your mother is dead!
What?
I can't use Haki for 10 minutes...
Stop following the legacy of the deceased!
Na... mi...
Here we go!
I'm gonna distract them so you just run!
Okay?
I need to rest.
Gum-Gum...
Okay. Let me take care of you.
Defense!
O-Okay-ju.
Alright, guys!
Carry Luffy into Kingbaum's mouth!
...King Kong Gun!
Chopper was right.
Ouch!
We underestimated the Emperor's clan!
What?!
Oh, boy!
--Ow, ow, ow!
--Are you alright, Sanji-sama?!
You tell them to do it, too!
I thought you were the master of this forest!
Is it...
But now, I've just got to do it!
Y-You...
King-sama told us not to
allow you into the kitchen.
What?
What the?!
Whoa-whoa... Are you gonna fight me?
Please!
Let me... stay!
I've got no choice-ju!
Homies, do as she says!
Even though I'm a lovely girl,
if you take me lightly, you'll get hurt!
Oh, no!
What?!
It's hard!
Let's just buy time!
You can't eat my biscuits!
Is he deflating?
Straw Hat can't fight anymore.
I'll kill you first.
Be careful with him!
They're quite hard
so that they can block your attack!
It's done!
They're not common biscuits!
Do it!
You saved me, Nami...
Gust Sword!
Get some rest.
Oh yeah! They're biscuits!
He's coming!
Now! Run!
Damn...
Weather Egg!
Let's go-ju!
I've already reached the limit.
--Where are you going by yourself?
--To see my mother.
Let's run! Now!
The medical ward is at the far end
and the weather is...
This is so humiliating-ju!
--I can make it.
--But...
Weather Egg!
Stop following me.
Rain Spark!
Thunderbreed Tempo!
Don't tell my father.
That way, huh?
You guys should fight me!
I need 10 minutes.
Get in your houses!
I gotta hide somewhere.
Biscuit Warriors, kill him!
It didn't work!
What an interesting skill.
But it just burned the biscuits a little
giving off a nice aroma...
Don't get caught, guys!
Dammit!
What did you say? A woman?
Its sword crumbled?!
Why are you defending a mere cooking wench?!
Luffy!
They're no longer the warriors that they were!
What?! This is not your food!
BRULEE'S MIRRO-WORLD
They got softened by the rain!
So gentlemanly.
You can move quite quickly.
The food fell on the floor.
Gum-Gum...
That little brat...
This is called Aligot.
It's made from cheese blended into potatoes.
S-Stop!
...Gatling!
I'll make her pay!
Your back is wide open!
Sanji-sama, I'll clean it!
Once my wound is healed, I'll cut her up!
Potatoes increase your immunity
and stabilize your blood pressure.
Before that, let's take care of
the raccoon and the rabbit first.
They sure are softened!
When did you...?!
Is the son of Germa that
important to you guys?
They're very nutritious.
S-Sanji-sama!
It's not over!
And maybe because you guys are so special,
Are you here by yourself?!
Oh, I don't understand.
the cut of meat in the confit
has been carefully selected too.
If you go against Mama,
you'll definitely be killed.
It's a very elaborate dish to make
for breakfast.
Oh, there he is, Chobro!
Is he worth saving at the price of your life?
What? Really?!
I appreciate what you did...
Isn't that Sanji?
But we can't
let Queen-sama have stomach trouble...
Oh, please don't, Sanji-sama!
Which one?
A person of royal blood mustn't
eat food off the floor!
I think you'll never understand.
Hey, are you out of your mind?!
That's disgusting!
It definitely is Sanji!
But maybe it tastes good...
Hey, Sanji!
Sanji-kun is...
It's perfectly flavored too.
Sanji!
The spirit of the poor has taken root in you!
What?!
...a perverted ladies' man
and annoys me sometimes.
No, that's not Sanji!
Stop doing such a disgraceful thing!
Yummy! Nice and crunchy!
Run! If they find us, we're in trouble!
But in order to save his friends,
Don't, Niji! The wedding is coming up!
Yes!
He ate Cracker-sama's Biscuit Warriors-ju!
he'll risk his life!
If he's in trouble,
What?!
How could you eat them?!
it's our turn to save him
at the risk of our lives!
Biscuits are food!
Damn...
That's right, Luffy!
Once you eat them, they can't turn back!
Where is Sanji?
That's only natural!
We have to find him
before it's too late...
Thank you, sir.
Eat as much as you can!
Sanji!
Is it? I see...
There's a lot I can learn from you!
You only bring shame to the Vinsmokes.
Did you come to see me in this rain?
What a crafty woman-ju!
What's shameful to me is
being part of the family!
Your father will be mad if he finds out.
--Uh-huh.
--Your Majesty.
Bring it on already!
What?!
An idiot who has no respect for food.
A man who beats a woman.
You're a coward sending your puppets to fight
and watching from safety!
This is from Sanji-sama.
CHOBRO, SOMETHING BIZARRE CAME!!
Are you trying to provoke me to fight?
The arrogance of royalty that compels you
to see your servants as less than human!
Did you make this for me?
All right. I'll fight you.
Mm... Mm-hm.
Everything about you guys goes against
what I stand for!
I hate pain but I don't
think you can hurt me!
Epony!
Y-Yes, Your Majesty!
Storm Cloud Rod!
Mama's in a good mood-nasu.
Don't be presumptuous!
Bring what Sanji really made for me!
No wonder.
What you're saying is the kind of
nonsense all those losers spout, Sanji.
How dare he...
Tomorrow is the tea party and today,
the whole Vinsmoke Family will come visit.
Well, yes.
What's with that kid?!
But it was damaged on his way here
so I threw it into a trash can.
I couldn't understand what you were saying
since we were young.
You're right-nasu.
--Bring it to me!
--Yes, ma'am!
Take this! Take this!
I hope Pudding-sama will be happy-nasu.
There! There! There!
Yeah, I'm jealous of the groom!
Royalty has its own reckoning of the world!
Wow, nice!
Sanji-sama is probably getting ready
at the Germa Kingdom's castle by now.
Omelet rolls and fish and a banana?
You're the unreasonable one!
I'm gonna torment you thoroughly
and take my time killing you.
I bet so-nasu.
Sorry, Mom! I messed it up!
He's right.
You're more wrong than ever.
--Hear that?
--Uh-huh.
I tripped over and dropped it on my way here.
--Sanji's in Germa's castle now!
--Uh-huh!
So enjoy the terror.
It's been crushed and it
got wet in the rain...
Is it because of the bad
influence from this man, Sanji?
Let's hurry!
We must find a mirror to the castle!
Let's try.
I got it, Chobro!
Don't touch...
It's good!
Big Mom's ability to collect information
is greater than people think.
What?!
--Really?!
--Yes!
So you were working at his
restaurant until two years ago.
Mom!
We've already zeroed in on its location too.
...my friend!
Sanji, will you cook for me again?
Luffy, pull back for a while!
Seems like this picture was taken recently.
Straw Hat!
There we go.
Uh-huh!
No! I'm gonna eat them all!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Nami.
The sea restaurant, Baratie!
There's a way to make them more delicious!
I'll leave the rest to you!
What?!
Yeah! Count on me!
Let's go, guys!
What's wrong? You're turning pale.
Meanwhile, at the secret underground facility
in the Germa Kingdom...
Okay!
Where did your spirit from earlier go, Sanji?
What am I thinking?!
How could you do that to...
What are you doing over there?
Say something. Huh? Hey!
...Cosette-chan!!
Mom!!
What?! Don't let them get away!
You cooking wench.
Sanji, will you cook for me again?
What you did was a high crime!
I'll teach you a lesson!
Wait, Sanji! Don't forget that we're
holding a hostage in the East Blue!
Um...
Stealth.
I can't believe it...
You like that damn cooking wench?
You want cookbooks and utensils?
What are those?
I'll eat as many as I need to!
Wait for me, Sanji!
These are bracelets to prevent
him from escaping-bon.
Don't fight back.
Otherwise, there will be blood in the East Blue.
Is somebody there?
Seems like both the Straw
Hats and Sanji himself are
Henry...
going to oppose this marriage-bon.
...Needle!
I'll lend you these bracelets
and tell you his weak point just in case-soir.
Somebody, help! Call a doctor!
Hey, stay with me!
His weak point?
BRULEE'S MIRRO-WORLD
Damn! They did this behind my back!
Meanwhile, in Brulee's Mirro-world...
"The All... Blue"?
What did she do to deserve this?!
"Where fish from all four seas live..."
Well, only in the worst-case scenario
where you become uncontrollable,
"A legendary sea"!
They knocked a woman unconscious...
It's strange...
I'll use it as a threat like,
"We'll chop this guy's head off."
I put two shackles on each of them
but why aren't they here?
Look! I told you that it was Sanji!
I've never met such scum!
That's the silliest thing to do, Sanji!
You restrain yourself
just to save a mere old low-level chef.
You're right! That is him!
This isn't it, either.
We still can't find Sanji, Chobro.
It's your fault, Sanji.
So he's alive.
Why did Father tell such a lie?
Yonji!
Well, we'll find him!
Don't do anything stupid.
You know what we're capable of.
We gotta find a mirror in Germa's castle
at any cost!
You gave a woman of low birth
a taste of self-confidence.
Because he wants him to be dead.
You should've told me.
Okay!
Don't ever resist.
In that case, if he really dies,
will it make Father happy?
What do you mean by that, you asshole?!
If I knew you were in love
with that cooking wench,
I found you!
Give up on your friends and
accept this marriage to Pudding.
I wouldn't have messed up her face.
Do you want to see Niji?
Of course, he's the one who did it.
She's back!
Then, everything's going to be alright.
But if you have no problem
with that swollen face,
Follow me. I'll take you to him.
You can't escape!
I'll appoint her to be
your servant right away.
Once again, welcome back, Sanji.
You're gonna be fine. Don't worry.
I can't run anymore, Chobro!
To the Vinsmoke Family!
What's wrong? Are you coming?
Stop running around in the mirror!
Sanji!
I guess it's time to reconfirm our hierarchy.
Yeah, I'm more than happy to!
You are... a failure.
Where is he?!
Gum-Gum...
Well, you'll see.
Stop it!
...Giant Gavel!
You're a failure who deserves
to die, right, Sanji?!
Listen!
You kids are my greatest scientific achievements!
I will find the All Blue some day!
This is...
Gum-Gum...
You were curious, weren't you?
You were born as superhumans
through scientific modifications
...Rocket!
Because we weren't allowed to
go in here when we were kids.
And...
representing the best that
research has to offer!
...Munch-Munch!
Without living under the
sway of foolish emotions,
Ow...
Captain!!
Don't think I'm on your side.
I don't wanna get involved.
each of you will eventually
lead your own troops
and rule Germa 66 which will make further advances
using the power of science!
Those three are Father's ideal fighters.
That damn brat!
They don't have emotions
so they don't feel sorry or sad.
I gave you abilities! All
you need is training!
My body was successfully modified
but that's the difference between me and them.
Yes, Father!
You little...!
Bye.
Th-Thank you, Reiju...
So you've come to, little brat?
You're very lucky.
Oh, yeah. We'll climb up the Red Line soon.
You still gonna eat?!
Pirate...! Ow, ow, ow...
Seems like we'll fight some wars
in the East Blue.
Reiju-sama!
War?
There's no way you can move!
Whose kicks do you think you took?
Ichiji-sama!
Get underway towards the East Blue!
He ate them all.
54 Type-MBs. 30 Type-MSTs.
What about the ships?
The apple-juice-flavored
biscuits from before were good
Who knows... The sea was very rough.
And 21 Type-MHs need to be restocked.
Niji-sama!
but the melon-flavored ones were good too.
I wouldn't be surprised if they
were completely destroyed.
Got it.
The change of flavor worked!
You can eat forever like this, right?
We're the only ones who washed up here.
There's no fruits or animals
on this rocky mountain.
How much more can his stomach take?
The estimated travel time is
three weeks.
Sanji-sama!
We have no choice but
to wait for help anyway.
But I guess I ate too much.
That bag over there is your share.
That's obvious!
Now, Sanji-sama!
What?
People can't eat that much!
That's the food that luckily washed up here.
I bet your stomach can't take it anymore!
It's five days' worth of food
at most if you eat normally.
Use your head and eat.
Good thing that we're both cooks.
All right, I'm gonna make
more of them for you!
What are they?!
Are you curious what they are?
Wait a second! Is that your share?!
It's huge!
Germa 66 is feared around the world.
You're tired too.
Of course! I'm an adult.
My stomach is larger than yours.
And these are its soldiers!
Go, Biscuit Warriors!
You should be grateful
that I'm even sharing food with you.
Dad...
Don't expect any pity from me.
I can't do it...
Rain Spark!
You damn geezer!
You watch the other side of the sea.
This time, it's the original flavor!
Alright, Luffy! Eat as much as you want!
As soon as you see a ship, let me know.
Until then, we won't be in contact at all.
Oh, okay!
It'll be fine. I have
five days' worth of food.
She's doing it again!
Go faster! He's gonna catch up to us!
If I have five days,
a ship or two'll definitely pass by.
I'll eat and eat and eat!
I'm going the fastest I can-ju!
I can't go any faster-ju!
Then, we'll take Sanji back!
We crossed the Red Line
and entered the East Blue.
But just in case,
I'll divide them up for 20 days for now.
We're on course towards Kojia,
our target country.
If I have 20 days,
a ship'll pass by for sure.
GERMA 66
Judge-sama, it's time.
It'll be all right.
I'll definitely survive. It's easy!
It hasn't been 10 minutes yet...
Hey!
We're going to go destroy some country soon!
The preparations are complete.
You guys right there!
Okay, tell my children!
--Y-Yes?
--Can we help you?
I wish they'd let us fight too.
Bring him down!
DAY 5
We're going to leave for
the Whole Cake Chateau!
That's impossible!
Ow, ow, ow...
Impossible or not, buy some time!
For Luffy's recovery!
DAY 10
You never learn...
Now, go!
Ready? It's gonna hurt.
This is the last piece of
bread... It's gotten moldy...
Just do it.
DAY 25
She's the worst!!
It tingles a little...
Cracker-sama, forgive us!
Reiju, I...
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Ahh... How wasteful...
leaving this much food...
It's impossible as I thought!
Don't touch it.
I want to be a cook!
Even if you use us, we're no match for him-ju!
Just give up already-ju!
You guys stop eating the
customers' leftovers.
No!
Fire!
How is it?
It's my turn to help Luffy.
--It's Germa 66.
--What?! Do they truly exist?!
Keep running!
I ditched food that looked rotten earlier.
We have plenty of food.
If we get caught,
you guys will get punished too!
Where's Sanji?
I don't know.
The swelling has gone down.
--Why don't you have some, too, huh?
--I don't want it!
You're terrible-ju!
What's going on?!
Ouch!
Judge-sama, our target country
Kojia has noticed us!
It's a facial mask that
only works for swelling.
When it comes to the crunch, I'll...
It suppresses the normal physical reaction
so it only makes bruises worse.
Subdue them!
But it's better than your fiance
seeing your swollen face.
What did I say? Don't tell me that!
Come on. Come on.
Come here.
The members of the Charlotte Family won't take
their spouse's last name.
If I can... run away...
So if they accept you as a part of their family
you can live a happy life.
My last piece of bread...
Stop playing with a turtle!
Damn you...
How dare you!
...here in the East Blue...
You came back voluntarily.
Don't expect me to do anything.
DAY 70
Don't talk to me like that!
There's no second chance.
I'll never...
Humph! That will teach ya!
...have to see...
--Sanji-sama!
--Niji-sama!
I wonder... if that damn
geezer already died...
...Dad's face again, right?
Anyway,
where did you get your chivalry from?
What's the matter?
What's the matter? Bring it on!
He's still alive...
Step back!
And there's still that much food, too...
Woman! Woman! Woman! Woman!
Sorry...
Woman!!
You have only one chance!
What did you come here for, little brat?
Don't ruin it!
Shut up! We don't need a female chef!
Stop! Ouch!
I came to steal your food.
Cut it out!
I give up! Niji!
If you think you can kill me, go ahead.
Go ashore!
I'll die if I don't eat anyway.
Oh, please stop!
I teach people things through kicking.
Who is that?
I can't do that with a woman!
To think you to have this
much food all to yourself...
Why?! If she doesn't learn,
you can kick her!
Cracker-sama!!
Niji-sama...
Let go! I still wanna hit him!
You idiot!
Cracker?! Is that him?!
It's just begun!
What?
The key to your iron mask is in Father-sama's room!
Go get it!
Why is Sanji weaker than the others?
The gap in their scores keeps increasing.
Ouch!
What?!
I'm gonna go see what it's like outside!
Men mustn't kick women!
Okay?!
That's common sense from back when
dinosaurs were still around!
Uh-huh!
When you get into his room,
look for a skull symbol on the wall!
We got the test results.
Didn't I tell you that
we wouldn't be in contact until we saw a ship?
Listen, little brat!
Ichiji-sama, Niji-sama and
Yonji-sama are doing great.
You'll find a secret door there!
You can make as many mistakes
as you need as a human!
Why...?
But if you betray the honor of manhood,
Their exoskeletons have developed
This is all treasure...
What's wrong, Kingbaum?
and the figures of their flexibility and strength
already equal other strong soldiers.
I'll cut off your manhood at its root
and chop off my own head as well!
It's odd that
we can't eat when we have money.
Why are you taking Straw Hat's side?
What?! Why do you have
to do that to yourself?!
However, Sanji-sama is...
It pains me to say...
What is this?!
What's the meaning of this?!
There is a good reason for it...
Where's your food?
You haven't eaten anything this whole time?
I got it!
That's how a parent pays the price.
What are you doing over there?
What is it? Say it.
Hey! Say something!
You fool...
Don't become someone that I hate.
I have to say that he is a failure.
Sanji... Why are you here?!
We thought we successfully modified
the Bloodline Elements for all four of them.
No excuse.
Now, get back to work.
I'm gonna kill you all!
But for some reason, Sanji's Bloodline Elements
have turned back to their original forms.
Father-sama!
What happened to your leg?
That's a tradition from the dinosaur age.
I'm gonna get out of this kingdom!
Don't get in my way!
So you mean...
Sanji-sama is a normal human.
What's with him?
Woman, I'm Sweet General Cracker.
You got quite a sharp tongue
while you were imprisoned.
There is no easy sea where a normal kid like you
can survive on your own!
Why do you take care of me?
I-I'm stuffed now.
You don't want me to?
The soldiers of Germa 66?!
Screw you!
You'll die!
I want you to!
Reiju, you're so kind.
I'm sick and tired of fighting you!
Shut up! Be quiet!
Why are they in water?
That's culture fluid.
So what?! You can't stop me!
You're kind but why do you laugh at me?
They all have the same face...
Are they alive?
You fight, run away,
come back and eat!
That time...
That's a relief!
What else can I do?!
If I try to stop them, I'll be bullied too!
So it wasn't a dream...
Sanji, humans are...
I guess I'm human after all.
Is he really human?!
In order to save me, you...
...replicable!
I don't want that!
Even though you're useless,
I couldn't kill my own son.
Cracker-sama is something
but so is Straw Hat's appetite!
Germa has been a kingdom of science
for generations.
What about the food?
Did you give me all the food you had?
"NOLAND THE LIAR"
"THE DEVIL FRUITS"
Cracker-sama...
He might not look it but our father was
once renowned as a skilled scientist.
Hey, can he really make
an infinite number of biscuits?
Oh, there he is!
But you'll go away voluntarily?
That's right.
Before we were born,
You can eat that.
Without that leg,
you won't be able to be a pirate anymore!
Yes, he can-ju.
I made it for you.
But he'll run out of energy.
he was part of a lawless
foreign research team
I'm not gonna stop you.
You can take the key to the iron mask.
I guess...
No, you will!
and together with the famous Dr. Vegapunk,
he was working on weaponry.
Is it good?
Eat until you burst!
Then you'll finally give up on your friend.
Why...? I didn't ask for your help!
Sanji! Did you make food for a rat again?!
Him with Vegapunk?!
I can't think of any reason
for you to be kind to me!
I'm not gonna give up!
But can I ask just one last
favor as your father, Sanji?
Yes, in their younger days.
Royalty mustn't serve anyone!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
I'll eat and eat and go see Sanji!
Why...? Why did you?!
What Vegapunk accomplished at that time was
But I...
I'll bring out more Biscuit
Warriors for you then.
the discovery of the Bloodline
Elements within living things!
Your mother is dead!
Stop following the legacy of the deceased!
Because you...
you had the same dream as me.
It was just one step away from
usurping God's place
Don't ever admit that I'm your father...
Unlike your siblings, you have no talent!
because it was akin
to discovering the blueprints of life.
Eat them and pop, Straw Hat!
...in front of other people!
The All Blue...
So work 10 times harder...
No, 100 times harder than the others!
The World Government saw it as dangerous
and arrested Vegapunk.
And...
You all are part of my plan
to restore the Germa Empire!
...I'll tell Mama that you guys helped them,
Kingbaum!
Whoa!! Damn geezer, is
this the sea restaurant?
The research team was disbanded...
By which I mean it was bought up by the Government.
It's a shame that I don't
want anyone to know!
Don't disappoint me!
What?! But you've already
cut off the top of my head!
We're gonna be busy!
You realize that, don't you?
However, our father escaped
the Government's reach
We'll be fine 'cause I'm here!
That's not fair-ju, Cracker-sama!
and continued his research here in Germa.
We are just in awe of
Mama's Vivre Card that this girl has-ju!
Don't ever cook again either!
Hey, little brat!
His research on duplicating
and modifying life.
So we are just obeying Mama!
You're too slow, little brat!
I'm not, you damn geezer!
Yes, yes! That's right!
And then,
this underground facility has been built!
Fooling around with a woman again,
little brat?!
Save your excuse until you see Mama!
You got in my way for sure!
They're all duplicates of
just a few talented soldiers!
Little brat!
If it weren't for that woman's rain and strategy,
my hard Biscuit Warriors...
Little brat!
They're Clone Soldiers!
Is that how you run, Sanji?!
Little brat!!
Clone?!
...wouldn't have turned into
delicious crunchy snacks!
No progress.
--So he has no potential.
--No.
Shut up! This is a pirate battle!
Sanji!
How useless...
Don't catch cold.
Just because your weakness has been revealed,
What should we do?
don't take it out on our soldiers!
Of course, they're not aware of that.
O-Our?!
I can't believe that he got in an accident!
How sad!
Are we her soldiers now?
You see, Sanji?
I was expecting all five of them
to become warriors to lead Germa!
Many countries are afraid of our army
but at the same time, they wish to have it.
Got a problem?
I'm sorry!
What about the cruise ship at the port?!
Owner Zeff!!
I've lost a promising son!
Let's put an end to this, Biscuit Warriors!
It has nothing to do with us!
It's just an unlucky ship! Leave it alone!
It can't be helped
because they're strong and obedient.
Thank you for all the damn things you've done for me
over all these years!!
What? What's that?
They're programmed not to fear death
and not to turn on their masters.
This is it!
Get onboard that ship!
I'll never forget your kindness...
for the rest of my life!!
All I can do is eat them.
They'll turn back even if I break them.
Sanji! You're a boy! Stop crying already!
What?! What is this?!
When they die, we can just restock.
It takes five years to make
a 20-year old soldier.
But... Urp...
What's this? I can't take it off!
What are you guys doing?!
Listen! Don't ever come back here!
to be honest, I can't eat anymore.
This is the depot where we
keep a stock of the soldiers.
Make sure to protect me, Homies!
Uh-huh!
Did Sanji really die?
G-Got it!
I don't know. I don't care about that idiot.
Hey, Nami, can we try something
other than eating them first?
The sea is broad! You'll...
Look. It only takes five
years to create them,
Let's have a peaceful wedding tomorrow.
While I go break them and come back...
You'll definitely meet kind people someday!!
but they look like they've been around
for two decades.
Weather Egg!
We'll have lunch with Big
Mom and Pudding today.
Stop it! That's enough!
I don't know who you are to the Emperor!
Wait! I don't wanna stay here!
Get yourself ready to visit their castle.
Let me out!
But Luffy will become
the King of the Pirates!
Okay, Sanji?
Don't leave me behind!
I'm scared! I'm gonna die!
This makes me sick!
So there's no limit to his appetite!
I want my dad!
Dad! Help! They're gonna kill me!
What?! Nami, I've been
eating all this time so...
Damn Straw Hat... Where did he go?
I don't know why, but is
your stomach boundless?!
This is King-sama's decision.
Search for him.
No...
What? Dad's decision?
Rain Spark!
No way! There must be a mistake!
Run!!
King-sama said that he wanted to pretend that
Sanji-sama was never born.
10 minutes is long...
The warriors will get softened again!
Oh, no!
Sanji.
Don't look back!!
I can't even use Haki.
No... I can't...
What?
When I heard that you became a pirate,
Run! Sanji!!
I thought "That failure might've
grown up to be a better man."
But you haven't changed and I'm disappointed.
Oh, damn...
Niji!
Wait for me, Sanji!
You asshole...
Why...?
Dammit!
How could you do that to...
Please let me out, Dad...
I gotta go see Sanji!
...Cosette-chan!!
I'm sorry... I'm sorry that I was born weak!
Help me... Dad, help me!
Look at how he eats!
Dad!!
Using up all of his Haki,
Luffy is paralyzed and
Sanji carried the hope of his
Sanji's siblings were raised receiving
a lot of love from their father
Luffy eats and the biscuits multiply!
Cornered by the Biscuit Warriors
multiplying around him without limit,
father Judge and was expected
to rule Germa when he was a little prince!
Luffy is on the brink of blowing
up and he can't even move
Cracker's numerous blades come for him!
unlike Sanji who didn't
get any and had no one.
Luffy doggedly pursues a slim chance to win!
but when Cracker's fatal blade closes in on him,
Gear Four's new power kicks in!
Meanwhile, deep under the Germa Kingdom,
He was created by an immoral and
mad scientific experiment and the
It's eat or die!
With the memory of his late mother and
a dream to become a cook in his heart,
Luffy eats and eats like never before
and challenges the limits of his stomach!
Sanji sees a forbidden experiment -
the source of their immense military strength!
The deadly battle for taking back Sanji finally
comes to an end!
Little Sanji's wheel of fortune
starts spinning drastically!
hellish life he lived as
a child is now revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An Angry Sanji! The Secret of Germa 66!"
"A Battle of Limits! Luffy and the Infinite Biscuits!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Past that He Let Go of! Vinsmoke Sanji!"
"To the East Blue! Sanji's Resolute Departure!"
"The Power of Satiety! A New
Gear Four Form - Tank Man!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!