kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The goal is the last island - Raftel
and the Great Treasure of One Piece!
However, no one has ever reached
the legendary island...
...except for Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
It is the Great Pirate Era.
While the monsters of the New World
fight each other fiercely,
the Straw Hat Pirates are
in the center of the storm!
Their captain is a rubber man
who ate the Gum-Gum Fruit.
Monkey D. Luffy!
Zoro!
Nami!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Robin!
Franky!
Brook!
This tight-knit group of nine pirates...
...are making their way through the vast sea
with their sights set on the One Piece!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole
Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Sanji found out that the Germa Kingdom
was manufacturing Clone Soldiers underground.
Stop it! That's enough!
This makes me sick!
Then, he turned his fury on Niji
who beat Cosette.
Niji!
Meanwhile, in the middle of the battle against
Sweet General Cracker,
Luffy found himself in trouble
after time ran out for Gear Four.
Cracker-sama,
I didn't wanna do such a thing-ju!
She ordered me and I had no choice...
Good job, Kingbaum!
Kingbaum and the Homies led by Nami
saved him.
But they are now besieged by
Cracker's group again.
There is a good reason for it...
No excuse.
I'm gonna kill you all!
"The Past that He Let Go of!
Vinsmoke Sanji!"
Kingbaum!
I can't-ju! I can't-ju!
You're gonna tell me to fight Cracker-sama,
aren't you?!
I'm gonna fight him!
What?!
I want you guys to protect Luffy
with all your might!
Y-You're gonna fight him?!
Cracker-sama is unusually strong-ju!
A girl like you is no match for him-ju!
Whatever!
You just make sure to protect Luffy!
Na... mi...
I'm gonna distract them so you just run!
Okay?
O-Okay-ju.
Chopper was right.
We underestimated the Emperor's clan!
But now, I've just got to do it!
Whoa-whoa... Are you gonna fight me?
Even though I'm a lovely girl,
if you take me lightly, you'll get hurt!
Let's just buy time!
Straw Hat can't fight anymore.
I'll kill you first.
Do it!
Gust Sword!
Now! Run!
Let's go-ju!
Weather Egg!
Thunderbreed Tempo!
You guys should fight me!
It didn't work!
What an interesting skill.
But it just burned the biscuits a little
giving off a nice aroma...
You can move quite quickly.
Your back is wide open!
When did you...?!
Is the son of Germa that
important to you guys?
Oh, I don't understand.
If you go against Mama,
you'll definitely be killed.
Is he worth saving at the price of your life?
I think you'll never understand.
Sanji-kun is...
...a perverted ladies' man
and annoys me sometimes.
But in order to save his friends,
he'll risk his life!
If he's in trouble,
it's our turn to save him
at the risk of our lives!
That's only natural!
Is it? I see...
There's a lot I can learn from you!
Bring it on already!
You're a coward sending your puppets to fight
and watching from safety!
Are you trying to provoke me to fight?
All right. I'll fight you.
I hate pain but I don't
think you can hurt me!
Storm Cloud Rod!
Take this! Take this!
There! There! There!
I'm gonna torment you thoroughly
and take my time killing you.
So enjoy the terror.
Don't touch...
...my friend!
Straw Hat!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Nami.
I'll leave the rest to you!
Yeah! Count on me!
Meanwhile, at the secret underground facility
in the Germa Kingdom...
How could you do that to...
...Cosette-chan!!
What you did was a high crime!
I'll teach you a lesson!
Wait, Sanji! Don't forget that we're
holding a hostage in the East Blue!
Stealth.
I can't believe it...
You like that damn cooking wench?
Don't fight back.
Otherwise, there will be blood in the East Blue.
Henry...
...Needle!
That's the silliest thing to do, Sanji!
You restrain yourself
just to save a mere old low-level chef.
You should've told me.
If I knew you were in love
with that cooking wench,
I wouldn't have messed up her face.
But if you have no problem
with that swollen face,
I'll appoint her to be
your servant right away.
Once again, welcome back, Sanji.
To the Vinsmoke Family!
I guess it's time to reconfirm our hierarchy.
You are... a failure.
Listen!
You kids are my greatest scientific achievements!
You were born as superhumans
through scientific modifications
representing the best that
research has to offer!
Without living under the
sway of foolish emotions,
each of you will eventually
lead your own troops
and rule Germa 66 which will make further advances
using the power of science!
I gave you abilities! All
you need is training!
Yes, Father!
Reiju-sama!
Ichiji-sama!
Niji-sama!
Sanji-sama!
Now, Sanji-sama!
Dad...
I can't do it...
Ow, ow, ow...
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Where's Sanji?
I don't know.
Come on. Come on.
Come here.
Stop playing with a turtle!
How dare you!
Don't talk to me like that!
Humph! That will teach ya!
--Sanji-sama!
--Niji-sama!
What's the matter? Bring it on!
Sorry...
Stop! Ouch!
I give up! Niji!
Oh, please stop!
Niji-sama...
Let go! I still wanna hit him!
Why is Sanji weaker than the others?
The gap in their scores keeps increasing.
We got the test results.
Ichiji-sama, Niji-sama and
Yonji-sama are doing great.
Their exoskeletons have developed
and the figures of their flexibility and strength
already equal other strong soldiers.
However, Sanji-sama is...
It pains me to say...
What is it? Say it.
I have to say that he is a failure.
We thought we successfully modified
the Bloodline Elements for all four of them.
But for some reason, Sanji's Bloodline Elements
have turned back to their original forms.
So you mean...
Sanji-sama is a normal human.
Why do you take care of me?
You don't want me to?
I want you to!
Reiju, you're so kind.
Shut up! Be quiet!
You're kind but why do you laugh at me?
What else can I do?!
If I try to stop them, I'll be bullied too!
I don't want that!
"NOLAND THE LIAR"
"THE DEVIL FRUITS"
Oh, there he is!
You can eat that.
I made it for you.
Is it good?
Sanji! Did you make food for a rat again?!
Royalty mustn't serve anyone!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
But I...
Your mother is dead!
Stop following the legacy of the deceased!
Unlike your siblings, you have no talent!
So work 10 times harder...
No, 100 times harder than the others!
You all are part of my plan
to restore the Germa Empire!
Don't disappoint me!
Don't ever cook again either!
Is that how you run, Sanji?!
No progress.
--So he has no potential.
--No.
How useless...
What should we do?
I can't believe that he got in an accident!
How sad!
I was expecting all five of them
to become warriors to lead Germa!
I've lost a promising son!
What? What's that?
What?! What is this?!
What's this? I can't take it off!
What are you guys doing?!
Did Sanji really die?
I don't know. I don't care about that idiot.
Wait! I don't wanna stay here!
Let me out!
Don't leave me behind!
I'm scared! I'm gonna die!
I want my dad!
Dad! Help! They're gonna kill me!
This is King-sama's decision.
What? Dad's decision?
No way! There must be a mistake!
King-sama said that he wanted to pretend that
Sanji-sama was never born.
What?
Why...?
Please let me out, Dad...
I'm sorry... I'm sorry that I was born weak!
Help me... Dad, help me!
Dad!!
Sanji's siblings were raised receiving
a lot of love from their father
unlike Sanji who didn't
get any and had no one.
With the memory of his late mother and
a dream to become a cook in his heart,
Little Sanji's wheel of fortune
starts spinning drastically!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To the East Blue! Sanji's Resolute Departure!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!