kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
We are hope
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
I'm wanting you
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Close your eyes and listen carefully
Yes, we can! You can!
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
Let's look for your answer
kono shunkan
This moment
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
We are hope
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
There is a place I have to return to with you
boku tachi wa eien ni
We will be forever
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
Yes, we can!
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
To take back Sanji who
was being pressed into
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
If you can't pay for the food,
you're not a customer!
a marriage and left his friends behind,
If you're not a customer, beat it already!!
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole
Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy and the others infiltrated the
What's the matter?
Whole Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
I thought I taught you how to use a sword.
Luffy finally found Sanji
headed for the Whole Cake Chateau.
Luffy has been struggling against the
I refuse!
Biscuit Warriors that Sweet General
Cracker generates endlessly.
My hands...
But Sanji rejected his
friends' offer to regroup.
...are for cooking only.
But with Nami's power,
the Biscuit Warriors became nice and soft,
Be sure to come back, Sanji!
They got into a duel but Luffy
refused to fight against Sanji...
Hey, what are these?
soft enough for Luffy to eat.
You said your hands are important to you.
...taking the full onslaught of his attacks.
Without you, I...
I don't know who you are to the Emperor!
That's great.
Eat it.
Do you know the shackle collars
that the slaves to the Celestial Dragons wear?
I can't become the King of the Pirates!!
But Luffy will become
the King of the Pirates!
Wait!
Sanji!!
So there's no limit to his appetite!
If they try to escape from their masters,
they'll explode along with their heads.
Luffy promised to stay where he was
waiting for Sanji,
What?!
Nami, I've been eating all this time so...
I'll be here waiting!
Those work the same way.
but an army to avenge Sweet General Cracker
was organized at the Whole Cake Chateau
Sorry...
Rain Spark!
I won't eat anything
other than what you cook!
So you were working at his restaurant
until two years ago.
and started marching towards Luffy.
Sorry... Thank you... I thought I'd die.
I thought I was done...
Wait for me, Sanji!
Well, only in the worst-case scenario
where you become uncontrollable,
Be sure to come back, Sanji!
Dammit!
Let's have a nice wedding tomorrow!
Yes, let's.
I'll use it as a threat like,
"We'll chop this guy's head off."
Without you, I...
I've never eaten food so delicious!
I can't become the King of the Pirates!!
Why?!
I can't think of any reason
for you to be kind to me!
It's damn delicious, isn't it?
Meanwhile, Sanji in the Germa Kingdom...
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU IN PRIVATE LATER
I found a good cook!
Anyway, where did you get your chivalry from?
Why...? Why did you?!
Hey you, it's a good thing...
"A Storm of Revenge!
An Enraged Army Comes to Attack!"
Oh, no-ju...
...that he gave you food!
Ouch!
Because you...
you had the same dream as me.
Oh, no-ju!!
Men mustn't kick women!
Hey you, cook! Join my group!
I'm not gonna go anywhere!
That's common sense from back when
dinosaurs were still around!
Luffy...
Whoa!! Damn geezer, is
this the sea restaurant?
Be the cook on my pirate ship!
Huh?!
Luffy! Please! Hide yourself at least!
You're a good cook,
so let's be pirates together!
We're gonna be busy!
That's a tradition from the dinosaur age.
What did you say?!
We'll be fine 'cause I'm here!
It's okay to get away from
here just for a while!
Hey, little brat!
No!
You're too slow, little brat!
Sanji might come while I'm gone!
Cracker...
Fooling around with a woman again,
little brat?!
...has been beaten?!
You guys, back up a little!
Little brat!
Hit me if you can!
"The Power of Satiety!
A New Gear Four Form - Tank Man!"
Little brat!
Little brat!!
Don't do it, Luffy! It's impossible!
Don't you know whose territory we're in?!
Gum-Gum...
Hey, Sanji!
I promised him...
...Bullet!
Don't catch cold.
May I come in?
He's crazy!
...that I'd be here waiting!
You see idiots like that every once in a while.
Sanji-sama, it's time to go.
You'll have an engagement ceremony
at the Whole Cake Chateau.
Ones who will fight to the death
once they've set their eyes on a target.
Owner Zeff!!
"The End of the Adventure!
Sanji's Resolute Proposal!"
Thank you for all the damn things you've
done for me over all these years!!
Even if someone has hundreds of weapons
built into his body,
he can be defeated by someone
with a spear of blind determination.
Put this shirt on.
You're a member of the
royal family - Vinsmoke.
A HEARTBREAKING DUEL!
LUFFY VS SANJI! - PART 2
Is it about the weapons to survive
or a faith that conquers the fear of death?
You need to look like it.
Straw Hat...
This is how it should be. This is good.
How absurd...
The ultimate force means
the strongest equipment and power!
Hey, Sanji!
Your Majesty, something
is charging towards us.
The strong one is the one who survives!
It's been a while!
Then, that'll be me!
Get out! It's a trap!
What?! That idiot reached this far
into Big Mom's territory?!
Gum-Gum...
It's useless! Even pride will only get you so far!
What is the big tree behind him?!
It's running!
Luffy.
Hey!
...Bazooka!!
Are you really gonna wait here?!
How many Biscuit Warriors has he eaten?!
Sanji-kun!
We're right in the middle of enemy territory.
I'm glad that we made it in time!
Just as I thought, Mama is serious-ju!
No good!
After all, that's all you've got!
It's impossible for just the three of us
to fight those soldiers!
I thought I'd never see you again!
I'll wait!
Why are they... here?
Gum-Gum...
You guys should run away now!
Is that Straw Hat Luffy?
What?!
What?
Hey! We're here to pick you up!
No, Luffy!
I-I can't eat anymore...
...Bazooka!!
Pound said the people
who took down a Sweet General...
Go!
Sanji!
If you're sure it's all right-ju!
What?!
Stop it, you fool!
The Calicoach will turn over!
...ended up being annihilated
in the blink of an eye
Let's go, Sanji!
Rain Spark!
You said you'd be back in the note
but I didn't wanna wait.
Don't get carried away, brat!!
by Big Mom's vengeful army
that came along with a storm.
Can you escape?! It's a steel net!
So the enemy will come...
Banquet!
The game is over, anchor boy!
But Sanji-kun...
Sanji will come!
If I can get my arms and legs out,
the game is mine!
Dammit!
I was gonna come by myself but...
So I'll wait here!
You said your hands are important to you.
Why doesn't he flinch?
Why does he go that far?
If you try to get off of this island,
your hands will be blown off!
Gum-Gum...
Can he really eat forever?!
Crap! My head has been completely trimmed...
If someone declines Mama's invitation...
I'm getting heartburn just by watching it-ju.
Are you Straw Hat Luffy?!
...So Zoro and the others must've gotten
to the Land of Wano...
Yeah.
...Giant Gavel!!
I'm amazed that you didn't run away!
We'll chop this guy's head off.
I bet your legs were shaking
so much you couldn't move!
...That's why Nami, Chopper, Brook and I came
to pick you up. And...
Enough is enough, you guys!
I know he's got allies!
What's going on?!
You are a sacrifice, Sanji.
I haven't changed...
I said I can't eat anymore!
There was a big tree.
It was clear but suddenly,
dark clouds are gathering...
Faith...
Oh my!
But if you betray the honor of manhood,
I'll chop off my own head as well!
Reached your limit?!
It doesn't matter.
It does matter!
No way!
What's wrong, Kingbaum?!
No matter how you look at him, he did!
There's no way that a weakling of the
Sanji, I'm hungry!
That mountain is the Whole Cake Chateau
where Mama lives!
Worst Generation could've beaten
the Sweet General alone!
He's really going to blow up!
I don't think of you as my son even one bit!
Mama is angry-ju!
Those who laid their hands on Big Bro Cracker
are all our targets for revenge!
That's how a parent pays the price.
"A Heartbreaking Duel!
Luffy vs Sanji! - Part 1"
I'm not gonna... blow up!
--It's a shame that I don't want anyone to know!
--Sanji!
Big Mom is?!
We know that you guys came to this island
with your allies!
I don't wanna throw up what I ate
no matter what!
But...
No...
Hey, Sanji!
Spit out where they are!
Shut up.
Don't catch cold.
No way...
Then, I'm gonna make it comfortable for you
by stabbing you in the stomach!
Huh?
You've got to be kidding!
I said "Shut up"!
Don't try to act strong!
...And I had no choice so...
Is this the power of one person?!
Look out, Luffy!
So I put an end to this!
Hey! What are you doing, Sanji-kun?!
Linlin is always accompanied
by weather elements.
Muscle Balloon!
Nami, can you hear me?!
Chopper!
We have a problem!
Nothing can stop her when she gets mad.
--What is it?
--Sanji has...
Get packing, you low-class pirates!
Sanji has headed to Big Mom's castle!
I'm the one who beat the biscuit guy!
We gotta stop him quick!
Bring it on!
Yeah!
We're on our way to the castle now!
My name is Vinsmoke Sanji.
All right!
Great! Please hurry!
What about Brook's team?!
We're gonna crush you up!
I'm a prince
I don't know...
How are you guys?
of the Germa Kingdom!
We're okay!
If things go well, we'll see you guys and Brook...
I'm sorry for keeping it a secret.
Go!
I thought that it'd make you miserable.
What?
That doesn't look okay! Chopper?
The difference between our standings
couldn't be clearer.
What the...?!
Either way, we can't be saved from the outside!
If I stay here, I can spend money
and use soldiers and servants as I like.
Just keep...
Chopper?!
Nami, don't worry! We're fine...
Going back to that crappy ship
with you and your friends...
Gum-Gum...
How can I not worry?
...Jet Whip!
Prometheus-sama and Zeus-sama
are running wild!
Right, we're gonna go to the castle
to find Sanji-kun!
...or staying here,
marrying Big Mom's beautiful daughter.
Okay!
Once you rescue,
let us know through this mirror aga...
It's pretty obvious which is a happier life.
Mama is... outraged!
Gum-Gum...
Gear Four!
It broke!
...Bazooka!
Hey, Chopper?! Carrot?!
Don't take the note seriously.
What the...
It turned into a normal mirror.
Are they okay?
I won't go back with you!
Hold him down!
The weather's suddenly getting worse.
Tank Man: Stuffed Version!
I can't believe you've come all the way here.
Thanks for your trouble.
Those rats won't stop running.
They're so quick...
Get out of here... I forgot your name.
What?! He's huge!
Screw it! What are you talking about?!
I'm not convinced!
We can't waste time in a place like this!
Okay, I'll help you drive them off.
You look quite different from
the first transformation.
Sit back!
I have no choice.
When it comes to this...
Can you fight with that big fat body?!
I'll...
...send them away!
Let's run away now-ju!
Cracker-sama's blade can't cut him!
What is she doing?
No, wait!
How hard is he?!
I don't wanna get involved
in a fight like that-ju!
There's a perfect one!
You snot-nosed brat!
What?
You led Luffy and the others to this island?
And another one.
I'm sorry!
Don't push your luck!
Ow, ow, ow...
What the hell? From the mirror...
I promised them that I'd bring Sanji-san
to the southwest coast.
Straw Hat!
What should we do, Chobro?
What do you mean by sending us away, Sanji?
If I can't cut you, I'll just stab you!
But I couldn't keep my word
and now they're in danger because of me.
Ow, ow, ow...
Get packing.
You should've cleared the way.
Honey...
You too!
There is no other meaning.
Clear the way!
The enraged army will pass by!
Now, you guys, split up and look for them!
...Pretzel!
I see.
I was wondering how they made it through
the sea under so much surveillance.
An army to avenge Cracker-sama
has been organized!
Chobro, she's got allies...
Not yet!
I don't know what made you come,
Move! Get out of the way!
With this thrust, you'll burst!
Now I understand. But...
but I appreciate
that you took the trouble.
Let's take advantage of that power!
Take advantage?
Yeah!
...I wouldn't have gone to the coast anyway.
Crash Pretzel!
Having said that, if you really think about me,
you should've done the opposite.
To win back Sanji!
If you're worried about the invitation,
it'll be alright if I take the blame!
Rather than being with you guys
who are poor and weak,
If you attend the wedding, that'll be it!
Sanji-kun...
it'd be better to be part of
the rich and powerful Big Mom Pirates.
The highlight of the party will be a wedding ceremony.
Since Mama is so used to political marriages,
she puts bracelets on brides and grooms who are likely to escape.
Luffy!
Enraged army?
The groom is
the third son of the Vinsmoke Family,
I'll be happier.
If you try to get off of
the island with them...
I'm not so sure about you becoming the King of the Pirates
to be honest.
Sanji!
They'll explode.
Marriage?!
What is this? Is it hard or soft?
It's only human nature
to jump on the bandwagon.
Look how many there are!
My wedding ceremony?
Marrying a woman I don't even know?!
Seems like they're gonna go
after Straw Hat to kill him.
Your mom has the key to them.
Stop joking, Sanji-kun!
What are you talking about?!
Wh... What the hell is this?!
If you wanna get it, you have
to defeat the Big Mom Pirates.
You've got to be kidding me!
I don't want the Straw Hats
to become your subordinates either!
Don't tell me Mama has already...
Biscuit Warriors!
Then, all this time,
Yeah, she's already made those
arrangements and in the first place...
If I remember right,
he said he'd be there waiting for you.
Our captain isn't the type of guy
who works under someone!
--Rain!
--Nami!
you've been fooling me.
Don't pour water on the rest of the biscuits!
They can stay hard!
Luffy will...
Yeah, that's right.
...become the King of the Pirates!
I don't have a single ally around me.
Okay!
I've actually been looking down on you.
Nami-san.
Believe this if nothing else.
This is it for him!
I didn't mean to hide anything from my friends.
What is that glow? A flame?!
I'll be back.
Even though we're related by blood...
This ought to be fun to watch.
I can't believe it!
That's Bobbin the Disposer!
I can't get out! What is he gonna do?!
Tell them "Hi" for me.
I bet you didn't see it coming
so it's hard to accept.
I'll show you the power of being satiated!
Amande the Mad Moiselle!
This is what they do.
Oh! That's Montd'Or the Scribe!
I'll prove it to you. Get ready.
Gum-Gum...
Did your real family hurt you like that?
You can't even wish your friend happiness
I wonder how much
the total of their bounties is?!
Diable Jambe...
and you're just being selfish saying you're gonna take him back.
Yeah.
How could they...
No, Sanji-kun!
Seeing such an annoying captain,
It seems like I'm a failure to them
and they can't stand my existence.
the virtuous prince would be disgusted and probably say:
I'll be here waiting!
Joue Shot!
I've never even once thought
that I was happy to be born royal.
"Get packing, you pathetic low-class pirate!"
Fly away...
...to the end of the New World!
Well, I guess that captain
won't be stupid enough
Don't underestimate Sanji!
That's why I set out to sea...
Cannon Ball!
Even if he's happy
and doesn't want to come back,
to not run away after seeing that battalion.
...to find a place I
wasn't even sure existed.
he'd never talk to us like that!
But...
Crash Pretzel!
...if I resist the marriage,
Fly away...
my friends and I will be all dead.
...to the end of the New World!
On top of that,
We're gonna take Sanji back at any cost!
they'll kill my father figure in the East Blue
who I'm deeply indebted to!
Luffy! You're bleeding!
Sanji-kun, did you really...
Sanji-kun, stay safe.
Wherever I look, I have no way out.
Has he got smaller than before?!
So...
Get ready to fight.
It started raining.
Whoa... What?
Use your Haki or you're gonna die.
What's going on?!
I just wanna talk to you.
Why do I need Haki?
I decided to stop resisting!
No... this is... syrup.
Whoa...
Gum-Gum...
I'm not gonna...
...Giant Axe!
He's almost back to normal!
Is that humanly possible?!
...fight you!
Luffy?
I'm not gonna let even syrup in my mouth!
--Meat...
--Meat?!
Mama, Smoothie-sama of the
Sweet 3 Generals has arrived!
How hard is it to take out just one guy?!
I won't eat anything other than
what Sanji cooks!
Hey, young girl.
Don't push your luck-fa!
You're lucky.
Why?
There they are.
Okay.
Cream Monster!
Sweet General Katakuri-sama
will be here soon too!
That's Germa 66.
Oh, it's been a while since
they all got together!
I'm not gonna...
What's this?!
...fight you!
What about Cracker?
Isn't he home yet?
Ouch!
That's the power of fresh
cream's sweetness-fa!
I bet he'll be back soon
with Straw Hat's head as a present!
Then...
When the sweet cream sweetens,
your whole body will be burned-fa.
I can't wait!
...go away!
I'm not gonna do that either!
Hey, young girl.
Oh, damn!
That's Germa 66.
You've always...
Can you see Sanji?
...been selfish!
Is that it?!
Hm? Is that...?
I gotta go!
Luffy!
Straw Hat!
Hey, Sanji!
It's been a while!
Sanji-kun! I'm glad that we made it in time!
Welcome to the Whole Cake Chateau!
Please come in.
What happened?
Hey!
Mama is expecting you-bon.
Hey you, cook!
We're here to pick you up! Sanji!
Join my group!
Stop it, you fool!
The Calicoach will turn over!
Be the cook on my pirate ship!
What is it?!
Let's go, Sanji!
You said you'd be back in the note
but I didn't wanna wait.
Rain! Rain! Rain! Rain!
Go to hell!
I was gonna come by myself
but as you know, I...
Big Brother!
Gust Sword!
Please stop, Sanji-kun!
Those soldiers look weird.
They have the shapes of chess pieces.
We just came to pick you up!
Who is it?!
Luffy has...
Is it Big Mom's power?
Hey! What are you doing, Sanji-kun?!
...fought against their top officer all night
to get this far!
It doesn't matter.
They're all gonna become our allies anyway.
Get packing, you low-class pirates!
So his body is...
What's appealing isn't just their number.
Big Brother!
Cut it out, Nami!
Big Brother Cracker!
You saw the army that went
after Straw Hat, right?
Stay out of this!
This can't be happening!
He's one of our Sweet 3 Generals!
Nami!
Don't just stand there!
The next one's gonna come!
This is...
My name is Vinsmoke Sanji.
There were so many chimerical beasts.
Who did this?! I'll kill the bastard!
...a duel!
Yeah!
CHARLOTTE MONTD'OR
19TH SON OF CHARLOTTE, MINISTER OF CHEESE
This'll work out better for us
than merely reinforcing our troops.
We knew he had allies.
I'm a prince
CHARLOTTE OPERA
5TH SON OF CHARLOTTE, MINISTER OF CREAM
Kingbaum, you betrayed us.
Where did he fly from-fa?!
You call this a duel?!
of the Germa Kingdom!
You got it all wrong-ju!
I think he went to the woods...
I'm sorry for keeping it a secret.
CHARLOTTE GALETTE
18TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE, MINISTER OF BUTTER
...to take care of Straw
Hat Luffy last night.
Luffy!
I thought that it'd make you miserable.
At last!
Our dream will finally come true.
Let's go back, Kingbaum!
That means...
Sanji-kun!
I can't believe you've come all the way here.
Thanks for your trouble.
Straw Hat Luffy must be somewhere near-fa!
Our dream!
It can't be helped-ju!
Shut up.
Get out of here... I forgot your name.
Put out an emergency alert!
But there are only three.
Screw it! What are you talking about?!
I'm not convinced!
Okay, I'll help you drive them off.
Evacuate!
Sit back!
What happened?!
Knock them down at once!
Sweet General Cracker-sama got beaten!
I'll send them away!
What?!
Get out of my sight now!
Bring it on!
Oh, there's Mama! Mama!
--Mama!
Luffy!
Are you all being good?
Go away!
Luffy! Are you okay?!
Mama, mama!
Go away!
I ate a lifetime's worth of biscuits...
Help me...
What is it, Anana?
Dad, help me!
Get the hell out of my sight!!
The head chef won't let me use a knife.
I wanna cut my stuffed animal.
But you shrunk back down a lot.
Gear Four takes so much energy.
I don't think of you as my son even one bit!
Oh, no!
Dolce, Dragee,
go and borrow one for her.
No more playing tag. Just give up already!
Is it good?
Pound!
Sanji! Did you make food for a rat again?!
Where were you?!
No, Mama! Once Anana has a knife,
she'll pop our balloons!
Well, I'm sorry for running away.
I thought you were going to lose.
Royalty mustn't serve anyone!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
Yeah! She's bad!
I'm gonna kill her someday!
Don't ever cook again either!
You're being pretty honest!
Stop... Please stop, Sanji-kun!
Because the guy was one
of the Sweet 3 Generals...
We shouldn't say those things, right, Mama?
Get out of my face...
Well...
He was making food for rats again!
Everyone has 100 to 200 people
who they want to kill.
...now!!
Royalty mustn't cook.
Anyway, we won!
Be nice to each other, my children.
"The All... Blue"?
We'll have Big Sis Pudding's
wedding tomorrow!
We did it! We did it!
Chobro!
"Where fish from all four seas live..."
What?!
Yay! Yay!
Are you excited?
"A legendary sea"!
Carrot! We're done running!
Lighten up!
We beat one of the Emperor's top officers!
You get to eat a delicious wedding cake.
You never learn...
I... can't even move...
Yay! Yay!
What have we done...
Now let's meet!
The groom's family!
Reiju, I...
I refuse!
We helped them defeat Cracker-sama-ju.
Door!
It's far from over!
I want to be a cook!
Everyone knows that Mama's Vivre Card is
a powerful totem to us Homies!
I'm not your enemy-ju!
That is why even Mama's
children can't have one now!
If I can... run away...
Get out of my sight now!
Why do you have it?!
...here in the East Blue...
It's good to have you here, Germa 66.
Is that true?
So it's really quite a valuable thing.
I'll never...
Sorry to be late.
What's the matter, Chess Peacekeepers?
But you're in big trouble.
Emperor Big Mom!
The Chess Peacekeepers are slowing down.
...have to see...
We've had a little problem
but it should be okay now.
Why?
...Dad's face again, right?
This works on the Peacekeepers, too!
When Sweet General Snack got taken down...
That's a relief!
I refuse!
Even though you're useless,
I couldn't kill my own son.
The vengeful Cracker's
fleet blackened the sea
Luffy!
But can I ask just one last favor as your father,
Sanji?
and the angry Linlin created a storm...
So you're Black-Leg Sanji.
Gum-Gum...
You'll become my daughter Pudding's husband.
I heard it sank the enemy
ship in the blink of an eye!
...Elephant Gun!
Don't ever admit that I'm your father...
Storm?
No matter what I do, you're not gonna leave,
are you, you low-class pirate?
Don't be shy!
Linlin is always accompanied
by weather elements.
...in front of other people!
Weather?
On her left hand, Zeus, a thundercloud!
It's a shame that I don't want anyone to know!
If you're not gonna go
away, I have no option.
You realize that, don't you?
Cream Monster!
On her right hand, Prometheus, a sun!
I'm not gonna go easy on you anymore.
That cream thing again!
Don't regret this after you die.
Nothing can stop her when she gets mad.
Oh, Pudding! There you are.
Before she hears about this,
you'd better run!
Sorry for being late.
Get onboard that ship!
Sanji! You're a boy! Stop crying already!
I don't care if she gets mad!
Listen! Don't ever come back here!
Luffy!
Give up already-fa!
What?!
Uh-huh!
Anyway, I've heard a lot about him.
The sea is broad! You'll...
I'm the one who wants to get mad!
First of all, Sanji, that fool!
On the condition that I accept this marriage,
You'll definitely meet kind people someday!!
Your son's a cook, huh?
He's perfect for Pudding.
I want Big Mom to let my friends go.
TO MY BUDS, I'VE GOTTA GO
SEE A WOMAN. I'LL BE BACK.
How could he disappear leaving
a note behind suddenly!
Well, it doesn't matter even if he's not.
Sanji-kun!
Without telling us why!
It's a political marriage.
They're going after Luffy and the others.
Here we go!
This is my problem.
As long as you and I share mutual interests,
that's all it matters, Judge!
I'll be back.
I'm sorry!
My mother put you in such
a difficult position!
Tell them "Hi" for me.
I can't believe we got caught in the dispute at Kojia.
Thanks to Pudding's map,
we made it this far,
Yeah but it'd be nice
if our children are happy.
Stop!
It's not your fault!
We had a narrow escape.
but Pekoms went missing.
But...
And although Pudding said
that she'd bring Sanji,
A kid?!
May I... work on this ship?
Sanji-kun... Please stop...
Let's have a nice wedding tomorrow!
Until 13 years ago, I was in hell.
no one was there at the rendezvous point.
Yes, let's.
I'd do anything, any odd job!
I want to become a cook!
Please! I'm begging you!
We've wasted so much time in the forest
where we got lost!
I just came right back there again.
I should be happy to have been away from here
as long as 13 years.
Please! Please!
When they get married,
Sanji becomes Big Mom's subordinate, right?!
Please! Please!
The people who let me
polish my cooking skills
That's enough! Stop, Sanji-kun!
Please! Please! Please!
and the friends who I traveled with...
We'll leave!!
We gotta get going!
Please!!
I'm indebted to everyone that I met.
Yeah! When is the wedding?
I just wanna go away without hurting anyone.
Cracker said the Vinsmokes will enter
I won't!
a castle today, where the
wedding will take place.
My adventure ends here.
What time is it now? We gotta stop them!
--Tea
--Green tea
You're a good cook,
--Tea
--Green tea
A-Are you serious?
If you don't run away, you'll really...
What would you like to have?
so let's be pirates together!
I'm not gonna run away!
I'll have tea.
Tea! Tea! Tea! Tea!
Do it-fa!
Concasser!
I'm hoping to go someday...
to the Grand Line.
Tea!
Then let's go now.
Hey, tree!
It's not the right time yet.
Say... do you know the All Blue?
--Eat us! Eat us!
--Start with me!
You know where the castle is, don't you?!
Now!
--Eat us! Eat us!
--You can have me too!
No...
Well...
Oh, you don't?!
Carry me to the castle!
You need lots of honey, young man!
It's a miracle sea!
No way-ju...
It's very...
Luffy!
In that sea...
Sweet!
We're gonna take Sanji back at any cost!
La la lunch! La la lunch!
Don't hesitate!
--Sausage!
--Cabbage!
Where are you?!
BRULEE'S MIRRO-WORLD
--Ham!
--Pancake!
What?! Don't you know?!
It's no use running!
Delicious!
It's a legendary sea.
It's out there somewhere!
Thunderbreed...
I'll definitely find that sea someday!
Could you be quiet?
...Tempo!
What?!
Luffy! Luffy!
Don't say such a thing!
Let's have a delicious lunch!
The East Blue, West Blue, North Blue,
and South Blue...
There are too many!
Let's wait here until she goes away.
La la lunch! La la lunch!
A sea where fish from all four seas live...
That's the All Blue!
How strong...
La la lunch! La la lunch!
Okay.
After all, he's a Vinsmoke.
It's so noisy!
Maybe, that'll do!
My head is kind of... fuzzy...
How do I taste? Am I good?
To seafaring cooks,
that's an irresistible paradise!
Hey, don't cry. It makes me feel pathetic!
Chobro!
La la lunch! La la lunch!
That's my dream!
Don't yell!
Look!
La la lunch! La la lunch!
I'm sorry! But...
S... Sanji-san...
Luffy!
I...
Sanji!
Luffy! Luffy! Hey! Stay with me!
Pirates!
Red Shoes...
Luffy! Luffy!
Sanji-san!
Zeff's ship!
Luffy! Luffy!!
Steal!
I won't let your marriage with me be hell!
That's Sanji's sister.
What's the matter?
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU IN PRIVATE LATER
I'm not gonna be killed in a place like this!
Did you get cold feet?
Hey, Sanji!
I'm sorry! What am I saying?!
You're deeply suffering!
I will find the All Blue some day!
Why, after all this time?
The unwanted marriage
should be hell to you too!
Then, shall we get going...
to the Whole Cake Chateau?
Goodbye!
Sorry -
How could I say such a thing
when someone's in pain!
we should never have done this!
Whole Cake Chateau?
It's getting rough.
I'm ashamed of myself! I'm sorry!
Oh! A bitchy girl! How hot!
I guess that's Big Mom's castle!
Captain!!
That damn brat!
I've only known you for a short time!
There's no way I can fill the hole in your heart!
What?!
Sanji's leaving!
We finally found him!
In the first place, you didn't even say
that you're gonna marry me!
Look at us, Sanji!
Sanji!
The superfluous ties have
finally been severed.
I'm so...
Nami!
Thanks for waiting.
What's the matter?
Weather Egg!
--Let's go.
--Yes, sir.
Go hide somewhere!
We gotta tell Luffy and Nami quick!
What?
Yeah!
They're coming!
Yes, you should go tell them...
It's hit or miss!
So you've come to, little brat?
You're very lucky.
Please!
Pirate...!
What about the ships?
Who knows...
Luffy!
We're the only ones who washed up here.
What is that?!
You watch the other side of the sea.
I found you!
As soon as you see a ship, let me know.
Until then, we won't be in contact at all.
Boom out!
Wait!
Sanji!!
--Sanji-sama!
--Congratulations!
I wonder... if that damn geezer already died...
"Low-class pirate"?!
He's still alive...
I know you were just saying
things that you didn't want to!
Stop lying!
What did you come here for, little brat?
Did you think
that you could send me away that easily?!
I came to steal your food.
Screw that!
To think you have this much food all to yourself...
No matter how many times you kick me,
What?
you're the one...
What is this?!
What's the meaning of this?!
...that gets hurt!!
Where's your food?
You haven't eaten anything this whole time?
Hey! Say something!
Oh, no-ju...
I'll be here waiting!
Oh, no-ju!!
Luffy! Why?!
Whatever the reason is, he can't do this...
How many... are there?!
What happened to your leg?
Even if I get hungry or
spears rain down on me,
Shut up!
Should we stop, Sanji?
I'll stay right here and wait for you!
Keep going.
That time...
So it wasn't a dream...
Luffy, you gotta get away too!
In order to save me, you...
Say...
Run if you want.
do you know the All Blue?
I'm not gonna go anywhere!
Without that leg,
you won't be able to be a pirate anymore!
So that I can beat the hell
out of you when I catch you.
It's a miracle sea!
In that sea...
Like you could.
I guess...
What'd you say?!
Stop it. Not in front of the public.
Why?!
Our journey...
I can't think of any reason for you to be kind to me!
...isn't over yet!
Luffy...
Why...? Why did you?!
I'll be here waiting!
Have a great wedding day!
If you don't come back, I'll be here...
Because you...
you had the same dream as me.
Congratulations!
Luffy! Please! Hide yourself at least!
...starving to death!
Sanji-sama!
It's okay to get away from
here just for a while!
You're the cook of my ship!
The All Blue...
No!
Today, we Vinsmokes make a new start.
He was making food for rats again!
Sanji might come while I'm gone!
Whoa!! Damn geezer, is this the sea restaurant?
You guys, back up a little!
I won't eat anything
other than what you cook!
Don't do it, Luffy! It's impossible!
We're gonna be busy!
Don't you know whose territory we're in?!
We'll be fine 'cause I'm here!
Even if I get hungry or
spears rain down on me,
Woman! Woman! Woman! Woman!
I'll stay right here and wait for you!
Woman!!
Shut up! We don't need a female chef!
You're my... salvation.
I teach people things through kicking.
Sanji-san...
Sanji-sama!
I can't do that with a woman!
If I'm good enough for you...
Wave back to the citizens, Sanji.
Why?! If she doesn't learn,
you can kick her!
That's a big army... You can't beat it!
You idiot!
Be sure to come back, Sanji!
Ouch!
Men mustn't kick women!
Without you, I...
Listen, little brat! You can make
as many mistakes as you need as a human!
We found Straw Hat Luffy!
I can't become the King of the Pirates!!
But if you betray the honor of manhood,
I'll cut off your manhood at its root
and chop off my own head as well!
Let's go, guys!
I promised him...
What?!
Why do you have to do that to yourself?!
Let's get married tomorrow.
...that I'd be here waiting!
That's...
...how a parent pays the price.
Hey you, cook! Join my group!
Be the cook on my pirate ship!
After overcoming the tough battle,
Luffy finally sees Sanji again!
Cutting his emotional ties to his friends,
Sanji kicks Luffy full force! Blow after blow!
Continuing to believe in
Sanji, Luffy keeps fighting.
No matter how many enemies Luffy beats,
he sees no end to the deadly
struggle against the enraged army.
However, Big Mom's formidable children
show their devilish abilities -
However, they both cling stubbornly
to their goals and things go all wrong!
Sanji will be back!
Contrary to Luffy's expectation, however,
However, their journey isn't over yet.
Burning Cream and a creepy World of Books.
Will Luffy be able to win Sanji back?
In order to win his ship's cook - his precious friend - back,
Sanji is beyond the point
of no return and pressed
Can Luffy hold out against
their tremendously fierce attacks?!
to make the biggest decision of his life!
With their friendship in the
balance, they start fighting!
Luffy gets up over and over again!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Heartbreaking Duel! Luffy vs Sanji! - Part 1"
"I'll Wait Here! Luffy vs. the Enraged Army!"
"The End of the Adventure!
Sanji's Resolute Proposal!"
"A Heartbreaking Duel! Luffy vs Sanji! - Part 2"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!
I'm hoping to go someday...
to the Grand Line.
Then let's go now.
It's not the right time yet.
Say... do you know the All Blue?
--No...
--Oh, you don't?!
It's a miracle sea!
In that sea...
Luffy stands where he told Sanji
he'd wait without moving an inch
while black shadows that seem to cover the
whole land are coming for him with a storm!
Big Mom's vengeful battalion rumbles
the earth rushing at Luffy!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Storm of Revenge! An Enraged
Army Comes to Attack!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!