kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara tabidatsun da kimi to, we can!
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
umi kara umi wo mata ni kakete
Traveling from sea to sea
hitotsunagi no takara sagashi ni
In search of the one-piece treasure
sonna no yumemonogatari dato
Despite the fact that
everyone laughs and says
daremo ga waratteiru kedo
that it's just a fantasy
mune no takaburi dake ga rashinban
A rush of excitement is our only compass
shittakaburi shitero yo
Just keep pretending you know everything
kyoukasho nante sa guidebook
Textbooks are just guidebooks
ame mo namida mo itsuka wa yamu
Both the rain and our
tears will eventually stop
kao wo agero ikari wo agero
Hold up your head, pull up anchor
kokoro no arashi ga sugita nara
Once the storm in your heart subsides
kajitore saa kachitore
Take the helm, now, win a victory
ashita no kaze ga fuku koro niwa
By the time tomorrow's wind blows
harebare ho wo hare mune wo hare
Get refreshed, spread sail, chest out
dareka ni aitakunarun da
It makes me long to see someone
souzou tsukanai koto bakari daro
There are tons of unimaginable truth
miteminufuri suruna yo
Don't turn a blind eye
joushiki nante sa tasuuketsu
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
kono sekai no hate nante
kono me de mita wake janai
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
dakara ikou ze amano jack senchou
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
dekiyashinai koto tte nani?
mada nani mo hajimatte nai
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
subete shiritain da ima, yes, we can!
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
kono shunkan
This moment
We can! I can!
kono kaikan
This great feeling
ima ima, yes, we can!
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
To take back Sanji who
was being pressed into
a marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the
Whole Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy has been struggling against the
Biscuit Warriors that Sweet General
Cracker generates endlessly.
But with Nami's power,
the Biscuit Warriors became nice and soft,
soft enough for Luffy to eat.
I don't know who you are to the Emperor!
But Luffy will become
the King of the Pirates!
So there's no limit to his appetite!
What?!
Nami, I've been eating all this time so...
Rain Spark!
Wait for me, Sanji!
Dammit!
Meanwhile, Sanji in the Germa Kingdom...
Anyway, where did you get your chivalry from?
Ouch!
Men mustn't kick women!
That's common sense from back when
dinosaurs were still around!
That's a tradition from the dinosaur age.
"The Power of Satiety!
A New Gear Four Form - Tank Man!"
May I come in?
Sanji-sama, it's time to go.
You'll have an engagement ceremony
at the Whole Cake Chateau.
Put this shirt on.
You're a member of the
royal family - Vinsmoke.
You need to look like it.
How absurd...
How many Biscuit Warriors has he eaten?!
I-I can't eat anymore...
Go!
What?!
Rain Spark!
Dammit!
Can he really eat forever?!
I'm getting heartburn just by watching it-ju.
Enough is enough, you guys!
I said I can't eat anymore!
Reached your limit?!
No way!
No matter how you look at him, he did!
He's really going to blow up!
I'm not gonna... blow up!
I don't wanna throw up what I ate
no matter what!
Then, I'm gonna make it comfortable for you
by stabbing you in the stomach!
Look out, Luffy!
So I put an end to this!
Muscle Balloon!
What the...?!
Gear Four!
Tank Man: Stuffed Version!
What?! He's huge!
You look quite different from
the first transformation.
Can you fight with that big fat body?!
Cracker-sama's blade can't cut him!
How hard is he?!
You snot-nosed brat!
Don't push your luck!
Straw Hat!
If I can't cut you, I'll just stab you!
Honey...
...Pretzel!
Not yet!
With this thrust, you'll burst!
Crash Pretzel!
Luffy!
What is this? Is it hard or soft?
Wh... What the hell is this?!
Biscuit Warriors!
--Rain!
--Nami!
Don't pour water on the rest of the biscuits!
They can stay hard!
Okay!
I can't get out! What is he gonna do?!
I'll show you the power of being satiated!
Gum-Gum...
Fly away...
...to the end of the New World!
Cannon Ball!
Mama, Smoothie-sama of the
Sweet 3 Generals has arrived!
Okay.
Sweet General Katakuri-sama
will be here soon too!
Oh, it's been a while since
they all got together!
What about Cracker?
Isn't he home yet?
I bet he'll be back soon
with Straw Hat's head as a present!
I can't wait!
Hm? Is that...?
What happened?
What is it?!
Big Brother!
Big Brother Cracker!
This can't be happening!
He's one of our Sweet 3 Generals!
Who did this?! I'll kill the bastard!
CHARLOTTE MONTD'OR
19TH SON OF CHARLOTTE, MINISTER OF CHEESE
CHARLOTTE OPERA
5TH SON OF CHARLOTTE, MINISTER OF CREAM
Where did he fly from-fa?!
I think he went to the woods...
CHARLOTTE GALETTE
18TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE, MINISTER OF BUTTER
...to take care of Straw
Hat Luffy last night.
That means...
Straw Hat Luffy must be somewhere near-fa!
Put out an emergency alert!
Evacuate!
What happened?!
Sweet General Cracker-sama got beaten!
What?!
Luffy! Are you okay?!
I ate a lifetime's worth of biscuits...
But you shrunk back down a lot.
Gear Four takes so much energy.
Pound!
Where were you?!
Well, I'm sorry for running away.
I thought you were going to lose.
You're being pretty honest!
Because the guy was one
of the Sweet 3 Generals...
Well...
Anyway, we won!
We did it! We did it!
Yay! Yay!
Lighten up!
We beat one of the Emperor's top officers!
I... can't even move...
What have we done...
We helped them defeat Cracker-sama-ju.
Everyone knows that Mama's Vivre Card is
a powerful totem to us Homies!
That is why even Mama's
children can't have one now!
Why do you have it?!
Is that true?
So it's really quite a valuable thing.
But you're in big trouble.
Why?
When Sweet General Snack got taken down...
The vengeful Cracker's
fleet blackened the sea
and the angry Linlin created a storm...
I heard it sank the enemy
ship in the blink of an eye!
Storm?
Linlin is always accompanied
by weather elements.
Weather?
On her left hand, Zeus, a thundercloud!
On her right hand, Prometheus, a sun!
Nothing can stop her when she gets mad.
Before she hears about this,
you'd better run!
I don't care if she gets mad!
What?!
I'm the one who wants to get mad!
First of all, Sanji, that fool!
TO MY BUDS, I'VE GOTTA GO
SEE A WOMAN. I'LL BE BACK.
How could he disappear leaving
a note behind suddenly!
Without telling us why!
This is my problem.
I'll be back.
Tell them "Hi" for me.
Thanks to Pudding's map,
we made it this far,
but Pekoms went missing.
And although Pudding said
that she'd bring Sanji,
no one was there at the rendezvous point.
We've wasted so much time in the forest
where we got lost!
When they get married,
Sanji becomes Big Mom's subordinate, right?!
We gotta get going!
Yeah! When is the wedding?
Cracker said the Vinsmokes will enter
a castle today, where the
wedding will take place.
What time is it now? We gotta stop them!
A-Are you serious?
If you don't run away, you'll really...
I'm not gonna run away!
Hey, tree!
You know where the castle is, don't you?!
Well...
Carry me to the castle!
No way-ju...
We're gonna take Sanji back at any cost!
Where are you?!
BRULEE'S MIRRO-WORLD
It's no use running!
Let's wait here until she goes away.
Okay.
My head is kind of... fuzzy...
Chobro!
Don't yell!
Look!
Sanji!
That's Sanji's sister.
What's the matter?
Did you get cold feet?
Why, after all this time?
Then, shall we get going...
to the Whole Cake Chateau?
Whole Cake Chateau?
I guess that's Big Mom's castle!
What?!
Sanji's leaving!
We finally found him!
Look at us, Sanji!
Sanji!
We gotta tell Luffy and Nami quick!
Yeah!
Yes, you should go tell them...
I found you!
--Sanji-sama!
--Congratulations!
Run if you want.
So that I can beat the hell
out of you when I catch you.
Like you could.
What'd you say?!
Stop it. Not in front of the public.
Have a great wedding day!
Congratulations!
Sanji-sama!
Today, we Vinsmokes make a new start.
Wave back to the citizens, Sanji.
Let's go, guys!
After overcoming the tough battle,
Luffy finally sees Sanji again!
However, they both cling stubbornly
to their goals and things go all wrong!
Will Luffy be able to win Sanji back?
With their friendship in the
balance, they start fighting!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Heartbreaking Duel! Luffy vs Sanji! - Part 1"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!