If you can't pay for the food,
you're not a customer!
If you're not a customer, beat it already!!
Eat it.
Sorry...
Sorry... Thank you... I thought I'd die.
I thought I was done...
I've never eaten food so delicious!
It's damn delicious, isn't it?
I found a good cook!
Hey you, it's a good thing...
...that he gave you food!
Hey you, cook! Join my group!
Be the cook on my pirate ship!
Huh?!
You're a good cook,
so let's be pirates together!
Hit me if you can!
Gum-Gum...
...Bullet!
He's crazy!
You see idiots like that every once in a while.
Ones who will fight to the death
once they've set their eyes on a target.
Even if someone has hundreds of weapons
built into his body,
he can be defeated by someone
with a spear of blind determination.
Is it about the weapons to survive
or a faith that conquers the fear of death?
The ultimate force means
the strongest equipment and power!
The strong one is the one who survives!
Then, that'll be me!
Get out! It's a trap!
Gum-Gum...
It's useless! Even pride will only get you so far!
...Bazooka!!
No good!
After all, that's all you've got!
Gum-Gum...
What?!
...Bazooka!!
Don't get carried away, brat!!
Can you escape?! It's a steel net!
The game is over, anchor boy!
If I can get my arms and legs out,
the game is mine!
Why doesn't he flinch?
Why does he go that far?
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Gavel!!
Faith...
"A Heartbreaking Duel!
Luffy vs Sanji! - Part 1"
Nami, can you hear me?!
Chopper!
We have a problem!
--What is it?
--Sanji has...
Sanji has headed to Big Mom's castle!
We gotta stop him quick!
Yeah!
We're on our way to the castle now!
Great! Please hurry!
What about Brook's team?!
I don't know...
How are you guys?
We're okay!
If things go well, we'll see you guys and Brook...
What?
That doesn't look okay! Chopper?
Either way, we can't be saved from the outside!
Just keep...
Chopper?!
Nami, don't worry! We're fine...
How can I not worry?
Right, we're gonna go to the castle
to find Sanji-kun!
Okay!
Once you rescue,
let us know through this mirror aga...
It broke!
Hey, Chopper?! Carrot?!
It turned into a normal mirror.
Are they okay?
Those rats won't stop running.
They're so quick...
We can't waste time in a place like this!
I have no choice.
When it comes to this...
What is she doing?
There's a perfect one!
What?
And another one.
Ow, ow, ow...
What the hell? From the mirror...
What should we do, Chobro?
Ow, ow, ow...
You should've cleared the way.
You too!
Now, you guys, split up and look for them!
Chobro, she's got allies...
Let's take advantage of that power!
Take advantage?
Yeah!
To win back Sanji!
Sanji-kun...
The highlight of the party will be a wedding ceremony.
The groom is
the third son of the Vinsmoke Family,
Sanji!
Marriage?!
My wedding ceremony?
Marrying a woman I don't even know?!
You've got to be kidding me!
I don't want the Straw Hats
to become your subordinates either!
Our captain isn't the type of guy
who works under someone!
Luffy will...
...become the King of the Pirates!
Nami-san.
Believe this if nothing else.
I didn't mean to hide anything from my friends.
I'll be back.
Tell them "Hi" for me.
You can't even wish your friend happiness
and you're just being selfish saying you're gonna take him back.
Seeing such an annoying captain,
the virtuous prince would be disgusted and probably say:
"Get packing, you pathetic low-class pirate!"
Don't underestimate Sanji!
Even if he's happy
and doesn't want to come back,
he'd never talk to us like that!
Crash Pretzel!
Fly away...
...to the end of the New World!
We're gonna take Sanji back at any cost!
Sanji-kun, stay safe.
Has he got smaller than before?!
Whoa... What?
What's going on?!
Whoa...
He's almost back to normal!
Is that humanly possible?!
--Meat...
--Meat?!
Hey, young girl.
You're lucky.
Why?
There they are.
That's Germa 66.
Hey, young girl.
Can you see Sanji?
Is that it?!
I gotta go!
Luffy!
Hey, Sanji!
It's been a while!
Sanji-kun! I'm glad that we made it in time!
Hey!
We're here to pick you up! Sanji!
Stop it, you fool!
The Calicoach will turn over!
Let's go, Sanji!
You said you'd be back in the note
but I didn't wanna wait.
I was gonna come by myself
but as you know, I...
Hey! What are you doing, Sanji-kun?!
Get packing, you low-class pirates!
My name is Vinsmoke Sanji.
I'm a prince
of the Germa Kingdom!
I'm sorry for keeping it a secret.
I thought that it'd make you miserable.
I can't believe you've come all the way here.
Thanks for your trouble.
Get out of here... I forgot your name.
Screw it! What are you talking about?!
I'm not convinced!
Okay, I'll help you drive them off.
Sit back!
I'll send them away!
Help me...
Dad, help me!
I don't think of you as my son even one bit!
Is it good?
Sanji! Did you make food for a rat again?!
Royalty mustn't serve anyone!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
Don't ever cook again either!
He was making food for rats again!
Royalty mustn't cook.
"The All... Blue"?
"Where fish from all four seas live..."
"A legendary sea"!
You never learn...
Reiju, I...
I want to be a cook!
If I can... run away...
...here in the East Blue...
I'll never...
...have to see...
...Dad's face again, right?
That's a relief!
Even though you're useless,
I couldn't kill my own son.
But can I ask just one last favor as your father,
Sanji?
Don't ever admit that I'm your father...
...in front of other people!
It's a shame that I don't want anyone to know!
You realize that, don't you?
Get onboard that ship!
Sanji! You're a boy! Stop crying already!
Listen! Don't ever come back here!
Uh-huh!
The sea is broad! You'll...
You'll definitely meet kind people someday!!
I can't believe we got caught in the dispute at Kojia.
We had a narrow escape.
A kid?!
May I... work on this ship?
I'd do anything, any odd job!
I want to become a cook!
Please! I'm begging you!
Please! Please!
Please! Please! Please!
Please!!
I'm hoping to go someday...
to the Grand Line.
Then let's go now.
It's not the right time yet.
Say... do you know the All Blue?
No...
Oh, you don't?!
It's a miracle sea!
In that sea...
What?! Don't you know?!
It's a legendary sea.
It's out there somewhere!
I'll definitely find that sea someday!
The East Blue, West Blue, North Blue,
and South Blue...
A sea where fish from all four seas live...
That's the All Blue!
To seafaring cooks,
that's an irresistible paradise!
That's my dream!
Pirates!
Red Shoes...
Zeff's ship!
Steal!
I'm not gonna be killed in a place like this!
I will find the All Blue some day!
Captain!!
That damn brat!
So you've come to, little brat?
You're very lucky.
Pirate...!
What about the ships?
Who knows...
We're the only ones who washed up here.
You watch the other side of the sea.
As soon as you see a ship, let me know.
Until then, we won't be in contact at all.
I wonder... if that damn geezer already died...
He's still alive...
What did you come here for, little brat?
I came to steal your food.
To think you have this much food all to yourself...
What?
What is this?!
What's the meaning of this?!
Where's your food?
You haven't eaten anything this whole time?
Hey! Say something!
What happened to your leg?
That time...
So it wasn't a dream...
In order to save me, you...
Without that leg,
you won't be able to be a pirate anymore!
I guess...
Why?!
I can't think of any reason for you to be kind to me!
Why...? Why did you?!
Because you...
you had the same dream as me.
The All Blue...
Whoa!! Damn geezer, is this the sea restaurant?
We're gonna be busy!
We'll be fine 'cause I'm here!
Woman! Woman! Woman! Woman!
Woman!!
Shut up! We don't need a female chef!
I teach people things through kicking.
I can't do that with a woman!
Why?! If she doesn't learn,
you can kick her!
You idiot!
Ouch!
Men mustn't kick women!
Listen, little brat! You can make
as many mistakes as you need as a human!
But if you betray the honor of manhood,
I'll cut off your manhood at its root
and chop off my own head as well!
What?!
Why do you have to do that to yourself?!
That's...
...how a parent pays the price.
Cutting his emotional ties to his friends,
Sanji kicks Luffy full force! Blow after blow!
However, their journey isn't over yet.
In order to win his ship's cook - his precious friend - back,
Luffy gets up over and over again!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Heartbreaking Duel! Luffy vs Sanji! - Part 2"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!