Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Please help my friend.
Please call a doctor.
Whoa!
So this is a winter island!
"An Outcast's Dream!
Hiriluk the Quack!"
I will definitely get you there.
I haven't told you my name yet. I'm Dalton.
The name of those mountains
is the Drum Rockies.
I'm the captain of the
security squad of this island.
In the castle on top of the
tallest mountain lives Dr. Kureha,
Day 3. Prognosis, the
bacteria were reduced to 30%.
Don't die... Nami... Sanji...!
There's only one doctor here, and she
lives in the castle on the mountain.
the only doctor in our country who is
called a "witch" by our country's people.
Why in the heck would she
live someplace like that...?
Who are you?
Okay then, Nami. Hang on tight.
I'm counting on you, Captain.
"The Island Where Snow Lives!
Climb The Drum Rockies!"
I can't believe it!
Like captain, like navigator!
Okay...
Let's go!
Whoa! You're amazing!
All right, then, let's go...
before Nami dies.
"Blue-nosed Reindeer!
Chopper's Secret"
Just as you'd expect from a monster!
What?! Don't say things
that could jinx us!
But what happens if I do this?
Watch out for Lapins.
Ahhh! Please look at that!
We found them, Wapol-sama!
So these're Lapins?!
Poke, poke...
What?! What're you doing?!
Whoa... Wapol-sama...
What!
They're carnivorous, ferocious bunnies.
We've finally returned...
to our home, Drum Island!
Isn't that... backwards?
Hold it, brat!
If you run into a group
of them, you're dead.
They have bodies like bears,
but the agility of bunnies...
So funny!
Huh? You guys're...
Shut up! Go away!
How dare you do
many rude things to me!
and they attack in groups.
Won't you become my friend?
"Are You Happy?
The Doctor Called Witch!"
You're too slow... and you're
not completely hiding, either...
--I'll chew you guys up!
I really really like you!
Run!
--Get out of my way.
--I'll chew you guys up!
Just what are you?
--Get out of my way.
--Humph! You're stupid, aren't you?
Sh... Shut up, human!
Y... Your friend?
Why would I get out of your way?!
Ahh...
Become a pirate!
And, how's your fever?
It talked!!
I'm not interested in pirates at all.
And I never wanted a friend!
Looks like what you have on your
back and in your arm are half-dead.
Nami?
What're they doing?
Nami-san!
We have to... hurry to Alabasta...
If you become my friend,
my other friends will all be happy!
Never mind that, just rest.
Don't worry about anything right now.
Wait!
Be quiet, Chopper!
Why would I wanna
become your friend?!
When her own life is at risk...
Those damn bunnies...
This can't be happening...
Don't insult me!
Hold it! Oh, I know!
Nami-san, hang in there
just a little longer.
Hey, Sanji. What's the matter?
Chess! I thought up a new law.
Write this down.
What the heck is going on?
We have to go to that castle
where the doctor lives.
Hey... we're gonna run, Luffy!
Yes sir!
Those who ignore the king
are to be executed!
Your fever seems to have
come down a little, girl.
You're definitely funny!
Get out of our way, you damn bunnies!
"Dalton's Resolve!
Wapol's Corps Lands On The Island"
I'll definitely make
you become my friend!
Are you happy?
Ignoring me already?!
They're coming!
In order for you to get
a healthy smile back,
Guys! First, get the sick and injured ones,
who are ignoring me the most!
Yeah!
R-run? Where to?
Who are you?
Listen, Luffy!
I prepared an exceptionally
nutritious dish...
Hm?
--Yes sir!
38.2 degrees... Hmm...
You're doing more or less all right.
Don't you dare fight.
What'd you say?!
Doesn't matter where! Someplace far!
Thank you, Sanji-kun.
Why not?
Idiot! Whether you attack or get struck,
I'm a doctor. Dr. Kureha.
Call me Doctorine.
I'll take the woman on his back!
though you're still painfully beautiful
even after what your body's been through...
What?!
I'll take the man.
An avalanche...! An avalanche is coming!
Nami-san will feel the whole impact too!
Take this! Marimo's Surprise!
Good lord! When did you use
my kitchen without asking?
Doctor... Then I'm in the...
My secret to staying young?
She'll die...
Madam, the roast over there is for you.
Ahhh! Those damn bunnies!
They'll never get away with this! Dammit!
No, I didn't ask that.
What?!
It's high in protein and is
good for rejuvena-- Ahhh!
Listen Luffy!
Wh-wh-wh-what're we gonna do?!
Wh-wh-what're we gonna do, Sanji?!
O... Okay! I won't fight!
Don't you dare fight.
I'm not a "madam."
B-but, what do I do?!
Whether you attack or get struck,
I'm a sparkling single...
and still youthful.
How should I know?!
The first priority is Nami-san!
You're right. You're in the
castle on top of the mountain.
Nami-san will feel the whole impact too!
The second is Nami-san!
You're still 139 years old... right?
The third is Nami-san!
Just dodge! Dodge, dodge, dodge and run!
The fourth is Nami-san!
Then there were two others
besides me, right?
And the fifth is Nami-san!
Doctorine! Help me!
Got that?!
Yeah, they're sleeping in the next room...
very deeply. What tough guys...
Protect her even if it kills you!
But don't retreat!
Wait! Hey! Wait!
That's hard!
Got it!
Damn you! You'll regret this!
Wait!
But how?!
Flanchet Shoot!
Don't follow me!
This was the cause.
Wait! Wait!
What're you doing?
What... is this?
Humph. What a coward... It's no use.
This guy's gonna join us
and become our friend!
Dammit! In this snow,
I can't kick properly!
Over there! That cliff!
You were bitten by a bug called Kestia.
Oh, really?!
Cliff?!
Run! We need to get as high up as we can!
It's a poisonous tick that lives in jungles
with high temperature and humidity.
I didn't say that!
You did.
I didn't!
You did!
Once you're bitten by it,
bacteria come in and
It's coming!
Be quiet, both of you!
I'll show him...
They're all attacking at once!
Wait!
what a battle in a snowy area is like...
keep you in pain by lying dormant
inside your body for 5 days.
Wait!
Go into the forest!
I'll cover your back!
Okay!
Friend, huh? How deep a
meaning that word has to him...
It causes high fever of above 40 degrees,
Go left! We'll head to the mountain!
coinfection, myocarditis,
arteritis, cerebritis!
Got it!
We'll shake them off somehow!
To ask without knowing that...
Huh...?
Given the infection's progression
from the bitten area,
It'd take us until night
to finish fighting them!
There's no one... What's going on?
I'd say you've been
infected for three days.
These snow mountain animals really
are tough! We're at a disadvantage.
Good, we made... Ahh!
I wonder if they've already given up...
The suffering must've
been unusually harsh,
Oh no! We're not high enough!
but it would've eased up in 2 more
days even without any treatment.
Don't!
There was one man whom he opened
up to when he was alone...
Now this is a true battle in a snowy area!
In 2 more days...?
The white disguise!
Snow Powder Makeup!
Idiot! I told you not to attack!
Yeah, because you
would've died in 2 days.
Since they're so weak,
they'll be dead with just one shot.
Just leave them to me!
The man's name was Dr. Hiriluk.
Wapol... Wapol came back!
What?!
Sorry...
This isn't a joke!
He was a quack who gave Chopper
a name and called him son.
Check Mate!
It's called the "5-day disease."
What?!
Sanji! We can go up from here!
Stop it!
Dalton-san headed to Big Horn!
I heard that Kestia died
out 100 years ago,
Good! Go on ahead!
Those who can fight, grab a
weapon and head to Big Horn!
but it was useful that I kept
the antibiotic just in case.
Heave-ho!
Hurry! Those who can fight,
head to Big Horn!
Where did you guys come from?
Hold it!
Follow Dalton-san!
Were you out walking around
with your belly exposed
White bears...
Follow Dalton-san!
Did you find him?!
No! We can't find him!
in a jungle on an ancient
island or something?
Wapol came back!
That darn quack, Hiriluk!
--They're coming!
--You don't need to egg them on!
Everyone, grab a weapon!
We'll protect our country!
Lapins?!
Well, that's just silly...
We'll catch him no matter what!
Those're Wapol-sama's orders!
Anyway, run! To the top of the mountain!
Ah...
Grab a weapon! Head to Big Horn!
--Yes sir!
Did they protect him?
It's getting strong...
Yeah!
It's a coincidence.
Lapins never become attached to humans.
That ring a bell? What a crazy girl...
Nami-san, please be okay...
Hey, Vivi. Are you really sure
this is the right direction
Now...
to the Gyasta town where
the witch is right now?
Who in the world are you guys?
Stay in bed. Your treatment
hasn't completely finished yet.
Hmmm... When you put it that way,
I'm not really sure...
Who are we...?
Dammit!
It's too reckless for just the 6 of you to
travel in the Grand Line without a doctor.
We're in trouble if you aren't sure...
Thank you so much. So long as my
fever comes down, I'll be fine.
You are...
You can't go on like this.
Let's call a doctor.
Listen, if Luffy and Sanji managed to get
to the castle and didn't find the doctor,
My body will take care of
itself after that, right?
No. There aren't any doctors
in this country...
We're pirates. That's why you
guys pointed guns at us, right?
You're too optimistic.
they'd think, "What're we doing?"
This disease normally takes at
least 10 days to fully treat.
except for the Twenty MDs who
belong exclusively to Wapol...
Well, we may be a small group...
Unless we find the doctor soon and
ask her to go back to the castle...
We'll beg Wapol and call
the Twenty MDs. I'll go.
but as long as I, Brave Warrior
of the Sea, am with them,
Of course, if you want to
suffer some more and die...
I know that, but...
there's no need to worry.
If you know that, then do something.
You're a princess, right?
You don't have to.
I see...
Even with my medicine,
you'll have to rest at least 3 days.
But it's true that we do want a doctor.
That has nothing to do with this.
I'm not a witch. I'm a princess.
I was hoping to find someone
like that on this island, but...
What? I can't stay here for 3 days!
We have to take Vivi to Alabasta soon!
But...
I'll examine him.
Then you look at the map.
I didn't expect that there was only one
doctor, a witch living in that castle...
Hiriluk! N-no thank you!
Please don't!
What?! Don't be ridiculous!
There's snow everywhere. The map is...
A bunch of people you treated
ended up getting worse!
When a patient of mine leaves me,
It's a strange combination...
In short, you don't know...
Don't be modest. I just developed a
wonderful all-purpose drug yesterday.
Yeah! I don't know at all!
It seems that you guys're different
from the pirates that we think of.
she's either cured or dead.
I won't let you get away.
You don't have to be proud!
Dalton-san!
In any case, there should be
a sign for Gyasta on this route.
You're lucky.
Dalton-san!
Gotta bow...
Oh, hi.
So don't miss it.
I heard that you're looking for Dr. Kureha?
Got it. Leave it to me!
I'll watch for signs of the sign!
Hmm? It's not what you think.
This is a tranquilizer gun.
Yes, that's right, but the
sick person has already...
I use it when the
patient's pain is severe.
Oh, ignoring me, huh?
I... I'm gonna go get the guards!
I heard that she's in our
neighboring town, Cocoaweed, right now.
Please leave!
If you want money, I'll pay!
What?!
I don't take money from sick people.
I just want to help you.
Then they passed each other?!
Delicious!
Don't! Stop it! I've got a family!
Listen up, citizens!
Everything in this country is my snack!
Hey, owner. We've had enough already!
Croak! Croak, croak!
Croak, croak, croak!
He climbed this mountain
with his bare hands?!
I'm great! Why?
Your kid's voice is so loud
that I can't stand it!
This 5000m high Drum Rock?!
Thanks! You saved me!
Croak! Croak!
Croak, croak! Croak!
Kuromarimo, tell them!
Ah, I'm sorry.
Hmm? This is strange.
Did I use a wrong ingredient?
His entire body is nearly frostbitten.
What was he thinking dressing like this?
Hey, Tamachibi, what's wrong?
Does it hurt somewhere?
That's because you're
the king, Your Highness.
Don't let him get away!
Yes sir!
I thought frog extract would work...
Guess it was a failure. Oh man...
That's right! That's exactly right!
If I wanna eat a house,
Heat water immediately
and throw him into it.
If you just keep crying,
I won't know what's wrong.
You're disturbing customers.
This guy's bleeding badly.
6 broken ribs and a spinal fissure.
there's nothing like one cooked
well-done to a golden-brown after all!
S-Sorry... I didn't
mean for this to happen...
Yeah!
Tamachibi! Say something!
Hiriluk! Are you there?!
Wapol-sama.
I have some information for you.
Can I operate on him?
If you don't stop crying,
I'll lock you out!
What is it?
--Hold it!
I received a report that
some of the Straw Hats
Apparently, the most critical
one is this girl. She's dying.
What the hell do they
think they're doing?!
--It's the witch!
--Shh! She can her you!
rudely headed towards Drum Castle.
--Scary...
--Shh! She can her you!
She's with that creepy monster again...
Chopper! Have phenicol,
cardiotonic and tialcillin ready!
What? Why?!
Hmm?
It seems that they took a sick woman
to have her treated by a doctor.
Does she have an infection?
Yeah. The pathogen
isn't from this island.
Hey! That's enough!
Such idiots! No one lives in my
castle now, not to mention a doctor!
Are you happy, young man?
Well well... What a mean father...
Hm?
The doctor hunt has come
to the final stage.
I hear that you and I are the
only doctors left in this country.
If a child keeps crying, he's signaling
that something's wrong with his body.
W-well... I heard that
the outrageous Dr. Kureha
Don't worry. I'll make both that
bleeding kid and this girl all better.
Wapol is trying desperately to catch us.
even more rudely currently
lives in Drum Castle...
So rest assured.
Even if that wasn't the case, you're
already an outcast in this country...
Stay there, Chopper.
Doctor...
They're my friends...!
What?! That old hag's
living in my castle?!
since you're the worst of the quacks.
Doctor...
Sorry to interrupt...
Just how much does she intend
to mock me?! Kick her out!
Dr...
I won't get caught by some doctor hunt.
I get the picture. I'll save them.
Are you kids happy?
Doctor...
Along with Straw Hat, I'll eat her up!
I'll save this country using
medical science one day.
Chopper! Let's begin treatment!
Men, we're going back to the castle!
Dr. Kureha!
Oh? Didn't you mean to say
"destroy the country"?
Yeah!
My secret to staying young?
No! We didn't ask that!
There're people on the bridge!
Stop right there!
So this is it...
They're my friends...!
I still can't believe
she's a 140 year old hag...
I'll see you around, quack.
I don't wanna see you again,
you thieving doctor.
I can't see the top.
I'm still 139!
I'm... I'm hungry...
Who's that?!
Ahh! I was cut down! I'm gonna die!
Shall I make it better?
I can find the doctor... up there...
Hm?! Make what better?
He isn't sick or anything.
Dalton-san!
I came here to kill you.
You dying suits me just fine.
Meat...
I'll never get caught!
I'll save as many sick people as possible!
Hang in there a little longer...
You bastard, Dalton!
Nami! Sanji!
Are you... a doctor?
Venison stew needs to be
cooked in a pot for 3 hours...
So you're alive!
Hmm?
How dare you hurt Wapol-sama!
Then the meat becomes properly tender...
Well then, shall we go, Chopper?
It shouldn't be a big deal...
with the excellent doctors of our country,
Wait!
You've been shot? We need to stop
the bleeding right away or you'll die!
the "great medical care nation" Drum.
Meat...
I'm sorry. It was my mistake.
That's right! The Twenty MDs
External Injury Unit! Come forward!
Don't worry. I'll save you!
Venison...
It's a yeti! Shoot him to death!
Since I heard that the doctor
came down the mountain yesterday,
Starting an operation.
I thought she wouldn't
come down for a while.
Starting an operation.
I just made an ointment that even
works on broken bones 3 days ago.
Starting an operation.
Don't worry about it.
It's not your fault.
Starting an operation.
You're lucky.
Scalpel!
Needle!
Tin.
The issue here is Luffy and
Sanji's abnormal physical strength.
Hammer.
Ahhhh! Help!
Well... I really thought I'd die!
Even if we go after them
in the snow mountain now,
Don't let him get away!
Kill him!
we probably won't be able
to catch up with them.
Just like what happened now,
Wait, meat!
Shoot him!
If the witch is in the
town called Cocoaweed,
you're the only one protected
and citizens have no choice
we should ask her to go back
to the castle immediately.
but to suffer from sickness
without seeing doctors... Wapol!
Wait, Luffy! I'll cook this guy!
What are you?
You don't look like a human.
Yes, you're right.
We have no other choice.
Wapol? It's Wapol-sama,
my retainer Dalton.
Oh, yeah. You're that yeti that
people have been talking about...
Forgive us...
He's right! You don't
have the right to blather!
What?
Hm?
Forgive this country that doesn't
even have enough doctors...
Nami...
The three of us, you included,
were Wapol-sama's top brass.
N-no... It's not something
you should apologize for.
Nami-san!
You got better?
Yeah, thanks.
We were his loyal hands, remember?
She's right.
Okay, then! I'll make a nutritious
venison dish for Nami-san!
It's true that when you
were making people suffer,
Let's hurry!
Yeah! It hit him!
all I could do was just watch
It wasn't enough! Finish him!
Wait!
even though I was by your
side as one of your top brass.
I have to take responsibility for that.
I'm surprised!
They can already move around?
Wapol... Let's leave this country together.
What's that talking stuffed
deer with a blue nose?
My hands... hurt...
Avalanche...
We must not stay in this land any longer.
You asking me what he is?
Your hands, huh...? I see...
We were swallowed by the avalanche...
Dalton-san! You didn't do anything wrong!
H... How dare you...
Don't run away, meat!
Then, how about now?
Wait, Luffy! I'm telling you
not to eat it yet!
Ah! U... Usopp-san?!
That's right! You're the only one in the
government who fought for the citizens!
My leg hurts!
Usopp-san!
Who do you think... I am?!
See? You forgot that
your hands hurt, right?
What'd you do?!
Stop it, humans!
Usopp-san! Come on! Wake up!
Even when it almost killed you!
Hey! Wait!
His name is Chopper.
He's just a reindeer with a blue nose.
Are you happy? You're happy?
Good! Be good and quiet.
Humph! You should've died...
as the Captain of the
Drum Kingdom's Security Guard!
Hey!
I will never shoot you!
He's still alive!
Reindeers don't speak.
Don't yell. I just touched his leg lightly.
Usopp-san! Hang on!
I'm surprised that you survived in
this country without any doctors.
S-stop it, you jerks!
I heard a terrible noise.
Drum is acknowledged internationally
as a country with advanced medicine.
If he's different from
ordinary reindeers in some way,
My name is Dr. Hiriluk!
He's got pains in his hands and legs.
Come on! Usopp-san! Usopp-san!
If he's different...?
But who would know... that there
were actually only 20 doctors,
I'm a doctor!
He doesn't seem to have a fever,
Oh Vivi... Don't wake me up.
but the swelling on his leg
is due to purulent inflammation.
who worked in the research
facility of the King's castle,
I'm not food!
I was just having a beautiful dream.
It's pretty bad.
A field of beautiful flowers out of
this world and a beautiful river... Oh?
The bone has been infected.
Chopper, give me antibiotics.
and all the other doctors were exiled?
it's just because he ate a
Human Human Fruit. That's all.
That's right! Those who become
sick can beg for their lives.
--You're almost in the netherworld!
--Isn't that Zoro swimming in the river...?
A Human Human Fruit...
One of the devil fruits...
--Wake up! Don't sleep! Wake up!
--Isn't that Zoro swimming in the river...?
Doctor... will my son be...
The key to cure this disease
is the initial treatment.
If I feel like it, I might
lend them the Twenty MDs.
Yeah... He's a reindeer who
gained the humans' abilities.
All 74,000 Usopp Pirates, close in!
Don't worry. He'll be cured...
although he almost died...
If they don't wanna die, all they
have to do is obey me, the king!
No! Wake up! Usopp-san,
don't die! Usopp-san!
What?! Almost died...?!
Rats! Rats!
I'm going to do a little
operation on you, so be patient.
And I taught him everything
I know about medicine.
With that, my ruling is perfect.
That's the government of this country!
Hey, can't you at least use anesthesia?
Usopp-san! Usopp-san! Usopp-san!
Here is the shot.
You can't call that a government!
Don't be reckless!
Humph! You sure speak
your mind, don't you?
Phew, you saved me, Vivi.
Well then... since my
medicine works well,
Talk about having a
narrow escape from death.
Kill him! Kill your ex-captain!
I'm glad I'm alive.
this is it for the treatment.
But...
As I figured, you don't
get what I'm saying...
--don't you think my face is kinda swollen?
All you have to do is make sure he rests
well and keep his legs bandaged tight.
Wapol-sama.
That Straw Hat is up there...
--I-it's chilblains! Chilblains!
--don't you think my face is kinda swollen?
I'm starting to get a bit hungry.
--I-it's chilblains! Chilblains!
--My head feels kinda heavy...
--This is why it's not easy
to be in a snowy area.
--My head feels kinda heavy...
Yeah...
Once you immobilize his legs,
cool them well. Got that?
--This is why it's not easy
to be in a snowy area.
--Or should I say my view is kinda narrow...
I'll eat the rubber man for a snack.
You're the son of the previous
king who was good to me.
--More importantly,
--Or should I say my view is kinda narrow...
--we have to figure out our location
and the situation we're in quickly!
--Or should I say my view is kinda narrow...
--we have to figure out our location
and the situation we're in quickly!
--My lips are kinda big... Kinda...
About the fee, well... I'm almost
out of trash bags and toilet paper.
We're going up.
--we have to figure out our location
and the situation we're in quickly!
--yeah, I agree...
I was hoping that you'd
come to your senses some day,
but it seems like that
was wishful thinking!
That was Chopper and Hiriluk's
first encounter.
Also all the plum wine and
the food you have... And...
Ahh! There he goes! Ox Ox Fruit!
Ahhh! What's that?!
The model "Bison"!
I'll take 50% of this restaurant's assets.
Ahhh... That was close...
I saw a field of flowers...
Don't flinch! Fire!
What?!
Chopper... take them to our sled.
Dalton-san!
Wha...?! Hey, that's outrageous!
Half of the assets?!
Suddenly hitting an avalanche in
this cold... I must've run out of luck.
We can't hit him!
He's dodging them!
I'll show no mercy even though
you're my ex-subordinates!
Dalton-san!
Hey, owner! Don't be fooled!
That's a rip-off!
But this is a sort of
winter swimming, I guess.
Dalton-san!
Did you find him?!
Dalton-san! Don't die!
It must be!
Zoro.
He almost died?! Wasn't he really
just crying because he fell?!
Hm? Oh, Vivi.
We'll find him in time, for sure!
Be alive, Dalton-san!
Fiddle Bam!
So what happened... to the
reindeer taken in by Hiriluk?
Huh?
How dare you abuse your
position as a doctor!
Who's that?
Hm?
He's right!
Don't just stand there! Help...
You're a terrible person!
What?! You can talk?!
Gotta bow.
Don't take advantage of
people's weakness, you witch!
He's strong! How powerful!
Like I said, don't just
stand there and help us!
Oh, it's you, Usopp!
What're you guys doing here?
So this is the wild power...
the power of a Zoan type devil fruit...!
Why did you stay quiet for 3 days?
That's my question!
Stop it, Chopper. It's just the
blabbering of a bunch of kids.
I've had enough with you all.
What the heck is that thing?!
I thought you'd hate me if I talked...
A country where the king
is the first to run off
We found him! We found Dalton-san!
When I talked to humans the
other day, they shot me...
What idiots!
Old lady...
when the country is in crisis
should just die out!
That's what you lowly bunnies
get for going against the king!
I feel a lot better.
What?! They found him?!
You don't have a chance,
fighting against the two of us.
because it's strange for
a reindeer to speak...
Great!
Dalton-san!
Thank you!
Just give up.
Humph! I didn't think I'd use my
real power on mere bunnies, though.
You speak, so what?!
Dalton-san!
So, who is that?!
Oh...? I got a good tip.
I can speak, too...
a lot better than you can.
Dalton-san!
It couldn't be helped...
We've come to assist you!
since they're the most
violent animal in Drum.
Let us fight with you!
I'll reduce the fee to 49%.
We'll protect this free country!
This is terrible...
Get out of here! Chopper!
What?
Just wait... Straw Hat!
There's no heartbeat.
I'll pay you. Thank you.
Above all, I've known you so long.
Ahh...! Hey, kid.
Dammit! It failed again!
Hey, are you okay, Chopper?!
Hm?
Don't forget... the happiness
you feel right now, okay?
That's unfortunate for you.
Become one of my crew!
Please, old lady!
Don't...!
Your weak point is...
We need a doctor on our ship!
Hmm? Well, you aren't okay
to start with, I guess...
Luffy... You said that's your name, right?
Okay!
Yeah.
Did you just say "old lady"?
Yeah, I did, old la...
Watch... what you say!
Why are you calling me Chopper?
You're Tony Tony Chopper.
Why...
Doctor...!
...did you shield us...?
I'm still in the youthful 130s.
After all, you're a reindeer and have
fine antlers that could chop down trees.
Dalton-san!
Whoa... What an incredible old hag...
That's a cool name, isn't it?
That's what I'll call you.
Doctor...!
Dalton-san!
Are you asking me to be a pirate?
That's your weak point, kind Dalton-kun.
It's ice-cold!
Don't be ridiculous!
It'll be a waste of my glorious time.
My body is becoming numb...
it's like I'm trapped in ice!
Chopper...
This is a death befitting you!
I'm not interested in the sea.
Seems like I've still
got a long way to go.
Listen, Chopper. Always observe patients,
and give them proper treatment.
If I suppress my 'self', even fire should
be cool and ice should be lukewarm.
Who cares? Let's go on
an adventure, old lady!
Wh-what's going on?!
Hm? What's going on? An earthquake?
Hey hey. I just told you to
watch what you say, didn't I?
Doing so will save people's lives.
Hey, Karoo! Come along with me!
Doctor...!
Hey, this isn't good. We can't go
further because of the deep snow.
So they're pirates...
This is an ideal way to strengthen
your inexperienced body!
Let's go! Patients are waiting
for me today once again.
Hm?
Ah! Ow!
Looks like we went up the mountain...
Hm?
Get out of here, quack!
Ah!
Sanji!
Hm?
I thought lizard eyeballs would work...
What's... this rumbling?
--Wait, meat!
--Wait!
Never come back!
Usopp-san! Could this be...
Go away!
Run! It's the guards!
Hold it, brats!
Ahhh... A.. Avalanche...?
Chopper! We'll use the decoy plan!
I didn't expect to see this many fish.
What's that?!
Th-that... that was close...
25631... 25632... 25633...
Take care!
I guess I'll go for another dip.
Wait!
Are they coming?
What?
Hold on, Nami-san!
I'll cook a nutritious reindeer dish!
No, they aren't.
You almost got me killed!
Hm? What's going on? How noisy...
All right! Looks like we lost them.
Oh yeah?! You failed to die once already!
You clumsy blue nose!
Before that, I'll eat you guys!
Winter swimming?!
No... not yet.
Yeah. After swimming
in the river for a while,
Hm?
Don't call me blue nose!
They're persistent!
Old hag!
I had no idea where I was any more.
Where the heck did she come from?
So I was walking while
doing muscle training,
25634...!
She's coming! She's coming!
and then I ended up in a forest.
Dressed like that?
You're stupid, aren't you?
What're they doing?
Anyway, give me your coat, Usopp.
I don't care about the food.
I just want some peace and quiet.
Doctor...
Hmm?
No way.
This is... the first time
I've fought with someone...
Nami-san might've gotten sick
due to mental exhaustion...
Are they irritated because they're hungry?
--Then your shoes!
--No!
--One of them!
No...
--No!
--One of them!
Makes sense... To fight,
you have to have an opponent.
Snow...? Even though
this is inside the castle...?
Hold on a sec...
It's your own fault, isn't it?!
Oh no! We're not high enough!
Then... is it your first time
for this as well?
Look over there! There're people.
Don't tell me... they're...!
Cold...!
Hm?
Hey... I remember those buildings...
--I should close the door.
Hmm?
--Stay in bed!
--I should close the door.
I'll give it to you. It's a gift...
as a memento of our making up.
What?
You still have a fever!
What do I do now?!
You... Who are you?
I don't. It seems like
it's pretty much gone.
A gift? Making up?
You're right! This is Big Horn!
We ended up... coming back!
Looks like I lost them...
Oh, yeah!
Even so, no!
You don't look like an ordinary villager.
Since Doctorine's medicine works well,
the fever goes away quickly.
Sanji! Grab my hand!
Step back! Step back!
The way you speak... sounds to me
like someone from the military.
But Kestia's bacteria
still remain in your body.
We both go through hardships
as outcasts, don't we?
Dalton is already dead!
You saved my skin!
Yeah, but... even though
we won't sink in the snow,
Have the antibiotic shot
and stay in bed, or you'll...
I was... a subordinate of...
the ex-King, Wapol...
There's no way Dalton-san
would die from an attack like that!
But don't hold a grudge against humans.
we'll go straight down the mountain
if we don't do anything!
You guys're Dalton-san's
ex-subordinates, aren't you?!
Thank you...
This country is sick right now.
Hm?
What?!
Don't you care?!
You've been attending me, right?
We're retainers of King Wapol!
Hell no! We've come all
this way and were almost
Both the citizens and the king
suffer from a sickness of the heart.
Sh...
If you become Wapol-sama's enemy,
you're dead meat!
People would probably say that
you can't treat a sick country,
at the foot of that chimney mountain!
I was the captain of this country's
security squad since the previous king.
Shut up!
Hey, what's the matter?
We were just a step away from the doctor!
but that's not true.
I don't wanna be thanked by a human!
Wh-what's the matter?
Luffy! Come up with a way to stop this!
Once my invention is complete,
this country will be saved!
What's the matter with you,
dressing like that?!
Don't mock me! You jerk!
However, when the king died...
Dammit, those damn hopping bunnies!
There used to be a master-thief
in a country in the far west.
Dalton-san's buried under
the snow of the avalanche!
Don't be silly, you dummy!
Next time I see them,
I'll simmer them in a pot!
and his son, Wapol, became the king,
What?!
Seriously, don't be so...
He had a serious heart disease.
What?!
Dalton-san is?!
this country changed.
He's the type that
can't hide their emotions...
Yeah. We can't dig him out
because those guys get in our way.
Oh, yeah! I've thought of an
interesting law today again!
He went to see every possible skilled
doctor and got treated by them,
but no one was able to cure him.
Step back! Step back!
I'll exile all the doctors!
After being told he'd die,
he passed by a mountain
What?!
If you have any objection,
go right ahead and bring it on!
Exile them?!
Doctors?!
while frustrated and unsettled.
This castle is strange.
It's cold and there's snow inside.
That's right. I'll keep just 20 superior
doctors and make them my private doctors.
What're we gonna do, Sanji?!
There... he saw a sight that
he had never seen in his life.
There's only one way!
Usopp, I remember their clothes.
Oh...?
I christen them the "Twenty MDs"!
Run!
They're the ones who attacked
us on the sea, right? Right?!
The "Twenty MDs"?!
Ahhh! It's cold!
That's right, the "Twenty MDs."
We'll exile the other doctors!
Like I told you before, you're slow!
What the heck's... with them?!
Yeah, that's right.
That's our great Wapol-sama!
That's a wonderful idea!
Then they're our enemy, aren't they?
Cherry blossoms! He saw vivid
cherry blossoms all over the mountain!
They're our enemy, right?
What's the word? Are they on our side?!
No...! If you do such a thing,
who'll see our people when they get sick?!
Well, they're our enemy...
but why are you so...
Look at this...
Oh no! Luffy! Look ahead! Ahead!
And then, he went to see another
doctor and was shocked...
You think their sickness
has anything to do with me?
Ahhh! A rock! We're gonna crash!
because he was told...
You aren't so courageous
without Dalton, are you?
Those who want to see a doctor will
have to prostrate themselves before me!
"You're completely healthy."
There's snow everywhere in the castle.
What?
He was cured! It was indeed
a miracle! Don't you think?
There's no one whose family
members don't get sick.
You can't crash!
You're carrying Nami-san!
The doors for the unused
rooms are all frozen, too.
There'll be no one who can go
against me in this country!
What?! Mr. Bushido!
But this was unmistakably medical science!
By being emotionally moved, some sort
of change happened in this man's body!
Who's that?!
Hey you! Stop it!
If you attack them, you'll...
Am I a genius or what?!
In other words, there's no disease
in this world that can't be cured.
That's easy to say, but...!
This is warm! I'm borrowing it!
No matter what anyone says about me,
I'll save this country as a doctor!
Then those who became
sick had no choice
You... asked me because of that...?!
but to ask for Wapol's mercy
in order to see the Twenty MDs?
--Look! They're angry!
Hold it! Hold it! Hold it!
That's why I raised this skull
towards all the diseases!
We're crashing!
--You!
--Look! They're angry!
You were on the ship with that
guy who blew Wapol-sama away!
Yes, and pay excessive medical fees...
You have to treat ladies... gently!
It's the same as ruling the country by
taking the citizens' lives hostage...
Oh? You guys never learn, do you?
Skull...
Hey hey, Luffy! Give up on
asking that old hag to join us!
This is a symbol of the belief
that nothing is impossible!
Sanji!
She's not a doctor!
She's trying to kill us!
That's not governing...! It's a crime...
I will save this country as a doctor!
By raising this,
I'll fight just like pirates do!
Are you guys looking for...
Are you guys pirates?
Just as I thought... There's no mistake...
these?
Yes...
Hey! Reindeer!
R-real ones?
Real ones.
Sanji!
Join us and become our friend!
You have a flag with a skull?
Ahhh... That hit me good...! Dammit!
Hmm? Whoa! That looks delicious!
Bring him down!
It's attached to our ship.
You idiot! Don't do stuff
like that without telling me!
Are you interested in pirates?
No! You idiot! No!
You idiot!
It's cool to be a pirate!
Okay, okay. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Ahhh! Sanji!
Doctor, what are pirates?
Hawk Wave!
Ahhh... dammit! I got carried
away and swam too long!
Pirates?
But... Then... wanna come, too?
Pirates are incredible guys at sea.
Where am I? Where's the ship?
What?!
They have large, well-trained
bodies and eyes like an eagle.
Geez... I can't tell where
I am with all this snow!
To the sea! Why don't you
come with us...? Hm?
Their voices are like
a thunder splitting the sky!
Ahh! It's coming!
If you do, that'll help me a lot!
It's not stopping!
If we have a doctor on our ship,
I won't have to stay here for 3 days, right?
This village will be swallowed!
Oh, it's already over?
Get out of here!
On top of that, on our ship, we...
D... Don't be ridiculous!
I'm a reindeer!
Ahhh! I'm saved!
We're getting out of here!
Chess! Kuromarimo! Get on!
What a disappointing bunch...
Are you... really a pirate?!
Hey, old lady! Sorry to bother you,
There's no way I can stay with humans!
but will you take me
to the nearby village?
Robson!
Hmm?
Robson, Serious Mode!
Yeah, I am...
Huh?
To start with, don't you
get scared when you see me?
Like I've been saying, join us!
It's fun to be a pirate! Pirates sing, too.
What're you doing showing your
belly in this damn cold weather?
Wapol-sama! Please let us ride, too!
Amazing...
I'm a reindeer, but I stand on
two legs and I even speak...
All right! Good job, Zoro!
Just as I instructed!
What a weird old lady...
Shut up! Get out of here on your own!
What? Th-they sing?
Hm?
Be careful what you say.
Yeah. And they dance, too!
What? Are you trying to scare me?
Robson! Hurry up! It's closing in on us!
Let's find Dalton-san!
Yeah!
You call that being a pirate?!
I'm still in the youthful 130s!
That's right!
And they go on lots of adventures!
My nose is blue, too...
Thank you!
W-w-w-w-w-w-w-w-w-w-we'll
be fine! Don't worry, Vivi!
Adventures? So pirates
go on adventures then?
Let's go, Chopper. We don't have
time to bother with a weirdo.
Hurry up! Dig everywhere!
Wait, you hag!
Of course! Pirates risk their
lives to go on adventures!
Even if we get swallowed,
I'll save you for sure!
What the hell was that
stupid old hag's problem?!
So, what's all this fuss?
You can meet lots of amazing people!
Hey, do you think
Luffy-san and the others...
I'll explain it later! Let's help them!
Whoa, it's cold...
It's cool to be a pirate!
There're tons of incredible guys at sea!
There you are!
Damn! I'll be in trouble
if I don't do anything...
Reindeer!
Dalton-san! Please be alive!
Could they have been swallowed
by this avalanche?
Wait!
I guess I'll do muscle training or
something to warm my body up for now.
Chopper, go out to sea some day.
Ahhhh! Wapol-sama!
If you do, you'll understand very
well how small your problems are.
Ahh!
Those brats sure are quick.
We're here! We've finally returned
to my country, the Drum Kingdom!
Ahhhhh!
This island that you were born on
is like this compared to the world.
Doctor... Doctor...
I don't like it... girl...
What?
Really?
Are you tempting the reindeer without
my permission while I'm not here?
No, it's smaller! Like this! It's true!
Doctor...
Oh? Do I need permission
to make a move on a man?
Humph, having watchmen
as if they're a military...
What on earth were they thinking,
shooting at us...?
No, you don't. If you wanna
take him, go right ahead.
Your future lies beyond that sea!
Hm?
But it won't be easy.
He has a scar in his heart...
Oh, my dear Drum Island!
Great nature that towers majestically!
The good times passed in the
twinkling of an eye... And...
It's a big scar that
even I can't cure...
Chess, is the castle all right?
The moment he was born into this world,
Yes sir. It's in a good shape,
just as we left it, Wapol-sama.
his group and even his
parents abandoned him...
What?
because he had a blue nose.
Then on to the castle!
Let's go back to the castle!
The time to bid farewell...
He always walked at the very back
of the group all by himself...
I'm done being a pirate!
I'm going back to being a king!
comes for everyone...
even though he was a new-born child...
Now, go forth, Robson!
And one day, he ate a devil
fruit and was treated
It took one year.
Now your treatment is complete.
Huh?
as a monster even more.
Hey, Robson! What're you
just standing here for?!
Your injuries are
completely healed, Chopper.
Now, get moving already!
Yes! Thank you, Doctor!
Wapol-sama! There's a problem!
Well then... take care...
What's the matter?
What?
The ship...
Now, leave! Live as you please!
I'm busy with my research!
of the pirates from the other day
is at the riverbank!
The reindeers fiercely
pressured him to leave.
What?! Those bastards...
Hang in there. We're almost there.
He was no longer an ordinary
reindeer in any way.
I no longer have any moral
obligation to take care of you!
Why are those Straw Hats in my country?!
Don't you die on me!
Nami, are you cold?
Hang in there just a little longer.
How dare they just come waltzing in
here when they said they didn't know!
Still, he wanted friends...
Doctor! I'll never cause you
any trouble! Please let me in!
So he went down to a village,
as a human this time.
Listen. Hold this. Stay here
and wait for me a little longer.
I'll massage your shoulders everyday!
I'll make you tea and clean the house!
Go flying!
Hey... what's that creature?
Does he realize what I had
to go through after that?!
But his figure wasn't
exactly human, either.
Please! Let me stay!
Hey! Go over there and
kill them all already!
For some reason,
his nose stayed blue, too.
I don't have any friends!
I have no place to go!
Well, actually, the ship is empty!
It must be a yeti!
What?!
It's dangerous!
Get the children inside quickly!
We don't where they went!
Do you wanna be executed?!
Doctor! Doctor!
I'm sorry, Wapol-sama.
A gun! Bring me a gun!
Shoot him to death!
Please forgive this clumsy subordinate.
You damn monster!
Doctor! Doctor!
Hmm... Chess, Kuromarimo...
Go away!
The two of us inspected the
footprints coming out from the ship.
Chopper!
It looks like they headed to Big Horn.
Look at this, Doctor.
I'm injured. Hey, Doctor!
I see... You guys're geniuses.
Look at this!
Then we'll first fire a salute in Big Horn
to celebrate the restoration
of the Drum Kingdom!
Oh, it was you guys.
Why... Doctor?
He didn't know what was wrong.
No wonder I thought
it was an awful syrup.
Go... to the sea! Go anywhere!
Nor did he know what to blame...
They'll never get away with this!
Don't ever come back here!
Who are you talking about?
You damn monster!
Idiot! Of course them!
What?! What did you say...?!
Them meaning...?
He just wanted friends,
yet he was called a monster...
They've already left this town?!
And just a moment ago?
You said some Straw Hats
are going up the mountain
to the castle right now.
He was no longer a reindeer...
For crying out loud!
She healed my sickness earlier.
Then this is what happened!
He wasn't a human, either...
They have a huge grudge against
us over what happened between us,
He's lived all alone like that...
Are you looking for
the doctor, Dalton-san?
so they caused an avalanche
on that snow mountain.
Forgive me, Chopper!
We've got an urgent case.
Do you know where she went?
Can you guys heal the scar in his heart?
Oh no! That's what happened?
If you're looking for Dr. Kureha,
someone said she headed to Gyasta.
Then, this avalanche was their doing...
Hey, Luffy. Look at that door at
the front entrance. It's wide open.
Let's go! We'll follow
them on the snow mountain!
Gyasta?
Where is it?
I'll teach them a lesson
about battling in the snow!
With Big Horn being the middle,
it's in the other direction from this town.
Hm?
I'm gonna... die...
We passed each other, too?!
No wonder it's cold.
It's a town where ice-skating is popular.
In any case, let's close this door.
--Well, it's got nothing to do with this.
Yeah, you will...
We made it...
--Oh...
--Well, it's got nothing to do with this.
With it open like this, there's no difference
between outside and inside the castle.
--Oh...
--And we didn't ask, either!
Tell me! How many more days do I have?
--Calm down, Usopp-san!
--And we didn't ask, either!
--Yes ma'am.
Hey! Stop it! Don't touch that door!
--In any case, let's head there.
--Yes ma'am.
Oh? If you're asking me
to examine you, I refuse.
Now that we've come this far,
we haven't a moment to lose.
You don't have the money to pay my fee.
Huh?
Yeah, you're right.
Never mind what he says.
Let's close it, or we'll freeze to death.
Dalton-san...!
Doctor...
Tell me!
True.
There you are...
Hey! Didn't I tell you to... stop it?!
Aren't you supposed to stand watch today?
You can't kill a person
with a tranquilizer gun!
What's the matter?! What's going on?
How did you get injured so badly?!
What's with him? Why is he angry?
All the watchmen except me...
I'll tell you. You'll die at 5 pm
on the 10th day from today.
were killed...
You won't have to suffer any more.
What?!
Suddenly... a submarine
sailboat appeared...
Hey Luffy. Come over here.
10 days... That'll be enough...
Hm?
In 2 days... In 2 days, I'll complete the
research I've continued for 30 years...
and they killed everyone...!
Who do you mean by "they"?
Calm down and explain.
I will... make cherry blossoms
bloom in this country!
Look up there.
Hm...?
Dalton-san! Help!
Cherry blossoms? So the research
you've continued for 30 years
Ah!
Doctorine...
The antibodies are responding.
We're not strong enough...
If we don't do anything...
was about making cherry blossoms bloom?
Yeah, I figured that much.
What's going on?
They're baby snowbirds.
Well, if we close the door, they'll fall...
The miracle cherry blossoms that
saved you, a master thief, long ago?
Then, what's the cause? Explain.
So it's them?
It's Wapol! Wapol came back!
That's why they can't close it...
That's right!
Kestia...
What?
What did he just say?!
That's right. Kestia.
Wapol?!
You're a fool. This is a winter island
where it's bitter cold year around.
Is that true?!
You attend the girl.
Cherry blossoms won't bloom here.
Okay.
Hey! Dalton-san!
They will! I was a hopeless
thug and dying,
but I lived on and was able to
have a profound change of heart.
It's cold!
Hold on a sec...
Every human in this world can be saved!
I'll settle this...!
What is it?
Ah! Wasn't he speaking earlier?!
I don't intend to bring about justice...
I'd like to prove it here in Drum,
the land where I was born!
Well, come to think of it, I sort of
remember him standing on two legs.
since you and I are both equally guilty!
Listen. What you're trying to do
isn't medical science or any science.
I will definitely get you there.
He's a monster!
Even if the cherry blossoms bloom,
it will do nothing to human bodies.
Don't die...
Wh... What the heck is that?
He's walking on two legs...
Just wait... Wapol!
both of you...
Hiriluk!
He's a reindeer...
He's fluffy...
He's short...
He becomes big...
There they are!
Who are you?
And he's a monster!
Please look at that, Wapol-sama!
We found them!
Chopper! We're alike. So I will
at least teach you before I die...
Hold it, brat!
Those damn bunnies...
have really done it...!
How dare you do
many rude things to me!
I'll beat you up!
that there's nothing
impossible in this world...
This can't be happening...
Hey, Sanji. What's the matter?
What the heck is going on?
and that you can do anything, too!
But the story of these two
doesn't have a happy ending...
Hey... we're gonna run, Luffy...
What a cool guy! He's interesting!
What? Run? Where to?
Sanji! Let's have him join us!
Doesn't matter where! Someplace far!
I'll show you...
the miracle cherry blossoms!
An avalanche is coming!
The world is awfully big
so even if there is treasure somewhere,
Even this sleepless town
has dozed off for now
the odds are astronomical
So relying on dumb luck
won't get you anywhere
From today forth,
something's going to change
So even,
if someone stops me or
laughs at me from the shadows
I'm sure I can start fresh,
since I'm not alone
the ship will continue forward
Bon voyage!
Forget about them!
I know I'm a fool,
but I gotta go
Just by having you by my side,
I feel I can become strong
The crazier the dream,
the cooler the ambition
I wonder how far I can go,
towards the place that leads to the future
I know I'm a fool,
but I'm gonna fight
The farther the sea,
the more heavenly it surely is
Off in the distance it shines,
encompassing the world
Do everything you can,
and you'll get a little nearer to any horizon
Before dawn
Nami! Did you see the reindeer?
Boy, that was close!
I'm glad I'm still alive.
Hey wait, reindeer!
Doctor! Where's the doctor?!
Hey, Luffy. Are you really
listening to-- Hey, where'd he go?!
Don't run away, meat!
Geez, you guys! Cut it out already!
Luffy, hurry! We need
to get as high up as we can!
Suddenly hitting an avalanche in this cold...
I must've run out of luck.
Hold on, Nami-san! I'll cook a
nutritious reindeer dish right away!
Geez... I wonder if he's chasing
Tony-kun again... He's refusing!
Well, it's not that we're
not trying to eat him.
Ahhh! They're following us!
But this is a sort of
winter swimming, I guess.
Chopper has had lots of
hardships in his life.
I don't care about the food.
I just want some peace and quiet.
That's not true! Are you stupid?!
What on earth is happening
on the mountain?
I wonder if Dalton-san is okay.
Can he take on Wapol and his men alone?
Huh? Wasn't that reindeer speaking?
I see...
I've decided to make him join us
and become our friend!
I wonder if Luffy-san
and the others are okay...
But I heard that there was
one person who accepted him.
But that's just what you want, right?!
Come to think of it, I sort of
remember him standing on two legs.
I will definitely get
you there. Nami! Sanji!
Whoa! What's that sword?!
He's pretty good!
Seriously... I wonder if there's
any medicine that works on fools...
Really? What kind of person was that?
So hang in there a little longer.
He's a monster!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Dalton's Resolve!
Wapol's Corps Lands On The Island"
"The Island Where Snow Lives!
Climb The Drum Rockies!"
"An Outcast's Dream!
Hiriluk the Quack!"
"Blue-nosed Reindeer!
Chopper's Secret"
"Hiriluk's Cherry Blossoms
And The Will That Gets Carried On!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!