Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Please help my friend.
Please call a doctor.
I haven't told you my name yet. I'm Dalton.
I'm the captain of the
security squad of this island.
There's only one doctor here, and she
lives in the castle on the mountain.
Why in the heck would she
live someplace like that...?
I'm counting on you, Captain.
I can't believe it!
Like captain, like navigator!
All right, then, let's go...
before Nami dies.
What?! Don't say things
that could jinx us!
So these're Lapins?!
Whoa... Wapol-sama...
What!
We've finally returned...
to our home, Drum Island!
"Are You Happy?
The Doctor Called Witch!"
Ahh...
Nami?
Nami-san!
We have to... hurry to Alabasta...
Never mind that, just rest.
Don't worry about anything right now.
When her own life is at risk...
Nami-san, hang in there
just a little longer.
We have to go to that castle
where the doctor lives.
Get out of our way, you damn bunnies!
They're coming!
Yeah!
Listen, Luffy!
Hm?
Don't you dare fight.
Why not?
Idiot! Whether you attack or get struck,
Nami-san will feel the whole impact too!
She'll die...
What?!
O... Okay! I won't fight!
B-but, what do I do?!
Just dodge! Dodge, dodge, dodge and run!
But don't retreat!
That's hard!
Flanchet Shoot!
Dammit! In this snow,
I can't kick properly!
They're all attacking at once!
Go into the forest!
I'll cover your back!
Okay!
Go left! We'll head to the mountain!
Got it!
We'll shake them off somehow!
It'd take us until night
to finish fighting them!
These snow mountain animals really
are tough! We're at a disadvantage.
Don't!
Idiot! I told you not to attack!
Just leave them to me!
Sorry...
This isn't a joke!
Sanji! We can go up from here!
Good! Go on ahead!
Heave-ho!
--They're coming!
--You don't need to egg them on!
Anyway, run! To the top of the mountain!
It's getting strong...
Nami-san, please be okay...
Who in the world are you guys?
Who are we...?
It's too reckless for just the 6 of you to
travel in the Grand Line without a doctor.
We're pirates. That's why you
guys pointed guns at us, right?
Well, we may be a small group...
but as long as I, Brave Warrior
of the Sea, am with them,
there's no need to worry.
I see...
But it's true that we do want a doctor.
I was hoping to find someone
like that on this island, but...
I didn't expect that there was only one
doctor, a witch living in that castle...
It's a strange combination...
It seems that you guys're different
from the pirates that we think of.
Dalton-san!
Gotta bow...
Oh, hi.
I heard that you're looking for Dr. Kureha?
Yes, that's right, but the
sick person has already...
I heard that she's in our
neighboring town, Cocoaweed, right now.
What?!
Then they passed each other?!
Hey, owner. We've had enough already!
Your kid's voice is so loud
that I can't stand it!
Ah, I'm sorry.
Hey, Tamachibi, what's wrong?
Does it hurt somewhere?
If you just keep crying,
I won't know what's wrong.
You're disturbing customers.
Tamachibi! Say something!
If you don't stop crying,
I'll lock you out!
--It's the witch!
--Shh! She can her you!
--Scary...
She's with that creepy monster again...
Hey! That's enough!
Well well... What a mean father...
If a child keeps crying, he's signaling
that something's wrong with his body.
Stay there, Chopper.
Sorry to interrupt...
Dr...
Are you kids happy?
Dr. Kureha!
My secret to staying young?
No! We didn't ask that!
I still can't believe
she's a 140 year old hag...
I'm still 139!
Shall I make it better?
Hm?! Make what better?
He isn't sick or anything.
Are you... a doctor?
Well then, shall we go, Chopper?
Wait!
I'm sorry. It was my mistake.
Since I heard that the doctor
came down the mountain yesterday,
I thought she wouldn't
come down for a while.
Don't worry about it.
It's not your fault.
The issue here is Luffy and
Sanji's abnormal physical strength.
Even if we go after them
in the snow mountain now,
we probably won't be able
to catch up with them.
If the witch is in the
town called Cocoaweed,
we should ask her to go back
to the castle immediately.
Yes, you're right.
We have no other choice.
Forgive us...
What?
Forgive this country that doesn't
even have enough doctors...
N-no... It's not something
you should apologize for.
She's right.
Let's hurry!
My hands... hurt...
Your hands, huh...? I see...
Then, how about now?
My leg hurts!
See? You forgot that
your hands hurt, right?
What'd you do?!
Are you happy? You're happy?
Good! Be good and quiet.
Hey!
Don't yell. I just touched his leg lightly.
I heard a terrible noise.
He's got pains in his hands and legs.
He doesn't seem to have a fever,
but the swelling on his leg
is due to purulent inflammation.
It's pretty bad.
The bone has been infected.
Chopper, give me antibiotics.
Doctor... will my son be...
The key to cure this disease
is the initial treatment.
Don't worry. He'll be cured...
although he almost died...
What?! Almost died...?!
I'm going to do a little
operation on you, so be patient.
Hey, can't you at least use anesthesia?
Here is the shot.
Don't be reckless!
Well then... since my
medicine works well,
this is it for the treatment.
All you have to do is make sure he rests
well and keep his legs bandaged tight.
Yeah...
Once you immobilize his legs,
cool them well. Got that?
About the fee, well... I'm almost
out of trash bags and toilet paper.
Also all the plum wine and
the food you have... And...
I'll take 50% of this restaurant's assets.
What?!
Chopper... take them to our sled.
Wha...?! Hey, that's outrageous!
Half of the assets?!
Hey, owner! Don't be fooled!
That's a rip-off!
It must be!
He almost died?! Wasn't he really
just crying because he fell?!
How dare you abuse your
position as a doctor!
He's right!
You're a terrible person!
Don't take advantage of
people's weakness, you witch!
Stop it, Chopper. It's just the
blabbering of a bunch of kids.
Old lady...
I feel a lot better.
Thank you!
Oh...? I got a good tip.
I'll reduce the fee to 49%.
I'll pay you. Thank you.
Ahh...! Hey, kid.
Hm?
Don't forget... the happiness
you feel right now, okay?
Okay!
It's ice-cold!
My body is becoming numb...
it's like I'm trapped in ice!
Seems like I've still
got a long way to go.
If I suppress my 'self', even fire should
be cool and ice should be lukewarm.
Hey, Karoo! Come along with me!
This is an ideal way to strengthen
your inexperienced body!
I didn't expect to see this many fish.
I guess I'll go for another dip.
Are they coming?
No, they aren't.
All right! Looks like we lost them.
No... not yet.
Hm?
They're persistent!
What're they doing?
Are they irritated because they're hungry?
No...
Hold on a sec...
Don't tell me... they're...!
You... Who are you?
You don't look like an ordinary villager.
The way you speak... sounds to me
like someone from the military.
I was... a subordinate of...
the ex-King, Wapol...
What?!
I was the captain of this country's
security squad since the previous king.
However, when the king died...
and his son, Wapol, became the king,
this country changed.
Oh, yeah! I've thought of an
interesting law today again!
I'll exile all the doctors!
What?!
Exile them?!
Doctors?!
That's right. I'll keep just 20 superior
doctors and make them my private doctors.
I christen them the "Twenty MDs"!
The "Twenty MDs"?!
That's right, the "Twenty MDs."
We'll exile the other doctors!
That's our great Wapol-sama!
That's a wonderful idea!
No...! If you do such a thing,
who'll see our people when they get sick?!
You think their sickness
has anything to do with me?
Those who want to see a doctor will
have to prostrate themselves before me!
There's no one whose family
members don't get sick.
There'll be no one who can go
against me in this country!
Am I a genius or what?!
Then those who became
sick had no choice
but to ask for Wapol's mercy
in order to see the Twenty MDs?
Yes, and pay excessive medical fees...
It's the same as ruling the country by
taking the citizens' lives hostage...
That's not governing...! It's a crime...
Just as I thought... There's no mistake...
Ahhh... dammit! I got carried
away and swam too long!
Where am I? Where's the ship?
Geez... I can't tell where
I am with all this snow!
Ahhh! I'm saved!
Hey, old lady! Sorry to bother you,
but will you take me
to the nearby village?
Huh?
What're you doing showing your
belly in this damn cold weather?
What a weird old lady...
Hm?
Be careful what you say.
I'm still in the youthful 130s!
Let's go, Chopper. We don't have
time to bother with a weirdo.
Wait, you hag!
What the hell was that
stupid old hag's problem?!
Whoa, it's cold...
Damn! I'll be in trouble
if I don't do anything...
I guess I'll do muscle training or
something to warm my body up for now.
We're here! We've finally returned
to my country, the Drum Kingdom!
Humph, having watchmen
as if they're a military...
What on earth were they thinking,
shooting at us...?
Hm?
Oh, my dear Drum Island!
Great nature that towers majestically!
Chess, is the castle all right?
Yes sir. It's in a good shape,
just as we left it, Wapol-sama.
Then on to the castle!
Let's go back to the castle!
I'm done being a pirate!
I'm going back to being a king!
Now, go forth, Robson!
Huh?
Hey, Robson! What're you
just standing here for?!
Now, get moving already!
Wapol-sama! There's a problem!
What's the matter?
The ship...
of the pirates from the other day
is at the riverbank!
What?! Those bastards...
Why are those Straw Hats in my country?!
How dare they just come waltzing in
here when they said they didn't know!
Go flying!
Does he realize what I had
to go through after that?!
Hey! Go over there and
kill them all already!
Well, actually, the ship is empty!
What?!
We don't where they went!
Do you wanna be executed?!
I'm sorry, Wapol-sama.
Please forgive this clumsy subordinate.
Hmm... Chess, Kuromarimo...
The two of us inspected the
footprints coming out from the ship.
It looks like they headed to Big Horn.
I see... You guys're geniuses.
Then we'll first fire a salute in Big Horn
to celebrate the restoration
of the Drum Kingdom!
What?! What did you say...?!
They've already left this town?!
And just a moment ago?
For crying out loud!
She healed my sickness earlier.
Are you looking for
the doctor, Dalton-san?
We've got an urgent case.
Do you know where she went?
If you're looking for Dr. Kureha,
someone said she headed to Gyasta.
Gyasta?
Where is it?
With Big Horn being the middle,
it's in the other direction from this town.
We passed each other, too?!
It's a town where ice-skating is popular.
--Well, it's got nothing to do with this.
--Oh...
--And we didn't ask, either!
--Calm down, Usopp-san!
--Yes ma'am.
--In any case, let's head there.
Now that we've come this far,
we haven't a moment to lose.
Yeah, you're right.
Dalton-san...!
There you are...
Aren't you supposed to stand watch today?
What's the matter?! What's going on?
How did you get injured so badly?!
All the watchmen except me...
were killed...
What?!
Suddenly... a submarine
sailboat appeared...
and they killed everyone...!
Who do you mean by "they"?
Calm down and explain.
Dalton-san! Help!
We're not strong enough...
If we don't do anything...
What's going on?
So it's them?
It's Wapol! Wapol came back!
What did he just say?!
Wapol?!
Is that true?!
Hey! Dalton-san!
I'll settle this...!
I don't intend to bring about justice...
since you and I are both equally guilty!
Just wait... Wapol!
Those damn bunnies...
have really done it...!
This can't be happening...
Hey, Sanji. What's the matter?
What the heck is going on?
Hey... we're gonna run, Luffy...
What? Run? Where to?
Doesn't matter where! Someplace far!
An avalanche is coming!
The world is awfully big
so even if there is treasure somewhere,
the odds are astronomical
So relying on dumb luck
won't get you anywhere
So even,
if someone stops me or
laughs at me from the shadows
the ship will continue forward
Bon voyage!
Forget about them!
I know I'm a fool,
but I gotta go
The crazier the dream,
the cooler the ambition
I know I'm a fool,
but I'm gonna fight
The farther the sea,
the more heavenly it surely is
Do everything you can,
and you'll get a little nearer to any horizon
Doctor! Where's the doctor?!
Luffy, hurry! We need
to get as high up as we can!
Ahhh! They're following us!
I wonder if Dalton-san is okay.
Can he take on Wapol and his men alone?
Whoa! What's that sword?!
He's pretty good!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Dalton's Resolve!
Wapol's Corps Lands On The Island"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!