kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
There is a place that I want to go with you
susumiyuku kouro nara
The sea route that we take
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
crushes my helpless heart
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
I'm wanting you
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Close your eyes and listen carefully
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
Let's look for your answer
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
There is a place I have to return to with you
boku tachi wa eien ni
We will be forever
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole
Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy finally found Sanji
headed for the Whole Cake Chateau.
But Sanji rejected his
friends' offer to regroup.
Be sure to come back, Sanji!
Without you, I...
I can't become the King of the Pirates!!
Luffy promised to stay where he was
waiting for Sanji,
but an army to avenge Sweet General Cracker
was organized at the Whole Cake Chateau
and started marching towards Luffy.
Let's have a nice wedding tomorrow!
Yes, let's.
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU IN PRIVATE LATER
Oh, no-ju...
Oh, no-ju!!
I'm not gonna go anywhere!
Luffy...
Luffy! Please! Hide yourself at least!
It's okay to get away from
here just for a while!
No!
Sanji might come while I'm gone!
You guys, back up a little!
Don't do it, Luffy! It's impossible!
Don't you know whose territory we're in?!
I promised him...
...that I'd be here waiting!
"The End of the Adventure!
Sanji's Resolute Proposal!"
Just as I thought, Mama is serious-ju!
It's impossible for just the three of us
to fight those soldiers!
You guys should run away now!
What?
No, Luffy!
Go!
If you're sure it's all right-ju!
Are you Straw Hat Luffy?!
Yeah.
I'm amazed that you didn't run away!
I bet your legs were shaking
so much you couldn't move!
I know he's got allies!
There was a big tree.
Oh my!
It doesn't matter.
It does matter!
There's no way that a weakling of the
Worst Generation could've beaten
the Sweet General alone!
Those who laid their hands on Big Bro Cracker
are all our targets for revenge!
We know that you guys came to this island
with your allies!
Spit out where they are!
Shut up.
Huh?
I said "Shut up"!
Don't try to act strong!
I'm the one who beat the biscuit guy!
Bring it on!
All right!
We're gonna crush you up!
Go!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Whip!
...Bazooka!
Hold him down!
Let's run away now-ju!
No, wait!
I don't wanna get involved
in a fight like that-ju!
You led Luffy and the others to this island?
I'm sorry!
I promised them that I'd bring Sanji-san
to the southwest coast.
But I couldn't keep my word
and now they're in danger because of me.
I see.
I was wondering how they made it through
the sea under so much surveillance.
Now I understand. But...
...I wouldn't have gone to the coast anyway.
If you're worried about the invitation,
it'll be alright if I take the blame!
If you attend the wedding, that'll be it!
Since Mama is so used to political marriages,
she puts bracelets on brides and grooms who are likely to escape.
If you try to get off of
the island with them...
They'll explode.
Your mom has the key to them.
If you wanna get it, you have
to defeat the Big Mom Pirates.
Don't tell me Mama has already...
Yeah, she's already made those
arrangements and in the first place...
I don't have a single ally around me.
Even though we're related by blood...
This is what they do.
Did your real family hurt you like that?
Yeah.
How could they...
It seems like I'm a failure to them
and they can't stand my existence.
I've never even once thought
that I was happy to be born royal.
That's why I set out to sea...
...to find a place I
wasn't even sure existed.
But...
...if I resist the marriage,
my friends and I will be all dead.
On top of that,
they'll kill my father figure in the East Blue
who I'm deeply indebted to!
Wherever I look, I have no way out.
So...
I decided to stop resisting!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Axe!
How hard is it to take out just one guy?!
Don't push your luck-fa!
Cream Monster!
What's this?!
Ouch!
That's the power of fresh
cream's sweetness-fa!
When the sweet cream sweetens,
your whole body will be burned-fa.
Oh, damn!
Straw Hat!
Go to hell!
Gust Sword!
Who is it?!
Nami!
Don't just stand there!
The next one's gonna come!
Yeah!
We knew he had allies.
Kingbaum, you betrayed us.
You got it all wrong-ju!
Luffy!
Let's go back, Kingbaum!
It can't be helped-ju!
Shut up.
But there are only three.
Knock them down at once!
Bring it on!
No more playing tag. Just give up already!
Chobro!
What?!
Carrot! We're done running!
It's far from over!
I'm not your enemy-ju!
What's the matter, Chess Peacekeepers?
The Chess Peacekeepers are slowing down.
This works on the Peacekeepers, too!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
Cream Monster!
That cream thing again!
Luffy!
Give up already-fa!
On the condition that I accept this marriage,
I want Big Mom to let my friends go.
They're going after Luffy and the others.
I'm sorry!
My mother put you in such
a difficult position!
Stop!
It's not your fault!
But...
Until 13 years ago, I was in hell.
I just came right back there again.
I should be happy to have been away from here
as long as 13 years.
The people who let me
polish my cooking skills
and the friends who I traveled with...
I'm indebted to everyone that I met.
I just wanna go away without hurting anyone.
My adventure ends here.
Do it-fa!
Now!
Luffy!
Don't hesitate!
Thunderbreed...
...Tempo!
There are too many!
Maybe, that'll do!
Hey, don't cry. It makes me feel pathetic!
I'm sorry! But...
I...
Sanji-san!
I won't let your marriage with me be hell!
I'm sorry! What am I saying?!
You're deeply suffering!
The unwanted marriage
should be hell to you too!
How could I say such a thing
when someone's in pain!
I'm ashamed of myself! I'm sorry!
I've only known you for a short time!
There's no way I can fill the hole in your heart!
In the first place, you didn't even say
that you're gonna marry me!
I'm so...
Weather Egg!
It's hit or miss!
Please!
What is that?!
Boom out!
I'll be here waiting!
Even if I get hungry or
spears rain down on me,
I'll stay right here and wait for you!
You're my... salvation.
Sanji-san...
If I'm good enough for you...
Let's get married tomorrow.
Continuing to believe in
Sanji, Luffy keeps fighting.
However, Big Mom's formidable children
show their devilish abilities -
Burning Cream and a creepy World of Books.
Can Luffy hold out against
their tremendously fierce attacks?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"I'll Wait Here! Luffy vs. the Enraged Army!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!