kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro butsukeatta yorokobi mo
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida kawakashita setsunasa mo
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
There is a place that I want to go with you
susumiyuku kouro nara
The sea route that we take
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
crushes my helpless heart
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
I'm wanting you
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the morning when the light comes in
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Close your eyes and listen carefully
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
Let's look for your answer
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
There is a place I have to return to with you
boku tachi wa eien ni
We will be forever
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
To take back Sanji who
was being pressed into a
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
a marriage and left his friends behind,
marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole
Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy and the others infiltrated
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
the Whole Cake Island
Luffy eliminated Sweet General Cracker
in the Seducing Woods
Brook and Pedro who snuck into the Whole Cake Chateau
from a different route,
Luffy clashed with the enraged
army that was organized
Luffy got knocked out by the enraged army
that was organized to avenge Sweet General Cracker,
Big Mom became furious after learning
Cracker, one of the Sweet 3 Generals,
and finally saw Sanji again,
to avenge Sweet General Cracker,
got taken down by Luffy.
started their operation
to get a copy of the Road Ponegliff.
and he and Nami were held captive
in the Whole Cake Chateau.
but Sanji rejected his
friends' offer to regroup.
but he got knocked out and captured.
To avenge him,
She deployed an enraged army on Luffy.
Meanwhile, Brook and Pedro
who snuck into the Whole Cake Chateau...
Be sure to come back, Sanji!
Big Mom talked to them
through a Transponder Snail
Luffy didn't retreat from the spot
where he decided to wait for Sanji
and got furious when she learned
Nami was her runaway daughter Lola's friend.
Without you, I...
Pedro-san, would you be
willing to serve as bait?
and he faced the enraged army
gathering all his strength.
You don't know my other name, do you, baby?
I can't become the King of the Pirates!!
That's exactly what I was thinking.
If you know where she is, tell me.
Bring it on!
Children don't know how indebted they are
to their parents as they say!
Around the same time, Chopper and Carrot
who got caught by Brulee,
Luffy stayed behind to wait for Sanji
Meanwhile, Sanji was with Pudding...
She's a dumb daughter who ran away
rejecting the biggest-ever political marriage!
were about to execute a plan.
and clashed with the enraged army
that was organized to avenge Cracker.
I made sure to get tied up in Heavy Point
It's Soul King!
Meanwhile, in a secret meeting with Pudding,
Sanji revealed what was on his mind.
so I could escape from these
chains instantly by transforming.
If only she had gotten married submissively at that time,
I could've got tremendous power!
The soldiers infused with souls...
Now's the chance!
You're my... salvation.
...will not be able to stay on their feet...
Then Luffy picked a fight with Big Mom
although he was in captivity.
I just wanna go away without hurting anyone.
I'd already have beaten
Kaido, Red-Haired and even Whitebeard,
Sanji-san...
My adventure ends here.
...when they face my
serious shout of the soul!
If I'm good enough for you...
Straw Hat, you're already doomed!
I won't let your marriage with me be hell!
and become...
Meanwhile, in front of Luffy and Nami
...the King of the Pirates by now!
Shut up! If you wanna fight,
show yourself, Big Mom!
who were held captive in
the Whole Cake Chateau,
He learned Pudding's feelings
and made a decision.
Pudding showed up.
If I'm good enough for you...
I'm gonna fight you right here right now!
Listen, there is something
that I have to tell you two.
What a boring story, Big Mom.
Let's get married tomorrow.
Luffy keeps fighting
without knowing Sanji's decision.
Lola didn't marry.
Then Luffy finally got knocked out
in the battle against the enraged army.
"A Fateful Confrontation!
Luffy and Big Mom!"
What is it, Pudding?
You haven't become the King of the Pirates.
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Whip!
I actually...
Hey! Come on, Big Mom!
That's all.
"Invading the Chateau!
Reach the Road Ponegliff!"
Gum-Gum...
Just because you're the Emperor,
don't be cocky!
...Giant Axe!
...was proposed to by Sanji-san.
Show yourself!
I'll win Sanji back!
What?!
I'll fight you!
We're the ones who'll have the last laugh!
A GUEST ROOM WHERE SANJI STAYS
Don't push your luck.
"Goodbye!
Pudding's Tearful Determination!"
At the same time, Brook and Pedro
who snuck into the Whole Cake Chateau,
You're a Rookie who just
entered the New World.
"I'll Wait Here!
Luffy vs. the Enraged Army!"
That's presumptuous of you
to request an audience with me.
were attempting to infiltrate the Treasure Repository
where the Road Ponegliff is kept.
IN THE OUTSKIRTS OF SWEET CITY
Plus, they don't need my help in killing you.
Goodbye!
Gum-Gum...
Sorry - we should never have done this!
...Hawk Gatling!
What's going on-soir?
It made me happy.
I'll be here waiting!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
But...
Hawk Rifle!
Listen carefully, Straw Hat.
...I know Sanji-san is just being nice to me.
Baron Tamago, it's the intruder!
If you give up on Sanji completely,
I'll let you leave alive.
Hustle up!
I'm causing everyone trouble.
Don't let him do whatever he wants!
That's not true...
The intruder's in the other area!
Screw that!
Now, in the pirate Emperor Big Mom's castle...
So don't worry.
Sanji and Pudding's wedding...
I'm not going to marry him.
...is very special to me.
Let's start...
...a special live show!
So sit there quietly
until everything is over.
You bastard!
Listen.
"Shout of the Soul!
Brook and Pedro's Lightning Operation!"
Everyone...
I'm not gonna go anywhere!!
Stay safe.
Straw Hat, if you spoil what
I've been looking forward to,
We're currently searching for the intruder!
A lot of guards have been injured
by the attack on the Treasure Repository!
He's already reached his limit! Attack!
I'll really make you pay for it!
The attacker has explosives!
Luffy!
Thunderbolt...
Don't let your guard down!
...Tempo!
I can't believe they let this happen
the day before the tea party!
Hey, wait, Pudding!
Oh, yeah! Do you remember?
When you ate all the candies
that were made for me,
I can't create big thunderclouds like those.
Luffy.
There he is!
Nami!
you gave me all the treasure
that you got from King Neptune.
But I can use Big Mom's thunderclouds!
I'm glad that you came to.
Goodbye.
I was worried
because you've been passed out all this time.
We have a lot of treasure with us here.
What?
Where's Reiju?
So quick!
I don't know. She left for somewhere earlier.
A GUEST ROOM - THE VINSMOKE FAMILY
There's more to come!
You can have it all!
In compensation for the sweets!
Oh yeah, I remember! Nami!
--Tea
--Green tea
I'm gonna free you now!
--Tea
--Green tea
Which'd you like to have?
Guess what we found in there!
Thanks for all the damage.
How is this possible?!
This won't come off no matter how much I pull!
This is it, intruder!
I'd rather have booze.
What is this?!
What?!
Get down here!
That's useless, Straw Hat.
Wh-What if you had to choose?
Don't say that you want it back!
Tea.
Yes!
It's a legendary treasure box
that was passed down for
Anyway, Father, where will Sanji and
his wife live after they get married?
generations on the Fish-Man Island.
It's the Tamate Box.
I wasn't paying attention.
Of course, in Germa.
I didn't expect that a girl like you could
make such a big lightning strike.
Shoot!
Then, I can take my time and
pay him back for kicking me.
Did you do this?!
I wonder why Neptune let go of it.
Of course! Who else could
do something like this?!
PRISON LIBRARY IN THE WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
The daughter is the key.
It's certainly a national treasure.
I wonder what's in it.
Shoot him down!
Let us out!
If we don't hold her as a hostage,
we don't know what they'll demand hereafter.
Huh? Why would I wanna do that?!
You bastard! I shouldn't be here!
We're dealing with pirates.
I love treasure boxes!
Run!
I see. A hostage, huh?
I gotta get back to that spot
before Sanji comes!
So forget about the candies.
Maybe they want to hold Sanji hostage too
in case something happens, huh?
I'm going to open the Tamate Box in front
of everyone at the tea party tomorrow.
Luffy...
Don't be silly, Niji.
Well, good luck with that.
But you'll never be able to get out of here. Ever!
Even if they do, would killing
Sanji upset us that much?
It's gonna be fun!
It's not gonna be fun! Sanji won't marry!
Where is he now?!
Famous Sword...
He went downstairs to the third floor of Red-Bean Baum Cake,
near the Courtyard!
You're right.
Damn!
Never!
...Shirauo.
It won't be easy to take him down!
Corner him in the garden-soir!
I can't wait...
It's not what you think-ju!
We didn't mean to change sides!
...to live close to Sanji again.
--Oh, yeah! I wanna see Pudding!
--Luffy!
--Roger!
--Clank.
--I need to talk to her! She's my friend!
--Don't mention her!
Amande-sama!
Didn't he come for the Ponegliff?
Huh? Friend?
SANJI'S ROOM
What's wrong?!
May I come in-nasu?
There is a member of the Straw Hats
who can't be located-soir.
Don't be absurd.
Why would the bride be your friend?
Yeah.
Slow Ballad.
Thank you for going shopping.
It's nothing-nasu.
Pedro is bait-bon!
Um, I got some news-nasu.
Luffy!
We're currently holding
Straw Hat and Cat Burglar-nasu.
Stop joking around!
Why don't you shut up a little bit? Slurp.
By the way, girl,
They got Luffy and Nami-san?
I heard you killed Lola.
--Let's close this door!
--Yeah!
What are you talking about?!
She's my friend!
I'll catch you alive soon.
It's okay.
Oh, no!
She gave me the Vivre Card
as a token of friendship!
After me and Pudding-chan's wedding tomorrow,
Ouch...!
Let's eat them! Let's eat them!
I-If you're going to kill
me, d-do it quickly!
they'll be free.
What should we do, Chobro?
I'll put my signature on Mama's Vivre Card,
I made a deal with Big Mom...
It's pointless killing someone quickly.
About this time tomorrow,
I'll gain Germa's military strength
so if you run into trouble,
you can use this to find her.
Now he can't get inside...
When you see her, tell her I'm doing fine.
I cut at the most painful
and tormenting speed.
and we'll all have a delicious wedding cake!
Oh, boy! That was really close.
Thanks, Lola.
What?
Carrot, lend me your ear.
Lola was doing fine.
What?!
My ear?
That's the message she sent.
There, I delivered it.
If you don't run away,
everything will turn out for the best, Sanji.
Listen, we're going to...
She told me that her mother was a pirate
Okay, okay, got it! That's my Chobro!
I can't handle any more soldiers!
but I didn't expect that
it'd be Emperor Big Mom.
I can't believe it, Straw Hat.
And a Mink Man and Soul
King are still rampaging.
What are you whispering about?!
He doesn't seem like
he was fighting Big Bro Cracker all night!
Lola thought that if I showed you
the Vivre Card, you'd help me...
Guys! Attack them already!
There you are, intruder.
Brook!
Screw that!
Sweet General Smoothie and Baron Tamago
went to subdue them,
Go!
Well, there are a lot less than before.
The Chess Peacekeepers aren't that weak!
but they're still struggling to...
Only Pedro-san could've done that!
How could he tear them to pieces like trash!
That's enough.
Mama...
What kind of creature are you?
You're very strange, even for this country.
Can I have my groceries?
Now, bring it on!
Wh-What the...
Yeah, here they are-nasu.
If you're hungry, I can bring you something
like nasu (eggplant).
I agree.
No thanks.
What are you guys doing?!
Those are just reflections!
Mama would be happy.
--Can I use this kitchen?
--What?
I don't need her to be fine.
Luffy!
I want her dead!
What?!
Pudding-chan didn't show up at the dinner table
so I'll cook something for her.
If you know where she is, tell me.
I'm gonna take care of you!
I'll send an assassin right away to kill her!
I see-nasu.
Cream Monster!
I'm surprised by the fact
she still thinks that we're family!
I'm worried about her.
TREASURE REPOSITORY
Children don't know how indebted they are
to their parents as they say!
Get him!
Yes, I heard that she
still doesn't feel well...
Ouch!
She's a dumb daughter who ran away
rejecting the biggest-ever political marriage!
--Clank.
--Hey, Baron Tamago!
MIRRO-WORLD
Ouch!
"MIRRO-WORLD" - BRULEE'S HOUSE
Smoothie-sama!
Oh, ow, ow, ow...
You were right. There's another one.
How interesting, reindeer!
You became muscular.
I won't forgive her!
Yes!
That one is bait like you said.
Security is very tight as I thought!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
But...
Oh, Pedro-san, there they are!
Oh, no!
Damn Pedro! He created a big mess!
One of you can have me as a wife!
Especially you! Do you wanna marry me?
Brulee-sama!
The two Ponegliffs and...
We let him get into the Treasure Repository
and lock the door.
Absalom is gonna marry me!
...the Road Ponegliff!
Sorry. It's my fault.
I think you two will make a great couple
and I wanted to help!
Electrical Luna!
--Let's do it, Carrot!
--Uh-huh!
But there is only one entrance
to the Treasure Repository.
It is said that...
What?! Really?!
Even if he can steal the treasure,
it's impossible for him to run from Smoothie-sama.
...there are about 30 Ponegliffs,
inscribed stone blocks...
TREASURE REPOSITORY IN THE WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
I'm here to save you, my friend!
...that have never broken for
over hundreds of years...
Th-This reindeer's strong!
As long as you guard the door closely,
there won't be a problem-dezvous.
I'm gonna run over and kill you!
Lola!
...which exist in the whole world-bon!
Lola! I'm so happy to see you again!
You're right. Count on me.
If he beats the guards inside and comes out,
I'll kill him. Is that okay?
It's just for you because
you and I are like sisters.
What?!
And only nine of those 30 Ponegliffs
have specific kinds of information.
The rabbit can fight too! Be careful!
No, the man inside is probably a skeleton-bon.
Mama would love to have that strange beast.
Lola...
If you take those to the
last island - Raftel,
Watch out, Carrot!
If only...
Beat him but don't kill!
...she had gotten married
submissively at that time,
the stones will reveal the
truth of this world-soir.
Got it.
I could've got tremendous power!
I'd already have beaten
Kaido, Red-Haired and even Whitebeard,
Please don't do it, Sweet
General Smoothie-sama!
Please! Please!
Huh?! Chobro!
and become...
Have mercy on me, Smoothie-sama!
Pedro-san told me.
What? What?!
...the King of the Pirates by now!
BISHOP　　　　　　　 PAWN
Through Big Mom's ability, you are all infused with human souls.
KNIGHT　　　　　　　　 　ROOK
KING　　　QUEEN
Smoothie-sama...
What's going on?!
That means you Chess Peacekeepers are...
This is bad! I gotta tell Mama!
Now, what should I do with them?
...driven by soul!
But, in order to go to the last
island Raftel, you need...
Lola's friend, Cat Burglar Nami.
Leave it to me, Chobro!
Oh, no!
Choo-choo! Choo-choo!
Choo-choo and choo-choo and choo!
How powerful!
...four Road Ponegliffs, the red stones!
I'll make you cough up where she is.
Idiots! No one can catch up with me
once I start running...
Wait a sec!
It's not tuned yet!
Including the one delivered by Jimbei
the other day...
Tear him apart!
Gum-Gum...
Ouch!
A present for you. I got it on my way here.
Garchu!
Oh no.
That's not gonna happen, Straw Hat!
What a boring story, Big Mom.
What?!
It's from me too!
Elephant Gun!
Guess who?
...we Big Mom Pirates have two Ponegliffs
What?!
No, no, no... Let go of me!
This is it, you damn skeleton!
Lola didn't marry.
Not yet!
and one Road Ponegliff.
I said "Let go of me"!
Oh, please!
That means three stones in total-vous plaît.
You haven't become the King of the Pirates.
W-W-W-W-Wait, wait!
Okay.
What?
I-I'm gonna crash!
I know how important those three stones are.
That's all.
I can't stop!
Please wait!!
There!
Luffy...
But...
I'm gonna pick a fight with you again!
Yes! We beat Brulee's group!
ONE OF THE SWEET 3 GENERALS OF
THE BIG MOM PIRATES MINISTER OF JUICE
...why did you suddenly
tighten security now, Tamago?
Just because you're the Emperor,
don't be cocky!
I got nothing to do until the tea party.
C. SMOOTHIE - 14TH DAUGHTER OF THE CHARLOTTE FAMILY
BOUNTY: 932 MILLION BERRIES
I'll win Sanji back!
Chobro!
So I don't mind guarding them.
What?
We're the ones who'll have the last laugh!
All right!
Now we can use Brulee's ability
to jump in and out of the mirrors!
Yes, thank you-renaissance.
What is this place?
Let's travel in this dimension
across the island to look for everyone!
There is a former pirate captain
who came to this island about five years ago.
What happened?!
Soul King's shout of the soul...
He is a Mink Ponegliff thief
and it seems that...
...is still far from over!
he has snuck onto this island again-souffle.
Baby!
Oh, no!
You don't know my other name, do you, baby?
His life was spared because his
compatriot Pekoms begged for his life.
Why did he return?
You're in...
...the World of Books!
Pedro!
A GUEST ROOM WHERE SANJI IS STAYING
If you get all four red Road Ponegliffs,
you can reach Raftel.
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow...
It's Soul King!
Please...
Everyone, withdraw safely.
Luffy, what is he doing?
Ow, ow, ow...
In other words, that's the road
to become the King of the Pirates!
Here's the finale!
TREASURE REPOSITORY IN THE WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
That's a quest worthy of
the Four Emperors-bon.
The Chess Peacekeepers!
The soldiers infused with souls...
Now, all that's left is those who can't
be destroyed by the shout of the soul!
What are these?!
For the sake of Mama, we put our lives on
the line to protect these stones-chocolat!
...will not be able to stay on their feet...
...when they face my serious shout of the soul!
Get off of me!
Baby.
OUTSIDE OF THE TREASURE REPOSITORY
IN THE WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
Luffy!
Go!
Brook.
SPIRITS CELLAR
What? They increased security?
Yes, they were calling her
Sweet General Smoothie.
She is a beautiful woman with long legs.
Sweet General... That
means she's a top officer!
I thought so.
No wonder she looked strong.
You'd better check the Courtyard of the castle-nasu.
It's hopeless.
They now have perfect security.
What's the matter?
Isn't it odd? No one's here.
They have good soil
so they grow beautiful flowers there-nasu.
There's no chance even at night.
I thought the Chess Peacekeepers were here.
I'll show you-nasu.
Our last hope may vanished
when Tamago noticed I was here.
You're right.
No, I know where it is.
I-It's cold!
Luffy and the others are having difficulty.
What do you need flowers for, Sanji-sama?
H-He disappeared!
It'd be nice if we could
complete our mission smoothly.
I was touched by what you said the other day.
What's going on?
Pudding-chan!
Song of Scratches...
What the...?!
In order for Luffy-san to become the
Blizzard Slice!
King of the Pirates, he'll need
the Road Ponegliff someday.
"MIRRO-WORLD" - BRULEE'S HOUSE
The intruder's around here somewhere!
I've already cut you.
Look for him!
What?
But it won't be so easy to come back here.
I guess this is it.
Rather, we have to clash with them head-on
if we really want to come back.
There he is!
Please! Don't do it!
The keys!
Damn you!
Cream Monster!
Damn you...
I don't think we all could
make it this far again.
I don't wanna be eaten!
How dare you do that!
That's right.
Given this, maybe now is the rare chance.
We found the intruder!
He's heading that way!
I've got to do it!
You guys are hungry, aren't you?
Luffy!
--Keep him away!
--Clank.
We're starving!
--Surround and catch him!
--Yes, sir!
But if we invade, both of us will get killed!
Let us eat already, Brulee-sama!
Let's go!
Swallow Banderole!
Who is Baron Tamago's target?
It's me.
That looks crocodelicious...
I asked my partner to risk his life
before I came here!
Stop it!
This will be the finest game dish ever.
Pedro-san, would you be
willing to serve as bait?
Don't eat me!
Stop!
--Let me down!
--Just give up already.
That's exactly what I was thinking.
I have to get what I need...
Luffy! Get down!
...or I'll lose face!
Nami!
Brulee dug her own grave.
I knew it wasn't gonna be that easy.
Watch out!
Who said that I don't have a face to lose!
What? What?!
"MIRRO-WORLD" - BRULEE'S HOUSE
Cream...
What's going on-soir?
...A face to lose! ...A face to lose!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring,
ring, ring... Clank.
Boil, boil, boil! Boil, boil, boil!
...Punch!
...A face to lose!
Boil, boil! Boil, boil!
Luffy!
Baron Tamago, it's the intruder!
The Carrot that got caught with me at that time
was a fake one.
The Tiger Mink is here!
Guards, can you hear me?
Chobro, help! It's hot!
No, he's a Jaguar Mink!
No...
Answer!
It's a frog that has been transformed into
a mirror image of Carrot by Brulee's ability.
I need to hurry up.
Pedro... He was already in
the castle as I thought.
I'll give you one more-fa!
Stop whining, you brat!
I don't eat humans.
We can't handle him...
These are the keys.
But the Minks could be edible so I gotta try.
The real Carrot...
Pedro-san! I'll do it!
Don't eat me! I'm not delicious!
Smoothie-sama!
...is in the attic.
Let Carrot go, Brulee!
Open the door!
Stop! Don't eat me!
She's not a real rabbit!
Of course, she's not delicious!
P-Please wait, Smoothie-sama!
Please! Help! Chobro!
What? You think so? Then,
maybe I shouldn't try.
He's right! I'm too tough
and stinky and disgusting!
I thought I was summoned for security.
But...
Help me!
Seems like it's more fun to be out there.
I'm not gonna let her go.
Keep your mouth shut, you odd reindeer.
What? Please wait!
But I feel bad for the frog.
You'll join Mama's collection
of strange beasts!
There are 16 enemies in this house.
C-Collection of strange beasts?
That's right. So just sit there quietly.
The most troubling ones are
Randolph, Aristocroc,
the mysterious chimney man Diesel,
Look what he's done...
and... Brulee.
My only chance to get them off-guard...
Okay! We managed to get to this point.
Damn Pedro...
Don't let them get away!
Get him cornered!
...is the moment they drop the fake Carrot.
I made sure to get tied up in Heavy Point
Randolph, cut the rope.
so I could escape from these
chains instantly by transforming.
WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
I guess all the guards inside got beaten...
Oh, dammit, dammit!
Okay.
Probably.
I'm giving Chopper trouble!
Pedro will be mad at me!
Luffy and the others will be spared.
Big Mom promised me.
This is the only entrance.
Prepare to attack.
Your pretty face will get scalded!
It's been six hours since I used Monster
Point yesterday so I can use it already!
As long as I get married,
Baratie will be okay.
Yes, ma'am!
She'll go crazy once she gets dropped.
I gotta put the lid on right away.
When the delicious soup is ready,
dump her in!
Of course, it's hard to say goodbye to my friends
but then, no one will die!
Here we go, Brulee-sama!
Boil, boil, boil! Boil, boil, boil!
That's what matters most!
Why am I not happy?
She's gonna be delicious! Let's try!
If I look gloomy like this, Pudding-chan
who is the only hope will be troubled.
Boil, boil, boil! Boil,
boil, boil! Puff, puff!
Now! Carrot!
Chobro!
Uh-huh!
I...
Now's the chance!
You want some?
Winding up and...
Boil, boil, boil! Boil, boil, boil!
Sanji-san!
No.
I won't let your marriage with me be hell!
I'm here to ask you a favor.
Boil, boil! Boil, boil!
Is the intruder in there?!
What is it? I'm listening.
Mama! You didn't have to come!
I can handle it!
If I make her worry,
I'll be the lowest scum!
I'm going to marry Pudding-chan.
Get out of my way, Smoothie!
WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU LIBRARY
What are you doing, Randolph?
Don't make a lovely girl like her sad!
Be my usual self!
In return,
Here it is.
Brulee-sama,
someone came down from the attic!
Yes! I'm a romantic cook!
I want you to let my friends go!
What?!
There is always an infinite
universe in a book.
Pudding-chan!
There are two rabbit girls!
Pudding-chan!!
Look. This is a super-rare, man-eating lion
which has a human face.
Who are you?
I'll make you happy!
Don't you know whose treasure...
"Manticore."
PUDDING'S ROOM
...you're messing with?!
Good!
It's a strange beast escaped
that from Impel Down
Big Sis Lola's?
Calm down! Hey!
Yes. The girl had a Vivre Card
during the attack of
Blackbeard two years ago.
Don't tell me it's...
Hurry up, Carrot!
and the Homies in the maze-like
forest were intimidated.
Count on me, Chobro!
Loincloth, loincloth!
It moved!
Big Mom!
And this one is my pride and joy!
By the way, Pudding-sama, the dress you
chose yesterday was rejected by Mama.
What is she gonna do?
I'm begging you.
Oh? What a strange creature!
Okay.
Randolph! Just cut the rope!
Isn't it beautiful?
Please wear the dress Mama chose tomorrow.
What? R-Really?!
What a shame. But it's living in the book.
O-Okay!
Yes, really.
Mama has planned out everything
after the wedding too.
Those animals in books will never age.
When it comes to reasonable deals,
I can be reasonable myself!
Also...
That's how it's supposed to be because
what's in a book should never change.
I'll let all members of the Straw Hats
Carrot!
Pudding-sama, it's still raining in the yard.
who are your friends for now
leave this island alive!
Pudding-sama?
Help!
Take this!
That's odd.
I promise.
The books in this library contain
rare creatures from across the world.
Pudding, as long as you do as
I told you, you'll be alright.
What?!
If you drop the idea of running away
and marry without resistance,
Oh, no! You can't do that! No!
Cool!
You're like a doll, Pudding.
That's what my son Montd'Or is capable of.
Nooo!
I'll turn a blind eye to everything!
Recently, we got a Centaur from Punk Hazard
Good girl, Pudding.
--Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
-Brulee-sama!
I appreciate it!
I'll make Pudding-chan happy at any cost!
and a Griffon that we
found in the South Blue.
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow...
I even got something like this!
Ouch! Ouch!!
A Long-Limbs human!
Oh, you're so in love with my daughter!
I'm glad!
Help!
All right!
Let me out!
Even a human?
She's not gonna kill me.
After all, we're family.
Rumble!
Big Mom.
--Brulee-sama!
--This is bad news!
Since I stepped into this country,
I've seen a wide variety of races.
You are...
I wanna choose who I'm gonna marry myself!
Listen.
The things that the Straw Hats have done to me
are normally inexcusable.
Of course! Because that's the kind of country
that Totto Land aspires to becoming...
But there is one race that I don't see
and I couldn't stop thinking about it.
They destroyed the maze-like forest
and took down one of our Sweet Generals.
If they're here, we would know.
You damn brat!
You speak like you're something.
Time to start our countercharge!
On top of that, at the Fish-Man Island,
not only did they eat my candies...
It's the Giant Tribe!
The intruder is passing through
the hallway near the Courtyard!
They say that all races are living in this country
but I haven't seen even one of them.
...but they also picked a fight with me.
PRISON LIBRARY
But that's okay. For today.
Corner him from both sides!
All I've seen is people who
are bigger than the others.
I don't mind hearing some nonsense.
But now, the top priority is
you and Pudding's marriage.
You bastard! Let me out!
All hands, shields up!
It's nothing compared to
how much fun I'll have tomorrow.
If things go well,
Hey! Are you listening?!
about this time tomorrow,
I'll gain Germa's military strength
Clank.
Warty-head!
Hey, wait, Big Mom!
Oh, yeah?
Charge!
and we'll all have a delicious wedding cake!
Just let me out already!
I guess you haven't happened to run into one.
You're so funny!
Oh, I just didn't get a chance.
Shut up-fa! Keep your mouth shut!
You've got to be kidding!
Mama!
How could you pick a fight with Mama
in this castle?!
Damn! I'm gonna destroy this thing!
If you don't run away,
everything will turn out for the best, Sanji.
Almost there!
Shut up! Bring it on, you fools!
It's no use! Just sit quietly-fa!
Yeah!
What do you want?
Ma... Mama... Ma, we... we... we have
brought those... those two here!
Alright! We cornered him in the Courtyard!
Lola...
Damn! What are they up to?
Enough with that-fa!
Okay.
It's been a while-bon!
Will you excuse me? I'm very busy today.
The weather isn't so nice
but have a good afternoon.
THE COURTYARD IN THE WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
Hey, big brothers and sisters!
Thank you! Thank you!
Oh, this is unusual.
Anglaise, what's up?
Baron Tamago!
What's the matter?
What do you need, Pudding?
W-Well, I got nervous.
Captain Pedro of the Nox Pirates!
They're the real Germa 66.
Pudding?
We have an intrudee at the
Treasure Room! Thank you!
Although you're my enemy,
I've already given you due respect.
Especially Ichiji-sama and Reiju-sama
were just as cool as I thought they'd be.
--Hey! Pudding! Get us outta here! We got caught!
--No, Luffy!
Luffy...
You mean an intruder, Anglaise?
We finally got him.
He gave us a lot of trouble.
Every time we face each other,
Shut up! How foolish you are
to be influenced by a comic strip!
That's it!
The other guys are listening too!
I'm not gonna brush my teeth today!
Thank you!
We avenged our big brother!
this scar on the left eye that we both have
itches-toi-et-moi.
What brought you to a place like this-fa?
The important thing isn't how they look.
And everyone's chasing after the intrudee!
Thank you! Thank you!
Five years ago, you really held on to life.
Brother Opera, can I talk to Luffy-kun and Nami-chan
in there for a minute?
Not the day before the tea party.
Those two?
Why are you doing the same again?
Luffy-kun? Yeah, go ahead-fa.
No problem. Tamago is on guard.
Yeah, I've already closed it.
Kingbaum...
You don't have much time
left to live-soufflé.
Hey, open it for her-fa!
Smoothie's there too. Slurp.
Yes, sir.
I hope so.
Let's see, what page was it?
If Mama finds out about this,
it's gonna be a problem!
Page 55-fa.
That day, Mama took...
Let me put a bookmark here.
51.
QUEEN'S CHAMBER
53.
Is that...!
Aren't you mad, Mama?
55.
...50 years of your life-bon!
A Vivre Card.
There they are.
I was wondering why the Chess Peacekeepers,
who are Homies, couldn't fight like usual
Pudding...
These two? I like the look on their faces.
Just because that squirt
picked a fight with me?
You two...
Lick!
and how you guys could
make it out of the forest.
No way, Zeus! Think about it!
Yes, I know that.
Hey, Pudding!
How long are you gonna keep us like this?!
We went to the coast!
Now I understand.
Let me take a shower!
Stop it! Pudding will be in trouble!
Why did you have Mama's Vivre Card?
My body is covered in sticky syrup!
Tomorrow, I'll gain Germa's power
and even the Tamate Box
I'm not...
It says "Lola."
Sounds like it's so sweet, Candy-chan. Lick!
PEROSPERO - ELDEST SON
OF THE CHARLOTTE FAMILY
You got beaten up.
What?!
Lola?! Did you steal it from her?!
Luffy-kun.
Oh, man! That runaway girl got killed?!
Nami-chan.
...expecting to go home alive!
Here comes Mama.
I'll eat the most delicious
wedding cake ever, too
I'm sure my brothers and sisters
did horrible things to you.
--Lola!
--What were her last words?!
What?
It's not like that!
She's my friend! She gave it to me!
Right?
I'm sorry!
I doubt it.
Huh?
That's right
A Transponder Snail?!
Tell Mama that yourself.
No, don't...
Unfortunately,
we were ordered to catch you guys alive. Let's go.
If I think of tomorrow
I can tolerate anything
I couldn't go to the coast where we promised to meet either...
I'm really sorry!
Oh, look at that.
That's okay. Raise your head, please.
It's been a while, Straw Hat Luffy!
Most of the Chess Peacekeepers
have been beaten.
How could I get mad?
You finally made it this far.
Why is she talking in whispers?
Is this Big Mom?
Tomorrow is going to be a great day
Let me out! I gotta go back!
Listen, there is something
that I have to tell you two.
A happy day
I'm gonna get out of here
even if I have to destroy everything!
Oh? I received a signal. Mama!
Whoa-whoa, you've still
got that kind of spirit.
What is it, Pudding?
They say that an intruder is creating a
ruckus around the Treasure Repository!
I'll...
Since you didn't bring the whole crew,
An intruder?
I thought you'd forgotten what you said to me
on the Fish-Man Island.
Wedding cake, Queen of the cakes
Luffy!
I actually...
Wedding cake
I'll kick your ass all over the New World
You bastard...
...was proposed to by Sanji-san.
--Hey, Luffy!
--I...
and make the Fish-Man Island my territory!
What?!
Wait...
...gotta go!
Don't tell me he's going for the Tamate Box!
Yeah, I'll kick your ass someday!
I can't stay in a place like this forever!
But we just came to take
Sanji back this time!
Please stop!
Who is it?!
Enough with bluffing!
Don't let him get away!
You're just gonna rot
away helplessly in there.
I'll... wait... here...
Straw Hat, you're already doomed!
Damn!
Catch him!
Oh, yeah! Okay!
Hustle up!
For Sanji...
Don't let him do whatever he wants!
Shut up!
If you wanna fight, show yourself, Big Mom!
Hey, Luffy!
The intruder's in the other area!
Now, in the pirate Emperor
Big Mom's castle...
I got an idea to get us out of here!
Luffy!!
What?
I'm gonna fight you right here right now!
Let's go!
Sanji!
Let's start...
...a special live show!
Pedro engages in a duel
against his fated rival Baron Tamago!
With lightning speed, Pedro leads the
Emperor's soldiers around by the nose!
Brook and Pedro finally start creating a ruckus
in the Emperor's headquarters!
The Straw Hats start a counterattack!
Luffy and Nami have been
captured in an inescapable cell
The captured Chopper and Carrot launch a coordinated attack
to pull them out of the fire!
in a book kept deep inside
the Emperor's chateau!
And his horrific past involving
Big Mom is revealed!
Meanwhile, Luffy comes
under hard questioning by
Brook puts on a live show
at the Emperor's castle!
Meanwhile, Brook and Pedro are trying
to sneak past
Big Mom but he challenges her head-on!
When it's all revealed,
Meanwhile, Pudding whose heart is wavering over her marriage
with Sanji tells Luffy and Nami her firm determination!
No one can stop these two,
Big Mom erupts into volcanic rage and
things are in a tense touch-and-go situation!
Pedro's lightning sword attack,
along with his determination, strikes the Baron!
Sweet General Smoothie and heavy security
fighting to get the Road Ponegliff
at the risk of their lives!
in order to perform an
unprecedented safecracking!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Fateful Confrontation! Luffy and Big Mom!"
"Goodbye! Pudding's Tearful Determination!"
"Shout of the Soul! Brook and
Pedro's Lightning Operation!"
"The History of the Left Eye!
Pedro vs. Baron Tamago!"
"Invading the Chateau!
Reach the Road Ponegliff!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!