My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole
Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy clashed with the enraged
army that was organized
to avenge Sweet General Cracker,
but he got knocked out and captured.
Meanwhile, Brook and Pedro
who snuck into the Whole Cake Chateau...
Pedro-san, would you be
willing to serve as bait?
That's exactly what I was thinking.
Around the same time, Chopper and Carrot
who got caught by Brulee,
were about to execute a plan.
I made sure to get tied up in Heavy Point
so I could escape from these
chains instantly by transforming.
Now's the chance!
Then Luffy picked a fight with Big Mom
although he was in captivity.
Straw Hat, you're already doomed!
Shut up! If you wanna fight,
show yourself, Big Mom!
I'm gonna fight you right here right now!
"A Fateful Confrontation!
Luffy and Big Mom!"
Hey! Come on, Big Mom!
Show yourself!
I'll fight you!
Don't push your luck.
You're a Rookie who just
entered the New World.
That's presumptuous of you
to request an audience with me.
Plus, they don't need my help in killing you.
Listen carefully, Straw Hat.
If you give up on Sanji completely,
I'll let you leave alive.
Screw that!
Sanji and Pudding's wedding...
...is very special to me.
So sit there quietly
until everything is over.
Straw Hat, if you spoil what
I've been looking forward to,
I'll really make you pay for it!
Oh, yeah! Do you remember?
When you ate all the candies
that were made for me,
you gave me all the treasure
that you got from King Neptune.
We have a lot of treasure with us here.
You can have it all!
In compensation for the sweets!
Guess what we found in there!
Don't say that you want it back!
It's a legendary treasure box
that was passed down for
generations on the Fish-Man Island.
It's the Tamate Box.
I wonder why Neptune let go of it.
It's certainly a national treasure.
I wonder what's in it.
I love treasure boxes!
So forget about the candies.
I'm going to open the Tamate Box in front
of everyone at the tea party tomorrow.
It's gonna be fun!
It's not gonna be fun! Sanji won't marry!
Damn!
--Oh, yeah! I wanna see Pudding!
--Luffy!
--I need to talk to her! She's my friend!
--Don't mention her!
Huh? Friend?
Don't be absurd.
Why would the bride be your friend?
Luffy!
Stop joking around!
Why don't you shut up a little bit? Slurp.
By the way, girl,
I heard you killed Lola.
What are you talking about?!
She's my friend!
She gave me the Vivre Card
as a token of friendship!
I'll put my signature on Mama's Vivre Card,
so if you run into trouble,
you can use this to find her.
When you see her, tell her I'm doing fine.
Thanks, Lola.
Lola was doing fine.
That's the message she sent.
There, I delivered it.
She told me that her mother was a pirate
but I didn't expect that
it'd be Emperor Big Mom.
Lola thought that if I showed you
the Vivre Card, you'd help me...
Screw that!
Mama...
I don't need her to be fine.
I want her dead!
What?!
If you know where she is, tell me.
I'll send an assassin right away to kill her!
I'm surprised by the fact
she still thinks that we're family!
Children don't know how indebted they are
to their parents as they say!
She's a dumb daughter who ran away
rejecting the biggest-ever political marriage!
I won't forgive her!
One of you can have me as a wife!
Especially you! Do you wanna marry me?
Absalom is gonna marry me!
I think you two will make a great couple
and I wanted to help!
What?! Really?!
I'm here to save you, my friend!
Lola!
Lola! I'm so happy to see you again!
It's just for you because
you and I are like sisters.
Lola...
If only...
...she had gotten married
submissively at that time,
I could've got tremendous power!
I'd already have beaten
Kaido, Red-Haired and even Whitebeard,
and become...
...the King of the Pirates by now!
Lola's friend, Cat Burglar Nami.
I'll make you cough up where she is.
What a boring story, Big Mom.
Lola didn't marry.
You haven't become the King of the Pirates.
That's all.
Luffy...
I'm gonna pick a fight with you again!
Just because you're the Emperor,
don't be cocky!
I'll win Sanji back!
We're the ones who'll have the last laugh!
A GUEST ROOM WHERE SANJI IS STAYING
Please...
Everyone, withdraw safely.
TREASURE REPOSITORY IN THE WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
What's the matter?
Isn't it odd? No one's here.
I thought the Chess Peacekeepers were here.
You're right.
What the...?!
The intruder's around here somewhere!
Look for him!
I guess this is it.
There he is!
Damn you...
We found the intruder!
He's heading that way!
--Keep him away!
--Clank.
--Surround and catch him!
--Yes, sir!
Let's go!
I knew it wasn't gonna be that easy.
What's going on-soir?
Ring, ring, ring... Ring,
ring, ring... Clank.
Baron Tamago, it's the intruder!
The Tiger Mink is here!
No, he's a Jaguar Mink!
Pedro... He was already in
the castle as I thought.
We can't handle him...
Smoothie-sama!
Open the door!
P-Please wait, Smoothie-sama!
I thought I was summoned for security.
But...
Seems like it's more fun to be out there.
What? Please wait!
Look what he's done...
Damn Pedro...
Don't let them get away!
Get him cornered!
Oh, dammit, dammit!
Luffy and the others will be spared.
Big Mom promised me.
As long as I get married,
Baratie will be okay.
Of course, it's hard to say goodbye to my friends
but then, no one will die!
That's what matters most!
Why am I not happy?
If I look gloomy like this, Pudding-chan
who is the only hope will be troubled.
I...
Sanji-san!
I won't let your marriage with me be hell!
If I make her worry,
I'll be the lowest scum!
Don't make a lovely girl like her sad!
Be my usual self!
Yes! I'm a romantic cook!
Pudding-chan!
Pudding-chan!!
I'll make you happy!
PUDDING'S ROOM
Big Sis Lola's?
Yes. The girl had a Vivre Card
and the Homies in the maze-like
forest were intimidated.
By the way, Pudding-sama, the dress you
chose yesterday was rejected by Mama.
Please wear the dress Mama chose tomorrow.
Mama has planned out everything
after the wedding too.
Also...
Pudding-sama, it's still raining in the yard.
Pudding-sama?
Pudding, as long as you do as
I told you, you'll be alright.
You're like a doll, Pudding.
Good girl, Pudding.
She's not gonna kill me.
After all, we're family.
I wanna choose who I'm gonna marry myself!
You damn brat!
You speak like you're something.
But that's okay. For today.
I don't mind hearing some nonsense.
It's nothing compared to
how much fun I'll have tomorrow.
Clank.
Hey, wait, Big Mom!
You're so funny!
You've got to be kidding!
How could you pick a fight with Mama
in this castle?!
Shut up! Bring it on, you fools!
Lola...
Hey, big brothers and sisters!
Thank you! Thank you!
Anglaise, what's up?
We have an intrudee at the
Treasure Room! Thank you!
You mean an intruder, Anglaise?
That's it!
I'm not gonna brush my teeth today!
Thank you!
And everyone's chasing after the intrudee!
Thank you! Thank you!
Not the day before the tea party.
No problem. Tamago is on guard.
Smoothie's there too. Slurp.
I hope so.
If Mama finds out about this,
it's gonna be a problem!
QUEEN'S CHAMBER
Aren't you mad, Mama?
Just because that squirt
picked a fight with me?
No way, Zeus! Think about it!
Tomorrow, I'll gain Germa's power
and even the Tamate Box
I'll eat the most delicious
wedding cake ever, too
Right?
That's right
If I think of tomorrow
I can tolerate anything
How could I get mad?
Tomorrow is going to be a great day
A happy day
Oh? I received a signal. Mama!
They say that an intruder is creating a
ruckus around the Treasure Repository!
An intruder?
Wedding cake, Queen of the cakes
Wedding cake
Don't tell me he's going for the Tamate Box!
Who is it?!
Don't let him get away!
Catch him!
Hustle up!
Don't let him do whatever he wants!
The intruder's in the other area!
Now, in the pirate Emperor
Big Mom's castle...
Let's start...
...a special live show!
With lightning speed, Pedro leads the
Emperor's soldiers around by the nose!
Brook puts on a live show
at the Emperor's castle!
No one can stop these two,
fighting to get the Road Ponegliff
at the risk of their lives!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Shout of the Soul! Brook and
Pedro's Lightning Operation!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!