My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro butsukeatta yorokobi mo
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida kawakashita setsunasa mo
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
To take back Sanji
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy and the others infiltrated the
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole
Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Whole Cake Island
Luffy was held captive
at the Whole Cake Chateau
Pudding whispered a few words to Luffy and Nami
who were held captive by the Big Mom Pirates.
Brook who snuck into the Whole Cake Chateau
Meanwhile, Sanji learned
Pudding's terrible real character
To obtain a copy of the Road Ponegliff,
Brook snuck into the Treasure Repository
to get a copy of the Road Ponegliff,
and started taking drastic
measures to escape.
and Big Mom's plot to seize Germa's scientific technology
by killing them all.
and got in a deadly fight against Big Mom.
faced Big Mom.
Meanwhile, in order to obtain the Road Ponegliff,
Pedro invaded the Whole Cake Chateau,
If you don't stop,
your hands are gonna tear apart!
Meanwhile, Sanji, determined
to marry Pudding,
Sanji not returning is
the worst thing that could happen?
Everything was a setup.
That's what I'm trying to do!
came to know her true colors
and deadly plan for the wedding.
but Baron Tamago stood in his way.
What?!
I don't think so.
Done!
Do you think no one's gonna die?
No! Don't do it!
They saw each other
for the first time in five years.
It's perfect!
I have no choice!
What kind of fool regards his own death
as part of a plan, young lady?
Is there any other way
to get us out of here?!
Your most recent memories
involving me have been cut.
I'm not...
Isn't it better to have your
arms being torn apart...
Meanwhile, Sanji was learning about
the secret behind his birth from his sister Reiju.
Let's have a joyous wedding tomorrow.
Stop dreaming!
Will I marry that lowlife?!
...than die?!
A captured Luffy ignored Nami's pleas
...expecting to go home alive!
There's no way that you're a failure.
No way!
and continued to try to break free
at the expense of his own arms.
In the world of mirrors, Chopper and Carrot
started their operation to find Sanji.
Our mother protected her child
at the risk of her own life
No way!
and he was born with the spark of humanity.
Five Thousand Brick...
That child is you, Sanji.
...Fist!
She was trying to set us up
from the beginning!
"The History of the Left Eye!
Pedro vs. Baron Tamago!"
That's why you're kinder than everyone else!
What did Sanji ever do to her?!
Dammit!
Jimbei!
I heard you got caught.
I'm glad that you're okay.
Mama's aim was to get your
Army of Clone Soldiers and
Things can't get any worse!
Are you okay?
SWEET CITY
We were all fooled! Sanji, too!
I gotta let him know!
Let's talk later.
Dammit!
scientific technology from the start!
First, do you want to get out of there?
Sanji!
Look after Nami, Jimbei!
We do!!
"Moist Cigarette!
The Night Before Sanji's Wedding!"
Not here!
At the wedding tomorrow,
Sanji!
you Vinsmokes...
Oh, there's a ghost!
"Sora's Wish!
Germa's Failure - Sanji!"
"To Reach Sanji!
Luffy's Vengeful Hell-bent Dash!"
will all be eliminated!
Not here either.
WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
Look for Straw Hat!
Hey! Are you still gonna do that?!
Which way did he go?!
I'll do it as many times as I have to!
MEDICAL CENTER
He got out of the underground Prison Library
and ran through the first floor already!
"The Undaunted Soul!
Brook vs. Big Mom!"
Oh, my!
She was bleeding badly
but the wound already started healing.
--All hands, go to the second floor!
--Yes, sir!
She has unbelievably hard skin
and strong recuperative power.
No, no, no!
They're getting thinner than before!
Sanji!
WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU - SECOND FLOOR
So this is how Germa's modified humans are.
That's what I want!
There he is!
While we're hoping for someone to come help,
Straw Hat Luffy!
Is it farther away?
If she stays in bed, I think
she'll heal enough to attend the tea party.
Where are you?!
Answer if you're there!
You're so unfortunate to have
such a dumb brother.
we'll lose everything
and eventually get killed by Big Mom!
Wake up, Brulee!
Yeah, you really are!
Where is the mirror to the Whole Cake Chateau?
Take him down!
That's so stupid!
I don't wanna die like that!
Oh? It seems like she's gonna pass out soon.
Stay with her all night tonight.
We saw it once before.
Don't get in my way!
Don't forget to notify the Vinsmokes.
Well, she's been bleeding a lot.
Where was it?
If we leave her like this, she'll
be dead before the morning.
I'm sure they're worrying.
Gum-Gum...
Diesel! Don't you know?!
Tear yours apart too!
Yes, sir.
...Pistol!
That'd save us the trouble,
wouldn't it, Pudding?
I'm going to the medical center
on the fourth floor.
How do I know? Dammit!
What?! Are you crazy?! No way!
Then, I'll take care of you too
so quit moaning!
I wonder if Luffy and Nami found Sanji.
There are so many wounded people
across the castle tonight - I don't have time to sleep.
We can't let that happen.
That'll ruin our whole plan.
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
I don't wanna see your arms being torn apart!
Stop!
I hope so.
They said they'd go to Mom's castle, right?
Thank you for your service. Take care.
Don't be so unreasonable!
Guys, get back!
We need her to live until tomorrow.
I'm...
Uh-huh.
As long as we're touching Brulee,
we can jump in and out of the mirrors!
...not a man who dies in a place like this!
--Cadenza-sama!
--I'll take care of him!
No!
I can't let him cause any more trouble!
This dimension is connected to
the mirrors across the Whole Cake Island.
So we can eliminate all of you Vinsmokes
from this world!
He seems like he knows something about Sanji.
We should've reached the castle already.
Brat, don't push your luck!
Brulee! Wake up!
Gee!
Do you forget that you fell
at my brother's feet?!
Anyway, we gotta try to find it ourselves
until she wakes up!
Oh, no. I made a ton like I always do.
You're the guy from that time!
Let's keep going until we find it!
I don't think Pudding-chan
will eat this much.
Now, Big Sister-sama.
Gear Two!
What am I thinking?
You guys will pay for this!
Get out of my way!
It'll give us trouble if you die like this.
Where am I?
Oh, well, if she can't
finish it, I'll eat it.
And it'll give us trouble
if you reveal my ungraceful nature
Why are you still thinking?
as you've just seen.
Sanji!
You've already got your answer.
Whoa! You made a lot!
Stop it, Luffy! What are you thinking?!
I hurt my leg...
Abandon Germa and run away, Sanji.
Sanji-i>san, you're really a good cook.
Do you remember how that happened?
It's no use.
Germa clings to their past glory
and stands for nothing but destruction.
That's what everyone says.
But I can't eat this much.
The world doesn't need us.
When I was walking around the castle,
Why don't you have some too?
If you don't stop,
your hands are gonna tear apart!
What are you...?
I ran into some soldiers who
were going after intruders...
All Big Mom wants is our
scientific technology.
Open your mouth.
That's what I'm trying to do!
Stay calm. It won't take long.
What?!
...and I got involved, maybe?
That'll be nice!
I don't think she's interested in
taking your mentor's life.
It doesn't feel right, does it?
Of course not.
Your father and brothers who treat
the seafaring restaurant as hostage...
Pudding-chan, here I come.
Your memory has been overwritten.
What?
No! Don't do it!
I'm gonna tell you what
really happened to you.
Are you going somewhere-nasu?
I have no choice!
...will all be dead tomorrow.
Is there any other way to get us out of here?!
We deserve that
because we're a group of assassins.
Yes, I'll go and get comforted
by the one-and-only ray of light in this world.
Isn't it better to have your arms being torn apart...
Break these bars already, Jimbei!
I only have a grudge against them
but why do you have to die, too?!
Then do you want this nasu (eggplant)-nasu?
...than die?!
Fish-Man Karate!
Maybe, later.
A little more to go!
There is a bit of humanity left in me
PRISON LIBRARY
Shark Brick Fist!
No, no, no!
They're really gonna break apart!
but I'm our father's accomplice
who was modified not to disobey him.
My hands are dirty too.
I deserve death.
Stop, you silly boy.
This is the power of the Memo-Memo Fruit.
No way!
--What do you want?
--I'm here to see Pudding-chan.
Everyone has a roll of film in their minds
that records memories.
That's what I expected of Montd'Or's book!
--No, silly boy.
--What?
So I gotta tear my arms apart!
Please. You let me through earlier.
IN FRONT OF PUDDING'S ROOM
You have scary experiences and sad memories
Stop it!
I told you it's no use-fa.
No!
Baron Tamago!
No means no, silly boy.
and things that you wanna forget, don't you?
Hold on, Luffy!
Why not?
Pudding-sama is in the middle of something!
There is another way.
Are you okay?
Books can be destroyed by fire.
Cheep!
Dammit!
Are you gonna burn the cage?
Are you sure?!
Something?
You are...
Yes, if you two can get out of there
before you're engulfed in flames.
Are you still trying? Stop!
Maybe, she's changing into pajamas?
Cheep, cheep, cheep.
That call is...
I'm not gonna stop!
That's impossible!
--Then, give this to her.
--What is it?
Is he gonna evolve?
But that's the only way to escape!
I cooked for her.
Into Viscount Hiyoko?!
As you know, we don't have much time.
You cooked?
Viscount Hiyoko?
Yeah, she wasn't looking so good before
Big Sister-sama!
Let me know when you're ready!
so I hope she feels better
even a little by eating...
Cheep! Cheep!
--Alright. Do it!
--That quick?!
That's terrible!
No, silly boy.
Oh, no... Come to my room and lie down.
No, I'm still not ready!
Is that all you can say?!
You ate the Devil Fruit.
Just give this to her!
We're really gonna burn!
BARON TAMAGO WAS REBORN AND
EVOLVES MORE...
I'll kick your butt, silly boy.
Go away, silly boy.
I'm impressed with Germa 66.
Burn it up already!
I should tell...
What are you talking about?!
You'd been shot in the leg but
you still made it that far.
Indeed.
You're uselessly tough!
It's burning up there too!
Big Sister-sama!
VISCOUNT HIYOKO
It's almost there!
She's right!
Oh, no! We're gonna die!
Viscount Hiyoko's sword technique
which surpasses Baron Tamago's.
That's terrible!
Now, I paste strips of memories
I'm starting to hear things too!
Prepare for a taste of it!
from some soldier who's been shot
by a stray bullet here and...
What are you doing up there?
Bring it on!
No! I don't want fire sparks!
Edit!
Alright!
As you can see,
I'm trying to get a copy of the Road Ponegliff.
Done!
It's perfect!
Ouch!
Hurry up! Luffy! Nami!
You're very honest.
Your most recent memories
involving me have been cut.
But you have nowhere to run.
Let's have a joyous wedding tomorrow.
Give up and come down here!
Call the soldiers and
take her to the medical center.
Okay.
TREASURE REPOSITORY
Wait a minute.
We got out!
I think there's a balcony off her room.
TREASURE REPOSITORY
I think I've been through
something like this before...
--Is he for real?
--Are you really gonna fight Mama?
You're quite a man with backbone.
I'm sorry, both of you.
Yes, because I need a copy of that stone.
Yes, my backbone's all I got.
Thanks to you,
I didn't have to rip my arms apart!
Like I said,
I'm gonna take you down
and get a copy of the stone!
You've got balls!
You look so relaxed.
It's raining a lot.
When you face the Emperor, you have no choice
but to turn defiant instead of being nervous.
Come to think of it, we first met...
I like you even more!
I'll definitely add you to my collection.
...in some prison like this.
You're my... salvation.
Oh, do you want to fight me?
Yeah.
Look! They were all captured in the same book
as you two.
Sanji-san...
All right!
Not a single opening.
--Zeus!
--Yes, Mama!
If I'm good enough for you...
Yes, because I haven't fulfilled my mission yet.
The World of Books is as big as your imagination
which means it's infinite.
Your mission?
I'm gonna take you down
Big Mom has so many strong lackeys
like Montd'Or.
and get a copy of the stone!
Let's get married tomorrow.
--Prometheus!
--Yes, Mama!
Thank you, Jimbei!
But why are you here?
But let's do it!
The Sun Pirates that I led are also
affiliated with Big Mom.
Let's pass it through the window.
Maybe, I shouldn't do this.
I'd look like a Peeping Tom.
What?! Is that so?!
Surrender already!
You think I can be beaten so easily?
Oh, but...
Well but we'll become husband and wife
tomorrow.
No way. I'm putting my life on the line!
That means this is...
So even if she's changing...
Yes, this is a rebellion.
I can't go back now!
E-E-Even if she's naked,
it's not gonna be a crime.
I see. Do whatever you want.
Not so fast!
What? Is that okay?
Gavotte Bond en Avant!
At the Fish-Man Island,
you said that you had responsibilities.
I just threw them away.
Someone heard screams
from the Prison Library!
Zeus!
Good. She's fine enough to laugh.
Yes, Mama!
--What's going on?!
--They've already noticed!
They're indeed quick.
ZEUS, A THUNDERCLOUD
There she is. Pudding-chan!
You can't so much as lay a finger on Mama!
First, we have to hide
where they can't find us.
I'm sorry that I don't know when to give up!
Prometheus!
Who is she talking to?
Yes, Mama!
That's a lesson I'll be sure you learn!
--Yeah.
--Let's go then!
Reiju?!
PROMETHEUS, A SUN
Why is she here?
I got hungry all of a sudden.
What does she want from Pudding-chan?
Napoleon!
You get hungry under these circumstances?
Yes, Mama!
Luffy expends three times more energy
than others doing even the simplest things.
NAPOLEON, A BICORNE
It's okay. I'm not saying
that I wanna eat something.
Stop dreaming!
Will I marry that lowlife?!
Your stomach is growling.
Swallow Bond en Avant!
You'll be mine!
Never mind!
No way!
I won't eat anything
other than what you cook!
No way!
COURTYARD ON THE THIRD FLOOR
WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
Even if I get hungry or
spears rain down on me,
I'll stay right here and wait for you!
PEDRO
FORMER CAPTAIN OF THE NOX PIRATES
BOUNTY: 382 MILLION BERRIES
Anyway, Jimbei, thank you!
I'm Mama's favorite.
Especially because of my acting skills.
Soul King. Do you wanna stop
fighting and surrender now?
I actually...
BARON TAMAGO
KNIGHT OF THE BIG MOM PIRATES
BOUNTY: 429 MILLION BERRIES
She cares for me so much these days
to the extent that I get annoyed.
...was proposed to by Sanji-san.
No way.
I still have an ace up my sleeve.
It's too easy for me to fool a guy
to keep her happy.
I'm not going to marry him because...
Straw Hat and Cat Burglar are
already ours-bon.
Do you?
Tricking the Straw Hats
was a piece of cake too.
...that idiot who played right into my hands
and fell for me...
Yes.
I know their weakness.
Give up-bon.
Only my family knows my true nature.
...will be shot dead by my own hand...
So what?
Just like the Chess Peacekeepers,
...in the middle of the wedding.
Then, let's have it out-bon!
I'm sure you three are infused with someone
else's souls through Big Mom's ability!
Things can't get any worse!
We were all fooled! Sanji, too!
I gotta let him know!
Baby!
PRISON LIBRARY
Look after Nami, Jimbei!
This little...!
Luffy, wait!
There are tons of tough enemies in the castle!
Boy, he won't shut up-fa.
And you're not fully recovered!
Don't you remember what happened this morning?!
Yeah, Soul King will rest those souls!
Damn Pudding!
I'm not gonna be defeated this time!
Luffy, stop!
They're really gonna be torn apart!
I'll make her pay...
Your Electro won't work against me
anymore-s'il vous plaît!
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
Interesting! Try it.
Oh, yeah!
...at any cost!
That call is...
Is he gonna evolve into the third form?!
I actually...
Into Count Niwatori?!
How silly.
Do you believe me?
...was proposed to by Sanji-san.
I must take him out now.
Of course, I do.
I know you wouldn't lie to me.
I'm not going to be scared of the Minks-bon!
Stop!
What?!
But I didn't realize
Pudding's real character was this heinous.
Baron Tamago to Viscount Hiyoko
and now, to Count Niwatori!
I guess you're prepared.
It made me happy.
That's right. I'm wearing special tights
that protect me from Electro-feuille.
You noticed something?
But...
As he transforms, he gets stronger!
I wasn't completely sure.
...I know Sanji-san is just being nice to me.
But I thought she seemed a bit too perfect
He ate the Egg-Egg Fruit!
Count Niwatori is the true knight!
You should be terrified!
so I was spying on her on my own.
I'm gonna sort things out with you here!
I'm causing everyone trouble.
When he's transformed,
he'll get strength that you're no match for!
I didn't know that.
That's not true...
For the sake of my dead friend.
Yeah!
Stop him!
If she wasn't planning to marry me from the
beginning and they were gonna kill us all,
So don't worry.
I'm not gonna wait.
That must be the Whole Cake Chateau.
Stop!!
the promise to pardon Luffy and the others
as long as I married her...
Oops.
I'm not going to marry him.
What? What?!
The sweet smell drives me crazy.
That doesn't work.
...doesn't mean anything at all!
No, it doesn't.
Listen.
It's literally a candy country.
No way!
I thought everything would be alright
if I sacrifice myself!
H-How come? Why is this?
I'm not going to marry him because...
What are we gonna do now, Pedro?
Okay, I'll stop.
You're also a good guitar player.
I want you even more.
But that was just a fantasy!
How could I be so naive?!
We're talking about Big Mom.
It's not gonna be easy, Zepo.
...that idiot who played right
into my hands and fell for me...
This is it.
Big Brothers?
Our father is a smart man
but he was being too arrogant in this case.
Hey, did you hear what she said?
Just come here already!
Big Brothers! I thought so!
...will be shot dead by my own hand...
--You-gara...
--Pekoms.
Yeah, come on.
He's dealing with the Emperor.
He should've been more careful.
Big Brother Pedro! Big Brother Zepo!
...in the middle of the wedding.
Garchu!
Nice to have so many soldiers around.
Garchu...
Garchu!
But this is a good opportunity for us.
We're not gonna keep you guys alive either.
Garchu...
You bastard! What are you doing?!
We'll be back right after this...
Why are you here?
I think Germa should be allowed
to be brought down.
Grr! I'm a member of the Big Mom Pirates now.
Get back!
Run!
Let's pretend that we don't know anything
The Big Mom Pirates?!
and let Big Mom do as she has plotted...
What are you two doing here?
Cut the crap! If you attend the tea party,
you're gonna die too, Reiju!
It's nice to be bait.
Don't do it!
It's better you don't know.
Hey, wait, Pudding!
Oh, are you worried for me?
What are you talking about?!
How is it?
Goodbye.
Parting memories are suspect.
We cornered them!
You pathetic rats.
Don't think that you're indebted to me
for helping you once.
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
She was trying to set us up
from the beginning!
We've been ambushed?
Get off of the island with the Straw Hats,
Sanji.
What did Sanji ever do to her?!
Dammit!
Huh?! I can't do that!
Even if I could, what about Baratie?!
You can't go any farther-bon,
Ponegliff thieves!
I'm not going to let anyone
enter the Treasure Repository-bon!
Think about that after you escape.
Let me try!
Sanji! I'm coming now!
If you stay here, we're all gonna die.
Sanji, you can't die.
For our mother's sake!
You'll never pass through here-feuille!
Gum-Gum...
Sanji!!
What do you mean?
There is a memory I can't forget.
...Hawk Gatling!
We're gonna get in there
or our trip to this island will be wasted!
You people are so naive!
Humph! Is that all you got?!
The evil army Germa 66?
Oops! That was too strong.
Get knocked down again!
Stay in your fantasy world,
you dumbasses!
But don't worry, Mama, he's alive.
Whoa-whoa, you went too far.
Straw Hat!
Gum-Gum...
He'll be added to my precious collection.
...Eagle Bazooka!
Come on! Can't you control your strength?
Mama's aim was to get your
Army of Clone Soldiers and
scientific technology from the start!
What are you talking about?
Now, come to me.
Spit it out!
A big fight between our parents.
Where's Sanji?!
I was only a child
so I was wondering why our sweet mother
was that angry.
How obnoxious.
My, you are so defiant.
But it became clear afterwards.
Oh?
No way!
Our mother was pregnant at that time.
You're more merciless than them!
We know you guys won't obey us
and we don't need you.
How hard her skin is!
What? You can still move?
She was strongly against turning you four
into cold killing machines.
Baron Tamago-sama!
The whole Germa Kingdom is anchored
in our territory right now.
--Mama, leave him to me.
--No, to me.
Hey, don't get in my way!
Are you okay, Pedro?
You guys are like flies swarming over a
--Are you serious?!
--Of course I am!
Let me do it!
I'll give him the finishing blow!
I am but not him.
sweet candy which, in this case,
is Sanji's political marriage.
How could you do such a terrible thing?!
Now...
No, you can't kill him!
I can handle it better.
Well done.
The surgery is prepared.
It all went as Mama planned.
Damn you!
I'll go first! Then you go!
Don't do it! They're my children!
Without emotions, they're not humans!
--That's not fair!
--Shut up! Back off!
At the wedding tomorrow,
--No.
--Do as I say!
I want them to be monsters.
Winning wars is all that matters.
you Vinsmokes...
Why should I?
How annoying.
What are you guys doing?
That's enough!
Don't give us trouble.
The re-establishment of the Vinsmoke Family
that once conquered the North Blue.
--He's not pretending, is he?
--I don't know.
will all be eliminated!
Big Mom...
What it takes to accomplish
that goal is strength.
Seems like he's had enough.
I'll give my children the ultimate strength!
Jeez.
--No!
--Take her!
You're an exception!
I have to bring you down myself-s'il vous plaît!
Au... Aubade Coup Droit!
What are you--? No! Let go of me!
Honey! Don't do it!
They're my kids!
No!
You'll lose more than an eye this time!
--Napoleon, you can't cut in!
--That's not fair.
Then the surgery was performed.
I did it because you guys were too slow.
You son of a...!
But our mother later took a drug
to foil our father's plan.
You finally quieted down, Soul King.
IN FRONT OF THE DOOR TO
THE TREASURE REPOSITORY
What?! Another problem?
You've fought enough already.
Are you satisfied?
Yes, ma'am.
Boss Jimbei is in the castle and...
You...
Don't tell me he rose in revolt!
Yes, seems like he did.
Hey, what are you doing, Sora?!
We have one mess after another.
She took a powerful drug that could affect
the manipulated Bloodline Elements.
What shall we do?
Alright, tell all soldiers this.
Are you still trying to get up?
But her desperate action was fruitless.
Germa 66 once conquered
the North Blue by force.
Okay.
Yes, I am.
They found superhuman-like abnormalities
in my brothers' body one after another.
That was close-bon!
The six Vinsmokes at the top
will be riddled with bullets tomorrow.
Tomorrow's mission is
Mama's long-awaited dream.
Why? Why do you wanna get up, Soul King?
Y-Yes.
--What will happen if we fail?
--What?
I can't believe it!
My left eye still itches sometimes-feuille.
The hall will be...
In the worst case, what'll happen?
...covered in red.
I remember the pain of
getting stabbed by you-toilette!
For the stone, Soul King?
--The surgery was a success.
--Great!
Bang.
NITRO THE JELLY
Don't worry! Their genetic blueprints
won't be affected by some drug.
Instead of getting Sanji back,
you want a copy of the stone so much?
I remember too, of course.
RABIAN THE CARPET
What happened that day
remains etched into my left eye!
Yes.
I-I don't even wanna think about it!
Sanji-san is a kind man.
Me neither.
If we bring any more problems
to the moody Mama,
That's why I figured he'd never come back.
But even at the moment of death
it'll affect tomorrow's mission.
Let's play!
But it's strange.
Only Sanji-sama is...
please don't get your blood everywhere
and scream miserably out of control.
You're right!
I don't know what kind of
trap you set for him...
Then what shall we do?
That can't be right.
Let's watch over his growth.
You have to be careful.
A-Are you telling me to lie...
Look what you've done, you thieves.
...but he's extremely kind,
If the wedding cake gets
blood-splattered, Mama will be mad
If you lie to Mama, you'll be put to death.
Big Brothers, why?! Grr!
so once he's determined to sacrifice himself
for someone else, he'll stick to it!
F-Forgive me!
and she'll destroy the place.
You tried to steal something on my island
If there is no problem,
we don't need to tell her anything.
On the other hand, our captain
believes in himself and goes his own way!
and you stabbed Tamago's eyeball.
The .36 Caliber Walker Percussion Pistol.
Don't you think so?
You have to pay.
Y-Yes, I think so!
It's up to those two young men to decide
what's for the best!
The bullets are known as Candy Jackets.
Are you hungry? Hold on.
We're on the fourth floor.
Bring the roulette!
Block up all the paths to this floor!
They are designed to pierce through
armored soldiers behind shields.
Here.
Handle everything in the lower levels.
I see!
You spin it first.
Is it good?
Then you came for the stone
because you have nothing to do?
You realized its power firsthand,
didn't you?
Solve all the problems immediately!
Sanji-sama is feeding birds!
Yes, ma'am. Understood!
No, if worse comes to worst
and Sanji-san decided not to return,
They'll penetrate
all of your metal-enhanced bodies.
He mustn't have that kind of attitude!
If so, it's safer to kill them
than capture them!
Sora!
You kept growing up as a human.
--That's fine. I give you permission!
--Yes, ma'am!
I don't want him to blame himself!
What the...
Big Bro!
I can't wait for tomorrow!
On the other hand, our mother
got weaker and weaker due
I want to tell him there was a great payoff
from this rescue mission!
How'll Sanji look when I, who he trusted
so much, point this gun at him?
to the after effects from the drug.
Then she died because of me?!
So I must get it! The Road Ponegliff!
Don't think that way!
I can't wait to see that!
What a cute creature.
He truly believes that you love him!
You're a skeleton from tip to toe
but you're alive - it's a miracle.
I'm taking 100 years of your life!
I think your idea of "worst" is too light!
Mom...
Reiju! Come here!
Sanji not returning is
the worst thing that could happen?
How you fought was impressive too, Soul King.
Stay with me, Zepo!
How is your dad doing?
That'll be something to see.
The Chess Peacekeepers are
totally afraid of you.
I don't think so.
All he does is train us
and he never plays with us!
Do you think no one's gonna die?
He's just happy that Ichiji, Niji and Yonji
seem to be fine soldiers.
Zepo...
Maybe all of you will die!
You're not known as Soul King for nothing!
Their arch-enemy.
Zepo!!
How'll he look?
What kind of fool regards his own death
as part of a plan, young lady?
I see.
Big Brother Zepo!
Let's see... Maybe like this?
What is that?
But...
Sanji cooked for me!
NAPOLEON, A BICORNE
There wasn't enough for 100 years.
...you can't beat these three.
ZEUS, A THUNDERCLOUD
--That'll be great!
--So funny!
Did he?
PROMETHEUS, A SUN
He only had 30 years to live.
I'm giving them my soul directly.
MIRRO-WORLD
What do you think Sanji told me today?
Or like this?
Since you're his partner,
I need you to pay the rest.
So their souls are in a different class.
St... St... Stop!
P-Pudding-chan...
He said "Get well soon."
Okay! Tickle, tickle, tickle!
What's the matter?
You're not looking.
He's the greatest kid in the world!
Now, give me the remaining 70 years.
Tell us already!
We finished the inspection, Mama!
Carrot's special tickle, tickle, tickle!
Our mother looked truly happy
from the bottom of her heart.
We're talking about your brother.
There is nothing in his clothes!
Stop!
She's right. Why don't you listen?
Sanji got beaten up by Ichiji
and the others again!
Stop tickling me!
There is nothing in this tube either!
Listen!
Just say it! If you don't,
she'll tickle you forever!
Do you wanna know how he proposed?
--In his cane sword...
--And in his cloak...
He's so weak!
Sunny-side Legs!
I'll say it! I'll say it!
I see.
There is nothing!
Okay, Carrot, stop.
Do you want me to call someone?
He didn't steal anything!
That was hilarious!
Okay.
That's okay. Instead, Reiju,
When he pulled off the face pack,
he looked terrible.
come closer.
I'll make you pay for this!
That's good then, Soul King.
Answer our question.
Which mirror leads to the castle?
I'm sorry to suspect you. Pet, pet.
I'm sorry.
With that ugly face,
he said something like this.
I don't think I can make it
until you kids are fully grown.
I don't remember which mirror leads to where!
This is it-bon!
How frustrating. What a humiliation.
"It seems like I'm a failure to them
and they can't stand my existence."
I really wish I could.
That's not the right answer!
The Tamate Box goes without saying,
But...
I mean you gotta ask the mirrors!
But... what?
but I can't let you steal
a copy of the Ponegliff or other stuff either.
You sound exactly like him!
--Ask?
--The mirrors?
Stop doing that funny face!
That's right! Mirrors know
what they're reflecting!
I now understand why she smiled.
It'd be foolish if I allowed you to take it
and let someone reach Raftel again.
It makes me cry. A man's confession.
You're getting tired-bon!
I think she wasn't regretting
what happened to you
What?
Now, give me 70-years' worth of your soul!
"Until 13 years ago, I was in hell."
or her own decision and everything.
I'm not gonna mess up like I did with Roger!
"I just came right back there again."
Please, Mama!
He was like a big brother to me!
Mirror, mirror!
Which one of you is a mirror to the castle?!
Cool! How cool can he be?!
If you take 70 years,
Big Bro Pedro will die too!
He read the stone with his strange ability
that allowed him to hear the voice of all things,
I am!
At the end, with a gloomy face...
Me!
--It's me.
--Me too.
Stop, Pekoms. That's pathetic-bon.
"My adventure ends here."
Mom!!
but we have someone who will eventually
have a similar ability.
I'm begging you, Mama!
They answered!
Pekoms...
--Here! Me too!
--Me too!
I don't give a shit!
Me too!
What are you doing here?
I'm a mirror in Galette-sama's closet.
Stop crying, Pekoms! All right.
Yeah, who gives a shit?
Dad...
I'm a hand mirror in a guest room
on the second floor.
The ones who will reach Raftel next
will be none other than us.
10 years. I'll take off 10 years.
But I was waiting for that exact moment.
I'm a mirror in the ladies' room
on the fourth floor.
Such compassion to lay flowers for the dead
is useless in my own son!
What?!
By showing tears right there,
Do any of you reflect Luffy or Nami
or Brook or Pedro or Sanji?
Mama!
But you took away an eye from Tamago
and that's serious.
I won his heart.
Oh, my dear Pudding!
We were just talking about you.
We're looking for them!
--Who?
--What do they look like?
I'm sorry! But...
I'll take 60 years of your life!
What's wrong?
Has your third eye opened to its true power?
Sanji-sama passed by earlier.
I...
Oh, yeah. They don't know how they look.
Come on, Mama!
You say that every time you see me!
Stop crying!
Aren't you satisfied, Pekoms?
Count on me, Chobro!
I'm good at drawing!
Sanji-san!
I'm not pure blood of the tribe!
What? Drawing?
There's no guarantee
that such power will awaken in me.
I won't let your marriage with me be hell!
W-Well...
Coward!
Crybaby!
Uh-huh!
PRISON LIBRARY
Seriously, men are dumb.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
But you certainly have the rare Three-Eyed
People's blood in your veins.
Stop! No!
You too. Come on.
Hey, Big Mom!
Yes, sir.
If you don't have an awakening
as a Three-Eyed People member,
you're just a creepy-looking girl.
How many years will you spare for this?
But our father's beliefs were
the total opposite of our mother's
Seriously, stop it, Luffy!
You're scaring me! That's enough!
Big Bro!
and he never accepted who you were.
That fool pulled me into his arms tightly
right there
P-Pudding-san?
It's pointless to die here!
The dawn of the new world is coming!
Three-Eyed?
He blamed you for everything that happened
and gave you a hard time.
and said in a forced whisper.
Stop it! Your arms are
gonna really be torn apart!
I have to go back!
No! The fact that we know each other...
I don't care!
I gotta tell Sanji about Pudding's true colors!
Don't ever cook again either!
...must be kept secret!
What are you doing?! Bring it on!
That skeleton man.
That rat!
"You're my salvation.
Let's get married."
I didn't expect him to be here.
Well, he got caught so that's good.
You're so handsome.
"Let's get married."
I'll reduce it to 50 years.
No! I said don't do it! Luffy!
Sanji is a worthless failure!
"Let's get married!"
Go on with your life.
Listen, Mama. It's too embarrassing for me to
talk to you right here so let's go to your room!
Failure! Failure!
Ow, ow, ow... A little more to go!
"Let's get married!"
Stop it! I can't breathe!
Okay, of course. No problem.
He's so reckless-fa.
Hey, girl.
Legs Benedict!
Wait! I don't wanna stay here!
Hey.
Where's Sanji?!
What?! I'm busy now!
That's such a pathetic proposal,
don't you think?!
Let me out!
Don't leave me behind!
I'm scared! I'm gonna die!
Mama told me to get Lola's whereabouts
out of you during the night-fa.
Say it-bon, Pedro!
Why did you come back?!
I want my dad!
Dad! Help! They're gonna kill me!
So just say it now-fa.
I'm asking where he is!
No! I'm not gonna betray my friend!
Oh, so funny!
Okay, I'm gonna torture you-fa.
To this nightmarish island where your partner got killed
and 50 years of your life was taken away!
Who's gonna marry a damn failure like him?!
No! Don't say that so casually!
I'm gonna shoot you with a bowgun
once every five seconds
Mom...
The Straw Hats saved my home country
and I'm indebted to them!
so spill it whenever you feel like it-fa.
I...
Cadenza-sama!
What're you talking about?
That bastard! Attack him!
Can't you at least bring me a decent prince?!
That'll kill me! Don't do it!
Then just come clean-fa.
Screw you, Warty-head!
I'm not gonna let you do that!
I'm gonna get out of this kingdom!
Don't get in my way!
It's gonna be okay, Nami!
I'll break my arms in five seconds!
On top of that,
I believe they'll lead the world to the dawn one day!
That's a relief!
What?!
Sanji, you have to run away.
No! I don't want either!
I'm not gonna stop you.
You can take the key to the iron mask.
Sanji!!
Don't be a baby!
Hey! Is anybody here?
I forgot to mention it but those bracelets...
But can I ask just one last
favor as your father, Sanji?
Oh! Whoa-whoa! I thought you weren't
allowed to enter the castle now!
If you try to get off of this island,
your hands will be blown off!
Pedro!
The dawn of the world will come before long!
There are fights everywhere.
Don't be so hardheaded.
They won't blow up because I swapped them.
Don't ever admit that I'm your father...
I'm sorry, Opera.
...in front of other people!
Is there any other reason
that you can't escape?
In time, the Straw Hats will surpass you-gara people
and change the world!
Five Thousand Brick...
What?!
Get it together, Sanji!
It's a shame that I don't
want anyone to know!
...Fist!
They can't do anything!
Where do you think you are-bon?!
You realize that, don't you?
Outta my way!
It's the Whole Cake Island-bon!
Consider what's important to you!
So what?
What's important to me?
I believe in the Straw Hats.
Stop Straw Hat!
That's why I'm happy to spend
the short remainder of my life...
...for them!
Run!!
Don't look back!!
Join my group!
Even though our mother is no longer with us,
her grace is still there inside of you.
But don't get me wrong.
Be the cook on my pirate ship!
I'm not gonna die here!
Where are you?!
Sorry. Why don't you sleep for a while?
They haven't met their goal on this island yet!
There's no way that you're a failure.
You're a good cook,
so let's be pirates together!
Jimbei!
Our mother protected her child
at the risk of her own life
Oh, Luffy! Nami!
Why are you here?!
You'll never meet...
and he was born with the spark of humanity.
I heard you got caught.
I'm glad that you're okay.
...such great friends...
That child is you, Sanji.
...like them twice!
Let's talk later.
That's why you're kinder than everyone else!
First, do you want to get out of there?
Outta my way!
Sanji!!
We do!!
I'm not gonna die now.
Desperate, all-out attacks!
Brook strikes a blow with everything he's got
The shame of the family.
Cutting ties with his friends,
Sanji looks forward to marrying Pudding, his only hope.
Hellfire burns his bones
and lightning strikes his thin body!
Retrieving Sanji is within sight!
Jimbei and Nami run around inside the castle!
That's what Sanji used to be called
but there was a loving parent's
selfless affection behind it.
and Pedro tries to carry out his mission -
both of their fights come to a thrilling climax!
And, anxious to share the secret plot behind
the wedding, Luffy rushes to find Sanji!
Brooks squares up to
the Emperor's overwhelming strength all by himself!
However, when a dark plot behind the wedding
and a stunning secret are revealed,
His mother Sora's Struggle. And her decision.
Meanwhile, Luffy has broken out and
launches an attack on the Big Mom Pirates to save Sanji!
Luffy fights hard battles against enemy
officers that stand in his way one after another,
His uncompromising thoughts
for Sanji motivate him
Reiju shares the secret behind the
birth of the kindhearted Sanji!
he stands in a daze all alone
as the cold rain pours down his back.
to swing the blade of his soul at Big Mom!
then Reiju who once saved his life shows up!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To Reach Sanji! Luffy's Vengeful Hell-bent Dash!"
"The Chateau in Turmoil! Luffy, to the Rendezvous!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sora's Wish! Germa's Failure - Sanji!"
"The Undaunted Soul! Brook vs. Big Mom!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Moist Cigarlette! The Night Before Sanji's Wedding!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!