kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
There is a place that I want to go with you
susumiyuku kouro nara
The sea route that we take
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy was held captive
at the Whole Cake Chateau
and started taking drastic
measures to escape.
If you don't stop,
your hands are gonna tear apart!
That's what I'm trying to do!
What?!
No! Don't do it!
I have no choice!
Is there any other way
to get us out of here?!
Isn't it better to have your
arms being torn apart...
...than die?!
Are you okay?
Dammit!
"Moist Cigarette!
The Night Before Sanji's Wedding!"
Hey! Are you still gonna do that?!
I'll do it as many times as I have to!
No, no, no!
They're getting thinner than before!
That's what I want!
While we're hoping for someone to come help,
we'll lose everything
and eventually get killed by Big Mom!
That's so stupid!
I don't wanna die like that!
Tear yours apart too!
What?! Are you crazy?! No way!
Then, I'll take care of you too
so quit moaning!
I don't wanna see your arms being torn apart!
Stop!
Don't be so unreasonable!
I'm...
...not a man who dies in a place like this!
No!
Oh, no. I made a ton like I always do.
I don't think Pudding-chan
will eat this much.
What am I thinking?
Oh, well, if she can't
finish it, I'll eat it.
Whoa! You made a lot!
Sanji-i>san, you're really a good cook.
That's what everyone says.
But I can't eat this much.
Why don't you have some too?
Open your mouth.
That'll be nice!
Pudding-chan, here I come.
Are you going somewhere-nasu?
Yes, I'll go and get comforted
by the one-and-only ray of light in this world.
Then do you want this nasu (eggplant)-nasu?
Maybe, later.
Stop, you silly boy.
--What do you want?
--I'm here to see Pudding-chan.
--No, silly boy.
--What?
Please. You let me through earlier.
IN FRONT OF PUDDING'S ROOM
No means no, silly boy.
Why not?
Pudding-sama is in the middle of something!
Something?
Maybe, she's changing into pajamas?
--Then, give this to her.
--What is it?
I cooked for her.
You cooked?
Yeah, she wasn't looking so good before
so I hope she feels better
even a little by eating...
No, silly boy.
Is that all you can say?!
Just give this to her!
I'll kick your butt, silly boy.
Go away, silly boy.
Wait a minute.
I think there's a balcony off her room.
It's raining a lot.
You're my... salvation.
Sanji-san...
If I'm good enough for you...
Let's get married tomorrow.
Let's pass it through the window.
Maybe, I shouldn't do this.
I'd look like a Peeping Tom.
Well but we'll become husband and wife
tomorrow.
So even if she's changing...
E-E-Even if she's naked,
it's not gonna be a crime.
Good. She's fine enough to laugh.
There she is. Pudding-chan!
Who is she talking to?
Reiju?!
Why is she here?
What does she want from Pudding-chan?
Stop dreaming!
Will I marry that lowlife?!
No way!
I'm Mama's favorite.
Especially because of my acting skills.
She cares for me so much these days
to the extent that I get annoyed.
It's too easy for me to fool a guy
to keep her happy.
Tricking the Straw Hats
was a piece of cake too.
Only my family knows my true nature.
PRISON LIBRARY
This little...!
Boy, he won't shut up-fa.
Damn Pudding!
Luffy, stop!
They're really gonna be torn apart!
I'll make her pay...
...at any cost!
I actually...
...was proposed to by Sanji-san.
What?!
It made me happy.
But...
...I know Sanji-san is just being nice to me.
I'm causing everyone trouble.
That's not true...
So don't worry.
I'm not going to marry him.
Listen.
I'm not going to marry him because...
...that idiot who played right
into my hands and fell for me...
...will be shot dead by my own hand...
...in the middle of the wedding.
We're not gonna keep you guys alive either.
Hey, wait, Pudding!
What are you talking about?!
Goodbye.
You pathetic rats.
She was trying to set us up
from the beginning!
What did Sanji ever do to her?!
Dammit!
Sanji! I'm coming now!
Sanji!!
You people are so naive!
The evil army Germa 66?
Stay in your fantasy world,
you dumbasses!
Mama's aim was to get your
Army of Clone Soldiers and
scientific technology from the start!
How obnoxious.
My, you are so defiant.
We know you guys won't obey us
and we don't need you.
The whole Germa Kingdom is anchored
in our territory right now.
You guys are like flies swarming over a
sweet candy which, in this case,
is Sanji's political marriage.
Well done.
It all went as Mama planned.
At the wedding tomorrow,
you Vinsmokes...
will all be eliminated!
Germa 66 once conquered
the North Blue by force.
The six Vinsmokes at the top
will be riddled with bullets tomorrow.
The hall will be...
...covered in red.
Bang.
NITRO THE JELLY
RABIAN THE CARPET
But even at the moment of death
please don't get your blood everywhere
and scream miserably out of control.
You have to be careful.
If the wedding cake gets
blood-splattered, Mama will be mad
and she'll destroy the place.
The .36 Caliber Walker Percussion Pistol.
The bullets are known as Candy Jackets.
They are designed to pierce through
armored soldiers behind shields.
You realized its power firsthand,
didn't you?
They'll penetrate
all of your metal-enhanced bodies.
I can't wait for tomorrow!
How'll Sanji look when I, who he trusted
so much, point this gun at him?
I can't wait to see that!
He truly believes that you love him!
That'll be something to see.
How'll he look?
Let's see... Maybe like this?
--That'll be great!
--So funny!
Or like this?
P-Pudding-chan...
What's the matter?
You're not looking.
We're talking about your brother.
She's right. Why don't you listen?
Listen!
Do you wanna know how he proposed?
That was hilarious!
When he pulled off the face pack,
he looked terrible.
With that ugly face,
he said something like this.
"It seems like I'm a failure to them
and they can't stand my existence."
You sound exactly like him!
Stop doing that funny face!
It makes me cry. A man's confession.
"Until 13 years ago, I was in hell."
"I just came right back there again."
Cool! How cool can he be?!
At the end, with a gloomy face...
"My adventure ends here."
I don't give a shit!
Yeah, who gives a shit?
But I was waiting for that exact moment.
By showing tears right there,
I won his heart.
I'm sorry! But...
I...
Sanji-san!
I won't let your marriage with me be hell!
Seriously, men are dumb.
That fool pulled me into his arms tightly
right there
and said in a forced whisper.
"You're my salvation.
Let's get married."
"Let's get married."
"Let's get married!"
Stop it! I can't breathe!
Hey.
That's such a pathetic proposal,
don't you think?!
Oh, so funny!
Who's gonna marry a damn failure like him?!
Can't you at least bring me a decent prince?!
Sanji!!
Hellfire burns his bones
and lightning strikes his thin body!
Brooks squares up to
the Emperor's overwhelming strength all by himself!
His uncompromising thoughts
for Sanji motivate him
to swing the blade of his soul at Big Mom!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Undaunted Soul! Brook vs. Big Mom!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!