kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
There is a place that I want to go with you
susumiyuku kouro nara
The sea route that we take
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
crushes my helpless heart
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
I'm wanting you
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
Let's look for your answer
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
There is a place I have to return to with you
boku tachi wa eien ni
We will be forever
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
To take back Sanji
who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the
Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Brook who snuck into the Whole Cake Chateau
to get a copy of the Road Ponegliff,
faced Big Mom.
Meanwhile, Sanji, determined
to marry Pudding,
came to know her true colors
and deadly plan for the wedding.
Stop dreaming!
Will I marry that lowlife?!
No way!
She was trying to set us up
from the beginning!
What did Sanji ever do to her?!
Dammit!
Mama's aim was to get your
Army of Clone Soldiers and
scientific technology from the start!
At the wedding tomorrow,
you Vinsmokes...
will all be eliminated!
"The Undaunted Soul!
Brook vs. Big Mom!"
You're so unfortunate to have
such a dumb brother.
Yeah, you really are!
Oh? It seems like she's gonna pass out soon.
Well, she's been bleeding a lot.
If we leave her like this, she'll
be dead before the morning.
That'd save us the trouble,
wouldn't it, Pudding?
We can't let that happen.
That'll ruin our whole plan.
We need her to live until tomorrow.
So we can eliminate all of you Vinsmokes
from this world!
Now, Big Sister-sama.
It'll give us trouble if you die like this.
And it'll give us trouble
if you reveal my ungraceful nature
as you've just seen.
What are you...?
Stay calm. It won't take long.
This is the power of the Memo-Memo Fruit.
Everyone has a roll of film in their minds
that records memories.
You have scary experiences and sad memories
and things that you wanna forget, don't you?
You are...
Big Sister-sama!
That's terrible!
Oh, no... Come to my room and lie down.
I'm impressed with Germa 66.
You'd been shot in the leg but
you still made it that far.
You're uselessly tough!
She's right!
Now, I paste strips of memories
from some soldier who's been shot
by a stray bullet here and...
Edit!
Done!
It's perfect!
Your most recent memories
involving me have been cut.
Let's have a joyous wedding tomorrow.
Call the soldiers and
take her to the medical center.
Okay.
TREASURE REPOSITORY
--Is he for real?
--Are you really gonna fight Mama?
Yes, because I need a copy of that stone.
You've got balls!
Not a single opening.
But let's do it!
Gavotte Bond en Avant!
You can't so much as lay a finger on Mama!
That's a lesson I'll be sure you learn!
Swallow Bond en Avant!
Soul King. Do you wanna stop
fighting and surrender now?
No way.
I still have an ace up my sleeve.
Do you?
Yes.
I know their weakness.
Just like the Chess Peacekeepers,
I'm sure you three are infused with someone
else's souls through Big Mom's ability!
Baby!
Yeah, Soul King will rest those souls!
Interesting! Try it.
Oh, yeah!
Yeah!
Oops.
What? What?!
That doesn't work.
No, it doesn't.
No way!
H-How come? Why is this?
You're also a good guitar player.
I want you even more.
Hey, did you hear what she said?
Just come here already!
Yeah, come on.
We'll be back right after this...
How is it?
Let me try!
Oops! That was too strong.
But don't worry, Mama, he's alive.
Whoa-whoa, you went too far.
He'll be added to my precious collection.
Come on! Can't you control your strength?
Now, come to me.
Oh?
You're more merciless than them!
What? You can still move?
--Mama, leave him to me.
--No, to me.
Hey, don't get in my way!
Let me do it!
I'll give him the finishing blow!
No, you can't kill him!
I can handle it better.
I'll go first! Then you go!
--That's not fair!
--Shut up! Back off!
--No.
--Do as I say!
Why should I?
What are you guys doing?
That's enough!
--Napoleon, you can't cut in!
--That's not fair.
I did it because you guys were too slow.
You finally quieted down, Soul King.
You've fought enough already.
Are you satisfied?
Are you still trying to get up?
Yes, I am.
Why? Why do you wanna get up, Soul King?
For the stone, Soul King?
Instead of getting Sanji back,
you want a copy of the stone so much?
Yes.
Sanji-san is a kind man.
That's why I figured he'd never come back.
I don't know what kind of
trap you set for him...
...but he's extremely kind,
so once he's determined to sacrifice himself
for someone else, he'll stick to it!
On the other hand, our captain
believes in himself and goes his own way!
It's up to those two young men to decide
what's for the best!
I see!
Then you came for the stone
because you have nothing to do?
No, if worse comes to worst
and Sanji-san decided not to return,
I don't want him to blame himself!
I want to tell him there was a great payoff
from this rescue mission!
So I must get it! The Road Ponegliff!
I think your idea of "worst" is too light!
Sanji not returning is
the worst thing that could happen?
I don't think so.
Do you think no one's gonna die?
Maybe all of you will die!
What kind of fool regards his own death
as part of a plan, young lady?
MIRRO-WORLD
St... St... Stop!
Okay! Tickle, tickle, tickle!
Tell us already!
Carrot's special tickle, tickle, tickle!
Stop!
Stop tickling me!
Just say it! If you don't,
she'll tickle you forever!
I'll say it! I'll say it!
Okay, Carrot, stop.
Okay.
I'll make you pay for this!
Answer our question.
Which mirror leads to the castle?
I don't remember which mirror leads to where!
That's not the right answer!
I mean you gotta ask the mirrors!
--Ask?
--The mirrors?
That's right! Mirrors know
what they're reflecting!
What?
Mirror, mirror!
Which one of you is a mirror to the castle?!
I am!
Me!
--It's me.
--Me too.
They answered!
--Here! Me too!
--Me too!
Me too!
I'm a mirror in Galette-sama's closet.
I'm a hand mirror in a guest room
on the second floor.
I'm a mirror in the ladies' room
on the fourth floor.
Do any of you reflect Luffy or Nami
or Brook or Pedro or Sanji?
We're looking for them!
--Who?
--What do they look like?
Sanji-sama passed by earlier.
Oh, yeah. They don't know how they look.
Count on me, Chobro!
I'm good at drawing!
What? Drawing?
Uh-huh!
PRISON LIBRARY
Stop! No!
Seriously, stop it, Luffy!
You're scaring me! That's enough!
Stop it! Your arms are
gonna really be torn apart!
I don't care!
I gotta tell Sanji about Pudding's true colors!
That rat!
No! I said don't do it! Luffy!
Ow, ow, ow... A little more to go!
He's so reckless-fa.
Hey, girl.
What?! I'm busy now!
Mama told me to get Lola's whereabouts
out of you during the night-fa.
So just say it now-fa.
No! I'm not gonna betray my friend!
Okay, I'm gonna torture you-fa.
No! Don't say that so casually!
I'm gonna shoot you with a bowgun
once every five seconds
so spill it whenever you feel like it-fa.
What're you talking about?
That'll kill me! Don't do it!
Then just come clean-fa.
Screw you, Warty-head!
I'm not gonna let you do that!
It's gonna be okay, Nami!
I'll break my arms in five seconds!
What?!
No! I don't want either!
Don't be a baby!
Hey! Is anybody here?
Oh! Whoa-whoa! I thought you weren't
allowed to enter the castle now!
There are fights everywhere.
Don't be so hardheaded.
I'm sorry, Opera.
Five Thousand Brick...
What?!
...Fist!
Sorry. Why don't you sleep for a while?
Jimbei!
Oh, Luffy! Nami!
Why are you here?!
I heard you got caught.
I'm glad that you're okay.
Let's talk later.
First, do you want to get out of there?
We do!!
The shame of the family.
That's what Sanji used to be called
but there was a loving parent's
selfless affection behind it.
His mother Sora's Struggle. And her decision.
Reiju shares the secret behind the
birth of the kindhearted Sanji!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sora's Wish! Germa's Failure - Sanji!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!