My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
There is a place that I want to go with you
susumiyuku kouro nara
The sea route that we take
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
crushes my helpless heart
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
I'm wanting you
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Close your eyes and listen carefully
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
Let's look for your answer
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
There is a place I have to return to with you
boku tachi wa eien ni
We will be forever
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Meanwhile, Sanji learned
Pudding's terrible real character
and Big Mom's plot to seize Germa's scientific technology
by killing them all.
Everything was a setup.
Done!
It's perfect!
Your most recent memories
involving me have been cut.
Let's have a joyous wedding tomorrow.
A captured Luffy ignored Nami's pleas
and continued to try to break free
at the expense of his own arms.
Five Thousand Brick...
...Fist!
Jimbei!
I heard you got caught.
I'm glad that you're okay.
Let's talk later.
First, do you want to get out of there?
We do!!
"Sora's Wish!
Germa's Failure - Sanji!"
WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
MEDICAL CENTER
She was bleeding badly
but the wound already started healing.
She has unbelievably hard skin
and strong recuperative power.
So this is how Germa's modified humans are.
If she stays in bed, I think
she'll heal enough to attend the tea party.
Stay with her all night tonight.
Don't forget to notify the Vinsmokes.
I'm sure they're worrying.
Yes, sir.
I'm going to the medical center
on the fourth floor.
There are so many wounded people
across the castle tonight - I don't have time to sleep.
Thank you for your service. Take care.
Where am I?
Sanji!
I hurt my leg...
Do you remember how that happened?
When I was walking around the castle,
I ran into some soldiers who
were going after intruders...
...and I got involved, maybe?
It doesn't feel right, does it?
Of course not.
Your memory has been overwritten.
What?
I'm gonna tell you what
really happened to you.
Break these bars already, Jimbei!
Fish-Man Karate!
PRISON LIBRARY
Shark Brick Fist!
No way!
That's what I expected of Montd'Or's book!
So I gotta tear my arms apart!
Stop it!
No!
Hold on, Luffy!
There is another way.
Books can be destroyed by fire.
Are you gonna burn the cage?
Are you sure?!
Yes, if you two can get out of there
before you're engulfed in flames.
That's impossible!
But that's the only way to escape!
As you know, we don't have much time.
Let me know when you're ready!
--Alright. Do it!
--That quick?!
No, I'm still not ready!
We're really gonna burn!
Burn it up already!
What are you talking about?!
It's burning up there too!
It's almost there!
Oh, no! We're gonna die!
I'm starting to hear things too!
No! I don't want fire sparks!
Alright!
Ouch!
Hurry up! Luffy! Nami!
We got out!
I think I've been through
something like this before...
I'm sorry, both of you.
Thanks to you,
I didn't have to rip my arms apart!
Come to think of it, we first met...
...in some prison like this.
Yeah.
Look! They were all captured in the same book
as you two.
The World of Books is as big as your imagination
which means it's infinite.
Big Mom has so many strong lackeys
like Montd'Or.
Thank you, Jimbei!
But why are you here?
The Sun Pirates that I led are also
affiliated with Big Mom.
What?! Is that so?!
Oh, but...
That means this is...
Yes, this is a rebellion.
I can't go back now!
What? Is that okay?
At the Fish-Man Island,
you said that you had responsibilities.
I just threw them away.
Someone heard screams
from the Prison Library!
--What's going on?!
--They've already noticed!
They're indeed quick.
First, we have to hide
where they can't find us.
--Yeah.
--Let's go then!
I got hungry all of a sudden.
You get hungry under these circumstances?
Luffy expends three times more energy
than others doing even the simplest things.
It's okay. I'm not saying
that I wanna eat something.
Your stomach is growling.
Never mind!
I won't eat anything
other than what you cook!
Even if I get hungry or
spears rain down on me,
I'll stay right here and wait for you!
Anyway, Jimbei, thank you!
I actually...
...was proposed to by Sanji-san.
I'm not going to marry him because...
...that idiot who played right into my hands
and fell for me...
...will be shot dead by my own hand...
...in the middle of the wedding.
Things can't get any worse!
We were all fooled! Sanji, too!
I gotta let him know!
Look after Nami, Jimbei!
Luffy, wait!
There are tons of tough enemies in the castle!
And you're not fully recovered!
Don't you remember what happened this morning?!
I'm not gonna be defeated this time!
Do you believe me?
Of course, I do.
I know you wouldn't lie to me.
But I didn't realize
Pudding's real character was this heinous.
You noticed something?
I wasn't completely sure.
But I thought she seemed a bit too perfect
so I was spying on her on my own.
I didn't know that.
If she wasn't planning to marry me from the
beginning and they were gonna kill us all,
the promise to pardon Luffy and the others
as long as I married her...
...doesn't mean anything at all!
I thought everything would be alright
if I sacrifice myself!
But that was just a fantasy!
How could I be so naive?!
Our father is a smart man
but he was being too arrogant in this case.
He's dealing with the Emperor.
He should've been more careful.
But this is a good opportunity for us.
I think Germa should be allowed
to be brought down.
Let's pretend that we don't know anything
and let Big Mom do as she has plotted...
Cut the crap! If you attend the tea party,
you're gonna die too, Reiju!
Oh, are you worried for me?
Parting memories are suspect.
Don't think that you're indebted to me
for helping you once.
Get off of the island with the Straw Hats,
Sanji.
Huh?! I can't do that!
Even if I could, what about Baratie?!
Think about that after you escape.
If you stay here, we're all gonna die.
Sanji, you can't die.
For our mother's sake!
What do you mean?
There is a memory I can't forget.
What are you talking about?
A big fight between our parents.
I was only a child
so I was wondering why our sweet mother
was that angry.
But it became clear afterwards.
Our mother was pregnant at that time.
She was strongly against turning you four
into cold killing machines.
--Are you serious?!
--Of course I am!
How could you do such a terrible thing?!
The surgery is prepared.
Don't do it! They're my children!
Without emotions, they're not humans!
I want them to be monsters.
Winning wars is all that matters.
The re-establishment of the Vinsmoke Family
that once conquered the North Blue.
What it takes to accomplish
that goal is strength.
I'll give my children the ultimate strength!
--No!
--Take her!
What are you--? No! Let go of me!
Honey! Don't do it!
They're my kids!
No!
Then the surgery was performed.
But our mother later took a drug
to foil our father's plan.
Hey, what are you doing, Sora?!
She took a powerful drug that could affect
the manipulated Bloodline Elements.
But her desperate action was fruitless.
They found superhuman-like abnormalities
in my brothers' body one after another.
I can't believe it!
--The surgery was a success.
--Great!
Don't worry! Their genetic blueprints
won't be affected by some drug.
Let's play!
But it's strange.
Only Sanji-sama is...
That can't be right.
Let's watch over his growth.
Are you hungry? Hold on.
Here.
Is it good?
Sanji-sama is feeding birds!
He mustn't have that kind of attitude!
Sora!
You kept growing up as a human.
On the other hand, our mother
got weaker and weaker due
to the after effects from the drug.
Then she died because of me?!
Don't think that way!
Mom...
Reiju! Come here!
How is your dad doing?
All he does is train us
and he never plays with us!
He's just happy that Ichiji, Niji and Yonji
seem to be fine soldiers.
I see.
What is that?
Sanji cooked for me!
Did he?
What do you think Sanji told me today?
He said "Get well soon."
He's the greatest kid in the world!
Our mother looked truly happy
from the bottom of her heart.
Sanji got beaten up by Ichiji
and the others again!
He's so weak!
I see.
Do you want me to call someone?
That's okay. Instead, Reiju,
come closer.
I'm sorry.
I don't think I can make it
until you kids are fully grown.
I really wish I could.
But...
But... what?
I now understand why she smiled.
I think she wasn't regretting
what happened to you
or her own decision and everything.
Mom!!
What are you doing here?
Dad...
Such compassion to lay flowers for the dead
is useless in my own son!
Stop crying!
Coward!
Crybaby!
Let's go.
You too. Come on.
Yes, sir.
But our father's beliefs were
the total opposite of our mother's
and he never accepted who you were.
He blamed you for everything that happened
and gave you a hard time.
Don't ever cook again either!
What are you doing?! Bring it on!
Sanji is a worthless failure!
Failure! Failure!
Wait! I don't wanna stay here!
Let me out!
Don't leave me behind!
I'm scared! I'm gonna die!
I want my dad!
Dad! Help! They're gonna kill me!
Mom...
I...
I'm gonna get out of this kingdom!
Don't get in my way!
That's a relief!
I'm not gonna stop you.
You can take the key to the iron mask.
But can I ask just one last
favor as your father, Sanji?
Don't ever admit that I'm your father...
...in front of other people!
It's a shame that I don't
want anyone to know!
You realize that, don't you?
Run!!
Don't look back!!
Even though our mother is no longer with us,
her grace is still there inside of you.
There's no way that you're a failure.
Our mother protected her child
at the risk of her own life
and he was born with the spark of humanity.
That child is you, Sanji.
That's why you're kinder than everyone else!
Desperate, all-out attacks!
Brook strikes a blow with everything he's got
and Pedro tries to carry out his mission -
both of their fights come to a thrilling climax!
Meanwhile, Luffy has broken out and
launches an attack on the Big Mom Pirates to save Sanji!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To Reach Sanji! Luffy's Vengeful Hell-bent Dash!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!