Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Whoa!
So this is a winter island!
The name of those mountains
is the Drum Rockies.
In the castle on top of the
tallest mountain lives Dr. Kureha,
the only doctor in our country who is
called a "witch" by our country's people.
Okay then, Nami. Hang on tight.
Okay...
Let's go!
Watch out for Lapins.
They're carnivorous, ferocious bunnies.
If you run into a group
of them, you're dead.
They have bodies like bears,
but the agility of bunnies...
and they attack in groups.
Run!
What're they doing?
Those damn bunnies...
This can't be happening...
Hey, Sanji. What's the matter?
What the heck is going on?
Hey... we're gonna run, Luffy!
"Dalton's Resolve!
Wapol's Corps Lands On The Island"
R-run? Where to?
Doesn't matter where! Someplace far!
What?!
An avalanche...! An avalanche is coming!
Ahhh! Those damn bunnies!
They'll never get away with this! Dammit!
Wh-wh-wh-what're we gonna do?!
Wh-wh-what're we gonna do, Sanji?!
How should I know?!
The first priority is Nami-san!
The second is Nami-san!
The third is Nami-san!
The fourth is Nami-san!
And the fifth is Nami-san!
Got that?!
Protect her even if it kills you!
Got it!
But how?!
Over there! That cliff!
Cliff?!
Run! We need to get as high up as we can!
It's coming!
Good, we made... Ahh!
Oh no! We're not high enough!
Wapol... Wapol came back!
What?!
Dalton-san headed to Big Horn!
Those who can fight, grab a
weapon and head to Big Horn!
Hurry! Those who can fight,
head to Big Horn!
Follow Dalton-san!
Wapol came back!
Everyone, grab a weapon!
We'll protect our country!
Grab a weapon! Head to Big Horn!
Yeah!
Hey, Vivi. Are you really sure
this is the right direction
to the Gyasta town where
the witch is right now?
Hmmm... When you put it that way,
I'm not really sure...
We're in trouble if you aren't sure...
Listen, if Luffy and Sanji managed to get
to the castle and didn't find the doctor,
they'd think, "What're we doing?"
Unless we find the doctor soon and
ask her to go back to the castle...
I know that, but...
If you know that, then do something.
You're a princess, right?
That has nothing to do with this.
I'm not a witch. I'm a princess.
But...
Then you look at the map.
What?! Don't be ridiculous!
There's snow everywhere. The map is...
In short, you don't know...
Yeah! I don't know at all!
You don't have to be proud!
In any case, there should be
a sign for Gyasta on this route.
So don't miss it.
Got it. Leave it to me!
I'll watch for signs of the sign!
Oh, ignoring me, huh?
Delicious!
Listen up, citizens!
Everything in this country is my snack!
I'm great! Why?
Kuromarimo, tell them!
That's because you're
the king, Your Highness.
That's right! That's exactly right!
If I wanna eat a house,
there's nothing like one cooked
well-done to a golden-brown after all!
Yeah!
Wapol-sama.
I have some information for you.
What is it?
I received a report that
some of the Straw Hats
rudely headed towards Drum Castle.
What? Why?!
It seems that they took a sick woman
to have her treated by a doctor.
Such idiots! No one lives in my
castle now, not to mention a doctor!
W-well... I heard that
the outrageous Dr. Kureha
even more rudely currently
lives in Drum Castle...
What?! That old hag's
living in my castle?!
Just how much does she intend
to mock me?! Kick her out!
Along with Straw Hat, I'll eat her up!
Men, we're going back to the castle!
Yeah!
Stop right there!
Who's that?!
Ahh! I was cut down! I'm gonna die!
Dalton-san!
I came here to kill you.
You dying suits me just fine.
You bastard, Dalton!
So you're alive!
How dare you hurt Wapol-sama!
It shouldn't be a big deal...
with the excellent doctors of our country,
the "great medical care nation" Drum.
That's right! The Twenty MDs
External Injury Unit! Come forward!
Starting an operation.
Scalpel!
Needle!
Tin.
Hammer.
Well... I really thought I'd die!
Just like what happened now,
you're the only one protected
and citizens have no choice
but to suffer from sickness
without seeing doctors... Wapol!
Wapol? It's Wapol-sama,
my retainer Dalton.
He's right! You don't
have the right to blather!
The three of us, you included,
were Wapol-sama's top brass.
We were his loyal hands, remember?
It's true that when you
were making people suffer,
all I could do was just watch
even though I was by your
side as one of your top brass.
I have to take responsibility for that.
Wapol... Let's leave this country together.
We must not stay in this land any longer.
Dalton-san! You didn't do anything wrong!
That's right! You're the only one in the
government who fought for the citizens!
Even when it almost killed you!
Humph! You should've died...
as the Captain of the
Drum Kingdom's Security Guard!
I'm surprised that you survived in
this country without any doctors.
Drum is acknowledged internationally
as a country with advanced medicine.
But who would know... that there
were actually only 20 doctors,
who worked in the research
facility of the King's castle,
and all the other doctors were exiled?
That's right! Those who become
sick can beg for their lives.
If I feel like it, I might
lend them the Twenty MDs.
If they don't wanna die, all they
have to do is obey me, the king!
With that, my ruling is perfect.
That's the government of this country!
You can't call that a government!
Humph! You sure speak
your mind, don't you?
Kill him! Kill your ex-captain!
As I figured, you don't
get what I'm saying...
You're the son of the previous
king who was good to me.
I was hoping that you'd
come to your senses some day,
but it seems like that
was wishful thinking!
Ahh! There he goes! Ox Ox Fruit!
The model "Bison"!
Don't flinch! Fire!
We can't hit him!
He's dodging them!
I'll show no mercy even though
you're my ex-subordinates!
Fiddle Bam!
He's strong! How powerful!
So this is the wild power...
the power of a Zoan type devil fruit...!
I've had enough with you all.
A country where the king
is the first to run off
when the country is in crisis
should just die out!
You don't have a chance,
fighting against the two of us.
Just give up.
Dalton-san!
We've come to assist you!
Let us fight with you!
We'll protect this free country!
Above all, I've known you so long.
That's unfortunate for you.
Don't...!
Your weak point is...
Why...
...did you shield us...?
Dalton-san!
That's your weak point, kind Dalton-kun.
This is a death befitting you!
Wh-what's going on?!
Hm? What's going on? An earthquake?
Hey, this isn't good. We can't go
further because of the deep snow.
Looks like we went up the mountain...
Hm?
What's... this rumbling?
Usopp-san! Could this be...
Ahhh... A.. Avalanche...?
25631... 25632... 25633...
Hm? What's going on? How noisy...
25634...!
Oh no! We're not high enough!
What do I do now?!
Oh, yeah!
Sanji! Grab my hand!
You saved my skin!
Yeah, but... even though
we won't sink in the snow,
we'll go straight down the mountain
if we don't do anything!
What?!
Hell no! We've come all
this way and were almost
at the foot of that chimney mountain!
We were just a step away from the doctor!
Luffy! Come up with a way to stop this!
Dammit, those damn hopping bunnies!
Next time I see them,
I'll simmer them in a pot!
What?!
What're we gonna do, Sanji?!
There's only one way!
Run!
What the heck's... with them?!
Oh no! Luffy! Look ahead! Ahead!
Ahhh! A rock! We're gonna crash!
You can't crash!
You're carrying Nami-san!
That's easy to say, but...!
We're crashing!
You have to treat ladies... gently!
Sanji!
Ahhh... That hit me good...! Dammit!
You idiot! Don't do stuff
like that without telling me!
Ahhh! Sanji!
Ahh! It's coming!
It's not stopping!
This village will be swallowed!
Get out of here!
We're getting out of here!
Chess! Kuromarimo! Get on!
Robson!
Robson, Serious Mode!
Wapol-sama! Please let us ride, too!
Shut up! Get out of here on your own!
Robson! Hurry up! It's closing in on us!
W-w-w-w-w-w-w-w-w-w-we'll
be fine! Don't worry, Vivi!
Even if we get swallowed,
I'll save you for sure!
Hey, do you think
Luffy-san and the others...
Could they have been swallowed
by this avalanche?
Ahhhh! Wapol-sama!
Ahh!
Ahhhhh!
Nami, are you cold?
Hang in there just a little longer.
Listen. Hold this. Stay here
and wait for me a little longer.
Oh, it was you guys.
No wonder I thought
it was an awful syrup.
They'll never get away with this!
Who are you talking about?
Idiot! Of course them!
Them meaning...?
You said some Straw Hats
are going up the mountain
to the castle right now.
Then this is what happened!
They have a huge grudge against
us over what happened between us,
so they caused an avalanche
on that snow mountain.
Oh no! That's what happened?
Then, this avalanche was their doing...
Let's go! We'll follow
them on the snow mountain!
I'll teach them a lesson
about battling in the snow!
I will definitely get you there.
Don't die...
both of you...
There they are!
Please look at that, Wapol-sama!
We found them!
Hold it, brat!
How dare you do
many rude things to me!
I'll beat you up!
Even this sleepless town
has dozed off for now
From today forth,
something's going to change
I'm sure I can start fresh,
since I'm not alone
Just by having you by my side,
I feel I can become strong
I wonder how far I can go,
towards the place that leads to the future
Off in the distance it shines,
encompassing the world
Before dawn
Boy, that was close!
I'm glad I'm still alive.
Suddenly hitting an avalanche in this cold...
I must've run out of luck.
But this is a sort of
winter swimming, I guess.
What on earth is happening
on the mountain?
I wonder if Luffy-san
and the others are okay...
I will definitely get
you there. Nami! Sanji!
So hang in there a little longer.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Island Where Snow Lives!
Climb The Drum Rockies!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!