My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
I don't have to worry about Luffy and the others.
They can flee on their own.
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
All members of the evil army Vinsmoke will die.
I'll die too.
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
Just as Big Mom planned.
We are hope
That's for the best.
That way our enemies get what they want.
It feels short but it was a fulfilling life.
The joy of letting our true feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro butsukeatta yorokobi mo
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
Oh, food!
The pain from how we laughed our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida kawakashita setsunasa mo
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
Are you Vinsmoke Sanji?
If you don't come back, I'll be here...
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
...starving to death!
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's not for you!
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
I'll be here waiting!
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Straw Hat!
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
What's wrong with you?
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
To take back Sanji who was being pressed into a marriage
and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole
Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole
Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
where Emperor Big Mom is.
Nami and Jimbei joined
Chopper and the others in the Mirro-World,
Chopper and Carrot in the Mirro-world
got back together with
In the Mirro-world, Nami and Jimbei
finally reunited with Chopper and Carrot.
With Jimbei's help,
Luffy successfully broke out of the Prison Library,
and found Brook who was held captive,
to their surprise, in Big Mom's bedroom.
Pedro, Nami and Jimbei who
had their own troubles.
and went on a rampage by himself
searching for Sanji.
Let's get going!
We gotta get Brook, Luffy and Sanji!
Luffy was on a rampage in the Whole
Cake Chateau looking for Sanji
After taking great pains, they finally
switched Brook and his double successfully.
Brook who was caught by Big Mom
saw Pudding's real face.
Spit it out!
and came across Sanji's sister Reiju.
Where's Sanji?!
If he's not being fooled, that's good.
Meanwhile,
Luffy was running to see Sanji again,
Meanwhile, Brook who had snuck into the castle
to obtain a copy of the Road Ponegliff,
Thanks to her, I got to try my gun.
Aside from that, I've done everything I can.
I gotta be there waiting...
but Big Mom's soldiers kept blocking his way.
With this, I definitely can
riddle Germa's modified human bodies with bullets.
What? Why are you going that way?!
fought a deadly battle against Big Mom
but was defeated.
This isn't the rendezvous point!
He finally arrived at the
rendezvous spot. However...
Luffy kept fighting
in order to wait for Sanji at the rendezvous point.
What a cute creature.
That meat is...
You're a skeleton from tip to toe
but you're alive - it's a miracle.
I've got to be there waiting!
...not for you!
At that spot!
How you fought was impressive too, Soul King.
And Sanji was thinking of Luffy.
Will they be able to meet again?
"Deciding to Say Goodbye!
Sanji and his Straw-Hat Bento!"
And Pedro who was causing a distraction
for Brook,
I have to stay awake...
lit dynamite after a fierce fight
against Baron Tamago.
Otherwise, I won't even know if Sanji comes.
"The Emperor Rolls Over!
Rescue Brook Mission!"
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
Luffy.
Where are you, Luffy?!
I'm sure... you'll be...
What's going on?!
...there!
--I just heard a loud noise from this way!
--Who was it?!
"The Chateau in Turmoil!
Luffy, to the Rendezvous!"
"The Rendezvous!
Luffy, a One-on-One at His Limit!"
You're Straw Hat Luffy, right?
Is that it?
We'll take care of you right here.
Luffy!!
What happened?
B-Bobbin-sama!
Get out of my way!
BOBBIN THE DISPOSER
A FIGHTER (BISHOP), BIG MOM PIRATES
BOUNTY: 105 MILLION 500 THOUSAND BERRIES
What happened to the wall?
--What happened here?
--Who did this?
--It's nothing.
--B-But...
This is it.
VISCOUNT HIYOKO WAS REBORN AND
EVOLVES MORE...
You guys can sit back.
COUNT NIWATORI
Which direction was it?
Count Niwatori, glad you're okay!
Bobbin-sa...
Damn Pedro,
I can't believe he detonated himself.
It's that way!
Okay, let's get out of this city...
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it myself.
Count, there are so many wounded!
Get out of my way...
He'll never ever get away with this!
Put out the fires-bon!
Take the injured to the medical center-soir!
Even the devil himself...
Yes, sir!
...comes from hell...
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
...to attend Mama's tea party!
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
Don't get in my way!
MIRRO-WORLD
We are hope
Mirror, mirror!
Here's the other three!
This skeleton and the straw hat
and the spiral eyebrows!
Oh, that was close!
You could be dead now, Pedro!
Are you okay, Chobro?
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
I'm okay because I'm Chobro.
Have you seen them?
Tell us if you know!
You can barely stand, damn brat!
How reckless you are!
Pedro, I was so surprised!
I can't believe this!
We're inside the mirror?!
--Two boys and a skeleton?
--Has anyone seen them?
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
Stop trying to act strong!
--Have you seen them?
--No, I haven't.
That girl...
I was even more surprised.
--Have you?
--No, I haven't seen them.
Jimbei! Why are you with these rats?!
Hey, Pedro!
I haven't either.
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
Brulee.
Imagine if you were called to from inside a mirror
all of a sudden.
This is obviously treason.
But you came up with a plan like this instantly!
That's our Pedro!
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
I heard you just sought to leave our crew
but got scared by the roulette.
Here!
The skeleton is here!
--It's from that way!
--Let's go see.
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Nice to have so many soldiers around.
Hey. Go faster. You're too slow!
I owed Mama for protecting the Fish-Man Island
after Whitebeard died.
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
I can't go any faster than this!
You guys are too heavy!
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Since I was leaving,
I wanted to fulfill my duty to her.
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
It's nice to be bait.
Stop grumbling. Just run.
That bastard, he can't get away with this!
But I only smell death and evil intent
from that roulette.
A-All right! Gee, what jerks!
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
I'll take him out for sure!
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Roulette?
The mirror down there might be that mirror.
Vinsmoke Sanji!
It's a good thing that you didn't do it,
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei.
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
Anyway, is this a mirror dimension?
That mirror?
Five years ago, my partner spun the roulette
asking mercy of Big Mom
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
It's hard to believe.
Well, you'll see.
No one can come in or get out of here
without Brulee. So it's safe!
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
and lost his life.
I...
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
Just hurry up!
I...
Dammit!
I can't stand getting pushed around!
I...
That thing is made to kill whoever spins it.
We can get away through this dimension
with Sanji!
I'm so surprised!
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Tell us what you know!
A...
So it's rigged?!
About everything!
Of course it is, you idiots!
Mama won't let anyone leave alive!
No, you surprised me!
We've arrived. We've arrived.
A ghost!
What?! Luffy and Nami have been caught?!
So Brook is here.
Whether it's a minor intruder...
You screamed at a critical moment!
...or an affiliated pirate
who was once loyal!
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
Yeah, that's what I heard.
This mirror is...
Thank you very much.
I'm worried about Brook too.
I hope he got a copy of the Ponegliff without trouble.
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
Anyway, I'm glad that you're alive.
She'll welcome those who come to her
and kill those who leave!
Yes, I thought I was going to die!
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
This mirror is so big.
They're all in danger! Let's hurry up!
That's her...
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
I am dead...
We don't have time!
Hey, look!
Carrot! Is everyone's portrait ready?
There's Brook!
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Yes, they're ready, Chobro!
Let's get going!
We gotta get Brook, Luffy and Sanji!
When they tightened their security,
You sure?! Well done!
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
it was impossible for us
to get a copy of the Road Ponegliff.
I'm not going!
You're over the weight limit!
Then, let's search for everyone
by showing them to the mirrors!
Brook!
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
Mirror, mirror! Thank you!
Let's go!
But I pushed it
and put you-gara's life in danger.
Okay!
You're welcome!
Garchu!
Hey...
We are hope
Something big is enveloping Brook...
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
I'm sorry!
What are you saying?
Everything you did was for us!
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
Like you said, since we were invading just
the two of us, we had a chance in a million.
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
Mirror, mirror!
Tell us where these people are!
No way...
They look nothing like them!
Oh, ow, ow!
That girl with long hair ran by here earlier.
If we were to try to get Big Mom's Road Ponegliff
some other time,
What's wrong, Prometheus?
I can't believe this...
The cut Soul King gave me
was deeper than I thought
The mirror talked!
an all-out war between pirates
would be unavoidable!
What? That means Nami has broken out?
Is she with Luffy?
and it's opening again!
That place is...
How pathetic!
That's why we had to try the mission
even if it was impossible!
She was with Boss Jimbei!
I mean, we gotta give this one credit.
What are you gonna do?
J... Jimbei?
Because no one's ever hurt you guys before.
That room is...
"A Liar!
Luffy and Sanji!"
Wh-What?!
...our Mama's bedroom!
Here, this is the copy.
The one of the Emperors - Big Mom?!
But, anyway, Pedro-san,
I can't believe you got away safely.
Sanji! Where are you?!
Wh-Wh-What should we do?
It's a good thing that he's alive but...
Copy...
Outta my way!
What?!
I was so desperate at that time too so I couldn't think of
anything other than asking you to be bait.
--Brook...
--I didn't expect him to be in such a place.
It's me, Sanji!
Mama, are you gonna keep
that skeleton here forever?
What? "That skeleton"?
Pudding-san, how could you call me that?
Listen to me! Sanji!
Wait a minute, Brook!
Don't tell me this is...
But why is she sleeping with him?
Get packing, you low-class pirates!
Stop him!
--Yeah, of course!
--Too close!
It's a copy of the Ponegliff.
--He's in a deep sleep too.
--How could he even sleep?
There's no other creature like this!
It's a work of soul art!
That was a close call!
Sanji!
Wake up, Brook!
Just when I finished copying the third paper,
Where are you?!
I'm gonna carry it around for a while
rather than put it in a book.
there came, believe it or not, Big Mom!
No good. He's not hearing you at all.
No...
Back down, guys!
You did a fine job with Straw Hat.
He's a strange bony creature.
Mama won't let go of such a thing!
Cabaletta-sama!
I didn't expect them to pass through
the Seducing Woods.
You got it?!
Straw Hat!
Oh? Didn't I take you down before?
But don't worry.
But we've successfully confined them
in a book at the Prison Library.
There was even a Sweet General!
Did you take down all those guards?!
I can make her loosen up her hand.
That was my big brother, Cadenza!
Mama! It's Brulee!
Yeah, I went to see them too.
That serves them right.
Choo!
I'm gonna smash you up!
--Help...
--Choo!
Big Mom's Ponegliff is something that
other Emperors of the Sea are eager to have!
"That serves them right"?
--Cut it out!
--Cover their mouths!
--Are you gonna kill them?
--Yeah, after the wedding.
Electro!
Sanji...
I sent bargirls to everyone in Germa.
You really...
I think they're drunk by now
and totally unsuspecting.
Um, yes.
I'm not like my brother! Physical strength isn't all I got!
C. CABALETTA - 8TH SON OF THE CHARLOTTE FAMILY
Did it wake Big Mom up?
I've been waiting for you.
Okay. But Reiju was snooping around me.
What?!
I don't care.
I'll just beat up whoever gets in my way!
You're late.
He got our Ponegliff?!
Oh, good. She's still sleepin...
She's very intuitive.
But it's already been resolved.
What's the matter, Sanji?
Brook!
Gum-Gum...
She...
What? You didn't kill her, did you?!
That's amazing!
...Jet Bullet!
She sees us!
Get out of my face...
What, Mama?! Don't you trust me?!
I only shot her leg!
It's a miracle!
The Treasure Repository is a room to which
even Big Mom's relatives aren't admitted easily.
...now!!
I shot her once and erased her memory.
I can't believe what I'm hearing.
What's the matter, Straw Hat?
You're something!
I didn't ask you to wait.
Oh, it's just a fly.
Then, could I see your panties...
Quit it!
Pudding-san? I thought that
you were a very nice girl.
His bones got broken again!
I refuse!
So we accomplished one of our goals!
I guess she hasn't noticed us.
Be careful. You're our precious bride.
All there's left to do is taking back Sanji!
You just made a promise
saying whatever you felt like.
If she tries to get revenge,
it'd be a big deal.
Thank you for your concern, Mama.
But...
No! What, what? What's wrong?!
Gum-Gum...
...thanks to her, I got to try my gun.
...Hawk Gatling!
He woke up!
Brook! Over here, over here!
With this, I definitely can riddle Germa's
modified human bodies with bullets.
Come to us now!
You're always like that.
I'll be here waiting!
Brook!
Don't be selfish and force things on others.
Oh, it's just a fly.
That's great. You're such a smart girl.
You're the cook of my ship!
But you came.
Don't go back to sleep!
I...
What is it, Mama? An enemy attack?!
...won't eat anything
other than what you cook!
Tomorrow,
your gunfire will be the cue for everything.
I'm sleeping!
Eat what you can.
Damn you!
I can't wait.
Food...
There you are!
I guess he's finally dead.
A decorated hall.
Unending applause and laughing!
I dropped it on my way here.
It's been crushed and it got wet in the rain.
Appearing there is the groom Sanji
No way!
and our sweet bride!
The wedding kiss
will draw everyone's attention.
Even if I get hungry or
spears rain down on me,
I'll make you suffer just as my brother did!
It's just another failure, isn't it?
Sanji, with his goofy face, will try to lift your veil
and kiss you.
I'll stay right here and wait for you!
That's when...
How powerful they are!
...he sees your third eye for the first time!
Be sure to come back!
Sanji!
The moment he sees his beautiful bride's
creepy real face,
It's good!
How can we...
...save...
he'll fall back a little!
Brook...
I-I gotta tell S-Sanji...
That's the moment! Okay?
Kill him with one shot.
From those monsters?!
I have to...
Sandwiches and hamburgers!
They're Robin and Franky's favorites!
...be there!
Sanji?
Aim at the spot between his eyebrows.
It's here.
Oh, the groom from Germa.
That scum betrayed you guys!
Pudding-san will kill Sanji-san?!
Just leave that shit-bag alone already!
Everyone there will be stunned and frozen!
The best food ever!
The people of Germa will become upset
and as they turn around and run,
Yum!
You put all of our favorites in here!
All right.
I'm gonna give you the finishing blow!
Hmmm...
it'll already be too late!
More hair, maybe?
I want them to have this!
Countless guns will be pointing at
the unarmed Vinsmokes!
Hm, then how about this?
Yeah, looks good to me!
Don't speak bad about Sanji!
So good!
Where did you find this?
I found it in a death chamber in the castle.
There'll be no time for them to be scared
before their blood spatters!
Straw Hat!
Yum! Yum!
What?!
Seaweed from the kitchen
is a substitute for his afro.
You can't get away from me anymore!
Don't lie!
Like fireworks,
the sound of gunshots won't stop!
Okay, it's done.
A rain of bullets that'll keep piercing through
their bodies even after they die!
Gum-Gum...
--Oh! It looks exactly like Brook!
--Totally!
Oh, that was so good!
...Hawk Rifle!
A pool of blood expands on the floor!
If we can replace Brook with this,
I had almost faded to nothing!
The lifeless forms of the six Vinsmokes!
I don't think she'll notice
that we took him away.
Gunshots will become shots of joy!
Have you had enough?
Yeah! The food you cook really is the best!
Now, if we place Brulee
at the midpoint of the mirror,
And the real party begins there!
If you're finished, leave.
Let's celebrate with a cake!
Let's celebrate with tea!
we can go in and out of the mirror
as we want.
I'll stay.
What are you saying?!
Come with us!
When they lose their useless leader,
Damn! I'll make them pay for this!
Don't make me repeat myself!
I'm not going back!
I think it's all set now. Let's begin.
the whole of Germa will become mine!
Why?!
The Rescue Brook Mission!
First.
SANJI'S ROOM
I insulted my captain who
came all the way for me,
Challenge 1!
Okay, I'm gonna go!
Don't make any noise!
and did my best to hurt you
even while you didn't fight back.
Big Mom is cautious
even when she's sleeping.
If you think it's dangerous,
come back.
That's why I can't go back to your ship now.
Yes, the groom - Sanji-sama surely is
sleeping in his room.
Be careful, Chobro!
I can't believe it!
Cabaletta-sama has been defeated!
I know! You can just count on me!
Don't let him out or let anyone in until morning.
Keep close watch.
Second.
Yes, ma'am!
That damn geezer who I'm deeply indebted to
and the sea restaurant Baratie
Sanji!
where I grew up...
Oh, no! I fell asleep-nasu!
In Sanji-sama's bed!
...have been taken as hostages
in case anything goes wrong.
Is he not back yet-nasu?
C-Chase him!
That's why I can't escape from the wedding.
Stop!
I guess he won't come
back any time soon-nasu.
Well, then let's sleep
a little bit more-nasu.
Sanji!
MEETING ROOM
So, Pekoms was with them until Chocolat Town.
Sanji! Where are you?!
Their objective is to take Sanji back.
Third.
There were six of them when Pudding
lured them to this main island.
My evil biological family has been
trapped by Big Mom.
Sanji! I'm hungry!
Soul King is in Mama's hands now.
In a few hours from now,
they'll all be killed.
Oh, oops!
Where are you, Sanji?!
Don't touch!
Watch your step, Chobro!
Pedro detonated himself in the Courtyard
on the third floor, right?
What?!
Relax! You're almost there!
WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU - THIRD FLOOR
As long as you don't run away,
everything will turn out for the best, Sanji.
Neither of them are there?!
Indeed-cock-a-doo.
No!
--They passed by quite some time ago.
--They're not here now.
Two down.
Now, if I can just climb this bed...
And of the four who entered the Seducing
Woods, a rabbit and a raccoon...
Even in Sanji's room?
Yeah, instead,
some weird guy's sleeping in there.
...got caught by Big Sis Brulee -
she reported so at noon today.
What's wrong?
To my biological father,
older brothers and young brother...
If he's not in his room, where is he?
What is it, Chobro?!
D-Don't tell me he's about to...
That means four out of the six of them are out.
The problem is...
I have no obligation.
--...sneeze!
--What?! Chobro, no!
That's it. I think I know where he is.
I have nothing but resent for those scumbags!
It's outside so there's no mirror.
...these two who took down Big Bro Cracker
and got out of the Seducing Woods.
--Fight it off!
--Please, Chobro!
You're a failure who deserves to die!
This morning, Luffy and Sanji-kun...
Hold it! Hold it!
We surely locked them up
in the underground Prison Library.
Don't ever admit that I'm your father...
...fought there.
What?!
...in front of other people!
Why is there a rumor that they broke out?
That's our Chobro!
Luffy and Sanji got in a fight?!
It's a shame that I don't
want anyone to know!
Okay, just go!
Abandon Germa and run away, Sanji.
Alright, wait for me, Brook.
I'll save you now!
Why, why?!
Sanji has his position
as part of the Vinsmokes.
But I...
You'll never meet...
...can't...
You're right.
Only one of us was
there in the Prison Library.
...such great friends like them twice!
He must have come here
for a compelling reason.
What happened, Big Brother Opera?
They say Jimbei appeared.
I don't think it's that
easy to take him back.
...turn my back on them!
You dummy!
But if you wanna get him back,
you must hurry up.
That's groundless!
Don't make me repeat myself-fa!
I'm so scared! Really scared!
In fact, where is he now?
I was going to tell you when everyone gets together
but the thing is...
There's no information-fa!
No one has come to the basement!
--Are you okay, Chobro?
--Somebody else has to go.
...if they hold the wedding tomorrow,
As I promised to Mama, I was torturing
Lola's whereabouts out of them!
Okay, let me go next!
it's not going to be a peaceful one.
WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU - FIRST FLOOR
Challenge 2!
They didn't know anything
so I burned them to death!
What do you mean?
There they are!
--They're coming, Jimbei!
--Hold on tight!
You guys came here with Pekoms,
didn't you?
I know I went a little too far.
Oh, Pekoms!
Okay, I made it this far...
Is he okay?
We lost of him on our way.
Five Thousand Brick Fist!
D-Don't you trust your brother, Montd'Or?!
TURN BACK
I-It's really expanding!
Yes, but he got involved in somebody's plot
--Look for the right time!
--Go when it's deflated!
Of course I trust you.
and was almost fed to sharks.
Do you think Luffy met Sanji-kun safely?
I can't say that I failed
to guard them! Never!
Plot?
Deflating...
If we hadn't noticed...
It's already hard enough to look for him
in this giant castle!
Mama will take all of my lifespan away-fa!
Inflating...
Now!
But he is running in bad shape fighting enemies...
I hope he'll be alright.
he'd be dead.
That's it!
Brook, Brook, wake up.
How are Sanji and the Vinsmokes?
For those three reasons,
I can't go back with you guys!
Hey, Brook, wake up now.
They are all in their rooms.
Stop!
Oh, no! The snot bubble's coming!
We must keep up too
and get out of this castle already!
Okay, it's all good!
Run!
A-Are you guys...
All the intruders have been caught!
...monsters...?
Oh! There he is!
Right now, in the giant kitchen,
they're preparing for tomorrow!
Chase him!
Boss Jimb... I mean, Jimbei's risen in revolt!
How pathetic.
Bargirls shouldn't pass out from drinking.
Let's make it a great wedding tomorrow
for our precious sister Pudding!
Did she notice...
If you understand, get lost.
Staaare...
Stop!
It's staring right at me...
Yeah!
This way!
I wish they'd sent us
that girl, Sanji's friend, instead.
Block their way!
I know! That girl named Nami, right?
I like strong-minded girls like that.
Is that...
A stuffed bunny!
That's not gonna work!
Expand the coverage and patrol until morning.
I heard she's already been caught by Big Mom.
Oh, no! I think we will be surrounded.
Yes, sir!
Oh, it's just a stuffed bunny.
I'll ask her if we can
have that girl tomorrow.
I don't trust Opera.
What? Isn't there a way out?
What? That worked?
Can you take the back, Nami?!
Now's your chance, Carrot!
Count on me! I'm fed up with this!
Alright, that's enough drinking for today.
We'll have a party tomorrow night.
I'll do it this time...
There they are!
Stop!!
We Germa will form an alliance
with Emperor Big Mom
Nami!
You guys are annoying!
Get off of the island with
the Straw Hats, Sanji.
Storm Cloud Rod!
and conquer the North Blue again!
There's still a fly?
Huh?! I can't do that!
Even if I could, what about Baratie?!
What an annoying fly!
We glorious Germa have been scorned
Think about that after you escape.
and insulted by hateful
countries of the North Blue.
If you stay here, we're all gonna die.
The day we get our revenge on them
will come soon!
--I'm so scared! Really scared!
--I know, I know.
Tomorrow, we'll celebrate it in advance!
What?! Chopper!
We need to switch again.
What?
How disappointing.
When it comes to this...
Chopper! Why are you here?!
Gum-Gum...
That failure who'd been nothing but the
shame of the Vinsmokes for a long time,
...Pistol!
Oh! Chobro!
I must do it!
Carrot!
Challenge 3!
finally came in handy!
Nami! We're here to save you!
You're right!
The fish that we caught with Sanji as bait is very big!
I see! I'm sorry!
When our enemies see Big Mom's
Jolly Roger on Germa's fleet,
Oh, no!
More enemies are coming from the front!
There you are.
Brook!
Say what you really want!
Hey, wake up!
they'll lose their spirit to fight.
Nami! Get in the mirror now!
Brook!
We can conquer the sea more mightily
from now on.
It was a good thing that
we widened our search to the city.
What?
Oh, no! Did I wake her up?
We gotta thank Sanji.
Sanji!
Thank Sanji?
Answer if you're there!
No, she just turned over.
Stop, Straw Hat!
This is my chance.
Sanji!
To that failure!
While her hands are off of Brook...
Hey!
To that beneficial punk!
There's something you need to know!
Where are you?!
--Now, Pedro!
--Switch them quickly!
Cheers!
I must do it in an instant.
Listen to what I have to say!
Sanji! I'm hungry!
Switch them as quick as I can
so she won't notice.
Don't let the Vinsmokes see anyone
until tomorrow's tea party.
Just cook something, you fool!
Ow, ow, ow...
Sanji-kun, what are you gonna make today?
Escape spectacularly!
Roger. I've already deployed soldiers...
And go back to my friends!
IN FRONT OF THE GUEST ROOM
FOR THE VINSMOKE FAMILY
...to the medical center on the
third floor where Reiju-sama is.
Where did he go?
--Don't lower your guard.
--Yes, sir.
He's so quick! Which way did he go?
Sanji! I'm gonna catch something big!
That's our Pedro!
Let me call you Brother Pedro!
The Vinsmokes can't escape their destiny.
In here?
You can count on us!
Pebro!
Don't say so much openly!
Oh, thank you so much, Pedro-san!
Gum-Gum...
Idiot!
...Gatling!
Don't mention it.
Damn! I can't hit them!
Oh! Thank you.
I can't open it!
Okay, I'm imagining it perfectly.
--Let's go that way!
--Yeah!
Damn...
Those bastards!
You're Sanji's sister!
She's rolling over!
Who snatched the food?!
That's right.
Why did you do that? I'm in a hurry!
Are you okay?
I knew it was you guys!
You're looking for Sanji, right?
He was just here.
I can't believe I let my guard down!
As your punishment, no dinner!
Dammit!
What? Really?!
Where did he go?!
Did he wake up?!
Pudding was fooling us!
They're so cheerful every day.
No.
But that's good for us.
Boy... Did I make this for Pudding-chan?
I never thought
that I would look forward to mealtimes one day.
Sanji's bride Pudding said she'd kill him!
He's out of Big Mom's hands!
Okay, I'll go!
What was I thinking?
Challenge 4!
Are you okay? Did you get hurt?
Super great food, please, Sanji!
Brook, wake up!
Feed us more, Sanji!
Thank you. I'm okay.
He knows about Pudding.
Brook!
What?! Has he known all this time?!
These are all their favorites.
It's me, Brook!
He just found out.
Ghost!
Forget them! Forget them!
I convinced him to get away from this island
What is it?
but he was worried about
the hostages in the East Blue
Are you still here?
and the harm that it'd cause to you guys.
Luffy... I...
Oh, no!
By "hostages," you mean Baratie?
You annoying fly!
I know them well too so if they're really in danger,
I'll even go there and fight for them!
You...
Seems like he created quite a ruckus.
Heavenly...
...Fire!
I...
Do you want something to eat?
N-No thanks!
I...
Did we finally beat him?
I wanna go back to the Sunny!
I'll be here waiting!
Yes!
If you don't come back, I'll be here...
Don't get in my way!
...starving to death!
That... That was close.
But I can't get the courage to run away!
You're the cook of my ship!
Thank you, Jimbei!
I won't eat anything other than what you cook!
This is it for him!
The mission succeeded!
Woo-hoo!
This is great! I'm so relieved!
We're currently holding
Straw Hat and Cat Burglar-nasu.
Once the wedding begins, I know...
Luffy has fought against their top officer all night
to get this far!
...I can't stop anything by myself!
But that's good. Sanji...
So his body is...
I don't even consider...
I...
But...
...gotta get back... to that spot!
...those scum as my family!
Sanji knows about Pudding.
...you said you'd be here waiting!
But I...
If he's not being fooled, that's good.
Gum-Gum...
Aside from that, I've done everything I can.
I wanna save their lives!
Sanji, I'm almost there.
Okay, thank you, Sanji's sister!
...Jet Pistol!
What? Why are you going that way?!
This isn't the rendezvous point!
Well, that's how you are.
Where are you, Luffy?!
There you are, Straw Hat Luffy.
You got us! Let's crash the wedding!
Didn't I beat you up right here before?
Sanji!
Dammit! Don't get in my way!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
We'll chop this guy's head off.
It's not working.
What's wrong with him?
You are a sacrifice, Sanji.
If you don't run away,
everything will turn out for the best, Sanji.
Hey! Stop!
This isn't for you!
At the wedding tomorrow,
you Vinsmokes...
...will all be eliminated!
I'm sorry. There's somebody
that I really wanna give it to.
We're here to pick you up! Sanji!
I'll be here waiting!
Gum-Gum...r
Get packing, you low-class pirates!
...Gatling!
If you don't come back, I'll be here...
...starving to death!
I don't have to worry about Luffy and the others.
They can flee on their own.
He hasn't been hurt at all.
It's too late for me to turn back, Luffy.
Luffy!!
Is that all you've got?
All members of the evil army
Vinsmoke will die. I'll die too.
You're not that strong.
Just as Big Mom planned.
Gum-Gum...
That's for the best.
That way our enemies get what they want.
Oh! Something hit the house!
...Bazooka!
It feels short but it was a fulfilling life.
--My house!
--What's going on? It's so late.
Oh, food!
It's my turn now!
A person?
Are you Vinsmoke Sanji?
Montd'Or said you were sleeping in your room.
If you don't come back, I'll be here...
H-Hey! Are you okay?
...starving to death!
You're so persistent.
Don't touch it!
I have to... wait for Sanji.
That meat is...
...not for you!
No one's here?!
I'm not gonna let you go.
I'll go tell them to open the gate.
No need.
It'll open soon.
There you are.
Nice try.
I heard a loud noise from that way!
But this is it, Straw Hat!
I gotta get there as soon as possible.
You son of a...
I'll be here waiting!
CHARLOTTE KATAKURI
ONE OF THE SWEET 3 GENERALS
(SECOND SON OF CHARLOTTE)
BIG MOM PIRATES
Hey, stop, you bastard!
What am I doing?!
Five hours thirty minutes left
before Big Mom's tea party starts.
I've got to be there waiting!
At that spot!
Sanji is coming back to the Straw Hats!
After the deadly battle,
Luffy and Sanji finally see each other again!
Tiptoe silently, stealthy.
Save Brook, sleeping alongside the Emperor!
Death or escape.
Sanji, who has lost everything, is torn by the ultimate conflict.
Suffering from never-before-experienced
hunger,
Luffy continues fighting beyond his limit.
Their next objective is to execute a daring
Though Sanji hasn't yet figured out
His lifelong dream and days of
adventures with his friends...
mission to save Sanji's family
from the deadly wedding!
his course of action, he digs through
a heap of rubble searching for Luffy.
In an extremely tense situation,
Meanwhile, Luffy, nearly fainting from hunger, fights deadly
battles against his pursuers in order to see Sanji again!
Will Sanji truly throw it all away?
The key to the plan is one
of the most dangerous men
The two men never supposed to see each
other again try to reach the fateful spot!
the Straw Hats try to invade Big Mom's
incredibly destructive bedroom,
The fight to take Sanji back
finally comes to a climax!
but they can't wake her up no matter what!
from the Worst Generation, Gang Bege!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Emperor Rolls Over! Rescue Brook Mission!"
"Deciding to Say Goodbye! Sanji and his Straw-Hat Bento!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Rendezvous! Luffy, a
One-on-One at His Limit!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Liar! Luffy and Sanji!"
"Sanji Comes Back! Crash!
The Tea Party from Hell!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!