kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
To take back Sanji who was being pressed
into a marriage and left his friends behind,
Luffy and the others infiltrated the Whole
Cake Island where Emperor Big Mom is.
Nami and Jimbei joined
Chopper and the others in the Mirro-World,
and found Brook who was held captive,
to their surprise, in Big Mom's bedroom.
After taking great pains, they finally
switched Brook and his double successfully.
Meanwhile,
Luffy was running to see Sanji again,
but Big Mom's soldiers kept blocking his way.
He finally arrived at the
rendezvous spot. However...
Luffy.
I'm sure... you'll be...
...there!
"The Rendezvous!
Luffy, a One-on-One at His Limit!"
This is it.
Get out of my way...
You can barely stand, damn brat!
Stop trying to act strong!
That bastard, he can't get away with this!
I'll take him out for sure!
Vinsmoke Sanji!
I...
I'm so surprised!
A...
About everything!
No, you surprised me!
A ghost!
You screamed at a critical moment!
Thank you very much.
Anyway, I'm glad that you're alive.
Yes, I thought I was going to die!
I am dead...
When they tightened their security,
it was impossible for us
to get a copy of the Road Ponegliff.
But I pushed it
and put you-gara's life in danger.
I'm sorry!
What are you saying?
Everything you did was for us!
Like you said, since we were invading just
the two of us, we had a chance in a million.
If we were to try to get Big Mom's Road Ponegliff
some other time,
an all-out war between pirates
would be unavoidable!
That's why we had to try the mission
even if it was impossible!
Here, this is the copy.
But, anyway, Pedro-san,
I can't believe you got away safely.
Copy...
What?!
I was so desperate at that time too so I couldn't think of
anything other than asking you to be bait.
Wait a minute, Brook!
Don't tell me this is...
It's a copy of the Ponegliff.
That was a close call!
Just when I finished copying the third paper,
there came, believe it or not, Big Mom!
You got it?!
There was even a Sweet General!
Did you take down all those guards?!
Big Mom's Ponegliff is something that
other Emperors of the Sea are eager to have!
You really...
Um, yes.
What?!
He got our Ponegliff?!
Brook!
That's amazing!
It's a miracle!
The Treasure Repository is a room to which
even Big Mom's relatives aren't admitted easily.
You're something!
Then, could I see your panties...
Quit it!
His bones got broken again!
So we accomplished one of our goals!
All there's left to do is taking back Sanji!
I'll be here waiting!
You're the cook of my ship!
I...
...won't eat anything
other than what you cook!
I guess he's finally dead.
No way!
Even if I get hungry or
spears rain down on me,
I'll stay right here and wait for you!
Be sure to come back!
Sanji!
I have to...
...be there!
All right.
I'm gonna give you the finishing blow!
Straw Hat!
What?!
Neither of them are there?!
No!
--They passed by quite some time ago.
--They're not here now.
Even in Sanji's room?
Yeah, instead,
some weird guy's sleeping in there.
If he's not in his room, where is he?
That's it. I think I know where he is.
It's outside so there's no mirror.
This morning, Luffy and Sanji-kun...
...fought there.
What?!
Luffy and Sanji got in a fight?!
Why, why?!
Sanji has his position
as part of the Vinsmokes.
You're right.
He must have come here
for a compelling reason.
I don't think it's that
easy to take him back.
But if you wanna get him back,
you must hurry up.
I was going to tell you when everyone gets together
but the thing is...
...if they hold the wedding tomorrow,
it's not going to be a peaceful one.
What do you mean?
You guys came here with Pekoms,
didn't you?
Oh, Pekoms!
Is he okay?
We lost of him on our way.
TURN BACK
Yes, but he got involved in somebody's plot
and was almost fed to sharks.
Plot?
If we hadn't noticed...
he'd be dead.
A-Are you guys...
...monsters...?
How pathetic.
Bargirls shouldn't pass out from drinking.
I wish they'd sent us
that girl, Sanji's friend, instead.
I know! That girl named Nami, right?
I like strong-minded girls like that.
I heard she's already been caught by Big Mom.
I'll ask her if we can
have that girl tomorrow.
Alright, that's enough drinking for today.
We'll have a party tomorrow night.
We Germa will form an alliance
with Emperor Big Mom
and conquer the North Blue again!
We glorious Germa have been scorned
and insulted by hateful
countries of the North Blue.
The day we get our revenge on them
will come soon!
Tomorrow, we'll celebrate it in advance!
That failure who'd been nothing but the
shame of the Vinsmokes for a long time,
finally came in handy!
You're right!
The fish that we caught with Sanji as bait is very big!
When our enemies see Big Mom's
Jolly Roger on Germa's fleet,
they'll lose their spirit to fight.
We can conquer the sea more mightily
from now on.
We gotta thank Sanji.
Thank Sanji?
To that failure!
To that beneficial punk!
Cheers!
Don't let the Vinsmokes see anyone
until tomorrow's tea party.
Roger. I've already deployed soldiers...
IN FRONT OF THE GUEST ROOM
FOR THE VINSMOKE FAMILY
...to the medical center on the
third floor where Reiju-sama is.
--Don't lower your guard.
--Yes, sir.
The Vinsmokes can't escape their destiny.
Don't say so much openly!
Idiot!
Damn...
Those bastards!
Seems like he created quite a ruckus.
This is it for him!
We're currently holding
Straw Hat and Cat Burglar-nasu.
Luffy has fought against their top officer all night
to get this far!
So his body is...
But...
...you said you'd be here waiting!
Where are you, Luffy?!
I'll be here waiting!
If you don't come back, I'll be here...
...starving to death!
Luffy!!
After the deadly battle,
Luffy and Sanji finally see each other again!
His lifelong dream and days of
adventures with his friends...
Will Sanji truly throw it all away?
The fight to take Sanji back
finally comes to a climax!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Liar! Luffy and Sanji!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!