Luffy and Sanji who had parted ways
finally reunited at the rendezvous.
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
Listen, guys.
We're gonna crash Big Mom's tea party
and the wedding
We are hope
and save Sanji's family!
Then, Sanji'll be back with us!
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
B... Big...
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
The pain from how we laughed our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
Luffy... She's the Emperor of the Sea!
And then, Jimbei suggested a plan to Luffy.
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
You know Capone "Gang" Bege, right?
Yeah, he's the one who took Sanji away.
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
The main event of the tea party is
the wedding.
As you already know, Big Mom intends to
kill all the members of the Vinsmokes at the wedding
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
and acquire all of Germa.
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
Bege is going to kill Big Mom!
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
What?!
What the hell?
Seems like everyone has their own plot!
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
I feel bad for Pekoms
but under the circumstances,
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
do you really want to
make an enemy of Bege?
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
Luffy! Sanji!
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
Let's join Bege!
susumiyuku kouro nara
The sea route that we take
What?!
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
"A Secret Meeting!
Luffy vs. the Fire Tank Pirates!"
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the morning when the light comes in
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
But you're right!
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
What?!
Hey, are you crazy, Luffy?!
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
You actually like it, Luffy?!
See, I told you!
We are hope
Luffy, four out of six of us are against it!
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
Didn't you hear about Bege-san's ill deeds?!
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
Well, that way, everything'll
work out, right?
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
You can't make a decision like that...
Actually, I've already made an arrangement.
Do you want to meet him?
Okay, let's see him now!
What?!
Luffy and Sanji who had parted ways
finally reunited at the rendezvous.
Sanji parted ways with the Straw Hats
after the duel against Luffy.
Don't worry.
You can say no if it feels off.
Our goal is slightly different from theirs.
He thought he was determined but
We're gonna crash Big Mom's tea party
and the wedding
he found himself leaving
the Whole Cake Chateau.
We're gonna crash Big Mom's
tea party and the wedding
We're gonna crash Big Mom's tea party
and the wedding
Luffy, Sanji. Bege and his clan's base is
in the northwest of the island.
Afterwards, Luffy and Sanji saw each
other again at the rendezvous point.
and save Sanji's family!
Then, Sanji'll be back with us!
The eight of us will head there first
from this dimension. See you there!
Say what you really want!
And the meeting on the assassination of
the Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom, has begun.
Luffy and his clan allied with Bege
who is plotting to kill the Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom.
As Luffy announced his plan,
Stop counting us in!
I...
Jimbei suggested he ally with Bege
who is in charge of the tea party's security.
It seems like it's the most
important treasure for her.
Everyone has their own objectives
as the Tea Party is finally about to start.
Okay, got it!
I...
Okay, let's see him now!
If we break that picture in half,
what do you think will happen?!
Thus, Luffy and his group went down to
the base of Bege's clan - the Fire Tank Pirates.
I wanna go back to the Sunny!
FIRE TANK PIRATES' BASE
NORTHWEST WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
I need you to take that role, Straw Hat!
"The Family Gets Together!
The Hellish Tea Party Starts!"
So, what kind of guy is he?
Did you kill Bobbin?
Okay!
You heard what Jimbei said.
But I can't get the courage to run away!
Yes, he was going after Black-Leg.
FIRE TANK PIRATES
I'll do it!
Think of him as a scheming
and brutal mafia boss.
After all, Germa are my heroes.
Will I marry that lowlife?!
"Luffy Engages in a Secret Maneuver!
The Wedding Full of Conspiracies Starts Soon!"
Once the wedding begins, I know...
"PHANTOM GUN" VITO
Alright! Let's go!
Are they really coming here?
Yeah!
Wait a minute!
No way!
...I can't stop anything by myself!
Father?
Do you know how dangerous it is
to break Mama's precious portrait of Mother Carmel?
"HIT MAN" GOTTI
"The Deadly Pact!
Luffy & Bege's Allied Forces!"
I don't even consider...
Jimbei isn't the type of man to joke.
At the wedding tomorrow,
you Vinsmokes...
You need to think twice...
...those scum as my family!
Since we're both standing against Big Mom,
Well, I just came up with an awesome way
to show up at the scene!
But I...
we shouldn't make extra enemies -
he's right about that.
...will all be eliminated!
I wanna save their lives!
Now it depends on what Straw Hat will say.
A way to show up?
What?! What is it?
Sounds like fun! I wanna hear it!
If we don't like it...
Me too!
No way. If I tell you now,
it'll ruin the fun.
Well, that's how you are.
Sanji-san...
We'll just kill him!
What?!
--What was I worried for?
Sounds good.
Then, I'll be counting on you.
S... S... So...
You got us! Let's crash the wedding!
Yeah!
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
Now, do you know when to break the picture?
So cute!!
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
"Sanji Comes Back!
Crash! The Tea Party from Hell!"
When Sanji kisses Pudding, right?
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
Idiot, I won't do it! I can't!
What?! You won't kiss her?! Why?!
OUTSKIRTS OF SWEET CITY
It's good, isn't it, Luffy?
We are hope
Why don't you guys restrain yourselves?!
Didn't you hear what Brook said?
IN FRONT OF THE TEA PARTY VENUE
Everyone, please line up here!
What? These are for us to eat, right?
The wedding kiss
will draw everyone's attention.
Jimbei came to help?!
Let us do a security check before entering.
Yeah, I was surprised too.
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
That's exactly the moment...
You guys are nothing but nuisances to us.
Oh, here they come!
That's good. So Nami-san is okay too...
...Pudding-san will shoot Sanji-san!
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
Killing all of you right here is
the easiest solution...
But now, the problem is
how we join them.
I'll dodge the shot.
So the gunshot is the cue.
Once they hear you're coming back,
I'm sure they'll be happy.
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
Okay! That's easy!
Alright, let's go over the plan.
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
When Pudding shoots the gun,
You sure about that?
Straw Hat breaks the picture!
If I die, you'll lose your chance
to kill Big Mom.
Goodbye!
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Big Mom will shriek.
Sorry - we should never have done this!
Congratulations!
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Because there'll be no wedding.
And we'll put the Invisible
Symphonia System on.
I'm too ashamed to see Nami-san...
If I'm not back there at least two hours
before the wedding, they'll be suspicious.
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Say "earplugs."
Yeah, unfortunately, you're right.
Then, it's all downhill from there.
Nami and the others care about you
more than I did.
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
So we can kill everyone else except you.
While the people are in a panic,
you guys will rescue Germa.
You're in our way. Move.
But I scared her.
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
I won't let you kill my friends either.
And with the KX Launcher
and the deadly poison gas shell,
We have to do a search.
Don't take us so lightly.
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
Huh?! Who do you think you're talking to?!
We're not going to make a misstep
like we did in Zou.
I have full authority over
security of today's Tea Party.
we'll assassinate Big Mom.
Oh, the rain is stopping.
We are hope
Finish everything in 10 seconds tops.
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
We don't have time to intimidate each other.
This is Big Mom's order.
10 seconds?
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
After that, the longer we stay there,
the more likely are we to die.
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
Luffy, does your gut tell you
that you can team up with them?
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
We'll keep all kinds of weapons here.
So it's a race against time.
What do you think?
Hmph!
That's the first rule of assassinations.
MIRRO-WORLD
It all depends on Straw Hat.
He's the real one-rero!
I found it!
I don't have anything else!
You sure?! Chobro!
After he breaks the picture,
there'll be three seconds before Mama starts crying.
We'll keep your Raid Suits too.
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
Do you think they can hear us
through this piece of glass?
No one's allowed to bring any weapon in.
Raid Suits are no exception.
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
Whether or not he can stop the Ministers
who'll come attacking is the key.
The mirror I was talking
through the last time we spoke
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
broke on the tree monster Kingbaum's head.
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
What happens...
Yeah! Count on me!
...if we refuse?
How do we escape?
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
As soon as we kill Big Mom,
It broke!
this dumbass will come in!
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
So...
Yes, I'll come in!
...I think there is at least a piece of glass
that connects to this one.
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
"Dumbass"?!
--He's such a piece of crap.
--Is this jerk part of the plan?
You're Caesar, aren't you?!
Shut up!
We are hope
What?! Caesar?! Where?!
Listen, since I can fly,
I'll plunge into the site with a mirror to escape!
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
Hey! Luffy!
He was there the whole time...
Hey!
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
How could you not notice...?
Stop!
Luffy!
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
Along with that woman!
Don't count me in! Mama will kill me!
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
Are you there, Luffy?!
--Is that...?
--It's Chopper!
You guys did a great job
bringing Brulee here.
Hey!
We couldn't have hoped for a more useful power
to help us escape.
Answer me if you're there!
Damn!
I can't make the impossible possible!
Chopper!
Your compliment doesn't
make me happy, you fool!
No matter how much I try,
I can't make a drug to turn people into giants!
Luffy!
If that's what Big Mom wants,
we'll go along.
You fool!
Hey!
Once you finish,
dive into Caesar's mirror quickly!
Luffy! Can you hear me?!
This research is so pointless!
I'm not gonna work anymore!
Big Mom will still be shrieking.
Hey!
Here it is!
And then, we can just run away
in the mirror dimension in comfort.
--Soft and fluffy...
--Moist and fluffy...
This is it! It's a piece of glass!
Go ahead and do as you like with me,
Big Mom!
Welcome to Big Mom's Tea Party.
Can you hear me?!
...life
Think of a mirror that is big enough
for you to come out on your ship.
--Start repairing the cake!
--Yes, sir!
Why is his voice coming from a mirror?
There's no such thing
Caesar Clown!
A life of torment, the taste of tears
It's a long story but
they're in a mirror dimension.
A big mirror...
STREUSEN - GOURMET KNIGHT
HEAD CHEF, BIG MOM PIRATES
This is the venue layout that Bege got.
Oh, the dresser!
I-I-I'm working my butt off!
Tell Big Mom so!
A pinch of salt
A mirror dimension? Chopper and the others?!
Uh-huh!
Tears of mortification
Big Mom will sit here.
Are you okay, Chopper?
There's no need.
A tablespoonful
The mirror will provide you the quickest way
to escape from the island.
I'm getting nervous.
I wonder if this plan's gonna work out.
Oh, Luffy! Great! You're really there!
What?
If that's how it is
at least for your dessert
Through the Mirroworld,
we can get to the Sunny in no time.
When I asked them to let me watch over you,
they agreed without question.
Okay! I'm all ready!
Luffy! Is Sanji-kun there too?!
Don't you want some sweet cake?
That's quite a plan.
Luffy?
I'm now a trusted Rook!
Yeah, I think it's gonna work well!
Yeah, he's here!
Don't worry! Everything's gonna be alright!
Head chef! Head chef!
No, you have to be careful.
That's great!
So you got to see him again, Luffy!
I'm going out for a bit.
Pedro is right.
That's my heart?!
--Soft and fluffy...
--Moist and fluffy...
Yay!
If you make even one small mistake,
you'll face death...
Going out?! To where?!
I'll get you out of here
if you help me with your power.
Oh, I don't have enough time!
--Soft and fluffy...
--Moist and fluffy...
That's how dangerous it is.
Sanji-san, I'm glad that you're okay.
You fool!
Who do you think you're talking to?!
--Soft and fluffy...
--Moist and fluffy...
These bastards...!
--Soft and fluffy...
--Moist and fluffy...
I'm a genius scientist
who can even destroy the world!
Once each of us gets to our own ships,
our alliance is over.
How are you guys?
--Soft and fluffy...
--Moist and fluffy...
We saved everybody from
inside the mirror, Luffy!
We should just get out of this territory
as fast as we can.
--Soft and fluffy...
--Moist and fluffy...
Good luck in battle!
Brook even got a copy of the Ponegliff!
--Soft and fluffy...
--Moist and fluffy...
Okay!
I know who you are.
Really?!
--It's gonna start!
That's why I came.
I guess we're set.
I'm impressed with you guys!
--Soft and fluffy...
--Moist and fluffy...
It's time for Mama's Tea Party!
The party starts at 10, right?
Y-Your compliment doesn't make me happy,
you fool!
Damn!
I served Big Mom and now Bege!
Two and a half hours to go...
--It's time!
I gotta work anyway!
I gotta go back to my room
since I'm the groom.
You fool!
EASTERN INLET
Are you doing your job-rero?
You silly little goose!
No, Pekoms! You still have to rest!
We have to go back too.
Let's get ready for fake security duty.
I am! Who do you think I am?!
Luffy, it's good that Sanji's there
but did you guys come to an agreement?
A Porkswagon comes rushing
This is more my cup of tea
than the other one!
Grr! Has Jimbei really told Mama
about that damn rat Bege?!
I wonder if he can make it
Hey, Bege. Could you do me a favor?
The greatest piece of art
will be completed soon!
--He's late
--He has to hurry
What is it?
When I show up in a funny way...
Of course!
The big guests...
Don't try to be funny!
You're gonna die!
By now, I'm guessing that the traitor Bege
has been beaten relentlessly by Mama!
That's good to know.
Sanji is not coming back yet.
The Straw Hats will be here shortly-rero.
...will come out!
What?!
What?! Straw Hat?!
Grr! You guess?! Your guess isn't enough!
I gotta make sure to tell her...
Oh, come on!
I don't ever wanna see them again!
Who did this?
Whoa-whoa.
--Well...
--Our Bobbin the Disposer...
When they're around,
everything goes wrong!
Who killed him?!
You need to keep resting, Pekoms.
LOAN SHARK KING
W-We haven't found the killer yet.
Father wants you to attend the meeting too-rero.
But, Praline,
in case they stop him from telling her... Grr!
We're investigating!
"GOD OF FORTUNE" DU FELD
Listen, guys.
Don't be late.
When did he get shot?
We're gonna crash Big Mom's tea party
and the wedding
If that's your concern,
it's even better for you to leave it to Jimbei!
Probably, late at night.
The Straw Hats did it?
You'll be beaten again in your condition now.
Just keep quiet!
and save Sanji's family!
Straw Hat? No way...
QUEEN OF THE PLEASURE DISTRICT
I can't believe it!
Then, Sanji'll be back with us!
Brother Opera said he burned Straw Hat
and Cat Burglar to death after torturing them.
I've got no choice!
He's right, Pekoms!
As a ship's doctor, I won't allow you to go!
STUSSY
I don't know about that.
I can't trust him until I see their dead bodies.
Don't ever get up!
He's right! He's right!
C-Caesar?
No, I am Bege's sworn brother...
--Yeah.
--Rest! Rest!
MAJOR UNDERTAKER
I have a report.
Someone saw Sanji-sama heading to
the outskirts of the city late last night.
B... Big...
"Gangster" Gastino!
"GANGSTER" GASTINO
DRUG PECLO
What? Sanji?!
Straw Hat and Sanji...
You guys are acting weird.
--He's not trying hard enough to hide...
--"Gastino"?
Luffy! She's the Emperor of the Sea...
Gulp!
PRESIDENT OF THE WORLD ECONOMIC JOURNAL
If either of them killed Bobbin...
There was something going on
all through the night in the inlet.
Because he's a gas human?
I don't want risk everyone's...
I mean, Nami-san's life over a personal issue!
The way he laughs is the same!
The wedding is out of the question.
"BIG NEWS" MORGANS
I saw some people carrying things around!
Oh, you're not him. Sorry.
So...
No, you are right!
He's obviously Caesar!
Gulp!
IN FRONT OF SANJI'S ROOM
WAREHOUSE KINGPIN
Where's Sanji?
We can't let Pekoms know that
Jimbei is trying to be part of...
He's in here.
What?!
Oh, so it is you!
Why are you here?!
Any visitors?
After we saw him sleeping in his bed last night,
no one entered or left.
GIBERSON "THE HIDER"
You think I'm here because I wanted to be?!
You idiot!
...the Big Mom assassination plot.
Yay!
Because of you fools,
I was handed over to Big Mom
Are you sure?
I appreciate that you saved me
but I gotta go!
Yes, sir! I am sure!
SHIPPING KING
and when I was in a desperate situation,
he threatened me with my heart again!
Damn you!
No, no, we can't allow that!
I heard you and Luffy got into a big fight
so I was worried, you idiot!
What do you mean by that? Grr!
I've been pushed around!
"DEEP-SEA CURRENTS" UMIT
Hey, Sanji! You there?!
Tell Trafalgar Law
that I'll kill him when I see him again!
What are you guys hiding?!
I'm so relieved! Really, you idiot!
GULP!!
Hey! Are you there?!
Gulp!!
If I get a chance, I'll kill you too!
You simpleton!
Cut it out! That's so dull!
Why did you get invited-nen, undertaker?
Oh? Sanji-san?
If we do that, then Sanji-kun will
come back to us, right, Luffy?!
Sanji-san?! Where are you?!
You're so small-minded
Stop it
Stussy-sama!
That's just a waste of time.
O... O... Oh no-nasu...
Can't an undertaker celebrate
people's weddings?
Straw Hat.
On top of Sanji-san's disappearance,
if they find out that I was sleeping...
Nami-san... I...
I won't have anyone who smells so much like blood
talking shit about me, Du Feld!
Do you wanna join hands or not?
Oh, Sanji-kun.
This is it!
M-Mama will kill me-nasu!
FIRE TANK PIRATES' BASE
This is Bege's base!
Hey, I'm so happy to be invited
For terrifying me like that...
What's wrong?! Aren't you there?!
What should I do-nasu?! What should I do-nasu?!
What should I do-nasu?!
Morgans-sama!
This marriage will make a headline!
Germa and our company are strongly tied
I'm coming in.
I'll never forgive you!
So, what kind of guy is he?
But it's a story that has already been
spread across the underworld
You heard what Jimbei said.
Nami...
You coward!
--So it's too old!
--That's right, that's right
How annoying...
What do you want from me this early?
It doesn't need to be transported
First, let me punch you for shooting Pekoms!
But let's forget about it for now.
There isn't much time left before the tea party.
Were you in the room this whole time?
Hi there, how are you?
Welcome
Think of him as a scheming
and brutal mafia boss.
Of course.
I'm gonna get you back no matter what,
Sanji-kun!
Perospero-kun
Here I go!
Leaders of the underworld
What?! Is it a proposal, Nami-san?!
THUMP
Is there anyone who can prove
that you were here?
If you walk through the castle
you're going to be a little late
Stop it!
I don't know why but I feel as ease.
You ordered a soldier to watch me.
Would you like me to... Lick...
What?!
...take you there?
Hey! Eggplant Soldier!
My hero! Vinsmoke Sanji of Germa!
Alright, Luffy, we know what to do now.
Pull back your fist, Luffy!
We can't come to an agreement like this!
Y-Yes-nasu.
Yeah.
Was Sanji here the whole time?
I'm happy to see you again-rero!
But he shot my friend!
By the way, Sanji's sister saved my life.
Y-Yes-nasu.
Wow!
It's you...
Are you sure?
Someone talks bad about Father,
I can't take!
Hey, where's everyone else?
Are you Bege?
Y-Yes-nasu.
No, Gotti! Calm down-rero!
Don't be in such a rush.
They are here or rero.
Cut it out!
I don't care. Let him do it.
Hey, isn't that enough?
What do you mean by "rero"?!
So I wanna save them all.
I gotta get ready for the wedding.
Kick these bastards out!
Oh, Luffy! Sanji!
Yes, let's save them all.
You back off!
Sanji!
By the Candy Escalator!
But it won't be easy.
Why?!
Not yet.
You made me worried, you bastard!
Even though we're not aiming to
take Big Mom down,
What?
I'm sorry for that... Hm?
I knew this would happen...
Straw Hat died.
she always looks forward to
those tea parties.
Well, it can't be helped...
That aside,
why do you look like that?
Do you like Big Mom?
By crashing it,
we'll unleash the Emperor's wrath.
Why don't you guys go take a bath too?
I see.
--No way!
But I don't believe it.
That means you're on the same side.
--This is amazing!
--His candy sculptures are always...
Why are you relaxing?! We don't have time!
And you don't even like to bathe!
Straw Hat is still alive and plotting something
secretly with you, isn't he?
Even if you don't share the same lifestyle or goal,
you have the same enemy to beat!
No, you two must take one too-rero.
On top of that, I think you guys have already faced
various Ministers on the island,
...very artistic!
I'm a prince of Germa Kingdom
who will marry Big Mom's daughter today.
And then, we'll talk-rero.
You can kill each other later,
A bath under these circumstances?!
but if you join hands now
it'll be in everyone's favor!
I'm humbled.
but they are just the tip of the iceberg
of the Big Mom Pirates.
Father doesn't see anyone who is dirty.
I don't care if a low-class pirate plots something
or dies a dog's death.
Mama hates late arrivals.
Even tougher ones will attend the tea party.
So shall we?
Who's dirty?!
If my preparation runs late because of you,
Oh, the staircase is moving!
And underground rulers
from around the world are invited too.
Big Mom'll get mad, don't you think?
What's your plan?!
How beautiful!
I have the perfect plan.
This is great. Very easy.
Let's just do it!
Then, I'll be through with you guys!
Let's go.
See you later.
On the other side, there are only...
You can have these.
Wait for three minutes
and you can lick the Candy Escalator too.
Good job.
You surprised me-nasu!
Now, I got to go too.
Hey, Sanji!
What should I do-nasu?!
To the hellish...
...Tea Party.
Sanji, what are you doing?!
What should I do-nasu?!
The guests have arrived!
What?!
Lola was turned into a warthog zombie?!
...ten of us.
S-Sanji-san?
Hey! Don't count us in!
And she was chasing around
the guy who she fell in love with!
Shh! Be quiet and do as I say.
It's for your own good too.
Don't fudge it!
There are only eight of you!
That sounds like her!
I hope you all get killed!
At that time and again
in the forest of monsters,
Sanji-san,
where have you been until now-nasu?
Luffy.
I don't know what would've happened to me
if it weren't for Lola.
I've already told everyone down here,
I see! But you guys saved my sister too!
Thank you!
but I need to share something
that sounds slightly unrelated.
They're rulers of the underworld.
I told you.
I went out to deliver Pudding-chan food.
Oh, I'm crying tears of joy.
You know Capone "Gang" Bege, right?
Bege.
We have been very close since we were kids.
Oh, that's right-nasu.
I have no interest in
the assassination of Big Mom
Because we're twins!
Don't ask what happened after that.
It's not cool.
but is she the kind of person
who can be killed by guns and cannons to begin with?
A zombie! I can't imagine a dead person moving.
The sea is like a wonderland!
O-Okay-nasu...
And so, Lola has turned back to a human.
Yeah. I'm sure she's still
doing well as a pirate.
My impression of her is like an iron balloon.
It feels like it's impossible to kill her.
I wonder if she found someone to marry...
CHEESE TOWN, MILK ISLAND
Today is a holiday because of the Tea Party!
Yeah, if you call it an assassination,
you have to kill her in one blow.
Big Mom sounded so mad when she talked about
Lola running away from a marriage.
Let's celebrate with Supreme cheese and beer!
Otherwise you'll be in a siege and killed.
Smells good.
So Pudding-sama's old enough to marry now.
Please come in.
The groom is Germa 66's third son.
We'll have a strong ally!
Is the Emperor of the Sea
as strong as they say?
This place always looks delicious-nen.
Of course! She's a monster!
Welcome, guests.
Yeah... that was a big deal.
PEANUT TOWN, NUTS ISLAND
Hi, Smoothie.
She wasn't even awake when we tried to get Brook back
but I thought we were gonna die!
The family of the Du Feld
Conglomerate has arrived.
What?
Would you like a welcome drink?
Mama is reviled by all Giants
in the world for a reason.
A bunch of celebrities will attend as guests!
Today, we have a piece of Mt. Mauri Lava,
a beautiful woman who stabbed a thousand men,
She is someone who even killed her own son
for sweets.
Congratulations!
All Giants in the world?
It's a little too early!
The Minister has arrived! Open the gate!
CHOCOLAT TOWN, CACAO ISLAND
That's why even though
Totto Land has a diverse population,
and a giraffe that makes funny sounds.
That's okay! I'm so happy!
There's no need.
Despite that, why did you choose
the tea party with all of her Top Officers in attendance,
--I'll have a cup of the giraffe.
--Me too.
Today's Sanji-sama's wedding.
there are no Giants.
I'll open it.
Okay. I'll squeeze it now.
The escort soldiers couldn't
even enter the castle.
as the stage of the assassination, Bege-san?
Giants really exist!
THIRD SON OF CHARLOTTE
(MINISTER OF BEANS)
BIG MOM PIRATES
Obviously, we can't attend either.
One day,
Well, it's no wonder you'd ask that.
Of course not.
No one needs a guard for a wedding.
a man showed up saying he
had fallen in love with Lola
That's very funny!
CHARLOTTE DAIFUKU
First, let me answer...
at first sight and wanted to marry her.
Yeah, it should be a peaceful day.
Under certain conditions,
all we need is five seconds to be able to kill Big Mom!
Here you go.
WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU
And, believe it or not, he was
Loki the prince of Elbaph, the Giants' country!
Everyone from the Vinsmoke Family,
good morning!
Only five seconds?!
A prince?! Wow!
It's not only five seconds-rero!
Tastes great and it's smooth going down.
Mama became so happy and teary-eyed.
It's not that easy to steal five seconds
in the site-rero.
Yonji!
Wake up and change!
SIXTH FLOOR - A GUEST ROOM IN THE BAUM CAKE
She thought if Lola became
the princess of Elbaph,
What happened to Reiju?
She's not in her room.
Open it!
The Big Mom Pirates is made up of
a bunch of skilled fighters and they'll be there.
her long-standing feud with
the Giants would be resolved
I refuse your body search!
Oh yeah,
I haven't seen her since yesterday.
No, you can't do that, Mr. Jigra.
Within a split second,
people like the Sweet Generals will block us-rero!
and she'd even get access to their army
which is said to be the world's strongest.
Oh, Reiju-sama finished with her preparations
in another room.
Let go of me!
I said "Let go of me"!
I see.
Then, it'll become a head-on fight
and we have no chance of winning!
I can't wait for Mama's tea party.
I see...
There is still an hour before the Tea Party
so take your time.
ORGAN DEALER JIGRA
But she ran away.
BIG MOM'S TEA PARTY STARTS
Big Mom's tea party starts...
Is Big Mom already inside?
After that, everything went wrong.
IN FIVE HOURS
...in five hours.
Wh-What happened?!
NINTH FLOOR - BIG MOM'S BEDROOM
I got an invitation for
the last Tea Party too.
You know Capone "Gang" Bege, right?
This assassination plot was begun with
the capture of Caesar.
She tried to use me as a substitute,
Call the Ministers!
Yeah, he's the one who took Sanji away.
but he noticed that I wasn't Lola.
It's Gastino!
Don't ever call me that in front of Big Mom!
But for the life of me, I couldn't go.
I-It's not moving! It's dead!
And her relationship with the Giants
got even worse.
Because I had my mother's funeral!
Listen!
When we accomplish this mission,
you'll give me back my heart and free me!
My lovely skeleton!
Then, she gave up the idea of
becoming friendly with actual Giants
I wrote a letter explaining it
but what do you think
Big Mom sent me afterwards?!
That's the agreement!
and started investing in research
to turn people into giants.
Don't forget.
That's too bad but, Mama...!
If you break your promise,
I'll kill your son at any price!
Today, you have the Tea Party
that you've been waiting for...
He's one of the Worst Generation
with a name as infamous as yours.
Her anger towards Lola only amplified
and she was branded a criminal in this country!
And what else?
It was my hospitalized father's...
Stop worrying about that, Gas-hiko!
Bege will keep his word!
In the West Blue where he comes from,
five powerful mafia families...
If she comes back, she'll get killed!
The wedding cake!
Gas-hiko?! No, it's Gastino!
Furthermore, she couldn't stand looking at me
because I look exactly like Lola...
...rule their underground society.
Gas-hiko!
The Five Families of the West -
one of the bosses of the five...
You little...!
Get that damn face out of my sight!
Doesn't matter...
Whatever your name is now, you're still a loser.
Mr. Morgans and all the other VIPs
have already arrived.
...was "Gang" Bege.
Every time I saw her, she hit me without mercy.
So, for years, I always had fresh wounds.
His nickname "Gang" traces
back to his younger days
You see, he has an important job,
which is...
\when he became notorious as a hit-man.
That's right!
EASTERN INLET, WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
I thought I'd be killed by my own mother!
A hit-man...
Let me show you what I made!
I heard he was a sick young man
who liked to hurt helpless living things
I can't see that monster
as my mother anymore!
Deadly poison gas - KX Launchers!
Hey! Who shot?! He's a guest!
You can't do this to me!
Untie me, Grr!
and watch them get weaker and weaker.
One is enough but I made two extras!
Each of them can inject five grams of
deadly organophosphate...
ALADDIN
THE FIRST MATE OF THE SUN PIRATES
We'll leave some water and food.
But since Lola is a happy-go-lucky girl,
You are...
I'm sorry but I'm sure
someone'll find you soon.
How terrible is that?
I guess she'd never imagine
that her mother wants to kill her.
...d-directly into your body!
He did the same to crime families.
Screw you!
Where are you guys going?! Grr!
It's the most audaciously sinful murder weapon
in history!
ONE OF THE SWEET 3 GENERALS
I see... Everything makes sense now.
BIG MOM PIRATES
--We'll leave this country.
--What?!
SECOND SON OF CHARLOTTE
That's why you guys were
carrying out your stuff all night long...
The gas will destroy average people
by just touching their skin.
So when Bege said he was going to kill Mama,
I felt nothing at all.
BOUNTY: 1 BILLION 57 MILLION BERRIES
How does it taste?
I wish it were more bitter.
Goodbye.
So if it's injected directly into your body...
Then, how about this?
You might think I'm terrible
but that's the truth.
Sweet General Katakuri!
You guys are the Big Mom Pirates' affiliate
and you're leaving the country...
CHARLOTTE KATAKURI
Boss!
Well, well, the bath felt so good!
I'm 100 percent sure...
That means you're betraying Mama.
No, 200 percent sure that you'll...
You little...
Why did you shoot him?!
Does she know about this?!
Ah, just like heaven!
...die!
You're definitely gonna die!
We can't let her know.
The lead tastes bitter, doesn't it?
No, I refuse to move on to the next life!
This is what he was going to say.
I want everyone to die!
She'll kill those who leave.
Feels like we finished fighting.
I can't get loose. We still have to fight!
That's who she is, right?
"What do you think
Big Mom sent me afterwards?"
Even when he became a young mobster,
he always aimed to kill bosses of the underworld
Okay, I get the picture.
So you have a weapon
that will kill her if it hits?
Jimbei expresses his gratitude to you.
and even after he got his own family,
he only killed his rival bosses.
"It was my hospitalized father's head."
Luffy-san, Luffy-san.
He does?!
No, unfortunately,
I found milk in here!
even if this shell hits her
when she's at full strength,
"I'm here today to get revenge."
We're very lucky to hear Pekoms' story.
Hey, don't go into our fridge without asking!
it won't pierce through her hard skin.
"Open the gate."
Bege?
I don't think Bege can pull off his plan
to kill Big Mom that easily
Bang.
Don't resist.
That's exactly what I needed.
My tooth has cracked.
Bang, he shot.
There aren't that many weapons
that'll work against Big Mom in this world!
What? Are you betraying me?!
Two of your men would've been shot.
but I can't believe Mama is plotting
an assassination of Germa too.
I got my face broken.
You're outnumbered!
That's right.
Bege!
Thank you for the milk!
If Luffy and his clan find out about it,
they'll push themselves to save Sanji.
My sword...
Is it wrong for me to throw a jelly
bean at him before that happens?
...was bounced off her body too.
But Bege...
They'll be in danger and I can't just sit back!
I've got to help them!
...never showed interest in
his enemy's post or territory.
Then it's pointless to have that thing!
Luke Bege.
He just took money and goods.
You gotta pay attention.
Tell Mama that it was my call.
That means I will raise...
BLOODY TRAGEDY! AN INTERNAL FEUD?!
I said it wouldn't work when she's at full strength.
WAKING NIGHTMARE! UNDERGROUND REMAINS TENSE
Oh, all healed!
...a full-fledged rebellion.
This is what you're gonna say.
THE UNDERGROUND SOCIETY IN CHAOS
TRIGGERED BY THE ASSASSINATION?
There are two conditions we need
to make the KX Launcher work at its best.
CHARLOTTE PRALINE
21TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE, MARRIED TO ALADDIN
How is that possible?!
I will betray Big Mom.
"I see."
Hey, guys.
Have you really washed yourselves-rero?
To fufill my duty to her,
I once told her directly that I was leaving.
"Alright then."
First, we need a setting where
no one can attack us for five seconds.
Afterwards he enjoyed watching
bloody tugs-of-war within groups
Yeah, totally!
Let us see Bege already!
He'll be the biggest pain
in the ass at the party.
Second, Mama should be weakening.
and how it upset the leaders
that were secretly connected.
But I took it back,
Not yet-rero.
He has trained his Haki of
the Color of Observation
because of the numbers
written on the roulette.
What kind of convenient situation is that?
He is really a disgusting man.
so much and now he can see
slightly ahead into future.
Those numbers represent the number of my friends
who would be victimized along with me!
Oh, how cute!
His bounty is over a billion.
What are you doing?!
I didn't know he had such history.
He's a monster!
There is one place where all those conditions
will be met...
He was a terrible person.
Can we wear these?!
That's why I need you all
to get away from here.
I see... Alright then.
But when you hit someone,
you'll get hit back.
How do I look?
The price that Big Mom wanted me to pay...
50...
That's the tea party!
He began to be targeted constantly
by those seeking vengeance.
...was an unreasonable sanction
that was more than taking my life!
No, 100 raiders...
Oh, Pez!
...are coming.
What?!
You're looking great, Brook!
On the day of the Tea Party,
the Hors-d'oeuvre Ships,
How do I look?
interceptors from each island,
will escort the guests
However,
I'm sorry! Your daddy-waddy was too loud!
Bege even enjoyed that.
He built an impregnable castle and fought back,
You look nice too!
ORGAN DEALING ASSASSIN GROUP
Hey, look what I found!
and security will be lax.
It's okay, it's okay!
And if something happens at the Tea Party,
it'll draw everyone's attention.
Riddle them with bullets!
It's been more than a year
since we allied with Mummzie-wumzies...
then mocked his enemy's disappointment.
That's useless.
Oh! That's so cool!
So that's your chance to escape!
An impregnable castle...
You're still speaking baby talk.
So I guess he still hasn't
shown all of his strength.
Right?
But we've never seen her get hurt.
Alright. We'll take the chance
and break out of Totto Land.
That's not working!
That's the robot from Germa's comic strip.
I guess Jigra couldn't wait for us.
After he got bored with life on land
and sailed out to sea, he did the same.
But it's still a deadly venture.
Even when she destroyed the city...
Why do they have that here?
The organs of the Tea Party guests
and the members of the Big Mom Pirates!
I'm prepared for that.
That's not a problem - but Jimbei,
Maybe, there's a big fan.
Boss!
Even when bullets...
Who did this?! Damn!
I'm gonna go on ahead.
We can sell them high
and make a fortune!
we just want to help you to become free.
...or bombshells hit her...
He became infamous for targeting only the captains of
well-known pirate groups.
Nami-san!
Yes, I know.
No, you don't!
Even when she sank a ship...
In order to save Straw Hat,
you'll even sacrifice yourself!
She didn't get even a single scratch
on her tough body.
Say I join the Straw Hats one day...
Can I have your liver?
For someone still targeted on the sea
by enemies seeking revenge,
Give us your hearts.
being under the wing of the Emperor of the Sea
is the perfect safe haven.
She is like an iron balloon
as you said.
I will fight for the captain Straw Hat Luffy
at the price of my life!
So he decided to affiliate with Big Mom.
But...
...there was one time
I saw Mummzie-wumzie getting a scratch.
Aladdin, it's just a matter of...
I appreciate how you work every day
so for the next tea party,
...doing it now or later.
You're talking about the incident of
Mother Carmel's picture-rero!
I see. Do as you like.
I decided to put you in charge of security.
Don't let me down.
That's right.
Can I have your liver?
This is your last chance.
But do your best to save your own life too.
What?
At tea parties, they always put a picture
in the seat directly across the table from Mama
Okay?
Once you come back with us,
I'll drive you like a horse.
I am honored.
Give us your hearts.
We'll set sail for the Fish-Man Island.
Damn!
and no one will sit there.
Your job is done, guys.
Be prepared!
If Big Mom finds out that we left her crew,
Big Mom thought highly of his finely
honed alertness and defensive capability.
It seems like
it's the most important treasure for her.
she may turn her rage on the Fish-Man Island.
Nami-san!
So he took the title of a "Rook" soldier
for the upcoming tea party
A picture?
Does that mean you'll never let me go?!
Yes.
You're worried about the Ryugu Kingdom too,
right?
It's a portrait of Mother Carmel!
You're extremely sexy after a bath too!
and has been entrusted with
full authority over its security.
CHARLOTTE OVEN
FOURTH SON OF CHARLOTTE (MINISTER OF BAKING)
You could say that's Mama's only weak point!
Why are you telling us this now, Jimbei?
I won't forgive you, Chiffon?!
I can't believe you!
CHARLOTTE DAIFUKU
THIRD SON OF CHARLOTTE (MINISTER OF BEANS)
Yes.
If security guards are on our side,
nothing can stand in our way.
How can you help someone
who wants to kill Mama!
Are you Big Mom's sons?!
We'll save it at any cost!
Who is that person?
Your organs will fetch high prices!
Seems like Mama is indebted to her
but we don't know the details.
Chiffon-sama, please think twice!
You know no one can ever kill Mama!
What?
What do you mean?
I'm sorry!
The main event of the tea
party is the wedding.
She's a figure of mystery.
Don't mention it!
We've known each other for decades.
Is she dead?
Rip all of their organs out!
Big Sis Brulee!
As you already know, Big Mom intends to
I heard she disappeared.
You know what she has done to me, don't you?!
We'll live to see each other again,
Jimbei!
You think you caught me like this?!
So she is a missing person.
kill all the members of the
Vinsmokes at the wedding
Even we family members don't know the specifics.
Lola is in danger
and Bege and Pez are my only family!
and acquire all of Germa.
I don't need anyone else!
Bege is going to kill Big Mom!
Once at a tea party, a servant accidentally
knocked it off the table...
Why would Jimbei feel grateful to me?
Oh, it's okay, it's okay.
What?!
--The knife melted!
--Run!
By the way, did he tell Mama...
What the hell?
Seems like everyone has their own plot!
Hurry up and get ready to leave!
They're too strong!
Yeah!
Alright! Let's go!
Hey, wait! You bastards!
You can't escape.
Yeah!
Luffy, Pekoms who guided you guys to this island
was actually taken by Bege and his clan,
Mother...
Wh-What the?!
Where've you been, Reiju?
It's none of your business.
and was approached to
cooperate with their plan.
I know you guys were partying until late.
Of course, I asked them to change my room.
I was stunned by Mama's reaction to it.
Pekoms... So that's what happened to him.
Don't interfere with adult stuff, idiot.
She turned pale and
let out a loud shriek that I'd never heard before!
Let's go.
The Tea Party will take place on the rooftop.
You underestimate Mama too much!
It was different from her Hunger Pangs!
At last,
we proud Germa 66 will have
Big Mom's power on our side
All we could do was just cover our ears
to protect our eardrums...
Since Pekoms is a very loyal man,
and rule the North Blue again!
People were passing out
and collapsing one after another!
Bege let him fall into shark-filled
waters to keep him quiet.
You're in a good mood.
Know your place, losers.
But most importantly...
On top of the shriek, she exercised
her Haki of the Color of the Supreme King!
Sanji hasn't run away, has he?
Th-They're monsters...
What?!
Both the groom and the bride are
fully prepared.
Just because of a jostled picture.
What are you thinking, Sanji?
Why didn't you escape?
The point is what happened next.
But...
You know what's going to happen.
...my friends saw that
and saved him in the nick of time.
Know your place!
Loser!
He is now resting.
Mama knelt down from shock
and, believe it or not,
Good. So he's okay.
He's been through a lot.
she scraped her knee
and it was bleeding!
Damn Bege, I'll make him pay!
I was surprised because I'd never thought
she had red blood like normal human beings.
Are you Bege?
No, I'm not!
You?
Meanwhile, Luffy is...
THE SEDUCING WOODS
Do you really think so?!
When she breaks down like that,
her body becomes fragile.
Luffy, here comes my main point.
Wait!
It'll be nice if we can make it out alive
but this is the Emperor of the Sea.
Then, which one of you is Bege?
Well, wait. He'll be here soon-rero.
I came up with a plan
after I learned everything from Pekoms.
So, at the tea party today,
Where did they go?!
It'll turn into a scene of carnage for sure.
if we break that picture in half,
what do you think will happen?!
I asked myself "What would you guys do?"
Okay, everyone's here, right?
I'm depressed.
And finally, at the Whole Cake Chateau...
And I was sure when you
learned the whole thing,
What's wrong?
Are you a bit cleaner now?
Pre-wedding jitters?
you would say you want to
save Sanji and his family.
I don't think so!
Mama would be devastated!
It's said "Clothes make the man."
It's about time.
And no one there would be able to move
for more than five seconds!
After I kill that stupid-ass Sanji,
I don't want his blood on me...
I won't do business with anyone
who doesn't care about their appearance.
I feel bad for Pekoms
but under the circumstances,
Then the KX Launcher will show
its real strength...
do you really want to
make an enemy of Bege?
...and in order to go back to being a good girl,
I gotta erase everyone's memories.
Now, we have three and a half hours to go.
and the Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom -
will die!
When I think about all that...
The tea party starts at 10 in the morning.
Let's decide.
What a pain in the ass!
About five hours from now.
First, whether or not we join forces...
The news of the assassination of Big Mom
will spread across the world!
Unlike the ten of us
who don't even have a plan yet...
But isn't that shriek gonna
make us paralyzed too?!
It's time for the Tea Party.
Don't count us in!
You damn brutes!
I'll let them know what you are up to!
Don't worry. We have these.
Listen, Luffy,
Bege's group is fully prepared for today.
"Invisible Symphonia System"!
At the Tea Party, the Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom
is plotting to kill
Oh, earplugs!
Everyone! Thank you for coming all this way!
every one of Germa including Sanji.
If just breaking a picture would create
such a big mess,
Luffy! Sanji!
we gotta save Sanji's family
at that moment too!
And at the same Tea Party, Capone "Gang" Bege
is scheming to assassinate Big Mom.
Let's join Bege!
Hey, don't think it's someone else's problem!
What?!
It'll take about three seconds
before Mama'll have the attack after breaking the picture.
Wherever you look, all you see is sweets!
During that commotion,
Sanji is planning to rescue his family.
If you're surrounded by the angry Big Mom Pirates
before it gets messy,
The Minister is here! Open the gate!
A FEW HOURS LATER
A few hours later,
There's no need.
Monkey D. Luffy, one of the Worst Generation,
it'll be miraculous for you
to stay alive for three seconds!
And the one that holds
the key to everything...
I need you to take that role, Straw Hat!
and Capone "Gang" Bege.
Eat!
...is Straw Hat Luffy!
Wait a minute!
That means Luffy is going to be bait!
Drink!
And enjoy the party to your heart's content!
Bege! Nami and her friends saved Lola!
Between these two pirates,
an unprecedented operation is hatched.
How could you ask him to take a deadly role?!
CHARLOTTE OVEN
MINISTER OF BAKING (FOURTH SON OF CHARLOTTE)
BIG MOM PIRATES
Okay!
Enjoy everything...
Everyone has their own objectives...
I'll do it!
BIG MOM'S TEA PARTY STARTS
IN THREE AND A HALF HOURS
...that'll take place here!
Big Mom's tea party starts
in three and a half hours.
...and the hellish Tea Party starts soon!
What?!
Big Mom's tea party starts in three hours.
Leaders of the underground and
a whole new set of Big Mom's
Changing into a new outfit,
Big Mom, Germa, the bride Pudding!
They each have their own agendas and schemes!
Luffy and Bege finally sneak
into the hellish Tea Party!
Luffy vs. Bege!
The chaotic meeting finally starts!
Luffy and the others prepare
for the impending tea party!
strongest and most terrible children
gather at a gorgeous venue!
The dignified groom Sanji and
the lovely bride Pudding!
There's only one weak point for them
to take down the invincible Big Mom.
The two rogues from the East and the West!
As the clock ticks down to the hellish tea party,
Dark plots and strategies
behind their smiles!
When the man with a billion berries bounty?
What is the secret weapon that holds the key
to fulfill the mission?
Luffy and Bege are incompatible
with each other!
the most important role in the assassination mission of
Big Mom is entrusted to Luffy!
Sweet General Katakuri's
horrific ability is revealed,
While a tense mutual deception gears up,
a bloody wedding begins!
In a tense atmosphere,
a forbidden meeting now begins!
An unprecedented pirate alliance is formed!
the hellish Tea Party finally starts!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Deadly Pact! Luffy & Bege's Allied Forces!"
"The Broken Couple! Sanji and Pudding Enter!"
"Luffy Engages in a Secret Maneuver!
The Wedding Full of Conspiracies Starts Soon!"
"The Family Gets Together! The
Hellish Tea Party Starts!"
"A Secret Meeting! Luffy
vs. the Fire Tank Pirates!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!