My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
There is a place that I want to go with you
susumiyuku kouro nara
The sea route that we take
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
Sanji parted ways with the Straw Hats
after the duel against Luffy.
He thought he was determined but
he found himself leaving
the Whole Cake Chateau.
Afterwards, Luffy and Sanji saw each
other again at the rendezvous point.
Say what you really want!
I...
I wanna go back to the Sunny!
But I can't get the courage to run away!
Once the wedding begins, I know...
...I can't stop anything by myself!
I don't even consider...
...those scum as my family!
But I...
I wanna save their lives!
Well, that's how you are.
You got us! Let's crash the wedding!
"Sanji Comes Back!
Crash! The Tea Party from Hell!"
OUTSKIRTS OF SWEET CITY
Jimbei came to help?!
Yeah, I was surprised too.
That's good. So Nami-san is okay too...
But now, the problem is
how we join them.
Once they hear you're coming back,
I'm sure they'll be happy.
Goodbye!
Sorry - we should never have done this!
I'm too ashamed to see Nami-san...
Nami and the others care about you
more than I did.
But I scared her.
Oh, the rain is stopping.
MIRRO-WORLD
I found it!
You sure?! Chobro!
Do you think they can hear us
through this piece of glass?
The mirror I was talking
through the last time we spoke
broke on the tree monster Kingbaum's head.
It broke!
So...
...I think there is at least a piece of glass
that connects to this one.
Hey! Luffy!
Hey!
Luffy!
Are you there, Luffy?!
--Is that...?
--It's Chopper!
Hey!
Answer me if you're there!
Chopper!
Luffy!
Hey!
Luffy! Can you hear me?!
Here it is!
This is it! It's a piece of glass!
Can you hear me?!
Why is his voice coming from a mirror?
It's a long story but
they're in a mirror dimension.
A mirror dimension? Chopper and the others?!
Are you okay, Chopper?
Oh, Luffy! Great! You're really there!
Luffy! Is Sanji-kun there too?!
Yeah, he's here!
That's great!
So you got to see him again, Luffy!
Yay!
Sanji-san, I'm glad that you're okay.
How are you guys?
We saved everybody from
inside the mirror, Luffy!
Brook even got a copy of the Ponegliff!
Really?!
I'm impressed with you guys!
Y-Your compliment doesn't make me happy,
you fool!
You fool!
You silly little goose!
Luffy, it's good that Sanji's there
but did you guys come to an agreement?
Sanji is not coming back yet.
What?!
Listen, guys.
We're gonna crash Big Mom's tea party
and the wedding
and save Sanji's family!
Then, Sanji'll be back with us!
B... Big...
Luffy! She's the Emperor of the Sea...
I don't want risk everyone's...
I mean, Nami-san's life over a personal issue!
So...
Yay!
Damn you!
I heard you and Luffy got into a big fight
so I was worried, you idiot!
I'm so relieved! Really, you idiot!
You simpleton!
If we do that, then Sanji-kun will
come back to us, right, Luffy?!
Nami-san... I...
Oh, Sanji-kun.
For terrifying me like that...
I'll never forgive you!
Nami...
But let's forget about it for now.
There isn't much time left before the tea party.
I'm gonna get you back no matter what,
Sanji-kun!
What?! Is it a proposal, Nami-san?!
THUMP
I don't know why but I feel as ease.
Alright, Luffy, we know what to do now.
Yeah.
By the way, Sanji's sister saved my life.
So I wanna save them all.
Yes, let's save them all.
But it won't be easy.
Even though we're not aiming to
take Big Mom down,
she always looks forward to
those tea parties.
By crashing it,
we'll unleash the Emperor's wrath.
On top of that, I think you guys have already faced
various Ministers on the island,
but they are just the tip of the iceberg
of the Big Mom Pirates.
Even tougher ones will attend the tea party.
And underground rulers
from around the world are invited too.
On the other side, there are only...
...ten of us.
Hey! Don't count us in!
Don't fudge it!
There are only eight of you!
I hope you all get killed!
Luffy.
I've already told everyone down here,
but I need to share something
that sounds slightly unrelated.
You know Capone "Gang" Bege, right?
The Minister has arrived! Open the gate!
There's no need.
I'll open it.
THIRD SON OF CHARLOTTE
(MINISTER OF BEANS)
BIG MOM PIRATES
CHARLOTTE DAIFUKU
I can't wait for Mama's tea party.
BIG MOM'S TEA PARTY STARTS
Big Mom's tea party starts...
IN FIVE HOURS
...in five hours.
You know Capone "Gang" Bege, right?
Yeah, he's the one who took Sanji away.
He's one of the Worst Generation
with a name as infamous as yours.
In the West Blue where he comes from,
five powerful mafia families...
...rule their underground society.
The Five Families of the West -
one of the bosses of the five...
...was "Gang" Bege.
His nickname "Gang" traces
back to his younger days
\when he became notorious as a hit-man.
A hit-man...
I heard he was a sick young man
who liked to hurt helpless living things
and watch them get weaker and weaker.
How terrible is that?
He did the same to crime families.
How does it taste?
I wish it were more bitter.
Then, how about this?
Boss!
You little...
The lead tastes bitter, doesn't it?
Even when he became a young mobster,
he always aimed to kill bosses of the underworld
and even after he got his own family,
he only killed his rival bosses.
Bege?
Don't resist.
What? Are you betraying me?!
You're outnumbered!
Bege!
But Bege...
...never showed interest in
his enemy's post or territory.
He just took money and goods.
BLOODY TRAGEDY! AN INTERNAL FEUD?!
WAKING NIGHTMARE! UNDERGROUND REMAINS TENSE
THE UNDERGROUND SOCIETY IN CHAOS
TRIGGERED BY THE ASSASSINATION?
Afterwards he enjoyed watching
bloody tugs-of-war within groups
and how it upset the leaders
that were secretly connected.
He is really a disgusting man.
I didn't know he had such history.
He was a terrible person.
But when you hit someone,
you'll get hit back.
He began to be targeted constantly
by those seeking vengeance.
However,
Bege even enjoyed that.
He built an impregnable castle and fought back,
then mocked his enemy's disappointment.
An impregnable castle...
So I guess he still hasn't
shown all of his strength.
After he got bored with life on land
and sailed out to sea, he did the same.
Boss!
Who did this?! Damn!
He became infamous for targeting only the captains of
well-known pirate groups.
For someone still targeted on the sea
by enemies seeking revenge,
being under the wing of the Emperor of the Sea
is the perfect safe haven.
So he decided to affiliate with Big Mom.
I appreciate how you work every day
so for the next tea party,
I decided to put you in charge of security.
Don't let me down.
I am honored.
Big Mom thought highly of his finely
honed alertness and defensive capability.
So he took the title of a "Rook" soldier
for the upcoming tea party
and has been entrusted with
full authority over its security.
Why are you telling us this now, Jimbei?
If security guards are on our side,
nothing can stand in our way.
What?
What do you mean?
The main event of the tea
party is the wedding.
As you already know, Big Mom intends to
kill all the members of the
Vinsmokes at the wedding
and acquire all of Germa.
Bege is going to kill Big Mom!
What?!
What the hell?
Seems like everyone has their own plot!
Luffy, Pekoms who guided you guys to this island
was actually taken by Bege and his clan,
and was approached to
cooperate with their plan.
Pekoms... So that's what happened to him.
You underestimate Mama too much!
Since Pekoms is a very loyal man,
Bege let him fall into shark-filled
waters to keep him quiet.
What?!
But...
...my friends saw that
and saved him in the nick of time.
He is now resting.
Good. So he's okay.
He's been through a lot.
Damn Bege, I'll make him pay!
Luffy, here comes my main point.
I came up with a plan
after I learned everything from Pekoms.
I asked myself "What would you guys do?"
And I was sure when you
learned the whole thing,
you would say you want to
save Sanji and his family.
I feel bad for Pekoms
but under the circumstances,
do you really want to
make an enemy of Bege?
The tea party starts at 10 in the morning.
About five hours from now.
Unlike the ten of us
who don't even have a plan yet...
Don't count us in!
You damn brutes!
I'll let them know what you are up to!
Listen, Luffy,
Bege's group is fully prepared for today.
Luffy! Sanji!
Let's join Bege!
What?!
A FEW HOURS LATER
A few hours later,
Monkey D. Luffy, one of the Worst Generation,
and Capone "Gang" Bege.
Between these two pirates,
an unprecedented operation is hatched.
Changing into a new outfit,
Luffy and the others prepare
for the impending tea party!
The two rogues from the East and the West!
Luffy and Bege are incompatible
with each other!
In a tense atmosphere,
a forbidden meeting now begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Secret Meeting! Luffy
vs. the Fire Tank Pirates!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!