Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
I will definitely get you there.
Don't die... Nami... Sanji...!
"The Island Where Snow Lives!
Climb The Drum Rockies!"
Ahhh! Please look at that!
We found them, Wapol-sama!
Hold it, brat!
Huh? You guys're...
How dare you do
many rude things to me!
--I'll chew you guys up!
--Get out of my way.
--Humph! You're stupid, aren't you?
Why would I get out of your way?!
Looks like what you have on your
back and in your arm are half-dead.
Hold it! Oh, I know!
Chess! I thought up a new law.
Write this down.
Yes sir!
Those who ignore the king
are to be executed!
Ignoring me already?!
Guys! First, get the sick and injured ones,
who are ignoring me the most!
--Yes sir!
What'd you say?!
I'll take the woman on his back!
I'll take the man.
Take this! Marimo's Surprise!
Listen Luffy!
Don't you dare fight.
Whether you attack or get struck,
Nami-san will feel the whole impact too!
Damn you! You'll regret this!
Don't follow me!
Humph. What a coward... It's no use.
I'll show him...
what a battle in a snowy area is like...
Huh...?
There's no one... What's going on?
I wonder if they've already given up...
Now this is a true battle in a snowy area!
The white disguise!
Snow Powder Makeup!
Since they're so weak,
they'll be dead with just one shot.
Check Mate!
Stop it!
White bears...
Lapins?!
Did they protect him?
It's a coincidence.
Lapins never become attached to humans.
You are...
Thanks! You saved me!
Don't let him get away!
Yes sir!
What the hell do they
think they're doing?!
Doctor...
So this is it...
I can't see the top.
I can find the doctor... up there...
Hang in there a little longer...
Nami! Sanji!
Avalanche...
We were swallowed by the avalanche...
Ah! U... Usopp-san?!
Usopp-san!
Usopp-san! Come on! Wake up!
He's still alive!
Usopp-san! Hang on!
Come on! Usopp-san! Usopp-san!
Oh Vivi... Don't wake me up.
I was just having a beautiful dream.
A field of beautiful flowers out of
this world and a beautiful river... Oh?
--You're almost in the netherworld!
--Isn't that Zoro swimming in the river...?
--Wake up! Don't sleep! Wake up!
All 74,000 Usopp Pirates, close in!
No! Wake up! Usopp-san,
don't die! Usopp-san!
Usopp-san! Usopp-san! Usopp-san!
Phew, you saved me, Vivi.
Talk about having a
narrow escape from death.
I'm glad I'm alive.
But...
--don't you think my face is kinda swollen?
--I-it's chilblains! Chilblains!
--My head feels kinda heavy...
--This is why it's not easy
to be in a snowy area.
--My head feels kinda heavy...
--This is why it's not easy
to be in a snowy area.
--Or should I say my view is kinda narrow...
--More importantly,
--we have to figure out our location
and the situation we're in quickly!
--Or should I say my view is kinda narrow...
--we have to figure out our location
and the situation we're in quickly!
--My lips are kinda big... Kinda...
--we have to figure out our location
and the situation we're in quickly!
--yeah, I agree...
Ahhh! What's that?!
Ahhh... That was close...
I saw a field of flowers...
Suddenly hitting an avalanche in
this cold... I must've run out of luck.
But this is a sort of
winter swimming, I guess.
Zoro.
Hm? Oh, Vivi.
Huh?
Hm?
Oh, it's you, Usopp!
What're you guys doing here?
That's my question!
What idiots!
That's what you lowly bunnies
get for going against the king!
Humph! I didn't think I'd use my
real power on mere bunnies, though.
It couldn't be helped...
since they're the most
violent animal in Drum.
Just wait... Straw Hat!
Doctor...!
Ah! Ow!
Sanji!
Th-that... that was close...
Winter swimming?!
Yeah. After swimming
in the river for a while,
I had no idea where I was any more.
So I was walking while
doing muscle training,
and then I ended up in a forest.
Dressed like that?
You're stupid, aren't you?
Anyway, give me your coat, Usopp.
No way.
Nami-san might've gotten sick
due to mental exhaustion...
--Then your shoes!
--No!
--One of them!
It's your own fault, isn't it?!
Look over there! There're people.
Hm?
Hey... I remember those buildings...
What?
You're right! This is Big Horn!
We ended up... coming back!
Step back! Step back!
Dalton is already dead!
There's no way Dalton-san
would die from an attack like that!
You guys're Dalton-san's
ex-subordinates, aren't you?!
Don't you care?!
We're retainers of King Wapol!
If you become Wapol-sama's enemy,
you're dead meat!
Hey, what's the matter?
Wh-what's the matter?
What's the matter with you,
dressing like that?!
Dalton-san's buried under
the snow of the avalanche!
What?!
Dalton-san is?!
Yeah. We can't dig him out
because those guys get in our way.
Step back! Step back!
If you have any objection,
go right ahead and bring it on!
Usopp, I remember their clothes.
They're the ones who attacked
us on the sea, right? Right?!
Yeah, that's right.
Then they're our enemy, aren't they?
They're our enemy, right?
What's the word? Are they on our side?!
Well, they're our enemy...
but why are you so...
You aren't so courageous
without Dalton, are you?
What?! Mr. Bushido!
Who's that?!
Hey you! Stop it!
If you attack them, you'll...
This is warm! I'm borrowing it!
You... asked me because of that...?!
--Look! They're angry!
--You!
You were on the ship with that
guy who blew Wapol-sama away!
Oh? You guys never learn, do you?
Are you guys looking for...
these?
Bring him down!
Hawk Wave!
Oh, it's already over?
What a disappointing bunch...
Amazing...
All right! Good job, Zoro!
Just as I instructed!
Let's find Dalton-san!
Yeah!
Thank you!
Hurry up! Dig everywhere!
So, what's all this fuss?
I'll explain it later! Let's help them!
Dalton-san! Please be alive!
Doctor... Doctor...
Doctor...
Hang in there. We're almost there.
Don't you die on me!
We made it...
Doctor...
Doctorine...
The antibodies are responding.
Yeah, I figured that much.
Then, what's the cause? Explain.
Kestia...
That's right. Kestia.
You attend the girl.
Okay.
Who are you?
Even this sleepless town
has dozed off for now
From today forth,
something's going to change
I'm sure I can start fresh,
since I'm not alone
Just by having you by my side,
I feel I can become strong
I wonder how far I can go,
towards the place that leads to the future
Off in the distance it shines,
encompassing the world
Before dawn
Hey wait, reindeer!
Don't run away, meat!
Hold on, Nami-san! I'll cook a
nutritious reindeer dish right away!
I don't care about the food.
I just want some peace and quiet.
Huh? Wasn't that reindeer speaking?
Come to think of it, I sort of
remember him standing on two legs.
He's a monster!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Blue-nosed Reindeer!
Chopper's Secret"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!