kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
There is a place that I want to go with you
susumiyuku kouro nara
The sea route that we take
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
Sanji and Pudding's bloodbath wedding
finally began.
Luffy and Sanji who had parted ways
finally reunited at the rendezvous.
Sanji and Pudding's bloodbath wedding
finally began.
Luffy and Sanji who had parted ways
finally reunited at the rendezvous.
Sanji and Pudding's bloodbath wedding
finally began.
With the gunshot cue, Luffy and the others
went into action to break the portrait.
Luffy and the others successfully broke
the portrait of Mother Carmel,
We're gonna crash Big Mom's tea party
and the wedding
To assassinate Big Mom, a plan was hatched
in which Luffy shatters the
portrait Big Mom holds dear
I...
and save Sanji's family!
but their objective - Big Mom's shriek -
hasn't come yet.
Now, I'm leaving the Big Mom Pirates!
after which Bege delivers a final blow.
Then, Sanji'll be back with us!
I wanna go back to the Sunny!
In order to accomplish that,
However, the assassination plot of the Vinsmokes
has already been put into action.
Luffy allied with Capone "Gang" Bege
who is plotting to kill the Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom.
That means you're my enemy now, right?
What a beautiful eye!
Listen, guys.
We're gonna crash Big Mom's tea party
and the wedding
With the Tea Party close at hand,
the guests showed up one after another.
Oh, boy.
I've never seen such a pathetic assassination as this!
Jimbei!
Being moved by Sanji's unexpected kindness,
Pudding couldn't shoot him...
Go to hell!
and save Sanji's family!
This is more like just
violence instead. Lick.
Then, Sanji'll be back with us!
Everyone has their own objectives...
And with the gunshot cue,
Luffy and the others' plan has been put into action.
"The Mission Failed?!
The Big Mom Pirates Strike Back!"
...as the Tea Party finally starts.
To accomplish that, Luffy
allied with Capone "Gang" Bege
Don't you think so, Judge?
Eat!
Drink!
who is plotting to kill the
Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom.
I have... devoted my whole life...
And enjoy the party to your heart's content!
We'll take Sanji back!
My everything...!
Everyone has their own objectives
and the Tea Party has finally started.
Towards getting revenge on the countries
in the North Blue!
Enjoy everything...
I can't stop them!
...that'll take place here!
They'll come out of there!
To restore the Germa Empire!
Mama.
Here's Mother Carmel.
Are you okay, Luffy?
Big Mom!
Big Mom!!
Yeah.
"The Broken Couple!
Sanji and Pudding Enter!"
Say something, Big Mom!!
Yes... Our beloved...
I won't let you get away! Straw Hat!
...Mother!
Jimbei!
And then...
Whaaat?!
Go to hell!
Look at yourself!
"Returning the Sake Cup!
The Manly Jimbei Pays His Debt!"
NINTH FLOOR
A WAITING ROOM FOR THE BRIDE AND GROOM
Okay, ladies and gentlemen!
It's today's main event!
This is the Tea Party venue.
Everything just started.
Tell me...
it's not true!
The bride and groom
finished their preparations
The 35th daughter of Charlotte -
Charlotte Pudding-sama and...
It's no use. Look at her.
and they're going through the ceremony
which'll start at 12, one last time.
Everything is going well.
--Mother... Cake...
--She's confused by a series of shocking events.
...the third son of Vinsmoke -
Vinsmoke Sanji-sama's...
It's on now...
After the exchange of vows,
the groom lifts the bride's veil
...royal wedding...
It made me a little nervous when the portrait of
Mother Carmel was broken,
and kisses her.
...starts now!
Look! Over there!
ABOUT THREE AND A HALF HOURS AGO
BEGE'S BASE
The wedding kiss
will draw everyone's attention.
but the intensity of her anger pushed her
over the edge of sanity so we were okay.
Give it up!
A mirror inside the wedding cake?
Who the hell is that?
That's exactly the moment...
Yeah!
If you can put a mirror inside of it for me,
Alright! If I show this to Big Mom again,
things are gonna go as we planned, right?
Pudding-san will shoot Sanji-san!
H-He broke the... portrait of Mother Carmel!
I can jump out of the mirror
dimension like "Wham"!
That fool!
What a great actor he is!
Then it's gonna be sweet and fun!
S... traw... Ha... t...
Sanji-san?
It doesn't need to be sweet or fun!
What's the matter?
The bloody wedding now begins!
Don't make me repeat myself!
Your job is...
Oh, nothing...
I'm just getting nervous...
You can only see slightly ahead into future.
Oh, no! This is a big deal!
I know!
You want me to break the picture, right?
Me too...
"A Deadly Kiss!
The Mission to Assassinate the Emperor Kicks Off!"
But even if we can't see it,
But I wanna get out there
in a funny way when I do it!
Mama...
S-So cute!!
we all have the right...
Don't be silly!
Yes!
WHOLE CAKE CHATEAU - ROOFTOP
...to change the future!
Alright!
Are you thinking of
breaking the wedding cake?
It's broken!
You guys don't know how much
Mama is looking forward to it...
Wake up!
What the hell?!
I thought the fake Straw Hats were all animals!
Hey!
You made copies of Nami and
the others in the woods.
"Run, Sanji!
SOS! Germa 66!"
Straw Hat?
Yeah!
We're almost ready.
She can make copies of someone by reflecting
Okay.
them in a mirror and projecting
them on other animals!
Luffy!
How interesting!
Okay! Big Mom sees the broken picture!
Hey, stay in there!
The ceremony has begun! Luffy!
Now, if she just shrieks...
You can't mess around now!
Go back in!
I can eat more...
So what?!
What is he thinking?!
Wake up!
Oh, I can get out from here too!
What is he doing?
I caught them...
Turn them all into me.
Do you wanna let Sanji down?!
What?!
What's going on with your body?!
AT PRESENT - THE WEDDING PARTY VENUE
It's so cool!
Don't play with my body!
P-People are coming out of the cake!
Don't be so serious!
This deadly poison KX Launcher
is ready to fire-rero!
Hey! Is there any way to wake him up?!
He was running around the forest
right before he fell asleep so...
What are you doing?!
Get out of my way!
Maybe, I should've killed them...
Food is the only thing that'll wake him up.
Hey, do you have any meat?!
We don't have time!
What now?
--Meat?
--He's gonna have breakfast now?
Oh my...
--Hurry up!
--Okay!
Vito, what are you doing?
Oh my! I can't believe it!
Father, it's amazing!
He peeled off his face!
The president of the WEJ
and Germa's boss are talking-rero!
No! This is how I really look!
It's another flashy bit-nen...
Don't get in my way!
So disgusting!
No, that's not it, Du Feld.
This is big news!
Of course, they talk.
They both have ears and a mouth.
What... What?!
I don't want you guys to shriek!
He's a pirate from the Worst Generation!
Well but it's an extraordinary party-rero!
Straw Hat Luffy!
The eldest son and the Minister
of Candy - Perospero.
S-Soul King?!
The unimaginable is happening!
The eldest daughter and the Minister of Fruit -
Compote.
I thought that you were dead!
Why is he here?
The second son - Sweet General Katakuri.
Yeah... I died just once a long time ago.
Are they all Straw Hats?
The 14th daughter - Sweet General Smoothie.
Why are there so many of them?
Do you know...
Run! The cake is collapsing!
The third son - Daifuku
and the fourth son - Oven.
...who that is...
Countless monsters all around.
They're coming one after the other...
What are they?!
It was so encouraging to have them
on the same side,
...in the picture...?
Straw Hat Luffy?!
M-Mother...
but it freaks me out to think
that we'll make enemies of them all-rero.
Get out of my way!
Why isn't she shrieking?
That bastard!
Huh? "Enemies"?
This is your requiem!
If you have time to do that,
go check downstairs.
D-Don't tell me he came
to take back the groom!
Oh, no! It's just like the other day!
Mama's gonna go crazy!
Just listen to it with that
stupid look on your face, Sanji!
Okay, Father. Let's go, Gotti.
I heard that the wedding
cake will be very fancy.
I don't want them to see my face!
Do you have any idea who that is?
I can't wait to see Pudding-sama
in a wedding dress.
Pudding-chan, pull yourself together!
If they do, they'll kill me!
And the wedding cake!
Shut up!
It finally started...
The crucial moment is coming.
They already know it's you.
The photo frame is...
Those guys are wreaking
havoc using your ability!
Sanji-san, thank you!
There!
Oh, I know why!
Sanji-san, I'm...
Go get it, Luffy!
--Wedding cake...
--Soul King!
Okay! This mirror is the linchpin
for the allied forces to get out.
...so happy!
What's going on, Montd'Or?!
P... P-P-P-P-Pudding-chan...
Stop!
Once I fulfill this task,
I'll get my heart back.
I thought that Straw Hat Luffy and the other one
died in the Prison Library!
And when I get there,
I'll teach all of them a lesson!
Me... Me too!
Mama's not thinking straight!
She's gonna go mad!
Dammit!
Opera, that dumbass...
I knew he was lying!
Kill Straw Hat and the others before that!
No! No! Stay rational!
How dare he try to save his own skin!
Luffy!
We have to keep alive until Big Mom
goes out of her mind!
Mama.
If you don't pay attention, you...
Here's Mother Carmel.
Okay!
Straw Hat!
You... you... you'll...
How's everything going inside?
Yes... Our beloved...
You'll get killed!
I'm not hearing her shriek yet...
How's Big Mom?
My...
...Mother!
...precious...
Help!
Marriage
Oh, it's nice to see Mother
smiling brightly as always.
...cake is...
Stop it! Get off of me!
Marriage
The cake is...
Marriage!
Just as we planned...
She's like the sun.
The cake has been destroyed
and the herd of Straw Hats is going crazy...
Tough love...
Those idiots! How much more
do they wanna screw around?!
What the...?!
I've been in...
That's right.
Mother is the light of this world!
She's acting weird...
Bitter love...
The portrait of Mother Carmel
has been broken too...
Give us back our weapons!
We're gonna beat the hell out of them!
Oh... I was looking forward to it...
I've been in...
Fell in love, fell in deep, got hurt...
I don't know who she is, though...
So then, why isn't Big Mom shrieking?!
Mama, please keep your composure!
I know how you're feeling.
This is my first Tea Party
so about this lady...
And I've reached the aisle
Please relax...
How are you related to her, Big Mom?
What's going on?!
I said we'll handle it.
Even if rain falls down on me
Don't stick your nose...
Don't worry.
Even if spears rain down on me
Cake!
I, Perospero, will keep
you all firmly protected.
...into my memory!
Luffy-san, listen to me!
Don't ever let that hand go
Head chef! Please get away from here!
Big Mom's had too many shocks
in quick succession,
Mama is acting strange!
Lick!
so she doesn't know
how to focus her anger.
--Head chef!
Firmly...
Here comes the congratulatory...
Bring me a new cake...
Cheers!
Okay! I'll do it if you say so!
Solidly!
Th-That's impossible...
How's everything going down there?
Wedding cake!
The cooks finished preparing for the Tea Party
so they're enjoying a banquet.
Life...
...or...
...wedding cake?!
Leave it to me!
We blocked all passages while they're at it.
Are you okay, Pudding-chan?
Good. With those being blocked,
no one can come up for a while.
Stop Straw Hat!
Don't let him get close to Mama!
Let's go somewhere safe.
G-Guys...
Now we'll set the Horned Transponder Snails
to jam radio signals
It's the Soul Pocus!
Their lifespans will be taken!
This is quite a scoop!
and isolate the venue.
Big Mom can tap into
everyone's obsession with staying alive!
--Don't forget to set up for you-know-what too.
--Yes, sir.
Why are you getting in my way?!
If you fear death even a little bit...
Look! There it is!
Bege!
H... H-Help!
Bege, you bastard...
No!
Stop, Pudding-chan!
Shut up!
Go to hell, Katakuri!
Look! This is who I truly am!
Everyone who ruins my pleasure...
I'll take your lifespan!
You must be shocked! And disappointed!
All there is left to do is set up for it.
Bege?!
What we need is in that room.
Don't worry.
You're gonna die soon!
MIRROWORLD
Hey!
Go! Go!
What are you guys doing there?
Okay, that way!
What are you doing, Gang Bege?!
Well, we're out of booze
so we came to get some...
The voice we just heard...
I guess Big Mom is throwing a fit outside!
Oh, you guys ran dry too?!
I knew you'd betray us, Bege...
We're kind of desperate too.
It's this way.
This is how I fooled so many people!
The venue is getting messier than we thought.
Bravo!
Mama! I'm really sorry!
But you guys don't look familiar.
And yourself?!
Beautiful! Brilliant!
I don't have time to fight them all!
How gigantic! And stately!
Whoa...
You've been fooling yourself,
haven't you, Pudding-chan?
Stay at the mirror.
Looks delicious!
What's wrong-rero?
It's a magnificent wedding cake!
Oh, sirs!
Thank you for making the rounds!
I'll make you pay for this!
You did a wonderful job, Streusen!
I have to give you praise!
Is there something wrong-rero?
Have you released them all?
Well, there are two unfamiliar guys.
Maybe, they're invaders.
This Luffy is the last!
It's more than I deserve!
You're my daughter but that creeps me out...
Grow out your bangs, Pudding.
It's not working!
I can't wait to eat it!
All right! Let's go, Pedro!
Just to be safe, this needs to be taken care of,
right, Gotti?
Yeah! To back Luffy up!
She's a monster!
Yeah.
Look! She's a freak!
I won't let you do it!
We gotta go too! To back Sanji-kun up!
You were unlucky-rero.
Don't do it!
It's amazing! The sweet cake will be the altar
where we make our vows!
Are you ready?
Ouch!
Yes, I have my earplugs!
What the...?!
We'll rescue Sanji's family!
Sh... Shut up!
No, you're amazing!
We brought you a present, a combined gift for you
and your daughter-nen, Charlotte.
Okay, we'll leave the rest to you, loser.
An idiot like you can't...
Oh, stop! Come on, Sanji-san!
You can't have it!
Is he that bad?
Just drop dead already!
Oh, that's a treasure box!
I won't let you take it!
He's the worst!
Pudding-chan looks beautiful...
Feels like watching my old self.
An idiot like you can't...
My favorite!
I wonder what's in it.
How many decades ago was it-nen?
Move aside, Pudding!
Soul...
I brought you a present too, Linlin.
What?!
I guess someone wants to die.
...Solid!
Once I get my heart back,
I'll teach them a lesson...
Ouch-nen!
Take one from me too!
Mine's something rare from the south.
I got it back.
Have fun, my guests.
Uh-huh! I went to the farthest north.
Pudding-chan!
Brook!
The climax will come soon...
I'm so grateful!
For always getting so many presents like this!
Cold air...
That bastard, Straw Hat...
He can't mess with me!
Thank you!
Are you okay, Pudding-chan?
Let me handle this man, Luffy-san!
I'm so happy!
You blew it! You're useless!
Speaking of treasure box, Mamigo,
Yeah! Thank you!
You asshole!
Big Brother Daifuku!
I heard you've landed a
great undersea treasure.
CHARLOTTE DAIFUKU
THIRD SON OF CHARLOTTE (MINISTER OF BEANS)
A PUFF-PUFF FRUIT EATER AND A LAMPMAN
It'll be over before you know...
Nothing will start until you kill the groom.
Which one is the real Straw Hat?!
Oh?
You can't get away...
You have quick ears.
That's my Morgans.
Please. Enjoy the wedding
from these VIP seats.
How annoying...
And it's true.
Monkey D. Luffy...
The treasure box that'd been passed down
for generations among the undersea royalty!
It's about to start!
Let go of me!
I know your name now.
The bloodbath!
Come! To the New World!
Come and fight me!
For some reason, Neptune let go of
his hold on it and it's here now.
In a few minutes...
Go, Genie!
At the moment of the wedding kiss...
What a boring story...
I'll burn you up!
The bloody banquet will begin...
That's awful.
You haven't become...
the King of the Pirates.
Geniiie!
This is the legendary...
I'm sorry! But I need you to go away,
Vinsmokes!
But I don't have any flesh to burn!
...Tamate Box!
I'm gonna pick a fight with you again!
Along with that chattering mouth,
I'll burn you to the marrow of your bones!
What's that?!
Just because you're the Emperor,
don't be cocky!
Oh! Look how stately it is!
Sanji's lucky!
What's in it?
If I'd known she was that pretty,
I wouldn't have minded marrying her.
Brother Daifuku!
I'll win Sanji back!
You have a good sense of humor.
Have you opened it, Mamigo?!
We're the ones... who'll have the last laugh!
Wait! I promise I'll get it done!
With Big Mom's daughter? No way.
At the huge feast after Pudding's wedding,
He's a sacrifice. Don't forget.
You couldn't do it at that moment...
You got no chance now!
I'll open this along with everyone's presents,
and show it to you all!
Once you're married,
you'll be under Big Mom's control for all your life.
You're right.
That's the last thing I want.
The cake has... collapsed...
How useless...
I can't wait!
Pudding-chan!
I see... We're surrounded by
the siblings of Charlotte,
I'm thrilled to see such a precious moment!
I've been waiting for this day too!
and quite easy targets.
Brother Peros!
Genie-uine Rage Hunt!
And we're unarmed
so we're basically sitting ducks.
Shoot them up already!
Dammit...
Collier Strike!
I know.
That's how it should be...
Dammit...
Father!
Boy... The man who sees the future
wants everything fast.
Germa is an irrelevant kingdom now.
Oh, are you finished?
All the preparations are done-rero.
But...
How dare he ruin the wedding cake!
But for this occasion,
I can see the future too.
Sanji...
Okay. Good job.
Guys, go get changed.
Yes, sir.
I want you to get away.
Which one is the real Straw Hat Luffy?!
Being bound in my candy,
you guys will die with pitiful faces!
You have a plan, right?
Can I trust you?
Caesar, bring out the mirror.
You jerk! You called me that again!
Where is he?!
Luffy-kun!
That's the only future I see!
So this is the entrance to the Tea Party.
It's time.
Is she dumb?
It's just a diversion strategy.
MIRROWORLD
Enjoy it as much as you can,
losers of the world!
Show yourself! Straw Hat!
If we'd at least had the Raid Suits,
Stop!
Meat...
Does she think that he'll respond?
Don't use me anymore!
we wouldn't have let you do as you like!
Caesar Clown?
Meat...
I mean, if he responds...
You're a loser too.
Raid?
Just hide that mirror somewhere around here.
Meat!
Shut up! My heart is at stake!
What is it? Is it some kind of weapon?
Lick.
Shut up! I know!
How easy.
Luffy, the gunshot cue to start the mission
will be any minute!
When Big Mom starts shrieking,
Once the assassination of Big Mom succeeds
they'll be desperate to see me show up...
Whoa-whoa, why would you want to bring
such a thing for your son's wedding?!
bring that mirror and burst into the hall.
That's your job.
Yeah, let me finish this first!
I can't wait anymore!
I'm here!
You're a loser too.
That's our only escape route.
Whoa, hey! Not yet!
Run, Reiju!
I can picture it!
He... He responded!
Loser!
Be sure not to get any ideas.
He's the worst!
It's too late for me to betray you!
There you are, Straw Hat...
Who's a loser?!
Oh, no!
Bege and his people are up to something!
In sickness and in health,
I'll destroy you!
for richer for poorer,
It's you again!
to have and to hold,
Don't get in my way!
till death do us part...
Diable Jambe!
I pared it off.
Hurry up, guys! We don't have time!
Information leaks will
bring unexpected crisis.
Flanchet Strike!
You can't tell us that!
Sanji...
It's 30 minutes to the wedding.
What is he doing?
He's making a fuss...
Genie-uine Rage Split!
Are Straw Hat and the others ready?
I hope he's not playing around like a fool again...
Do you plight yourself to love
and to be loyal to each other?
Check for yourself!
They're in your body!
My wish is finally gonna come true!
That's the photo frame!
Sanji...
I underestimated your kindness.
My... precious...
Vito... Gotti...
Is the Launcher ready?
Hey, you fools! Why're you sleeping?!
We're good-for-nothings
but you still won't abandon us.
What's wrong, Pudding?
Why are you collapsing?!
You should be getting ready!
Gum-Gum...
Yes, we can jump out anytime,
Father.
Let them sleep.
Now you may lift her veil and kiss her.
...Jet Gatling!
I've always hated being a Vinsmoke
It seems like they haven't slept much
since they arrived.
Something wrong, brother?
and been ashamed of it.
Straw Hat... Do your best.
I'll wake them up 10 minutes before.
Fish-Man Karate!
You saw the future, Katakuri!
But...
I can't believe this.
No, let go of me!
Sharkskin Palm Thrust!
...when I saw you as a grown man...
I'll ditch them
as soon as they get in my way.
They're coming in hoards!
Run!
No problem.
Jet Stamp!
I'll lift your veil.
I'm watching out
and getting ready for them.
I felt relieved!
Come on!
Okay.
You guys are so persistent.
That must be the real Luffy.
Once Luffy breaks the picture,
we'll burst in after three seconds...
Because I noticed there was still conscience
in our family's blood...
What are you doing, Bege?!
Those idiots... How ridiculous.
Uh-huh...
Be quiet! I'm the head of security!
They'll suspect me if I do nothing!
Are you listening? Be serious!
I know!
Thank you, Sanji!
You need to go back inside.
Uh-huh...
I got the captain!
What a touching camaraderie. Lick.
I'm gonna get into the hall.
Alright! Kill him!
Zeus!
Hey, Mama!
Everyone, prepare yourselves!
Prometheus!
But it's over now.
That's not a bad idea to do it now.
Yes, Mama!
I'll beat them all at once!
Now, it's fun time!
Screw you!
Once we enter,
Listen! We're in trouble.
there's no turning back!
Alright!
Why isn't Big Mom shrieking?!
It's easy!
I hope you're ready too...
Take this!
He can do it!
I can't fight this many!
Gum-Gum...
Vinsmoke Sanji!
Jimbei!
Run!
Oven!
What?!
This is the real one!
You bastard!
Hey, Pedro!
Don't let him land any hits on you!
The other Straw Hats are...
...the animals of the island,
that were transformed by Brulee's ability.
What the?!
Don't pay them any mind!
I see! So they used Brulee's ability!
No! No!
Damn...
I remember you, Pedro!
She is very cute but don't be fooled!
What the hell is this?!
You're like a big brother to Pekoms!
My limbs are buried and I can't pull them out!
What kind of ability is this?!
I...
You came to steal Mama's Ponegliff
but you failed foolishly
Katakuri! Are you trying to help me?
You're my son - you can't do...
I wasn't planning on getting married
when I came here so...
Take a good look, Sanji...
It's really strange to me to sit side-by-side
with you like this now...
and lost an eye and years of your lifespan
miserably.
No, Mama!
At...
At my creepy...
He was going after...
...third eye!
You came back with such a short lifespan.
Which means...
I feel like I'm dreaming...
...you're prepared to die, right?
Stay cool, stay cool.
...Mother Carmel's portrait.
I'm not gonna get fooled again.
How do you know its importance to us?
Oh, no! Sanji's family is...
Good boy.
I've always been prepared!
I thought only people close to us knew.
Is it...
Stay like that...
Where's Luffy?
I'll burn you to death!
Spit it out! Who told you?
...a good dream or a bad dream?
What a beautiful eye!
Shut up!
Let go of me, you fool!
Three seconds is long past!
Damn... The mission is suspended.
Oh man, she's so cute!
What's going on?
Somebody! Just break the picture!
Of... o-o-of course, it's a good dream!
She's not shrieking at all!
Hurry up, Luffy...
Really?! That's good!
Hey, calm down!
She's just acting!
She's planning to kill me!
Luffy!
Damn.
Leave it to me, Pedro!
Brook!
Oh?
I'm okay. I'm alive.
I mean, I'm dead...
Ocean Current...
Maybe, I was really just dreaming...
...Shoulder Throw!
No, no, no! Don't get screwed!
Believe what you saw!
I didn't know you could do that!
What?
Run!
You bastard!
Sanji-san, is there something wrong?
I'm sorry! When I saw it up close,
I couldn't take my eyes off...
Pedro!
Anyway, listen to me, Luffy-san!
Don't touch it, Luffy! Go!
What? N-No, no, no, no! It's just...
Thanks!
What the hell are you doing?!
Five Thousand Brick...
What is she doing?!
How could you do this to us!
Oh, yeah!
Don't hesitate, Pudding!
...Fist!
A-About the wedding kiss... Um...
Pudding... chan?
Oh, no! Bege, get off of me!
In case you have a problem...
doing it for the first time in front of the people...
What is he saying?
You don't need to explain about me...
Damn! That isn't the way it's supposed to be!
That was close...
Appearing there is the groom Sanji and...
I-I-I don't mind kissing
you on the forehead or...
Katakuri ate a special kind of
the Paramethia-type...
Tell me this is a mistake!
Bege!
Big Mom!
...Mochi-Mochi Fruit.
...he sees your third eye for the first time!
Kiss me on the mouth.
We're gonna become husband and wife.
Go to hell, Katakuri!
Jimbei!
You can get away from it with liquid
but you better not touch it in the first place.
Lick.
The moment he sees his beautiful bride's
creepy real face,
Jimbei?
I trusted you! Even the underworld
is ruled by honor and decency!
I'm the one who told Luffy
about Mother Carmel.
Oh no, you don't!
he'll fall back a little!
Since I'm your ally,
I hear those talks.
Say something!
It's not cool to act like that now,
Father.
What was that?!
Those idiots!
How dare they interfere...
We're doomed.
Sanji-sama crashed into the ceiling?!
Screw him!
We're bound in candy.
They came this far to take back Sanji!
Mama...
How did he end up like that?
What is he thinking?!
They took all of our weapons.
We don't even have the Raid Suits.
The wedding has been ruined...
He's bleeding so much!
Since I was born, I've never been told...!
I thought that silly Straw Hat was dead...
Oh, no!
We've been totally set up.
I guess we aimed too high.
Sanji-san!
Don't worry, members of Vinsmoke.
Not a single person has ever told me
that this eye's beautiful!
What's wrong with this damn dirty water imp?!
We Charlotte will handle this...
I wanna blow him away already!
What's so funny, you fools?!
What's wrong, Pudding?!
Just shoot him!
Lick!
No one's ever...
Unfortunately, you're the one who made your sons
cold-hearted...
You...
I thought you gave up leaving my crew...
Father-sama.
But you defended the guy
who broke the cake...
You're my daughter but that creeps me out...
Grow out your bangs, Pudding.
They don't even fear their own death...
I take it as complete mutiny,
is that okay with you?
They're my young brothers,
but I can't see them as humans.
Yes... I understand, ma'am...
Jimbei?
Mama... No!
Yes, I'm absolutely okay with that.
She's a monster!
Oh, boy. I've never seen such a
pathetic assassination as this!
So creepy!
What's wrong with this kid?!
You have some nerve...
This is more like just
violence instead. Lick.
You don't look happy.
I want to leave your crew and...
Look! She's a freak!
No, I am happy...
M...
Let's have fun.
It's a big day for our dear brother and sister.
Don't do it!
Don't you think so, Judge?
Mother...
...join the Straw Hats!
Yes...
I have... devoted my whole life...
How's that, freak?!
What?!
My everything...!
Freak! Freak!
Towards getting revenge on the countries
in the North Blue!
Everything is okay, right?
This'll make a headline!
To restore the Germa Empire!
Yeah... There is nothing wrong.
M...
The former Warlord Jimbei joins
the Straw Hats!
That's good.
Today is more special than any other day.
Freak!
Big Mom!
Say something, Big Mom!!
Well, okay...
Do as you like after leaving.
Don't drop your guard. Lick.
Mother!
Go away, freak!
But I need you to pay the price
for leaving.
I know.
--You're sick! Stay away from me!
--No... I'm not...
Mama!
--Freak!
--I'm not a... freak!
You don't wanna live your life in shame,
do you?
I'm glad that you seem like you're
having a good time, Judge.
I'm not... I'm not...
Right...
Of course, I am!
This is the best day of my life!
Look at yourself!
If you promise that
you won't hurt anyone else,
I'm not... I'm not... I'm not...
What? Germa's gonna get wiped out?
I'm not... I'm not...
I'm not... I'm not!
It is for me too!
Because we're gonna become family soon!
I'm happy to give you my lifespan -
as much as you can take!
All right!
Oh! This is big news!
I'm not!!
Hey, what are you talking about, Jimbei?!
You can't join my crew if you die!
To the North Blue's... No...
I'm not!
To the soon-to-be world's strongest family...
I love to take people's lifespans!
I'm not!
He's crying!
I see...
That's how much you don't like me.
Cheers!
I'm not...
You'd rather die than
stay where you don't want to be...
Tell me... it's not true!
It's no use. Look at her.
I won't feel sorry for you!
I'm not...
--Mother... Cake...
--She's confused by a series of shocking events.
Oh... Here we go again!
The Soul Pocus!
It made me a little nervous when the portrait of
Mother Carmel was broken,
All right! You got yourself a deal...
but the intensity of her anger pushed her
over the edge of sanity so we were okay.
I'm not gonna shut up as you make fun of me!
You fool...
You stupid sons of bitches...
Stay...
Bang.
I'll wipe you all out!
I truly understand your passionate ambition,
Judge...
Run!
Yes?
It's almost time.
Please proceed to the venue.
Lick.
...or...
But do you listen to what a cow has to say
when you're about to eat it?
...life?
Sanji-san, are you ready?
Yeah.
Life!
Pudding-chan...
Shall we?
Mama...
Die and become our flesh and blood,
Germa 66!
It... can't be stopped now...
Screw you...
The time has finally come...
Is Jimbei gonna die here...?
I'm nervous but excited too!
Me too.
Screw you!
Go to hell...
Sanji's family...
I'm gonna kill you!
I'm really...
Luffy-san, listen to me!
...really excited.
I'm an ugly freak!
Big Mom's had too many shocks
in quick succession,
so she doesn't know
how to focus her anger.
Hey, did you forget the plan, Pudding?!
It's twelve o'clock! It's twelve o'clock!
Let's show her the broken portrait again!
Pudding-chan, are you okay?
Okay! I'll do it if you say so!
You do it! Priest!
Stay or...
Hey, isn't it too late...?
...life!
That's no use! He'll dodge!
What's wrong?
H-His soul isn't coming out of his body!
The guy from earlier is coming!
This can't be true...
He's not even a bit afraid of Mama!
Katakuri!
Alright! Carry on! That plan will work!
Of course not...
Okay, ladies and gentlemen!
It's today's main event!
I'm a man who wants to be
part of the future Pirate King's crew...
Katakuri is looking pale!
He dodged!
That means he saw the future
where the things get messy.
The 35th daughter of Charlotte -
Charlotte Pudding-sama and...
Straw Hat! Go now!
I can't be intimidated by
a mere Emperor of the Sea!
Now, take care of the rest by yourselves.
Go, Straw Hat!
That's the gunshot, Luffy!
...the third son of Vinsmoke -
Vinsmoke Sanji-sama's...
Okay!
Well, I guess they can't hear me.
Great! I can make it!
Jimbei! Pedro!
...royal wedding...
We gotta back Straw Hat up with all we've got!
Follow me!
What was that gunshot?!
...starts now!
The priest fired!
No, he got shot!
Why?!
Mama... can't take his lifespan?
What's going on?!
Is this--?!
Marriage!
--Marriage!
The people of the allied forces!
What the hell is going on?!
Katakuri, what happened to Pudding?!
Marriage!
All of you,
get your Invisible Symphonia ready!
We have a bigger problem!
It's an unanticipated situation, Mama!
--Invi...
--Oh!
If you won't take my lifespan...
The earplugs!
Not even I can do anything!
Bege?
What did he yell out all of a sudden?!
What should we do?!
Sanji hasn't been shot!
I'm returning the sake cup.
Is the plan still on?
--Marriage!
Mama got injured?!
Can you make it?!
Let's go!
You know that's the only option we got
to blow up everyone with their guns, right?!
How awesome!
I'm sorry, Mama!
I had no choice but to do what they told me to!
She's become weak!
Without further ado,
here are the bride and groom!
We'll take Sanji back!
Now, I'm leaving the Big Mom Pirates!
Bege!
Hey! Somebody, stop Bege and the others!
Shoot Straw Hat to death now!
Thank you for all your troubles!
What the--?!
Wow!
I can't stop them!
I refuse.
Bege!
They'll come out of there!
How dare you betray us!
What?!
Goodbye, Big Mom!
I can't believe he's doing it now...
The Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom Pirates!
How cool... Jimbei...
And the evil army - Germa 66!
Alright! If I show this to Big Mom again,
things are gonna go as we planned, right?
Yay!
The young couple will connect
their notorious families' paths to their dreams!
Mother...
Please... listen to me, Mother...
Mariage de Raison!
Flambage Shot!
With the two tying the knot, another flower
of evil will bloom out madly in this world!
No one...
Congratulations, Jimbei...
...listens to what I say.
Give it up for them!
That means you're my enemy now, right?
Big Mom!!
Hey, Mother...
Look at that!
You can only see slightly ahead into future.
For this extremely beautiful day!
Jimbei!
Where did you go?
Go to hell!
But even if we can't see it,
Give it up!
we all have the right...
...to change the future!
That fool!
What a great actor he is!
S... traw... Ha... t...
Why did you disappear all of a sudden?
Whaaat?!
The bloody wedding now begins!
The secret of the Emperor
of the Sea, Big Mom's birth
In order to make Mama shriek,
Luffy clashes with Katakuri!
The hellish Tea Party is in chaos!
At an altar on a stately wedding cake,
a vow of love has been made!
The portrait of Mother Carmel has been broken!
But after the moment of joy,
The dutiful boss "First Son of the
Sea" Jimbei finally takes action!
and the fateful encounter with
her only weakness, Mother Carmel.
Meanwhile, when Reiju prepares to die
with the rest of the doomed Vinsmokes,
the Big Mom Pirates' supernatural powers are
brought down on Luffy and the others
Puddingfs heart wavers and
tears fall down her cheek!
To fulfill his duty, he brings out a sake cup
Taking place on the legendary
island of the Giants,
which represents the bond
between mother and son!
and when a fierce battle breaks out,
an unexpected crisis falls on Sanji and Judge!
When their romantic wedding kiss triggers
all the plots to be carried out,
the kindhearted Sanji, letting go of his past grudge
and bad family relationship,
In order to join Luffy's crew,
the world's strongest girl Charlotte
Linlin's sweet and grim,
he engages in a fierce clash
against the Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom!
old and secret story is revealed!
Luffy finally makes an appearance
at the stormy Tea Party!
unleashes his full-power kick!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Mission Failed?! The Big Mom Pirates Strike Back!"
"Run, Sanji! SOS! Germa 66!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Mom's Secret! The Giant's Island
Elbaph and a Little Monster!"
"Returning the Sake Cup! The
Manly Jimbei Pays His Debt!"
"A Deadly Kiss!
The Mission to Assassinate the Emperor Kicks Off!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!