My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Close your eyes and listen carefully
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
Sanji and Pudding's bloodbath wedding
finally began.
With the gunshot cue, Luffy and the others
went into action to break the portrait.
Now, I'm leaving the Big Mom Pirates!
That means you're my enemy now, right?
Jimbei!
Go to hell!
"The Mission Failed?!
The Big Mom Pirates Strike Back!"
Are you okay, Luffy?
Yeah.
I won't let you get away! Straw Hat!
Jimbei!
Go to hell!
Look! Over there!
Who the hell is that?
H-He broke the... portrait of Mother Carmel!
Oh, no! This is a big deal!
Mama...
Yes!
Alright!
It's broken!
What the hell?!
I thought the fake Straw Hats were all animals!
Okay! Big Mom sees the broken picture!
Now, if she just shrieks...
What is he doing?
This deadly poison KX Launcher
is ready to fire-rero!
He peeled off his face!
No! This is how I really look!
So disgusting!
What... What?!
I don't want you guys to shriek!
S-Soul King?!
I thought that you were dead!
Yeah... I died just once a long time ago.
Do you know...
...who that is...
...in the picture...?
M-Mother...
Why isn't she shrieking?
Oh, no! It's just like the other day!
Mama's gonna go crazy!
Do you have any idea who that is?
And the wedding cake!
Oh, I know why!
--Wedding cake...
--Soul King!
Stop!
Mama's not thinking straight!
She's gonna go mad!
Kill Straw Hat and the others before that!
Luffy!
We have to keep alive until Big Mom
goes out of her mind!
Okay!
Straw Hat!
Help!
Stop it! Get off of me!
Those idiots! How much more
do they wanna screw around?!
Give us back our weapons!
We're gonna beat the hell out of them!
Please relax...
I said we'll handle it.
Don't worry.
I, Perospero, will keep
you all firmly protected.
Lick!
Firmly...
Solidly!
Are you okay, Pudding-chan?
Let's go somewhere safe.
Stop, Pudding-chan!
Shut up!
Look! This is who I truly am!
You must be shocked! And disappointed!
Don't worry.
You're gonna die soon!
This is how I fooled so many people!
And yourself?!
You've been fooling yourself,
haven't you, Pudding-chan?
You're my daughter but that creeps me out...
Grow out your bangs, Pudding.
She's a monster!
Look! She's a freak!
Don't do it!
Sh... Shut up!
An idiot like you can't...
Move aside, Pudding!
Pudding-chan!
Are you okay, Pudding-chan?
You blew it! You're useless!
Big Brother Daifuku!
CHARLOTTE DAIFUKU
THIRD SON OF CHARLOTTE (MINISTER OF BEANS)
A PUFF-PUFF FRUIT EATER AND A LAMPMAN
Nothing will start until you kill the groom.
Let go of me!
Go, Genie!
Geniiie!
What's that?!
Brother Daifuku!
Wait! I promise I'll get it done!
You couldn't do it at that moment...
You got no chance now!
Pudding-chan!
Genie-uine Rage Hunt!
Collier Strike!
MIRROWORLD
Stop!
Don't use me anymore!
Shut up! My heart is at stake!
Once the assassination of Big Mom succeeds
they'll be desperate to see me show up...
You're a loser too.
I can picture it!
Loser!
He's the worst!
Who's a loser?!
Diable Jambe!
Flanchet Strike!
Genie-uine Rage Split!
My... precious...
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
Fish-Man Karate!
Sharkskin Palm Thrust!
Jet Stamp!
You guys are so persistent.
What are you doing, Bege?!
Be quiet! I'm the head of security!
They'll suspect me if I do nothing!
I got the captain!
Alright! Kill him!
That's not a bad idea to do it now.
Screw you!
Listen! We're in trouble.
Why isn't Big Mom shrieking?!
I can't fight this many!
Jimbei!
Oven!
You bastard!
Hey, Pedro!
Don't let him land any hits on you!
What the?!
I remember you, Pedro!
You're like a big brother to Pekoms!
You came to steal Mama's Ponegliff
but you failed foolishly
and lost an eye and years of your lifespan
miserably.
You came back with such a short lifespan.
Which means...
...you're prepared to die, right?
I've always been prepared!
I'll burn you to death!
Three seconds is long past!
What's going on?
She's not shrieking at all!
Brook!
I'm okay. I'm alive.
I mean, I'm dead...
I didn't know you could do that!
Anyway, listen to me, Luffy-san!
What the hell are you doing?!
How could you do this to us!
Oh, no! Bege, get off of me!
Damn! That isn't the way it's supposed to be!
Tell me this is a mistake!
Big Mom!
Lick.
I trusted you! Even the underworld
is ruled by honor and decency!
Say something!
It's not cool to act like that now,
Father.
We're doomed.
We're bound in candy.
They took all of our weapons.
We don't even have the Raid Suits.
We've been totally set up.
I guess we aimed too high.
What's so funny, you fools?!
Unfortunately, you're the one who made your sons
cold-hearted...
Father-sama.
They don't even fear their own death...
They're my young brothers,
but I can't see them as humans.
Oh, boy. I've never seen such a
pathetic assassination as this!
This is more like just
violence instead. Lick.
Don't you think so, Judge?
I have... devoted my whole life...
My everything...!
Towards getting revenge on the countries
in the North Blue!
To restore the Germa Empire!
Big Mom!
Say something, Big Mom!!
Look at yourself!
What? Germa's gonna get wiped out?
Oh! This is big news!
He's crying!
Tell me... it's not true!
It's no use. Look at her.
--Mother... Cake...
--She's confused by a series of shocking events.
It made me a little nervous when the portrait of
Mother Carmel was broken,
but the intensity of her anger pushed her
over the edge of sanity so we were okay.
I truly understand your passionate ambition,
Judge...
Lick.
But do you listen to what a cow has to say
when you're about to eat it?
Die and become our flesh and blood,
Germa 66!
Sanji's family...
Luffy-san, listen to me!
Big Mom's had too many shocks
in quick succession,
so she doesn't know
how to focus her anger.
Let's show her the broken portrait again!
Okay! I'll do it if you say so!
Hey, isn't it too late...?
What's wrong?
The guy from earlier is coming!
Katakuri!
Alright! Carry on! That plan will work!
Katakuri is looking pale!
That means he saw the future
where the things get messy.
Go, Straw Hat!
Okay!
Jimbei! Pedro!
We gotta back Straw Hat up with all we've got!
Follow me!
The people of the allied forces!
All of you,
get your Invisible Symphonia ready!
--Invi...
--Oh!
The earplugs!
Bege?
What did he yell out all of a sudden?!
Can you make it?!
You know that's the only option we got
to blow up everyone with their guns, right?!
Bege!
Shoot Straw Hat to death now!
I refuse.
Alright! If I show this to Big Mom again,
things are gonna go as we planned, right?
Flambage Shot!
You can only see slightly ahead into future.
But even if we can't see it,
we all have the right...
...to change the future!
S... traw... Ha... t...
In order to make Mama shriek,
Luffy clashes with Katakuri!
Meanwhile, when Reiju prepares to die
with the rest of the doomed Vinsmokes,
the kindhearted Sanji, letting go of his past grudge
and bad family relationship,
unleashes his full-power kick!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Run, Sanji! SOS! Germa 66!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!